<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@noahzgordon I’m hoping we nominate a member who unified, not win via a narrow, confrontational coalition (as Trump… https://t.co/aLdNZiv9Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @MLPast1620 @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends To be fair, FoxNews is state media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Christ flowing through us  Christ, his #love, his #mercy, his love Christ flowing through us living #water poured… https://t.co/3QAzLOYZxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AugieNash It's fine. I've got a lot better things to do with my money than invest in their real estate projects. #stlcards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn my coach sat me down and gave me a talk because i missed the game and practice this weekend without letting him know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando sales x un fernet y birras tranqui y terminas cargándola @TheGingerMamba 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBelieveInART Soooo good ! “It’s all in the crust” Lol you’ll see what I mean. Crazzzyyyy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingSimmonsPC These are the types of issues we think are important in Nevada. Carry on in Alabama.😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelTaxi the second I saw this I thought of you 😁👌 https://t.co/6XyS7bBJiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC The Superintendent is right on the Mark with everything he said. The media blew this out of proportion because… https://t.co/E9YEmRCqEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[De donde sacan esta mamada? Nunca he visto a alguien aquí que diga que no vale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost KILL YOUR NEWBORN BABY! (Vote Democrat in 2020!) https://t.co/BLfU4kWyHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I woke up at 4am and havent been to sleep since...I'm going finish this paperwork up and get in this bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamshametral @BillyCorben @roywoodjr @MatthewACherry No one said hardscrabble. Why has no one said that yet? Raggedy, sure, but damn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_Danner @Beer_Notes @Zimmerino @goodbeerhunting @OlympicTavern @austinlouisray @vpellegri20 You had to go an… https://t.co/GixP2ZPOu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Barrel Runner by @foundersbrewing @ 55 Temple of Awesomeness — https://t.co/YzPMxVc6sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blowout Pricing $4.95 #craftbeer #beer #ipa #dipa #beer #draftbeer #growlerfill #beerlover #newenglandipa #hazyipa… https://t.co/36WQ1yheIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bit odd, but still tasty - Drinking a Strawberry Frosted Pastry by @DecadentAles @ Fairlington Villages  — https://t.co/UWBxjJnuQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever #republican convinced #liberal #dumbasses to not have kids because of #climatechange should be elected President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone remember back in 2000 when an image of the Virgin Mary supposedly appeared on someone's window in Perth Amboy? 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_Vaezi خودتون از همه بهتر میدونید که آخر خط هستید.بازگشت دروغگوی بزرگ @JZarif را جشن بگیریدولی جشن اصلی را ما بز… https://t.co/YJnI9LE7BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[📽️Time for a candle lit spooky👻 movie &amp; popcorn.🍿 #StayingInTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbelPrieto11 El 24 de Febrero de lo que se trata es de cómo los cubanos concebimos debe ser NUESTRA patria. Es es… https://t.co/ho1XFzCvQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If reports are true and in the end Rosen is there for a 3rd rounder I think it’s a no brainer to make that trade an… https://t.co/67puHu2nzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OccupyWisdom @TFMetals @michaellebowitz And never negative before?   You’re the one manipulating data. I cen reed jus fyne thenk yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deputy Coxen hanging out with her students at Middleburg High last week as they had an exciting pep rally. To say t… https://t.co/JqQkKTrqvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian Some people are intimidated by great looking photos, don’t allow the naysayers to deter you!!  You l… https://t.co/CyLOmrq6Ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might kill the man that made my momma cry and happily serve the sentence. You don’t talk to my mom like that. You picked the wrong one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdfsoccer This is a monster #VISL #Div2 game...... hope everybody is fully staffed !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PorschaColeman .@PorschaColeman you look fabulous! CHEERS #ONELOVE #JAZZ https://t.co/AHFloIzxxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE Spring Training coverage from Tampa coming up in minutes on #FiOS1News https://t.co/8f3IzDIjax]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart couldn’t take getting @Bharper3407 and @iAM_JoshJacobs within a few months of each other. #flyeaglesfly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjzero @ericstephen @bruce_arthur Championships flying right past @TheGoonsFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregnikolay @Shapalicious I know it's a joke. But man, I'd love a 4-story design with a proper design.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonp_eggert @NeilLesinski @mcooke49 @estl189 @gr8mathteacher @Donn_Mendoza @hubbardbradford @mikelubelfeld… https://t.co/bqyG7Mxacl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like answering along to some of @TylerIAm's trivia questions and winning but never calling in in case I dont']]></document><document><![CDATA[@Izokamen @GloriaMonteneg @alvarosarco @KikeBravoPrado @ppmarino @MarthaChavezC Nada bueno Te pierdes de la nariz de Hechizada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed my executive coaching session with Steve Lassiter, Assistant Superintendent, Pitt County Schools… https://t.co/t1S1i94Knj]]></document><document><![CDATA[First you tell them humans are like a cancer on the planet's surface. From there it proceeds naturally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's coming the strong survive and the weak parish that is natural! We are coming for you walls won't help you 911 won't help you!! COWARDS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samdaman32215 Michael Jordan played against defenses made up of Kindegarten teachers, USPS drivers, Welders, and J… https://t.co/LekKaraaw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marujatarre sera que mando al copiloto a sentarse junto con su esposa, no veo otra manera]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, guys, I’m starting to wonder if this Patriots team is corrupt. It’s a wild idea, but I’m starting to have doubts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roboheartbeat I am so bad with the aiming :( But it’s fun...just wish they counted Downs in Stats and gave you XP… https://t.co/5hpj0ePy6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3Lfwqsfzcq  TALK BLACK TO ME!!!! THAT'S ALL I WANNA COMPREHEND!!  Powernomics Rules Of Politics 1-7!… https://t.co/rqYviOvQXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure you are proud big Karl @karlosrossi1   Tell her stay hungry!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give It Receive It ✔️ @ Pembroke Pines, Florida https://t.co/W4gkTUZnmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This VCU game looks like the dead under I thought it was, no clue to the playground bs in the first half that made me take VCU 2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTT2020 If Attorney General BARR don't Arrest Andrew McCabe Hillary Peter Comey and the rest of the Crooks FBI… https://t.co/s7AMkIQOjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanRomberger @AOC Did I say big corporations? No! The top 1% of individual incomes in this country pay approximat… https://t.co/h3AvVG1nJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como olvidar aquel encuentro con este toro de Lidia, sufrí pero salimos con rabo y cola. Los envidiosos dirán que n… https://t.co/3G6XeL1OOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinCarinci Honestly, I don’t think I’ve seen site plans yet...I’m not sure...I’d have to look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really impressed with @amyklobuchar and she might just end up winning my vote. Very well spoken and insightful and… https://t.co/p152tvR80N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riding to the Golf Show in style.  Watch out Novi! @ Northville, Michigan https://t.co/UeeX0S7Yas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuffyOnWCMF Why not mix it up after only scoring five goals in the last three games?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackpot 2019 Runner Full SWAT Gear Big Congrats. 100Miles.  #runninglove #runningaddict #runningday #runningbuddies… https://t.co/jh4oVlnVyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[No wonder the US is called the land of the brave. You have to be to live beyond the crime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Giants don’t believe in using #nfldraft 1st round picks on these 3 positions. I went bank to 1980. https://t.co/HrRRU5NRpz #nygiants #nyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chemo day... mama taking a quick nap 💤 during the treatment ❤️🙏🏾 @ Cancer Care Centers of South Texas https://t.co/yHwVJxWUCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is brutal. If you sit beyond row 20 on an MD or 737.  Guess what? No carry on for you, unless you’re a priority member.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man am I one lucky dude! 😍 Love this gal so much @jinedlamata @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/uqp21kI3Ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be sharing God's word in four services today at @CVCTweets. Grateful for @Chad_D_Allen and team- and thi… https://t.co/qLcvIChV4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clay_risner @HarpethNDNeers @BaylorBoBantus That’d probably be our best bet. That way we could reliably install it… https://t.co/yxgraU0fsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godson1800 Hi, We can definitely help you in design and development of your website at an affordable price.  See o… https://t.co/ZQr5heFo0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly2277 @Twitter Where is anyone. Read my Instagram. I am going down rapidly Kelly... buried with zero acknowleg… https://t.co/ihYFOIIaYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrisResists Hmm, so the price for Pence’s Soul is 4 years as The Vice President and standing in for our #ConMan In… https://t.co/SUvH65Vudf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it won’t have any impact on gun violence cause criminals don’t obey the law DUH. It’s just an excuse to dis… https://t.co/DMJWjAOQ1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllWaltrip @KyleBusch Sad they ceated the Kyle rule to limit his wins, Jacked the history books really by limiting his races.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @DonaldJTrumpJr you can't be that ignorant, you do realize she won the popular vote; like @POTUS LO… https://t.co/XqiYvx0zeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll dryvit in the fucking wall,,,,and hope for hell after the fact https://t.co/8A4nzaqToD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great #saturday folks #southerncalifornia #pasadena en Amara Chocolate &amp; Coffee https://t.co/ZmO89hsLX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncannygirl @illtanteish @BenjiSamit And we are thrilled and honored to have had the chance to work on the same pr… https://t.co/kKc6mDLR83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_kevstaaa Endgame, I think it's way, WAY WORSE.  Especially if Natasha finds him after he's cleaning that blade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@EconAllianceSC held another terrific advocacy day in Olympia. Great conversations with legislators about regional… https://t.co/7c9bskVfsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played a great game!!!  Congrats @ChrisvVogt!!!  Get another W 2morrow!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Nevada desert, 20-minute drive from my house. Snowed like the Dickens today. Doesn't happen too often, but a sure… https://t.co/a7e2mPQiPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Apeiron Dry-Hopped W/ Citra by @infinitealework at @infinitealework — https://t.co/UyzuKVGjWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurlKevlar @figurativelol Dude that shit was the worst cause bacon was like 2 bucks or some shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Russian collusion is still very alive, that was much of the intelligence committee meeting wit… https://t.co/vESSjtTvb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting list of innovative tech changing the world we live in.  @angela_smith77 See #5 for data science applica… https://t.co/xY8xB0GNnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjamingilpin A5: We do on the on the spot positive officer referrals. Students have to take them home to be sign… https://t.co/zB6GJ99zY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @kimfreethinker All I noticed was her difficulties in bending forward.   Obviously has more than one m… https://t.co/aBZmn871wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samzhang428 @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You didn’t finish that statement...OUT OF THE OVAL OFFICE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a side note, getting the band back together from thousands of miles alway is tedious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come people are scared to confront @IvankaTrump she is a criminal https://t.co/z0Syh2lNKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @BetoWisconsin - looking forward to helping turn WI blue again in 2020! #Beto2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear if I could I would blow all my money on vintage games and computer parts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millermusing Hmmm, I draw the line at doing snow angels. https://t.co/EWE8DUGwhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is State using that emoji to represent Elon as a reference to Elon Musk? If so, points for creativity.   https://t.co/o5B72pW77N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyDeathDay2U is great!!! if you love the first one you will like this one!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@sixers please go to the nba finals so I can drop my whole bank account on tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrellwhitelaw I don’t know what you are talking about https://t.co/qHx1Y59pkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indians have any extra @MrLapara  bobbleheads for the fans here? Who couldn't make it to Arizona?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real friends share tweets / posts on the daily. If y’all aren’t doing that you’re not really that close 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deaconpunnett Arlington, Virginia, Trinity Episcopal Church. Was a Vestry member back 1998-2007 at Saint James' in… https://t.co/68idi1LLo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afflictions are sweet preservatives to keep to saints from sin, which is a greater evil than hell itself.  - Thomas… https://t.co/FbAWtAeVbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to cold-cock the asshole running the @peta account talking shit about Steve Irwin. Idc if it’s the stupid fo… https://t.co/3z0dYcvhmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtonpittman and also, that $173 came with a social wage Americans couldn’t dream. It’s totally dishonest to do t… https://t.co/99Pnqp2dc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018 Ford Escape. So glad the climate controls are finally entirely decoupled from the touch screen. Adaptive cruis… https://t.co/RFMjCQRsGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar I did have a bacon peanut butter nd chocolate doughnut and it was amazing though]]></document></documents></author>