<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Luimelia  #AmarEsParaSiempre  #luimeliaEH @PaulaUsero #CarolRovira https://t.co/RaYfGCtfks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ro773_ @ZachLaVine @NotARoleModeI @DejounteMurray @Double0AG @this_vid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alexa_rubes I took mine out after a year and a half it sucked so mf badly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RozayRoyce Drums over flats and French toast over everything else but that’s all that makes sense here 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjolmstead I’m with you, Sarah. I so appreciate #TheLaunch mentors take the time to explain and “break things down.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanalda love your pod!!! So cool that you’re using Calm. If you ever want to talk about teaching kids to communic… https://t.co/Dzj8OKctS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babies!!! ⛷🏂 @moparedes @ozsanchez12 #masonjames #milavictoria #losamo ❤️ @ Dover, New Hampshire https://t.co/XAnKJH0oe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you've used the snapkit autolayout framework for so long that you've forgotten the following is needed for aut… https://t.co/pQyEs4Jin4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to playing in Palm Desert. #bluesforbandit #akikohamiltondechter #organjazz #hammondb3… https://t.co/VrPw8QAwtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonChampionTV One of the saddest, strangest stories I’ve covered in some time. Those poor babies :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who I talk to is nobody’s business, done telling everybody my stuff because for some reason it affects them too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey strangegirljenn and scattermatterstudio  #BabyBesties are looking for some new friends to come and play with th… https://t.co/PajuTUmyIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Republican Party is now comprised of two types of people: the religiously insane and grifters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes Mother Nature can be a real flake. Sending Toronto another 15-20cm of snow??!! Have we not suffered enoug… https://t.co/bXBK2BDhYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it feels like every day can be a challenge for its own reasons. Some days are harder and some days you fe… https://t.co/mbYT8mVoCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soulhorsetx Just seeing this now.  Have you raised enough $$ to save that pregnant mare?  Twitter might be lagging… https://t.co/ezDj41Ju8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachmanANjax Odds are these skills will take a person farther than the ability to hit a ball.  Few make it the pro… https://t.co/TgawSEZ15g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toxicity up his? You should cancel the GoFundMe from people who were betrayed from your Wholesomeness. #Hollywood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @hadip @codeorg Help us fund public education in Texas so we can develop and promote more programs like these!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilTNangel @iamchriztopher @Todd7M @RealOCEmily @DrJamesMercer @KathyLovetro @Loubiegal @afinekimmie… https://t.co/04qyVQMZ9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m really really really pretty and funny how do i sign up to marry myself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekjohnston Will Ostiguy started Boston’s Sober High Schools.  God love you both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Great Camps For Kids!  Almost March Break For Your Little Ones And Here Are A Few Fabulous Camps. Great For Ag… https://t.co/GXbbwYFUKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Wednesday morning Twitter and HHD!! Have an awesome day ❤️😍💙 https://t.co/AsCgB52oaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @SimySemsem @consuiglesias @carolina_smal @TereOrt51687394 @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce… https://t.co/CBFilZV7up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legend of the Guardians: The Owls of Ga'Hoole (2010) Dir: @ZackSnyder Animation: @animallogic  I sat in the theater… https://t.co/GljjmId0Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNiebuhr15 @isrealiniv @JenniferAnWorld @gothgymnast Says the guy with a bunion tattoo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagina a vida do cara q 5 anos dps da gnt já ter acabado a família ainda fica falando p gnt voltar kkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love elephants? Sign this petition telling @PizzaHut and @KFC to end deforestation in their supply chains https://t.co/orXbsQEM2Z @YumBrands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbiethetexan @TexansTORO1 @MadingES @HISDSupe @HoustonISD @HISD_ACC @HISDFACE @A180_HISD The whole presentation was outstanding!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im about to taste the rainbow! I’m in heaven!   https://t.co/CtyySdR3ar  Revolutionize Your Mind  TAF💪🏽… https://t.co/p0loHpl2Wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yannick_bisson I loved it—-great seadon finale. A slicer of a peek into Murdoch’s history. ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StandUpAmerica How is he not credible? So anyone who identifies potential corruption and or questionable tactics w… https://t.co/Shbdb8Ypwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Gacek37 Remember when you sold dubra out of plastic water bottles for $10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@870South @williamlegate BUSTING OUT HYSTERICALLY LAUGHING‼️🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 I needed a good laugh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your boyfriend says “i don’t care, I’m not moving, you can stand behind us, or you can leave” please inform me of w… https://t.co/g5mQyCNW15]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello can y’all drop their performance on YouTube now so I can watch that a thousand more times. THEIR CHEMISTRY WOW 😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[She thought she was broken...til she found that one little piece. But making it fit back in again was a whole different story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami Good morning Sami and have a great weekend 😘❤️💋😘❤️💋 https://t.co/5BBMHBAUQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay2019  opportunity to thank my great educator of social awareness, justice, womens rights, im… https://t.co/u2wx85tTvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileyMariee_ @norvina1 i just cant get myself to stop tweeting her norvina im so sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braeden asked me what I wanted him to bring me back from Vegas and I said White Castle. He laughed but I’m low key not kidding]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, after taking a long, hot shower:  u know what i could really use right now? a long, hot shower]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spudfunkel @RollingStone Ang Lee won for Brokeback Mountain as well in 2005.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Francin_P @WBrettWilson @jjhorgan Yup. Science, it’s pretty cool. Data doesn’t need our approval. https://t.co/ZyFaNam9P4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome to work together with our Hi Tide family and the district to be graduation ready! #proudprincipal @MBSHPTSA… https://t.co/XKPLCrhVkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello I am watching Alice in Wonderland for the first time in my life !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetingclip I forgot how fun these games are and this is really crowded!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_connection @SeekingReality7 Nothing says comedy like making flippant, bad jokes about a rapidly escalating wa… https://t.co/iaGFzv9Ixa]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are best! Thank you! I’ll say it again...Maryland’s #1 porn star! Adore u]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can have everything in the world... but without someone who truly understands you, you have nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traitor #NYvsSeattle @ Upper West Side Manhattan https://t.co/asfXGrnLUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending Breakfast to end #endviolenceagainstwomen2019 @ Casablanca Winery Inn https://t.co/VAhRgI6wMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad place right out my back door for the next day and a half. #serenity #sogreen #labrynth @ Alton L. Collins… https://t.co/4hePxDaVnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carper_tj Omg I’m so sorry idk how I missed this 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️.Lol oh god I’ve to ans this ?That place is stunni… https://t.co/e2wN8slk6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the worst feeling is when you wake up and you’re not ready to get out of bed but your bladder disagrees with you 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Jesus is the obedient one. The center of his life is this obedient relationship with the Father. This may be hard… https://t.co/uoRsmlyPgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgomaster @Ryland_Adams @shanedawson @Garrett_Watts @_morganadams_ That’s beautiful.  Great work Morgan!  ✌🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miles saying hello to Lady Liberty @ Lower East Side https://t.co/wNvByRy1wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Destinyyyyyy85 @bmthofficial @olobersyko My friend won KROQ tickets and it was super last minute. SO WORTH IT THOUGH 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marxistfilm OMG I love watching him scramble. I love my QB!!!!!! @CameronNewton]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MingGao26 @01pod @Mytweetydogs @Bookorama If that whole shitshow could be blown open soon: From the people who sta… https://t.co/KtSlmbqjIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_artiga @Vovchick22 @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton @AOC @IvankaTrump when do they bring it up,  at 3 AM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I’ve improvised everyday items for eating tools. And if I had someone willing to clean it for me, I would a… https://t.co/khW6Dh96KG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Just Entered @BiGGsGolfTalk #March #Giveaway to WIN a @ShotScope V2 #Golf #Watch. ENTER TO WIN! @wcuebas  https://t.co/7GtR0N6qy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigSky3450 @davenpbc @krassenstein Naive fools and willful ignorance for the win. Damn fucking morons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are top 10 #SpringCleaning Ideas from Professional #Organizers! #Donate your unwanted items to help those in o… https://t.co/FjLhFdvR8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManiaFanatic_ @MarkTepperSWP @BernieSanders Yeah when have you heard the term “safety net” recently? a person lose… https://t.co/G23s9EsEa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronSmarter It’s probably easier to communicate visually + orally than through words; easier to speak what’s on y… https://t.co/yRqXQQTYfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FitOver40  Happy Friday! @ LA Fitness Jacksonville-Old St. Augustine https://t.co/qtne1beswJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[O problema é que mulher nunca pode dizer que tá enjoada sem vir um idiota dizer iiiiiiih tá grávida]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just thinking this. If @MTV’s smart, now’s the time to dust off those reruns...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddmrosenthal @KatieHeigl @cheddarbob85 Suits is so good now that you are on it and it’s ending they should have… https://t.co/4TJwPa41ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thank you to @HTHTscience for teaching our students some new and fun experiments today!! 🧪🧠🔬 https://t.co/uoFSBvkgF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it acceptable for me to eat two krispy kreme donuts rn? cause i’m about to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penblogger @LeonWhi63670221 @akuscg @TT197 @Louis2M2 @FoundOne14 @abytw @johnhpetroff @Shaun_Girk @imvala… https://t.co/3TTSbzWKwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s Rosie? Gracias Chef Nelson Umaña for allowing our production to record a segment for @tophermorrison you ar… https://t.co/fCsjPhCJgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kc_boilermaker well I mean it’s not a huge sample but I had 903 margaritas in Cancun and didn’t have one I didn’t like.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this absurd horror-comedy (don’t watch if ur afraid of heights djdjkd) https://t.co/ygHxtg0zpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Price to Pay 4 Poor Decisions! #Manafort #ThrowAwayTheKey CNN: Toobin: 'Enormous' physical toll taken on Manafort.… https://t.co/So4ZTUkock]]></document><document><![CDATA[How exciting to host a national championship at @WestVirginiaU! https://t.co/isDyTrfoqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kohls I feel most rewarded when I'm at my best with my kids #LoveKohls @gofooji #gofooji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my miles in on skis this weekend. Fresh snow, sunshine, lake views, and little crowds! #skitahoe… https://t.co/sRQDOYftTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @GayleKing for continuing to be a role model in so many ways. Your grace, poise, integrity, and objectivi… https://t.co/nh3t1ksMpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t think I was going to be able to make it but... May 24th. Nashville. The Funeral. It’s happening. 🖤 @PalayeRoyale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_troyjohnson @SanDiegoMag I would argue that a healthy balance is ideal. I like to try new restaurants while also… https://t.co/gYm2Zf28Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get that he wants to stick to his values, but since he and all his cohorts were unable to fix this mess before Tr… https://t.co/8qQ0EKGC7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harpywoman honestly would say the exact same thing abt Pisces moon but only felt entirely comfortable (and accurate) dragging myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald, you are the disgrace. A humiliation to America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few pics of our current Bengal Laci Scheefer and our future Bengals! Five girls from @RMS_DentonISD winning their… https://t.co/McIKJTtQyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/zu9QbxyBrm.  Hope enough pressure is out on the president so he will release every name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the girl who i once claimed as a best friend, fucked my ex of 3 years but tweets about loyalty— weird flex but OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigiAdams @JakeMillerTech @ericcurts @jmattmiller @alicekeeler I agree!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOMORROW on Spotify 🦋 #SugarHigh #NewMusicFriday https://t.co/FnyE1KvibS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs @RealMattCouch She was reported to ask questions in court last week &amp; wrote the opinion on a 9-0 case]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never ceases to amaze me that when someone is in trouble, people are willing to say "I'll pray for you" but not ask "how can I help?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberlydressler @Amsterdamsel @fareehaali @Jenny_Radloff @rmgenson @robynhannah @AllisonSnow @dhauss @chinamartens… https://t.co/IvSkNyGZHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a disgusting lie. America is not The Handmaid’s Tale. #7in10forRoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like in life...Ignore the trolls! Concentrate on the positivity of #luimelia @PaulaUsero #CarolRovira society… https://t.co/2dawDgBcAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wonderful and makes me laugh every time I look at it. I wish it... #hilarity #snicker #smile #humorous https://t.co/Yfov0TWR3i]]></document></documents></author>