<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My favorite quote of the day: “This campaign was going to be the greatest infomercial in history” — Michael Cohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @drsherv for joining us at #AUASummit19 and your willingness to get more involved! There’s so many ways t… https://t.co/TFdGx2V9TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sallyforth18 @senatemajldr @LindaLouMcBroom A turtle’s gotta do what a turtle’s gotta do, Sally. 🐢🐢🐢🐢🐢🐢😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! Mental health for first responders and everyone touched by tragedy is important. Put on your own oxygen… https://t.co/dh1OASPxFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__ayduchis__ @Nostradamus_Col @ClaudiaLopez ingenuos los q creen q esa loca cumpla algo! No escarmientan en la Pre… https://t.co/2K6IxyOvMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Snapchat trying to tell me that I’m going to be an old cat lady when I get older because my Snapchat map shows m… https://t.co/jxjEEII5Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we add “curly” to the mix to include woman that look like me? I hate when this question is asked because it exc… https://t.co/eRqRVNqRmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokerpami71 Let me know what you think. I still haven't decided if I'm going to watch it or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump should be concerned about those bombs coming from North Korea, the people at the border are… https://t.co/eogDTIh9UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What's that that I smell. Oh yeah the strong smell of fear. I get it though. You are fixing to go down buddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Welcome to a new week, when possibilities renew and we dive in with our weekend energy stores. What a… https://t.co/EV5tqaEvS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[me to my drivers ed instructor WHILE SOBBING as he’s yelling at me to parallel park downtown. 🥴🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving these!  There’s so much great history in @IndyParksandRec 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 #PrideoftheParks #parkslife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouCounterplot My brother and I finally saw Mark Chesnutt a couple years ago and we had a blast. He was great. My… https://t.co/GZwNuRVurP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Em n I really went to goodwill for a storage space thingy but ended up buying just clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Texas,    As much as I love you and the life you’ve given me here, it’s kinda rude that’s it’s gonna be 9 degr… https://t.co/SQsnIGgKna]]></document><document><![CDATA[chvrches, jade bird, and bishop briggs coming too, but I’ve already seen them]]></document><document><![CDATA[People often ask me where do you get your energy? I cherish a good night of sleep and I always drink my juice! unle… https://t.co/ilIDyr4uC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s HBCU election time and I’m so ready to see how creative these campaign ads are bout to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Hose Clamp,dacromet 65Mn steel (black  color). https://t.co/FYMjgqTNeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made myself cauliflower pizza with turkey pepperoni for the first time. 🤤🤤🤩 #KILLINIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY!!  Now is the time to get what you really wanted. #jadedbodybutter #happythursday… https://t.co/gmbtRH5xAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered my bed from @Wayfair for my new place. Ordering my mattress soon. It’s so exciting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan, God controls our universe and earth’s climate.  Read the Bible because it explains the earth’s climate in th… https://t.co/vV0k8Iwv9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[My before and after with my beautiful friend tylerclarkofficial! Thanks for making me all Farrah Fawcett pretty tod… https://t.co/tq8BFn6XWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@79Aspen @diamondslil @DebbyCov So even a well known place like Ticketmaster can make money off people like that? S… https://t.co/c8qSxvlJCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddp @McFaul I've had surgeons throw scalpels at me!  Thankfully they had poor aim!😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[6%⬆️ flat tax/disproportionate burden on mid/low-income ppl who use T as ONLY transport-esp women-for grocery, kids… https://t.co/UEXtpzP1gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyPolSide @cslick803 @KamalaHarris @amyklobuchar Personally, I have a few candidates that I’m excited about. Klobu… https://t.co/B9GDP4Cu5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need my eyebrows threaded... but I can’t put the fate of my face in just anybodys hands 😂 HELP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing my fellow Travellers where to cut co$t in Amsterdam! hint: you don’t need a VIP skip-the-line guided Tour.… https://t.co/vUlKQoRtA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got dressed for the club and ended up at the bar... 2 “shimmering divas” later 🥰🤤🍫 https://t.co/0u9PWMgz2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just... a good human. Freaking love that @JJWatt leads by example. What a cool experience for this kid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piper Friday forensics has been cancelled. Saturday (at this time) is still a go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my fav shows all year! #Oscars ⁠ ⁠ @redcarpet 💃 #FunFact I have such a crush on @RyanSeacrest ☺️ #ERedCarpet https://t.co/tGbGQg4zLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXNashville You would think smugglers would know about how good Law Enforcement Agents are on interstate 40 in Te… https://t.co/zyOHEewcBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall please stop liking that tweet my boss will see that i did it for likes :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[We lost a really good actor but a better man!  Luke Perry was a kind, honorable, gentle, family man. I loved him n… https://t.co/ajjLi05iLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang farcical. #laughter #laugh #smile #hilarious https://t.co/kMtc0tCEtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Tom Lehrer https://t.co/p0x1nrq3bN https://t.co/HDyT4ogZhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A partner or a friend isn't suppose to be your emotional source of recovery, happiness or mental sanity. So when th… https://t.co/pNTtKTd3cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL tell everyone to be ready at 7 because I’ll get home from work at 7.. it’s now 8 and NOBODY is ready. I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veronicajauriqu And that’s a tough truth for me! You know how much I loved him as a kid, being president of the Mo… https://t.co/eAHGpuS4jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My lawyer was telling me no, but my ego ... my ego was telling me yes!” 🤣  R. Kelly Interview Cold Open - SNL… https://t.co/Z2wUJyu7fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethiopia's state broadcaster says there were no survivors from Ethiopian Airlines flight crash  https://t.co/tjBeZRfkGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NelsonGashagaza Didn't those falls/lake/towns have names before they were named Victoria?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@losowsky Well it’s about Syria so either ISIS or national bureaucracy, depending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicoxw1 @TerryLCline2 And I still say this money he wants isn’t for his wall but for his own pockets. Just like th… https://t.co/4xtAPNpbSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Dr. Seuss! ❤️ Unless someone like you cares a whole awful lot, nothing is going to get better. It's… https://t.co/tIwEH0rLlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#45 planned a trip out of the country to visit his murgerous pals WHY?  #pompandcircumstances  distraction for the… https://t.co/20a0RPKK1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨Style is a way to say who you are without having to speak...✨💚 @ Nassau County, New York https://t.co/5gc9B0H9GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseAPaul I was wondering what was going on when I drove by at 9:15 today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YRInsider @CBSDaytime Well that just ruined it Summer must be a match if they’re going to play let’s make a deal.… https://t.co/pbUOzALNlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassius_a @ayellowduchess @onairfest @IanNFox We miss you! Come back to NYC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew Tash I was different the minute I saw her take her shoes off to fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterAskin1 Please people in San Bernardino help this poor kitty Cupid get a forever home before its to late,ADOPT… https://t.co/7q67rtf9EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl shut the fuck up i bet you don’t even know every single thing you’re supporting when wearing that hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to laugh. #funniness #snicker #grin #clever https://t.co/L6Ojzbi9j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guys I just wanted to remind y’all that my acoustics playlist on Spotify has now reached 6 hrs !! Pls send me a… https://t.co/yZ92S0Nb7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This issue and parents' #advocacy around it made front page news in our local paper today. #SpecialEducation… https://t.co/CBptYiA2mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You understand what you confront..  #MusicMonday #111 #death #rebirth #comingsoon #newrelease #supportlocalartists… https://t.co/d42q9GYlT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffries McCabe said this himself to sell his book!Sounds like jail time for them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently my roommate and I are watching two separate episodes of The West Wing in different rooms of the house. #TWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a really great day, week, month.. yo this is my semester! This dog here is how I'm feeling tonight! Thank… https://t.co/T93IbHKJpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this account adds you, please block and report. It’s not me. https://t.co/8Q2mIXmvM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adrianbird___ Imma buy it with the gift card you got me do basically you are the one buying wingstop :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Y33T3RS @stfutony WHY THE HELL WOULD YOU POST THIS?! YOU ARE DISGUSTING!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryjoyonto @SpeakerPelosi @JoaquinCastrotx @realDonaldTrump Nancy Pelosi wants the wall, just not under President… https://t.co/EhcrbmnjTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just nominated my favorite girl scout troop! We made it to round two!! WOOT! WOOT! Vote for troop 60947 💚 https://t.co/0MYH6ILYkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collection of stairs #newyork #stairs#highlinenyc #collections @ West Side, New York https://t.co/K3OeHusoCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deciding to stop and tan or rushing home to my amazon packages and dogs are always my biggest dilemmas after work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how I be acting when it comes my nails lmao. But once one break and I can’t get it done that day it’s over. 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwynellRoland Shit's disgusting! Had it in Minneapolis thinking different state of mind and situation! Nope still Ewwww wtf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #moonlitnight beckons for a walk on the #beach. #lovers #poets #philosophers #shipcaptains and more of us feel th… https://t.co/Wmy0f57Hah]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao i feel like the Kardashian’s saw this all playing out differently in their heads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nezua @andrewkimmel @robvato You don’t have to donate anymore, he will be taking a hell of a lot more money from y… https://t.co/6ZvfAa3yUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imillhiser If dems can't find a way to get senate on board, sure we'll wait it out. No big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neauxna I don’t suppose you’d have time for a coffee with me in Gentilly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO ONE seems to grasp; Hillary herself wrote the BULK of the Salatious Stories=Dossier!Christine Blasey Ford often… https://t.co/qrP1uwN5mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl in my class had a really hard exam today. Her boyfriend made everyone in his frat text her “good luck”  I need love like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyelash extensions are so fuckin expensive. I'm about to learn to do that shit myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki704 They are the fucking bestest. @GatlinGroberg thinks they are an abomination but don’t mind him. I am fascinated with cotton candy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[really thought i was the only one that planned my dreams out like this 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shannon_Hogan @PeterAllocco @NYIslanders @91Butch @brendanmburke @IslesWhiteSUV Thank you so much! Means PS - If y… https://t.co/MUpAGAND03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philadelphic Right! Totally. (I rant, too 😆) But...we’re lucky to live in a place where we have a ton of other opt… https://t.co/uTYsy1LC6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm shocked that people are shocked. Why wouldn't trump override rules for his family, order waivers, require NDAs,… https://t.co/Phk2Gwdfjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another amazing weekend with my Miss Arizona Family. Congratulations  to Whitnee Wright Cordes Carrie Brumbaugh Gag… https://t.co/6RNpL6yhK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i've been tweeting about the social so much. that's alright tho because they're my new favorite people😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing the 3️⃣! My house numbers are made from old metal gas station numbers. If you find a 3️⃣ that matches, plea… https://t.co/JWyFJYiPug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shansdoe @marvismartian Cause they're being paid directly from tax payers so they have to show where the money is going]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO GONE LOVE ME?? WHO GONE MAKE ME FEEL GOOD?!? https://t.co/W86bW5wDvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesseorrall And a backup system for those who suddenly lose income and/or their healthcare. I think ACA should be improved, and built upon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit is getting real at my job, the takeover is happening and no one knows who’s gonna go and who will keep their j… https://t.co/6bZ8m31K9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I knew Target wasn’t for me when I met a girl that goes to Harvard and she told me meeting Malia Obama wasn’t really that cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será transmitido por @MTVLA #AyudahumanitariaVenezuela https://t.co/WNNtjRxstt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ps she’s wearing the PRICELESS Tiffany diamond..... 128 karats people!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 27: feels good to be home. #skiseason #skicolorado #freelancelife . . . . #skiingislife #skiforever… https://t.co/I4w8NR06mP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMoore @RealCandaceO @prageru We have to have ID FOR EVERYTHING 😡🇺🇸😡🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @HWJablo Absolutely unbelievable. These people are delusional. #AndrewMcCabe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmeyer115comcas @LuvMacyIsabella I do not follow him - can’t bare the site of the vile creature]]></document></documents></author>