<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@alguienomas @fdelatg @TasteAtlas @TacoTrail @XBorderConsul @carlos_glezgtez @gomezpickering @FernandoKras… https://t.co/liUCf6puNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Justin Bieber says he’s struggling and asks for prayers in cryptic Instagram post: It’s still not… https://t.co/zLiTQbpJfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneofBrooklyn @brittballard @nowthisnews You are wrong. I fought for exceptions on these grounds long before it p… https://t.co/T8IFIq6Qor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Private Mortgage Insurance! That’s what PMI means. Stop yelling at me! @RickieFowler @RocketMortgage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Brickman @DeRushaJ More snow in Vegas. About 2" this time and some of it is actually sticking to the roads. M… https://t.co/qNDvcgAsfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAAllStar @SDinwiddie_25 @_bigjayy_ @RODIONS1 @BrooklynNets Brooklyn’s in the house*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rojo_ub @LiamPaulCanning @Chulufeni3 That match I thought he doesn’t have the minerals to play in this league much… https://t.co/xxtUsOMcLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenWolfe I can't help but like you and your excellent tweets, Aiden!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y seguimos en la Sima con Gol del Mejor del Mundo #Messi Arribaaaa el equipo Azul Grana. @oleimi1 #ForçaBarça https://t.co/po2Fc3C8YY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just went on a rant when a co-worker made light of the constant surveillance we’ve walked into willingly and the “1… https://t.co/aauX4JM3rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning loves, I hope everyone had a great weekend. It is the start of another week, lets get this bread, lets… https://t.co/lfTFRDHuUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[SIGN THE @BOLDPROGRESSIVE PETITION: All Democratic 2020 candidates should offer bold plans to break up big monopoli… https://t.co/fxBp4YYiC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityNews MISSING WOMAN - Gabriella Antoine - Missing since Jan 23rd. She has a medical condition that affects cogn… https://t.co/djianD2LGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys know the rest of the story: it works and it’s a huge victory for the Continental Army.   Although the Brit… https://t.co/JeWunQZUrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyjoe1083 If there is a loving God, life shouldn’t necessarily be ease and comfort. But it shouldn’t be abject… https://t.co/bNtpVtgTNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in doing so, they protected some people more important than Epstein.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @ecclesias @realDonaldTrump Hell no ! https://t.co/9z5bR5oDiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find out you're actually getting a tax refund this year, you celebrate with tacos. #ThanksSecondKid https://t.co/A2E3WGsDWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke to the great @tarzancr about his Friday showdown with Amir Khan.  Check it out!👇 #CallToGreatness  https://t.co/n8YGoXoc87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYGiantsCountry Me and you both...  why isn't there some sort or action taken against these people? They report an… https://t.co/ycL7CJOpHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I doubt it's a feasible or affordable but let's say he's right who's going to pay for it you? What about those of u… https://t.co/jsUCWIfjkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of myy coworkers really get on my nerves. They complain about everything as far as the work, they wanna make m… https://t.co/jRayj5Tb47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cam Reddish (DUKE) knocks down a three anddddd the 🐐 follows that up with a timeout....  80-67 UNC w/ 2:44 remaining.  #UNCvsDUKE 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fallabel My last a1c was 6.9. I saw a new eye doctor a few months ago and he looked at me and said, " you sure you… https://t.co/RzYxT4yImC]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is definitely a liar when the need arises and then he tells the truth when he thinks it will help take the heat… https://t.co/rDQ1abvvCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaffordBros Almost had this problem yesterday. Luckily I had @panerabread for the win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scoring has slowed down. Knapper cuts it to 17-14 as Colony has tightened up on the defensive end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up in the middle of the night to “Core Values” all over my timeline. Hopefully the vods are still up tomorrow lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh my homies gassed me up to talk to this one girl last night and i spilled a whole cup of henny on her 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words can’t describe how proud I am of my roomie. Comeback athlete of the year is calling your name 🥳… https://t.co/BiBfdpQt5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCI_101 @cosminDZS @matthewasears More like the confederate’s baseball team.  Not really a terribly offensive thin… https://t.co/D4jv3ubuTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Yep, China is going to buy 10M metric tons 10 years from now. What BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You do not represent civil rights. None of us in Alabama wanted you here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @VashtiQV @tinseymiller @Mhollstein @ClaudiaC @DianewasHR @echoicpoetry @juliet_cromwell… https://t.co/6UvaSTYuNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell Love your work Darren! But I don’t understand why you keep promoting a brand that discriminates and p… https://t.co/gIVBa7CIPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioMomesso36 Where you getting ready for an audition with Happy Days Mo? Great Leather Jacket Fonzie. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Big Homie, you’re one helluva guy and an even Bigger role model keep doing you! Your influence on everyone i… https://t.co/wfOudyLbwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst beat down ever @DrHugeShow @TheStrapPodcast @SuplexCityLimit @smarktodeath @superkickingit @SATPOD @SATPOD… https://t.co/6cr8BSs0Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indianapolis Indiana will take Amazon on and give them quality employees!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PUGASounds I think I'm just scared to become one of those guys that are successful yet "big headed" or "arrogant".… https://t.co/a9CEnBtUmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doshhabrianna @tr3glove @_darren4 Sprit not that bad as long as u aint going far. Vegas she was wild for trying that. Lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoje entra o horário de verão aqui, mas só começa a valer 2h da manhã. Tipo, como isso????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houstontexans32 @TheWrapRadio Awesome Kenneth! Great picture of you both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@telesurenglish @NicolasMaduro Hugo Chavez is a hero to millions of Latinos my age who refuse to be a subject to th… https://t.co/f6PyGuTRRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larrycollmus Good one but @VeitchIan threw the first punch  https://t.co/ubiZNpYM0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Brodiesmith21 and @KelseyLowrance on getting married last night!! Can’t wait to see what the future holds for them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to get started? Click the link! https://t.co/KlcnzoeBn8  #creditrestoration #credit #financialfreedom… https://t.co/gMzraj4xT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Metallica Crafted a Metal Masterpiece in ‘Master of Puppets’ https://t.co/ZJeoZeRsTW @UltClassicRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ITR is going to be the most involved I’ve ever had to do.... 22 (or 24) teams getting covered tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchpberg @dino4dino @PatGarofalo @LittleSenator When faced with the claim that a first century religious text ju… https://t.co/YiVG5e57yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio #MarcoTheLiarRubio #77RubioLiesPerWeek https://t.co/SFqpyQandv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_James32 @SithLordAR Well this is contact year and for all that is worth it needs to be brought up. He plays grea… https://t.co/gOi66ccqzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHNabors @oopsadoop @LovelyLu @jkheaton Good morning y’all! Hope all is well. We are having an astronomical high t… https://t.co/e3AVy8YvcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @TheRealS0s Fatal Flaw In Climate Change Science https://t.co/ageLOcdfaY #Solarweather #Astrophysics #ClimateChange #Science]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gescol @Airbnb Si llegas al JFK es de buscar algo en Brooklyn o en Queens, algunas zonas no son muy seguras. En Ma… https://t.co/tnldq9qL9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyPlaskett thank you for being spot on in the hearing! Excellent job! I hope there is an investigation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum He does realize that Donald Trump tells more lies than anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day in Epcot...   #tourbreak #fam #famreunion #wdw #waltdisneyworld #epcot #missionspace #barfbag… https://t.co/iZZKOLJdIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does he have to boost defense budget, he is having his own little peace talks with the leaders who hate us the… https://t.co/1CkBRasWdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@discountcompost @FriedmanCassie it’s like the twitter 4 option poll just isn’t nuanced enough or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepyiis_ I got so excited lol idc how many times that happens ill get excited every time😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahMargarett So according to a lot of the things that’s I’ve seen and read regarding Tony, the MCU doesn’t want t… https://t.co/cU3tG8RLjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PantsuitPolitic He’s not being held accountable for those garbage-assed shorts he has on either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks everyone! Did 46 min on treadmill, 30 leg presses 130lbs, floor stretching, and 4 sets of 10perfect push ups!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Activity #3...walk about town! Awesome day!⛳️⚾️🏃🏻‍♂️ @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/vx2aT9HYBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it, we’re good for each other. But it ain’t been, because it didn’t need to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS FRIDAY NIGHT! #IfYouKnowYouKnow #FirstFriday https://t.co/fLayzZ2drY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could have gotten two old vintage  fostex speakers if I had a car ... Gonna plug it in a realistic 8 track amp , warm sound ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good god @anthemgame feels so good! Unbelievably happy to be a #LegionOfDawn owner right now. This game is insanely… https://t.co/RqruYkrdXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari-  what do you want to be in the future? C- a more educated version of me Sari-  that is it? C- I need to learn… https://t.co/mRfWPi2tM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this cute there's something wrong with you. Jensen Ackles on bad driving--the horn of righteousne… https://t.co/pGJn2HxEJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilbertinho619 Same, just like the effort I don’t have to put in really makes the difference lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueKofi watch your back entering the chamber tonight, @NiaJaxWWE may jump you and take your spot.  #ElminationChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Chris. If you're around here again, stop by. I've already added more since your visit 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is fat ass lying @realDonaldTrump .   On a luxury  vacation in Florida  of course playing golf . https://t.co/Y3mUN72lWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok so I took off ow work to sit back and watch The Match on live Twitter feed ....beteeen @Back9Ben and… https://t.co/eLA9EiqHRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[New money in budget for widening of Banwell, Dominion near Totten, reconstruction on Ypres @CTVWindsor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun house show last night. Debuted a new song, and it felt great. 👍🏼 https://t.co/33A30KP00y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two faces of the Never Trump movement marry in Miami https://t.co/XG5Sla9u1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is sad when NASCAR CEO has to tell the drivers to race and make it a show! The 500 wasn't single file in a tra… https://t.co/LFby2qfOiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[First thing Clare said to me this morning: Daddy, it’s your birthday today! Let’s go on a birthday run! Done, sweet… https://t.co/3rkazO6eXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trailertrack When can I expect the first trailer for Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark. Rumor was it was supposed… https://t.co/Ei2FmyTKTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc Why was she babysitting at 11 and I read the day care provider left her alone with the baby hmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump offers Venezula a generous settlement under Guaido! Will the dictator step down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thorpeta17 You failed your highness. I'm a fuckin jedi, like my father before me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PQ. Vous savez très bien que j'ai soutenu le PQ avec des dizaines de tweets avec son projet de GRAND DÉBLOCAGE mis… https://t.co/05RJoPj2Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsBlove24 @KBoyd1516 @ChrisTuttell looks like #kindersCAN is headed to @VanceCoSchools!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of their wins at #TheOscars these two albums are gonna be on repeat for the next month   #SpiderVerse… https://t.co/rkq8GOMamW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThadLibs @Levy14Gillespie First 2 times you try to play video a pol up gon come just close out twice then play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Trump is on the world stage and some idiot asked him about a convicted liar in the USA trying to smear his former employer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[black(out) on black(out) with g tonight, but the transformer blowing up didn’t stop us from continuing in the dark… https://t.co/YpuZ316uin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZWormley @KingJames @2chainz Shits cray. All I know is he can’t be worst than Kobe 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaaan hard to beat the Stunner. And not just cuz of Austin. He made it great but anyone doing it is just awesome… https://t.co/ncKS1kgERt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JannyMir @bettyboop_pr Gracias men!! Alante, busca en mis fotos los esparagos envueltos en bacon...  Vamo a meterle...💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/PKVEyVAubZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_sharims @dreamerofspring @desiderioDC @BresPolitico Tiffany = not under any cloud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel bad for Zion, never want to see a player get hurt. Feel bad for those people paying 2500 to see him in this game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parked for the night due to weather @ Love's Travel Stop.  Whitestown IN. https://t.co/j3frjJo1ZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a D-D-D-D-D-D-H Double THAT! by Boiler Brewing Co. at @boilerbrewingco — https://t.co/IWK6SKQ5DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and #HappyThursday from my alternative music station. ☕️ @KHOU @chitakhou @SallyKHOU11… https://t.co/qOiJhSZ8kx]]></document></documents></author>