<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#girls #triplets #friendship #promo #babes #red #promotion #veterans #money #hugs #hands #addmeonsnapchat #addme… https://t.co/2xd4TieZlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKChiWriting I’ll take @LightfootForChi over @ToniPreckwinkle any day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trilliaventuras HAHAHAHAHAHA OMG THAT IS AMAZINGGGGGGGGGG https://t.co/F9s2rvIMyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjo4_ I know, 75$ for VIP .... we would just have to road trip &amp; idk if i can get .... but i really wanna go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkingMichael Please share it with your friend @m_onchis. He needs it at least twice a week 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 4 maybe 5 years I found out that my brothers ex talked shit about my family. While they were together.  Not o… https://t.co/y52KE5EJDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in tears over the most beautiful things this evening. I hope and pray for more nights like this one. Enjoy this… https://t.co/5IF0szZsGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to California and you best believe the only eyeshadow palette I’m packing is the @jamescharles artistry palette 🎨 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put myself through a lot of NECESSARY shit to get through this UNNECESSARY SHIT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t believe i held off on watching The Magicians for so long it’s SO good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseaBallerini @ElvisPresley @youtubemusic @nbc Omg...you did a fantastic job singing for the Elvis Tribute! Job well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahkbrown11 sitting there while karma takes care of things...but not wanting to speak up because she’s a… https://t.co/mZgLjygDW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[But if I drive out demons by the finger of God, then the kingdom of God has come upon you. https://t.co/mT82VbLJVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not saying what theme because my bday is in December and if someone steals it we’re fighting lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[All smiles at our Third Thursday event last week at 519 Broome in SoHo. #TogetherFromAfar #IrishNetworkNYC #INNYC… https://t.co/8JMkBQaYwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to the @dallasmavs game! Going to watch this @luka7doncic everyone is talking about!! @1053SS @Shippyfunsports @SkinWade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsDC @Chrisconsrv1776 I totally agree!!!Fabulous speech!!Love this President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stibuni @mrs_soller @ESLTechies You are the beat!! @MariaGDove and I would love to hear what’s happening in Texas… https://t.co/TPnAsNJhXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tad bit of snow.  You can't see where the beach ends and the water begins. https://t.co/ofq5QTBjQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Sunset ⚓️🌴🌅 #nofilterneeded #sundaymood #sundaysunset #marinalife #seasideliving #marinadelrey #losangeles https://t.co/mg2KK3FyCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[my roommate ALWAYS has the windows closed, and now that I’m sick, this bitch wants them OPENED.... sorry sis it ain’t happening this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Cohen hearing and thinking about my friend @tj_lsudad ...😳😳💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was here...  #specialboggs #basesloaded #poughkeepsie #newyork #willboggs #alicat876 @ Bases Loaded https://t.co/lvDZt23ESn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolarToday Hay que hacer caras y colocarlas en toda venezuela en diferentes lugares para recordar todos los héroes… https://t.co/at0XHOYiTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won our first match of the day! Let’s go @CrushSouthVB @bertbrantley https://t.co/ZvmM8lHAZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Its not very considering the Intelligence community has been shown to be infilatrated by the DNC, and… https://t.co/0povNtHx8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoPenguin2 @MrsSpuds @72cricket @RidenerTina @BxglL @sharon_schwan @sannbs @ACog1984 @CSonafelt They need to be all fired up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarGoshTV I know your birthday is coming up.  My husband is 2 year and 3 days older . My sons is 4 days after yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/OrtG9PIWEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArturoMontoya57 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews 2+ years of a bogus investigation and still no evidence of anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CatholicTwitter #Love #Lent #Repent  https://t.co/NzOskISHLY https://t.co/1XybfA1eOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my kid was little he called 911 to ask detectives to our house to help him find a missing toy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@englishcomp Please allow me to recommend The Weight of Ink by Rachel Kadish...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#deadlift applying jaffestrength pinky grip felt a big difference thank you for the gift of knowledge on your post… https://t.co/Xsk07KAOsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cupcakesn_rose Oh my goddddddd my ex... I TOLD him one time, if that gets in my hair, I’m gonna smack you. And I had to smack him. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BourgeoisWells anytime love! it truly makes me so happy to see you being successful and doing well 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went to avengersstation on the tail end of our #Vegas - Grand Canyon trip. We're a family of 6 (kids ages 13, 10… https://t.co/Z9Hft9lIt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Maskednyan/Machonyan! Based off of Tiger Mask! https://t.co/ewiELiUxJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of coworkers made herself a burger yesterday, put a large quantity of mayo on BOTH burger buns, and then happil… https://t.co/z2YO5JRHJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIME Why would someone pay to hear her speak? I honestly can’t take it.  It’s torture to hear her talk. I have to turn her off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A recent survey by the Society for Women’s Health Research found that schools often disregard kids’ restroom right… https://t.co/0I2Pic9yWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow BOMB SHELL😳 But it’s not cool she used the N word 😡 but I saw myself in her.... You can’t make a man like RICH… https://t.co/KIqifsvKRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyDalglish @Mme_Mac @Surrey_Schools @bcedplan @CityofSurrey @Rob_Fleming Tell that to every single parent who v… https://t.co/HUSxgfMpsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyanide_cookies @fallenangel8504 Just seeing you there at all was enough ❤️🤗 I miss you! It’s been too long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTG_CEOGEH Louisiana gumbo. Chicken and sausage or some variety of seafood ( shrimp, crab, oyster). Either will do. 😋😋😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthemRespect Literacy should definitely be a requirement because the functionally illiterate can and will tip sca… https://t.co/au1T2so3um]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lil_yenta My husband is a letter carrier. When I met Sanders I thanked him for his fight for postal workers and their families.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lee888123 @DerekPa56710094 @SUPERGOCHOo @stradagangelica @meerbakker @BrownieJohnston @saladesvertes @khanhakim_k… https://t.co/mqBUHSRhSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[do not try n ignore me when i see your active , i will pull up n snatch you by yo raggedy ass hair hoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA He should know he has been mentally chrall his weird life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s win this for our beloved  💙💙😍 Please don’t forget to vote on the site too.  Thanks!  #VoteKathrynBernardo… https://t.co/gm0nvoNgfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this amusing there's something wrong with you. Going to write this on the board I'm my math class… https://t.co/iRgHWlpazm]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘LegenDerry Food Experience’ Evening / Legenderry Food Strategy  https://t.co/U5TnrY3UE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep it here @KOANewsRadio for live coverage of the bill signing and the emergency declaration announcement at 8am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @c7five So glad you have your tokens and don’t parade them around. What a very offensive statement!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[you're going to snicker. The Simpsons/ Bart and Homer https://t.co/PQ1mHxys9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[👩🏻‍💼👩🏿‍💼👩🏽‍💼👩🏼‍💼👩🏾‍💼 No More Excuses. Recruit and Develop Women Leaders. https://t.co/xRA2jYDqLT #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be a nightmare. Especially for our child care providers - who by the way are private businesses.… https://t.co/blq4nNFAzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNC please please please don’t support the propaganda arm of Trumpland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles https://t.co/Gf3ZFTAdeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlysintothat @hekatesgal @imisspoundsigns DONT DO IT it’s a slippery slope! Just do some fun assed nail art]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 days to opening day! Tickets on sale today! I'm getting my Opening Day ticket! Go Brewers! 👍🏻😁👏🏻🎉🙌🏻⚾️  "The game… https://t.co/KwfCOCb2sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheryltreadwel2 Presidential HUMPING. His 1939 mental people don’t see or don’t care HOW MUCH TRUMP HATES AMERICA… https://t.co/7IOJsqOtjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cats are on the road again today — looking for some bigtime wins on Sunday to start the new week in the #NovaNation… https://t.co/WrsW6GKNej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you miss #OTAS19 in Boston? Check out our IDC Link for takeaways and #OpenText’s event highlights at:… https://t.co/zQk5Iprkwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself So many lives and family were unchangeably altered and broken during that horrible time in history. We… https://t.co/EfAq3VPMh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iron Mike. #miketyson #espn #tko #boxing #boxers #tyson https://t.co/bg5IzOULD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the three flat tires and so many other problems that I’ve had in the span of two weeks time, feeding the skyd… https://t.co/izfdDYqPhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders One time the daughter of the woman who babysat me made rice with just water, not cooking it (she was pr… https://t.co/VGMW6rS6gD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is 3pm: 82 year old Glenda Jackson is onstage right now telling a storm to blow winds and rage in @KingLearBway.… https://t.co/VmDyaC9cqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Whats his carbon footprint fir each plane he rides. Get you bike Jay]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're testing the Kings pregame hype presentation. It's the most intense in the league.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un día como hoy de 2006, sesenta y cinco mineros mueren tras una explosión de gas en una mina de carbón en la local… https://t.co/Kb9K0fHPCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder who @RealKevinConroy uses?  Fortress of Solitude: Getting Insurance For Batman’s Batcave. https://t.co/WllxRdP3oA  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[PERFECTION!! #BakedPotato #NotFried #JustDelicious #ThisIsLove #HomeMade #ILoveMyPotato #InstaGood… https://t.co/wIkjZcXDC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MARTINSBURG: Superintendent Manny Arvon alludes of a special meeting with the Board of Education on Thursday regar… https://t.co/q3K9Ju9ai5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pet sitting two adorable miniature Aussiedoodles &amp; I’m so Inlove 💕even jesse said they were cute 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is why im still not used to highways ): im nervous as shit all the tome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Guns For Hands by Twenty One Pilots https://t.co/VN40YunVAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the person who gave me one of my favorite baseball memories EVER ❤️ @FlavaFraz21 #HRDerby… https://t.co/KSa3jgUjbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Michael K (@kenskrew) for remembering safety from orientation and using it!! #LeadByExample… https://t.co/KSspfguxYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how #AOC is reppin teachers✊🏽 #sideeye #gasface #WTF #THINK #readbetweenthelines #momentorMOVEMENT @ Taylor… https://t.co/vMijIlJQSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Accountability is strong, bitter medicine. HRC’s most reflexive defenders, like Bernie’s, never have quite gotten there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shower and getting ready and headed to work #DaylightSavingsTime kicked my ass I'm tired]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliec76 @That1WelderGuy @nancyxsweet @AOC Nothing is free...keep that in mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonWhi63670221 @NoFacebookForMe @laundry_guy @ACMeyor @jk11195355 @provdcrumblover @alshadowdancer @DWCDroneGuy… https://t.co/ObLXo1kIcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corriasmith Sometimes people ask me for photos from three years ago. I'm like.... I AM NOT YOUR INTERN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tag @GameOfThrones in the replies if you can! It would mean the world to me if HBO saw my makeup 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another analysis by @gaywonk that could fit in Journalism &amp; media studies classrooms;]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said “okay pose in 3..2..1!” And this bitch pulls out the LOOKS https://t.co/CBKnsrScLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regarding today’s decision, Sacramento State alumnus Marcus Jones says, “I was upset and pretty much hurt for the f… https://t.co/NOEIpOfASB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar your response to Q re former staff speaking out: Yes, some are unhappy w/me and they have the right t… https://t.co/ufh78aDzvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickIngraham @samtripoli Praise “Bob” Amen and awomen https://t.co/e1REOFoMFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously.  I want to hang out with it’s you two together. O. M. G. I can’t even imagine the excitement]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my friends who have survived hate crimes: I see you and I’m holding space for you. I know how difficult thes… https://t.co/4hl6ibab7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle on @nbcsnl wearing a T-shirt that says, “Protect Trans Kids.” My hero! #WontBeErased]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never would of thought of getting a promise ring but I guess I was wrong 🙈🥰 https://t.co/ugFsQaBfTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supper at Desert Wind begins on Monday. Open to all children ages 1-18. Hours 3:15 - 4:45. #TeamSISD]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a guy at Coal Fire Pizza wearing a Villanova National Champions hoodie. Ew. #pcbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[People: for the LAST time!  When you receive something that doesn’t fit you the way you like but it has been accura… https://t.co/PyQO9D0Yt3]]></document></documents></author>