<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Juste un petit thread pour expliquer qu’après @NASAInSight , l’équipe #sspa de @ISAE_officiel est très fière de por… https://t.co/yF1KRgbCJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorianCS6 Ese es otro tema Hahaha a mi me pareció más como para el funeral de tu sugar daddy. Jajajjaja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day I live my life based off if ppl like me or not is the day I die😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland is going to school as Walt Disney today! I was surprised he let me draw on his face... #MySonPortland… https://t.co/bjSdtdyRig]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #crew96 season wasn’t meant to be. The millionaire owner and billion-dollar league were supposed to win.   But… https://t.co/bKJEFCj4TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marymac6 You’ll have a long long wait. Great campaign advertising. Shows their racism word by word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fabchart @jackandtimmusic Jack &amp; Tim. You've got my *Vote* 😎👍🇬🇧 https://t.co/L7kGdPFR9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hooded Merganser on the #CTRiver today. @petermarteka @CTAudubon @CanonUSAimaging  @Sigma_Photo @PetzoldsMarine… https://t.co/TOtnhHUegb]]></document><document><![CDATA[AM Data: First evidence of a broad-based sequential acceleration in European economic data since the headfakes we s… https://t.co/MBpFKJUJc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205 @Al_Gorelioni @alllibertynews… https://t.co/IPUhyMdwot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMobyKeech @XPets1 @We4Dogs @macwhittle @BonniedaWestie @MillieOTLFP #XPSHQ 👋👋👋👋💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiCrazies @davidhogg111 Show me where the NRA is advocating to REPEAL the already existing law that PROHIBITS… https://t.co/imv3kEvgwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[All i do is win win win no matter what.... #FEScreditRepair https://t.co/yUd8t7Y8Vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one deserves the spotlight more than @TrueKofi! It’s time to give it to him even more give him his Mania Moment!… https://t.co/gAp7rs5k02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffavril @PurdueOnBTN @BoilerFootball @arouxBTN Hey @cliffavril .. any chance of u making a comeback?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dinmeister @emrazz I hope he loses her in public. I hope she strands him and he has to call mommy for a ride home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats a Alfonso Cuarón. Ojalá pueda mostrale Kubernetes, la película. https://t.co/Jk07LGALgD  #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliespiering Please check out their stories. And please, let's do something this time. #SinceParkland #GunSense  https://t.co/4JI7F1P6Q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7BOOMERESIASON It is the greatest sport not only to play but to watch in person.  TV doesn’t omit justice.  They s… https://t.co/CsZGnjnwWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put our children first. #sos #StopStateAidCuts #saveobparas @NewJerseyDOE @GovMurphy @NJSenatePres @DrLRepollet… https://t.co/OLz0oNquPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @MarkMeadows @Jim_Jordan These two are embarrassing.  Clowns who may go down too before this is al… https://t.co/OQ5zJ59X2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenNeverson @Mrz_BrwnSkin @SammieAlways Comeeeee onnnnnnnn yesss https://t.co/EZkHOhJZlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que día !!! Pero con la satisfacción de haber salido con todo !!! Gracias Dios 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS  @donlemoncnnnews Don, Trump have screwed up and divide… https://t.co/MHtOzlzOt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Two things I care about, getting paid and getting laid. And if I can do both,.... that would be illegal. “ - my clients are hilarious 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s play a game shall we? 3 computers in a row. 2 MacBooks and something called an MSi laptop. Which 1 is Mark’s?… https://t.co/7cCB7NpVcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am about to depart on my week long journey to New Orleans. I am attending a Keller Williams event. I am taking Am… https://t.co/J3gSwPtmb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passion.........Humility ......Thankfulness....Wonder were he learned all of that? 🔷🔶🔷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CABornTXRaised Well that sucks!! 😞   I didn’t know I had to go through all this before I could monetize my video.… https://t.co/GtVMWTPerd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You fucking coward. So tough. So how long did you serve again. Draft dodging bag of crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikekimster Infrastructure on the Coastside is very fragile, despite being 25 miles from both San Francisco and Pa… https://t.co/gcGq3IkyNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. Just broke up with my TV provider. Gonna get on that Youtube TV    life. #cutthecord #buhbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallofMax @Indian_spirit_ With the way that cats like to knock things off shelves, I don't think so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen’s explosive opening statement about Trump, annotated: The full text of his opening statement, with hi… https://t.co/mmKcygTWoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I over slept for my airport leave time and the security line is ridiculously long... At least I've got precheck hav… https://t.co/1pDDAy88R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhiloBro Waiter - Would you like some coffee, Doctor?  Descartes - I think not (and suddenly disappears).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este domingo debes adelantar el reloj y Rubio espera acabar con esta práctica https://t.co/6gbcnPWnzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pastel de #Zanahoria #cumplañero  #PorSiAlguienPreguntaba #Food #FoodPorn #Tijuana #Cake #CarrotCake en Vitro https://t.co/UrUMKC6P6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#monstercookies - just out of the oven - yummy! @ Aurora, Ontario https://t.co/CBT8ERQz7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorie_lady @JoyceWhiteVance Exactly, that's my question... There putting this Woman's life @ risk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeuroNupe17 Bruh. I went on a week bender. Her pen was strong. You make the earth move is prob my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_DMcDonald It’s always good to have a theme too. Great for morale. 🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you hear a little girl screaming “Lady Gaga won the Oscar” somewhere in Baltimore don’t worry it’s just me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oswaldears I like to think it's set before 'Father Time' whenever I watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsHuggie @RachelbooTwitch @JustBreezy_R6 Vancouver :) they get so much rain there isn’t much snow :p. I want to m… https://t.co/QJY8QGFlFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[W/2:56 left in 1Q: #Clovis coach rips off his blazer and chucks it against the wall. #HobbsHoops #EaglesHoops leads… https://t.co/hvPoU1Mqpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiltonAGabriel @LucindaLC @UnfilteredSE @matthewjdowd @secupp Uh-huh! You keep thinking that brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rear view mirror is smaller than the windshield because we’re not supposed to spend so much time looking back. #forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregnixhuman @MrDelicious13 C’mon man don’t be hyperbolic. They’re not that big.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, it had been a minute since I went to the bathroom without my phone. Felt like forever but I’ve discovered seve… https://t.co/3xLgyitKGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't courts ruled that immigration is strictly a federal government responsibility?  How does a state have stand… https://t.co/IaHfqC3Gld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian4NY @WhisperMaPhone @NJTrainDelays @GirlReporterNJT @PVLWarriors @f @StratoMasterGuy @aew1776 https://t.co/V8Adg6TMnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t leave money on the table just because you don’t realize how big you can get” - @garyvee   Thank you Gary for… https://t.co/Me1P0ZVZcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_simionas people 6’7&gt; need to start a union to get more y’all friendly forms of travel lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Root of It All by Twin Leaf Brewery @ Twin Leaf Brewery — https://t.co/zci3Nypxsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorilla Media WORKING!! WORKING (205WORKING™) @ Birmingham, Alabama https://t.co/ChZrIDrf6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonBisca Claro análisis. Soy seguidor del Barza y coincido con lo q expresa Don Bisca.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh...so it's not about The Constitution? #Trump #TrumpWall #TrumpEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnyCostaki Actually, more research is needed to answer this question. I'll check back with you in a month...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina holds on to snap #FlaPanthers three-game winning streak, move 10 points ahead of Florida in playoff race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids read “The Pet Goat” just moments after not only when George Bush was told America was “under attack”, but also… https://t.co/L7ISl7J1lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leozuckermann @lopezobrador_ LADRONES COMO @EPN  CORRUPTOS COMO @FelipeCalderon  JAMAS HE VISTO QUE LOS CUESTIONES… https://t.co/6vchsvJjll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @NBCNews Complicit @GOP tries to protect you while Mueller is racking up dozens of indictments. Yo… https://t.co/HY9PX1UYAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My feelings are always irrationally hurt when I realize someone that I don’t know, and sometimes haven’t even ever… https://t.co/2Wl6P4tjxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvansTireSD any discounts on a tire rotation if I bought my tires there? Thanks for answering! ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vijaya if speech drives a person off your platform, that person STILL has the choice/opportunity to come back on.… https://t.co/uifwMx06BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please get Carolina out of the top 25... too much pressure on the season as it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most exciting parts of Boudoir is all the different looks women can achieve. A common myth is boudoir is… https://t.co/5x0MROuskC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamilfame Justo ayer platicabamos eso mi esposa y yo, Como es posible que existan mujeres que aguanten maltrato po… https://t.co/ANjEe0hjAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow is pretty and all but where is creek season 🏞 // sophiabringass @naualphaphi @ Flagstaff, Arizona https://t.co/6pau4jnZb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night attending allevenlondon event. Thanks for having us out❤️ . @kenpavessalon #allevenlondon #losangeles @… https://t.co/Ke956taBGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuchyB @jguaido @lafm Uno entiende ahora, la cobardia, pasividad de gobiernos y su diplomacia de franceses, Ingles… https://t.co/25u4mF2pl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidodell 55-47 Ducks - Final. Sucky game. Both teams played sloppy. We played sloppier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing that isn't bigger in Texas is the hours they sell booze.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: Ignacio 38, Dolores 14. No big surprises for the Bobcats as they have cruised into halftime. #copreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I try to watch the @OrlandoMagic they are lethargic and unenjoyable to watch. Flat, uninspired, no sense… https://t.co/eKi7H0tuKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @DeionSanders “30 for 30” &amp; still get chill bumps when #SidBream slides into home winning Game 7 of the NLCS. @Braves]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/10 Present! :) (at @PlanetFitness in Milwaukee, WI) https://t.co/HQQ9YVFKWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please someone tell this Congresswoman “AOC” to Shut Up! You make a fool of yourself every time you open your mouth… https://t.co/9rGw1S17Ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing that separates humans from most other organisms is the way we communicate and share]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachstrick20 @ChadSimmons_ @JLeeAURivals @benjaminwolk @Rivals I put a lot of work in it that day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship Sunday .. The Quiet before the storm @InsiderExposure #ieNationals https://t.co/Bu9IPgYUAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the train watching a man eat applesauce and then vomit it back up into his backpack is JUST a bonus for me on this fine Saturday :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing I wanna do when I come back to NY in June is jump in the great waters of Robby mosey field 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BringBackTheBuz @Walker_Harris3 That’s a hard take when you don’t know him personally or have an idea of his work ethic or anyone’s else’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus, a major wrinkle in the already sinister story --  https://t.co/zN3x6787vT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett This is @JussieSmollett this morning ... https://t.co/DIz7N7vvSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed doing this new set yesterday🔜 #portrait #vans https://t.co/1jFJMFUSEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the ink dries and a guy is on my team, great. To sit and fret over tweets and rumors? Nah. Sports are fun. Tha… https://t.co/3xxMUjtw1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you want to see/hear? More about #datingaround , music, costumes, designs, funny shit but not too vulgar, w… https://t.co/Nzs3KbbWeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeytuffsucks god we straight up drippin so hard but why am I 15 ft away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC The Jeep is crazy in the snow😂. Do you like 60 to 80mph and I damn Jeep in all that snow and won't slip up]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls trip day 1 🚩  just posted my first try-on haul on youtube with kulanikinis ! check out my story for the link… https://t.co/HiengdlAxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@praeclarum @VisualStudio @mjhutchinson Yeah I suspect this is the case. I would love to know what the factor might… https://t.co/KkmM065rsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Frightful treatment of Alex Jones and InfoWars was only start. Need more like FoxNews NewsMax etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmarrero2 @nataliauci16 Al final todos terminan así https://t.co/wxA55GIHZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesustarre Coye lo de fè ta peluo pa los Pemòn. Pero bueno...el tal "santo padre", es jefe de cartel pedòfilo. El… https://t.co/BCPFiRCaKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and #HappyFriday from my alternative music station. Watching @KHOU. @chitakhou @SallyKHOU11… https://t.co/BEVpTg7w9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck I feel bad for the people that dropped $350 plus to sit nosebleeds when the @MapleLeafs are losing 3-0 and the… https://t.co/0v2A0yTUcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News Alert:    The White House plans to use $8 billion in previously-appropriated funding to build 234 mo… https://t.co/153YZwRXlG]]></document></documents></author>