<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@adriennewhitma1 @SpeakerPelosi Let’s talk about the miss use of Presidential power then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parkerrholtt well I wasn’t going to see this until you made it show up on my timeline, so now all I have to say is… https://t.co/P2iQCs7Cd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chesse47 @seanspicer @GOPChairwoman @CPAC @GOP That will stop if you stop looking at the mirror.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @viramontes29 @Cmarquez_EES  staff and volunteers for another successful career day]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bitcheslovemurder, our true crime-themed sketch show, opens tonight, and I had to shout out my @MyFavMurder women.… https://t.co/0AAkdC4tCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had a wonderful day of internship while shadowing Principal Ken White at Highland Springs HS. Thank you… https://t.co/7WhOj1vZMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieFire I know!! Florida man is a self-perpetuating meme by the media, honestly.  I think this state likes bein… https://t.co/m3gTsfrslZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, some psychos really are meant to be together. You really have to be in the right headspace as someone. And a l… https://t.co/sl1Vj48AKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenTedCruz How about letting the true nature of the law, deal with the natural outcome? Instead of making deals, p… https://t.co/8TG41eI67x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I have to pull a restraining order in order for you dudes to leave me alone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiteMomba Like I said, anyone that sends unsolicited sexual content should be able to be prosecuted. I don’t give… https://t.co/HOCvRQZfnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LunchWithLea Episode 325 #podcast #webseries Subscribe to the podcast at https://t.co/gIhkefj5KA Watch the web-ser… https://t.co/UekG4VIw6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmund_Fraud @mcfunny @Plasticdoe @Rosewind2007 @badzoot7 @KimPaddockASD @djt10 @JuliaHadley15 @SueQuez @jkellyca… https://t.co/1plMNupKN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waterparks natalie desmarais and alysa parr for chicago please we’ll bring you snacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RustyFirmin @Queen_of_Gif @roqueandrolle @darty_sp I’m talking about Darry’s fabulous canines. I’m quite smitten b… https://t.co/Dw5Ms4XP9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a punishment for people who falsely accuse rape. Hands down no question]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter has some of the dumbest people and the most gullible. Y’all read a tweet from a teenager and assume it’s al… https://t.co/8jZhEUhADk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look guys: I don’t seat around the table. Giving speeches. Or pass useless legislations. I act when people are deaf… https://t.co/UeWf1sXNoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is true they should have used their whole hand not just their thumb!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaSeison You should follow @aaron_watson and discover his story! An amazing talent, father and husband!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preshave breakfast (@ Uncle Bill's Pancake and Dinner House in Saint Louis, MO w/ @patienc173835) https://t.co/hXLzB25imU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsonBraeden @SEMPA360 MDs (and DOs and NPs) are all welcome to this refresher!   Lord knows we all probably nee… https://t.co/iQUkdOJwFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, I know I’m not at NBA All Star Weekend but I’m also not average...🏁💁🏽‍♀️ #DAYTONA500 over all sporting events… https://t.co/fH143L5SnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came home to 3 cop cars, an ambulance, and a fire truck in front of my house. Apparently there was some sort of ker… https://t.co/XOrmTZmY8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinFree Mine is when I cannot retrieve an item off the counter without knocking various other items over/off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @JamesAALongman Key word used multiple times “hopefully” #smirks #smiles #noremorse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlfromhever She returned to England in disgrace over being the mistress of Francis 1 . He had some not very comp… https://t.co/MejKUWRh3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty Little Thing💞 #prettylittething #liketkit https://t.co/Q9TNY7pRnA https://t.co/nkIBtnM7jb @ Downtown Raleigh https://t.co/FFW2sDGCZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been talking about romance and why it should be in indie stores to booksellers all day and it is legit so much… https://t.co/HnZAatMgKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope I can get my vip ticket Tuesday for the Cincinnati show plz dont sell out. 🙏🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the night this album came out and I stayed up all night listening to it - can’t believe that was 2 years… https://t.co/EN9yOrBqDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo I legit love confusing people like am I single ? am I taken ? Am I talking to someone ? Am I not talking to anyone ? Who knows 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed! After all Uncle Gary is the kids favorite uncle! #AMillIonLittleThings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vogueandcode Uhg. I don’t even know what to say. So happy to hear that things are looking up. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crtaylor33 I think you are dead wrong and I feel you completely missed the point. I would ask that you think quiet… https://t.co/XpSsqmUSVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Election fraud isn’t solved by a “do over” its solved by disqualifying the guilty party and swearing in the other c… https://t.co/XXkkS7UAai]]></document><document><![CDATA[The white bitch came out in me today at home depot. Their customer service is garbage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely see the limits of Bernie’s politics—very weak on empire/settler colonialism; sees race, gender, sexual… https://t.co/5SaYfiZSp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christiella823 @EricJay2232 @ScottHech If Kalief were white he wouldn't have been arrested in the first place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerryPerry59 It was great speaking with you. :) have a wonderful night. Hope to talk soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Field Hockey Clinic Date Change For This Weekend Feb16 is now Feb23- See website below https://t.co/45boTEbAd3… https://t.co/V7OWiXmfAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/ZB74pAY7ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now , something positive before I metaphorically explode https://t.co/xTI2YjiE0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesternMustangs @WesternWHKY tough one team !  Let’s get after it in game 2.  #learnandmoveon #goStangs]]></document><document><![CDATA[best set of roommates youve ever seen @ me @ Rowan University https://t.co/5a0mTDyWVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPhiladelphia Um..you paid less taxes each paycheck therefore there’s less to return to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL that the guy I see in the break room every day who I thought was some random developer is actually the lead sin… https://t.co/ZnREN17YcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s frustrating how people will try to “talk” to married people, knowing damn well that they’re married and not caring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there’s a lot to say about having friends who just all silently know when we’re hurting and in quiet ways w… https://t.co/WPafh0axag]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get mad about things anymore, it’s so pointless to stress your self out about things you can’t control ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[kingmejessica requested our services @ work....we came thru and performed our Deluxe Car Wash on a few vehicles....… https://t.co/9NZJy1EHUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bandssssssss Ask if she’s into girls first, then based off that answer you will see what the vibe is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @RandyResist I hope someone will ask the GOP leadership this question. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cutterpinciaro I didn’t even get to eat flyer tonight so imagbe how I’m feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneilgerald_ @dumblondemusic Review it on your YouTube please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SingarRTO @SoldOutAnon @_Daniher @shadygrooove @intheMatrixxx It may be so. The point is it’s out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome educators to follow! #PLN  F @MissEduTech  O @MrSeanOlson  L @Sharonsobal1  L @clegleiter… https://t.co/ypNFM4lfVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber But in this case we don't know if Trump intervened, or asked the DOJ to intervene. After all, he hasn't… https://t.co/jmfEyRJ4RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grazie, Paulo, for reminding me this. ❤️ #neverwasteyourtime #ichosekindness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pato3232 #B2BMX showing how they use @Demandbase  @Engagio to get beyond AQL's (automated qualified leads). Gotta… https://t.co/Aw0GUEcDlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous Maggie- most amazing eyes and hair ever! She is so sweet and a pleasure to work with! hairqueen_maggie… https://t.co/hROTqjvx4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@failedmanman Someone at work asked why he was wearing women’s underwear lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd much rather spend my time laughing at the photos of Roger Stone than actually reading the articles about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 3.0 mph W. Barometer 29.640 in, Rising. Temperature 23.8 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 82%]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Weekend Pre-Birthday Winery Fun. #blindtasting #single #winetasting @ Monte De Oro Winery https://t.co/JvzbsT5grj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximetoubart , "Bonsoir" from San Diego, California, ou je profite de votre pur meunier. Cheers to @kandlwines fo… https://t.co/AQg6KNcJuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to do what I love daily. I get to feel supported and respected in ways that I was never at my 9 to 5. There i… https://t.co/PaUKdrq3GV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TakeCarePT @brookekeith25 Hahah i was going to tag @brookekeith25 but I saw she already favorited it😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exciting to have dedicated Members spending their valuable March Break at #OSSTF meetings.  Thanks @1977seg for… https://t.co/PwGQ1MVaku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freefall alcohol inks #art #abstract #abstractart #painting #contemporaryart #sea #seascape @ Denton, Texas https://t.co/WlRpOQSkDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy to be seeing more articles on privacy assessment of available data.  “We got ahead of it. That was our… https://t.co/miSDnmiY2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always too understanding... @ Mount Pleasant, Wisconsin https://t.co/vc6T7G2Kko]]></document><document><![CDATA[still remember the #FatTuesday when our vp David Geene got to @16thAvePS bright and early with his grill and made t… https://t.co/oXL14GHm4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dabablebass @VioletSilver @ContraPoints @AOC *present not prevent. Terribly placed typo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @NatashaBertrand He lies about everything thing else, so it stands to reason he could have been ly… https://t.co/e65qriRQU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAlvarado_WDS @melwill24 @SurrattCubs @cisdinsttech She’s amazing that little one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrugPolicyOrg @AOC Yeah just what we need more Pothead Socialists...idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUTH_MOOSE @ThePerezHilton And if tristen sexually abused her then KarJener’s need to stand beside her and defend her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMiller510 @dakasler Want change? Support @AsmKevinMcCarty and #AB392 to modernize California’s outdated use of… https://t.co/VFPlw9kpB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda suspicious that we’ve never seen Ally and Lady Gaga in the same room at the same time 🤔🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united Hey @united - I just got an email from the race saying you ARE offering discounts to runners. How do I get… https://t.co/jTCBJTVs53]]></document><document><![CDATA[#greatdayinthesalon  #reflectionshairsalon #hairsalon #hairbykimberly #loveourclients #lovemycareer #happiness @ Re… https://t.co/kFFGnPgLp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes me so upset how i really liked my job and my stupid fucking coworker is going to ruin everything for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#flashbackfriday to the start of the CrossFit open last year.  Not sure which facial expression I’ll have after 19.… https://t.co/jnyFqgCgi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casualcactii @melaniejmark @bcliberals @bcndp @MikeSmythNews @CKNW @j_mcelroy @CBCStephenQuinn @steeletalk And har… https://t.co/ICPyhKixQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnarmedOracle This is good, the effects of mercury are too well known but this could land]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new workshop comes your way! Maia Horvath will be facilitating a mixed media workshop @CreateART4GOOD ! Start wit… https://t.co/POzkvImFBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day @PollyRyonMS!  NBD! #PRMSROCKS https://t.co/l3Tu0vT9j1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@btsxvv @squishyboytae just wanting to fight venus always https://t.co/2oudh2aJz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Coloring book might be better!  Easy to visualize, short chapters, and crayons!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sneak peak of @FJDugan’s group act for the talent show! If you want to see the whole thing, you’ll have to come t… https://t.co/5pDra5zDJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success in business does not depend on what you say, what you hear, what you feel, what you see. It depends on what… https://t.co/Df3CAiCJWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you work in a refinery, if you work at a wellhead, if you work on a pipeline, if you help export climate change-… https://t.co/5enr6ThGHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out here doing the thing. Excited to be a part of the inaugural year of this festival and to be celebrating women c… https://t.co/dWviJy6c5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! Tell me about one way you are consciously trying to develop community where you live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drown drops this Friday and we're partying on Thursday to celebrate! Pull up to @DorchesterArtPr to see me and my b… https://t.co/bhzaFwZeHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[😆 can anyone relate?  . . . . . #weareallwingingit #perfectlyimperfect  #lovemylife💕  #quotestoliveby @ Utah https://t.co/AfJwakXai5]]></document><document><![CDATA[so b2k and the jonas brothers are reuniting...i’m honestly just waiting for big time rush to get in on this]]></document><document><![CDATA[BULLYING PLAYERS LMAO  When did I EVER tweet or message Kinkaid saying anything negative?  Not liking a player is n… https://t.co/ZK5c6q48UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jogging Capitol Hill with @backonmyfeet in 15-degree wind chills. BRRRRRR! https://t.co/MAIXB8UxP5 https://t.co/NKxmIVxNZ5]]></document></documents></author>