<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#venezuelaSos  #VenezuelaStarving  #SocialismKilling @IlhanMN loving @NicolasMaduro #Dictatorship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_ryan_boyle @henrykleeKTVU @belynda13 @AlamedaCountyDA @UCBerkeley @UCPD_Cal Agreed you enjoying the consequences of stupid decisions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Yep. I was a Republican and I've never been so ashamed of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leyrer @RedHat Sadly, no! I know it's hard with so many awesome candidates, but you can only vote for one in each… https://t.co/OtitZxJZp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Model Hypnotized by Dr. Lenny Moore. She thought her mind was too strong to get hypnotized. Everyone thinks t… https://t.co/iF6M9yYPfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucker was just released and I’m in love with it. ❤️😂 I’m re-living my childhood and couldn’t be happier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:25.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanGemmell @lakehuronloon I do think we ran into a buzz saw in 12 though. @followtheheater #driftisagift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timburchett Come on Tim! Everybody knows you have to pass it first to know what’s in it!! I pray you are part of t… https://t.co/wrw7iJS6sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Democrats are so desperate lmao. If they just focused on the election they could probably win]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems that people weren’t raised to clean up after themselves. Leaving your shit in the hallways and bathrooms for… https://t.co/Cm9BnE3HNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah bro “who you foolin” on gunna’s new tape the best track just off the beat alone SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wish you a very Happy and memorable Valentine’s Day! Share your Love and Happiness! Happy Valentine’s Day from t… https://t.co/btDuRcQYmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecity2 Steph's on a 5-year, $200 million deal. So, you're getting him at $100 million over the first five.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let the door hit you on the ass on the way out @AntDavis23 quitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OEL. 2-0. OEL has 2 goals &amp; 5 assists in past 5 games. That is OEL's 9th of the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yahboykfitchh I’ve heard it bad and incredible. Come summer time I’m gonna be rippin a couple on hertel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingCahill93 @YoungNBA Imagine Emitt Smith not celebrating passing Walter Payton because his team sucked lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smashed a shoulder workout in between hijinks with missjesyo. They say if you love what you do , then you’ll never… https://t.co/ZD0S6MsWbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Collins1971Russ @DrPaulGosar Omar should be impeached. It’s the only way to stop her cancer in the Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CochinoChuy After yesterday's result I am optimistic Inter can get a 1-0 win at the San Siro in the return leg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX29philly the idiot can’t even do a hot chocolate man on the street story , so inept, get rid of her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blind_Nycteris @NaomisLitPix I think you and i might have similar style.  Fortunately or unfortunately, word count… https://t.co/9Ovqfd7LhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_verynicegirl Since you’re calling him ‘dude’ he’s probably homeless  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should have defrauded the government and banks out of millions. He'd have been better off, lighter sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having Kyrie in fantasy is so frustrating. Dude misses like 2 games a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyBrogie  They've taken over my room! Getting ready for an epic Night at the Musuem tonight! #nevadacubpride https://t.co/QnAPO9MwC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one “when your guy friends say bring your homegirls... like you ARE MY homegirls” 😂😭 I related to that so much… https://t.co/TDsKL88ejm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @SenatorMenendez Who will pay the $273 million tag for extending the EITC to Puerto Rico? Your constitu… https://t.co/neWWC9gw8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist “Quality” journalism? I do think that true journalism has a code of ethics such as multiple sources;… https://t.co/iYrYuS4LOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se puede estar jugando con los sentimientos de los demas o eres o no eres]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC says what our whole generation is thinking when she says the #GreenNewDeal is a requirement for a presidential… https://t.co/XNhk4boYUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodGetslastWord @KatTheHammer1 @realDonaldTrump I had no idea how bad the media is or the deep state problem until… https://t.co/WCJK5bDXKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colossal  Mount Whitney, the tallest peak in the mainland United States, dwarfs a valley cactus hidden in the sea… https://t.co/KYqMAkh9ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolak22 @NCAACWS @Husker_Baseball You just mad NU beat y’all at your only good sport this year🤣 Calm down Jaysker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand18Austin I was there Sunday when it “snowed” you woulda been there to but you refused my invitation....AGAIN!!! 🤣🙊🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaiahMT_1996 @TommyTweedy @_Tyrant9 @EGP_Compton Malik v Tweedy rn looking spicy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Spike Lee finally get his diaper changed? #60YearOldCrybaby #BlacKkKlansman #Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[... and then come see us at @slucare vascular surgery to be evaluated for a transcarotid stent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone MUST explain great circles to these people.  The fuel required by that flight path would be insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews I feel sorry for the next generation of “adults” that are going to have to… https://t.co/vWlTshDxU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hecticbuthappy Last time I had Rumchatta was at your place in GF! #ilikewhereyourheadsat]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one of my fav events of the year: @Dromm25’s annual Elmhurst #LunarNewYear⁠ ⁠Celebration!  Only place on planet… https://t.co/liHXeihlqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyBadgerFC @RedThreadFarms @SmithAgConrad Ha! I didn't even notice anything different from any other day. Guess… https://t.co/TxiWkU7tn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yanelis_H The nerve of him!!  What’s this disrespectful fvckers address?  I will fix his ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excitables at #ETSD3 at Burbank, CA Find me! I'm wearing my green 2009 Summer @311 Tour shirt and sweater Row G https://t.co/bBBcfqZAoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see all my old JGR buddies and DH win that one for JD. Too cool🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Lord replied, “Don’t say, ‘I’m too young,’ for you must go wherever I send you and say whatever I tell you. An… https://t.co/9V9l7BziP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F_EstradaBelli @ArchaeologyCarl Awesome. I’ll be in Tikal next week. My inner Indiana Jones is geeking out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@RosiannaRojas will be in touch” was in a real email from yesterday, and I gotta day, I’m pretty dang excited about it. 📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theycravek @KBEVSSS #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19 #tsu_rys19… https://t.co/eFgXzB0K9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 7 people have been living here consistently for nearly a year. At times, they’ve been utilizing resources at the Community Kitchen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the only way to grow.. — #lifestyle #selfcare #life #mental #friday #positivevibes #choices @ Phoenix, Ariz… https://t.co/CKAMvuJNo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of the like three and a half movies I saw this year, Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse was the best. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[This entire thing that Mueller has finished seems very fishy to me. We have not heard a word from Trump, Barr or Mu… https://t.co/FRB7RfVW4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had to explain what “Stop the Presses” meant to my kid and he looked at me like I was from the Neolithic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly!  Evil 🍒 picking push-poll numbers.  F! You! @chucktodd you evil corporate oligarch fellating ho  F! You!… https://t.co/N8KgeWOQTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris__martin of course, i wouldn't push such trivia on someone who was beginning... ^_^;]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we are going to need all us on the front line. Thank you Sequencer  Together we WILL bring this Nation back to… https://t.co/Q7cRzylD12]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had this on a loop for the past 5 minutes and I haven’t stopped laughing the entire time 💀😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the only 2k I’ve played where I wasn’t able to play a 2nd season in Mycareer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judah47 I'm hoping, Judah, that Boston and its environs sees at least ONE all snow event before astronomical Sprin… https://t.co/pSuTu7XjZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am incredibly honored to be a Truman Finalist. I am looking forward to my interview and to meeting fellow Finalis… https://t.co/8wLuZnRpDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lara Logan Mike Drop Clip (Media Bias) https://t.co/Tdko8W0612 via @YouTube “the left doesn’t control the media? Yo… https://t.co/sjVClyLquC]]></document><document><![CDATA[she out her acting like her man  choosing to cheat multiple times didn’t have anything to do with this 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT Good Morning… https://t.co/Q65jJiZoWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh if I don’t get up and make this coffee soon, I ain’t gone make it today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink was definitely having a moment on the red 👠carpet at the #Oscars last night.  This James Nares is  on point an… https://t.co/wGS8WNnzUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Run me ragged but I don’t fret bc there ain’t been one to slow me Down yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sing to me. Laugh with me. Cuddle with me. Long conversate with me. Do anything with me. Cause I’m bored not doing anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you do? C- there is no proof of the mind scape except for that people snap.  People believe in many thin… https://t.co/ttEzIV3I0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly what I was thinking he know that lil white boy scared for life lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[America Its Past Time For We The People To Stand Up And Fight Like HELL To SAVE OUR AMERICA  LETS ROLL👈👈👈👈👈👈👈👈 🇺🇸🇺🇸… https://t.co/gUsVmMP0vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently tried out #FinalFantasyXIV. Everyone meet Brotein Powder. The prettiest bro there ever was. https://t.co/Ez5dGruOvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaGhete Maybe! Anyway, maybe it’s a natural experiment worth trying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidduchovny your transition a few years back from actor to musician (saw you in Asbury) to novelist inspired me… https://t.co/XbH4kTx5Wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continue the support🌎 Appreciate everyone that has been listening🙏🏼 If you haven’t heard, please do so🔥more coming… https://t.co/kaCdyirPqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen just get the bad games out now. But half the Metro is in the rear view mirror......wake up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity No politician will be arrested for corruption. The other fear if one i… https://t.co/2pX8eEYQRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to thank twitter for putting me on to Greys Anatomy cuz i am hooked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatCounterPunch &gt;&gt;&gt;That Reminds me of this #Rockefeller Quote. #HumanCommodities #Serfs #VeriChip https://t.co/7QlvwS8TBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#afirmación #afirmacionpositiva #afirmaciondeldia #salud #amor #riqueza @ Doral, Florida https://t.co/OmRFe74yJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanfielder do you make the plans first, or is it all just justification?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhg76 @Claylude @NombreEsJustin It's not aggressive. It's progressive. Don't you see the peace that Clay has brought?]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida nos está dando una señal a hanoi y a mi así que ya empezare a escucharla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at @dolbytheatre for @LiveKellyRyan and their #afteroscar show! #lightcarriers  @PRanganathan @ Dolby Theatre https://t.co/Kr1HYELyRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also cool if you PERSONALLY edit your photos, but without consent it’s not, in my opinion, legitimate]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Technologies That Are Reshaping Customer Experience https://t.co/QJq0i8QdxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s pump-up music at swim meet is “Stairway to Heaven.” Wait. What?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSchuiling I said the same thing when he did it too https://t.co/zvZ0Iyr8mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Paper ballots are important, but we must also insist on paper records of vote total reports from each… https://t.co/3wfPG39Vvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Condecorar a "militares" que impidieron la entrada de la ayuda humanitaria, es por decir lo menos, una accion aberr… https://t.co/TASEgKCBe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great News out of Quebec!! Questerre $Qec.ca has gone ahead to acquire it's partner, expect stock to jump 20%   Co… https://t.co/jwYdvl0iTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank u Connor. Appreciate u and ur family so much. Some of our biggest supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry for my snap y’all I’m bored n speaking nonsense you dumb if you think I’m serous]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if no clear winner emerges from all this, a two-man sack race will be held on consecutive Sundays until a champ… https://t.co/nTSYjTVeFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[In two and a half hours, check out @CBCCavendish. I channel my inner Capra. https://t.co/7DxVK2bxgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Annette!  Have a great week! . . . . #hairbyangel #godisgood #aloxxihair #davines https://t.co/MCPoRWEmaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blame it on a government mindset that renders us guilty before we’ve even been charged, let alone convicted, of any… https://t.co/jkFbBX8qXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaaneegm No hagas caso de comentarios negativos, es tu fe a Dios y tu confianza en ti misma. Con fuerza]]></document></documents></author>