<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#IdBeOnTrialFor some outstanding parking tickets from the 1970s.  ( This was before reciprocity between Boston and… https://t.co/pPLKNPkfCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey They already got it but much like Venezuela it didn't get past corrupt government.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin Another in a string of 'best' judges to match trump's incompetent 'best' people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so embarrassed, this is America how can we continue to support this stupidity and write her a check?! https://t.co/GyA6dsuqn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Alva Johnson is stupid enough to work for tRump she deserves the crap pay and the other disgusting elements of t… https://t.co/LYI1Oci4iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @CarnivalPLC,  Roses are red, Violets are blue, You can stop burning heavy fuel oil, We believe in you!… https://t.co/IKJLnSfoUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deborista Acho que tem a tese no Instituto de Artes. Te passo a referência depois]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss helping with class valentines (and by helping I guess I mean watching them intentionally choose who should r… https://t.co/x6x7QEj4iJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a surprise!!! 😆 Trump’s Nomination for the Nobel Peace Prize Was Apparently Forged. Twice. https://t.co/RBP766wV9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anastasjoy @janbllvll_jan @myrahenry24 @lcollinsp @SenSanders @AOC *percent of votes. Never showed up to VOTE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevo_Bevo I love that you officially quoted yourself as saying this 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClientBrittneyP @brittneybad_azz is getting in some personal training live with #GloryFitness #gotthatgodjuice pra… https://t.co/B4O2SVwV0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper just gave the best acting job of his career, looking like he was interested in the story some woman… https://t.co/d7md3mpVGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gambotage Here is something that may give you an Ah-Ha moment yourself.  People never asked me why I thought the e… https://t.co/gZJlrIfHKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA We should also legalize magic mushrooms which not only grow naturally all throughout the US but are… https://t.co/cDyDGMccyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO:  mY NAME is Luchita....I'm a warrior in the army of the Lord! https://t.co/aTleqFMUPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate when my mom thinks I’m hiding something from her just cuz I’m smiling at my phone sis I’m looking at cute memes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying Kylie Jenner is a self made billionaire is a bit of a stretch don’t ya think????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigguyinabowtie We missed you at NearpodTransform this year!  #NearpodChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blessedmamita I'm not exactly sure, but I feel like it's rained at least a llittle every day for a week and a half. It's crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get insight into how #ATX prepares for influx of 200k - 400k people in one week for #SXSW19 and other events.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be the embrace that keeps you warm  For you're the sun that breaks the storm  I'll be alright and I'll sleep s… https://t.co/ncryyZrNgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyvonBora @DanComp02107462 And now she is in the arms of https://t.co/oiKukRtWh9 from all pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NIEUW: want behind every strong woman is a bunch of other strong women. 💪👯‍♀️  https://t.co/bOLr0n2xHM  #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me in supporting deployed service members by wearing red every Friday. #RedFriday @fox6now @fox6wakeup https://t.co/bx8JXD6xfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting to me how many different versions of the same story you can hear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peeperpea29 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @karenslinn43 @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @ClockworkHamma @JackConnie @ann4252… https://t.co/fvvgOwNzT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when Alex sends me cute shit on the nights I work. Cause I’ll be so busy that by the time I can actually sit d… https://t.co/uqYPK7Hpdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I don’t got the flu yo. So weak, so tired, nauseated, and no appetite 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great group!! Spinning for the Women's Care Center!! Thanks to @jimmiebell and @stasi_bogtrout for leading t… https://t.co/2VCKlA6R17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all talking real crazy bout my Bills man all I gotta say... keep that same energy. 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storm, an American Pit Bull Terrier in DC, needs a home now! See her on https://t.co/JVtEQUPiwS https://t.co/lpNciovmYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[People like this annoy me so bad, but I’m not gonna lie and say I didn’t laugh 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiscottiNicole @ThirstyBeesNY @fablefy @thewrightleader @Greg_Moffitt @KFelicello @Mind_on_ASaP @heARTISTatWORK… https://t.co/zz5XlGsMo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you only like that band bc the members are hot”   “you only watch that show bc the actors are hot”   FUCK OFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[East High’s Food Service Tream won a National Hero Breakfast Award for their efforts to ensure our Blue Aces are fu… https://t.co/46BN9sUbn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunDMR @SashaAnnSimons Right? The lil kid equivalent of that person in the office who wanna microwave their leftov… https://t.co/jLlFuIaied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@para82nd_1 @realeftypickit @RickyCa69392149 @Persistence2017 @DexCMacB1 @yeahunoeme @Narc_Problems… https://t.co/NH1FmmiF4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of great perspectives to ponder in this 2019 Immersive Design Industry Annual Report]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though Noelle is only a month old I personally don't talk to her like a baby, and it drives me crazy when peop… https://t.co/n1nB6hM3W5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird Not in there own house. Isn't  that interesting, they want them every where else, just not in there own house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want some flea market corn in a cup brah with extra everything. Fak you mean sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need to be up in 4 hours to head home and all i’m thinking about are donuts and coffee from wawa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @mixedlinguist for clarity here. I should've said English's phonics (letter-sound correspondences), not phon… https://t.co/EoVLRGN8gS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh! IM SORRY!! I guess you forgot how to mind your own fucking business.  🖕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorge Ramos now speaking with Univision Networks about the #Venezuela regime incident.  He's at Caracas hotel talki… https://t.co/gwXqPJLnXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[As scary as it is with graduation right around the corner, I’m R E A D Y for a new chapter 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to top it off I did a peel off face mask last night which some got stuck in my hair so it’s a really bad hair day for me 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shante, you stay...as @Rupaul might say. #BillyPotter #GlennClose So much fabulous on display. #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[had pretty horrible news at the beginning of the week and i’ve tried to shut out any feelings i have towards it bec… https://t.co/JsuKWW1qfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gary_wassner i would love to hear/see more comments from you, have you ever think about have a Podcast or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The private mansion studio where women only dance every day wearing whatever we want is a dream come true for a fem… https://t.co/XqVnPxqQ1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner time!!! @putacalenturaBD  @Samantha19xxx https://t.co/oJoUDiw6dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby brother is 2 and he always uses my mom’s phone to go on Instagram and watch workout videos because it shows… https://t.co/7eCh9OVpxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger either he's too stupid; he actually could care less; or he's taking orders - I used to assume from P… https://t.co/lfOgD4HNmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve already taken your bra off and someone asks you to go out, and it’s... https://t.co/laim3Enro3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr So where are we with the gun laws in New York.  I don’t own one but I also don’t want a socialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maiabisceglia @VibeTickets @SM_Army1998 @LukeMassie @FairTicketing @shawnwwreports @BTSRadioUK @BTS__Europe… https://t.co/I4M02xg6jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlawlessBob @GldnHarvest #soybean “quick glance” at planting date results at the Agronomy in Action plot in Clinto… https://t.co/iLLJW7a70I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is pouting because we won't give him a chicken. https://t.co/zm9U5jCUiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rafting away.  20120516. . . . . . . .  #evergreentrees #riverrun #olympicnationalpark #hohrainforest #hohriver… https://t.co/n057TAhlEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to listen to @Sonyareneepoet speak at @MadisonCollege 🙌🏽💖📚 https://t.co/VTsPgym7Xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @IlhanMN She says shiny about Jews and you give the bigot a pass #hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[All ready for the Little Rock 10K. I love the costumes others are wearing @ Little Rock Marriott https://t.co/fwyocXKtBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[:: Goddesses Energy :: When you know you know 😝 :: #aliciaadanna #geminihairdiary #fauxlocs #purplehair… https://t.co/1D0YiBibGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing room only to hear about holistically managing water infrastructure and resiliency.   #NLCCCC #RebuildWithUs https://t.co/q7SAXoGSnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning y’all, time for a quick ass kicking in the gym (at @UltaBeauty in King of Prussia, PA) https://t.co/vklynP78Bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Woman's day to all my #SPNFamily !! @_KingBooks_ @FangasmSPN @kimrhodes4real @RuthieConnell… https://t.co/FSQ8nps5bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so it begins...I can feel the gray hairs starting to multiply. How the heck am I old enough to have a teenage d… https://t.co/3geTAZjX20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conniejopl @GRadioMarketing @rmiestilodevida @LARSAVISIONTV @Armando_Alcala @MikaRodriguez07 @osunahaydee… https://t.co/Rp9YUZfTcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdenheimer What about getting your period before a big night out 🤦🏻‍♀️🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Romans58 @gatewaypundit About a year ago, was tweeting about how the young black men are finding crates of guns,… https://t.co/ugDWeidCNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stadium Series at the Lincoln @ Lincoln Financial Field https://t.co/9dwhxSMZVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNAM_MX @CanalOnceTV @IPN_MX Muchísimas felicidades que haya muchos canales 11 😍🌹❤️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th graders have some interesting ideas for improving instruction and engagement. https://t.co/JTpmAPO0Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm interesting piece now they are laying ground foundation for their criminalities in order to evade justice from… https://t.co/67XjYzfyXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get this ball rolling! Glad to see Facebook might just be taking a stand for #vaccines #Science after all. Ea… https://t.co/ohRFt5HwUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspf42 @AdamParkhomenko @tweetzydeetzy He was absolutely right about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback Sunday! Day off last week with these beauties. :) #theoldglobe #lajollacove #sealsandpelicans #nofilter @… https://t.co/gJjzTYQHPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabryluce @Jose93571656 @Viviane6677 @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @janaplauen… https://t.co/5unKU1Xlto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tarte Shape Tape is cool but NOTHING beats Estée Lauder Double Wear https://t.co/jg25nwABcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RutgersCancer  Thank you for your leadership re NJ’s #1 cancer killer, lung cancer. #LCSM @ScreenNJ… https://t.co/01pQ3JL2Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so drained. Like school is draining the life tf out of me and it’s literally just a class that’s stressing me]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last stop is the most important one! Congrats to this class of #CircleOfHonor @UPS service providers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are not Native American, you are illegal and if you have no respect for Native American values you should go… https://t.co/e4R0mHYFWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[...do I have to explain how to care for someone you trust...make em feel like there's no one else around, pick em u… https://t.co/dLomATAZxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[call me stupid call me sad, you’re the best i’ve ever had, you’re the worst i’ve ever had, and that keeps fucking w… https://t.co/gmxTdmd4Gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbMcQuade @FrankFigliuzzi1 @JoyceWhiteVance @JillWineBanks @matthewamiller Save us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OaklandEA Force Elementary School sends our support!  Stay strong! #OaklandTeachersStrike #Unite4OaklandKids… https://t.co/ObTl5ss6YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZuluBall2019 @ New Orleans Ernest N. Morial Convention Center https://t.co/JgYbqGH1jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[To mullet or not to mullet seems to be the question. I think im projecting a stereotype. Now I remember why it's be… https://t.co/276MkvTBJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreasavage @Allison_Tolman @truTV That episode was hilarious holy ship Tolman &amp; Savage beasts !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to pack for spring break but uhhhhhhh I haven’t done laundry in almost 2 weeks so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyphy_republic Years of posting on other social media caused problems?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyriesi Crawl back there real quick and fall. Fall real heard in front of the oldest building. Get that free tuition]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuirkyJERK With my luck the whole thing would fall off in the middle of the night smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saluting the strong leadership - both male and female - who champion and support women every day of the year!… https://t.co/5C9WdEtpuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinelogan my mom did the opposite of this over break and poured that pre-made chai that comes in a box into our l… https://t.co/33pchWLzNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBD Facial Mask... Take advantage of the Anti-inflammatory Benefits of My NEW CBD INFUSED Facial Masks. CBD is Exce… https://t.co/5opn1WfkUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash They are jealous she is the prettiest First Lady we ever had !!! And one of the smartest !]]></document></documents></author>