<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LindseyPelas Careful she only cares about herself and what people can get her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marielle’s widow Mônica Benicio marched as part of the samba parade in Rio. Pretty amazing tribute and symbol of re… https://t.co/kJoXBZUhRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Space Age Bachlor Pad by @AOH_Beer at @seventhsonbrew — https://t.co/TraqQy074Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alaidi Yea all about the Benjamins. Let’s see if data can walk the talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temporary reduction but it buys back *a bit* of time that we had already fumbled away.   Let’s. Get. Planting.   (E… https://t.co/dMNMjmIFjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in love with my best friend and we do best friend shit, no fights over here 💯🙅🏻‍♂️it’s all love over here ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gregorymaguire #thewickedyears  I'm rereading the fourth I'm this series. I love falling in love with a series all… https://t.co/g3VUiivciX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasio27 @gregolsen88 @BarackObama @dukebasketball @GoHeels @ZionW32 @Panthers @UNC_Basketball Why dont you learn t… https://t.co/lBhMgAy63W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just absolutely love watching the left eating themselves alive. What a time to be alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shpearo @SHowrigan I understand how that works and everything and agree that it’s shitty but at the same time do h… https://t.co/A20pIPUupm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood this morning, feel like dancing the night away #Mood @terannhilow can I have this dance.... https://t.co/1XiQpLBDYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy bad headaches are driving me insane, nothing touches them really and they come out of nowhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samesfandiari Right. Giants are still on city owned land with Oracle Park. Warriors bought the land. That’s crazy, especially in this area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martinez likely an injury sub.  Otherwise subbing out your 10 down a goal is not good.  Liked the Tommy Mac additio… https://t.co/0Z2zd6Wu67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continuar con el Kingdom Hearts 3 o calar el Saint Seiya Soldiers Soul?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheIdahoPress Just leave them alone. They are not substantially hurting anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianneDMR Having a virtual caucus is a hacker's dream! How do they plan to prevent bots, geo-spoofing, intrusion, etc.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you forgot (or are too young to have witnessed) how AMAZING Larry Legend was...This is fantastic!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heart of a Lion, a song by A-ron, King Tru on Spotify https://t.co/f5kNzfAcrT @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Beli… https://t.co/Pk1q24IER7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been trying to get some more knowledge about #Buddhism for a variety of reasons but mainly because I think… https://t.co/45hHOUNZSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shirastweet @mclynd @DrJDrooghaag @sarbjeetjohal @KirkDBorne @ChuckDBrooks @AudreyDesisto @guzmand @TheRudinGroup… https://t.co/hSLzo6PWZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was hysterical how awkward @ncthompson10 looked on the Jumbotron with @Marlins_Man 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to speak to Deebo and share some of his story. He’s going to make whoever selects him look like a… https://t.co/sE5OyR8prw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our liaison has been on the phone with your representatives for FIVE hours, and have been shifted around from fligh… https://t.co/3HspyvGTZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabbiDGerber I hope the first tool that gets deployed on the moon is Iron Dome, Bc you _know_ someone gonna fire a rocket at it. 🙄🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My $0.02: The new Olympic Q system not only shows a disconnect among athletic officials, fans and athletes but also… https://t.co/mxuLdFUIn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimReboulet @HSEStrength @HSERoyalsBase Would’ve been 360 with some of the treatment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Royersford, PA? https://t.co/i2jamaxp96 #Engineering]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:33 left, Deering leads Bangor 28-16. Bangor just cannot hit a shot. #VarsityMaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao this was me this morning about to push ppl off the treadmill like calm down you showing out too early!!!  #gym… https://t.co/gBpHu4ztHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen And when Trump tries to revoke press briefing privileges from CNN news correspondents from asking questi… https://t.co/doAfzZPBTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingfishertimes Not to mention the Piedmont girls advancexto the semi finals.  Yes 1/3 of Piedmont is in Kingfisher county!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just let us have our parade now @NHL no need to risk any other players in the league getting injured]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrjaxtaylor @FlaPanthers @NHL @spittinchiclets @NHLNetwork @SiriusXMNHL You should see the Marlins games, even worse!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Remember when you boycotted a Fox News debate because you didn't like Megyn Kelly, the mo… https://t.co/sUA33prpL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hands were shaking but I was loud and proud of my mentee, tyler.terrell, on being recognized as a 2019 Jim Rhati… https://t.co/LPVHfRBRiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[sit at the #throne of #Christ  come before the #Father the #Son, the #Spirit, sit at the throne of Christ at our… https://t.co/lpJ4DzXWL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to work hard, so he can play harder! My biggest motivation is my son Renton. He pushes me to be a better fat… https://t.co/0ZdwGl9IPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLSeattle_ @NHLtoSeattle @cotsonika @mogulboy you're one of the best people I know. Love you bro!!! https://t.co/I0ZLQAkUop]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I knew I was going to live this long I'd have taken better care of myself. #fifty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWaxman @FaustMN @ScottSandalow Warm pineapple is one of the world’s most unappetizing things]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔊🔊🔊 ITS NOT THE GOVERNMENT'S JOB TO END RACISM........  It is your personal responsibility to see your Sin and Repe… https://t.co/5k0VCHpmKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IconicDevotee @NamelessGuy96 What words exactly was said that makes him racist? Those are serious accusations with limit information]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEN U EAT THE HOTTEST HOT SAUCE 🤣🤣 Check it out on HOT ASS WINGS https://t.co/tWOaVOVVwJ https://t.co/ydE9jgvYBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilithLiberated The problem is that even in a civil suit, the odds of a white person winning are still better than… https://t.co/bxqQvF7s1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hate U Give Little Infants Fucks #2Pac #ThugLife #OnParleJamaisDesConsequences]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at Game Day #2: the @OHLIceDogs vs @ErieOtters 7pm  @yourtvniagara . Join @EdBurkholder @agalloway31 and myself for the call !]]></document><document><![CDATA[An estimated 42 percent of Portland, Oregon, residents are religiously unaffiliated. https://t.co/KwbnVvCLpG # via @HuffPostPol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy President’s Day! #PresidentsDay @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/1TsArLp7yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeDelMoro @ScottMStedman On a scale of 1-10 how much trouble is Rudy Giuliani in when it comes to the latest rev… https://t.co/lbPbtQsqRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Browsing dating profiles in Ohio:    -She’s cute -Nicely written summary  Huh, maybe I’ll contact her….  scrolls so… https://t.co/FcNtmaF4Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally agree &amp; nobody played harder than your HSquad teams! Always enjoyed watching your teams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two WI Republicans -- Jim Sensenbrenner and Mike Gallagher -- cited separation of powers and concerns about ceding… https://t.co/Q1KP2mZnDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[WITH GOD ALL THINGS ARE POSSIBLE!  ENJOY YOUR DAY! 🙏🏿😉😄🙏🏿 @ Columbia, South Carolina https://t.co/8fqU00jZEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this my psycho ex....?? @M_Sweeney_ @GabeTate I’m really concerned 😂😂😂 I’ve had similar messages before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mafhoney @MNYorkie @OK_Dumbass Cant refute that. I know better but still didn't follow my own advice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[21’ TRY TIME!!! RODRIGO SILVA makes it over the line after a series of phases from a line-out at the 5m!   #GLENvAER | 05-14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else got Alarms set for all hours of the day? I can’t be the only one https://t.co/J65APJ5SDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_courtneym_ oh okay. i just asked because i’ve been to windsor a few times. it’s pretty cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gopher1110 edina target (frozen desserts section- not cookie dough section)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyn1cole Great for when it's another Saturday Night and you ain't got nobody?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigirules7 Used to be Capn Crunch, but now days I like Honey Nut Cheerios https://t.co/TvmaEn1tyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyB08 @JayJaylavaugh @ManoMagic101 @BleacherReport But hey if you a patriots fan like me i cant say anything bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad that #FirstResponders have to put their lives at risk just doing their jobs on a simple MVA. Please folks… https://t.co/YhDsbEI8M6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamwhoismoses ESPN is giving him the same hype they have Johnny Manziel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTammara @jemelehill True but, she's still in the game and now in addition to getting paid more, she's also produc… https://t.co/llh27hiVtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yung_cp3_ Nah you said +15 I thought you was doing an alternate line . I ain’t touching that bad boy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The retreat went so well!!! Thank you all for the prayers, God is so good !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s something that doesn’t get much attention. Illegal aliens call #USBP when they need help!  Feb 17: 2 illegal… https://t.co/Ur98HuTjq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/ this reminds me of my consulting work in prison with treatment specialists. Often the view of prison staff, incl… https://t.co/JZVIbHsOJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Thomas Keller Thinks Farm-to-Table Is Absurd https://t.co/lS9nbK7oa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found some new rocks. It was a good day.   • • • • #exploreeverything #ridered #honda #motorcycles #xl350 #vintage… https://t.co/JZuUNsMXHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But seek ye first the kingdom of God, and his righteousness; and all these things shall be added unto you.” Matthew 6:33 KJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump I wonder what your connection is with the Epstein case is. Is THIS why you're not firing #Acosta?… https://t.co/jFpLjmOoef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the suit, they are so gentle with him and yet... Passive agressive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wormsloe Historic Site  #Savannah Savannahga #Georgia #landscape #Nikon #lightroom #architecture #photographer… https://t.co/7ObEIydISJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the opportunity to partner with West Ottawa Schools this week and challenge their students to respond “above… https://t.co/bNSdKn7Vgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiet121 Lol Yes, but “Weekend at Bernie’s” should have won in 1989, I’m still terribly upset with the dipshits a… https://t.co/5h8h0DYW19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from Long Beach Comic Expo 2019, not the gymnastics or truck and Jeep show. @LBComicExpo #exhaustion @ Long… https://t.co/ZvjoCGkwoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather Nauert Withdraws: ‘Past Two Months…Grueling for My Family’ https://t.co/35mNlAHmnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s not been a player that’s left his mark on this season like James Harden.  He’s having one of those years wh… https://t.co/PKHa8WfOHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baltimoresun How we as a society allow our schools to fail like this is our biggest downfall. We wonder why drugs… https://t.co/p76ffsxTxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing more annoying than everyone posting the same concert on snapchat, enjoy it, stop putting 6 full minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Los Angeles International Airport - @flylaxairport in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/tvPwePPcNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍺 (@ Yeti Corporate Headquarters in Austin, TX) https://t.co/PbGIPLKBVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The way of fools seems right to them, but the wise listen to advice.” Proverbs 12:15 NIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why haven’t you bought your tickets 🎫 yet? @FLBlogCon going on it’s 9th year! #flblogcon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Ed you have become unreadable. We get it! You hate the President. We get it Ed, go do s… https://t.co/ON50kvKCuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[taking a look back on my state win today, i just want to thank everyone who has pushed to make me a better person a… https://t.co/QsVrETVxFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brewers I love his “uummmmm”. He does that all the time. My manager!! Proud to say it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizKilmerWPXI @WPXI Why do you need a script, you need to wing it and see what happens!!!!!!! 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The  always-direct .@dynarski explains dynamics behind “for profit” institutions of higher education. Policy makers… https://t.co/Gtwk6vXK5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMcCale @ChristophersKC @Dantej21 Except it’s not. Its now widely accepted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanDorman Agree, as I said I know it's a thankless and tough job. But it keeps happening, this one is more forgivable tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin enjoy your day. And I give you Angelica as a birthday present. I just don't want to marry her no more khe… https://t.co/sZc0VIYTPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicious696 @DivisionAcademy @ALIDIka1000 @AgentTED78 @obiadekanobi @ElitesGaming1 @TheDivisionGame I want to know, gift or purchase?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laura_baich @wtiu @InsideIU @IUBloomington The local @PBS station is celebrating 50 years. @wtiu yay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch? I’m directing that bih forsureeeeee, so many layers, so many stories, so so much heartbreak 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having your DP hit at midnight has to be one of the most satisfying feelings ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️ Road Construction Alert: @GoMiamiDade will be working on a road improvement project located at the intersection… https://t.co/MbXGlijyHP]]></document></documents></author>