<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ErinCBS12 @SavanahResnik @CBS12 I’m tired and stressed just watching this! You go girl😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gf: so they she said- Me: tell that whore you're talking to I said hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photographyfromsue thankful for a beautiful nonrainy day yesterday so we could go listen to @DavidKatilius with… https://t.co/uh0aZ9Tpfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringin’ this back cause FFXV feelings are surging back to me!⭐️Dino Ghiranze x Ignis Scientia 💖fav rarepair ❤️Like… https://t.co/Lk9UWMh6el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmnlaw @McGovernBrian Won’t be long before the rest of Navesink River does the same. #MassExodus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrea_Brook_LO @racheljcox87 @KateMcNeill6 @jeansciqueen @CTSKeeley Does a quote from my science textbook count as evidence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Tips For Your First Year in a Long Distance Relationship  https://t.co/OFzIgv9csw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listed at $289,700 - 7897 Country Lake, Bartlett, TN!  Brand New quality construction! 3bdr/3bth - Beautiful s… https://t.co/51w62OW9Sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s bringing this beauty home today? #DAYTONA500 https://t.co/iggPb05u3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We can never know what to want, because, living only one life, we can neither compare it with our previous lives n… https://t.co/cfTJ58xdSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #Voted for @JumaaneWilliams for NYC #PublicAdvocate polls are open til 9pm! #LetsGo #Itstime https://t.co/BrKk5aF8EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcsa444 @cocando @jguaido Amnistía con bono extra para el primero que suelte el Yoyo sobre la muerte de Chavez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do managers/bosses not have the capacity to just drop stuff?   Like if something’s already been discussed can y… https://t.co/7RmVlxJRYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Well hell tRump is a rich white male....he can F’n do anything #tRumpIsAPig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrelandALLIE2 @social_stars @miragoto @CodyPurvisMusic @iamdelaneygrant @EmilyFaithMusic @farewellamusic… https://t.co/um6QE3PfPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MUSC Children's Care in North Charleston, SC https://t.co/5aq21xcQVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart can’t handle the Luke Perry news. Death from strokes hit me so incredibly hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Lesson No. 1 from Brother Vlad - don't hesitate to show the world, especially your o… https://t.co/QTdugV0wjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[(1/3) @brandy1960: RT @isnardobravo: El colega @jorgeramosnews probó en (2/3) por lo menos dos horas lo que ha agua… https://t.co/SuDAaNh6xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 Sounds like a good list. I think I would like seeing a duo of those people too. Has Beto said for sure h… https://t.co/pnfezuQHek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanneBlasberg I begged a guy to put his phone in airplane mode because he was texting while we were taking off an… https://t.co/nzrwOoL3OE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@opinionatedwino Hahahahaha no idea over here. I can definitely tell you what old white people are listening too though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phant00m_ the ones that done found me so far, aint shit so ... but ima take your advice friend 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacquiw9 @WKCDOGS Thanks Jacqui! Belle is full of mischief at times, but one of the easiest dogs I’ve ever owned. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @politico OMG I want to tape that Cavern of a mouth on that yapping bitch every time I see her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sleeping peacefully for once then responsibilities woke me up. Now I’m mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shutupshealea This an ungrateful thing and likely contributes to why folk with anxiety don't do big events often.… https://t.co/AnhimKp7ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron fans, a player getting bailed out by his teammate isn’t a shot at his career. Derek Fisher made a game winne… https://t.co/v8uvKZRLvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneaking around, disrespecting the institution of Divorce. 😂 #thekids #SplittingUpTogether]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquelineCord Wrestling UNI always felt like a Ballard vs. Denver-Tripoli dual. Lots of Iowa rivalry especially w… https://t.co/Aeu0arO2aB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see no other explanation. I have long wondered how this nation could elect such fundamentally different men. Obam… https://t.co/2PhQxWyksM]]></document><document><![CDATA[cannot wait to be home from work 14 hours from now just so I can stay up late &amp; sleep iiiiinnn even later]]></document><document><![CDATA[First impressions are huge for me... hard to come back from a bad one with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you live in Madison and you’re not at @HighNoonMadison for @trapperschoepp tonight I don’t even know what you’re doing with your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH MY GOSH #RamiMalek #memes! 😆🤣😂 A video of Rami Malek listing his fave things is getting the meme treatment    https://t.co/KmQYFrfQ5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really try to love someone until it cuts you all up inside and you still won't know how to let go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody said only ugly ppl be up at this time 🤣🤣🤣 let me go to sleep 🥴😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDoctorMike could you please do a video about your experience in the Level 1 Trauma Centers you've worked in? O… https://t.co/z9WAaQEXtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDelMarKid @NotCloudyAllDay Happy Birthday. May you have many more years filled with health, love, lots of peppe… https://t.co/ojslEjM8C8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theupstairskid Thank you 😭 need a new one since my hair is red now though 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Garlic Noodles with Prawns will put you in that "FRIDAY FEELIN'" mode immediately 😎 . TAG everyone 👇👇👇 . Hue… https://t.co/z6XJXjkQj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really think I need a job somewhere on the coast... https://t.co/Pt68MVCay7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Carp777 @Corp125Vet @SueCole40712634 @12231026 @9NEWS Hell no build the damn wall now!!! https://t.co/clxGkPNk2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Thank you Joy! That was my comment earlier, emancipation was the reason cited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mackenzie_vore @trutessa @nyastreaty @malmiddletonn You forgot @Ca13bSmith]]></document><document><![CDATA[my work is so toxic you can’t even tell people what time you start anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelCo85329620 @pbsmith70 @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids @jacknicklaus Shut up BOT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And no this is not right and open attacks are very illegal activities like these are very suspicious and wrong… https://t.co/XweiftnJEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanger got her wish, how awful. @HamillHimself @HuffPost @nytimes @Alyssa_Milano @AOC @KamalaHarris… https://t.co/FGO57weR8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge thank you to https://t.co/S1cE61s7DX for writing about TAXII!  . . . . #film #shortfilm #losangeles #mumbai… https://t.co/UJgTYyHWLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at Icon 9pm! Turn Back Time is Back and we are bringing all the Black Excellence that you can handle! I’m e… https://t.co/Axa7S4gFzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madonna pays tribute to Luke Perry on Instagram. ❤️ https://t.co/KnxQoOBXIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie Keep it simple Adam, there is no mystery with these people. They think they are entitled.  Both have it out… https://t.co/cp7hxAmKsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what her lil ass get lol - I’m glad I don’t have a brother cuz he would’ve tossed her and I woulda got ontop… https://t.co/zbbYPt4XwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all think there’s another “earth” out there somewhere that’s striving because they’re not doing the same dumb shi… https://t.co/r6qjr3XMul]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you guys start seeing me suddenly start to close in, don’t act surprised, you should’ve known this was bound to happen🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallonTonight congratulations Jimmy and the Roots!! You Rock! #20Million]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalGeoff2 @DucadiSpalato @doctoralexa OMG..You are so insane. NO, Trump wants people to come here legally. I… https://t.co/9iPyhkT5RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnitude 1.4 #earthquake, 22.5 km NE of Eureka Dunes, CA https://t.co/2H6jp2M3mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[**NEW INK** 💀❤️“Hell bound, but heaven sent.” 💀❤️ Tattoo by: @DaVinci_Tattoo with eternalink @hivecaps  @saniderm… https://t.co/ebCrVy55uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long week away in North Dakota, I'm glad that I only have these boxes. https://t.co/uy79tO4SiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love @ Redemption Outreach Community Ministries, Inc. - ROCM https://t.co/U8WwNncUaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog 🐾 does not care there is editing to be done ✅ #wantsattention #needsawalk #thatfacetho #dogproblems… https://t.co/rzyloakTs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a bee fly into my car the other day and everytime I think about it, I can just hear it buzzing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quotes from my day... All from me to students “be better.” “I was trying to being subtle but I’m literally talking… https://t.co/zciBVM3koR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now she wants to snuggle and watch Riverdale smh https://t.co/ugRuFy6qfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to back goals by Kalil Archambault to open the second: one 48 seconds in, and another four minutes later.… https://t.co/FQ4AzWQRTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blaylockbrant At some point I’d like to think we could get some Fat Bottomed Girls played]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some funniness. Best of 2013: The Year's Most LOL-Worthy Internet Finds: Each year the Internet brings us hila… https://t.co/jzViE1N517]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL I HAVE BEEN LOOKING FOR A REASON TO LEAVE MY JOB AND GUESS WTF JUST HAPPENED IN THE PROCESS OF MOVING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You care so much almost makes ya wonder if it wasn't completely manufactured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is completely laying on all of my blankets and i have the smallest bit of blanket. But you have to make sacr… https://t.co/tyQsQOhhFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuintirNa The crazy times began in 1992; when the Clintons rose to power. They transformed the pro labor Dems into… https://t.co/4fVSpHod0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good to see our friends Barb Ikerd &amp; Beverly Darby at the Capitol for Kansas Black Legislative Day! #ksleg https://t.co/UgkSFklHuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[More testimonials that the V3original works.... Get yours today. https://t.co/jXPLPtuR6V /theresarobnett  ID 164894… https://t.co/f5bUuzZzPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my goodness @BetteMidler just gets better and better. And now I’m in tears! #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you!! We need an experienced, classy man to beat Trump and can hit the ground running as president. Along wit… https://t.co/6Jy163NjI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanessaHickey6 Thanks! They are opening a @McAlistersDeli near me and will order for sure!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC So why did he say he didn’t think he had the authority? He does not know anything about the office he stole! What a disgrace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you you have an hour and half break before your child plays second game. @ Omni Dallas Hotel https://t.co/ukwcquADXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you tweet about all of your problems 24/7 and never handle it on your own, you’re a child 🤣🤣 byeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passando o Valentine’s Day fazendo o que eu mais amo fazer ♥️ @ Universal Studios Hollywood https://t.co/ARWaXMPoBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @jljacobson My god another example of trump’s promoting his own self interests...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going to try to stream from my dslr cam today to improve quality. ^_^]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Loss Prevention Detective - Oxnard, CA - https://t.co/AnO84rhgqa #security #Oxnard, CA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFootsweep @wrestlingberlin Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja Borja B… https://t.co/ZxtGXiT1ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Arts And Science Center in Independence, MO https://t.co/FzMHGSBEnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pollo frito, arroz con gandules y aguacate. Classic puertorican meal brought to you by our awesome team work.… https://t.co/9qKKLmuE5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for an excuse to get glammed up and support a great cause?  Look no further than next weeks elegant affair,… https://t.co/cS249EjXUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had an awesome day at SWE’s Heart Challenge yesterday.  Explorers have given over $5K to the American Heart Asso… https://t.co/a2nY21pbUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are ready for you, high school students!! #StepIntoCollegePhilly https://t.co/Le4w7YhqwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vayda and Liberty are crying bc they are imagining if they weren’t sisters]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you ever forget what you did for four months of your life because i’m concerned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendship is sweet, fun, hard, and all the things. Glad to be able to pick up and go with these girls and their hu… https://t.co/e2fslNXbiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @ValentinoAndy77 @CodiePrevostUK… https://t.co/4YKQFFTJjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicNielsen3 Kinda creepy!! Lol also rude- let the man just do his job 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieputh I mean but let’s be real, Tangerine Dreams, Full of It, Kiss Me, And Beautiful Corruption were everyth… https://t.co/Npa8Uz1dgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbitalk @cspanwj @kathrynw5 @CBSNews @StevenTDennis @business It is about the Presidents responsibility and powe… https://t.co/ETj7wzWDES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warning signs ( Global refugee crisis )- The New Indian Express Published  Last Updated: 16th September 2017 06:47… https://t.co/Fn43lRVY3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s they way it rolls. Way to support Austin. Keep it up. We love you Post 🥰⭐️🥰 @PostMalone @PostMalone_Fans… https://t.co/tPpnoYPcYm]]></document></documents></author>