<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/DEVeGtaLUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My excuse for not running was cause I didn’t have a phone to listen to music and now that I do I have no excuses fuck :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy triste porque deje mi carro en la agencia y me lo quitarán por 4 días 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsnjwn It's not the public , it the place and the management . It's gotten do bad as far as how things are run and… https://t.co/wl2unF6Ywf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richcurren @XCleXo Yes, I’d say so.. especially when the “slur” was just “homos” and they happened to be homos fig… https://t.co/RapUo65bih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk when i became such a loner girl but i really do everything by myself. I’m okay with it though 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final score — Mojave 59-Churchill 60 in overtime — great game by both teams — super proud of Mojave coming back as… https://t.co/Ba63O5rnaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can see how we feel on our face 🤣🤩 @keithwong7268  #vacationstart#seeyousoonhongkong#happymood#vacation#smile#g… https://t.co/pjRW9aojqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[sad that i’m not seeing kacey tonight, so i’ll be enjoying the concert from the comfort of my room :( https://t.co/ENaHPz4YTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were wondering how dumb men are, I told a guy I was buying candles and he thought I was buying them to help heat my apartment]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨I made it to the OASCAR’s! Oh, that little stage behind me...it’s just the OSCAR’s —Academy Awards stage; that’s a… https://t.co/VQoFINQDzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_gutierrezcit yes girl 💕💕💕💕💕 just love each other &amp; respect each other and be selfless and kind]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a day when folks are talking about books, I’m hearing tremendous praise for this one.  It’s got my attention bc… https://t.co/xnK6neyj1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The grass always looks greener on the other side , until you get to the other side ✍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The accuracy of this tweet is scary I shouldn’t have been shakin my ass to this song lmfao💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_polliard @MarkWarner Both Mark Warner &amp; Tim Kaine have vote to support infanticide!  We shall not miss this on Election Day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just noticing that X sampled the i8 Seatbelt chime in Sad! The song starts playing in my head every time I hear it]]></document><document><![CDATA[whew my friends love to hit me with “well I noticed but didn’t wanna say anything cause that’s your friend” after t… https://t.co/jUyGKOHui7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT -My babies and niece. Oh how time flies! #Love❤️ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/EjIYSAYdlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/FKe571W2Dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardinal George Pell found guilty of child sex abuse  https://t.co/9PZfnNNRw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard on the news in NJ:  “dress warm - it’s 21 degrees today”  Very funny to this #chicagogirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[the irony of needing to work more jobs to pay for a nicer home just so you can stay out of the home longer working… https://t.co/woZ2TEZfcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woe to the world because His truth in me was made a lie and now nobody is believing me or will believe me.  I under… https://t.co/6DPq03U0nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter is soon gonna get trash to me cause ya a family I don’t wanna be a part of 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nonstandardrep It’s pretty easy to decipher when people haven’t done a basic google search.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terminado de ver el nuevo capítulo de #TheWalkingDead y estoy amando el camino que está tomando la serie, me encant… https://t.co/nhL5Kp5mkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgoldst Have you ever seen Annie Atkins’ graphic design work for movie props? It’s suh good https://t.co/9WjqPaC8ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is the waterfall laughing at me? We hiked in to Proxy Falls this weekend to experience silence. Th… https://t.co/3bfyC5uUWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part about my birthday being the day after Valentine's Day is that all the candy is 75% off 🙌🏻🍫🍬🍭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/a9U2AIZZVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarbageFan98 Let this Mal's Madness Mess pick-up  speed and be done with once and for all.  It's too darn long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 45 allowed the Russians to take pictures and to keep notes. We don’t not have any notes or original p… https://t.co/aPyXdOmL6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comey @WSJ Oh come on!! The press does not speak the truth... they speak their version as do you. We all speak our… https://t.co/2ZNWMi11aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive workplace #annuity market growth;  #CFOs are paying attention and acting 👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STEMTasticScien $247 to get Stem into my students hands. Germs be gone. @STEMfinity triple match share-donate-retw… https://t.co/xX6JGw5nH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. I just drove to Punta Gorda for a dentist appointment that’s TOMORROW. How’s your Tuesday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between my dentist and her assistant today, the two of them proceeded to hum the ENTIRE two hours I was there... even to Kid Rock😪 #whyme]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people have no feelings whatsoever. If they can vote for this then look out older Americans they’ll be coming… https://t.co/L8JLKzT0Yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HibernianPub We will be there Saturday night celebrating my 50th birthday.  I can't wait!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake is one! @parkavenuenyc ❄️ 📸@heidigreenphoto 🎂 empirecakenyc 🍫 @mmschocolate  @disney mickeymouse . . . . . . .… https://t.co/mtYWn8w5ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because @NICKIMINAJ is not just a rapper, she’s a versatile artist and a creative powerhouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you feel connected to the moral purpose of your work, you behave differently. And at the end of the day, all b… https://t.co/BOe8z0QwEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Oh... So tough Nancy. There is a difference between bad social media posts and threats. The last lin… https://t.co/SVRxaKMiM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawn_juris @politico Interesting that ALL those other networks are wrong, but only Fox is right.  Does that not m… https://t.co/V7YSz2A1Er]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to our Reylo Valentine’s windows from 2018.  Yes, we’re still down with a little dark side-light side co-… https://t.co/nurlGJwCBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettySmile_Zee That’s the name the coloring book. 15 artist including myself has a piece in it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrrrGraphics Lol. Are you mad that she did that or are you mad because she is correct. I would be mad at a man who… https://t.co/fFhJowsiZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was about to cuss out my upstairs neighbors for being loud AF but in actuality its just fucking thunder!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gymfan14 @gracekramer98 @katelyn_ohashi @Briellee97 @MargzettaF @jordyn_wieber @kendalposton Why can’t this be wor… https://t.co/IWN5qLCVDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If so then ‘I just watch’ Jordan and McCarthy MUST go. Oh and you as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A comfy setting for a conversation is a vital part to any event design, don't you think? This beautiful setting was… https://t.co/1N3dy8GDwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're a military family, living in "Military City" San Antonio. It's a punch in the gut that Trump will take $Billi… https://t.co/FMda2UAqCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnePatton @LynnePatton  U shamed every black person I know by being a prop at Cohen's hearing. There wasn't 1 bl… https://t.co/jmiKMOAyJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Christ had no hand in making that sign. Just saying. His good name is just being used by the bottom of the barrel types.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, some of you may recall several years ago at Gallifrey One, I carried around a custom Funko pop of one of our or… https://t.co/oJCzs7y3C9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 @thomasholleran Seriously? GOP? Who the hell are you people to make those kinds of assertations. Sick a… https://t.co/7wGWdil4it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Baby West, you are SO perfect and I love you SOSOSOSO much!!   #family #babyportraits… https://t.co/yW32VyBesy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because a woman runs for president and I’m a woman, does NOT mean I will automatically vote for her. #standupforwhatyoubelievein]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBMENHOT It’s ok you can say and think what comes to you it’s not your fault! But I care and I just want you to wr… https://t.co/pjrTWBxsjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rolling through the Bozeman Pass during a winter storm warning — just another #winter day in #montana. #montanalife… https://t.co/1WrQRV6YGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get out of ur hometown and experience living in a new area! I promise it’s the best thing you’ll ever do lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Papanier I don't know but I will retweet to see if one of my followers knows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Batista is back with a blue nose ring... since he's on #Raw I feel like it should've been red.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking my broke ass to work!!! Show me some love 💙💙💙  Likes, retweets, follows  accepted💯💯  Think I’m pretty, and s… https://t.co/zZ1eEDNL6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now faith, hope, and love abide, these three; and the greatest of these is love. 1 Corinthians 13:13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had 7 Rings stuck in my head for 2 days now and I’m not even mad about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typicallyargent @kitkatkels23 @SophiaBush oh you knoooooow!! only wish you could have been there❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELeeZimmerman You are so sweet but it’s actually not my birthday. It’s March 20th and I’m not 53 like Wikipedia sa… https://t.co/498y6xJLk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabey_python they’re so dangerous too!! here they hate tires so they love to pop car tires]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @ChrisCuomo Omitted an important word in your Tweet .... ‘unqualified’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @RobinhoodApp and we'll both get a stock like $AAPL, $F, or $S for free. Make sure to use my link.  https://t.co/Bvx4ypRKfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of SMWATX. Notes from a stellar presentation by Liz Feezor on using business principles to tell your story. A… https://t.co/Kaqnk4swCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my fave things since I was a kid was eating cold birthday cake for breakfast. From our daughter Leah’s 21st… https://t.co/NNO4nwPVDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chalkymacalpi OMChalky me Iz overwhelmed by yours adorable handsomes. Me demands Dreamies and me gets dem! Gib dem… https://t.co/RGWsTuNWUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police say the shooter shot into the home on Kimball around 3:15 this morning. One man is in critical condition. Tw… https://t.co/zysnoxAy0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin @ThatShockratees I’m so sorry this happened to you. Here’s hoping for a better Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn How To Use Instagram 📲 Like A Boss at my workshop on 2/27 in#nyc. There’s still time to register🎟:… https://t.co/5o0F3epkCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chakierrah @adidas @adidasoriginals Definitely one of my favorites from you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton Tom..she isn't going anywhere except GITMO...I read recently that GITMO is now open for business...the r… https://t.co/iC3law2Idf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GawkGawkThwack Yesss glad im not the only one sis. I gotta get one for the back too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get your #summer #blonde on! Call today! 920-213-8280 to book your next  #color! Put some love into your ha… https://t.co/Hm2vMVbJ8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJacieMaslyk So worth the investment! #AllinEDU https://t.co/JVmw4CXzlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartofAlderaan @MandaTheGinger @Carie80ESB @MegZCull @darth_swlove03 @Viamgu @irishgeekgirl @JettaRosewater… https://t.co/5gAPZzjzwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SveaElske @daveweigel Always was Repub tv, spewed hate from day one. Rupert rules the fools]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Take your snow and exit stage east ... https://t.co/wikbvbQK2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's for dinner.....Vegan Crispy Korean BBQ #plantbasedlifestyle #tofu #koreanbbq @ Menifee, California https://t.co/55XD8awoyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaladinCornelia @DearAuntCrabby I agree. I’m biased. High school classmate. But you are spot on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Founder’s Day @PhiPsiKentState! Your impact on the Kent community is profound and I am so proud to have known you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyjanefox Comb nausea trumped by 77yr old Kraft charged w solicitation. Ultimate image of power and privilege exploiting women 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior Lil’ Carmel de Lite. Would work great except for me being practically Snow White.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪 Empowering our youth! The primary weapon of @latinasurge is a simple one, #EDUCATION 💭 Connect to us as we contin… https://t.co/eDwi7WDJC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all the people who helped me make this drop off at @barrelhousetap to add to their @ywcadayton donation!… https://t.co/6F4pAzu4xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legoland security jam today is Crabb Family!🦀🦀🎶🎶 https://t.co/khBeJBUKBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so happy! 💗 The next @ChicagoMayor will be one of these two #amazing #intelligent #strong black women… https://t.co/JHC5PnrMnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jininx pala ni GoArcher kaya umabot ng 4th set eh! Lol #UAAP81WomensVolleyball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biscuitpancakes @rhettandlink @mythical @rhettmc @linklamont Oh John.....you will be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Augustus709 I don't want to fat shame anyone, but damn America, you have a problem. Obesity is the largest contrib… https://t.co/sKKnZ32XL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just looked at my calendar, I won’t be available after March 15 until May. This year is cray cray folks. #gradschoolproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Joseph, you are the faithful protector and intercessor of all who love and venerate you. You know that I have co… https://t.co/tfeggy5qos]]></document></documents></author>