<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My hubby with the great, one and only, Mr Joe Gibbs.  My heart is broken for the huge loss of their son, JD Gibbs.… https://t.co/tE0ejlg8XK]]></document><document><![CDATA[For reference, this is about my wanting corn chowder for lunch and instead getting stuck with clam chowder 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ArgoJournal Clay should wake up and start realizing that Potus is exactly the way Cohen has portrayed him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity 8 billion dollar wall with money, among other things, taken from cancer research for children. Donald… https://t.co/TFhzc4uzsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los hipstes son buitres. Carroñeros de subculturas y tribus urbanas. #quepasoolallo https://t.co/rdgrdpnypM]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY GOD I LOVE JOLEX. Their relationship is everything. The good, the bad, the ugly but so so so much good and suppo… https://t.co/IVppQvjiEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[anybody who’s upset we didn’t even have a delay today either call the board or have your parents call and let them know how you feel. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[KR has not been romantically attached to anyone since his wife died when he was only 28. All his girlfriends includ… https://t.co/ds6pKO5oNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always admired Karl’s creativity and originality at the House of CHANEL and beyond. May a true icon RIP 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makawitt I would probably cry. I’ve heard the parents in it are so oblivious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet, Trump hasn’t brought his company’s jobs back to America. Still made overseas!!! Hypocrite!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey solo mom  I live making healing food   Its has to power to transform your trauma into triumph  DM me to find ou… https://t.co/HNHoX55ljW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 @efero_patricia There's no debate. Question is: could Frump have that suit made in his size without using parachute material?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially been put through the gas chamber, been pepper sprayed and now tazed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets on sale now for Elvira: The Immigration Play opening in nyc next weekend. https://t.co/TEVz0zfwsd #nyctheatre #theater]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two eggs over easy rye toast potato orange juice coffee and water. It’s lit. Round #2.]]></document><document><![CDATA['The Send' marks start of 'greatest Jesus movement,' over 40,000 Christians gather, commit to missions: Hallelujah!  https://t.co/gA1n7O0Dpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day... Mais j’ai encore beaucoup de photos à poster après mon retour 🙊 @ Nassau Bahamas https://t.co/zd3jEax8vJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[7-game card is ready, Join the #1 ranked #CBB handicapper, right now. https://t.co/ByrROKzWpo… …… https://t.co/2X7ouqaR9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC Because she,being a typical Dem.,believes we common folk should do as the elite DC politicos say not as they do]]></document><document><![CDATA[**clarity they are actually SHOWING me about circuits because they are using inquiry and exploration! Soooo much goodness going on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf @IngrahamAngle Republicans need to come up with a, i.e. “Global Pollution Solution” 🌎 partnering w/ India… https://t.co/IcU8YLhVTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so funny cause I’m a dolphins fan and moes a patriots fan. This household is a mess. 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off we go! #southbeach #miami #miambeach #girlstrip @ Fontainebleau Miami Beach https://t.co/qsiR9ot5rD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fuelfriends @JohnGHendy It’s English. 1st period. (Occasionally it’s calculus) I constantly have to remind myself… https://t.co/VKtdXJe8g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtzNaturalle Let me know when you do. I’m out here ‘eye patching‘ it. https://t.co/EGIeB1Yeip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau This Liberal party did not intervene in any other substantial job losses and pensions in jeopardy wh… https://t.co/7wZhFHkDzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pahealy070 @SinBinVegas P Healy, yeah. That’s more what I’m thinking. In a 1 (maybe 2) goal deficit game, I can se… https://t.co/CudlHYh4WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi They aren’t worried about having another Democratic President. This national emergency will be just one… https://t.co/lKioezoAH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warriors... you got this! Pull out ALL the  stops today as you take on Northeastern! You got this! Dig deep! Aggres… https://t.co/fuSrlEmuiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Why get these kids excited about a situation still being studied. Sue AOC for panicking kids w her untruths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaviota330 This is the perfect girl for your Retirement ..she already knows how to live with us old farts!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo i just want any friend i’ve made to know that i luv them so much even when i am too busy to see them :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning from Turn 2!!! @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/a9y8M3brWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best feeling is when you feel like you are just bothering or annoying everyone 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Oh, the thrill of “dark money” funding a critique of your shortsightedness, and the convenient implication tha… https://t.co/pLldDpC6lP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 @trashtvforme Amazing how people have nothing better to do than to trash someone else’s success. Congra… https://t.co/7qLw0MUYKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinating info - we need to start sharing this info! @ONeducation @Build_ADream @gecdsbpro @WECDSB… https://t.co/eCwNa7bAxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved #JuliaRoberts #HeathCliff Fish bone earrings. https://t.co/p4GbwcOdZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[English 11 students provide peer feedback and work on revising and finalizing their personal memoirs, which are due… https://t.co/tLgxSPDVrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz You say you don't see color,  but to me that is a problem. I want you to see that I am a black Ameri… https://t.co/bT3bd5rKqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir It’s not that it’s changed.  It’s the ridiculousness about the times being so wildly all over the map… https://t.co/tlFz34HPUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NugBug96 @jmcappiello 🐀 🐀 Your boys are beautiful,love 💙💙 their coloring!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao listen. I told the landlord 3 of his fish dead becuz I went outside and they weren't moving in the tank and ba… https://t.co/DBbeZsQqdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontalbanCAMILA @rowfede Jajajaja y aquí sigo en su casa jajajaa no se está tan mal, es un cielo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What he said 👇!  It was an exciting race to watch! Great job, Fernando!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icecube Saturday will only be a “good day” if you swing by our chicken joint before your show in #Philly. ❤️🍯🍗  @franklinmhall #icecube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally don’t care what people say I love WWE and Trevor is the best bf ever because WE ARE GOING TO… https://t.co/Omc3gadjSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay me! I even get a jacket with my name on it! @ AMC West Melbourne https://t.co/UQOhrfLar4]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bf came over to help with my hangover before he went to work, wow i don’t deserve that guy🥺❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most hilarious and accurately “middle school” blackout poem we got this week. 🤣🤣🤣 #hayslib… https://t.co/ASIUSKwHVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks really interesting, I used to live right near that intersection. Figures they’d update it after I moved 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SincerelySherie Dude she does not even look like you 😂 I’m glad you made it 😂 also.. happy late birthday 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamronhall Congratulations on your little one. I can't explain the joy of motherhood, but luckily you will experie… https://t.co/HslVg6QqW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KT_Rams You approve of my dark circles and deathly appearance? Thanks friend 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚Want your students to share book projects w/ @Seesaw? Join me✴️tonight✴️2/12 at 8pm EST for Activities you can use… https://t.co/gB1ZFGA34y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPerez I get why this is important even tho it won't pass the Senate. But I'm beginning to think @HouseDemocrats… https://t.co/k8pSU6knhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Megan  I was born in the middle of the world  My age is a little too high  I like to think about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️🍻💋🔥The Sonoma Fires were raging. I had an ENTIRE CAR FULL OF PEPPERS rescued from the fire but no where to proces… https://t.co/aRIwVfdkuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz @MyraDSirois1 Sounds great.  I wonder how much we would save if insurance was not for profit again.  Ya know like before Nixon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_CMGreer Thank you beloved. You were so great on the air tonight I love watching you we need to get you a desk here lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Review: Dear Wife by Kimberly Belle @KimberlySBelle @NetGalley @parkrowbooks #DearWife #KimberlyBelle… https://t.co/SHoOO7HDbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The seats at the bar will be comfy af. There will be super soft blankets all over the place (cus who doesn’t love a soft blanket??)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Democracy has to be born again each generation and education is its midwife.” – John Dewey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamarrmeza Went to the mall not to long ago and can you believe that did not find not one damn turtle neck 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericpthomas @ColoradoParaMan @AbilitiesExpo Also important for the disabled. I can’t go because of walking problem… https://t.co/roKUwkOhmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is unacceptable. ICE detains, sexually assaults and abuse children  but no one is responsible for this because… https://t.co/MFgYiIGgzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The location has been revealed! Cannot wait to see everyone again. Dallas in July... y’all know the rest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After several hours and nine stores, I am now in possession of no fewer than FIVE new pairs of black trousers. Even… https://t.co/tC2kDp7Czz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterZThompson  I try not to compare, particularly between eras. Rocket? I didn't see him play; Gretz was great,… https://t.co/fCrmmDx9p4]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL at the people who subtweet but they don’t care about subtlety so they TAG the person 🙄  (@swagbrera )]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why i always play it safe and take one for each limb, can’t take no risks when it comes to pain]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘It’s time:’ @GovEvers announces proposal to reform Wisconsin’s marijuana laws. https://t.co/SXGnpgjqhR via @fox6now]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish men like women who were cute funny and real over fake slutty bitches 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post study abroad depression is 5000000000 times worse than post concert depression]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t drive down to Shenandoah without a stop at @redtruckbakery! walking fueled by creamy chicken and wild rice so… https://t.co/LteRcxWeFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[l just remembered that freshman year of HS l liked a boy and would Snapchat him and l downloaded thks app to open h… https://t.co/qlefrbK2Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight my love took me out for a random dinner, we got two desserts switching off after each bite with no guilt, t… https://t.co/uqwvea2o7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump is a mental patient. Why is nothing being done about it? https://t.co/7369e8uYxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: Colton only wants Cassie because she doesn’t want him...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to think that after Derek died greys went to shit but after rewatching i have concluded after George died it… https://t.co/E231RYFGLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @VH1 Nancy you are a trail blazer for so many women! Your leadership is highly respected. Thanks for all you do!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correction: Rep. Eddie Farnsworth is failing to protect kids. However, hope @KateBrophy can help us #dobetter to pr… https://t.co/kYvW9xKthz]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol my professor just cancelled class 20 min. before. Like I’m already up and ready thx tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to help a previous groom throw his parents a 50th Anniversary celebration! Congratulations! @ Chattanooga,… https://t.co/s8cFptqTTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mixed arm day with #delts and #bis and #tris the day after a pr breaking chest day... yeah, why not? #nodaysoff… https://t.co/hEEPl6V21W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EbenOfficial I’m omw back to LA from Vegas stuck in traffic and honestly listening to your music is so perfect rn… https://t.co/IWHD1rLTIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo did anyone else notice that gas went up like $.20/gallon in like a day......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@establishmentno @hockeygrandma23 @Melody7473 @silentdeplorble @__CassidyRae__ @MarilynLavala @freddyrace14… https://t.co/wVZMNzZqPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came across three wrecks, had to turn around half way to Troy and go down the SMALLEST back road to get to Luvern… https://t.co/v4GewxpYoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Bell Gardens: light rain, 53°F 62% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1015mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nthomas1231 I have Comcast/Xfinity in Grand Rapids, MI area and NO Hallmark Drama. We have Hallmark and Hallmark Movies and Mystery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing for warmer weather with this Spring refresh in Accessories! #Accessories #treatyoself #T1791 #brand https://t.co/5bgSepZ0B3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my 10 year old were locked on Thursday! She’s like we Are Titans! The right people won!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it has been years since @JenniferGrey had her nose done, but she just looks so very different...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaySano @Khoaalude It was one of those "pass it on" type deals, but a friend had put it in our yard because someon… https://t.co/NTkXynJhNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This horse represents how I feel this morning! 😴🐴 (Photo by Stu Brown) @FOX26Houston https://t.co/pewywvzrrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenSpeaksUp @SpeakerPelosi @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @AOC Rahm is worthless, THANK GOD, he is gone in May!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead That was sweet. Idk what it was about. I'm assuming it was a loved one in the past.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was so dead the morning after but was totally worth it. https://t.co/XbKpg8Mkdo]]></document></documents></author>