<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude, you got crushed in the midterms! Republicans lost 40 seats in the House! You must be high on adderall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roosevelt welcomes our African American Aerospace Pilots  🐻🐾💚 https://t.co/EYalOwSA1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHtsWrestling Showed hilites of Jump’s match Saturday night. Sorry you missed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFXBurke @davidfaber Yeah right, in case you have not noticed company’s are leaving NY for low tax states, did you… https://t.co/xalAz2dw98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wutitis101 @TheJonasKnox A lot of comedians are really hurting over this. He was a friend to many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @chuckwoolery And don’t forget #VoterID @KamalaHarris that’ll strengthen things too! #OhThatDontWorkfirYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/DU7Ainnwxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceboxCA I’ve been meaning to message you about that, as well! 😂 I’m free this Friday, until 4-ish PM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRamirezVE Preséntate en EEUU a defenderte de los cargos y luego ve a Venezuela para explicar quienes son los resp… https://t.co/OkltMXS8LC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furious R. Kelly has to be HELD BACK during his explosive first interview since being charged with sexua...… https://t.co/rHVSCO0tpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hace falta que nos paguemos con rencores, Tu eres libre de marcharte si lo quieres, No me importa sufrir puedes… https://t.co/duyCKaYb36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debralazebraa If you want something sweet I’ll recommend the silk brand, vanilla almond that one is also really good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trakspartakus11 Prezes dostal liste z Tel Avivu a Schetyna z Berlina, pedaly dobiora sie sami... https://t.co/WmDbwQjyNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 3 Sisters American Red Ale by @WildRideBrewing at @2sparkys — https://t.co/0AOxQ4NjDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHKogath @aevanko perhaps one of you know someone I can throw my zenny at so I can have one or both made?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NazVoice @VOATLANTA I’m not going to be there this year. I’m going to miss you. Have fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited to see Mika, Kreider, Vesey, &amp; Georgiev, on Tampa in a few years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annnnd @dwcase tweets are now being featured on @SECNetwork. In case you were still wondering if his Twitter was still a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @SebGorka We need if to cash a check, WHY not to vote. Judicial won a case in Los Angeles county Cali… https://t.co/VMkI4rqlX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fbf to last summer at @Hazeltine with a couple of my boys. Looking forward to warmer weather and blue skies soon.… https://t.co/vazXJ9P25O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I 👀 you are not really trying to break into true show biz. You want 👿 who is going to use you and destroy you… https://t.co/bg0o4Lfcxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insanity! Pretty sure we don’t give a f**k about “sharia law” in #America Maybe they should conform to OUR laws. Af… https://t.co/lUfERwVPWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math Coach's Corner: The 80/20 Rule: How Will You Spend Your Time? #laughter #lol #smirk #humorous https://t.co/cGbej3SAA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to MSNBC for airing #BernieInBrooklyn but their one-sided post-rally analysis couldn't be more negative.… https://t.co/Slt8xiX75P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasemccarty @scott_lowe I usually do a modified version of @altonbrown recipe for Brussels sprouts on the grill, f… https://t.co/7mC0lqOxHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_1791 @washingtonpost The brainwashing in the schools is in full effect. But when I was in elementary school… https://t.co/L5uUwC0SzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Represent #oldschool #indians Day 3 of Mizuno Showcase @ JustAgame Fieldhouse https://t.co/yIovNmux9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauBistro @nobby1955 @Quarterback_USA @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @POTUS #dumptrump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @espn how about "Lillard's 33 points more than enough in win over Celtics"? @Dame_Lillard @trailblazers… https://t.co/O1bu9DIeZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatPainReport This is also interesting because pain is not relayed back to the brain by way of the blood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun day in Austin! It was a pleasure to see @paulakerger and @Deggans to talk #ReconstructionPBS. I also got… https://t.co/1Npx5WYFQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 tix available for D1’s in Pitt. Sec 114, Row 5. Great seats! PM me if interested. I’m sorry, but I won’t be able to get back to everybody.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Robb Chadwick, currently serving as Commandant of Midshipmen at the @NavalAcademy.   Senate Conf… https://t.co/dv4wv3EcBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything in Pisces got me crying at the idea of my boyfriend hanging up the phone to go to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @MarthacastexT!  🥳 🎈 🎊 🎉  from your honorary dist K resident 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[from the #desert of #dry #bones a coming together new life, a rattling,  a joining, a growing new life by the proph… https://t.co/zr5YhMJoc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeitzkowitz @SenWarren This is a good step, especially in states or regions that haven’t yet enacted more cohere… https://t.co/9qTgGd0Lgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’re here for Jordyn, but I’d love it if you checked out my Apparel store https://t.co/mZ7DRBGPid. You kno… https://t.co/XJjO7QrABw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some one asked me with a straight face to show them a minimum of 10 years experience in 1996 during a interview I g… https://t.co/4Hq9PCl3Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerdFB Students of the Week for March 4-8, 2019 are:  • @EthanBingham6   • @_samburton__   • @zack_leininger   Con… https://t.co/4LUHGcpL4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYC_DOT Saw I posted twice. Thought the first one was only a draft. Thank you again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, that’s a very bad thing. I think I missed something. We are talking about the gun control-undocumented can’t ca… https://t.co/abr7azQ7VZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriaMaria_T @PCano2 La Iglesia nació en PENTECOSTÉS y por los merito de la Cruz obtiene las Gracias pero fue aqu… https://t.co/9WQrwV93co]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffAdams82 @thehill @KamalaHarris Yes, because they're Trump shills.  Obama wanted Hillary to lose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are one of those people that waits at stop signs for me to pull up to the sign and then go, why? And stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyK @Twitter @dickc @bohan @TJay @stephanied @ju2thalee @mooreryan @evanr @semurph @LiatBycel @LK Congrats you… https://t.co/OzjrTTTMTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndySullivan12 @ukfandan37 Sounds like they are pulling out all the big guns for the birthday bash! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some common reasons for rejection without review per Bauchner #pem19 https://t.co/XpewXXuUy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostMalone   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)  https://t.co/j0aZbvB0ii… https://t.co/siQL9PpNl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanAndrewsFox4 Eerie calm with occasional sprinkle just N of Weatherford right now. Hell of a Light Show though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 186: This charging cord was not put away properly so I fixed it. @elonmusk @Tesla @mayemusk https://t.co/mFWJhteEvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[they booed Joe Lacob when Chris Mullin got his jersey retired did he ban anyone from Oracle Arena?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People out here really supporting Bernie still? I’m sorry but those ideas and policies just won’t work in the capit… https://t.co/liWc52qSVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The airport received .58” overnight bringing our rain year total to 4.47” which is only .08” below normal, or 98% o… https://t.co/Q4Kz0CCP9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it’s a long way out I’ll agree with that but DIA is nationally recognized for its efficiency  Remember it’s spr… https://t.co/GEzPOIxUcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bifurcation would admit the reality golfers are already experiencing. Chiefly that the recreational game and elite… https://t.co/7rr20Ekh3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add in @UofT transit expert, Matti Siemiatycki on how to cut @TTChelps fare evasion losses.  We meet up with one of… https://t.co/PHsUBOfi12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rplantejr @CNN Was that a pun or a typo? Nobel or noble... I'm hoping it was a pun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Some trust in chariots and some in horses, but we trust in the name of the Lord our God.” Ps. 20:7-8  Grace connec… https://t.co/GHIaEnv9Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCGScoin @NGCcoin @CoinWeek @CoinWorld @coinagemag  @ANSCoins 1877-S Trade Silver Dollar NGC AU-58 for auction on… https://t.co/81IlZ6R29c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Scratch Bernie Sanders he's already lost one time.... as far as Kamala goes… https://t.co/VDQZqOwQ7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t expect people to have the same principles. We listen to each other and try to reach agreement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Who https://t.co/WyMzpV8R2y get this from the member of the trump crime family while the family is… https://t.co/tf64K9rSXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniel52464547 @RosaRubicon No you don't you need to measure the decay rate and then you can extrapolate the date.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_buttenham I dont know. TWN has 90 to below 90 after noon. I'll trust the official source (EC) before any private company]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah living life with depression and anxiety’s is a lot. But in the end I try to fight that with being positive and… https://t.co/ZATqju7d55]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the district (NC 11) that @RepMarkMeadows represents. You decide whether he COULD be considered a RACIST!..… https://t.co/peQTT8HWba]]></document><document><![CDATA[#celticstaugustine #albannach @ Saint Augustine, Florida https://t.co/XqGFJOR3Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i gotta change my myOxy password because somebody hacked into some Admissions program.  and now I’m being punished!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the first | @DuncanvilleBB leads DeSoto 16-8. Future Texas Tech G Jahmi’us Ramsey has a game-high 9 points. #txhshoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the weekend hanging Flash/Flood.   Join me at the opening on Friday March 15 to see more 😊  A huge thank you… https://t.co/Gz7W5hDOQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmasamun3 @JimValley @Fumihikodayo @Liger_NJPW Pretty sweet! Nice job. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliza_relman @BretBaier @AOC That’s commendable. We don’t need any more idiots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurtsuttonTV @clemsonvideo @ross_video Why aren’t your buttons purple and orange? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt @davidmweissman Yes, they are ones who have a plastic badge and carry wooden guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, we do know where trump is taking #funds from for his #FakeTrumpEmergency.. #CyberSecurity and #Military]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NECA_TOYS Thanks for all you and the NECA crew do! Your figures are truly works of art. And only about 5 months until 🌊☀️🌴🍔🍔🍔...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fathertorey @Melodie_Woerman @episcopal_news @DioceseSD @EpiscopalMI Oh indeed. They got that one perfectly right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UKIO2019 I’m delighted to confirm that our abstract on Artificial Intelligence in Breast Screening has been accept… https://t.co/0Gh0LGwK2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themightymct @LadyLakeMusic @RockmebabyTV @LizzJustLizz @ZestRadioShow @BsThorsen @robinbain @redTamsen @JulieLek… https://t.co/PtRona6UxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyePatriot @stoiquement @abelamundala @soniarolley @RFI @LitsaniChoukran @afrikarabia @jasonkstearns @Tresor_k… https://t.co/sLEvukt6Q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @JackConnie @suziday123 @MUC_Airport @Cbp8Cindy @cazij @magee333 @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG @ccatmpt… https://t.co/4zLcG3ejtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArkhamZeek @TaraHollyFigure @Twitter Yeah pretty much and the hate will flow like the mighty Mississippi]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT My legs are getting tired from dunking on the rando overnight trolls and want to get some sleep before sunrise d… https://t.co/rmpzIulPFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “Anyone want to go to Whole Foods with me?” My friends: ”We were actually thinking we could take acid and go to the Eagle.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well alright then...don’t hold anything back Senator Jordan!  Well done sir, well done 👏😎👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[W Y N W O O D 🎭 🖌 🇺🇸 en Wynwood Walls &amp; Art District, Miami https://t.co/TVSAu0MGGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blazindw @Footy_Headlines @USWNT It’s a billion times better than whatever this was. https://t.co/39C1vKEKQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[that it yields seed for the sower and bread for the eater, so is my word that goes out from my mouth: It will not r… https://t.co/HRWHPWjWuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hair is just barely long enough for my bun , bitch it’s back. https://t.co/7LLC8csCLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be the worst lineup I’ve ever seen. And I know prices for tickets are going to be up there too. Disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclyntravels @UA_Astrobotics @hensoncraig @WeAreCRMS That's awesome,next time let them do weather balloons with v… https://t.co/J7QZw8dIfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zisi Emporium for B Movies: 13 Hours in a Warehouse, Ghosts Botch a Robbery: https://t.co/Bvt6JOCMFU https://t.co/cCFgZqpoYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/w8aksqGLGJ  #realestate #realtor #realty #forsale #househunting #homesforsale #homesale #properties… https://t.co/7c7mVjau1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[From everything I've seen and heard the only movie that should have won an #Oscars is BlackkKlansman or The Favorit… https://t.co/wHMrcBaMIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewpprice Referenced from original artwork by Anna Lepeshkina https://t.co/uHCT7Zlszn]]></document><document><![CDATA[FROM THE BRONX, NY TO COLUMBUS, OH❗️EVERY STAGE GETS THE SAME AURA❗️I’m the hottest upCOMING African🇬🇭 artist From… https://t.co/V8svrfXvj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That full body massage on camera was VERY awkward...I didn’t realize @Nicolekayfit eyes were wide open as mine were… https://t.co/glAr8k5xd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I imagine this means Oracle of Ages and Oracle of Seasons are on the menu too, right? @CapcomUSA_ ?… https://t.co/YwsgTwCEuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soldierkevin17 @celtics @PutnamToday Just a joke my guy. I know their net rating offensively is actually a little higher with Kyrie.]]></document></documents></author>