<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DRoseTV Thanks, D-Rose! Glad to see you’re killing it up north. Hope those winters aren’t slowing you down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to take someone else's dog out in winter has reminded me how much I don't miss having a 9-5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taster. Outstanding brew! - Drinking a Hazy Rabbit by @lakefront at @lakefront  — https://t.co/ImboqHcR4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryandeiss Thanks for making the marketing world a better place. Happy to be in your community for the last five years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terry35509308 Vote for Trump in 2020 and make America great for another 4 years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert De Niro vibes rolling into the WVU-Bama tailgate in 2026. 👴🏻 https://t.co/P6rEvSZnWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be awesome.  Xbox and Marvel are eight up my alley.  (Want to upgrade too and this paint job looks amazi… https://t.co/palwZdcJdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Rob Horner from U of Oregon @SMARTCtr talking about implementation. #pbis #pbischat #mtss https://t.co/qR98kdXVqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biker_Ian It’s a big place! Took years to be able to just go without pouring over maps! The thaw is supposed to st… https://t.co/xTffjWwHD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems You do realize that as a defender of @realDonaldTrump, certifiably the most prolific lia… https://t.co/5Rs5zynGgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN If any die in Prison we all know who shut them up and i bet we never find  out if the did]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Cy Creek's Amanda Mcaleavey, who captures gold at the #UILState Wrestling Championships in the Class 6A… https://t.co/xPYEIZfTpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You still have a chance to make a right Mr. President, Use wisdom @realDonaldTrump @POTUS  1John 1:9 Holy Bible If… https://t.co/T14XZH9LJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas to Whittier in 3 1/2 hours straight shot 90% of the time. Like a Glove.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMackeyPG @disgruntledbill Couple of shit goals, oh well. I'm more concerned about our top d being injured. Missin… https://t.co/be4RVdzooD]]></document><document><![CDATA[SA Wallet Free AirDrop Event!  가입하면 APG 5,000 AirDrop 친구추천하면 APG 5,000 AirDrop 놓칠 수 없는 특별한 이벤트!  추천아이디: blackatter… https://t.co/hLSbJRg4lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until you in that one party and random niggas flock trynna hit the jay 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz This continues to become more and more embarrassing for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you applying for a #job soon? You can ask your interviewers sensible questions too.  #interviews #jobinterviews… https://t.co/NWS3mQ6AR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie @ScottWalker @MittRomney @LindseyGrahamSC Retire Brit. Your too fucking old to understand. Times are changin… https://t.co/WMCsRn0wqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying a new activity: Impulse Shuffleboard! Pushing puck with force sensor and comparing Force-time graph areas sh… https://t.co/jk79pmeZJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demoncrats Cannot Grasp Reality Since They Smoke Funny Substances Valued More In  $ EVERYDAY ; Than Mueller Probe S… https://t.co/e362DzCB55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cannaworldsite @Bklynbby @Raymosaki @Smokette_ @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @james_bong13 @_jena4n @Kunzitoons… https://t.co/iEy7OReJPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also like.... f I hope we play the browns before hunt gets to play. 🤦🏼‍♀️ browns gonna be good... real good. (Buuuu… https://t.co/h1yt9Ff1sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSDoubleA This is the earliest I’ve come here. I don’t like having to wear a sweatshirt to the park]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winnerbowzer I've watched that show twice. The one where some kids gets hooked on drugs(?) and pukes what looked l… https://t.co/iJ1bcMlYZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought some melatonin at target so it can help me fall asleep, took it almost an hour ago but I honestly just feel more awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tljones1908 @keithboykin Good luck trying to "fix" history. I am only interested in fixing the future for all of u… https://t.co/jnVDyxra3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget when me and @benji_leslie went to this guys house and his bird was just dead in his closet for who knows how long 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 Ways to Unleash Your Inner Dancing Queen @SparkPeople https://t.co/BGXtZcOSye]]></document><document><![CDATA[King TuT award 410 Devices sold Q3 and top score card! Guy Haper @akisselv @MartyHayes11 @mark_nachman @jimmills22… https://t.co/VucbSEZVb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That lovely lady!  #empirestatebuilding   @HeinvanHouten @nycmarathon @empirestatebldg @ New York, New York https://t.co/b9WLaxiKbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandajer I mean, my music taste has been based on Panic! At The Disco’s cover of The Greatest Show for a while n… https://t.co/hqFTH04T4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnybananas you are the Peyton Manning of the challenge.. just old and suck and it’s gonna take you getting carr… https://t.co/UFvWp1e11m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo @MorningsMaria @FoxBusiness @dagenmcdowell @Mitch_Roschelle @KevinRKelly_ @ntengler @PhilipWegmann… https://t.co/LJtvnwMnaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS Jacob Wohl a young conservative who was actively looking into @IlhanMN background had his Twitter account su… https://t.co/YqJta2B8uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppcorp Alleluia brother!!! We made it! Happy Friday! Have a fantastic day and weekend ahead! ☀️👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are New York tacos as egregious to Los Angelinos as LA bagels are to me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of a smart of by Trump tbh. Dem's just unveiled a climate change bill that is quite possibly the most unpopula… https://t.co/uCEW4vMzqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Mafia born from Italy my Romantic my single life was 29 years old. I live in Newburgh from New York. https://t.co/4bJCBY8Fkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMelina Hey Melina HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!! 🎁🎈🎉🎊🎂 Could you see your self in @IMPACTWRESTLING?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally slipped my mind that it’s daylight savings time. I was like Captain Marvel is NOT a 3 hour movie, lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaabeLopez @jram4775 Where you going it ain’t snowin you got a big meat and it’s showin....don’t get me started I’… https://t.co/VjP8T0Xf3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was a first half....Pistons 71 Cavs 38......Holy smoke factories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every internet dating profile is sort of like that game two truths and a lie, except the difference is that it is u… https://t.co/xKHjk8YP0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseballing at L Dale Mitchell Park as @OU_Baseball (6-1) opens a 2-game midweek set vs Arkansas Pine-Bluff (1-6)… https://t.co/keHGM6jflA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coloquei o Bruce aqui pra dentro, dog tá querendo batalhar com o bicho gigante mano]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes I wish someone will do a story on @CNN and @MSNBC anti @sensanders bias Either they ignore him entirel… https://t.co/0bZnrWcvf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landho69 @washingtonpost And the winner is.....                       Miss Information https://t.co/hgHKKAOZ4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can survive the journey and meet good people along the way then that’s a VICTORY.  Instagram: heavyweight_ny… https://t.co/i72SUigqx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraCohenSolo This is why you go to a legal sex worker. So there is no fear of arrest, diseases, robbery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was shooting a family film and the dog wanted more screen time. #Suddenly #Puppy @ San Francisco Bay Area https://t.co/Rsda6VaOq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t 2016 prove that it doesn’t matter how much corrupt 💴 the Dems raise? @realDonaldTrump beat Hillary with, basically, a Twitter account]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marble + resin wood art. Imagine all the possibilities | Luxury crafters  . . https://t.co/00TAr6nv9w info@artboull… https://t.co/qFnSM9GtPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illfat3d MANNN SOMETIMES I LOOK AROUND AND JUST THINK GOD PEOPLE ASSOCIATE ME WITH THEM... https://t.co/Ux5MamcyBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IShallResist @Kokomothegreat Perhaps his physical health is stable, but his mind is sick beyond sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrudat_ho29 No but I saw a speculation article on the Dolphins reddit page that was linking him to Miami]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @MarvelStudios but y’all doing way too much in @LegionFX like what drugs are you on and can I have some]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gans10848795 @SteveSaretsky @xelan_gta @brad_barrett @REWoman @jhwfung @rohanarezel @realTheProphet @416_Perp… https://t.co/ULOMdV6SS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This seems about right. "Senator! Senator!" https://t.co/IzTssuVAdW https://t.co/RF1FCJxs4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta Thank you. I will say that’s a first in the decades of flying out of ATL. So I reckon 99.9% accuracy is good enough ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[But wait, I thought Laura Kelly assured us that her plan would END the lawsuits and SOLVE the problems once and for… https://t.co/I4PQVTNc36]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys Some are WISE! They Stay inbounds! Some take Chances, Thinking Outside the BOX!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrific morning at the capital attending @nysut #CommitteeOf100 Hundreds of educators in Albany advocating for fai… https://t.co/gV5QzD60pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one still hurts #theonethatgotaway @ChicagoBears @spiceadams #DaBears https://t.co/dYBh89QAaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yandle turnover tracked down by Luongo...Avs still up 1-0 with 10:38 left 2nd...Lu with 18 saves so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paxtrader777 @RealBrianWatt @Cubby_Blu @mando1221 Lol Finishing the kids homework, I didn’t pay attention in class… https://t.co/4i1SpdxUzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHunnel @Regan0002112 @MrsPerrin @just_old_joe @WeStandWithEvan @Yakekoge @FactCheckU @DaddyJim52… https://t.co/wT34evjOyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ValentinesDay and #ThirstyThursday to all. https://t.co/xJHCb8xFgw @AlisonForKY @Kristileenews @InesLandmann… https://t.co/GoMv46sPDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shaken_Bacon I know. Part of me is like. Fallout is my jam. Why did I let people’s opinion stop me from joining th… https://t.co/so03BXdiIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We come to you tomorrow with a fun &amp; fanatical look at the 2019 Section 1 boys'/girls' hoops tournaments… https://t.co/M1Xu0AtQhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhorstkoetter I know it’s real too because I saw the first two attempts you made at tweeting this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilUno Legit didn't see John Wick for 3 years because I knew this happened in the movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOILING THE ISSUE TO SIMPLICITY CHATHLICS LEADERSHIP. DON'T FORGET TO BRING YOUR LIE ABSOLUTE CRIMINAL STATE CHURCH… https://t.co/vj9N593LBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbouie Yeah I am old enough to remember, and man, my parents were not saints, but I can't imagine any parents lett… https://t.co/Br3V1HN3cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were unexpected #Oscar wins, but I still got 15 categories correct. The #AcademyAwards are more interesting with surprises.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN @Espngreeny @JalenRose 28 for 70 in his last 3 games including all star game....apologize for you’re % ...will never win a title]]></document><document><![CDATA[POLITICO Playbook PM: Early takeaways from the Cohen hearing: And the White House kicks out several U.S. reporters… https://t.co/p5SDZ7EbGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cake for Audra's birthday! @ Charter Communications https://t.co/ncakNRBkEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertoVieiraP @GloriaMonteneg @exitosape ROBERTO NO PIERDAS EL TIEMPO LA CONGRESISTA M MONTENEGRO SOLO BOTA VENEN… https://t.co/OMVbEPLnCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s game is LIVE on https://t.co/wM1ZKCfP49, courtesy of @brocktv! 🏒  #WeAreBadgers 🅱️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cynthiadelavega Pfff y yo te amo masss, te diseñaron para generar todos los sentimientos que existen en mi ser]]></document><document><![CDATA[😎 I knocked out my law case brief presentation.💯 https://t.co/2wyrsb2UFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doopa68 brilliant cover pic too. I can tell what religion your family practices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT So very true Maggie. Let’s all reach into our collective pockets and chip in to pay for personal support… https://t.co/3WkBTngnCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@New_Narrative @MalcolmNance Not rooting for it. If he did we need to know and hold him accountable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh there’s a 50/50 chance that I just keep running until they shut us down at 11:00, which would be a pretty big c… https://t.co/XJ8nCUGg5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta @BrianKarem Jeez. How many crosses does this lady own. She wears them like the pillow guy - flaunting. Really gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you never try a thing how do you know that you can not achieve it..? #starttoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greninja216 @AestheticLiquid @RealMyUsername U are acting stupid right now. Learn grammar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[reMARKable comes to Maggiano's Little Italy of Bridgewater Friday, July 12. This performance of magic and hypnosi… https://t.co/ircN3lMm2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaxon time! 😃😃😃 #grandson @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/fg8DqLjYaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone got any theories for what we’re going to see tonight from the True Detective season finale?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADL Thank you for that opinion. I was beginning to wonder. Now, about criticizing Netanyahu and this apartheid he… https://t.co/BmXltP6Ipy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sykiatree @GobAbiertoBOL @HillaryClinton @GabbyGiffords @lucymcbath @SpeakerPelosi Further, 2A says nothing about owning guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear New York,  No 🧢 yall barbers are a different breed. 💈💇🏾‍♂️  Sincerely,  A Young Nigga From the South https://t.co/uIjI0aogkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[TBT to last weekend at Houston @NoraEnPure   💖 She knows how to get her fans pumped up🔥 https://t.co/OsffJ5aUJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[bbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggg farmer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC BETO O"ROURKE WOULD BE GREAT FOR RELIGIOUS TENT REVIVALS ,,IM SURE THERE ARE MORE THAN FEW PEOPLE HE WOULD E… https://t.co/6o56dFakmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The refs are atrocious in this Badger game. The boys are getting hammered down low with no calls]]></document></documents></author>