<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you Cohen for standing up for the truth. You may have lied for whatever reason but many feel you've redeemed… https://t.co/gXQm97jWh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much do I need to make to quit my job? #AshantiattheDMV https://t.co/qdwO4rVmMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a celebration! For George Washington’s birthday today, reenactors are showing us some of the basics about what… https://t.co/Gb1tc2rN4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feministabulous @GeorgeLakoff I agree with @GeorgeLakoff. But come on!   Being passionate about combating climate… https://t.co/0sDGNzqJNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That type of morning🙌🏽🔥💪🏽🏃🏽‍♀️🏋️🏽‍♀️ @ Workout Anytime Leeds https://t.co/sEzBiKlkNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Если бы у меня был стартап по выращиванию искусственного мяса, я бы назвала его Cowbucha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @GordonGChang @realDonaldTrump Watch Rachel Maddow tonight very interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gianna refuses to accept the fact that I live in the same house as her. “Kristin when are you leaving to go back to… https://t.co/sHxK4mdP5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are setting a very high bar for the president's to come after you. They will have to actually… https://t.co/CkyScoCAZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really been out here tryna get a bf since ‘16 but i only had 1 relationship, but yk that didn’t go so well, in conclusion, i hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago I wrote a piece on the instant community I found at #heartcamp18 Not only was it instant, it was lasting… https://t.co/eRjvlSpq0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so ready to build the page at home like a modern, awesome person, but I don't have our main font on my laptop 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evansrand @NBCNews Then the Admin has nothing to worry about, right? I think we should all be able to view the results.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @godfrey_andy and @MemRay to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I… https://t.co/gDUtVFKEOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 very proud of you for acknowledging your errors. ..will be praying for your wife and your children… https://t.co/KAqEf3DiLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you missed my try on yesterday check my stories bc my fav denim dress is selling fast 😩 But who doesn’t love a g… https://t.co/1pi3X1TZSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrshowell24 @JBDbiz @wakelet @RandallSampson He showed me the light, too:) 💙🌊 #WakeletWave #WakeletAmbassadors https://t.co/IRVH3tQqO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilya_poet chooses a poem by @KelliAgodon as the winner of the PSA's Lyric Poem contest! Read the winning poem:… https://t.co/lvqqBsw71k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies come bOOK this lavish full set 😍💎 Natural Set $60 Full Set $70  Hybrid Set $80   #stllashes #stllashtech… https://t.co/TVrGnMtQ1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He cannot be elected even against Trump and he knows it! He is to the left side of the political spectrum what… https://t.co/L6mv8xZqUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Well at Springfield is celebrating our 8th birthday today! We are forever grateful for all who have helped give… https://t.co/oBZY1961eJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is our support, our hope in the midst of the doubts, anxieties, fears and all the inner sufferings we endure. B… https://t.co/T2E0cNLz5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifeline peer project accomplishments: completed over 4000 recovery trainings. Referred over 6000 people to treatme… https://t.co/pH9DPNGD2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[This feels like Sarah Finnegan’s 900th weekly award this season.   (It’s actually her fourth gymnast of the week ho… https://t.co/9qGWR1df3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @becca_hansen3 to post the covers of 7 books I ❤️. No explanation, no review, just t… https://t.co/kfvmAaXhxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1 @_DomoWilson1 I don’t care if it’s 20 you send me I just need anything to help me please   Thank you   $kristinacantu19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I massacred a migraine and then made a bunch of (hospital) people laugh while taking their picture... "Say 'Debridement!'"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I love these new Representatives!!! White men cannot take being fairly questioned. It really irks the… https://t.co/4YT9ckh6uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished Michelle Obama’s ‘Becoming’. Yup, I feel inspired https://t.co/vHeX0yZtZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyeDoogie @Tristan1986 Tris did a great job! Worth watching, for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougboneparth Congrats!  Beautiful baby!! So glad baby and mom are doing well!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr appointment selfie 😂 #breastcancer #surgeon #drappointment #carle #millsbreastcancerinstitute #cancer #baldaf @… https://t.co/ZYS7pGzL30]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @godfrey_andy to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I'll challeng… https://t.co/aSMjhLlZrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeW78246413 @BestGoogleFact 💧 #Japanesemapletree https://t.co/y1Sl6ErTKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasinoJizzones I hereby retract my original tweet. It has taken 38 minutes for my wait time to INCREASE by 10 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I really meet a guy who also enjoys Taco Bell or am I just dreaming ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preference. It’s a fucking preference. There’s something out there you won’t like that someone else will LOVE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Good ! He shouldn't be rewarded for the hoax and made up lies. He made his bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[With patience, tenacity, discipline and a positive spirit, truly great changes can happen. Thank you for coming to… https://t.co/luoXQyk3Fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed on the put away the phone which includes turn off notifications.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan .... most definitely tan... more than just light skins out there ... anyways 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gurdur @Fuchsiarius I am trying to decide if being a sanity bulwark is a good thing. 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[“1080 pixels, my guy.”  -@kennyback44 talking about her eyes after she puts on her glasses. 🥴🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewFrishman This is why @SFIndependence is committed to #deeperlearning and disrupting the “pedagogy of poverty… https://t.co/rqVFigR0kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to get mentioned in this week’s hot pod! The Double Shift has so much good stuff cooking this season.… https://t.co/FSC66Yvn89]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you hurt my best friends feelings then you’re hurting mine as well. Don’t be mean. Think of how others might fee… https://t.co/2FuDXyvp3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never know who you’ll run into in WeHo akidwell87 Chapel https://t.co/OdeCyPykVz https://t.co/piUlnpChh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating undercooked chicken &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; soreness and tightness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bauk1234 @MyKillySoul the writing is incredible, the way she is written as so cold and non caring towards Drew and… https://t.co/SMg3w4PFtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and my baby brother...I'm 5'2" he's 6'3" #maui https://t.co/OoUaaLCsNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackamazon @BreeEssrig My 24ty birthday is on March 16th. Currently, this is my bank account as I can’t work righ… https://t.co/l8b1h9ZeZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally so emotional with love in fictional settings now, it’s actually embarrassing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloé takes the most L’s ... how you go from a crackhead to a serial cheater ...sis just start dating men your own race lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:47am - Shark Kevin O'Leary's feet hit the stage. #Aha #KevinOnWealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s absolutely NO way we are alone in this universe. That’s all I’m saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When everyone is accounted for and we're waiting for the fire trucks, we cuddle and give group hugs to stay warm!!… https://t.co/DJ4bezHB2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love working for an organization where our CEO sends special early morning email mentioning his incredible women ro… https://t.co/OEJxQzq40k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans once again believing whatever their party tells them to believe. You don’t go against the party if you’… https://t.co/vdiwbUHq4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[dance night is tonight @ 7 in marcus!! • • • come support us,, I know you won’t regret it:) @ Marcus, Iowa https://t.co/TsQj4dpEq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity outright lied re: @MichaelCohen212 representing him as a lawyer. I remember when this was first reveal… https://t.co/gC0vGjbsxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstMarkCap’s Annual CRO Summit kicks off! Looking forward to hearing from sales leaders at @LinkedIn, @Square,… https://t.co/VUTR54c96j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adiosbryann @thelaceyclaire Thank you for caring about my health. When I go outside, my skin is protected without… https://t.co/XnHvVfKNPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING first day of  #ExpoWest2019 #calmbeforethecrowds #glutenfreesnacks #cravehealthy #CPG #smartcookies… https://t.co/75XDk3SFqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to watch the reunion again. Define stalker ... Merriam-Webster version .... 🦗🦗#RHONJreunion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lisa82446588  FABULOUS 🌹 Enjoy‼️  Dexy's Midnight Runners - Come On Eileen (Original Promo Restored) (With...… https://t.co/I1Z5ixvTgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Traditional Plan passes today, I have to tell some of my students that they cannot get married one day in a… https://t.co/lUnreC0Cac]]></document><document><![CDATA[That back bend shot though.... #inheels #ingridrachelproject #onlyhere  #kckbackscincy #lastdayofbooze #titos#glowu… https://t.co/Avrlz8km4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! . . . Me working on my Wheel for #doyougetstrong that I posted earlier! I was so bad I couldn… https://t.co/xUSDmuvaVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[New 'Beluga' Airplane Might Be The Cutest Plane Ever @Dodo https://t.co/EYOupYTZQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we pay her salary? This is a direct lie to the American public . (Again)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 @giosuemiraglia @ABHcosmetics i cant wait to get that email AGHHHH what a day that will be. i actually cr… https://t.co/T7oAYQbRpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you thought all that talk about @Nike  shares dropping after #ZionWilliamson’s freak injury, think again.  Pre-M… https://t.co/6qcj8LKfWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelindaYoe @roads2 @KarenSLeonard1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @AnwarManwar004 @Jimmysimmonds1… https://t.co/bgkNXdejNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Bartender $$ Tipped"? What did you like most about that job? #bartender #Ada, OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[the bookstore here is incredible and I found this read I’ve had my eye on for a minnn by @theslumflower 💕 1 for me… https://t.co/SaSeMPPFHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelonelyisland just saw you guys were going on tour! I've enjoyed your content since the days of "Awesometown." W… https://t.co/cm2l11ZjA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Imperial House Parking Management Company in New York, NY https://t.co/hzRzRYHFrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hood_naturalist @SarahMackAttack Omg @RSTurner16 this is right up your alley]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say driving over the potholes, is like riding a roller coaster! Catch @DarrynMooreWSB's next live report in… https://t.co/YbP8HScTFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who hacked India and crystals nudes?? Y’all still leaking nudes...? Grow up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@y2roby @_its_all_good_ @Meraldo2 @MamieCole @GeorgeTakei Bless your poor little ignorant, judgemental, lazy heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I’m leaving with 10 minutes to get to work &amp; I live 25 mins from there]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CPHS_TWolves 11th &amp; 12th graders taking an impaired drive in a simulator - DUI simulation🚨🚔 #CPHSImpact2019… https://t.co/iGb78LGiQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start Your Day With Something Beautiful.♥️ Think ocean breeze. Really WARM ocean breeze. #wednesdaymorning… https://t.co/J4ETh1v7W6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @KamalaHarris Yeah sure, Kamala.....you defended his despicable anti-Trump crime! Maybe you financed it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings I wish you could tell Rep Jim Jordan his time is up and “shut up!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[paris got 5 seconds and they didn’t play any extra songs, twenty one pilots is a SCAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody @lt_gray AMEN! that is my response to everyone taht condemns an officer when they have to make the li… https://t.co/jjFyLxRQMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fragilevixenfic @kyouryokusenshi @xfilesdiaries @SerahSanguine @agoodwoman7 @LuzXRayMD @KikoCrystalBall… https://t.co/Tw9uC5vzIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIRMILES Green with envy here in Ontario...can only imagine what an amazing show it was!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duuuuudddeeee....  This is gonna be rough....  #PoorColton @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix don’t you dare cancel @OneDayAtATime #RenewOneDayatATime #RenewODAAT REPRESENTATION MATTERS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What reputable news organization would hire someone with a NDA signed with someone who needs to be reported on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allexxiaa23 when she though I saw her at the dining hall &amp; didn’t invite me over]]></document><document><![CDATA[No End in Sight to Venezuela’s Blackout, Experts Warn https://t.co/atvnwaLPa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissalvano @hlnkim @JordanDavisPoet She was an employee of the library in an admin position in HR, going through… https://t.co/96KQTZIoxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhatIShouldReallyBeDoing  Taking a risk once in a while!   That's me tight rope walking https://t.co/qDLF6lHsg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDDeezus Bro WDYM “is that shit good?” Bro it’s like the most watched show on earth...what do you think? https://t.co/gJZ1rClSjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i started playing break up with your girlfriend i’m bored in the car and my dad said “don’t change the song. i like… https://t.co/oZFhTEswRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @kev_egan’s name on @SiriusXMFC just now and tuned in just in time to hear him talking about @ATLUTD 😁❤️🖤]]></document></documents></author>