<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Emi_MonteCano POR FAVOR ESTHER YA PASARON 3 AÑOS DÉJAME CONOCER A RAULITO TIENE QUE VER A SU PAPÁ POR FAVOR QUIERO ABRAZARLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Dorsey replaces Jamie Collins, makes way for Austin Corbett in one move]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Well one of the Awan's  was killed in a accident ..... that Arkancide thing ... Maybe I' wrong ... n… https://t.co/KQhlEq1W5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[And in case you wondered, this is how a two-time Pulitzer winner cleans his lens ... if it's good enough for Stan G… https://t.co/rfNVnd6Qp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely on whatever wave you on’ 🌊 #southbeach @ Ocean Drive, South Beach https://t.co/Ao5krhp2IK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remote_orb it's an incredible book- i use it all the time. but there is a reason libraries/Interlibrary Loan exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who opposes language condemning anti-Musli bigotry, which is assuredly rife in Trump's America. (Indeed, post-9/11… https://t.co/XLLiGRRs2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I submitted these three light💡 repairs back in October and again in January to 311 with no avail, @ColumbusDPS… https://t.co/kdEchEkqTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfChannel @APinv @F_Molinari That’s right, he’s the guy that has whipped Tiger Woods butt in match play, especially the Ryder Cup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cari Champion, I respect everything Antonio Brown said. The media is the one saying what he should say and what not… https://t.co/caX1y9uyl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE_MandyRose @Maandyrose You are so sexy gorgeous woman you have good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ravenhaired_sub Its funny though that if i posted something revealing also i would get in a world of trouble lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 69/365 of “The One Year Uncommon Life Daily Challenge” by Tony Dungy and my reflections...  “Dear brothers and… https://t.co/CZuBsfFmkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have come to the day where the saying “dollars to donuts” means “even money.” @PatUnleashed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aeg0717 @charliekirk11 @AdamSchiff I think @RepAdamSchiff should testify in front of Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn_macmahon Rockets looking as good as I’ve seen them look all season. Amazing what a little TEAM basketball will do..]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT WILL COME TO PASS!! !  Don’t let Time taint your THING.  #BePatient  #Wait4It     “In the third year of Cyrus ki… https://t.co/KUL3mA0nB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished #kingdomhearts3 and I am SHOOK. I got the secret ending too and wow what a doozy it was. Thank god al… https://t.co/sb674Tv3pN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mooseletter @Buccigross That photo was taken at the waste management Phoenix open last month.  Believe me,  if it… https://t.co/tiU1OYtOfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of 🏈📚opportunities still exist. CA HS grad can go to a CA JUCO🏛 of their choosing for FREE their 1st 2 semes… https://t.co/09gxcX3M4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[*earnest q*: what’s the last song you heard that fucked up ur entire existence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . . Superchango studio 25901 interstate 45 N the woodlands TX 77318 #superchangostudio #thewoodlandstx… https://t.co/CIMMj3fr8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al Fong, Armine and Mark Williams are on my flight https://t.co/tgVa3JgWoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slipped while dancing with @KrystalVar and let me tell you what, just a shame. I slipped and bounced on my ass on t… https://t.co/EeRb0np1Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eCadence Soundgarden - The Day I Tried To Live https://t.co/XAkpE30sOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not been the same since you stopped wearing the “it’s not just a channel, it’s a family” shirt 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robdoar @_asalwas @paulgazelka @mnguncaucus It gives a concerned friend or family member an opportunity for early… https://t.co/iIA5azm3z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“U.S. History textbook portrays George Washington as country’s 1st president.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[actual rain &gt; the rain sound on my white noise app that i use to drown my existential crises]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York Times: Falls Can Kill You. Here’s How to Minimize the Risk.  https://t.co/cWyBIX0H7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jobforacow @beccalovebutton @beccalovebutton Every single word of this song just flooded my memory like Niagra Falls. Zamn, Zaniel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reybanara Es Perfecto, tengo como dos años de relación que no me pasa eso. Perdí la guera cuando llegue a los 93 kg 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be me when people give me birthday presents 😂 https://t.co/eagzyr9frf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seattle #publicmarketseattle Adios Seatle!!! bety4511 @ Pike Place Chowder https://t.co/gaZ4FmlXMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCommonConsent I think it’s pretty hard to accumulate that much wealth without taking advantage of people. I thin… https://t.co/DgVsCdskCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cover art that I did for one of my friends back in Maryland, new up and coming artist @spacebabyyyyy 🔥🔥🔥GO TAKE A L… https://t.co/aLAJ9pvjP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATP 500 Rio starts today on TSN  R1: Felix Auger Aliassime vs Fabio Fognini   Live on TSN2 at 5PM ET]]></document><document><![CDATA[I allowed myself to eat whatever I wanted all weekend and I’m paying for it big time. I couldn’t even eat my Torchys tacos today 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jérémy Ménez viendo como te haces tonto en tu trabajo. https://t.co/WcUxbdy5AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairbolsonaro @realDonaldTrump Se Trump ainda não tiver sido preso até lá.  Boa sorte, capitão!🤮👉👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaggsKaren @peterbakernyt No that would be the republicans in general...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Photon by @eqbrewery @ Alexandria Fire Station 209 — https://t.co/dIrq3AZbP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometines I think people is going crazy... en The STRAT Las Vegas https://t.co/GzWgjJZfr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DownWithDamon We definitely have bigger needs, but imagine Njoku and Hock 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahLyon @dribeiro_evil @BernieSanders What assumptions? Elaborate please. Fringe maybe. Third parties with int… https://t.co/moz0N1sYUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's a businessman. // Flacco trade: Why it won't make impact for Broncos | https://t.co/HA0WpQCnY9 https://t.co/h624O9SiT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan Where was this ? @BarackObama @HillaryClinton @KamalaHarris @JoeBiden should all denounce this atrocity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HubbardJeff 😂 Pack protein bars, juice boxes, and Zane Grey novels... you'll make a fortune!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know when a new episode of The Drunkalogues may come out because I don’t even know.  Here is… https://t.co/jfkbgFiHTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gonna be a great much up,we will be widnes thanks to team @mikeygarcia and @ErrolSpenceJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to help this little girl fall asleep has to be one of my proudest accomplishments 😊 @ Frankford, Phila… https://t.co/XkRiy7E7jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tom's Bar &amp; Grill in Saint Louis, MO https://t.co/SQuU1OLgnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneValicenti ask Dot are jersey barriers secured to ground especially along elevated route 6/10 connector.  Could… https://t.co/cu19MKENfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I say @veracruztacos but consult with local expert @elmundodemando  of @tacojournalism for the full Austin experience]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna go ahead and congratulate Lebron James for moving up to 4th NBA scoring list passing Jordan, before my Tw… https://t.co/YYqXfFIyq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[An @Ookay group of guys 😜#simshows #throwback #skywaytheatre #badhabitstour @ Skyway Theatre https://t.co/mD6zmvjQBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryCallahan The blind leading the blind! Pride is soooo dumbass blinding in most cases! This one is deplorable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CjornHoulio Man I wish. They only gave us Friday tickets they’ve been on lockdown for a few years. Sorry all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nunya_Bizznizz  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Another lawsuit is filed against the ME’s office. We’ll have this full report on #GoodMorningLubbock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraftDiamonds That’s the official time? Because his second run was a 4.46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apesar de los grises y de los cambios, te agradezco un día más que me has regalado con mis seres queridos 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SofiaEscobosa @jasiaflores Yo pensé  que le andaba pegando al vergas haciendo sus caras]]></document><document><![CDATA[AYYYYEEEE 😂 Bopperzz #LaurelHigh my Sophomore year this shit took over lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone I fucked with first on this app blocked me and I just found out last week]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are not at the table you are on the menu. Join the AMA to make sure that your voice is heard at the table.… https://t.co/kUEFysOLp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my best friend @alexpowdrell_ and she is a beautiful human being who I am lucky to know. This video is shor… https://t.co/X3UCgI55Bz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders running again is literal hell on earth....hell on earth I tell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freepsports @tigers @DetroitPodcast He isn't the only MLB player out there today who can't make it they the huge c… https://t.co/rQp0GgRiuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Liberals always root for the worst for America.  Take notice. Must be miserable being a liberal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still not a fan of Bono. Never have been. Enjoy your hate, Giovinco fanboys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brentsampson14 @kinsellawarren I had the same thought. Best wishes for the next stage of his life !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdie17946566 @john_starke @TheAlanNoble Well you can look forward to years of reading about the little truck bec… https://t.co/jkBSqUKCIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on February break this week, but I am writing the next chapter of my Latin I class novella “Aluna et Caelius” t… https://t.co/DGGjJidLfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tschwing32 Ha! Have to bite your tongue sometimes. It does say a lot about Linton though that Hale can be bad, and… https://t.co/wl0oenIqBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The look on your face when you’re in the wrong worship service on Sunday because you forgot it was… https://t.co/Pirayx5PXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Missouri's 1st Congressional District https://t.co/oeYKgmcYYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently I’ve become a total insomniac and eyes tell the story. What’s on my subconscious? Data analysis, writing,… https://t.co/wR99h6gORq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChampions @torontofc @CAIPanama Same awful defence. Same terrible midfield. Same idiotic 433. Vanney doesn't ha… https://t.co/DJSZfZFuaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mctait on with @nick_schwerdt sounding like John mox from varsity blues. Just one guy hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm I would shut Luka down..too valuable..but alas.he wouldn't stand for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[RODRIGUEZ, JOHNATHAN ANTH charged with POSSESSION CONTROLLED SUBSTANCE PG 3 &lt;28 GRAMS in #HOUSTON - https://t.co/9nTn3ZzAPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 14859 Telegraph #SantaPaula #CA  #realestate https://t.co/GAkVFlEMK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casaochoa An explanatory footnote with APA- format citation was, of course, provided. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a @hornets victory Saturday with a win over the conference rival @washwizards Keep Moving on up!!! #nba… https://t.co/RqsU8UktlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelongshot25 @cordagefan @SolomonKB @TheRealMarkCM @PalmerReport @JohnCornyn Obviously took offense to, and began… https://t.co/KJu0iKh7Uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, had our rental broken into tonight and a bunch of our stuff stolen! Lost @steveslagg s camera and luggage,… https://t.co/QB30BAhaH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#23 ya está disponible. EL HAPPY HOUR STRIKES BACK! ¡Más interactivo, más incoherente, más incordio que nunca! Desd… https://t.co/Fq3DEGR3Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Good morning Mr. President.  I trust you slept well? ...*snicker snicker*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier The younger they are, the less educated they are about socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl I am on the other side of your politics completely. But I can’t help myself liking you because I see your… https://t.co/Blku4ek3BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things are just amusing. Comic - Twilight's First Day #3 by muffinshire.devia... #comedy #tee-hee #smirk… https://t.co/6aFeWTietl]]></document><document><![CDATA[De repente deu saudade dessa paisagem... em Golden Gate Bridge https://t.co/0UHWPe8sdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_White @Paula_White Good Morning! Prayers you, @TheJonathanCain your @ndccOrlando @TheRealPWM team, and famil… https://t.co/cqwREiL24D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at Clovis West (29-3) as the No. 3 seeded Golden Eagles take on No. 14 Menlo-Atherton (24-4) in the first roun… https://t.co/fAG4tKfuSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darren_aus @WomenforTrump I DON'T WANNA BE NICE! https://t.co/kIgeAFzFGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahmgluck She’s a cutie love watching the different kids growing up on twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DETsportschat @Lions Because he will get hurt again.. guys injury prone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoAwayGreen @disneygoff @TomKMorris I was Instagram/Twitter, before social media]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s was such a pleasure directing this video to celebrate Rami #stompstompclap #RamiMalek #uet03 #BohemianRhapsody]]></document></documents></author>