<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[not to b dramatic but my grandpa use to make me dig holes when I got in trouble before I even saw the movie so NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loschivoskrew🐐🐐🐐 #mybikeleaningonstuff #dallasbrakeless #dallastx @ Oak Cliff Brewing Co https://t.co/K9EXc7OzTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @MsLynneMiller @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/vyEliCBKY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You know how many people hate oysters but never tasted one? I think about that shit everyday” @garyvee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonWLewis thanks for coming and sharing about Thailand 🇹🇭 https://t.co/7z9JOjKtKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spudly77 Sadly the players prob care less about the new stadium than the fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tailopez @DopeDances Her: "Did you fold the clothes like I asked?"  You:]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe that:  Any land owner that crosses the border knows the government reserved the right to enforce and impr… https://t.co/Ho0yyTPifJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night shredding pow at Brighton. It's dumping.Tomorrow will be epic. https://t.co/WHp49MzW1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’re not busy, you’re just #scrolling through. Stop and vote on this poll while you’re here though! My dea… https://t.co/h2BOFXZSuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introduced our foster to hockey tonight and he has not taken his eyes off the TV https://t.co/KClp8roGa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its amazing how ppl seems to forget the gas prices during Obama's presidency. Way below $2 a gallon. Also how he en… https://t.co/zfBG7kZ6yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re: Biscuits and Blisters. @mistymarierae writes like an old woman except when she don’t. She writes of a lost worl… https://t.co/bIrwbp97VU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Your logic is flawed. He lied before and is going to jail in part because of it. So now he won’t lie… https://t.co/X9hCSIQohk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guillecapora @AATenis @puppotenis De esto me preguntaban muchos Argentinos amigos #tenistas de @keybiscayne y se m… https://t.co/iyJclNxtKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmayemsinger @netflix It’s Netflix DVD upgrade, it’s like extra 10$ a month]]></document><document><![CDATA[He seems to believe that the flag will save him from going to Federal Prison For The Next Few Years! BYE FELICIA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[By far, my favorite part of my birthday yesterday. Thanks @glax_redraiders https://t.co/rc666b0xLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marisa_Ingemi Do you remember https://t.co/kNdKAItHtt? Basically that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soxxyfan got this one available, silver spectrum /5 Auto BGS 9/10! https://t.co/9EGurCFmpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time spent with any of my kids is just AWESOME!  coaching my son and this amazing group of 6th grade boys this week… https://t.co/q8uuvFtXOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When is the Ironton Buffalo Wild Wings and the Portsmouth Schmitt Group gonna get their act together? @BWWings, eve… https://t.co/Ff5xTumn9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mick_muldoon @Torikit @MikeStuchbery_ @gillksharp1 @tom_watson Yes. "anyone else without his long record of bullsh… https://t.co/0X0KYmlfpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the one! - Drinking a Birth of Hops #8 (Idaho 7) by @LevanteBrewing at @LevanteBrewing  — https://t.co/nQ1pqAFpGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been telling everyone @ZO2_ is the real deal! Best defensive PG in the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FC_CoachShav @KyleSandy355 We need someone to cover baseball beside us Dad’s..lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @hunterpierce97 are starting a GoFundMe for a kangaroo it’s only $5000 so stand by and donate to make our dream come true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeySovine Hopefully this is not a preview of what our spring is going to be like. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce That's funny right there I don't care who you https://t.co/gJEo33dYxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Say the sweaty fat liar.   What the count as of today. https://t.co/QZYCAyvwDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work so hard yet I’m still under appreciated....by nearly everyone. nobody wants to hear excuses they just need r… https://t.co/tp7SLE24di]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk all ye want but what’s tone said? He lied and the left happily played along, probably to help #HeelsUpHarris p… https://t.co/hcQrmtpCmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made my ❤️ smile!  I am so excited to get to meet this little guy face to face!  @LauraThomasNKC I’ve got big… https://t.co/NO5MgBj6Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what anyone says, BLAIR carried #GossipGirl on her back. Without her the show wouldn’t have lasted 2 seasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog I am a federal contractor and many of my colleagues were either furloughed or forced to work for free f… https://t.co/bIhKQtFp22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DieBoogeyman @TrialsGames Yeah. It’s more of the point. I wanted the gorilla suit lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresClinton had Many investigations on him by #Republicans but #Republicans could only #Impeach on Oral Sex in Off… https://t.co/unmHDDQY9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud of the way these ladies finished the season. Unfortunately we couldn’t close it with a championship, but… https://t.co/omdXkfvIB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGlantz3 @sternshow @cwotd @HowardStern @shalomshuli @MFBrooklyn @diamond_mike23 @askjillian @Misstabstevens… https://t.co/x4II6o4UGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karol I don't think it was the unpopular president, what the GOP has not grasped is of 53 house seats in CA the De… https://t.co/CIQ4mXisgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDavSmith I think if you’re signing a guy like AB to win now you absolutely keep Mack too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBM Can you spot the legend that is @DonnaExplorer ??? Great to see a rockstar IBMer in the advert #MadeMyDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@om_eye_goodness Tell her every day. She's across the country, so it's by phone or message, but she hears it daily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisZellner What happened? Did Kofi tell Dolan to #SellTheKnicks? @nyknicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to show my appreciation towards these hoes for saving me so many times and making me laughter when I'm… https://t.co/OWfgyS9Y4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUmarkwoods @SanMarcoTrain The only redeeming things about I-4 are @FloridaPolytech in Lakeland and the Ted Baker outlet in Orlando.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLayingUp @bsfantasyfeed Soly is actually being generous...it was way over two minutes. That memory still brings instant laughs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmittman I agree with what you said about class discussions in gen eds, and enjoyed the way you wrote about the… https://t.co/RzTFoXyRqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it interesting that advocates for Chick-Fil-A, Hobby Lobby, etc don’t see this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumb_librarian @voluntaryreboot I brought it on myself by taking on the Virbank admin thing so I don't complain.… https://t.co/WATH9OAP3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't get Huawei is a bad guy by now you should probably find other work. https://t.co/o2OzmnW1Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio Farm Bureau Federation Farmers’ Breakfast: Fred Yoder, Madison County Farmer, gave a great presentation. He in… https://t.co/LcbFd4SBVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottOsborne67 @parscale @Nike @realDonaldTrump Make Nike Great Again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was the best Rocky movie? I think 1 is the best but I really like how over the top 3 and 4 were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just finally sold our house today. Man, our landlord going to be pissed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spencer Lee Morgan (@expensivespence) is now advertising in Atlanta! https://t.co/s97fgM6A2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Hillary, With your position on abortion and infanticide you have no right talking about children in detention. Go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to keep riding the BIG BUS all day  Or   You want to change to world  Again  Your choice Steve   -&gt; @SteveCase   I'm here for ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukebasketball Zion Williamson will not play tonight against UNC. Yesterday coach K said he would not rule him out… https://t.co/5gPkf6jcPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerryxJohnson  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren @rudegirrl13 We need a moderate Democrats, not socialism or far right. All spell disaster to the American… https://t.co/6dvgHQf3IR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Crossing Across................ #sunday #weekend #igs_america #ig_northamerica #instamood #popular… https://t.co/ebc6lyZrtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jayden Brewer is not playing around.  @OrioleAthletics are running away with this one. 50-31 with 3:04 to play.… https://t.co/cb16TqXNPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdekstrand Being found guilty leaves him vulnerable to civil suits? No mention of driving privileges. Is being dru… https://t.co/2WGXFgEMnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we totally losing touch with reality? It seems we are accepting more violence than addressing it. This is uniqu… https://t.co/Gsr7MgcuIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're not a blubbering mess at the end of all that, next step is #StarWarsRebels . Different animation style, a… https://t.co/F5BgL7Dp1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant believe I'm saying this but I actually like a guy that DOESNT have a giant penis. 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[The U.S. set a new record for the number of migrant families caught crossing its southern border over an entire yea… https://t.co/G7XJ2f2Xp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at a wedding shower and I've had like 2 or 3 mimosas, a glass of moscato and I'm drinking a bloody mary now. Oh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fog has drifted in, creating some stunning scenery this evening. #hanoverpa #fog #fogphotography #nature… https://t.co/g56n7RDb1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[UnFun Fact: me and my bestie live 40 minutes away from each other ON A GOOD DAY💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kady Not surprised. When a man makes a promise (I.e. electoral reform) and then walks it back you realized he’s ju… https://t.co/bxygvC9kOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Hanagriff #Omaha -9.5 (bought down the hook) vs #WesternIllinois getting back in the winning track]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday @larry_kudlow When Larry speaks the market shines.When FED chair speaks it tanks. The past 3 mths, h… https://t.co/7zSUSDHOKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[bout to go live my best life and do hood rat shit with my best friends 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you look in a mirror  and only see you reflection  you are not looking hard enought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvmidd85 @feraciousfrank @MAGAGirl8 @Kfuller8870 @John_R_Berna @Libphobic @Psychictaxi @mbales250 @j_ankrom… https://t.co/0PxmDntmwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccaballhaus @maggieNYT But you went to him for real estate advice. Right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[how rude is it that you can't watch the final credits to a movie on @netflix without be ushered into another movie or show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow! @Neville_Garnham Much Appreciated! Humbled to know I have fans “down under!” #MillennialAdvocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @Lakers @Suns @KingJames Perhaps LBJ should let His teammates run the offense n try blending in more… https://t.co/GVSXrQQh2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Bolton has no "cojones" and he's an opportunist kiss ass. He is Trump's bitch!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever have an ugly cute chick? they ugly and cute at the same time...like a weird kind of cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's what he did with rock and Austin and Hogan and flair and Savage and warrior and @TripleH and @ShawnMichaels… https://t.co/UIkSBaoBPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfGodAndMan @AntonFletcher6 Thanks for making me laugh Jesus. Goodnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moe making all my tweets null and void lately. I knew it would work. #RipCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at University of Southern California - @usc in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/1gOE4yyq2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zack_bitcoin You can also set up a thermal sensor and hook it up to a fire extinguisher (is there are only a few and it's a remote place).]]></document><document><![CDATA[KKM Results: Shamrock Classic - 3/9/19  Logan: 6th Tucker: 10th Holley: 11th Jesse: 12th Tanner: 13th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson's songs have put radio stations around the world at a crossroads  https://t.co/qB2A4yuj1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las industrias ganaderas y avicolas son desleales con la humanidad, la envenenan con hormonas en sus cárnicos. https://t.co/YhJtjI3AQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt You have such a small world. Men respect their families grandma mother wife's and daughter's then th… https://t.co/9m2b9SiAAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDntLUHdeezHOES @IsntSheaLovely @DorianAleccia @Tawain_model13 Lol fran he really ain’t shit SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/dnPK8RwC9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terry_go_online @Ms_Riley_Guprz Dude... there are... https://t.co/TFYvLaYM3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Covers_Vegas Is there a worry that a spring training player is easier to buy off to throw a game? I mean.. it woul… https://t.co/u9CKOWyuE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What promising #FASD news and efforts from MN Rep. Richardson, MN Sen. Relph, Proof Alliance (fka MOFAS), Rebecca W… https://t.co/xJlhb0X47L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.. just wow.   16 Unexpected Discoveries People Found In Their Food That Even An Archaeologist Would Be Jealous… https://t.co/NbyLJ5njfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winding_sios @hkh_uk @redditchrachel a free trade agreement, during which after the 29th of March the UK can indep… https://t.co/8iSACIKJki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefAyotte @OttawaFirePIO @OttFire Congrats @OttawaFirePIO well done! 👍 Keep up the great work]]></document></documents></author>