<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 2821 N Ocean Blvd # 405 S #FortLauderdale #FL  #realestate https://t.co/PIZ3QgVDtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body of missing 58-year-old grandfather with dementia found, family says https://t.co/us0OtYtowj Details at 6:14 a.… https://t.co/QRcAHUEGTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I learned my lesson this time. Never will I ever be friends with a group of all girls again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌇Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🏙Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🏙This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/A6yG6LBHzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men marched asleep. Many had lost their boots But limped on, blood-shod. All went lame; all blind; Drunk with fatig… https://t.co/rgITu5t6Ab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 That's lovely Eva!! Your mum got to see your new place. Not surprising she loved it. 😊🌞👍👋☕️😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[El comentarista de @beINSPORTSes dice lo que en Argentina nadie se anima a decir: " El árbitro no cobra ni una falt… https://t.co/hUhJV6Y0Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguimos siendo el noticiero número 1 de nuestra región! Gracias valle de Texas #DecemberRatings #Telemundo40 https://t.co/J6bWJmhUZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadEyesArt So random but, I needed to read this. Literally got water and my dog too so I’m prepared haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoaddogAmerica @DGrimes2 You can't even speak American let alone proper English.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosBolsonaro Pedofilia é CRIME SIM!!!! Não me venham com essa papagaiada de “é uma patologia”! E a pena tem que… https://t.co/7PemEqr5od]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG OMG OMG DAY REDEEMED! On WUOT the host said “It’s four twenty!” Not “20 after 4”, not “20 minutes past the hour… https://t.co/aR1Ivor1ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the dumb men: 🗣🗣 whatever a woman chooses to wear does NOT give you the right to touch her inappropriately. Per… https://t.co/vsyeIBNgtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stats are in! Here is a snapshot of the #Guelph #realestate market for the month of #February 🏡🔑 • • •… https://t.co/afPDno4Oj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote NO on HB836. Take one minute to help out with No to HB836, No to Adoption Discrimination. https://t.co/lg4OjnQq2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demi is so funny. I love Hannah B laughing at the drama. #TheBachelor #WomenTellAll]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Monday I wasn’t swimming in paper work in months. I LOVE having an assistant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep - its that time for me once again. I seem to be on a 2 year rotation. Unprecedented number of jurors called in… https://t.co/hlema8wd4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monterogabriela que se puede esperar de la Lazo cuando es la mentora de la hija del HP Diosdado Cabello https://t.co/6wYRKf7EJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the book cover challenge from @kcbrown3 to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations, no revie… https://t.co/Twz0akjNJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @AnaCabrera Can you also find a way to mention passing of #HR1? This is what we want our country to be consumed with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really be confused when niggas on my TL say they don’t fuck with black women so why tf you followed me my nigga?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these years later, and I STILL get anxiety nightmares before an observation. In last night’s, my classroom was… https://t.co/ejTi358C3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He’s not dumb, he’s just stupid” Thank you for clarifying @kristinhubble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joearrigo I heard they were considering playing some pre season games this August. It would be cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbouzy Yes, I would have gone public as soon as he took my pension away. I'm not buying his bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @RepAdamSchiff "Maher told him again he should go on Fox. “I will go,” Schiff said."  LOL! Last time s… https://t.co/tSr7vrVwl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious #selfies. #latergram #LosAngeles #love @ Bestia DTLA https://t.co/MRT5NE15BO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the secret dungeon restaurant of La Esquina, super cool place! #resturants #foodie #dungeon #basement #bars… https://t.co/Qv2dJP01Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok this is nearly all true, except the hellmans mayo part. It has to be the McCormick mayonesa con limon lol all ot… https://t.co/sGgF7YQFod]]></document><document><![CDATA[They ask me, where I'm from? Where I come from? Or what is my ethnicity and I say... "I'm radiant and a Mermaid"… https://t.co/4vaFngneXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to see @cypheroftyr talk tomorrow at #SXSW2019 #sxsw also Tanya is the greatest name in the world. 🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cordellclass ♥️ this story. Astonishing characters. Flawless writing. Begs to be read aloud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CastleLeoch Part3 revisited - ‘you mean as your prisoner don’t you’ -@outlander_starz Series 1 - #catrionabalfe… https://t.co/EIMKLhrgHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter walk on the beach.  #seagull #beach #oregoncoast #centraloregoncoast #lincolncityoregon #taftbeach… https://t.co/Qza21mj4wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @CaththeWineLady @SteveKubota @joneill55 @Cbp8Cindy @jflorez @SideHustleWino @SashaEats… https://t.co/hDNvLoQqg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefourmonkeys @YandR_CBS I think it's Summer because she's jealous. This is Pay Back for what she did at the Abbo… https://t.co/IJPR2DWRlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right because mosquitos report their infections to the department of health. 😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnk777 @realDonaldTrump Thanks!The more information we can use against dtrump, the quicker he will be out the do… https://t.co/3B0ad8Zf74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Examination of inflammatory markers in midlife, and risk of cognitive decline.                Systemic inflammation… https://t.co/ZJuYGkQK3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods It is not news that a man beats out a woman in a race or wrestling or whatever. This allowing them… https://t.co/09exoPand1]]></document><document><![CDATA[But since Trump has become president I've found common cause with many of the same people I had a hard time listening to before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight #findom. Remember you’ll never be more than a little bitch and you’re only allowed to hump your pillow when I tell you you can 🖕🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrenDreger Cap floor concerns for Ottawa?  (We Coyote fans are familiar of such things...)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StylesPromoTeam @HarriezZzZz #StillTheOne #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that there’s nothing at all to do at night like I feel like I need to get up and do something right now but… https://t.co/kpo9sMAkGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce great job filling in for @IngrahamAngle!! Really enjoyed the show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea @adamknott777 @BlakandBlack @Watershedd It is the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost lunchtime!!! With ALL this SNOW #TheBistro will open a little LATE today for your lunchtime listening p… https://t.co/2jcR2EiFnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olayinkaojoR10 @joemhirsch How fun! I am searching Audible right now. Great pic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanMombie Perfect example of why we must have school choice.  Our public schools are awful.  Even the "good"… https://t.co/mPyG4bgEpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[on the Upper East Side with my current three roommates and expensive ass Pomeranian puppy]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s okay if you did me dirty i’m not gonna go outta my way to hurt you lol. God always gotchu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Normans_Edits @i_GhostTwd @ringleader1010 @fuckedchic @ItsKatieLester @Stef_Helen @Walkingdeadluv3 @twdandmetal… https://t.co/W04pIZnnAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new MI kulture pins are in! They will go out FREE with every order, and we will hold a drawing in our group onc… https://t.co/j2lSoMiGLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I️ am completely in awe of the wonderful student media publication @kentwired, they find another way to as… https://t.co/BqMflTQvdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that the Mad man?!🤣😜😂Thor an Tequila love to attack the water! They should be called GerMán Water Dogs😜😂 @ South… https://t.co/gnuZ5o5vD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night we belatedly celebrated @RealRonHoward’s bday. #Salute2Ron https://t.co/cyPibdSQ9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band that sounds like Hollywood undead just used “New York hardcore” as a mosh call out]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day a year ago, I spoke out on a stage in front of strangers about being raped. I’ll forever be so proud of… https://t.co/vI0pBLTmLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we not talking about these photos more? #ManCrushMonday https://t.co/G7Yao7DlHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'M JAMMING FUTURE😎 RAIDO.... MY FAVORITE💖 #1 FUTURE HENDRIX..... LUV YA😎💜🙏💖😘 https://t.co/EaXCDTVBZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we put together all the penguin research puzzle pieces during our group report jigsaw! #savethepenguins @ Ma… https://t.co/cc25T4IRLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is pervert Jim Jordan even allowed to ask questions? He should be in jail himself!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think someone on my flight just asked if they sell beer. This is definitely the earliest I've ever heard that question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelloBello will you have a pull up line ? My little guy is allergic to everything but Huggy diapers but he’s being… https://t.co/9Mufj3kdUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesleyThreshold @IntelligenceDoc @_danhabib @lesley_u So tricky!!!👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will have to believe me that, that is a puppy named Fiona who is in trouble for going poop and pee it the house… https://t.co/rtvFFrgxKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent my 87yr old moms “care package” yesterday with all her favorite snacks during Cleveland Indians games. I’m h… https://t.co/ew2Bje6Y5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crampell What goes around comes around. Depending on the backlash to the Trump/McConnell years in 2020 the Republi… https://t.co/O4gvtcivuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Angela Bassett is 60 years old and she looks goddamn amazing #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you read text differently because of technology? #readacrossamerica2019 meets #DigitalLearningDay… https://t.co/jXrDSqsX2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tefguy @kare11 @kare11wx Hi! Thanks for your concern. We got off the highway right where they have it shut down. 3… https://t.co/EFX7ncYqW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a massive fan of taylor’s personal essays but Elle has so many talented writers who deserve these big features :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God 🙏 R. Kelly Charged With 10 Counts Of Sexual Abuse https://t.co/682wZxqtLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissDahlELama Oh, you should DEFINITELY try them. It was like an adventure for my tastebuds. No regrets 😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Righteous Individuals Performing Law Inforcement Directives Rapidly Againt Gordon Our Nemesis @nbcbrooklyn99… https://t.co/OTKsuwfKgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khalees89459309 @ChipotleTweets Vegetarian not vegan. Vegans do not consume any animal products including dairy https://t.co/nwXE7OLP3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mister_Fuman @gregorytangelo You are the definition of bias. When you accept a business not baking a cake for gays… https://t.co/tMU3MF7mAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidPaulJenner @IlhanMN @isupportisrael_  @aoc @AJCongress @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer  Quit treating @Ilhan like… https://t.co/GrvN9WtlIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is brilliant! By the way my birthday is one day after years so that means you are a very intelligent creative… https://t.co/m0EMCzZamK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your president has our safety in mind, unfortunately, you have lost your mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ужас какой ветрище дует! Снаружи завывает, сайдинг, крыша - все скрипит. Лес шумит, гудит, как-будто оживленная тра… https://t.co/X0vjHcCWsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frenchifry @DavidPa86766073 @ssemekim @Gwtw121 @HoarseWisperer You certainly can tell who is a republican. Instead… https://t.co/b5MpyT3ka4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senato Romano “If this doesn’t pass will we run the Governors bill to still give the teachers a raise?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol at people who pass you in the turn lane then meet them at the red light. #smoothmoveexlax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your support of Nazis makes you the LAST person that should talk about anti-semitism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Situated on almost an acre you will love this beautiful home in the heart of Parkins Mill. Contact me to learn more… https://t.co/7rJYv0BUbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[MFAH lecture of Sally Mann’s A Thousand Crossings exhibition. @ The Museum of Fine Arts, Houston https://t.co/CYdeYzb0En]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is starting  to rain here at Celebrity Corner but volunteers like @FresnoPolice Chief Dyer and @FresnoFire Chief… https://t.co/0hoQY9q2KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of being terrified to talk about how I feel or anything important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajaja veo a los plebes tomar vodka y me dan ganas de vomitar... que buenos tiempos 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowAboutThatJaz @adambencloutier @Shawn_Smith1 Pizza followed by ice cream is the way to handle that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here refreshing YouTube twitter and it hoping for a miracle to see my as one of the winners I’ll die iconic… https://t.co/pzv1UiyFo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Följ med mig till Alby och stötta dessa ungdomar som skrivit en bok om det dödliga våldet. Bokrelease i Alby om gat… https://t.co/HLaNTapwOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenFeinstein: Oppose the Trump admin's changes to Medicare Part D to protect progress fighting the HIV epidemic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeniusItech Hi Mahmoud, we have vast experience in mobile app development and would be happy to build your restaur… https://t.co/wL0m4BcQE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found some Jamaicans at school today 😢🤧. When I heard the accent I was like https://t.co/dvifWgfYE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlenHansonNYC Her retort about burned champagne is truly my favorite Dynasty quote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJesselyn @Kelebration @ThePlumLineGS @SpeakerPelosi And the pot calling the kettle black]]></document></documents></author>