<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN  Don’t worry sis , we are with you on this . You are a truth sayer and they are liars . They are all lying… https://t.co/h8mmqr2WUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nisleecita Buenas noches me voy a dormir unas horas antes de regresar a la lucha por la luz y la democracia. No es… https://t.co/9nDnE2OYO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[First match back since Japan so I am scratching to get in that ring!!! First time wrestling in Ohio and first time… https://t.co/462lj0xMAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[College is over rated by people who didn’t go. It was juvenile when I went in the 70’s. It’s only gotten worse.The… https://t.co/NJTo42oWCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know. This my fav right now. @Thebadplus https://t.co/WosfTYq14M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My silly cashmere goats Cocoa &amp; Penny enjoying Maine snow today. https://t.co/tXQ8igTyfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mensfashion #malemodeling #beachattire #stleo #stleouniversity #walmartfinds #headbands #sunglasses https://t.co/1EwyTTzX3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonGlobe Why are political reporters incapable of describing politics without using boxing or war terminology]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellenjdasilva Bet you look adorable. (sorry that probably annoying!!)😜💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entertaining at the Bel Air Bay Club. #corporateentertainment #eventprofs #cabaret #show #magic #magician @ Los Ang… https://t.co/Isojx1Y21y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khrispayne Yo I just spoke to Ben, he randomly also said your boy smooky is on that track cuz we talking about pub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizNBntown Who said? McCabe? The guy who was fired for breaking 3 ethics violations (lying) There is no evidence of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hekglez @Eltiotonysoy @molotovmx @TiburonJaro8 @AkireLincho @Paul_Pellon @TuiteraMx @MIEF_WRATH @elhombredelsol… https://t.co/bSazL6WGr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley @camanonana @realDonaldTrump Thank you for clarity on the use of National Emergency Powers Senator,… https://t.co/zgr3epy9YR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diamond_Jax @notcapnamerica Wow, must’ve been in the Hamptons or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyzarzycki At this point does his tax returns matter?  Who cares if his net worth is between 1 and 5 million?… https://t.co/zzbCaGzWXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss the finale! I directed the first of these final two episodes, and it’s a humdinger!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 a.m workout this time weights. I am so sore from Monday it maybe slow. #InsaneLabz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it take @SpeakerPelosi are you scared of @IlhanMN? She is a scary Muslim. Am I Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in #MountainGreen! Tell me what you think!  #realestate https://t.co/JJnWj8q8xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joke. It will be a ,I love me celebration for the biggest disgrace of a president in the history of the coun… https://t.co/aI6WNJivg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THFC_Rob16 @SA_THFC @KatherineRupp @chicagospurs Do it mainly for the night out with the boys. It’s a great time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSBN @dylanmatt #abolishpublicsectorunions  Or at least police unions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeedeeKIRO7 @TracyTTraffic @KIRO7Seattle Ugh. Hope you make it wherever you are going. Otherwise, I hope you settl… https://t.co/2LsDJ9WwZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to 2019 Rebekah Atilano(@balla___2 ) for making 1st Team All-District in District 21-6A! One of the hardes… https://t.co/hhYrvjak5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to my boo that ain't really my boo cause you in a relationship with someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our third stop of the day was a visit to @intel campus.   #HouTechMission delegation had a working lunch with… https://t.co/oAMZTgLKcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom The Democratic Party has allowed the radical Muslims to take over and drive their party direction]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very interesting session @THINK #think2019 with Fresche Solutions #BP #GBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great pic. They’re smiling because they know they did something amazing and one day finishing second won’t hurt (ne… https://t.co/DotXr2h8Oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC To their credit, the West Virginian Republican Party did denounce the poster &amp; the hate speech it represented.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks I don't necessarily agree with the original policy, because I think it would be self-evident that on… https://t.co/SobJ8RbTv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tariqnasheed @JackPosobiec And there you have it boys &amp; girls, definitely a #HateCrime. #JussieSmollett hates himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @kellyjohnsonhas Hey Donald, the ants (all you are guilty of) will kill and consume the scorpion (you). @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Family Day 2019, hope the outdoors were involved ! #BruceTrail 5 min walk from our house - we don’t use it en… https://t.co/Mzt6tTeZmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwarshaw14 @empiregass @andrew_wiebe @MattDoyle76 Figured I could count on you Bobby 👌🏼 again, very much appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanDutra @MerlinCalo @doza321 @CausewayStreet @Dart_Adams Oh wait, you’re implying Kyrie has beef with Stevens. I see now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who was Agency DIR from 2012- 2016? [AGENCY DIR] [JOHN PERRY BARLOW] How did we know (prior to)? Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[universally accepted that *redacted* is the physical embodiment of… https://t.co/Vtww6Bu0rD]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is straight gangster social swag @MrPeanut. Pop that monocle like you own the joint, because right now you do.… https://t.co/4zpgSwTSNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roger_mace @ShawnG927 @Navy_Lady_45 @beckman_fredric @junogsp7 @ArizonaKayte @MagaGoldHat @cindy_nurse… https://t.co/oYwGoU4ZT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockets were still in the game and D’Antoni &amp; Paul gave the Lakers the game by getting Techs. 🛑 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Finally! SOMEBODY understands what I was going for” -God, watching Trump sign bibles]]></document><document><![CDATA[The basics always work.These type of  movements will be the source of the Strong Body Transformation (c) program, l… https://t.co/lAPYBW5HJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash headline should read democrats preparing to subpoena anyone Not agreeing with current narratives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmcmahon @kphellothere Those are, supposedly, Ronny Cox's hands actually playing the banjo  His name is Popcorn!?!!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and Earn Yours!! https://t.co/kTqiPySkeB #HOWLSEA2ON @StonyBrookFB https://t.co/8zrmVRPPPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Campbell passes to O’Connor for two! 21-17 LHS @hoops_jacket https://t.co/7vIszeqPCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is sort of a cheesy reflexivity  that is the engine of the pop side of social media.  The same tropes get end… https://t.co/vBiDblqMT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Processing a sample is lowkey more fulfilling than making a sound from scratch.......except snares i need to make m… https://t.co/zajhvjW0Sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christ sets us free so that we can become the people God created us to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwolffnj he met with staffers to discuss it and apologized via twitter, among other apologies he’s made- quite the… https://t.co/4Fu14BHv8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMBradshaw19 That thread is everything. @jamiestowell @AmandaHerridge will likely agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY @kaylaafromm ❤️🎈2️⃣1️⃣🎉🎉 WISH MY PHONE WASNT BROKE SO I COULD MAKE A FLIPAGRAM OF ALL THESE CRAZY PI… https://t.co/ctzTL9l0we]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you miss the presentation? Drop@by @hl7 booth #4849 at 4:10 for another chance to learn “what’s next for… https://t.co/req9v3HkHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eRewardsUS It'll take 20 minutes to boil 10 eggs! #eRewards #Solved 🥚😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump You are pretty pathetic Tina. You’d think with such a large Mellon for a head that you… https://t.co/heMbTfcsz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @FrankMurphyCom looks like a spot has finally opened up. @clydetombaugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCopeRacing , I wish the ol'  Purolator Lumina was in today's #DAYTONA500 lineup. Good luck to your team today.… https://t.co/ZHc7GYrzT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to garbage nuggets fans, players can’t have bad games. I do not associate with these horrible fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I took my demons into the bank of life and I made the biggggest deposit”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simultaneously thrilled at the banquet of exceptional SF we’re currently enjoying, and anxious at the very thought… https://t.co/ugr8pEbqCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClimaPeruMundo @ClimaciudadLima La tres estan ubicadas entre cordilleras y cuando se forma la inversion termica fu… https://t.co/4KECuwTriG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adventure_muffn Don’t be! And I only say that because I just finished my first round of edits on my first first dr… https://t.co/KhvNMFyfVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My friend” who kills his relatives with anti-aircraft guns and flame throwers, starves his people, and stomps all… https://t.co/E65pV81XlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToyBoxComix You looking at these? I’d think Space Ghost &amp; Bird Man might also be of interest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We could knock out this wall.” —every American who has ever considered purchasing property]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @BeavertonSD what’s the plan for the morning? You failed to update the media and parents this morning (the only… https://t.co/4kAE8VPjnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_Biancaxo I hope you eat soon. Hungry in mass transportation is the devil’s work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donald_Evans123 @CarolWalsh01 @WilliamGStovall @Phil__Oliveira @djdara207 This is awesome Don!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/YGq8uie6I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care as much Congress hearing testimony re McCabe and Comey as I do a grand jury hearing testimony!… https://t.co/M4GRP2i7oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haritaa5 @BBCMonitoring @BBCWorld They’re literally scared to death not to. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 1/4 of presidents say DeVos proposals on campus sexual assault would move federal policy in 'right direction'… https://t.co/9fIZ6cNwu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachP08 Anthony, congratulations but those of us who have known you for years always have thought of you as a sup… https://t.co/ePdOWP9uXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump is so enamored with the value of IG reports, why has he left so many IG positions unfilled for so long?]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the carnival chasers, how many carnivals do you attend per year before get tired of it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @emmarieDC The answer is Simple.. NO. Big Pharm will rip off the consumer for their personal gain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMNY_Archangel Yea that’s most def why. Reach was in a league of its own when it came to forge and customization.… https://t.co/XccFK9eywB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another macro shot of the iris with a couple more extension tubes. #macrophotography #macro #flowers #strobist @ Ch… https://t.co/q6wne8OdoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedjudges The arizona nominee should be voted on in the next couple of weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_h_thompson @JussieSmollett Any racial demographics with those stats? #AskingForAFriend #MAGACountryOrNot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JARonHussey @its_mrsvenus She’s at work, my behind is home... I got no problem pulling up to her job https://t.co/EYeH5dmbQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s just me...but I’m not out here actively looking for a relationship....if it happens, it happens...if it… https://t.co/FRVy4zf6R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms39211 @MitchellSmilie @jeremyminton9 @NealMcCready @AUGoldMine Tinker v Des Moines would be a good start for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamVTV @AOC How about this, Kambree ? Is this a “respectable look”? https://t.co/bSRjxhb3BO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franksting Middle class people hitting hard times is a thing, but my guess is that by the time such people get to… https://t.co/ag94uKxcdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuntener @Cristina_Lupica Good fuckinf God! BUT she cant ,prove they are married! Um ok... I smell a rat = Hailey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin go in on them Roland. Armstrong know #45 is a liar. Who is this white boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Links’s Awakening is the best Zelda game and I won’t hear otherwise. That ending will wreck you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rockefeller Center - @rockcenternyc in New York, NY https://t.co/O6vc4fQpQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 3 years after high school and I still haven’t used the Pythagorean’s Theory 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreethinkerInCA @CarmineSabia No, you’ve just proven you’re a gun tool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@In_The_Slot Is that the dual rink in Worcester right off the highway? I think I went down there last summer for a… https://t.co/HQP3OBmObq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aliyah’s biggest fans from Corpus cheering her on! Thanks Grandpa Andy and Grandma Yolanda for coming out to watch… https://t.co/8k0fBfOG7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @C_Sommerfeldt @NYDailyNews To side with GOP makes you vulnerable for GOP chalanges!! That makes as much sense… https://t.co/tcu9zdmCTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If anyone knows about lying and being crooked it’s you -   #Worstpresidenteverbyfar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Sen @thehill That was a problematic response, defensive, and yes, inexpertly expressed. I think she meant that… https://t.co/fASIb8wss7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah... #WrestleMania #WrestleManiaseason #TheAnimalvsTheGame #Marks https://t.co/O2XOaemRNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray For Venezuela:  "For the cause of the oppressed and the groaning of the needy, I will now arise," says the LOR… https://t.co/HddvWzPJst]]></document></documents></author>