<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Me to the associate at @myfamilydollar : Excuse me ma'am where are your Compact Disc players? Her: Excuse me. Compa… https://t.co/f3od4y2oiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the Holy Virgin Mary From Christian Psychic, Angel Guadiania. https://t.co/xdypgtoZD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to the umpires. Not sure what in the hell the 1B ump covering the plate saw but got it right in the end.… https://t.co/gP4GLduDhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyperboleGrant It really nails the feeling of of living in Chicago and being part of its music scene at that time.… https://t.co/FRpg1z0m6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning beautiful people of #twitter #lafayette #louisianamodel #nudehousekeeper #bbc #cock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inaugural Business Tour broadcast with @MorningAnswer @AM560TheAnswer today from Edison Park.. https://t.co/0beaBfVxjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is attacking Spike Lee for being 'racist towards him' .. nice to see that nothing has changed this Monday .. lol  #Murica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perla_mont Eres muy grande compañera... gran mujer... gran profesional, gran ser humano y eso a muchos les caga. Abrazote Perlita¡¡¡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanKoenigsberg Listening from WV, 30 min west of Pittsburgh on the Fan app. Need any and all Broncos news]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 AMAZING Last Minute Winners by TOM ROGIC for CELTIC vs KILMARNOCK, MOT... https://t.co/IyAXxVtQ7j via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allahpundit @benshapiro This fool is another delusional voice in the democratic party that is a radical Socialist.… https://t.co/3u6AOEL5hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels I hope and pray with you Mr Daniels we’ve tolerated it this long justice will come]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tigard is ready to make a playoff run. Need everyone's contribution. https://t.co/GlLQ218B3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting the week on a high note. @GeorgiaHempCo https://t.co/69fSpBhJ1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lovestained555 Do what you are. There’ll be other other opportunities to get paid for being someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Westchester, IL? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/L8vgK8ahTf #Purchasing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not let chronic pain own me. Should I talk about gun shot, cancer, colon bursting and stage 4 macula blindne… https://t.co/BJJKWa3WMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gage_c17 @MrBlh56 @dyllbob4life Tbh it was almost as boring as the pri fight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got pulled over and they didn’t shoot me... today was a good day 😂 https://t.co/EPv3aQTGp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside of the movie and TV critics, does anyone at EW ever criticize anyone in the industry or just look for exclu… https://t.co/hSfrsYnqRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should be mandatory that everybody watches, and falls in love, with The Greatest Showman]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you know Sunday is your Thursday https://t.co/9l4Furb7IA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t mess with Ayo, Trent, Giorgi B &amp; the rest of the #Illini   Anything can happen. Big10 tourney is up for grabs 🔶🔷🔶🔷🔶🔷🔶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be able to tell my kids shit your momma been hell she put me through all kinds of shit but hey I loved he… https://t.co/MLh9CHR3pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up next: Princeton prof and @TheProspect editor Richard Starr @StarrProspect on the wide-open Democrat field as I e… https://t.co/X5RgKKHmTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBTheShow Way to stab DC in the back. The whole derby DC love was fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tacotuesday on a cold but sunny day in Covington, just outside the office https://t.co/uCxMVsK1A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BurtonJM for this important critique and for your leadership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time we mobilized Hip Hop Culture to protest and help WIN the fight against the city and province to build a m… https://t.co/SYiN72Hix1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 14 degrees outside and i can’t function properly.... guess I’m staying in bed ALL day 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 The other day @criscarter80 said on @FTFonFS1 that fans can’t empathize with how player’s are treated by owne… https://t.co/LweqKpcuJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricDJuly Savage Dragon Shazam Spawn  Also collect anything Hellblazer/Constantine]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The oxblood leather was worn. The deep wrinkles, like decades of wisdom, were earned. It cradled Liam’s body like… https://t.co/HREFXqv1p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyDwyer10 @GarDolphin733 @markfuller86 @CoffeeIsLife06 @PamelaM5050 @lisaponyexpress @Starrbryte67631 @jodyemtp… https://t.co/8uDbx2ulab]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I ever want to do is remove the dock, icon labels and different icons. Is that to much to ask Apple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleycisco @JeffDLowe Keep me as far away from that place as possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YardHouse @DrunkPolkaroo @Paul__G__ @SudburyHomebrew @david_buist @ottawahockey @heatherington84 @xBeannote… https://t.co/u0peA3BWbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brogdan it is...any objections...if not we are dismissed https://t.co/e0TWfH51d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was closeted the first time the Jonas Brothers were popular so ty god for giving me another chance to publicly an… https://t.co/37iWfldivO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danjnolte @OutOfKenTroll @chicagobars If you use your own delivery drivers vs. if you use delivery through app.  D… https://t.co/sJxVUTqDxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for the digital transformation? #lol #DigitalTransformation https://t.co/z2ppIgdGxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller shoots down conspiracy theory that he tipped off CNN to Roger Stone arrest https://t.co/1CcwK5T3th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeceMoten @TomDekker2 @TheKilling99 @t_inker58 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity I’m telling you as someone who has l… https://t.co/Jid5G8RDrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuyfaudoa @EstebanMtzAlc @futpicante @MauricioYmay @herculezg Y tu al Milan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/ERWAUz92rD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contemporary economics is finally breaking free from its market fetishism, offering plenty of tools we can use to m… https://t.co/2i56uHCUqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PearlPolanski @SykesCharlie No. That’s a standard sock puppet handle. They have a name and random numbers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jim_enloe @ShawnEnloe2 @maggieNYT @matthewjdowd Me yes, the others look like fake news people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville I want to suggest an oldie but Goodie, AutoAmercan - Blondie if I win retweet my mural painting tweet :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[U &amp; @Danky_Tanky about to go crazy I’m already knowin. We need @CRAIGXEN on that shit though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaoDaoMan @skau61 @CharlieSaidWTF @KamalaHarris 70 year old parent(S) living with their children has always been a… https://t.co/hNxAmJDykj]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICQ Podcast Episode 288 - Amateur Radio Author Don Keith (N4KC)  https://t.co/UBnjJfeQMQ  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherfink I got two go to Oscars twice cos a friend hosted, so i get it. But it put the focus on winners, not jokes about them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to feel like I won’t finish all my movies. Getting a late start today and half the day tomorrow is a w… https://t.co/TKpkohglhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein 3 hours? Are you crazy?  Take a break Love your family Treat yourself with kindness We value you too highly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_westwaswon @craigsef so glad I got rid of that fuckin behemoth bed last year. so many awful memories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Er sexual misconduct, or whatever definition it fits. I’m not a lawyer. I just know it isn’t ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benatargiraldo's #40thAnniversaryTour! @metheridge is joining them for two shows! https://t.co/mTHbu1rLvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/CiUOBXEyWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great connecting with Rob Hunt and the Notre Dame Sports Medicine team today! They have an infectious passion for o… https://t.co/0D1TCsEPKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mulheron4 I would have definitely caught one of those fists and restrained her. No way I could take that many shot… https://t.co/7bGMozCPiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeliciousJazz @JazzMadridClub @kcsowriter @jordialmogaver1 @HOSTALPERSAL @yola5940 @LyndonMorris9 @Villacajazz… https://t.co/LsTzKh5uJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kireau @OwnTheThroneMov @TiffanyDavid113 @Ianaki @tijohnson One was shoveling 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a rare unanimous #waleg vote, the Senate approved a bill that would authorize Washington's public utility distri… https://t.co/hG5MoGJmuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an absolutely gorgeous sunset happen behind City Island!  Enjoy! @cbsnewyork #chopper2 @ City Island https://t.co/lBZaL9K9xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#10Años Aquí estoy, aquí sigo. 👊🏽                                                                      Aqui Estoy -… https://t.co/X62EqjxjdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset #colorado #nofilter #landscape #landscapephotography #coppermountain #snowboarding #snow #scenic… https://t.co/KNL2GXavbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be a better person.   I know it’s popular to demonize social media but I’ve met so many wonderful people… https://t.co/EVYPaszFBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW. SIX YEARS? 6 years ago today I saw @HannahMusic Georgas for the first time, at @MilkBoyPhilly, opening for… https://t.co/IclThk7dai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalalauren654 Here’s a pic of my friends dog so your cold heart warms up a lil https://t.co/lwfYl2ZzsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastor, can you lay your hands on my bank account? #Pastorchallenge #payday #bankaccount #raiseitfromthedead… https://t.co/r4GLMopRXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[”Stay true to yourself, yet always be open to learn. Work hard, and never give up on your dreams, even when nobody… https://t.co/i26PRXzHFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Live_for_Films The Bookshop--the cast is strong and effective in delivering the story. It's a fascinating look at… https://t.co/WH82zVa4bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeCSantos Every single adult should be escorted out tomorrow and fired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FoxNews--"Joe diGenova: Walls closing in on Obama DOJ officials"https://t.co/kIykCEZNDU"New text messages between f… https://t.co/Qql2iQQ73Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The fake news leader an enemy of American people has killed American people with his propaganda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonyaellenmann @clairlemon Even IF what this study is purporting is true, I still don’t quite understand the probl… https://t.co/lDoHTOkqUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how I’ve missed the baseball lingo.... “Get a hit kid” “Good eye” “Make him work” “Little hit here little hit” “… https://t.co/Wx50UWLBZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Luck to Logan Co HS juniors &amp; those across the Commonwealth taking the ACT tomorrow!! @LoganCoSchools… https://t.co/TVWYjCoDMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MiamiOH_BBall closes out the regular season tonight at Ohio. But this isn't the end of the road by any means!… https://t.co/GC46IGhFhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longballgirl @metrikk @KellyTownsend11 @noprezzie2012 @DanSerrano2 @JamesTHarris @Broomhead Principle himself neve… https://t.co/DY9MIMTDFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full video of Nolan Kemp’s 3/4 court game winner last week in the JV game. (Yes he got it off, see my recent media… https://t.co/QUvi3Qo7FX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_ankrom @yournewswire TWIGHLIGHT ZONE..MAN.. LETS GET REAL AMERICA..DOESNT EVERBODY DESERVE A LIFE OF PEACE N A J… https://t.co/mpQxswM8JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Travel changes you. As you move through this life and this world you change things slightly, you leave marks behin… https://t.co/lJ4mSDistY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Civil War victories this year:  Beavs: 3 That other Oregon team (Not PSU): 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of waiting around , I know exactly how this works even if I’ve never done this (build a tech app) one thi… https://t.co/SCTiF7WsJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subscribing to @Imperfectfruit is the best decision I’ve made thus far in 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad likes every one of my tweets even though I’m pretty sure he might get maybe 60% of the content and if that’s… https://t.co/gIZzCTaSDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWOODS_13 @QM7Jones I think #VerifiedRedJersey is the continuation of #YearofTheRedjersey...what you think @WIO_Jones ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“'Going to have to blame that loss on the stadium sound director. No energy because they didn’t play hype music or… https://t.co/lsfg9lUmDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching a Ride on Big wheels, steamtown Historic site. https://t.co/CDFfWtW7OS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This analysis of tRump by a psychiatrist is scary enough to keep you up at night. It is a must read and should be s… https://t.co/dytI1t2wOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoledOfficial @KenzieReevesxxx Ha! Ha!  That pic CERTAINLY doesn't look like a "pussy" to me... GREAT shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry University FL Fri Mar 8th AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 79 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millieannmiller @marklutchman @DoNotForget911 Yep, a money magnet. They are better than princes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squad of Republicans that went to the Kremlin on the 4th of July last year. Why?+ 2 senators that went on their own… https://t.co/eiNOzzuDUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those that needed a refresher 💸  - "The Corner" is #Separate#StaySquare#WeightShift]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not many options when coming from the struggle 💔 https://t.co/bnuVjsboJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sxsw2019  #sxsw #RobSpaz  #vibesinthecity  #austinedition @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/Kw0u8KDTjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @LukeGWilliams close out #IDCDirections 2019! It has been a great day. https://t.co/cHUAaAitvh]]></document></documents></author>