<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ParasiticLotus @CapnSweet @BBakhshandeh @MichaelAvenatti Hold on... let me get my questions right. You are asking… https://t.co/9uXCXIVv5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever buy soo much good food at the store that when you get home, you’re not sure what to make first?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_vanov @AlfredoJalifeR_ @marvinicio @norma22flores @Saucedina @PerezrobJ @hectorsmx Jamás Ivan. Mexico es reconoc… https://t.co/Y2ebGolAHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of my list are @LaurelAlizad @mckaelaD @MichelleJWeiss @ArchieDeskus @jenatemple @pinczuk @Kelly_Ducourty… https://t.co/oMfECawwoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 at @RedCon1Official with @fitcrunchbars !!!! Come on over to Booth #️⃣7️⃣2️⃣9️⃣ to find out what our ❓MYSTERY… https://t.co/52j79l0IoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandyn Burnette - Lost https://t.co/yL15hvKkwP  via @YouTube  STILL my favorite @Eman8 miss you #genius #Eman8… https://t.co/1PZ9Bx7Ruz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw someone read a poster on campus and then shoot finger guns at it. #nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: ok I’m about to crack down and study   **2 hours later after not studying ...***  Me: ok now I’m going to for r… https://t.co/1Y4jK1YvQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je ressens la même joie des partisans @AFCAjax qui célèbrent dans les rues de Madrid. Un match 👌🏾, victoire 4-1 au… https://t.co/gFBZzsNgMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s try something brianne, it’s called thinking before you speak 😊😊😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oaxaca_verdad @Jess42392725 @FelipeCalderon @Mx_Diputados El mismo mal rumbo que su escasez de gasolina? En serio… https://t.co/GWhei9xC96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I perfectly timed my DoorDash order on the way home from work so I could just get off the bus, pick… https://t.co/Vco4Dr5i1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKingLatifah So, that’s still her fucking who she wants and me fucking who I can, right? Well, at least a bitch… https://t.co/V0rSZ9eRoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrerucker51 @Itridpm @DudekLinda @hey_butter @landscaperstev1 @fishersusa @SarahGould_SA @evilgrrl @poppij… https://t.co/SefNEEOTqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieFrederix @sahouraxo @POTUS it's never been the govs  job to make sure me all have healthcare.  Those 65 and… https://t.co/d20Em71RuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[everybody mad that I changed my number and didn’t give it to them 😭😭 but how ima give it to y’all when I deleted all my contacts? lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[A calm,reasoned,fact based responsiveness, a refusal to react to semi-hysterical erroneous comments and insults, re… https://t.co/9uv151M2ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWF Feminists are afraid of conservative women.  Conservative women are proud to be women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing about Tannas is her pantry, she has literally everything in there]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We as Progressives need to change the conversation from the vehicle to the destination. What will the policy do fo… https://t.co/rKGkRc8oYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theorossi Thought it only fitting to return the favor 😘 https://t.co/z2HFCPzdFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[GO DAWGS! Way to go @UGAGymnastics beating undefeated Florida! Literally down to the last two competitors!! #godawgs #RingTheBell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@42bkdodgr @JillWineBanks Jr may find him self in more trouble than he expects.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of my friends were shot, I never had someone so close and young die because of being sick 😫 I yelled at God fo… https://t.co/105MaI3bnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch On constitutional rights they are criminals by the nature they are here illigally.  The Constitution… https://t.co/CxpaBfxUjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[today the girl I nanny was telling me how stressed she is about the future because she can’t decide if she wants to… https://t.co/Ud2HF3MhtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[if y’all only knew how hard it is to do this stuff especially being 16...idk her but let her do your nailsss!!😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabionPicheco @theSolemnBard @alovablenerd Yeah, we eat a little horsemeat but not as much as the Slovenes. Stripe… https://t.co/AMQ1i0HFKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikkilStarseed @SkyeSweetnam We try! Haha never want to put out work we don’t believe in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realllllly loving this Refresher! #nofilter Before and After! We added some #navy blue to the #rootage to really ma… https://t.co/SxeDlHFUJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moms. Good hugs, great advice, heart warming compliments. 12/10 couldn’t live without them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmusty40 @overanalyze1421 @abike199 @TMZ @twillynavy246 This whole little exchange 🤣 y’all win https://t.co/hIuKCdFEE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole day has been perfect wow i think somebody is tryna set me up]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got asked why I'm struggling to find the right guy.... Lol if only I knew why I have bad luck🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Trump said at CPAC, yesterday, that "they" were trying to get him out of office on some Bullsh%t, an… https://t.co/Z90y8I0WuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyann_ @BTS_twt This is the song that declared me as Army Tony, it’s so special to me. Thank you. 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Rink at Rockefeller Center https://t.co/xCNVyT31JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHermanCain She along with OAC and Tlaib. Were recruited by The Justice Democrats...they are pushing The New Gre… https://t.co/Jah6h7b7vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This outfit has no business in Florida. #wheresthesun #Floridacold https://t.co/iSD1GUDQr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasLovejoy @neiltyson Start with The Lion, The Witch, and The Wardrobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las Vegas  🚙  San Francisco ✈️ Los Angeles ✈️ Costa Rica ✈️   Ahora solo ocupo que sea Abril 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[God would never have chosen such a vile thing as Trump to lead a flea parade. Although we are seeing our innards an… https://t.co/CKo5OgvDPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Got me I have no idea. When you go in the voting booth it is just you and the ballot. You  vote your conscience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickRandall @Fishkybizniz @RampageRojo @PanhandlePaint @ReneeFiredup @UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump @TheCiscoKid2… https://t.co/WXsKl8p6fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliviaGaines I’m ready! #CrossroadsOscars #Crossroads #Anthology https://t.co/9BVr8tlDrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq @ReneeLibby2 Some days it just not fun anymore on any social media sites ( mean, nasty tweets by ppl w… https://t.co/asVwVvaUXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald You know the real reason she cried wasn't Ilhan Omar, but her utter lack of validation 4 her views from… https://t.co/ckYiOql15u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to thank everyone who sent me pet pics. It truly helped me get through the rest of my work day.  I'm watch… https://t.co/SJ2DAuM7aZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are some pictures from the crew working yesterday Go Tejano Day second shift at Diner✔️ — at RODEOHOUSTON. @ R… https://t.co/7kXSHWkSGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtGate21 @ak_square9 @BASIL2Slayer @MacoStyle007 @M0N1KA_ @perdiccasi @harveyspencer21 @Makedona_Aliti… https://t.co/xBCKr24jxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker literally just said  Do you ever take a selfie and think “wow is this really what I look like?”😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really just wanna know why basic girls think loving chicken nuggets is a personality trait. Everyone loves them. If… https://t.co/rorv8tqqp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suge Knight Will Serve 28 Years In Jail #Topbuzz https://t.co/l5h0RrWRLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In excess of 2,000 youth a year are held bc of the valid court order exception.” - Naomi Smoot of Coalition for Juvenile Justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karen_erotoo1 @barmore27 @RepJerryNadler @realDonaldTrump This is the most ridiculous BS ! They will stip at nothi… https://t.co/8xTSUwARws]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am fortunate enough to coteach with the wonderful @MrGaskinsBIS during my 4th bell of Pre-Algebra. We chat on a d… https://t.co/KZn2TUIk9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passports updated, check-in completed, hydrating furiously... we are finally headed to Cape Town, South Africa to s… https://t.co/ZX8OfabjyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your weekend was so lit you’re still fucked up on Monday #woeisme #needAA 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Panthrdan In case we wear navy, I didn’t want to clash! But don’t worry, I packed for both looks! 👌🏻🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debbiedoeslifex @CarterSteinhoff @zaaitir @eunice_pickett @Kommonsense7 Please, provide the statistics of infantil… https://t.co/KACiQoQmia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelerschic85 @louimpressme @CunningSq16 @TalkToMeForReal @TanziaMill @ltinsley1209 @LYNNIFY @calimom209… https://t.co/Djn9DXtLeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[No but seriously, what the fuck happened to @MattToka?   Sincerely,  A concerned former fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[6D by Brandi. Be Great. Get Lashed. Book with the best @coutureye link in our bio. @ CouturEye https://t.co/NQZEbwFTw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffAxisPaint @matt_tifft @TWilliamsLive @FitStopPerform @MoleculeSports @layneschranz @ToddGilliland_ @NosEnergyDrink @CMANGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @lanebryant this was a really bad color choice, white bra on white background? I have good color vision and cou… https://t.co/pxpgxp3vgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA If you people vote for Trump again I can't express to you how blinded by reality you are! We need a person wh… https://t.co/SKDjrXZgp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a people person. I literally love talking to and meeting people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this. When you take time to build a fun, safe, and trusting family environment, your students will be much mor… https://t.co/nIuBxjKJwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[New listing - 3 bed condo in the ❤️ of Savin Hill  https://t.co/imMiIdAg2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrammarUpdates I thought “were” was the appropriate word to use, but without that as a choice, I think “was” is the best answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank the Lord ! There is no national emergency ! There is no need for a wall !  There is still need in Puerto Rico… https://t.co/ZjzOyijhNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to have a BIG SESH w/ my niggas! I’m talking 2/3 blunts a head!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry's death sheds light on stroke prevention and warning signs  https://t.co/Q6BxE4C2zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pink Print was literally such a good fucking album. Nicki don’t loose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland to get systems up and running again,” it says.  “At this stage we have no further details about the origin of the attack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spotify or anyone - is there a way to get around this, so I can just continue saving music? https://t.co/S7Kgvb1wBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Interesting how the MAGA cap has the power to transform a pair of Nigerian brothers into a pair of w… https://t.co/7NGLlpmqK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2) Tough to answer if we don’t really all agree on what IS a soft skill but my personal opinion is Resiliance and… https://t.co/Utcqcokfcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Hmm..are they scared much?..donkey tails between the legs already..lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaKBrooks Ok...catch up with me at next HFR...I'll give you a lesson.  I'll bring the sheet, lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/SkoDRqYW5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marirosa221 @laurensrodka @anke_mayer @TereRose1 @KatieUpdates2 @lyndeeday @QueenMSheba @Susanjeanricci @Ibtbanksy… https://t.co/f7JeTSKkEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crissydanielle_ Hey Crissy, you should try using the site DietBet. A few fitness youtubers use it to help their su… https://t.co/3VvK6p8kAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KainYusanagi @neontaster The Nazis were far right. They also sent socialists to concentration camps. But, do go on… https://t.co/K619cAxAjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zacherykauff I don’t understand the hype about chick-fil-a... not that good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conz2006 @EmanuelEfunbote @marklevinshow He needs to be reported to the FBI.  Such hate speak should not be tolerated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that illegals cost American taxpayers over 100 billion/year is a national emergency!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sheer number of friends, relatives, and acquaintances who choose to be silent brings me closer to understanding… https://t.co/bqw7WpxaUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itmightbetrin why do we have the same nails rn https://t.co/7HTSVn4DcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is my favorite piece of media that my coworkers have ever created @GilletteTPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly coming on social media has been kinda bad for me lately - i'm dealing with so many "real life" things that… https://t.co/lS2RTmFGXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to clarify she referred to certain areas in PG County as N_____ communities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop making people feel like they have to tone down their personality to be around you, making someone feel like they’re too much is so ugly]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I have to do is turn in my essay and it’s time for SPRING BREAK thank you Jesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Explore the Underground Railroad’s ‘great central depot’ https://t.co/v1utD5nCfa via @NatGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have two distinct justice systems in this country.  https://t.co/epZolPpWjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst thing is losing a bond over something so wack. shit hits different]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @HillaryClinton @BillClinton Nope! They need an ogre to feel good about themselves. Sad but true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some white woman in my sociology class just said “East Oakland is where all them blacks live!”   BACK UP A MINUTE, SIS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So big huge snow drifts from the blizzard. They are taller than me I know this pic doesnt look like that but trust… https://t.co/HZvbwFXkA1]]></document></documents></author>