<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@amandamull And Johnny’s shorts with the line on the collars? Truly the best in the series. Man oh man would I like… https://t.co/dPJN5Zh4cZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Berman Finishes Fifth, Women's Golf Places Eighth at Kiawah Island https://t.co/GHv51ZaM40]]></document><document><![CDATA[PayPal CEO Admits Partnership with Far-Left SPLC to Blacklist Conservatives https://t.co/oUWqVPUyjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino After he pays the $40 million taxpayers have already paid for the first]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be back in Disney, here’s a wall pic to prove it! #wallsofdisney https://t.co/uCjGgrqVRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @aschindewolf to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day I'll challen… https://t.co/bvoW6ijInT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris another plague, resulting from you idol G-Dlessness. i, have read The Little Book of Noach. i know ho… https://t.co/TP0NVD5NJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brett’s Saison by STAMM BEER @ Union Street Saloon — https://t.co/epwGXXbjYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelersdepot what is their cap situation currently? I am aware the Ben extension will probably create some more room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanCarleton @tedmccoy You two are the best. Keep fighting that good fight. That is really unbelievable, but then, not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavileLodge It's not right to blame one group for what goes on. Those who don't want to be corrupt are just as res… https://t.co/qeefCjM2y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg Can you name at least one other thing Donald Trump achieved?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Misinformation Is About Who You Trust, Not What You Think https://t.co/f0ftzH50Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alwaysn4evaArt @shesforOKC @okcthundervibe @Dstl74 @John1and1 @justshannonbaby @cory_c_22 @JHillDaKid If Dennis wo… https://t.co/ODKg0EYcYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forestcasey @john_osborn @MacklinHogan Very few from the 80s, but lots from the 90s. XK220 comes to mind. 993 GT1… https://t.co/y3tsJ3jocg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good games yesterday to @RutgersEsports - y’all played great and all of us at NYU can’t wait until we get another shot at y’all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBotello @B1GMBBall @umichbball @MichiganOnBTN @UMichAthletics Of height and weight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my... Beta v Daryl... That was fun. Do that every every episode.  #thewalkingdead #beta #Daryl #bestfight @ Las… https://t.co/Dli60xEWSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOOK NOW! 📍Glamher24studios San Antonio, TX ✨5 Years In The Brow Game✨ AVAIL: Tuesday-Saturday 11AM-6PM 📞 Call or T… https://t.co/UgN88baZ55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJayWilliams good pick takings Kansas. Quit picking against @TexasTechMBB!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedSoxFund @RedSox @FenwaySouth We can play online, even though the Sox are in Florida? 🤟🏻😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For the past 2 years these scumbags have been harassing you Mr President as a cancer survivor I th… https://t.co/oEoRL9VuGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pookah72450 @sam_vinograd @realDonaldTrump I think you have exceeded your allotted time out of your cage. Get back… https://t.co/wi35NCC1U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Toxic politics mostly due to the vitriol Trump has poured into our system. Politics should be about ISSUES wit… https://t.co/atfBkqdUvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaroUribeVel Igual de sincero y oportunista que ud cuando dijo si contra la corrupcion y despues de campaña pres… https://t.co/osrUojBTFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuckSox_815 @CommentatorPmt @jemelehill @Twarmy22 @jdogg21PR So after all that text you pick out Tebow not kneeling. 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:02 to play in the second quarter....  South Johnston 30, Clayton 24  #HSOTScores #HoopState 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuronUrban That whole devolpment from north river road to down to bridge was piss poor planning, and is ignored. A… https://t.co/9rVhAGEMnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could the light in the fridge also please remind me why I’m opening the fridge in the first place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_daissssyyy @BobbyBounce Sweet "Hot" Meatballs too! https://t.co/QLFbnLc7kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[##PTSDSucks #EmbraceTheSuck #FirstResponderLivesMatterToo!! 🚓🚑❤️👮‍♂️🚒🖤💕🚔🚨🚁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Cardinal wrestling team and wrestling coaching staff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio on Sunday laid the blame for the scuttled deal between Amazon and the city at th… https://t.co/KBVKewZDoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone in an organization care about the QB’s feelings? They don’t care about the linebackers feelings?… https://t.co/8Ud7jIc0P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrtografiaReal No es fácil poner punto final cuando sabes que que no es falta de  ortografía!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodstuffpage @goodenough_fu @Imjenniferann That’s a beautiful woman I sure love, I wish she were my beautiful girl friend ⭐️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NothingLikeAliveMusicExperience #MusiciansWorkHardForFans #MusiciansWorkHardForTheMoney #livemusic https://t.co/vHGzPE4LCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaladinMichael showing a sweet stroke. Swishes long 3 after driving layup. He leads @OLLUSaints with 15. Saints le… https://t.co/wK4HMLaCfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Who, besides #HowardSchultz, has said that anyone “can’t openly support capitalism” when several Dems w… https://t.co/TeX5ANgcxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Industry 4.0 technology can be used to improve staff safety: https://t.co/pbg5OZilSE via @IIoT_World    #IIoT… https://t.co/fQI5VPqbdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamCheeky Thank YOU for taking the time to make the video! Always fun stuff from you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goknightsgo #fleuryshutout (at @KrispyKreme Doughnuts in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/Yz97RZf2L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleMan365 @JamboEveryone @SuperWeenieHtJr @1MinDisneyDream @dolewhipdaily @tomorrowsoc I don’t follow it but I’d join in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlexramos It’s in those countries that you see the revert to that default setting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again for supporting our event. @FTFCanada_ @patrice421 @joecola4 @vaughansoccercl @vaughanhpshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace casi dos meses que saqué esta foto pero como tuve que hacerla con una sensación térmica de -38° yo creo que mi… https://t.co/NYSCDLZg3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarbonWrangler @MCC_Berlin @Peters_Glen https://t.co/syTrEX8K72 seems much better in principle. No EOR temptation, no leakage potential.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to a very touching segment of the podcast 31 thoughts by @JeffMarek while traveling between Houston and N… https://t.co/cYG6HWLvsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teespring As an #IrishAmerican #Laborer I find this shirt to be incredibly offensive. Perpetuating ethnic stereoty… https://t.co/rP1hANqMG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 And they criticize Trump and he has lost money. Bastards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furious at my dad for making me have dinner with him tonight when I could be seeing my mother (Isabelle Huppert in GRETA)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough! The time is now.  At the #behest of silent millions we will rally to the cause!  Join the movement!  We are… https://t.co/OO70SaI3zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco Looking for work cause I lost my job. You know the normal American life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few photos while I was out watching some volleyball today!  Good to see the @scac_sports representing in CA… https://t.co/sevrEEIGpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylerFoster Swear my whole demeanor change when I see a look a like cop. Ive been told my vehicle is a cop car but i dont think so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benching with 275 plus 40lbs in chains using the Slingshot! Struggled on the last rep BUT I STILL GOT IT!!! If you… https://t.co/cgPuU4uzx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erik_Naught_6 @brennan_lloyd @allistairsdad @IvankaTrump Here's another fun fact https://t.co/QQNR8JT5Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate Sick to even suggest a violent crime against a child would be anything but a crime. Why in hell would you even suggest it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@connorfranta Here's more...  #InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰💵🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/L6NMPExHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dice Tower West! Dice Tower folks and friends in the building. Will be back tomorrow to begin the festivities. 🙌 https://t.co/ow55P9QiPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHill3204 @NLedford7 What does the @NCAA have to do to get some actual officials out there. Every game seems to get worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousNIK They were acting! LOL , maybe not all the way, 3rd base  I’m sure !!! 😂👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jailbreak iOS 12 Tweaks - Guest Mode for iOS 12.1.2 Jailbreak (Unc0ver C... https://t.co/a3YQqMN5zd via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you Pres! #MAGA 🇺🇸 #BetterBuildThatWall 🇺🇸🙏🏻💪🏻💪🏻🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 #ILoveUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unscriptedmike I don't get it. Why would anyone in their right mind even WANT obama on Mount Rushmore? It's a nati… https://t.co/6aUQpAPUNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, @SUBWAY i’m definitely super hungry right now at 1:46am https://t.co/TJmeqqRuMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donovan97655972 Health coverage for all same coverage, the president, the senator, the representative, the lawyer,… https://t.co/HnZFmYErPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jWo87PJBGY Quickbooks Enterprise Technical Support Phone Number +1-855-236-7529 For 24*7 help… https://t.co/ttsZSkuZQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathyhen_ @eluberoff It’s an “oldie” but a goodie. If you’ll be @ISTE in June, come see the poster session about t… https://t.co/emJTTdwtfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#THORsDaaayyy!!! @MattGranite  @DarbyDouglasTV  @thordiakow  20190228 https://t.co/FK8ayVVZ28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prelim round game tonight! Show out for 3 seed @GoBHSBulldogs girls basketball! #BEdford #BEthere… https://t.co/i9zFF08oub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another “Dub”!  Win &amp; advance, baby!  #FHSU https://t.co/5mYG8hHhUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Pad_Chennington for this beautiful analysis of 失われた時REGRET 🔑💍🔪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Yes his shit heel Son is now working for the Pussy Grabber’s defense team! What a Fucking surprise.#scumbagfamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepJeffries: Please sign the Lee-Hurd letter to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sun card...loving the hair. 😘💋🖤🖤  #brownjrart #tarot #drawings #draw #artist #art #artwork #pencil #pencilart… https://t.co/nfHADZYxjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serendipia_80 Muy buenos días Española y feliz miércoles tengas tu también cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:11 me and all my mutuals meet Taylor 💕 @taylornation13 @taylorswift13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnucklDraginSam @dbongino Yep! No bid (big) deal! Huh! Lol 😂! Absolutely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better still, if you are in a product based industry, offer them a free product on their birthday to ensure they co… https://t.co/18BTxs0ImF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been a wild third period. The @NHLFlyers have to bear down and hold on these last three minutes. #LetsGoFlyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Creekside by @BABrewing @ Poppa Rollo's — https://t.co/0DNuOVzM4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dumb StarCraft 2 custom games are so much fun and they also run at 14 FPS lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomHolliday7 @_RainyDayWoman @davidhogg111 @marcorubio @noNRAmoney For reference. https://t.co/yLKofglri0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tackleberry924 @SpeakerPelosi What a novel idea!!!.... They should do the same for “drug related violence”, that’l… https://t.co/GkdGyDJNPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The actor Gary Cole lives in the guest house where we shot Cathy’s house. In one of the tales where Cathy breaks th… https://t.co/ktBfnlxF4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you had to cut one of your top-3 sports teams, who are you cutting?  List your top-3 &amp; lmk who you cut.… https://t.co/uVgcT55CyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first paid writing gig was for Mondo 2000 when I was 18 and I had a syndicated newspaper column by 22 and a Puli… https://t.co/Brae9vtACN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing gets my blood boiling more than hearing someone - as some are at this cmte on allowing school vouchers - sa… https://t.co/YqRyVm0O5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼  #livingishardtheseries #danilotequila #daniloarmy #teamdanilo #comedy #talent #musicallyapp #music… https://t.co/pSYbYb5yzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thorstenbenner @ischinger Trump clearly out of sync with his own admin here. But even if Trump and China strikes a… https://t.co/EvOqYTKvho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CongressmanRuiz @fams2gether Husbands And wives should be together also]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t get wings today but did make chocolate covered strawberries 🍓 for the first time lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how these young leaders have organized to create solutions and real policy recommendations for their schools… https://t.co/EbW8l901LB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tropicalsteve @kellysue We just saw it as well.  Really enjoyed it and I agree about Fury.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just bought a coffee table and tv stand after 2 years of not having one so if you plan on ever coming over please V… https://t.co/1P7haGLcuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people be focused on the wrong shit man and not even trying to go forward 🤦🏿‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo @ConEdison make up your mind with this fucking water shit from 5th to Lenox ave on 117th. You got me filling up… https://t.co/MujV06wT4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarySue Please don't post fake news. This makes the cause look bad. Consider taking this down in good faith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quarter Rock Press - Pantera, a 28 años de 'Cowboys From Hell' https://t.co/w37auq7C4V via @QuarterPress]]></document></documents></author>