<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mitchell White completed the Austin Half Marathon! Time 02:51:17 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/uIdBeInoES #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be calling tonight’s @OUAsport women’s basketball semi-final at 6:00, on https://t.co/liNxoa6eWz. Still waitin… https://t.co/HJCz8uR5tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts on Max Boot's screed against historians: https://t.co/yScjnsMdzi #twitterstorians]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on the @AOC. #sxsw (@ ACC - Ballroom D for Featured Session: Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez and the New Left in A… https://t.co/aQdJTd7u9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruBluDad About seven miles Southeast of Salt Lake City center, in the city of Millcreek.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DETAILS before game🔥🏈 fundidoreslfa   🎥50 yds 70% power 💪🏻 #basic #fridaynightlights #lfg en Club de Football Ameri… https://t.co/mf2KH3B812]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you think when Granlund played there, the nets were three feet high off the ice, and a little to the right? #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Emily’s 18th Birthday 🎂 (@ B. K. Sweeney Uptown Grille in Garden City, NY) https://t.co/5MWWXCqclg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eric_Branch Why wouldn't Lynch at least try to drum up interest in #2 pick by publically talking up Murray? I woul… https://t.co/2gVh84ijSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookBubPartners any way to expedite getting an author profile setup on your site? thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurlingCanada @Lowetide @Curling_Alberta @TeamCareyCurl @chelscarey @sarahhwilkes @pooksbrown @danajferguson There… https://t.co/XNb1rTc0UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good day talking tech at Amway with a handful of business leaders.  Exciting things on the horizon. Thanks for the… https://t.co/kGYwBlgHkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roberttunstall @Electivirus Kingdom Hearts 2’s Critical difficultly halves the number of health upgrades players g… https://t.co/9jDoIhiORk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BajaChasr Yea try Disney worlds everything in Cali is super expensive especially now it’ll b cheaper I’m sure but airfare is gonna hurt]]></document><document><![CDATA[At ASU Open Door at Arizona State University West in West Phoenix. https://t.co/cIjV3z76M5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me desperté a las 8:00, dormí 4 horas nada más. Maldito espiritu de viejo sal de mi y déjame dormir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feisty_FL Yep, many illegal!! Then break our laws driving drunk!! Drunk drivers kill!! Hell no they go back to where you come from!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get a jump on your weekend and start looking for open houses scheduled now. Some are open on #Saturday as well as… https://t.co/SoL2smhVxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lajefajade I don’t need to smoke anything I want us to be as healthy as we can be no smoking no drinking the only… https://t.co/vmZIat6tiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyFieri is known for his DDD. During Fat Tuesday the NOLA Twi DDD were on the road to servicetown. Devin, Devin a… https://t.co/DHtBKVruST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattyB331 No interest. He wouldn’t succeed outside of a Brady/Rodgers-type offense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merritt out here living the dream!!! #merrclaire #ozziesdiner @ Ozzie's Diner https://t.co/AHYkOMDrOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#supermoon #Moon #night #nighttime #clearskies #dark #fullmoon https://t.co/RD3UnBY4pu @ Second Chance Clothing and… https://t.co/5nyL8Dp81e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, sad. What was the Turnout in each? Why? Yes why,  did so many voters stay home? #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife: If that’s what you want you can marry a girl from Orange County.  Me: No—no... no... no one should marry anyone from Orange County.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success is the progressive realization of a worth while dream #DoItTwiceDaily #GrowSZN . . . . . .… https://t.co/jJqxAbBiM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf “Build the wall” wasn’t compelling either. It was a pitiful three word mantra of inane stupidity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevAdamHamilton okay Rev I just spent an hour at work watching your video about the current crisis in the UMC. Pre… https://t.co/WGQ5yvymaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silver at 140lbs and silver in absolute. I was submitted twice by opponents who earned it. Props to them, it’ll mak… https://t.co/0FD6oFIOon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hospice of the Valley - Thunderbird PCU in Glendale, AZ https://t.co/yuOuoYFfcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickShielsPGA @TaylorMadeGolf @CallawayGolf @Titleist This is a great idea but I would like to see which combinati… https://t.co/eyf6Ln8zgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodmanHoops @Rob_LeP_UNC @WillAdkins11 @InsideCarolina https://t.co/YIL1p7Kq48]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's rather odd that any woman would believe that publicly publishing an abortion is their 'reproductive right.' Bu… https://t.co/6KWZjzr3Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh but that’s not acceptable. Embarrassing your partner is a sign of betrayal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/g5BwUnp9fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN How does @shotfighter26 have it scored after the first few rounds?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgieclemens @thomasmoreyouth @stmchapelhill @STMCSprincipal @KellyBrowne1 @frscottmccue @FrMatthewLC… https://t.co/oJq6UoGJKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished Bioshock 2. Very fun game until I became impossibly indestructible towards the end, and then they com… https://t.co/hzvQVHzkhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Editing is misleading. Makes it seem like parents are laughing at abuse. Uncool #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 2016 cycle, with its huge Republican field, the first formal announce was Ted Cruz ... on March 23, 2015.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed the game when it worked too, so I’m bummed as hell but if I can’t even start a single match after… https://t.co/rUjv2DkHjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phillies spending that stupid money to get Bryce Harper! 10 yrs/$330 mil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I STAND BY YOU MOST TIMES GOOD OR BAD, THIS WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT THE YOUNG MAN WAS BRUTALLY BEATEN… https://t.co/GswYwrqPrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicamreyes @AmakaUbakaTV @HeartEyes4Brady @antoinetteA @JC_NBCBoston @mariastephanos @jreineron7 @ericfisher… https://t.co/SSyYnGHbsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Maybe it will break off and float out into the Pacific! I know this is your state Devin, but it appears… https://t.co/JOq87vG3Df]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIVE LA CORRUPTION! Le Bloc soutient Trudeau dans l'affaire SNC LAVALIN. Il est d'accord avec un Accord de pousuite… https://t.co/Pm0Q5BSXUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put some effort into the things you do. Don’t half ass it, cuz once you start doing that you start creating bad habits. 🙅🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣can anybody get me insight on @Foxing 's set list for their tour rn? I see them in a few months but I wanna know w… https://t.co/seNO50LpkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is egregious. Stanley has so many good quotes too. Just proves Brian Kelly is an awful person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quinnipiac Men’s Lacrosse(@QU_MLAX) got its first win of the season against NJIT, 16-14. Quinnipiac is now 1-3 on t… https://t.co/Po4ACuJD0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had to sell my soul or give up McDonald’s.... I’ll make that a large fry and see y’all in hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrossingBroad nice pic... I had to make a small adjustment tho. @NHLFlyers @28CGiroux #StadiumSeries #LetsGoFlyers… https://t.co/tH6laOBtwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDawnMaly @lauraharris9595 Great meeting you two!!! I saw you walking on the main level as I was leaving but coul… https://t.co/ZyYSnKShBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanMofo2 @lockhart_jesse @JoeRoseShow @560Friedo I can't take you seriously when you say that because you are so… https://t.co/niKslwR2N1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iPolicy @BioBeef @TamarHaspel @jtiltonflood My wife suggests “fish removers.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katschott To quote Star Wars, if you strike me down I shall become more powerful than you can possibly imagine. Th… https://t.co/t60r9gko5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frc2706 @OttawaPiGroup @Raspberry_Pi @SciTechMuseum It was great to see the kids explore this last week! #rotaryphone #rjam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You get bad press because you are a bad prez. Liar, Sexual Predator, Putin's Russian Asset, Don't… https://t.co/nwwuMxpPhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schedule Update: Tuesday Feb. 26 @ Home 4:00 - WT v. Muleshoe  6:30 - WT v. Dalhart #AttitudeandEffort #RollTribe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please get a tv show with Megan Mullally and Nick Offerman off the sling commercials?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like visiting twitter for 2 things. Memes. And updating my profile/banner picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PizzaGateLibya @DCSharon @CoopersKingdom @TwitterMoments @mehdirhasan How did USA begin?And how was not a word hea… https://t.co/R3nwInXKH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love it if I had some type of verified lawyer on here. . YOU CAN OWN SOME ROYALTIES TO MY MUSIC.   Producer… https://t.co/KDMHYsCzml]]></document><document><![CDATA[VQ alert! Sneakers goes from Velcro straps to tying his laces like a #HIM. Come support him and bring your best mum… https://t.co/0jx0AUyzbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VINCE_RUGGIERO @BTB_MikeII @joey2900 @RFL630 @ChristinaMets15 you’re too fast for me! ☝🏼☝🏼☝🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning we’re at @Lina4HC’s Talking Transition Civic Saturday along with @hcfcd @METROHouston @BikeHouston… https://t.co/eXOiLxwpJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyoungjoo There was NO lineup at the Costco in Mississauga. It was the business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JZ_Flair @KingofAthens11 Seeing random wtf tweets on my timeline makes the world a better place. Continue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeBrownKY77, thank you for your leadership! @jmnemes, thank you for helping everyone see that this is about ou… https://t.co/ajScdkavo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no safe place for Jussie Smollett, he getting roasted any and everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[#writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram #tutorsofinstagram #poetry #poems #writing #freelance… https://t.co/9z6DJVdffy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToreyKrug 's song of choice tonight: "Whiskey In the Jar" by Metallica  #BruinsBeats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @pitopeludeo a lil #tb #youngprospects #rbi #Astros https://t.co/nla88PBjbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out for everyone who missed a chance coming get a MADE IN NOLA culture tee I will be doing a flash sale po… https://t.co/ca3m431vLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy St. Valentine’s Day everyone. Thank you all for your prayers and thoughts my mom is doing much better. #st.va… https://t.co/dSsd4wcvU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenofbrunch One time when they played at the Rabbit I was standing by the green room and he came out to a crowd… https://t.co/MJ2YNvvJSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations. I hope to see you continue your political career. I believe your future and our countries future a… https://t.co/mASGTGURpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashpoult @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/jRCPh2RBeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Everyone Should Know About Blood Clots https://t.co/c5tW9yNmWN via @clevelandclinic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaKosko Excellent and encouraging post—it's quite shareable, but that's not an option, so I'll use copy &amp; paste. Blessings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok watch any r Kelly live performance on YouTube and look at the audiences. You Cappin right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @drscott_atlanta @RepCummings Jim, can you also push to hold lawmakers accountable for when they lie? I… https://t.co/cuzWb3x7tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[16 year old Amy is back on her bs &amp; getting in her fuckin feelings right now 😂💀 #SoFarGone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyAStewart here they are. There are more but this is what they have out https://t.co/G4TOIt0qxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingerbums Oy you’re a cheep date like me one drink and your baked (nice to know I’m not the only one)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s a pretty sad day when the president of the United States is trying to negotiate for a more peaceful wo… https://t.co/lPBg9xbaVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day! ❤️⠀ _ 💪 Buy any 5lb Machine Whey Protein and you will receive 3 FREE Outright Almond Bars (C… https://t.co/Nz3fKpO2rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katpawsclaws The tax payers, including me are 177 billion dollars a year for illegal immigrants and your bitching… https://t.co/IuIRHwSYDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen this through FB.  What the hell is wrong with people https://t.co/Q2t75N8ON9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FitStarFlower Legit honest mistake so I just owned it and laughed about it... no pun intended but shit happens. It… https://t.co/Cqc1TT23Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @tacobell #skillschallenge is fun to watch... clearly it all comes down to the 3. #NBAAllStarWeekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think everyone is going to realize how good of qb Big Ben is after this year! Year after year they have great rec… https://t.co/qUXHd8GczD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi @SenatorSchumer  @GOPLeader  Do you ever think of the thousands of childre… https://t.co/nUUlY5k0c7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del Rosa CA Fri Feb 22nd PM Forecast: TONIGHT Mostly Clear Lo 34 SATURDAY Mostly Sunny Hi 59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this #cartoon We all have superpowers.  #happy https://t.co/SlpR2nSzwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapnCornelius I’m gonna say mid-30ies, but will take 40 - if he’s still gonna be with us. Otherwise, that’s gonna be tough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfannc5 Mornin brother!!☀️ Just another work day on this side of camp!!😪 What happenin on your side?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Mench one of my fav albums from last year. fun fact: her influences include Avril and Hillary Duff https://t.co/npWfHzFp1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[All day people have been posting about no longer supporting MJ and I was confused as to what Michael Jordan had bee… https://t.co/ldbih3PRHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely    The democrat states who have these ding bats and monsters representing their states...sad sad sad… https://t.co/kAzZ4iaVRZ]]></document></documents></author>