<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t know how everyone else’s morning is going so far, but I just fell all the way down the stairs..with my dog..b… https://t.co/1FbojvViQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RuPaul discussing my upcoming college graduation with my best friend. https://t.co/gAeV414z3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil is after me today  the morning I just had not going let him ruin my Valentine’s Day 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m asked to speak on certain subject matters, and in certain spaces, to certain people (think, anti-sex worke… https://t.co/3AZV9bjXNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GawdBodyHooper No, I used to work at call centers when I had no experience or education and everyone has too, call… https://t.co/YFRNzNz7N0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect weather for #vintageclothing shopping al fresco! With vintagechicdk  geraldine_vintage  dee_dees_creations… https://t.co/FyembkDjNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started my engineering degree at CC. @uofl has a great partnership with @Jefferson_JCTC that makes transferring e… https://t.co/43IPmxPEKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@23antoniomarcos @ZARATHOOSTRA1 @DauntlessCandy @cruzzer71 @tictoc Aye, exacatmente no es nada para nadie - totalme… https://t.co/8K3sCWRT7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freesoulless For today’s class, if you could please take out your notebooks and pencils:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tartine is a charming neighborhood restaurant with plenty of merits—one of which being that it is BYO. There really… https://t.co/ItoIWQozME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News12HV doing a story on @MSA_Security?? You guys know K9 Mattie! Now dogs can be torn from military families and… https://t.co/2sV0SV9BtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m not done. I’m annoyed when people say ‘real-a-tor’ instead of realtor. It’s LITERALLY spelled exactly how it… https://t.co/qkVnrwIerH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water is leaking out of an electrical outlet on the wall. I’m not going to be turning on any of those three switches for awhile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when you get #TMobile Home and Entertainment, Engineering and #MetroByTmobile together? Powerful discu… https://t.co/nYFDyrW5Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focused on a healthy relationship, my money, my credit &amp; keeping God by my side at all times 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaviota330 Look at that head tilt.... she's asking "What is it you'd like me to do? Perfect PTSD companion dog.. perfect....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today the Artsy Fartsy Art Lessons studio will be closed in order to lead a paper mosaic project at Kent Kids Art D… https://t.co/U0M2A66PVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tropical fruit 🌴🌴#fruit #tropical #sexychefwendy @ThePerezHilton @MichaelDinich @ElizabethAHD @MorganStrebler https://t.co/8OMw7hq22e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yelich_ivana @MacLeodLisa Not at all true.  Leaving families without proper funding is what she is working hard at… https://t.co/CFjt18NYIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunwatchers released a sick album today &amp; they're playing it for us. 2.22.19 . #sunwatchers #theglove #tgif… https://t.co/ZdDRiCUzkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Would Cohen be stupid enough to lie? Did his hubris get the better of him? I wouldn’t have thought less of his t… https://t.co/xBtEcv0pti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_giselflores they were so amazed 😂😂 but hey free drinks are free drinks 🤷🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this semester is gonna go by so quick bc it’s about to be March and next thing you know it’s fucking November]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a shepherd seeketh out his flock in the day that he is among his sheep that are scattered; so will I seek out my… https://t.co/JUQfqIBU8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbuseinV Never at any time have I wanted to or made any attempt to message him. Move on. F’real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the world is burning up, self-driving cars are coming, I think I’ll buy a BMW M4 turbo stick and drive as hard and fast as I can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herewegokids7 @cheri4trump The basket has to hold 63 million people,  we can fit more in though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine worrying about what other women do in their life and with their body, lmao ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New medical alert bracelet order. Thanks @amazon. #epileptic #epilepsy #EpilepsyAwareness 🎗💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mc_gisel @alana33534686 @highdratedhunni That would be the best thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truck vs. vehicle accident on on mm 44.2 on 80 Westbound.  NSP says driver was pinned inside vehicle...we do not ha… https://t.co/FXgHkxZQz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Location in Madera is hosting, I just checked the list. Share away!  #share #babysavingday]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex claims she dumped me because I “look like a dyke” so casually imma post more pics of me “looking like a dyke”… https://t.co/G6AWvFeI0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateSoumas @NBCNews I clicked on the link. So the child deserved it because he stuck his hand out with a sock on? I stand by what I said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bishopoftyler I wish my own bishop had your courage but he remains mute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m writing a research paper about how the shut down of planned parenthood will affect the public heath. If you hav… https://t.co/QlP52zAEYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tawang tawa nanaman ako hanep 😂 nagdrama na nga sinabihan pang may bebe 🤦🏻‍♀️ anuna sana nga meron 😪 https://t.co/2HhIGfscPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Thank you for always liking my comments it’s taken me awhile but I really like the show very much !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaels_mom @michaelmuhney @Derek__James Family is great at any time of day!  Hope you all have a great visit.  I… https://t.co/WWyHpKb0FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to bed at really-1a, woke up at really-5a.  This really-sux #DaylightSavings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone forgot to tell him it's not tongue out Tuesday! https://t.co/iHOP2Cn2gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franklin man sentenced to 9 years for child porn. He's 1 of 5 men from SW Ohio caught in FBI's Operation Pacifier -… https://t.co/s7bcHnRqMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onewiththesand So, so sweet. I just want to “boop, boop” their precious little noses.🐾😁🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump No ur passionate about money because u have narcissist personality disorder like Daddy Princess. Addit… https://t.co/eRjw7HADQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanakn @shaunking More work to be done. Is this common across the country? And what is the economic, personal societal cost?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to see the shield together again and back in action this sunday at @WWE fast lane this sunday.… https://t.co/GBWYWCW1fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs good music like this in their life. 😍💃 "Oldens by Kaylee Bryson" https://t.co/D20Xp8JiSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the rest of the day I’ll be continually yelling “30 YEARS OF MY LIFE!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus it's really hard to get mental health disability. Most of the time, people get turned down the first time they… https://t.co/hLSkiDByLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true! @amycwang this is why we need to conduct our mixed methods project!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyNoellex Girl that yard the same look I’m getting wow twining 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my coworkers is giving me major anxiety about the pending announcement of the deputy conservator positions a… https://t.co/pxO6eWyEc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fool me ☝🏾 time shame on you Fool me ✌🏾 can’t put the blame on you  Fool me 3 times, fuck the peace sign, load the… https://t.co/wIu1eJJXSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be annoying and continue posting about it like an ******* but it’s literally my favorite part of my day when I go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyCourtney23 @NosEnergyDrink We are waiting... https://t.co/ywEtz7jqvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im getting ready to go out by my pizza box and back to bed and watching Netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7_revealed @P_dPowell @CarolynDeniseL1 @DawnparksDawn @asouefan1 @Butta_15 @val_dmmc @markofzene @torij126… https://t.co/eWEAdD32lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanduh1287 I care!!!! I still can’t decide if I want to move there after graduation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had like 4 hours of sleep last night and I’m about to work until 12am and I have the worst headache ever and i really just wanna smoke]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Green New Deal can learn something from the old New Deal. It can’t all be done in one package without specifics… https://t.co/7CtqheyzSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommasGoneCity @blackrock But the DEMOCRATS are going to take care of all of us🤣🤣🤣🤣☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiring 6 new female dancers in NJ call for info @ Kenilworth, New Jersey https://t.co/00gANuHcrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @willbl Congratulations...been a long time to come. .over 100 years in trying . .wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @AOC Weekend Update: Girl You Wish You Hadn't Started a Conversation With..  YOU WILL SEE AOC!!  you really will!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Wow. I applause her for speaking up and standing her ground. And f that guy telling her to stop. DONT STOP 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed interviewing some of the Women on the Move at the onyxmag luncheon today!! LOTD: Blue and white gingham p… https://t.co/qHsvNF31Nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weathernetwork Just a lovely day out there yet again. Driving in Sleet and Snow after the Freezing  Rain in the da… https://t.co/3VyRIfxr6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow has finally begun to accumulate in lower Manhattan. https://t.co/MiXiMEeUhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to think I could do literally anything and sleep was for chumps.   Jet lag has determined that to be a lie.… https://t.co/YXWatW6JBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind starting to enter central Maryland, expect wind gust to 50mph or more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will i ever not have a problem with my love life even when i didn’t want one in the first place?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going through old videos from 2018  Whispers to myself “wow 2018 me needed a whole lotta Jesus”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwentyER @AnquanBoldin @Ravens Teammates delivered. Best. Day. Ever. 2/3/13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to watch Fleabag with @ChrisBerg25 tonight was the best decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one has had this much hype since Lebron, when you Obama coming to see you then your hype is through the roof, ho… https://t.co/XfWjZFPKi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’m seeing here is a white man apologizing for the racism of other white men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El unico plan q tienen organizado es el de desfalcar la nacion y matraquear]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but have you seen my lower body??? no other animal description will do it justice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makenziebrooke_ @LivePdFans As a law enforcement officer I have NEVER refused to feed anyone. I have given clothes… https://t.co/K3Z8yv6pRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump should have been arrested long before he ever had a chance to run for President.  Like if you agree. R… https://t.co/PjKCbLGDlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotQuiteAndrew @kinkwitch @WesterosHistory OOP also what I said! I think reforging could look cool on camera too t… https://t.co/otZ9wEPLiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish I could go back to the point where I owned zero items and my room was always clean]]></document><document><![CDATA[there are ppl out there who will share this and say something along the lines of:   “SEE LOOK HES NOT RACIST BUT YA… https://t.co/2HZY9lvJGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a $50 Amazon gift card from @eBookBetty Check it out! https://t.co/rTRxtnbqRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 ... I have been challenged by @Mr_Jones_1776 to post the covers of my top 7 books with no explanation or revi… https://t.co/W3lrqNB1ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skeletizzle @TheRickWilson I know and no one is talking about it. This story needs to gain some traction. Where is the outrage]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was picture worthy. Steak n Shrimp! Dinnertime! @ Foxys Landing Restaurant https://t.co/ESgS00XQKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Owen’s right here. Leo doesn’t know these people. They are complete strangers to him. All he would do is freak out #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCaroLove Ah, nope - Highview. They installed a new boiler a few months ago and it's been wonky all winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caramelicedtea It did happen in 1992 when I was on my way to Michigan. We had a layover and there was a commotion.… https://t.co/ik3orW1sT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rebuke (until GOT is over) all previous comments made about the world ending. thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @LindseyGrahamSC Will he before or after the intellectual giants Diamond and Silk?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you agree with ⁦@POTUS⁩ declaring a national emergency to get funding for a border wall? It’s our #wakeMEup conv… https://t.co/fSLw8JIiHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Fabletics I ordered my first pair of leggings from you guys and the package got stolen off the front door? Can you help??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biochemistry: Ligases - a cartoon. Definitely something that students won't forget... #humor #lol #smirk #hilarious https://t.co/m5epJioSgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shows in NYC this week. Come party. #thingstodoinnyc #standupcomedy #freecomedy #comedyshow @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/0VubZWLoZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenaFriedman I think the detail is just necessary since people rabidly think he was incapable of that.   I'm proud… https://t.co/ppw9nep1qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyDeal4 @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Apparently the Dumps @realDonaldTrump condone having sexual relati… https://t.co/EFa1KNTRUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the @realTTCU website! Become a member and unite to #KeepAmericaGreat.  https://t.co/Tltjgajclp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this is fancy.  #catSpa (@ Hit the showers!! in Deerfield, NY) https://t.co/QkmvHcFXvW https://t.co/dEVToECS88]]></document></documents></author>