<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tech at Iowa State Oklahoma at K-State.  Saturday.  Tech and K-State have at least a share of the Big 12 title on the line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why Trump’s “Muslim Ban” is just another political farce.  Just like his wall.  Just like his fake media cl… https://t.co/lNcCvOqHlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jett and I were watching Criminal Minds and he said “WHO COMES UP WITH THIS STUFF” I smiled to myself and said. “wr… https://t.co/X52To0CsD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Mag_ie_ real feminist icons. the representation matters. aang was cool but katara was the reason everything happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way the jazz would touch him especially with his resent behaviors thank god the jazz are not on his short list.… https://t.co/bxlN58gDZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Dont know why but the Britney Spears song Oops!... I Did It Again keeps popping up in my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[once I found that it's saving me a huge amount of $$, not to mention a great workout for a dude who HATES going to… https://t.co/xHmG5I98Mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stealthcrypto1 @realDonaldTrump What’s the point of trump 1999 tweet. You tweeted that it is “believed to” have pa… https://t.co/KrkUBT3bLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeaceLoveNGames Holographic chess like game where the pieces fight each other. I suggest you let your furry opponent win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero sexo oral y anal contigo amor bello a love ❤ me gustas mucho mucho a LOVE ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucaslagoons Did I win? ! Lol . Love your program and your ridiculous talent ⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skullanbone @PostDisclosure Drop some truly disruptive technology where it affects the wallets of those with means… https://t.co/sVLucMWlNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another paper, using both ribbon-like and planar structures to do a wider range of shapes of resulting 3-d things:… https://t.co/L7z9h7F5tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the lion goes the spoiled.  So take your rotting carcass spoils and fuck off now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retired9941 Quote: "Accepting homosexuality led to accepting transgenderism and will likely lead to accepting pedo… https://t.co/qS63Fc4Jxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNL is even more New York centric than usual tonight, but it’s also a great episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geekchic9 The “peace line” and other murals nearby, separating Catholics and Protestant neighborhoods in Belfast.… https://t.co/lyo6KqYw4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you feel the need to talk shit about my taste buds go fuck yourself bud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously question the idea that there are "multiple" $300 million contract offers out there for Harper. Gotta wo… https://t.co/ZqXKe82HXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @MMouser1 Because he was the only one n that locker room that didn’t know. So....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSasse #CantHide that you may be forgetting the “real costs” to live meaning the % required for each categories… https://t.co/AfvVNJD3jG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booty_platinum @Fapnormousyt @Unyque1983 @MahoganyRossxxx @bbwjulieginger @PinkKandiShoppe @LylaEverwettt… https://t.co/uKUllGBR9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[day one hundred and eighty eight // life on the road  Got the mobile work station going today from my @AloftHotels… https://t.co/tBpxc9l3Sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnerlou72 @DTrumpPoll @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Did your boyfriend give you that black eye?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at the gym at 7 this morning then I went straight from the gym to work and straight from work to 2nd shift cl… https://t.co/LqhRu7MhMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @DenverTeachers People is following Bernie Sanders you people are nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir @reply #Seattle makes me happy! It means enjoying family and breathing in the fresh air! 💚 #iFlyAlaska https://t.co/FOqbHB3Mbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe Thank God, someone has to come back and bust up these haters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great send off to a great man insta_kostya anywhere you go, they are lucky to have you!  . regularsbar keep… https://t.co/ob6jrTyrWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryleigh: “Daddy, when you blink does it make the whole world go dark?”  #dadlife #kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwhittalTWN @weathernetwork @StormhunterTWN @Seetvdocs @NikonCanada This is my snowbank and nobody is going to melt it on me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I bought these pants today ...... my wife thinks they are cute ....  @NickJacksonYB @MattJackson13 https://t.co/FxD22B1hP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcybelle424 @CynicXyz @silael1 @AbdulElSayed You would try to hide money too if the government was taking half your income lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallodemoraes @f_g_zampieri @marcelo_zapata @efan75 Here’s a later trial: https://t.co/ntWyX9vu7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Persuasion_Elli نمیدونم چه حسی برای خود اون دونفر داره ولی عاشق بودن و دوست داشتن این چیزها رو نمیشناسه 😉😉😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein There can’t be secret deals talk about a dark government this is truly a shadow government this is ou… https://t.co/nOnGKLh5F5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to repeat myself, again. Trump is not fit by any standard to be President of this country. His CPAC rant… https://t.co/vhVFp267Ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaranged @bill_slawski @DavidAmerland @JohnMuirTrust @methode @JohnMu https://t.co/zImgVfBUFG just completed David… https://t.co/eAHlC3MoQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soko3 Never played but the best story I heard was Farmer spiking it in Cody’s face...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bahahaha   "Alex Jones must submit to sworn deposition in Sandy Hook case, judge rules"  https://t.co/D6jnDVpiSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed north very quickly back towards Essex along the Connecticut River. @ Haddam, Connecticut https://t.co/GOsMw8TFUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BsbCheetahs One of our competitors, I just don’t get it.  Why try to diminish what some other team worked hard for and earned.  Classless]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a quick trip this weekend to see the water. @ Clear Lake Park https://t.co/SXjjsP7ZPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chilakajc @TPointUK @charliekirk11 @RealCandaceO @dominiquetaegon https://t.co/T3fvzbc7Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week from today.....looking forward to experience the squeal of the reel😀!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisMorganSmi Haha dude it’s such a good show! The entire show is incredible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying @MarcelMcClinton announcement for Houston City Council at large 3 with his fellow March for our Lives… https://t.co/ArP3ClmDTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattparsons24 @tjstanley15 @JMac2o2 @TiqueTP21 @CNN Lmao you misinterpretation of what I said is indicative of you… https://t.co/796MK6XQkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonniedaWestie @XPets1 @macwhittle @MillieOTLFP @TheMobyKeech @We4Dogs @BonniedaWestie What lager yoo hiding behin… https://t.co/bE9ojfD2T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurt_loder @chrismcquarrie @mattzollerseitz Awesome performance. And movie for that matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinregpad But who leaves for Brown? And how does that affect Cohens numbers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to listen to some audiobooks while I finish this last hour of work]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you live in the DMV and are looking for a great venue for your next company meeting, youth athletic team meeting… https://t.co/t2koYq8fAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Oscars into by Queen was way better than the Super Bowl halftime show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jus got finished playing some Madden now I’m watching the SpursVsRaptors game]]></document><document><![CDATA[28-0! @LexHSBasketball 64, @GooseCreekHoops 40 (final). @mason2carver with 28 points to lead Wildcats, who tie scho… https://t.co/4SXY4Q05t8]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I forget to bring my canvas bag to the grocery store one more time i swear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tothe_MaxT @MIRANDAjarrett @marshmellomusic @svddendeathdub @MattSteffanina Damn dude killer as always]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hung Eyelids by #EmilKazaz #fineart #drawing #contemporaryart #artforsale #artwork #artgallery #fineartgallery… https://t.co/TYmH9JzuiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stef2dotoh Don’t think we’ve had any tech issues, but I’m passing this on to our engineers.  Thanks for the heads up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love talking business wit my mom and my sister we’ve got some BIG things planned for our family s future]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛑Trump kissed campaign worker without her consent, lawsuit claims #Topbuzz https://t.co/QaKq2g45PM 🛑HE GOAT NEVER C… https://t.co/RvNMJKVdtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9NEWS @GShapiro9News Wakng up to Kyle, Susie and spots in 4x3 format. Life is good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Other than 45, does anyone else take you seriously?  Not that I mind your insistence on commenting - yo… https://t.co/vMR4BP62jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can a cat melt your cold loveless heart?   @zoe_kpoptv and I tackle animal therapy. #cats #catvideos #comedy… https://t.co/NP6XvetZFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow #blackeducatedandbroke on twitter @bebpodcast_atl, Subscribe to us on #SoundCloud &amp; #iTunes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slave2Sin @DoctorRaulDuke8 @CherSpitsitOut @DillingerLucas Awesome!!! Lucky girls!!! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynne Patton: ‘Racist’ Rashida Tlaib Played ‘Race Card’: ‘That Is Not the Resume of a Prop’ | Breitbart… https://t.co/03xYvMU6cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got that Midwest cold weather survivor guilt right now. https://t.co/4gTN1uXATX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, Dolan’s right. It’s not an opinion. It’s a legitimate fact that he should sell the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fact #facts #FavoriteThisTweet #pride #fyre #mannequinchallenge #HTGAWM https://t.co/wiI7cpcMgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[With snow levels down around 2,000 feet last night you can rest assured that there's a lot of snow in the mountains… https://t.co/4JVXhhjjD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucciJoseph @JoeMunyon @PhilMickelson @PGATOUR How about the oldest buys 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough, replace every republican voting against us protecting the border]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Just do what the hell he wants! Okay putting the kids in jobs not my first thought! But if they don’t cle… https://t.co/Tq2F9lzaow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarzanHarrison @COACHZOO88 @roberson_derick @GCoachdibo @Coach_JJohnson @_CoachJhill @CBuck08 @UIWFootball… https://t.co/iDcZdkHeb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INforests @ratiomom Sounds like public forest private profits. Private kickbacks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why We #Fail | 90 Seconds For Your #RealEstate Career  | EP52 https://t.co/QaL2Hae3Kh via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one in particular I have to agree, that’s why I said shit like this, oppose to saying order this. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun event tonight with the @ChesterfieldCC Young Professionals at the networking event at @Steambellbeer. https://t.co/DYTO42ihGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADDiane Don't be, you aren't going any more nervous then any one else, talking about your life, problems or anythi… https://t.co/viS82EGkvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of some of my very good friends. @Coach_jowen @coachlollar @Coach_Patrick9 @geauxtwl @CoachBeech… https://t.co/1kZ5y30AwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum What gives? It’s not even raining and the connection has kicked the bucket. https://t.co/3WU8k5A9H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diverse perspectives on public transportation from state to state, all with sound policy foundations. Thanks for th… https://t.co/mKjf1MmMbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickhansonMN visiting my bro who wrestles for ASU and then moving to LA in 3 weeks! You better fucking visit soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manslaper Sir, the monkey’s out of the bag and has been hiding your keys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stclairashley It's because feminism has lost its way. It's no longer about women's rights and empowerment.  It's a… https://t.co/WEdsFLpxpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know everyone would be disappointed if I came to #SanFrancisco and I didn’t post pictures from #Sakana. So here t… https://t.co/PuHApLtElJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlowstickEntmt drew a picture of dread ducky controlling me https://t.co/3PMsuQAnqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The peacefulness of being together by a pool late at night in February.#joespagnolo #lisaspagnolo @ Caribe Cove Res… https://t.co/5CpNS9IlPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT DO YOU MEAN IT’S THURSDAY ALREADY! 😱 PC: @wingchair  . #mood #photography #portrait #comedy #yikes #smile… https://t.co/Ne8qoZfzf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up at 10 o clock on your screen is Tropicana Field, where people don't go watch the Rays play. @IndyCar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @skinnypresident You just need to take a step back for a moment Ann  For some reason, you seem to be, p… https://t.co/QcR7t6iSa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @frederickhiller 4/ Am I missing something here? The individual machines don't seem to be insecure.… https://t.co/xyRtkxLi7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Sounds fine in principle. But there are no honest ppl in djt's circle. None whatsover. https://t.co/kQNzvGNKYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PEbasketball @InsiderExposure @EGBHoops @CKPremierBall @LBInsider @LBoogie213 @695HOOPS @skREESE32 @PBevBallNPrep… https://t.co/aV01oEAgul]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I hate worse than Tennessee is their theme song Rocky Top]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin palabras ❤️😍💋 . . #sergiojimenezphotography #photographyeveryday #cameramentv #photographystreet #vagabundo… https://t.co/lAFJyZzidv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you want to create an online course ... but don't want to 'go it alone?' Then check out my upcoming Coursepreneu… https://t.co/x0BdMs7wsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aQuiteQuietNerd @TwitterLive @enews Nobody! Thats Who!!! (Look! The Lamestream Media is Dying! And They CAN'T ACCEPT IT!!! Classic!!!)]]></document></documents></author>