<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[He wants to know, why Lizzie got to go with me.  And I am sure she told him that she got a treat (the vet gave her… https://t.co/RCvybRtOzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to go to the casino for the day with my parents 😌 hopefully winning big lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xinracthis Need more friends too #PokemonGO #TeamMystic https://t.co/qPbG62RuQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brown people have such funny metaphors and sayings. Just heard a brown auntie call something a “pile of filth.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySki Was there a reason they had to rush out of Las Vegas? Something about the abrupt departure made no sense. #sisterwives]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have reported many tweets of Donald Frump.   He is instigating violence among his “base” towards individuals, Dem… https://t.co/dV9oQto8LR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonknightgirl85 @4CherBear67 @JaimeRKOFan @stormteaser19 @Sheridanrosie78 @nkotb_roze @CncBhDdubminion… https://t.co/lwmqVYSPgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree.getting worried they r gonna escape unscathed. What do we care manafort and cohen r going to jail mainly 4… https://t.co/9K0tnXaCTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone brought Dippin' Dots to the bar for me tonight and I just don't even know how I got so lucky. 😂🙌🏼❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetETennessee @washingtonpost 50% of the country became apathetic and stopped voting. We stopped paying attentio… https://t.co/dNobunXCEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follett Corporation is hiring in #Scranton, PA! Read about our latest #CustomerService job opening via the link in… https://t.co/pW2aq8eBVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Enterprise Holdings? We're hiring in #StateCollege, PA! Click for details: https://t.co/0ILjqtudp7 #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaliDeplorable @jlsarg_john Why arn’t we paying our debt down with this money?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr8gscott @MayorJoyceCraig @mht_nh_health @cmchealth Wonderful story literally saving lives. I serve as a consumer… https://t.co/bQATJ7LopQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know work has absorbed your life when you realize you have been scouring Getty Images for way too long to find… https://t.co/pCjF1fOo4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[We coming for ya!! #swat #creep #prowl @CBS @swatcbs https://t.co/JbDSJLa0Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bone marrow aspiration from my sternum. Felt like my skeleton was being yanked out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaBodell Agree with my neighbors @RepMattKrause - fix the definition of “toll project” please. I’m another coh… https://t.co/jXOrmjA03c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alpharaye I’m voting for Elizabeth Warren. She’s been ignored b/c of the parade that looks an awful lot like what… https://t.co/Zj6D4BQKh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissyAnn7876 @Pedal2DMetals @Aug1405 @HLAurora63 @Razorsmack1 @whatznextfolks @TrumperSeaney @clovis1931… https://t.co/TXsy4Oid51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDesireSeries I don’t know how I’d narrow it down to just one. Probably the one where Jim and Pam finally kiss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wealthy white girls traveling for months at a time to exploited nations to “find themselves” is a form of coloniali… https://t.co/lUNdRKUOFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏽‍♀️🤨 @abronxchick @birdieglad @jihettly  @pannlewis44 @graceslick77 @veterans_i @Robin_Volpi @johnsondavid601… https://t.co/DqpHQakudE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I have often been asked whether I am a women or an athlete. The question is absurd. Men are not asked that. I am a… https://t.co/kIVrmxtTt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s a strange place to be— to realize you care more deeply about someone than they care about you. unfortunately t… https://t.co/EfS29ZEAsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#coltfordconcert #thelacsconcert @ North Carolina https://t.co/7pvhJHBtvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B103Rockford Weekend was awesome watching these kiddos with the Championship! #rockfordroadrunners https://t.co/gTcNFYi4r1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Cost Accountant" at Leonardo DRS? Applicant tracking systems look for specific keywords. U… https://t.co/E2rSIiCIlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You too Ves....heard from Faz this morning..he said to tell everyone hello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic home, move in ready- Schedule your showing today! 😃🏠 https://t.co/I342stl7nC https://t.co/FA2NZRiNkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me last night after 11: oh dang I'm so tired, I'm not setting an alarm and I'm getting up after 7am so I can be wel… https://t.co/z8VF4r6vaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #CBJ took Wennberg out of the line up and the whole team can’t score!? Multiple people keep pass instead of sho… https://t.co/0zevgNG2kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast Who cares? Obama poses with Farrakhan and Hillary ( I think) sleeps with bill. Big story here Beast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@len7weets the sweetest Siberian Husky- Scarlett https://t.co/eF3ReBWlNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paintsoundpress @BoycottUtah My granny on her death bed said ..Never let anyone tell you how you feel...Till one g… https://t.co/0Km6jD7HHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had access to the tentative program of President Bolsonaro's visit to Washington. Here is part of the schedule -… https://t.co/lQaCaG1qiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ we’ve never had a duesome but more importantly we’ve never had multiple sex”]]></document><document><![CDATA[u know you really fine wine and dined urself when u fed urself a box of chocolates, sushi, sake bombs, and a whole… https://t.co/PRlXpyGtIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Believer037 @PoeticPastries @POSITIVEandUPL1 @julesrprecious @fourcornersfld @MMcLaughlinsong @julie_dibble… https://t.co/TKAZB0fRuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its that time of year again. 😋 @McDonaldsCanada  #yourfavoritedriver https://t.co/fOknjRyZhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @cyntmarshall is a riot! Talking about how she told her college boyfriend “I will call you when I graduate!” And… https://t.co/0ImJVxGQL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that Pokémon Go doesn’t have an Ash Wednesday themed event just means they’re not trying hard enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#diorrouge #dior you killed it with this simple. Enough product to really try the colors. Great packaging. You can… https://t.co/1oAyLrxG1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pop into one of our Career Day presentations at AIMS!  https://t.co/6iBlLnXIAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[After life had us crying, laughing and leaving us hopeful. Thank you Ricky Gervais for another great series. Love y… https://t.co/bdTCFNvhrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaturePornVids From my experience with domestic cats I would say Ali is feeling crowded and needs his own territory with a few friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Jersey makes the best clouds. ☁️ #NJ #NJTP #clouds https://t.co/fVS3MlmoYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm.  Up and have nommed.  Considering getting the E streetcar before heading to my planned meeting, and bonus that… https://t.co/BIpAuD0ldi]]></document><document><![CDATA[somebody in this house is gonna have to cough up $250 since one of my car keys is missing 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows 4. 2017: Trump gets added to investigation TWO YEARS after it began because FBI realized Trump was… https://t.co/HuHDjeeuRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @GregNorberg @sherry25793049 @UnitedHomepage Oh Lord.  😳 But more accurate!  😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. The people here are so friendly and chatty. Not just staff in shops and restaurants but the general public too.… https://t.co/dUb8QTUg2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regrese de mi último viaje el 28 de Diciembre y para el 6 de Enero ya había comprado los boletos de avión para mi p… https://t.co/Nsh36l0T1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASU HELP AZ HELP US.  Wear it with pride.  T-Shirts   Large $23.99   ExLarge $24.99  Make checks/MO out to Mary Wh… https://t.co/mbOnr4OmuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hpsacredtext Hi there-I wanted to let you know that somehow I was recently automatically unsubscribed from your Pa… https://t.co/yta67UXqlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for tonight’s premiere of #JustAddRomance with @MeghannFeghann and #LukeMacfarlane on @hallmarkchannel a… https://t.co/cvsgkpMBvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My third article is up! This month I discussed the challenges of horse shopping...🤔🤫 horseauthority #horsecolumn… https://t.co/tN6ZANQIZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy bc even though Ari seem so lame to me now the girl so damn fine it’s crazy I can’t even unfollow ha ass on ig lmao smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing I could be there to witness @STUWH history, but cheering from Ottawa! #gotommiesgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle I really miss seeing you on Live PD.  I wanted to come to the Watch Party, just can't.  This is goi… https://t.co/XGYzFipqme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentally trying to convince myself it’s not that cold out and I need to get outside for a run #BundleUp #YouCanDoIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been the same since someone told me shrimp the cockroaches of the sea]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking at houses in Conroe makes me so excited for my future, I cannot wait to find my perfect home and start over]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when people forget my birthday, friendly reminder: 10 days! Friday, March 15 https://t.co/MLTIiuvqfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rubbed the belly for good luck 👋 💛  📷: kuya_jeremy @ Morikami Museum and Japanese Gardens https://t.co/Hf2kAgA5Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldCarr @itsSpencerBrown @seanspicer @marthamaccallum @FoxNews @yaf Take your own advice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarzChainz Have you spent any time researching #QAnon? Mostly primary sources and directives for people to do thei… https://t.co/Ra7yjoljwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere Are we getting MLBTV subscriptions this year? #padresfanswanttoknow #Machado @Padres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even on a cold, rainy, dark day Charlottesville is utter perfection. I grabbed dinner at an adorable little French… https://t.co/ZwRmSxeLnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know Twitter has completely destroyed your sense of humor when you laughed out loud at this]]></document><document><![CDATA[The water from the fire hoses freezes so fast, firefighters make sure to bring in salt trucks to help the roads out… https://t.co/54X7xbLsmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump He’s doing what he does everyday: tweeting, eating junk food, golfing. #LaziestPresidentEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriticLeeMovies My husband and 22 year old son LOVED Captain Marvel. They thought it was great, including the musi… https://t.co/2l6EjuM4pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up, @caribu - FaceTime meets Kindle for Kids with 200k+ paid users, targeting military families and grandparen… https://t.co/0GYNw4Pajj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silence is Consent. [Maria Ressa] I do not consent I will not consent I will hold #Tech Accountable.… https://t.co/2WRE41shQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I inherited the Thank You card from work from the family of @Redsfan304. The Personnel Mgr told me that no one else… https://t.co/lDPi96fBDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Neal Overall Finalist top 10 MI DECA in Business Services Operations #captainpride #wkhs_deca https://t.co/gYuNRIjgdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Quieres mejorar tu piel? ¿Quieres contribuir con un buen  Resultado! 💚🖤💥💥💥🖤💚🖤 Te presentamos el mejor Shake del mu… https://t.co/KcjyMuFEiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else feel like when your PMSing the littlest shit can throw off your whole day? I’m talkin minuscule]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note To Self: #freeshipping #nofinderfees #freegiftcards  Shop with #VanessaJ @VAzFemFabFun @ Saks Fifth Avenue https://t.co/al8DxTcXRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopping for some more Chardonnay. (@ Wikieup Trading Post in Wikieup, AZ) https://t.co/4ycsCQCtqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mastercard Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/5YIqethgHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about how productive I was with jet lag when I got back from Sri Lanka. I did two-a-days at the gym, y’all! I never do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @RoleplayWendys @ZeeMarieK and @HeroKing7077 for winning my 200 follower raffle! I’ll be dming you soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #NDEagles stole the show! Congratulations ladies 🤗🤗 https://t.co/IPe2S4YRFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying by @KeshaRose will never not make me want to cry when I hear it]]></document><document><![CDATA[sectors or the activities covered by each sector as may be necessitated by the circumstances of each sector or acti… https://t.co/DYQl7kT6PL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Alpena, MI! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Retail Sales Associate / Star… https://t.co/eg2uSkWqs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I care too much about my Spotify clout and not enough about my LinkedIn clout]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be a part of this really exciting weekend!!! Can’t way to dabble in some new indie games. Are you an… https://t.co/iKFm2sjUYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally don’t even care and fast forwarded the whole Nicole being bullied but not really because she’s kind of th… https://t.co/NxpLP0Jsv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullpenbabe @crazycharisma @elefantvanishes @Zippy_TMS Except me maybe? 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence God bless you. Relax a take care of yourself. We miss your incredible force of positive nature ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to start working at my new location this week.🥰 Even though I’ll miss the girls from my old one.☹️ m… https://t.co/03DIwRCD4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned on Beerbongs and Bentley’s as we cruised into New Jersey to complete the mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful chance to win a book! @kalysta12 @ajromanowski23 good luck everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doskey64 @Union_Jacky @Disorganised1 @jessix @LilyLilyMaynard That only means it would be preferable to improve our HRT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Esto comieno papas de los paw patrol” basta chicos, como se puede extrañar tanto a un enano de un metro o menos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't you have more inportant things to do as your allways on vacation you appear to way behind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join my Cimorelli group on Messenger by visiting: https://t.co/JrbE4tc4rU]]></document></documents></author>