<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@fragileheart And they sound like they’re from “Jeuhsey” rather than Australia or whatever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanBroaddus @HelmanDC @Marcus_Mosher @VoiceOfTheStar ... the best thing for a cowboys fan is to turn off all new… https://t.co/TOnUbS3s93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Studies Show that Vaccinated Individuals Spread Disease - https://t.co/bQmEI8h9Y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it happen.. Emma &amp; team have done a tremendous job! #PRSSA #PRStudChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to BoozeDancing TV! https://t.co/rCiAyL9Kjh via @YouTube @boozedancing #donttellme #showme #boozyvideo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpatricksmith is too late to kraft an opinion for #reasonabledoubt @markgeragos @adamcarolla #besthour]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:37.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know who you don't see Tweet'n their asses off anymore? Anthony Smith fans, that's who... where did y'all go??😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chilly2u Totally 100 percent agree with you....but my point is the joy it brings some to see the sport struggle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I felt my country had failed me. Whatever that means. And I fled to a new country. I would want to learn the lan… https://t.co/quvSCpVZJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News!! Donald Trump will not build the Most Beautiful Wall on the Mexican border. The Wall Will Be Built A… https://t.co/qKCgSZREd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new year started with new tracks dropping from @HeyNove and @ohtistheartist https://t.co/533JNBGbSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darsal @RidingAmokAG @peterkrupa @LhasaCM @BikeEveryDay I still miss my 95 Toyota Tacoma 4x4 sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I have nothing to learn from the person who beat me by 4 million votes.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I'm Malik or Enoch... I'm singing the thong song just loud enough for Diakite to hear it, just to aggravate him.… https://t.co/98TbYx1Cvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dental Meeting Magic in 360’. I had a BLAST performing as the luncheon break entertainment and may have numbed some… https://t.co/jvtFTdaEK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HoyconMhoni #MartesdeMhoni @mhonividente 🧿 @ClubMhoniFans @magdaproducer ✨📺🔮🎬🎥 @programa_hoy @Canal_Estrellas… https://t.co/WS4YkuohlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrFan Wow! So,  I'm guessing the wall will be literally sky high in order to stop planes? LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks amazing! Proud to have gotten the chance to work on it   https://t.co/tAr6EtYbjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. That shit got in my head,” Riojas said, when I followed up on messenger the next day. (He’d been stopped three t… https://t.co/LteH4nmECZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmccurley1 Probably to help avoid injuries on plays at bases? But irrationally is like to think it’s to encourage SBs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylermillwood31 Agreed! We need it to only rain on Monday’s and Tuesday’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Texts from Dad ( 10 Pics). My dad would be the one to do stuff... https://t.co/z3WyWZZA3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobJMP2 @MikeFender5 @tlvance63 @goldendoekd @SRex41563921 @arkiegal411 @EricJoh37288055 @hotblondtrouble… https://t.co/mzVYBKLwrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll tell ya one thing, it’s no surprise the @DallasStars have the least powerplay opportunities in the league when… https://t.co/sAUmqFHPQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigFrostGaming @FOX29philly How so?  Who defines what qualifies as free speech?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a second job, got a gym pass, planning a photoshoot, heading to the studio tomorrow; Cheers to a new chapter in my life 🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZuckerman That contract is a bailout to a failed process for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherLyWGRZ @WGRZ Regardless, it’s a crazy number. I’m in Kenmore with my family huddled in our bedroom to keep… https://t.co/DCyhKRyjOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to hang out with me, and you tell me you’ll call/text me, AND then you don’t. Even to reschedule or can… https://t.co/nTeyPVQ9zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside the pinnacle of Iowa sports, Wells Fargo Arena for state wrestling.  Carroll’s Abe Dirkx (145) will take on… https://t.co/FTcndQUuPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNcricinfo de Kock in for Boucher and opening with Amla. Gibbs down to #3 and the rest follows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright so, more than 10 Pizza Rolls, and a can of Spaghetti and Meatballs ChefBoyardee, oh and water in my little… https://t.co/MBs36KEmHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old folks aren’t always evil, despite what twitter says.   Am at meeting of volunteer affordable housing coalition… https://t.co/HYCs9vjDOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh...... and for everyone who’s bf/gf goes to Rosarito without eachother, THERE WILL BE CHEATING GOING ON. I hooked… https://t.co/OVcHA56TGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarissaGreenTHD It was great to work with this week Dwayne. Thanks for being the unofficial photographer and videographer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinLCappy Just bought a Perrier because of this ad hopefully @Perrier hires you]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the #weekend! Time for #revelry and #stankfaces! Come join @shadieststreet as we make our return home to jamia… https://t.co/PdBZ2xNbsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un pakistanais qui se moque d’un chinois parce qu’il parle l’anglais avec un accent bizarre😂🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[People bring up shit from two years ago because they know I’ve been thriving since]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love all the great events going on in our city this weekend. It’s gonna be a great day for sun, music and the beach… https://t.co/D6GvrZexqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmcreynolds7 @RealHughJackman I wanna be as rich as you when i grow up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFClaude It is. But it’s much better than low-functioning depression and I wouldn’t trade it for a quite few other chronic illnesses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickJohanningm1 @WillRadtke17 @MikePat42 Yo I’m making these throws fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ @RondaRousey @MsCharlotteWWE @BeckyLynchWWE Thinking a McMahon in every corner; HHH with Rhonda, Steph with Becky, VKM with Flair]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @BottleMixx in Raleigh, NC https://t.co/ljObvHk9wg https://t.co/6tLYVwr4dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chandler Prep wins the defensive battle 39-26 led by 2021 6-7 C Darian Masi w 7 pts 12 rebs 1 blk. @bballcoachdub… https://t.co/Fh5v0D1jMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[2kYates Experience ATL #DroppinSoon ♨️♨️♨️ @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/TxR6taK9YO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Anderson with the bronze at 132 pounds @WAHS_Dragons @ Meadville Area Senior High School https://t.co/p8dsmHbXqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny have to watch the whole thing for a full understanding of the meltdown]]></document><document><![CDATA[👰🏻Closeup studio shots of Deborah’s ceremony look! 👰🏻 . See more of my favorite 📸 (and the bride’s final studio vis… https://t.co/cCSMtHgGKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donavon I jumped into a project that was started in 2016, with React 15.4.x. I see a lot of this. I mean that... I mean this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@archaeologyart @seeyouitaly Wouldn’t the colosseum have had it’s  marble outer covering then?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKiDNamedKoVie @peta Yes they responded to this one! https://t.co/C5696QNWMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Madame Librarian    Merian AmericA What's A Book worth when You vaLue A-Letter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Michael's Fight For Life. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/MoMlxDpR27 via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you tried Captain Morgan Caribbean White Rum? #diageorep #captainmorgan #rum #whiterum #Caribbean #unspiced https://t.co/qRRiDeeZH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sronga93 @Marceldesrosie1 Thank You, Sharon. That’s Mom and Dad for you. I guess that’s where I get my Love for Mu… https://t.co/6qaKGQJopb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tpaopao12 with 20 pts 14 rebounds 7 assist and 4 steals to send La Jolla Country Day to the regional final Tuesday… https://t.co/X80jVRGatM]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Years night I remember messaging someone happy birthday instead of Happy New Years and have yet to figure out who it was 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you really sit back and think on it , niggas real life trash....you can’t be mad at women for thinking how the… https://t.co/rz9t89P2aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcadehaven @GrantonGranton @wx_becks @NJwhalegirl Right there a dead seagull]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atomicelroy @apls452 @yablowza @that_karen @cke5 @gary_needham @robklippel @RaymondPettibon @martinidemisec… https://t.co/G5t11AYYAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[“As of 2/25/19, your account ending in 5792 has a negative balance of $-2.18.....”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao look another soft rags fan. Tried to bullshit he had an MBA in finance. I called him out... he blocked me lmf… https://t.co/dXjOjK6Wek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuaneMieliwocki @MrsMieliwocki @rgay So many quotable moments from that show. Like “You Yada yada yada’ed iver the… https://t.co/OeQRv0XafY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariastephanos @PositiveNewsSt2 @WCVB Happy belated birthday hope you enjoyed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliMallik5 @afshanzeb14 tu phir taalaq aysey he qayim kar leen kiya BF aowr GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having finally seen #TheFavourite, I can safely say, the @TheAcademy actually got something right.... #OliviaColman… https://t.co/QNvaRboMi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timerican I have a 4 yr old princess. Love seems too insufficient a word to describe the father/daughter relations… https://t.co/XN3XJ13miX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianstone27 They aren’t bad but I’d still prefer a plain potato chip over a plain tortilla chip]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad wants to have his own tv in his room so he can play his movies and my mom said “no mames pinche películas del año del culo” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is proclaimed Prescribed Fire Awareness Month  "Whereas, prescribed burning is property owner's right and a b… https://t.co/DMUqkC2HWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Wiener San Francisco is years behind in building an underground train 3 miles. A transit center unable to be… https://t.co/NfikqCgU8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday chuck! Hope you have a good one fam! Much love ✊🏼🎉 @Charliee_G24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShiDavidi Damn. I do like this one. Buchholz proved last year that he can still bring the goods. Hoping there will… https://t.co/rxW9mxt6Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naw, she said you are going to have to make an offer higher than the cash offer because they are likely to take that over an FHA .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjonlovitz Speeks I spoke, You're fired.  Get out! Sure he says he quit, but after all..... he's a liar.  Instant classic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeRiveraSN I don't know, I think the stuff at the high school and college level is probably more sport and it dri… https://t.co/yAezXAbfTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetFreedom29 She’s not the only one and she shouldn’t pay for everybody else’s crime peter struck a belong ‘s with her and many more]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I was in the park another kid started beating me up, but eventually stopped because I just stood there lookin… https://t.co/NtNhpuFBHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to game 149. Because not everyone cancelled their games tonight.... @ Kennett High School (New Hampshire) https://t.co/DuznOEGX6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should be excellent!  Will Freddie make an appearance, @brianmaycom @DrBrianMay ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizKilmerWPXI  A true Notre Dame broadcast with Blue and Gold Could aubstitute Pitt but will not Looking great @kamenta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetingtalya @KatieSMiller @iSocialFanz @SteveSasman @saradmoore @MidoriVerity Did we cross paths in San Francisc… https://t.co/iNUAB0MQau]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I finished "The Fault in Our Stars" last night. I truly enjoyed it. However, among John Green books, I still gi… https://t.co/tQJPrK8JsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone explain Bjelica over Giles down the stretch for me? @sactownroyalty @TimMaxwell22 @gwiss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winincal @charliekirk11 Question. Why does he choose anyone? Because he uses mankind to do his will to bring good.… https://t.co/LYoopOX7fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of reasons the Amazon deal wasn’t good for Queens. A fiscal argument is NOT one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MmmYeaaBritt I was at Starbucks getting a Carmel Frap and you popped into my head]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is IS leGAL isness for All is debts public And private. DEBTS Duty in exchange for beliefs Tr… https://t.co/UhMczRphVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not forget . . . Trump Paid to Silence an Extramarital Affair with a Porn Actress !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take: just cause a random celebrity wears something completely outlandish to an awards show, does not make it h… https://t.co/1aTTXn2aM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post thunderstorm rainbow tonight at @ocyouthsoccer training. The picture doesn’t do it justice. Makes me think abo… https://t.co/DEmIECrG8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseanneAre @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump He would get his ass kicked again but this time no matter who is run… https://t.co/x48MkDkb77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Sarah now I know where NOT to spend my money and eat 🍕🍗🍟🍝🍣🍜🥩🥐🥞🧀🍷🍩🥧🥮]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let's get let's investigate that of course unfortunately Obama had all the choirboys assassinated execution-styl… https://t.co/TSRItBwyZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to thank each and everybody for their loyalty over all these wonderful years at @RespectClub ! We appreciate… https://t.co/OhXWPWNutm]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FlyWithDale took flight with @BrooklynNets Team Hype during their dunk show today 🏀 https://t.co/pHuW72Ocz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing brings a smile then to see a friends success. So, with The Savvy Traveler’s debut of Rudy Maxa’s Tours at t… https://t.co/NHbKJQcDh9]]></document></documents></author>