<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I work out 6 days a week. I only rest (hardly) but intentionally don’t do much on the Sabbath Day which is Saturday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spread love💕  📸: @bagladies - . . . . . . . #december #blackfamily #blacklove #holiday #holidayportrait… https://t.co/jQKtvZrcv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYMag #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow #25thAmendment #25thAmendmentNow… https://t.co/1z4y9dPSs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hines_stephen @theEMSsiren @NYCEMSwatch @bellamagick315 @lesleyfinlayson I think fraud speaks to malicious intent.… https://t.co/DVyukTPGUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This country will never be a socialist country” -DONALD TRUMP THE 45th PRESIDENT]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s  a guy playing steel drums on the balcony at my apartment building and I’m kinda into it tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_riveraGWHS @CPSCivicLife @GWHS_patriots What was the leading argument?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed and I just checked into a hotel and at the desk is a sign that reads “We love our patients”     1. I LOST IT whe… https://t.co/eScY4C96gB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Purple &amp; #jimihendrix 💜🖤💜🖤💜🖤💜🖤🌕👽 #selfie @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/tFQfDnZ3Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.I.P The Fire-starter ❤️” I’m not saving up for anything… I’m cashing it all now. I’ve always had this thing insid… https://t.co/HXPoHBZC2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found this in my drafts.  I must’ve forgotten to hit TWEET... 2 more #WeConnect letters going out to… https://t.co/LN2zeky11H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!!! That is amazing. That is how I started with my first book. It all started with a blog ❤️ what kind of book d… https://t.co/Usw5IC7DOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[DT: when are you going to get serious? (Not at CPAC/ it was awesome, I had orgasm - soo good) but day to day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTweetOfJohn They mentioned these things before. We have enough proof to say that yes he did do it,he said he fi… https://t.co/biG0uUQ1SY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will someone please tell me who these people are? And then please explain to me why they’re dressed like Meg and Ha… https://t.co/TwW0tFSulq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#omg #triggered #Blackface I can’t take it anymore. Arerrfghhh GOD help us @NYDailyNews @TheFive @KamalaHarris… https://t.co/k6rWI4NjOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makeupwithalexa If you don't, I will for you till you learn to love it! You're stunning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to go to work just to sit and do nothing except waste money on the electricity bill. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indy_Austin But the people of “the state” vote for bullshit like Trump and Todd Young and Mike Braun. I have no ch… https://t.co/JKVTBSieoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[idc who i lose anymore ... as long as i don’t lose myself again ... i’m good]]></document><document><![CDATA[mamma always told i was gon break hearts i guess it’s her fault, stupid, don’t be mad at me i wanna see you bust down, thotiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[overheard in Walmart from a 6 year old girl: “I want expensive chocolate-like Gucci chocolate”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilmark_1 I would hope so 😂 can’t put ya mouth or spend ya money on everybody]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concierto increible 👊👊👊👊 #SoldOut en el @alextheatre  yoamandamiguel @diegoverdaguer @soyanavictoria 👏👏👏👏👏👏 Gracias… https://t.co/3VTtqCcTF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF. Most of the guys I know are working out, focusing on their career every day if the offseason. Where’s the bad… https://t.co/kQ0AxCl0Sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lenstria I see you finished fatal twelve. I’ll go thru your rot13 thread tomorrow but did you note the place I mentioned?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Middle Georgia Community Food Bank is at World Changers Church in Macon to help feed displaced Crystal Lake res… https://t.co/WHwOLxlhhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAahgases @GOT7Official Please remember you must include #SoompiAwards in your tweet in order for them to count… https://t.co/Yk6ChT7nvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@passeri_mazie @KathyMorse0914 I totally understand. I am going broke paying for my son’s phone calls and commissary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/J4hIHqjD53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday!  The C.A.T.WALK opens at 4:30 today.  Come and get one of these sweaters.  Warehouse Sale!          M… https://t.co/G983oBTSin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cee_Kay_ I just gasped ~ I was just talking about replacement trees...think I found her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MfromTropoya @lukisabatini @CelidaLopezc Que compren boletos de lotería, andan de suerte! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely morning beauties !💕💕💕 #motd - I was excited Becuz I found my stash of missing @jeffreestar lippies !!! 💋💋💋 s… https://t.co/pAuhQ3xKsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else feel like Meghan Markle has been pregnant for like 3 years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤❤🌚🌛🌛  #lilyandyodasfunnyfarm #pairadiceranchtexas #minidonkeylily #yodadog #fureverfriends @ Pair A Dice Ranch https://t.co/923Q6txZIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti I’m a fan of yours but that’s two tweets in a row from you within minutes that sound JUST LIKE TRu… https://t.co/o2WpFIHxqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSaul @BillSchulz @GenoBiscontePA Probably along with who knows what else]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dog-Killing Iditarod Starts This Weekend: Tell the Companies Who Support this Cruelty to Drop Out! https://t.co/8tPylrbYwU via @peta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's admiration for certain dictators is um interesting to say the least. #maddow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz You know who does @SteveSchmidtSES Howie doesn’t have his own thoughts or proposals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docpetit_art Mr. Petit my name is Megan. I’m so sorry for what happened years ago. Last July I honored Jennifer, H… https://t.co/5evwy6NzrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFK_KIMMEL @DrJimmyStar @pajberry @ArgoMemphis @JayMMetalFarmer @MojoMoomey @KruegerFAngel @TonyaRBlue1… https://t.co/6e0MiZk8jU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyAd53451729 This baby was just starting out in life and they didn’t care who could get hurt with bullets flyin… https://t.co/GrLsnZKdt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wholeheartedly agree. Perfect example, me. I’ve been in FB jail more times than John Gotti.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes That Hurt  Sometimes our feelings of hurt or anger r so strong They turn in2 over powering waves Let th… https://t.co/5KrmEQXifR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petewwinslow Hard to watch these republicans question. YES!   He did lots and lots and lots of bad stuff! What about Trump?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@semavav Afternoon mtg. #zerosuicide MA DMH with BristolCounty #suicideprevention #collaboration MA DPH Let's do th… https://t.co/UqrrYF3XyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I traded my double running stroller for a solo run on the beach with the sun + the sand. — #myhappyplace… https://t.co/9PVoU9jB4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can be BOSS or your can be a WORKER which both are fine but me ima be a BOSS”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I need is family and loving people in my life.   Which for some reason is continually elusive to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast and a little collaborative work with my  sis and with my beautiful Blizzard. #GodIsGood #BusinessWomen… https://t.co/AYsNTTMa8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @RoverDov123 @Gerhardschiefe1 @TonyaRBlue1 @DavidDiehl20 @MySwilly @loinclothnation Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_Kyle_PhD @KapeKarl Joran van der sloot damnnnnn forgot about that psycho. This is a good point. Ppl think jay d… https://t.co/066Ono6Ziu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofCRiowa says: Due to unsafe conditions, travel is not advised on Southwest roads on the outskirts of Cedar Ra… https://t.co/pXHiy8W9Uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevshiotelis @HembreeSprings @CMcAtee1 @jennysoberanis1 @HSEPhilpott4th @ecurrier91 @cub_hses @forte_jennifer And… https://t.co/ne8miRm2hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it’s a day of deep thinking for me about the state of society for sure....just watched #AGoodAmerican  I’m su… https://t.co/BL5R4olRdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Olivia baby they are building a dongy donut and basket Robinson in shrewsbury” -Baba]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Cool ranch                                            2. BBQ… https://t.co/HyJJY3cnef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Taisha @Esther188rod  HAPPY VALENTINES DAY 🎗️ TO YOU ALSO ♥️ MS TAISHA HAVE A GREAT EVENING ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN DO THIS NO MATTER WHAT! #authorsofinstagram #authorjasmineujackson #barnesandnoble #amazon #ibooks #itunes… https://t.co/0mibThXGj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here you see a bench in its natural habitat in downtown Sioux Falls. This creature may quickly disappear completely… https://t.co/yiHd1U9Ufs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for summer! #ottawa #cottagelife #family https://t.co/4OdjsmxnLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pretty kitty just accompanied me on a nice walk. @ Highland Springs Farm &amp; Barn With Inn https://t.co/CxWjtdOWrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just hold your dogs hands (paws) to show him you care? Or is that just a me thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy you became just a random number in my phone 📱 no name , just your number]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suIamith this is the site I use for all tv watching purposes https://t.co/ds70Wocbx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian I want learn to use her .wakeup liner, contours etc. I'm no spring chicken, but for once I'd love to… https://t.co/WKZq8KoLlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl it is time you rise up and show yourself what you’re freaking capable of.  YOU are ALWAYS in the drivers seat… https://t.co/if9Dq5BoHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greghowardbooks claimed taking naps as his super power. I have never identified with an author more! #SEYA2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker I think he has been looting the US Treasury since he took office.  We have paid millions to the Trum… https://t.co/C4aQEvjIiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The jerseys just keep gettin better😍... it’s VIDEO GAME NIGHT🎮  🕖Tip-off @ 7 🏀Silent auction for these beauties in… https://t.co/bo5Ptyk6ZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @uber driver is blasting some sweet gospel tunes and I am loving it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starisbornmovie did it to me again! Most of the scenes should have been kept in the movie! 😭😭😭 Kills me every time… https://t.co/RNliDlyuDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moye Mountain Lions r ready! R U? #IAmEPISD #episdlibraries  #Read AcrossAmerica https://t.co/bGOuD8wVEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Dahlonega: the music gave out before the basketball game, so the crowd sang the National Anthem. ‘Merica 🇺🇸 #HawkEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommytrull I can't, it was years ago. It tasted like the way feet smell and it just lingered. It was so disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I signed up for the 2019 Women Run Arkansas Training Clinic - Jacksonville on Mar 04, 2019! https://t.co/6xXwvdIUax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charleston....here we come! Can’t wait to hear My Side of the Fence and Island Time live! Seeing @DanAndShay for th… https://t.co/bM79iK2P11]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #flow of the #pond #frozen in time. Forming #lines and #patterns in the #ice. Telling a story of melting and re… https://t.co/dOWFt1E3bE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @RepUnderwood To do an efective job that's a statistic she should  familiarise herself with. This is examp… https://t.co/D2xKkPKmOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesGleick @TIME Cause it is and run by a bunch of Socialism who only care for Elite rich and leave their people… https://t.co/LR8lktYJyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_thisisshay @Mor_Gunn I want you to T all the way up but I need my shaybutter back in one piece 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myvidastyle That’s why I was holding off, tbh. But I got one with a zipper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th graders at @CraigHillGCSD enjoyed their Survivor Night themed Grade social! @GreeceCentral  @GCSDsuper https://t.co/L2LLisIwPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaLaurenS Does that include EVERY time you watch The Lion King? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to understand there are these ppl who call #JordynWoods a home wrecker but the same ppl are dying for… https://t.co/sZ0TaByUkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abject divisive anti American asshole. Tragic waste of space and a legislative seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Depends.  If you have a lot of guests who stay and shower, you will need more than for just you.  It also d… https://t.co/UYqjXM2IBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh oh! Balance issues! What if I fall?That's a long way down! 👀 Skipping the escalator taking the elevator. 🙂… https://t.co/LftkEguU74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week, I finally tasted fugazzi.mtl The newest restaurant of the jeremie_barroco @thebetobarroco crew. The rest… https://t.co/PZuHH72GeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The good thing about graduating in three months is I don’t have to deal with alll these RUDEEE ASSS freshman and so… https://t.co/g9vNZhzc5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[This going to happened, this what obama about, she lieing, he cant but she can]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I just accidentally swiped left on the love of my life, how’s ur day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[truly hope Demi Lovato gets the help &amp; stability that she needs ♥️ she doesn’t deserve all the hate she’s getting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Piccolo of five days ago was thinking of today chris Piccolo and left him some snackies. Good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fonchongo Jajaja pero que tercer mundista está tu tweet! 🤣😂 eso no quiere decir que no sea gay! Más ahora las loca… https://t.co/r0nmZMhDmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The One and Only #JimmyDore slammed the nitwits AGAIN! BAM! https://t.co/eJROMW7mjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[New mustard at the top of the hill #brassica #brassicaceae #mustard #hiking @ Metz Stage Stop Cemetery https://t.co/87RAMmxJEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to suck my own tit but I have so many cute dates I plan to have with my future girlfriend.]]></document></documents></author>