<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Grow the fuck up . #jackierobbinsleather #jackierobbins @ Jackie Robbins Leather + Jewelry https://t.co/UNn1xQPxB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time the update pops up on my phone/laptop, I hit remind me tomorrow... that sums up my life rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cause I smile and laugh a lot doesn’t mean I’m not fucking dying on the inside nor does it mean I’m happy ...… https://t.co/sosIFlXukd]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️VALENTINE’s DAY THREAD❤️     😌 single, taken, or whatever 😌    ❤️ DROP SELFIES OR PICS OF        YOU AND YOUR BOO ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never seen a group of ppl that likes to shove their beliefs down people's throat. Why must a toddler learn about… https://t.co/T7F621e95v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @Buford_WBB and @Buford_MBB for sweeping State!! Go Wolves!! 💛💚🏀💚💛 @bufordathletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 What a whole you are! Besides threatening a witness!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very informative discussion for disseminating projects...I’m motivated to publish! @AACNursing #AACNCNL19… https://t.co/jyAIx7PPSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So from what I learned in the GC @janehere__ has been cute their whole life https://t.co/x9Ut9v7Nn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started off my Saturday by doing #taxes. Things can only get better from here, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días @JoseLuis_Roma @Raul_Roma @RioRomamx Que tengan un excelente Jueves, los amo. 💜 #DeberíasEstarAquí]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bribut_13 @AleahM8701 @22reasonswhy_ Life’s too short not to show love on birthdays 😂😂🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sikntyrd54 @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @GOP How can that be when so many migrants coming North are poor and can’t afford… https://t.co/FrsHyLIhWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharpbiology substitution= there’s an extra 3 amino acids, insertion= there’s 7 extra amino acids added ,deletion… https://t.co/E2TnZZj1cA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YusufCatStevens ❤️ love ❤️ this song! I have been a fan of yours since high school ( a while ago, ha). You have al… https://t.co/qo1ryiXEWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Where I grew up even in their obituitaries women were “Mrs Sam Smith. “  Thank you @StephenKing for st… https://t.co/fISVRtzCGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royalsussexduo Never watched Suits. I first learned of Meghan from the Reitmans commercial. My impression was how… https://t.co/eTaluYdj3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping working son! Class of 2021 PG Rankings #1 OF in the state of MS.  #8 overall..... #55 OF in the Nation and… https://t.co/OjQi8kK52H]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and yami are no longer friends so don’t ask why I stopped hanging out with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have made a grave error by going grocery shopping with a very serious case of period brain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilgrim @funder He’ sounds like Trumps personal Fox rep. Maybe Sean agrees with him. Sounds like Fox and Trump mantra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sniffle. I'm feeling a little rejected. At least I'll always have @KCCauldron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some personal news: Excited to announce that I’ll be starting a PhD in Education Policy this fall at… https://t.co/mHhYbGU2Ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @VerCELLiScience to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanation, no review - jus… https://t.co/0lYyw7iq9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Friends from College. But do people still get divorced over affairs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the child within. #hypnotherapy #reikimaster #quantumhealing #bqh #pastliferegression #meditation #yoganidra… https://t.co/7TGP7EItVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if anyone takes words away from this scroll of prophecy, God will take away from that person any share in the t… https://t.co/cORVxKk6PT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How dare you not like any of my instagram photos after you showed the tiniest bit of interest and i instagram stalked you wow rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[*whew* how strong black parents are at hiding their emotions. If only many of them felt more outloud...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @SpeakersDotCa for a great event this morning - showcasing engaging speakers that we would be lucky to have… https://t.co/vGAsNPwaZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonderickcook this is literally my biggest fear, I unknowingly go out with a follower and then tweet about him]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re life is kinda busy and you schedule hang outs with your bffs via google calendar https://t.co/obKkrzTEZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ek_johnston #QueensShadow already had me in my feelings by chapter 1, so I'm probably going to be a mess when I fi… https://t.co/RDKUkjjbBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost done! Working on this story for you about expiration dates and why they may not be the strict, scientific gu… https://t.co/nS5SOBwrAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone missed mom.  #lifewithkitten #travellife https://t.co/ABfW1ZWgmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jocflojo @thedad ☝️sounds like a Mom with a teenager.  They could hear the ice cream truck ten miles away when the… https://t.co/WjC0iYLI13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never said you wasn’t enough, I always thought you were more than enough! Nigga I treated you like a fuckin king an… https://t.co/g4HfkM73EW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slothrop420 Its on my beggin’ list!!! 😋👍@therealjoebob 🤠🍿🙏🙏🙏🙏 https://t.co/to9RezYZU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Album out now on iTunes Spotify and Google Play @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/8wZffuxfVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does #katieholmes let #jamiefoxx treat her like the sidechick? Get the scoop https://t.co/RCjkLbvWXT https://t.co/Y6YZQid2AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boomergmb40 @SassyKadiK Thank you, I thought so as well, I am watching Sophie and the Rising Sun now, it is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s crazy so we have a manager that makes us feel uncomfortable calls us names makes fun of people going thru to… https://t.co/TtBJTNzbPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In scathing ruling, judge rips insurer for putting 'bottom line' over patients' health - CNN https://t.co/ESGHuxKpRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We cover up grief and hope that it will go away, because our sanctuaries are meant to be pristine and our services… https://t.co/OxZ62qrjA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberlydisney I just lease for three years so repairs usually aren’t a problem. What’s wrong with the Volvo on the 405?]]></document><document><![CDATA[mine didnt even show up to my graduation. (Invited them &amp; they had tickets.) 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive through at In N Out is really calm and relaxing I don’t know why 🧘🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @Oliviawittkop miss u 🖤🖤 hope today is amazing!!! https://t.co/3c6WaJOors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because we are both already extremely hurt and that hurts my heart alot just the way it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G_P_Clemente They do know the climate has been changing since forever,right? #idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHeatherEm @grounder761 @vinman905 @slinki21 @TheRyanSupreme @Puckywuckums @AmyInJetsLand @davidtabrown… https://t.co/7mxDYmGVXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadaSoccerEN @SkyBlueFC Good luck @Kailen_Sheridan today. @CanadaSoccerEN made a smart choice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @MSNBC  - the land of the deluded and biased running free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, join the #sangha at #bhaktiyogashala for #manta #medicine with #johannabeekmanmusic #dcstringer #jossjaffe… https://t.co/sb4miBIS0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Training Grapefruit League here we come, keeping the streak alive! A small detour to FL and not to Cactus Le… https://t.co/DeitfmNdzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_Luvs_Us @1madwoman1962 @karenslinn43 @Jimmysimmonds1 @CathyBawden844 @BeatriceLacy @debratankersle1… https://t.co/dC50aSDb6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter how many times you tell yourself differently, somethings just aren’t meant to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning I'm #gettingready for....   #coldweather #outsideworkout  Have to get my #miles in for @runrgrrun… https://t.co/d4oMoYBiiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned about the plane but I didnt know if I should publish the LLC or his name. Glad  someone got the onto do i… https://t.co/Hfaviwu7ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_M_J83 @bugg_ray @MakeItPlain Same here I have switched to @cnn in the #exmorningjoe hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Home Laundry Room And Backyard in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/P8FOlgXPWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera I believe it doesn't take much to impress you. Young pretty &amp; Dumb!! She is certifiably insane!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was an amazing win for an amazing guy!  Polar Bear proud - so glad we were there to witness history and cheer… https://t.co/UZOifdBPT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe i missed the restock of @jamescharles palette😢😢 now i have to wait weeks again wow i’m sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t forget that @khloekardashian got cheated on with someone she considered a sister,  heartache and heartbreak hurts at every age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of the #Oscars thus far. 🤩 #gillianwelch #davidrawlings  Goal: by the time #TheOscars get here next y… https://t.co/rxMA6FZD2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritersOtStorm @illiteratelight Are u guys going to be at the DC show?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyClichee @FemiOgunrinu @Mahraj08694306 @screen180 LMFAOOOOOOOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke And the Academy Award, along with applause from every hypocritical Liberal celebrity who has ruined… https://t.co/HGT56LJSHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumpies claim Obama is a Nazi and Trump is not, we have the freakin Auschwitz Memorial and Anne Frank Center accou… https://t.co/8lUpP7lhgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladufurrena @allvalleyanimal Dr. Google says it could be nothing or something serious. This is why we need veterinarians!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThatSkyTho #CloudsIllusions #BlessedInBmore #FederalHill #InnerHarbor @ Christ Church Harbor Apartments Inc https://t.co/wgYxcbtL8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @GayleKing Be careful.  Your love for Michael Jackson need not cover for child abuse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nephew is sleeping with me n bed n I wanna die kids got the most loudest snore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaStJohnBoxer @kristoffstjohn1 @DanielGoddard @YandR_CBS @MelodyThomasSco @shemarmoore @BrytonEjames @moonfrye… https://t.co/kFTQv3YEy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Will someone please spellcheck the president’s tweets already? It’s extra embarrassing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @Patriots U May want to ask @amazon to take this down cuz it says #SB53 w/the wroug year on the Cap and in the P… https://t.co/Fdie4hsYGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aorengo @Telemundo39 Si claro me sorprendió ni en México me avia tocado una lluvia así]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS is exactly how I feel! After years of continued severe depression my brain just doesn’t work the same and my m… https://t.co/1MqoZAcG76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @CaththeWineLady @FionaMorgan79 @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @joneill55 @cowineco @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/Gm1XhLjqAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me da gusto saber que cuando la gente  quiere y se lo propone puede lograr cosas tan maravillosas cómo está]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m mad bc in psychology we talked about depressants and stimulants (drugs/alcohol) and i have never been so INTERESTED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coincidence that I listened to @DwyaneWade’s interview with @Oprah today? 🤔 #gooff]]></document><document><![CDATA[He continues to be a genius. I can’t believe it’s the last one!! https://t.co/inTgs0gTXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m guessing it’s a UK based region? Honestly the same looks pretty sweet. #PokemonSwordShield]]></document><document><![CDATA[⛓ THE CELL TOUR ⛓  Arrives at @elreytheater next Friday with @BoomboxCartel! Secure your tickets while they last at… https://t.co/Ixb2yLmiya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only reason why my fiancé and I are fighting about getting a dog is because he knows I will consider it my child an… https://t.co/sVHOF4jYfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough and stuff 💋  • 📷: @kaelanbarowsky @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/UTYw1uC7ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PRIORITIES #BestDayEver #livingmybestlife #katespade #rampantconsumerism #bestdressedinlab https://t.co/2WV3q2KcIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 2 of 2 of a personal challenge of mine recording some fresh material. A couple of months prep went into the pr… https://t.co/E2VR42Upwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first year i actually dont care that im single for valentines day🤷🏻‍♀️ im my own valentine bitchhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianouch @kawaguchikoo @glossier Yea but they send them with every order. One little boy brow, new plastic pouch… https://t.co/xsjGHzxHAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need a green moment during your lunch break, here’s the beautiful story of how powerful just one tree can be. https://t.co/JFBa0ZH7Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SneezeCocoa Straight from Little House on The Prairie, Mary and Laura style😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @PucciaPatrizia @carolina_smal @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce @Alcioni5… https://t.co/Pvg21pyaRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some funniness. bahahahahaha Pop Star Powerpuff Girls | The Best Celebrity Memes Of 2013 #humor #tee-hee #grin… https://t.co/yiXuQylTyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i go eat dinner alone at a restaurant, should act like i got bailed on, see if they feel bad and comp my meal lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON They’re number 2.  We don’t need to wait for the inevitable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pulpanochita @FelipeCalderon @giiilllesderais @jenarovillamil Pero a él lo borracho se le quita pero lo estúpido n… https://t.co/QxC4hSEWde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_viciwill Hell, I have great memories of day trips up to Milwaukee from Chicago. That's what, 5% of the cost of an… https://t.co/0eg7wPSzqL]]></document></documents></author>