<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RachelTernes @AMMillman @thatdougdude Tell me when and I’ll tweet it out. I’m in Iowa and headed into work. I’ll c… https://t.co/Xvt52e7JIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyJumperIsBased Lol I ddnt know this even posted. I ddnt finish it. It was supposed to be something like when you… https://t.co/lRKWCLXClS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love our sausage hashbrown breakfast casserole. It's so easy to make and we can usually split it up and freeze the other half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas Another question going to the Game tomorrow, what time should we arrive. What is Knight time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dish_answers It’s working now. It was a yellow screen. We missed the first hour of GMA as result.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor Lola 🥶 it's 33 degrees now I know how my brothers feel on a warm day in Minnesota 😳 #coldweather #frosty… https://t.co/9PiFljbXmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Those closest to the pain are closest to the solution,” -@lsarsour  ((Also Another reason why #peersupport works!)) #MCH2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xander6981 @UmbrellaAcad Whatever do you mean? *affects innocent look*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartidoPSUV @NicolasMaduro @dcabellor @taniapsuv @DivaGuzmanPSUV @EduardoPinateS @dariovivaspsuv @ConElMazoDando… https://t.co/Kp2Ec8Num0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatiJinich If the apostles did it for the last supper…who are we to judge? 🤷🏻‍♀️😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaCantaloupeH @3gcry @ErickGagni @BlancaNayelyNT3 @clao50 @susanasilvi58 @immannymunoz @Atolitoconelddo… https://t.co/kOfBOmBZ2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJasonPugh @AndrewScheer Yes he went on about Canada not buying our own oil]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my cards read last night by an old high school classmate, and I'm literally still MINDBLOWN! We were both in TEARS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisburns no no no that when he inevitably dies many years from now he leaves me his house which i care for more… https://t.co/KkczOmuI9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Post! Motivated by Success: Embracing Perfection! What would it be like to be entirely motivated by success? 🏆… https://t.co/Qq3lxv4qXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michigan man charged with running illegal dental practice in basement https://t.co/s7Sv1Tt2xP via https://t.co/bl8HOdW0Au]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't think Andrea Kremer, Beth Mowins, Amy Trask, Pam Oliver, Hannah Storm know the game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunnySkyes53 @jennellen60 @jgcOCANADA @CheriJacobus @jayrosen_nyu @Sulliview @coldcardinal But do you really think… https://t.co/ePuPylPIih]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just Tuesday here...and it’s not too bad HAPPY MARDI GRAS YALL💜💚💛 https://t.co/G9Kd09agYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarinaDiamandis It is not exactly misogyny. It is not about hating so much women but about telling them what they… https://t.co/oAiSukR6Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're not following this guy....follow him.    He's got a scathing wit that reminds me of my smart, politically… https://t.co/9IKSFD1jHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorBennet @SenCoryGardner @RepTipton It is expected that this budget is not passed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Photo by @KristenBlush #WomensRights https://t.co/IamaG25Ylg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayyy happy birthday bb 😘 @DaniellaLira_  (did I do it right this time @nitzbluv?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbyyates808 @kgbreww so glad we got to hang out tonight! I love yall❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love the people who signed up for the lottery for the broad st run and they snapchat you about how “sad” they are… https://t.co/o3dAkTjmV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fckinkaren Lmfaooooooooooo true but I can try 😂😂I make them run away when they make a mess im sure i cAn make them do this 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TOUR_TRILOGIA_2019 #TEAM_TRILOGIA #LTJ #NEXT_LEVEL #NEXT_LEVEL_ENTERTAINMENT #GK5X #Gabriela_Knox #youtuber… https://t.co/E0or4ypSn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to get another blood work done tomorrow morning I’m so over all these dam test ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading my @people tonight reminds me that one day I’ll be seeing myself in these pages as we ramp up… https://t.co/4RQjZgKqP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkbenko Yes!! I just watched the trailer and am so excited to read this 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[from my #etsy shop: Awesome Vintage 80'S Signed #KARLLAGERFELD #Paris Spiked Jeweled Grommet Bracelet, Runway… https://t.co/wQpG7rx8si]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afossella just finished the Into The Woods ep and I can’t tell you how proud I am of how your outro writing has gr… https://t.co/m8sFmu2f32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaleighsReaders @SERaleighES @LeadwithReading @MHS_MrsG @kelseymwoodss @clarkeskinders @MrsRabb1 @geraldgivensjr I… https://t.co/8RQ3S1EXlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwatsky Can't wait to see you in Minneapolis at First Ave! Buying tickets was the best drunk decision I've ever made 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CornellBirds @MerlinBirdID Is there any way to integrate Merlin with eBird?. It would be fantastic to make a posit… https://t.co/MKfuftBGGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrezinho77313 Pra você vou garantir um ingresso então. Vou lhe mandar os detalhes por DM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from work and it's actually still light out.   #sorcery à Chicago metropolitan area https://t.co/Eirilk2P5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump hey, when u get back to the WH, find a thesaurus.... witch hunt is getting a bit redundant don’t you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 That’s OK. He probably knows more about piloting an airplane than anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black mold is also horrible for human health. Get rid of it right away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy vacations are strong! @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/qqqWvxGhbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@theebillyporter was best dressed in the black velvet tuxedo gown by @CSiriano. It was obviously homage to the lat… https://t.co/k4tMSn4Vx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[C'mon guys. be better  okeeee #beiNPL #MCIWAT 📺 HD11 #premierleague #arsenal  #Bournemouth   #RealMadrid #Mourinho… https://t.co/BmDTW0pd6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilisumaKegna @Fasikini @eskinder_nega @AlemuReeyot @asfaw_rafa @PMEthiopia @TakeleUma @mhadu @teshten መንግስት ናፈቀን።… https://t.co/IoOOIAwHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPchronicle @ewarren Being a bot, I guess it's kind of hard to watch the video where Warren explains how.   Sick… https://t.co/E3pfE4UzkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at LIRR - Rosedale Station - @lirrdeals4u in Rosedale, NY https://t.co/mnc33Hm6lX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blueequus775 @EkbMary @SonyaBaker2 @MustangRehab @sharon_elle @CeciliaCmaida @Joni_Looking @CyntWhite… https://t.co/gmV130XqcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Served HBO and oprah (with a small o) right! As a MJ fan, I'm gloating truth be known! https://t.co/3NX87R3ErK via @showbiz411]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKrackman EARL MANIGAULT THE GREATEST BASKETBALL PLAYER EVER!! GOOGLE HIM!! AND I QUIT THIS GAME,BECAUSE THEIR… https://t.co/hia8FjiDbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning. I'd love to explore and see this in person!!   https://t.co/IoNVpVTgwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a #socialmediaspecialist - I’m always pretty head down on my phone and computer. Thus video is a great reminder… https://t.co/Ih4Vvg2OGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We need more international collaboration, not less, in the digital age.” #techplomacy  https://t.co/DlImphq6cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @JerryLOakley1 @realDonaldTrump If this is true then the time to stop hiding is IS NOW. Come join us!… https://t.co/VNzh8I8DGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the key is acting like you have 7.62 in your account no matter how much you really have]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djuhnk Haha yaaass. Aside from the 💩 part. It never matters how many days I’m going it matters how big my bag is... I’ll fill it regardless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indygifted @gtchatmod Ruby Payne calls those meltdowns a result of an unregulated and unintegrated brain. The best… https://t.co/ESzE2ohZxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[2022 5’10 Ali Mack continues to impress. 300 M Hurdles: 48.74 100M Hurdles: 15.13 60M Hurdles (indoor): 9.34 Long J… https://t.co/wRuxToIUs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomellis17 to say I was pleasantly surprised is an understatement. I gasped. Out loud. In the theater. American Lu… https://t.co/FQTINJboRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[YG NEXT WEEKEND IN SAN FRAN W MY MOM CANT WAIT ❤️ IMMA GET HER LIT LETS HOPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️❄️❄️on the way = #pain   #humanbarometer  #chronicpainwarrior #kittylove😻 @ My Corner of the world https://t.co/HW289jp4Sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I for real wish more of my actual friends loved God as much as I do. It’d be pretty cool sometimes to have a convo… https://t.co/L7rHi0Mk4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset #keywest #ocean #picoftheday #bird @ Margaritaville Key West Resort &amp; Marina https://t.co/8MLBxssMGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s a special place in hell for people who block open seats on public transit by just standing in front of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, 6 torn pads. No wonder I felt that my flute wasn’t playing well! How does that even happen!!? #flute #fluteproblems #flutemaintenance 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just lounging on the couch watching cartoons and sharing pizza Pringles w Thomas ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notaLibbyever @Miki4473 @Rissa_Wood @TeddiMellencamp Im so over Dorit! I’d be so happy if these gals all stay for… https://t.co/P4I2EQjeaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic Write it for the generations to come, they will need to know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another new crush for #MCM. Met @AvatarAkyiaXXX for the first time in Vegas at the Smash Bar and I've been a smitte… https://t.co/z0cA91ZeFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caopazob Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Mike, Did you Agree or Disagree with Scarborough’s False comments??  It seems like you are neutral about his ba… https://t.co/WemKhQl0kV]]></document><document><![CDATA[💕Happy Valentine’s Day! Enjoying a fun Valentine’s Day Bingo with our 6th grade buddies💖@mbilecki_gses @gsesdallas https://t.co/kvkJVdpBM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[my teacher loves my man too and she put "coaster" .... yeah im not gonna cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenKnights yo.. check this out I think you should. https://t.co/UaVLDJIZ77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic Books are Racist. Why do people insist on hurting our children with them? There, fixed your headline for yo… https://t.co/fbbGTH5KQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay squad. I don’t give a fuck about followers so I’ll still post stupid shit on this account but if you a real OG… https://t.co/ZgXJZvlUHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come from a city where bitches will hate you for anything , ANYTHING. https://t.co/Ocwbxzks3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andym67 @aravosis Rosamond Pikes should have won for A Private War. Best performance by an actress since Kathryn H… https://t.co/wjVgeC7Yy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part of my day was my green juice break at Five Seeds!  Love your newly expanded space!  #fiveseeds… https://t.co/dVwEXqyCAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the worst black history month. PERIOD. Hopefully this doesn't take away from members of the LGBTQ community… https://t.co/n7n5Az22Uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two days with these great volleyball boys. Keep working hard. #imtiredandreadyforbed😴 #BUTilovedeveryminute💙 https://t.co/HJBErlOKBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneDayAtATime 2be honest it wasn’t 1 scene or  1 episode. I had the honor of being in the audience 4 the filming o… https://t.co/t83XxQWqC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day in Hopland. So much water here! @ Hopland, California https://t.co/Zvcj7ceso8]]></document><document><![CDATA[💰 🎥 At least 1 state is legally taking bets on the 2019 #AcademyAwards⁠ ⁠ https://t.co/KIkU9GXNmQ #OscarsOn2 https://t.co/rzc81ICm8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwcortes @scarolinewells @Det_Ramosfndn Omg. My deepest sympathy to him and his loved ones. Bless you all for what… https://t.co/GOxSyaBpA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That we are not living in the great creative days of the church , I deeply regretted. - W.J. Cunningham, Agony at Galloway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shadowdoc @CMGlastonbury @UCSFimaging So well deserved!!! Congratulations Christine, very happy for you and the department.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTrumplican @Fk__45 @DavidTaylorNYC @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Opinions are like @$$Holes 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking some time to learn about cats today at #wildthings19! Jen Kuroda is speaking about Bobcat research in Illino… https://t.co/07E9ZFrHkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s stuff like this that makes me sit down for the pledge . “ One nation , under god “ ... “ With liberty and just… https://t.co/AMiPdVsIwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIT_Spookery @emrazz Brava.Bravissima. You are a hero. Your Dad is super. I had no father. I love good fathers. Gl… https://t.co/Hfr1sHLzX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10MinutesDown You were too saturated with booze. You would have burst into flames!]]></document><document><![CDATA[R Kelly in a race with Cartoon Gangster (opsie, court order Gagged.) ....for top Twitter ranks, with billionaires l… https://t.co/JM8F2tkNli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson I love the music on your new album. It’s you in every song  I have loved your music for years. Some… https://t.co/IeubdfrVHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We also ventured to the Boynton Canyon Vortex for a different kind of vibe @ Boynton Canyon Vortex https://t.co/V1NBaTNdoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇Baby killers in charge of USA‼️Don’t let this happen to USA and our unborn and now, sadly and most outrageously, t… https://t.co/NTgneg7tNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Près d'une centaine d'avocats demandent au gouvernement de traiter les 18 000 dossiers d’#immigration https://t.co/ajZl0tdQLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else thinks @colton watched Jerry Maguire on the plane ride to Portugal? #TheBachelor #youcompleteme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite view in La Jolla! Who’s ready for Spring and for no more rain?! . . . . . . . #lajolla #sandiego… https://t.co/SV357NMJKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Activists Bring Legal Challenge Against Japanese Dolphin Slaughter https://t.co/lYvQeafL9N]]></document></documents></author>