<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Will  @DonnaKorn2 @PattiGood68 @ReverendRos #LaurieRichLevinson @AnnMurrayDist1  @SBBCBrinkworth @Robin_Bartleman c… https://t.co/EqyKOMc3bK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some more spiders we have in stock. They are all slings. #rhondasaviary #tarantulasofinstagram #tarantula… https://t.co/PEsXXyYGtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only money I ever made in public speaking was at a Women’s Day event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickNova777 @facebook @BrentBozell @Franklin_Graham Rewarded - Suspension, I asked my Community for Prayer Supp… https://t.co/32jxKgrlLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ I don’t get why people are addicted to cocaine... when their are French fries in the world...I’m addicted to Fren… https://t.co/S1I8o94qe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twinning, Food Bank donation and a new member of #CanineClassmates A great Valentine's at #TeamFES #EaglePride #SOAR https://t.co/eWS2O7zGIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was probably the coldest and wettest (is that a word? If not sorry, functioning on 3 hours sleep) night… https://t.co/4PPakXZ6Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all have blown me away with your thoughtfulness, curiosity, and level of realness with each and every one of yo… https://t.co/z5QhKjmNUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanDuque @Almagro_OEA2015 @ONU_derechos @mbachelet @marcorubio @RosLehtinen @carloslcurbelo @Pontifex_es… https://t.co/LJC9z7pqI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should the president declare a national emergency to get more border funding? I voted No on KGW. What's your vote? https://t.co/nVygh8777K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like really I’m stressed asf bc I have no way to my baby’s appointment this Thursday. 💆🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waddup I went to hang out with my friends and we drank tea and ate an absurd amount of cookies and I'm in a signifi… https://t.co/Dk3FRIHzLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquelinSusann @SheriffClarke @nytimes @realDonaldTrump @NYCMayor Sounds like she’s doing some illegal SCHIZZ!!! C’mon BARR!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright. That thunder just shook my whole house AND I see lightening. I’m scared now. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters You are such a nasty and hateful person. How can you look yourself in the mirror every day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg This should have never happened. You and yours are in my thoughts today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am i the only person who doesn’t gaf about the Tristan Thompson/Jordyn woods situation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just asked my Uber how his night was going twice and he ignored me both times so I’ll just go f*ck myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched the Jonas Brothers video 3x today solely for Sophie Turner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you all had a great Valentine's Day celebrating love and friendship. Feeling very grateful for all the love in… https://t.co/3jvmvmwU8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TapeFaceBoy @podomatic @AshFrith That's too bad. A company ought to stand by their work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngrierWHStaff That needs to be a meme. Pelosi saying "he's just not worth it"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally: @Pearson Sells Its US #K12 #Courseware Business—for $250 Million* https://t.co/B6zak301ds #edtech via @EdSurge]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just CANNOT WAIT for the 2020 election - so I can vote against whichever idiot of a Democrat makes it through the… https://t.co/lhlXQDoh4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one good thing about campus being closed is that I don’t have to go to my 3hr night class😭🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of high school is when school has any chance of being cancelled I suddenly have a lot of friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicahlSCC I got $50on humans finding some way to make both those options unethical. Rich people getting wagyu cock… https://t.co/MWdTDOREIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindaholmes Kinkeeping is real labor and once I found out the term for it, my life made a lot more sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never realized how many people I took for granted in high school and didn’t realize I would miss EVERYBODY after graduation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Playing to Win”: strategies for #women to build and win talks with #cybersecurity #conference #abstracts from… https://t.co/4g5lNsPMWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donations to my classroom are currently being matched!  https://t.co/BI6iDXqJcX I only have until March 12 to get t… https://t.co/sPjORAF9lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn This abrupt end to the Kim jong summit is fake! Don’t believe trump ! There is something very disturbing going on !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganchase97 @matitty25 That is NOT on Hulu?! WHAT?! HOW WAS I UNAWARE?! https://t.co/OS4HDqCRM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olejnik_lukasz1 @polskawruinie2 @Andruszkiewicz1 pokazał się w cyfryzacji???🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @umichbball Ann, you really need to chill out. I like you usually, but over the past year, you have bec… https://t.co/zp2OyuAuTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castillo with a strike landing right above the cross bar before the half, creating another quality chance for the… https://t.co/MOyVaDYgDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh cool, used to really like @shanedawson and his content but making conspiracy jokes about the wildfires in Califo… https://t.co/rVr0grBSe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lily just read her One Direction fan fic she wrote at like 13, and honestly...what a cliff hanger. Is Harry falling… https://t.co/XGvDA9a4bW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys basketball Regional Quarterfinal game vs Atlantic!  #gohounds #regionalquarterfinal @ Tracy Mcgrady Gymnasium https://t.co/SvDzguwS0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This chick I went to school with said “if it’s in the song it’s meant to be sung” NOT BY YOUR WHITE ASS]]></document><document><![CDATA[twistedbeauty77 at @TheSparkleBarAZ slayed my makeup as always 🔥 @ The Sparkle Bar https://t.co/JnikO79lUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 18 weeks now and I hear that a lot of moms start feeling movement this week, I’m terrified that I’m not going to feel any]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our writers sent in a list of their top NFL players from last year. @GAPeachPolymer put it all together and came up… https://t.co/pXm31d4eTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[5A State: top-seed @MHSBullpups take down 8-seed Seaman 57-41 #catchitkansas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC .@realDonaldTrump always supports criminals, dictators and sexual predators. Why do you think that is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could, for example, be this guy who actually thinks this is like a marriage instead of a war. That an apology a… https://t.co/w6vPKmBW5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, still, didn't manage to get a picture that does this place real justice. @ Alta Ski Area https://t.co/6UkCzFxWEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All this drip don’t need no stylist “ 💦💧❄️ @dreezydreezy 🎶 https://t.co/sCgSJPiCvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the worst parts of this stat is hearing the .@MapleLeafs STUPID GOAL SONG 3x in like 1 minute 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoveIsActuallyA pain in the ass 🥰 #SaturdayMotivation 🦋🐲🐉 https://t.co/ZKsKI24XPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *Noticing car parked by snowshoeing trail* Wow, that car has a David Hume sticker!!! 🙌🏼 Outdoorsie friends: Um,… https://t.co/PYdavbuj5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to the beginning of Always.Together. Forever♥️ . .  Happy Love Day 💕 #Throwback 📸 : #manpreetbrarphotography… https://t.co/PLRhvObMGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡!!!¡Attention All¡!!!¡ I am going to sleep right now and my socks are on]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ks43q7IRtY This world is in control of the antichrist and false Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!Have a beautiful day😀 @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/9i3Rkcg2Rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntunicorn You described that perfectly . Now I wanna toast him and eat him !!!  😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work really pays off. Thank you so much baby!! 😍😍 @Tristan_Harshaw https://t.co/IVhwtUMrfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If true I am through with her. The worst example of an independent women .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still get chills every time I hear this, but watching the two of them together...wow. ❤️ #ladygagabradleycooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don't yell at me, you talk aggressively &amp; it hurts my feelings ~Sadie, age 16 #Teenagers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betterthedeviI Who are you most excited for, just curious.(I am excited for Brooke!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jaspers last minute Valentine’s Day Box since we had to change his dr appointment @ Starship Corkle https://t.co/azo6Uh6NM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart! Thank you, @Dame_Lillard for making my night so special. I’ll never forget this night. Also shoutout to t… https://t.co/sXQgvEDe85]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this type of thing in theory, but the thought of doing it personally freaks me out. So I sat down and had a… https://t.co/Dx9M68Yair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #BNPPO19 !!! Paid almost 500$ to watch #djokernole tonight and since it’s been cancelled due to rain will I be… https://t.co/y6FrSb08TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[*through my life meaning past the moment pictured because i was obv not very happy with him in ~this~ moment😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be here @sxsw - who knows where we’ll end up and what stories we’ll tell. #SXSW2019 #eleanoramagazine https://t.co/BzfGndDqZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning REALLY!!! AGAIN! Turning the channel ! This guy needs #JESUS ! Nobody believes anything he saids! What A Whiner!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tribute to #TomPetty @fleetwoodmac Bittersweet ‘FreeFalling’ https://t.co/X9DZUhyoW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mood #thisisyourwarning @ Bellmawr, New Jersey https://t.co/xEET1Se8IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y más señora si me lleve a mi sobrinito acompañante jajajaja 😍 lo amooo se porto muybien https://t.co/848oJhhuTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días, ¿en qué nivel de señora estoy cuando ya me despierto súper temprano los fines de semana?  Con los atentos saludos, jóvenes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I personally answer them directly. I find that many times I can educate these people. And tell them th… https://t.co/F94EK1Br6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laker622 @realDonaldTrump I voted for Trump after two terms of Obama.   Lowering the corporate tax to be competiti… https://t.co/12CMVCnnED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiborMilian love #Florida #Newfoundland #Adirondack #MaineMariners #Reading #Jacksonville #SouthCarolina #Orlando… https://t.co/ojOAwq4PPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[💀WRATH Bk3 in #TheEliteSeven series by claire C Riley is LIVE!!!  I’ll do whatever it takes to become a member and… https://t.co/B5iyMrTSw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to UST though especially Sisi Rondina 💪🏻 pero sa Petron ka nalang mag-halimaw please! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovrega @salomonj Y la 4ta transformación esta plagada de ocurrencias. 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsfanmurph1 That’s not fair for the rest of the Latvian Knicks fans. Just because the one Latvian leaves the team. I’m appalled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyEmerson @BlakeMcIver @LA_Rockwell @bricuoco @TalFox This show is so special!!  Can’t wait for tomorrow night xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 would he like her as much if she hadn't changed her natural looks with plastic surgery?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gsfrktct @jlwesterfield That's exactly what we're doing and also getting more and more ppl to vote blue!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to Augusta where today a government oversight committee will meet to discuss the state’s child welfare syste… https://t.co/BRbyR3sDMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewS70484912 @DiamondandSilk Hi Diamond &amp; Silk:  I WILL FOLLOW U.  U R BREATHLESS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenergy5 @NYCMayorsOffice But I’m not up in the early morning so it’s more daylight during my waking hours 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my brother PIT. THIS shit still feels like yesterday. Take care of him mommy and Tomona Boozer. @ Upper Nor… https://t.co/MLfTCO1DaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔸💲10🔸 Size: M Description: Zipper runs through halfway on side, waistband stretches Color: Aqua Blue, White Horizon… https://t.co/6aAu243DIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an iris, if am not mistaken, shivering in the cold and wet outside my apartment building. I am in Texas but… https://t.co/1K2W178v2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lagot ako nito sa boyfriend ko! Sabi ko 9pm ako tutulog hahahahaha 2am na gising pa ako 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[*the jonas brothers are releasing a new song at midnight*  me: https://t.co/ZZDAyjDCeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m more making pancakes, bambi.” Yes! That’s what you said I heard you! Now it’s French toast. Okay whatever you say, buddy 😣🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t always trust our feelings. But we can trust the compass of God’s word...We need to trust that those words… https://t.co/goMdZU7TmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry couldn’t show you how it started. But this is what it looked like after!?  #Noborderlens #tnkarts… https://t.co/eLnFTzcbGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BootsRiley @GAMBA_CL People, considering how greedy people are these days, the Venezuelan crusade is costing American Taxpayers:]]></document><document><![CDATA[HE TOLD ME HE BUILT A TIME MACHINE LIKE ONE IN A FILM WE’D SEEN.... YEEeaAHhHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quietest day in class is heart rate day!! #PBS #PLTW https://t.co/tGy6iTCT7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have an amazingly generous and supportive corporate community in DM. Exhibit A:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist It seems like a logical explanation knowing the way these monsters work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really sad I didn’t get to meet @ReadSouthall especially since I threw that up on stage 🤷🏼‍♀️ #MGTS2019 https://t.co/Y8CtpAg1FI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys... if you’re gonna stand someone up, at least have the courtesy to do it before they go through the process of putting on their makeup]]></document></documents></author>