<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein Fight for our generations survival?  Lol, idiots actually believe this garbage. 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowing in #Vegas. #Wakeup! Late night jacuzzi time! #bubble-time #soak #hottubheaven @ The Lakes, Spring Valley https://t.co/uyFhkO6CUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinelizadrew Or I could just keep having occasional moments where I remember that it's a thing I struggle with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been saying this the last 2 years, @celtics are much better as a team w/Scary Terry ans Marcus Smart at point!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_2human @originalSennyD Players recruit all the time. It’s dumb that only lebron isn’t allowed to recruit lol. I d… https://t.co/zbBjCLHKW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/9pXn9LlUQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLEVELAND,OH (CLE) ASOS reports gust of 57 knots (65.6 mph) from WSW @ 2351Z -- KCLE 242351Z 25034G57KT 10SM BKN028… https://t.co/DjTfXAgXmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends, family, and clients, please help me vote. 🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽 Click Link in bio to vote. @ Macciola Inc https://t.co/XJuLcS8z2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagobars Image credit to @ZachWeiner &amp; SMBC comics. https://t.co/oDoZv0fuaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm happy thanks to @BrustersFresh chocolate raspberry truffle #icecream https://t.co/Yl5C5slLmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @Happy19111 @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/fcMNiEmpoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@resistandgrow We should wake up in a few hours to hear he is in contempt of court.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya’ll know there’s already a lot of money out there struggling to find a home, right? https://t.co/FEAdAyIZNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stay__true_2 @BradyJustBetter @ChaseDawg2 That would require Judge to actually make contact against Chris Sale, wh… https://t.co/YlcjmktxqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cory Booker is such a fake bologna sandwich I Realize one thing book I will never be president Troy my will just ge… https://t.co/otBzrrVi2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickeykoke Ya just wait... there is always generational talent available lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say It To Me S.A.N.T.O.S. #PHishNYEMSG #YouWillAlwaysRememberWhereYouWere #ThisIsWhatSpaceSmellsLike @phish… https://t.co/3sX4GzhaZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hear the train a comin' It's rollin' 'round the bend, And I ain't seen the sunshine Since, I don't know when I'm… https://t.co/rLV9sLe4vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next stop: Chicago. (@ George Bush Intercontinental Airport in Houston, TX) https://t.co/gBgOWoDCmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BizCoachjkr @peterdaou Again,if the main stream Democrats would recognize a "SOCIAL" Democrat, he would probably c… https://t.co/yWKq8zH5Xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything worse than being the second car to pull up to a red light while trying to make a right turn where… https://t.co/6bdKsI79sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RP_Quigs Mine is press box announcer @DougMarshLV , the drum bot with the beard who looks like Africa Bambaataa, T… https://t.co/EgbhOHYnll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ Sr presidente gracias x preocuparse por MÉXICO Ojalá Dios nos lo conserve muchos años]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter supported U 100% in past, but U R WAAAY off the rails with UR disgusting bashing of our President! You… https://t.co/r8JE16fQMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Field my senior year. Then I had a favorite player I looked up to that I felt like I can model my game after and hi… https://t.co/E0wy1QXLgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive… https://t.co/CSBB8G2l7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow’s Green Team Event 12:00-1:30 at our Winter Farmers’ Market. https://t.co/HT1IyPR2xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCorneliano2 A mi realmente no me queda duda de que EEUU se va a pasar por el forro del culo an cualquier gobier… https://t.co/7HE4rhgdW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Show! Come out and have a good time! @ PIT Chapel Hill https://t.co/InTpuVWnh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chapter 4: Joining Forces  They played music endlessly in the mountains of La Guinera.   The super Guatekes continu… https://t.co/zsLtFpwCsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartfelt condolences to the families of our valiant soldiers . May the souls of our countrymen who laid their live… https://t.co/BDURYfPFxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[- NEW PARTY ALERT 🚨 FREE FRIDAY 🚨 GVO 🚨 THE NEW FREE FRIDAY @club79miami  @Dj mani305 FIRST NIGHT FEB 1 COME WITH W… https://t.co/fX9JfOTjtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Truly Hate Bigotry And Discrimination in America U S A .!! There a whole lot Discrimination between different peo… https://t.co/DD1w4qdnY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganWorld Disagree. Maybe. McCain did a lot of wonderful things, but could have used his influence for unity for… https://t.co/190201gqfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actions speaks louder than words... so don't say you give good head.... prove it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coppy who broke enough rules to be banned from baseball for life or AA, who is still a respected and working man in… https://t.co/xqzS97mm5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[It can now be reasonably stated that Canada is a state sponsor of terrorism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you not getting that from me, just means I gotta do better. God is working on me though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s cool about this Sabres game is there are two guys playing for the Sabres tonight that I’ve never heard of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Harper and Machado stop being females and decide where they want to play?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahGraceD Personally I was team burn it all down and make Demi the Bachelorette.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Johnathan Hall, Social Studies Department Chair, and Tier 1 Leadership Program, ND. #GSUEdLead]]></document><document><![CDATA[You people Fr need to wait instead of rushing into relationships and actually find someone who truly cares about ev… https://t.co/pwK6e2XJgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @CalMBBall has the lead on #SunDevils 24-23. 3 minutes left 1st half. @SunDevilHoops 2-12 from 3pt land. #Pac12Hoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edddyflowers Nah dog take the L how do you not know ups don’t work holidays bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[home sweet home. where it all started (@ Luxor Hotel &amp; Casino - @luxorlv in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/PrExI7YSMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one should ever feel alone. Life as a student can be overwhelming. So grateful for the work of my colleagues in… https://t.co/CfCTCcDG6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m saying is that James did Samantha dirty in First Daughter. 12 and 27 year old Taylor both agree on this aft… https://t.co/7V3QiwyEFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I going to buy this bundle of semi-fascist space-wars books for shut-ins? You’re absolutely goddamn right I am https://t.co/1ys7Blz3BL]]></document><document><![CDATA[One bad day away from buying a pair of jorts and all white New Balances, I swear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateGearyWGR It's a lot of ego. Jarvis still there too. https://t.co/OHp7WVI5zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sue_Innovates @notsobigkahuna @CBCQueensPark @PeopleforEd I agree 1000%. EQAO results if they mean anything should… https://t.co/4Urhm7K6Ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OG_Pepitas Oh LOL. I was a theatre nerd in high school when the movies came out. My sister loved the shit out of i… https://t.co/NnWqEeRNJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finish up your Monday deck by arriving to the office early like: https://t.co/oZtLwI0mNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays @Mangan150 @CalebJHull Those studies are only slightly less accurate than the “global warming/clima… https://t.co/aN3RAeNa24]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-Show Hangs. #boocrue #bornofosiris #thesimulation #tour #tattoos #masquerade @ The Masquerade https://t.co/pZKpaVjRTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to a deposition in the case against the agency, a PHEAA employee in the debt collections area -- and wrot… https://t.co/z0X6PM4TGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFrias81 @Michael_Guajrdo @StevESPNKim Chavez prob was a light heavyweight by fight night-Lee simply couldnt move… https://t.co/X1fkv5AJnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Molinari cards final-round 64 to win Arnold Palmer Invitational presented by Mastercard https://t.co/IO1tBpgGpU.… https://t.co/9ZkQvQjhWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix intro still scares the shit out of me every time..                *DUN DUN*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo de Zidane es algo admirable. Volver a un equipo al que le haz dado todo para poner en riesgo tu leyenda, y otras… https://t.co/loQePpVuVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been having some ridiculously vivid dreams pop up the last couple weeks. This last one even mixed my life in L… https://t.co/GgrQc6Wiip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t no other bitch in the history of his life finna have him like this 🤞🏾 and I can put money on that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CitizenKuhn My administrators encourage teachers to create Twitter page connected to our school. All students show… https://t.co/uMT1Mi0BRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta Cmon man let this man Rest In Peace. He spreaded animal awareness and loved animals]]></document><document><![CDATA[This world we live in is full of sick and twisted people. If you have young children I suggest you block @YouTube o… https://t.co/RxgAJLTGJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_C_Campbell @kaattxo My favorite part is all the people in Alabama probably ecstatic at this legislation will… https://t.co/0Ii2VxX64y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorriOlds @chrissyteigen Well that was certainly a short lived rant...lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[México 🇲🇽 y Estados Unidos 🇺🇸 CONSTRUYENDO PUENTES CON MI AMIGO @antonio4ca en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/41vYyFOwmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGirlHasNoPOTUS @UpPastryPlate @davidgura @UPonMSNBC A #GaggleOfGrifters can also have a pack of #TreasonWeasels w… https://t.co/KPvhlg2txJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eldest daughter just found out Simmonds was traded.  “Who in their right mind would trade Simmonds?”  #truth #FlyersTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad the deputy is okay. Why isn’t this on MSM?? Of course, not part of the narrative. Fully support ALL law enforc… https://t.co/xULOYMuT8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul George the best two way player in the NBA right now. Gotta give MVP to Giannis tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[INDIA AMD PAKISTAN - VENEZUELA- this world is always  so close to really breaking out into some serious conflicts t… https://t.co/C1c5wxWP9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @SexySerenaB @TheRileyAnne1 @umajoliexxx @KrissyLynnxxx @JuelzVentura @KaylaniLive @Cassie_Ibiza… https://t.co/dWJeFyo4Tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 9th and 10th I will be hosting SGN March Mayhem Regs tournaments. 64 players, 2 dollar buy-in. Winner gets 80… https://t.co/KBMpbbcs00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDetailed @carrieunderwood I’m so sorry for your loss. My prayers are with you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[But then you came along and started pushing the boundaries of what is possible again, you along with many others be… https://t.co/EOawMfomwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon withdraws plans to build a HQ in New York. Virginia already approved an "incentive package" to build an Amaz… https://t.co/7OlXtAGCgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Healings don’t create halos... but conviction DOES create crowns!” Pastor Benjamin White @ Abundant Life https://t.co/7gdU96B3uX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephanienoel41 Just started rewatching when I'm on the road, this is good news]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bye Bye Babcock if we don’t get past first round Also don’t forget we we’re winning in game 7 !!! #bbb #noexcuses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por cuánto es hora de sacar los Cubanos. El pueblo de Cuba es mi hermano. Pero estos pichones de asesinos se les de… https://t.co/lglAINwgdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Hope there are many questions about #MedicareForAll and #GND .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four banks with area branches appeared on a list of banks with consumer complaints to the @CFPB, as compiled by… https://t.co/yGMpkgNXGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Irene_Dreams_ I'm so sorry get rest and dont push it we will see you when you are better]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to find more ways to use the Camera App on the Chromebooks! The students loved doing an assignment in a… https://t.co/DmN68w5kD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@optimuswaldge I mean, they’re not mutually exclusive. Morphine is medicine BECAUSE it’s a narcotic intoxicant. Als… https://t.co/ybeuX5o8xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[U look like an elite booster. Can I give u a list of shit I need u to steal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pablomariz777 @WSOP Monster Stack still only 1 entry total.   Re: Thw Big 50 - if you bust on Day 2 and there are… https://t.co/B4xguWipFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @KatrinaPierson ? Calamity? Trump campaign has 70% of the people in prison or flipping on him to tell the trut… https://t.co/grmz91yKiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a blast on our @trymystery date! If you haven't checked it out yet, it's a mystery date night planning app.… https://t.co/EHxGqjSKas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doxscund @NBC10Boston @lovehope So a crime u say pray tell of what u speek! I C NO crime! jml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willmaxey @MPowersNorrell Disclosure: I'm only joking, she made no such claim. But it *would* be erroneous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell I have been binging your series right now. Almost caught up. This series will be missed and I love all the characters. #Arrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @TuckerCarlson’s nonsensical opening monologue. Some things are clear: Irony is alive and well; NOBODY at… https://t.co/u8xIOHgrWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canada’s Deputy Ambassador to US @KirstenHillmanA talks about the Maine-Canada relationship w/ @WorldAffairsME - Ma… https://t.co/RAakdvxPDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adamwchs @audible_com Duly noted.. haven’t read it since high school, so it’s definitely worth a go. Thanks for the suggestion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBates100 @bendudman1 @gaypornfans @Scott_Hasting5 @vincentazz @DylanRosser1 @WomensEyeCandy1 @gavinperry60… https://t.co/GvUAfGAkBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo weyyyy Yoo!! Pero ahorita no me pidan nada porque tengo un mes ocupado]]></document></documents></author>