<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DomSicilian @capital_Tweet @solentos @ShannonSharpe @Dom2k It’s not subjective and you’re in denial. It’s ok. You… https://t.co/OTPzgSwTYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[What y'all think @VinceMcMahon would have @RealMelina do if she comes back? The same thing Mickie is doing putting over the young talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanhope14 Five months ago - hope you enjoyed it in between your complaints......]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Not often you see 92-8” @lisamurkowski #LWCFforever Thanks @Backcountry_H_A @nature_wonks https://t.co/nS962fFDUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardoHq @deximeruya @CreatureLives @AFreakyDude @DeityOfGaming @TNACreative @newpatriot77 @dbroncos78087… https://t.co/pVRVbBhzjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting serious around these parts.. 😉😁 @ Allen, Texas https://t.co/IjBtkfVwxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last few days for our @Bonfire endeavours.   OR  Become a Patron and get a free tlcOG tee.   Thanks for your suppor… https://t.co/BBXIAok4RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy son 21 meses de tu ausencia y no se porque hoy se siente mas fuerte... pero hoy al ver tu sonrisa me das animo… https://t.co/UFtYhXj8eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Cuánto más tiene que esperar la comunidad internacional para frenar ya la usurpación a la fuerza? @jguaido… https://t.co/uNNxOw0lE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1tbaines @agreatbigcity @TimeOutNewYork @ABC7NY @nycgov @nycfeelings @NYCDailyPics @nycgo @Artofvisuals @nypost @lottenypalace Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha whatever. Great job BEAVS!! Let’s go 6-6 on beam for a solid away score!!! BEAVS!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench Methinks showing up at a committee hearing that you are not part of, and where the subject of the all… https://t.co/6ygRtDrZK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude should’ve let her get 3 free punches to the face and then rocked her shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studio 54 doc has me wishing I had the chance to party there.. What a time it must’ve been!! 🕺🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Et tu Michael? Yesterday will hopefully be remembered as the turning point and the beginning of the end of this nat… https://t.co/F7zQMSF5KR]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great way to spend Sunday Morning @q1043 @kendashow https://t.co/NeI3XDwoXy Breakfast With The Beatles playing wi… https://t.co/pocO65OE21]]></document><document><![CDATA[6- would you do a recruitment speach? C- life as we know it is changing.  I have founded the psycore tonight.  I kn… https://t.co/ghnWATQxY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar.  I have had diabetes since age 14 and I'm 59 now. I have been married for 34 years and have one son… https://t.co/m52oYP12hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch time at Twin Peaks @ Twin Peaks Restaurants https://t.co/ALjy0OK0r3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jas_Cassidy @EricHolder HOLDER LIED TO CONGRESS, DIDN'T GET IN TROUBLE... AND HE SAYS WE ALL  SHOULD BE TREATED TH… https://t.co/tmuj92Koif]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest for @MilitaryTimes.  Remember that time Ukraine's president sent James Mattis an assault rifle? Now you do https://t.co/WRXlHC7Koo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between you and me, if Trump or his cult of supporters attack the Cohen statement for its misuse of the word “irony… https://t.co/9ouWc0Ew9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. T's Valentine's Day Message https://t.co/XJUu2Eivbt via @YouTube @aimeejo80 Since my voice didn’t do it justice this morning. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YOHANNA_NUNEZ Gracias al padre ! Me comí todas las uñas en esos últimos segundos! Mirándolo por Facebook y se frizaba! #casimuero!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palepeople @reviewjournal @AaronDFordNV How can we find a wall? And not our schools?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever been a grown man and packed jello in your lunchbox only to forget the spoon and eat it by squeezing it out and biting chunks off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Fix You by @coldplay on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/qwBqJkxNJb https://t.co/olLzfkf4Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @RealSugarLily @CynthiaMark14 @DLees28 @dilruba_lees @reeves5150 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best… https://t.co/UyRlPfUvwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[THAT @SKRILLEX SET WAS ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭 literally everything. that is the culmination of ev… https://t.co/yXakeRInD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassyDillon Did you forget you have 100k followers? Or that you have a boss who loves to torture his employees in these sort of ways? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a great stream today! Here is the VOD https://t.co/TgxJUN1IC4 special thanks to @BWheelerMTG for the battles at the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjs03093641 @ZandEDad @elyeathea @Danielladaney @DanielAshley13 @BadBoxArtMarc @devtheory72 @JanGilson… https://t.co/8Rg21y9kzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleyLambert19 Yessssee coffee Hayley you read my mind 😀😀😀😀 https://t.co/KU2KUjIPPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Goofy Regular by @DuckFootBeer at @duckfootbeer — https://t.co/FbsfN4ciXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Please pray for a family member of mine struggling with mental health.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel Smollett was quite willing to testify against anyone (innocent people) arrested based on his hoax alle… https://t.co/B20PFQsV9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t lie this Nintendo switch the young bulls got looks fire. It’s about forty times better than the brick that So… https://t.co/BRED1XYXQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GagnonFrancois aussi...enfin le respect s’installe à travers la LNH pour la troupe de Barry Trotz !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZAN_4PM I plan on watching Sanders' tape this weekend. Personally, I like Iowa State's David Montgomery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot clock or no shot clock. If you shoot 25% you aren’t winning. They shot 48% against Merrillville but still stru… https://t.co/43poXeb7b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so proud of our president...  Jugada magistral para nuestros niños y pueblo en general.... 😏  👏👏👏👏👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Torrie11 congrats on the well deserved induction into @WWE #WWEHOF @WWENetwork @WrestleMania it would be awesome i… https://t.co/aPNRrUvxYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ citando a calle 13.... luchando por relacionarse con "la muchachada"....y lo sigan creyendo un genio… https://t.co/NLppFuVg8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[All politicians lie but Democrats are the best at it. They’ve got a lot of experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast. (@ Angie's Restaurant in Fairfax, VA) https://t.co/ONMamc53Su https://t.co/tYDl5EFzeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The plan was to move Sister Jeans kitchen to St. Monica’s now that deal appears to be dead with this statement from… https://t.co/zUJ5XIiCJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this moment, the one and only Buddy turned to AJ, chose to jump off his mommas porch..... they made it to wherev… https://t.co/DU2SV9Dmfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manus37 @JohnDBeckTV @Scatter @savannahleemay @IamLilimar @daniellaperkins @dibenedettolexi @LilimarMum… https://t.co/11WGhinsYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich @CarpeDonktum But of course, you're not racist. No sir. Not at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themomma_bee You know Cody and I have all the love for you guys ❤️ big day, and I know positive results are coming!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonDelano investors “in a pickle” over future of @KraftHeinzCo - good one LOL - via @KDKA #SunBizPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[REAL ID driver’s licenses are now available to Pennsylvania residents who want them, PennDOT says https://t.co/pAgY21TgBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klnynews Your airport travels seem to have the makings of a 'Twilight Zone' episode. Looking forward to your posti… https://t.co/0I7bTXsKh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[MARK TAYLOR LASTEST INTERVIEW (02/15/2019) BUILD THE WALL! PROPHECY FEB.... https://t.co/Fp7xZgPMg3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gave some girl a blue bouncy ball today, thought it was time girls experience blue balls #equality]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Serving cold hamberders, tepid covfefe, and $29.99 red hats made in China. https://t.co/xTwd79ekcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will NOT let the Russians beat us! Hacking won’t stop @CDunning929 from running this show. Give my guy the follo… https://t.co/AjQPXXkVXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort @DonaldJTrumpJr @TwitchyTeam SCHIFF NEEDS INVESTIGATED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to spend. VAlentines Day alone @ Wang's Buffet https://t.co/U1jlbTkWNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was recently told that the rock I listen to is now labeled as “dad rock” 😕. The person that told me listens to… https://t.co/d2V6FjgthU]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for that. Next time. Maybe, don’t lead a guy on forever. I mean I almost died! That woulda been sad. Thoughts at 1:16pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing one of my longest friend, grow from where she was 2 years ago. From everything thats been going on, she has… https://t.co/IGJhTIgyob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce Pearl is such a good guy. I’d have him over to my house for a BBQ anytime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globeandmail @marshalederman Each of 48 letters are represented of Each of 48 States plus Two in the reading of :… https://t.co/6jgu4OYORh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @JumaaneWilliams driving at the far turn up 11pts with 67% reporting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DB_Legends when y'all release Gogeta blue his blast art cards should break blast armor. Just a quick idea pitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmaoist @zigzackly If camouflage is the new saffron is persiflage the new Teflon? If décollage is the new argument… https://t.co/outdRWmoIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreggDoyelStar Bravo! If this would’ve happened on the south side, we would’ve been vilified. But it’s ok up “nort… https://t.co/mI24qYQu45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marceldesrosie1 @KenLingenfelter Hats off to the “Hoopster” that replicated the bigger SS rims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ There's nothing worth more that would ever come close, No thing can compare, You're our… https://t.co/kzuxTBAHGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andre_Saj I knew it was because of that lmao I was gonna day middle cause R Kelly but I don’t know how good that album actually is]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HAPPENINGNOW: @PAAuditorGen is calling out government officials for taking gifts from voting equipment vendors. Mo… https://t.co/wm8pGcPgAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIE ABSOLUTE INJUSTICE JURISDICTION AUTHORITY JUWISH CULT ATTERNYS. WANT TO CONTEST MY LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE… https://t.co/ftnwsbGIlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is like a race we have ups and downs but we gotta make it to the finish line 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Michael Cohen for #bestactor2019 ! Had Ed K. Drooling and dreaming! But seriously, why… https://t.co/RUJ71EOgyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clay4499 @Brown1Carter @BtownBanners @dandakich I think douchebag is trying to coach when he should be just announ… https://t.co/Pl7DZ2zKEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#grammys2019 ☠👾☠👾☠👾☠👾 @ Los Angeles Convention Center https://t.co/sDDCf6Zoxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning cook up, easy like Sunday morning y'all! #hungry #hustle #beats #instrumental #music #musicproducer… https://t.co/moLDtrvf12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TH_Connoisseur @Hugebooblover13 @80_lieto_fied OMG I love your huge titties]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emplums We have a custom setup right now but are going to be moving to Storybook soon.   Storybook = component wor… https://t.co/Y2UC5f5aka]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promise I’m an adult.... 😶🤷🏼‍♂️ @ DR John's Lingerie https://t.co/cUqmZLGBki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems are the terrorist party. Beware as they probably masterminded 911. Now they have 2 terrorists in Congress Omar and  Rashida Tlaib💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGriesbaumJr @MitchMossRadio @Mike_Ferrin  I don't know about you guys but I can't wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No temptation has overtaken you except such as is common to man; but God is faithful, who will n… https://t.co/C9j8itSnYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[who tooted free peoples’ horn so hard that their version of a shirt on sale is $119??]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend is really out of my league in every way imaginable. I'm seriously blessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill wants more online retailers to charge Georgia patrons a sales tax https://t.co/0TpyHOsSNr #gapol @GAPoliticsNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trunzo_veronica @KamalaHarris I dont do any of that and i dont kill babys so a man treated you like shit so your g… https://t.co/RBY6wJZbqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ca snowflakes, Your tax dep libs want to tax sugery drinks. Hope you voters enjoy giving your $ to politicians,… https://t.co/2n5OlnOuES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyBiwer @dothedirtybird_ @scottcoleman55 Getting a Hall of Fame player at 26 doesn’t cripple any team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikMozolik @CraigHeffley I don’t believe the soldier customization stuff is there. I’ll follow up Tuesday (when I’m back in the office).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricardorossello @WhiteHouse @NatlGovsAssoc @realDonaldTrump @VP @mike_pence Dear Governor, Are you aware that the… https://t.co/aWBGDivbXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This summer will be a full year of electric car ownership and I couldn’t be happier. I talk to so many strangers ab… https://t.co/osJ32hCNsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday to #Dimebash2019 Backstage warmup &amp; hang w/the great Kyle Sanders and the indomitable… https://t.co/eXNYYT3VOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We walk away from our dreams afraid that we may fail, or worse yet, afraid that we may succeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickThorp1 @KnippenKc @KnippenNikki @QSchlagbaum @KyleeHoersten @hanneman_14 I'm going to see if I can make it to… https://t.co/rOivjgpBLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...looks like she's #unveiling her new super gonzo aerodynamic #Surfing #position!... #Supergirl #Surfergirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Just shot down every male rapper who supported him. https://t.co/R0CCdIhVxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep your 💩 in Seattle. Bring it to my door step and you will feel rock salt for amonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help @nate_oats win this drive to raise money for cancer research.  #NateOats #TIMEOUTFTW   A RT of this is also a… https://t.co/hmTylS0DrQ]]></document></documents></author>