<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Terrible shot  but all 3 of them are laying together on the couch for the 1st time! It's taken almost 4 weeks for I… https://t.co/8Zv6hmN1rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 1 year to the only YouTube video ever thank you @vvalentae https://t.co/Fo5e9563mO]]></document><document><![CDATA[เอ๊าาาา ใกล้นิดเดียวเอง ทำไมฉันไม่ไปtime squareวันนั้นล่ะ มั้ยยยยยย ลิซ่าา]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing @TheReserveIW our beautiful listing located at 49937 Desert Arroyo Trail. View listing on website in bio. @… https://t.co/pron9SiXge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watching @HunterKiller #USNavy rules &amp; proud to be American 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillsBaitShop Hey there!  Hope you are having a great weekend too, love the vacation pics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all wanna watch a show where there’s two characters who are in a relationship that’s cute af go watch season 4… https://t.co/XBWGE8tfqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rockefeller Center highlights, courtesy of Lego. @ LEGO https://t.co/8ayAtyj33y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_bmedina5 @kimrgz Next day we were back at my house like https://t.co/Kw2cBiTKec]]></document><document><![CDATA[now im laying in bed right after eating some hot cheetos &amp; takis &amp; you best believe my stomach is burning 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as I can sleep with you huh 💀🙄 I have no words for y’all females]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I hope I have worked enough Creighton/Providence games so that I can write a book on all the cool things I’ve heard from Ed Cooley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelticVisionOrg @BakerSullivan @whidbeyz @EdKrassen @AOC Absolutely! But just by the comments we can see the brain… https://t.co/uspJb7btiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s up in 2020 don’t fall for her phoniness!! Take her vote now and make her lose her race #2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingNewzman @PeggyCheek4 @realDonaldTrump Those who live in glass houses should not throw stones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roadblocks to job performance and career development are the top reasons employees leave companies. And when employ… https://t.co/TBZqa6KgSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: how much sleep? Not enough. Can I count the couch naps towards my total? Or the times I hit snooze?  #RunChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[You do not want our citizens here treated with dignity and respect.Illegals should be apprehended and sent back .Il… https://t.co/RoI5kjnNca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!! $7,650 raised during @HopeRises_News happy hour for Bella's Bumbas! 51 kids will know get their FREE wheelch… https://t.co/NlTjZ3o7lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[we need to think more about occupational “squeezes” that lead to more pressures on labor for less pay — these are r… https://t.co/hxbgHASCYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhateverIguess_ But 90% of rappers dont get involved in double homicides with substantial enough forensic evidence… https://t.co/eNSN7US71V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDunc1982 @AliOBrien16 @GMB If allowed back it doesn’t mean she gets her liberty. I see how he can’t fathom why sh… https://t.co/Uh63DD6pAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear from @SaulEwing’s new Minnesota Office Managing Partner @AlColemanJr re our MidWest expansion #Minnesota… https://t.co/lWlxxLBs86]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fave coworker was like “just so you know they sent a video of you on the phone to the gc and you might get in tr… https://t.co/TFRBpeV4OQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have known it would be horrible when they described non-binary folks as “gender deviant”]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Policía debe encontrar a los galgueros maltratadores! https://t.co/SuEf4ipZoW via @sosvox]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/6 Deniers- they want to sell another Jesus other than the Jesus we know about from our Bibles. Usually they want… https://t.co/rQgmbN6L85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teapot_tea Didn’t she do this to his first baby mama? Not that it makes it right or anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are GRAPE, STRAWBERRY , PEACHES, PLUMS, NUTS, ETC. HARVEST MACHINES NOW...... WHERE WILL THESE PEOPLE WORK?… https://t.co/vFgM4M5jrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanetETennessee @lynneguist I'm confused. Do people *not* pronounce the second t in trait?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovernorKayIvey @POTUS @fema What makes Alabama so much more important or deserving A+ treatment from FEMA over Ca… https://t.co/KNoCVzNVYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off we go (@ Monterrey International Airport - @aeropuertodemty in Apodaca, NL) https://t.co/Zm42xyseiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RationalBeing @krassenstein @drchatterjee @realDonaldTrump Well if your were talking about California breaking up… https://t.co/PMLwH0YReE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcspocky Oh, Spocky. So sorry you're sad. I will tell you the only joke I know. Why is 6 afraid of 7? Cuz 7 8 9.… https://t.co/ld6419S15A]]></document><document><![CDATA[if @SeaveyDaniel follows me i will go on the vegas strip and yell STREAM COLD IN LA BY WHY DONT WE]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT @Tiffani_Bova   When a metric becomes a target — that is, when it becomes the primary focus of a job —  it cease… https://t.co/N6lDOrhbVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might look like I’m on this trip alone - but I’m not, it’s just that dr3wcurto has been taking all the photos and… https://t.co/NsuUqF2aYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SolomonRDavid @NichollsBiology Sounds very interesting. Very valuable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz You should be CENSURED, and Twitter is forever. https://t.co/FqHTY9Kv5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[miss me with the “wanna come over and hang”  no. take me on a real date and if that goes good then I’ll, “come over and hang.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianTh45079330 @ThomasJTobin1 Moreover, where the Holy Father urges MERCY and points out HOW the medicine of merc… https://t.co/Wy4ZxVzy2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrippaTrips @pip_says @wyomingtourism @dsouzaashayne @markandkylee @StromfieldAdvs @TravelBugsWorld… https://t.co/aLjo7QiXhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every muscle in my body feels like it’s been put through the wringer. PMS + post-conference burn out is possibly th… https://t.co/yVOsTn81sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s criminal we don’t see enough from this series in general and I’ve never seen a Luka. Pattern doesn’t look too… https://t.co/wzL8J1FsG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrunosSF this SATURDAY!!  @cutso and I in the mix yeah? 🙃 yaaaa @ Bruno's Nightclub https://t.co/zabur6bjIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday March 5th  The moon is 1.8% waning in the sign of Pisces. Positive thinking keeps you a float today as peop… https://t.co/h9goZXpS84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eagerly awaiting the arrival of @pattonoswalt!! @ The Vets https://t.co/18F0dwV5u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frederickscior1  @Esther188rod  THANK YOU SWEETIE ❣️ VERY KIND OF YOU HAVE A WONDERFUL SUNDAY 1ST SUNDAY OF LENT G… https://t.co/Z0gFgfbAII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FRC5090 What time are you competing today? I was thinking of bringing my kids up! 💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ampxco’s tweets fill me with hope 😌 can’t do my makeup anymore but I’ve never worked with food before so damnit le… https://t.co/xnj4Ib9Szg]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ Walkin' past the mirror &lt;OOH&gt; Damn, I'm fine ... Let a bitxh try me, “BOOM” Hammer time👊🏾💥 ________ #MyaRay… https://t.co/2klmfcPqyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so jacked how the WOMEN are held accountable for whatever their dads do or don’t say to Colton? As soon as ano… https://t.co/kTV0whJ43n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OOsal @sherrilee7 Sorry.. That has been accomplished. Thx Trump &amp; the Cult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradTakei @GeorgeTakei When is ALL Greek going to be banned on EVERY campus in the country?!?!?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m not supposed to do this I’m a mom now but hey I’m feeling BoReD https://t.co/9x2pnG9f4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp “Yes, I was told a story of what happened before I arrived that day by John Blizzard, Vanderpump D… https://t.co/lSlEyNHJ8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanSmi12045449 @RyanEGraney @HillaryClinton @GOP The affordable care act is working. No more denials with pre-exi… https://t.co/xuSXSR8wnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenOfThroness @CelebLipstick @GardnerTally @susanmaclean41 @flashella10 @alysa_apollonia @ki_native @skipandpete… https://t.co/JDF9sXLnB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time in the new stadium. First time watching my favorite player. Although disappointed in his pic on the Jumb… https://t.co/v4qguBfjGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget my Twitter is public. Especially when people respond to my tweets that have nothing to do with t… https://t.co/WDkWFInTVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileahKromer @DEMurphy I’m more of a classic Arial girl myself, although I’ve been known to have some fun with Georgia or Baskerville.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessica_ArmyVet He's just not a church goer and is Christian in name only like a lot of other people. My problem i… https://t.co/JG6uiCA4h9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarraFion @morninglive @TasteofBurl Yummy Churros. It’s been a couple months since I’ve been @BarraFion . I think… https://t.co/r9sOIxd9b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHAPPYMEDIUM Happy Valentine's day to you and your hubby. 💘 https://t.co/T1aaQ2mDfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally thinking about the dumbest stuff right now when i should be sleeping]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romance is a bonus book is a great Korean show. If you like international stuff this one is it🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Minnesotan in me laughs every time things are cancelled for "expected" snow in KC. This is why my family thinks… https://t.co/hNyQeTiewI]]></document><document><![CDATA[girl no they can’t wait to brag about who they hitting smfh 🙄🤦🏽‍♀️ bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a brand new BART train! It’s nice. Let’s invest in public infrastructure and in our public services. Let’s get O… https://t.co/VLa4uE7Sg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day two of st patty’s month and I’ve already made over a grand lmao 🍀🍀🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danya_Rachelle @_hotttamale I don’t think I can do Texas because of the humidity. My curly hair just looks awful l… https://t.co/R6mQDjFJY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌 to the @BrunswickGroup SF crew for a fantastic 📘party setup at Monroe on Broadway (on IG). #grateful https://t.co/wZeG4bWwlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The Trump Organization is going bankrupt. Why don't you focus on working on your company instead of… https://t.co/6Gic1Jg29g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClintEastwoodLA @darlajane @i_womb @AliceOllstein @TheDemocrats Clint remake The way we were, with a Socialist Ame… https://t.co/xNpK6Q9shv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The democrats have lost their minds, they want to do away with private insurance. Who do they think they are? They… https://t.co/kHnpgUiOdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao me either but im about to. Too many bitter, jealous, and irrelevant people on social media giving their unpopu… https://t.co/hpMN0uCCnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Old North Sacramento, Sacramento https://t.co/8WoOuHZ59s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patton6966 will appreciate this being an ex-fireman! Just an average miracle happening in today’s crazy world! 😉✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Está vez que lleven la ayuda humanitaria en contenedores que no pueden incendiar tan fácil y llevar unidades de bom… https://t.co/EQ3gN1lv6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz He has a certificate in editing, didn’t learn much from that certficate]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an interesting, enlightening discussion with someone who most of us would write off. He was a white Massachu… https://t.co/TNgdZmBVPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the saddle again. In sunny ☀️ Tombstone AZ. At the O.K. Corral now waiting for the gunfite reenactment. The… https://t.co/yROPh4R8m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥💥💥How to create the perfect high-end decor for your home or gifts💥💥💥💥Comment below and I’ll show you more! 👇🏻👇🏻👇🏻… https://t.co/3C8tgcYiJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the squad from our Denver trip linked up and re-took a group pic but I was at work, so I photoshopped me in 😂 https://t.co/xRaNcVcdB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[She brought me her mouse this morning. Fred is her favorite. 🐀 I think she might like me a little ❤️🥰 #loveher… https://t.co/TYtLx1Dkuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her smile warms my heart! Moving to California and pushing Hannah to move down here was so important because lettin… https://t.co/GPrl3GMKpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@succ_ulentmom @yellow_laney Here's the thing. You do. You have every right to express your opinion but doing it li… https://t.co/9nht3h87VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmnemes @LouisvilleDad Many teachers calling in sick with PTSD symptoms over "sewer bill"  Sups made decisions to close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may now be part of the @MapleLakeISD881 Irish pack, but I will always bleed a little bit of navy blue… https://t.co/ZftxVZnGRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lethargilistic @neontaster He's an idea, stop talking about race &amp; gender.  Nobody cares about that stuff in real life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weinbach We are NOT Perfect so how can we find someone PERFECT! It will Never happen Will!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s official i’m getting a spider man and captain america tattoo. i can’t wait any longer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rilee_Tomkinson @c_nyreee Nah your man stopped hitting us up so we had to look elsewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I said before, look at the facts. Tristan has a history. Why does all the blame always fall on the woman? Jord… https://t.co/eSVbty68ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohioedison we’ve been without power all day. We reported it. I live in Beach City in Tuscarawas county. Any idea h… https://t.co/5IxN7s5AvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC "There is no shame in honest work,...it is a shame to steal." (An elderly Jewish woman told me that when I sha… https://t.co/U1H73U5pHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ari Melber on MSNBC is taking down Sen. Collins' pretense of being open- minded about Roe v. Wade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playoff game tonight at 7pm let's go Delta @MensDeltaBBall @MichCCAA @goliath_11bball @DjBlaylock3 @Thenameischaz5 https://t.co/3e2uJvULqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't imagine sitting at home all day again but I don't have the energy for much else...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonWarren6 @mimibeck617 @ohchadwick I have to agree with you. I also did not like the comment "did you eat toda… https://t.co/USoEOoENqP]]></document></documents></author>