<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@amyjccuddy The women from @Televerde  would definitely benefit from reading your book.  Education and empowerment… https://t.co/gZNhDNtkhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jason_quitt @OccultPriestess @dreamrunes @TheNightmareDoc @Rodney_Ascher The others were scam artists. The thing t… https://t.co/44jUq4ubXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fablefy They sound amazing! We need “down to earth” people to keep us grounded and focused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Shout!!! I shopped my sis @justjewels4u #poshmark and I love this animal print beauty!! #shopblackowned @ At… https://t.co/wtdFHxOXZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Inspiration I wont tell you....I'll show you. #newweek #newgoals #newmotivation #flourish2019… https://t.co/gVcMNG2lgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy athletic training month to the best trainers!! y’all deserve every bit of recognition this month bc y’all are… https://t.co/xNMx0aHHtw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxingrich We heard about it the next day on the radio. I was 2 years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched Bohemian Rhapsody tonight. It was so well done and Rami Malek deserves every award possible. Brough… https://t.co/IYYLzgNtAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marley4901 @CodyWolfeMusic That was exactly my first thought. Second thought after seeing his picture, "how many w… https://t.co/EfYFdGAVe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enen1 @Graceman66 @RevChuckCurrie @realDonaldTrump Because no one has responsibilities today. We are a deprived so… https://t.co/j7gDY5NC8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CouncilmanBMS @RectorSun Unrelated, Brandon, thank you fo participating in the Charm City documentary. Saw it a fe… https://t.co/4XG7QLTTQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump thinks his supporters are the most gullible people on earth. Are they really? The president is counting on hi… https://t.co/nyEEMaC8JU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to get another video of me throwing ginger at jastin but I missed really bad and it stuck to the wall and then fell off behind him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andy_fitze makes me wonder if #human-like #AI will schedule “breaks” between #tech conferences? On to #RSAC2019 #SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delayneserenity Omg it’s cute but I’m too short for it and couldn’t pee, I LOVE YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s honestly been such a stressful and annoying day and I just want to cry but I have to do HOMEWORK :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of the Styx song “Too Much Time on My Hands” - I can relate to this...there’s not enough vacation and to… https://t.co/4z8W0f5Y1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinnershells Shoot! I wish I could say I was a napper! #cantsleepduringtheday #TypeA #lasttimeinappedihadanewborn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Captainziggels @DFBHarvard @CovfefeLadyC @BreitbartNews No it’s that the dude is illegal… Americans go to jail for… https://t.co/9x4yrJVZU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me find out you a coke head too 🤣 fuck around and ruin both y’all lives 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Willloves2hunt @TallisMorgan @MollyV178 Hello! My name is Valentina and I don’t like whip cream. https://t.co/v1xhyPYwJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[this has been an eventful month for me. which event is more impressive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nuna_USA Can you just send me a video?  Couldn't find anything online. Would rather not waste time on hold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Any critical thinking person knows that...You point is well taken...But Trump doesn't know it yet, bu… https://t.co/F1pMjhwAGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kika_GuideDog @TheBabyShow @Bugaboo That is impressive, I have never been able to find a stroller that I could pull like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For work we wear basic black polos and my extra ass wears Burberry polos LOL. Antes muerta que sencilla 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta in your T sky club in ATL. Club is open until 10, bar until 9:45. Young couple of mixed race walks in at 9:4… https://t.co/siJOL2mooT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@argaman @americanarena @MollyJongFast @yashar I have German family and they had an entire cupboard of Spargelzeit… https://t.co/ypmTNzif53]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish one of this three guys could come here, I would fuck them for free, or both of them lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry for all my liked posts but I CANNOT with all the memes and gifs about jordyn/Kylie/kris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chronicle I think this perspective is an ivory tower academia model and discouages reflective academics  that serve the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessG_ Idk why people are obsessed with false allegations like the other 98% of REAL assaults don’t exist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All we do is win win win no matter what!!!!!! Congrats to the MBK, WBK SB and the BB team. #HAILSTATE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr This won’t b the last, wake up america before it’s too late, foot is in the door]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, at least we positively KNOW who NOT to vote for in 2020! PLEASE PRAY FOR THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA!!!  KIL… https://t.co/LTNlAbPIsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[México apuntaló en 2018 su liderazgo en el sector cervecero https://t.co/K3Os9wORce vía @https://twitter.com/eleconomista]]></document><document><![CDATA[He cannot even get on Air Force One w. an umbrella...hint: The Umbrella won.... #FakeTrumpEmergency… https://t.co/Z3WRqPxqSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time a guy messaged me and called me a slut when I’ve hardly ever spoken to him but when Ben messaged him he sa… https://t.co/1uxeIXD7n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fire Tower Red by @shortwaybrewing at @promiselandmkt — https://t.co/fsRG7VJQry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go Gulls!!! #hockeyhounds #gullslive #sandiegogulls #sandiegobunnies https://t.co/SogQQtZwvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did the waiter put enough whip cream on my hot cocoa? 🤔😍😂 https://t.co/ZeWAc6IpnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops I may have just accidentally sent people after Phil for a year-old tweet...oh well.🤷🏼‍♀️ (I was just retweetin… https://t.co/1q2An4j6Eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HengAnnie Ok but did you actually go try it? 😂 https://t.co/k6aMLj3REE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few more pic of my Trip To California from the day we did a little  filming for worldofwonder.  be on the look ou… https://t.co/SFZX1HrpDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__stepphhiiee See that’s one thing that freaks me out about getting pregnant 😂 everyone is different so I don’t know what to expect]]></document><document><![CDATA[The water taxi between the eastern part of Montreal and the downtown is going to be back again this year.   Last ye… https://t.co/i78w27milR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I claim my friend who keeps complaining about her boyfriend as my Dependent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite session of today was @mdial talking about empathy in AI and business. #SXSW⁠ #empathySXSW https://t.co/HRPBco5wAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday Yall!! I had an awesome time with my girl @iamrhonpeterson this morning while attending the grand op… https://t.co/TInVl1SHV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Suddenly realizes that I, a REDcard holder, should actually join this.* https://t.co/AgEwt9td3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travis_jou Even Ambrose places 5th in the men’s 400 hurdles with a 1:01:08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX @TriciaBader @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr A socialist,  well it figures. TRUMP 2020, This Country will never be socialist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julsrich @GoldenAgeFilm @tcm Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, love this movie with Elizabeth Taylor and Paul Newman 💜… https://t.co/eHe3dOI0mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people have a “Vision Board” I have a “Vision Sign” #soniarivera4houston https://t.co/3OLsdEmTFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jianshoney @KianLawley @KianAndJc @jaysee @jccaylen @Kian you’re so beautiful, and your outfit is so cute!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey BO, Dems! KR posted on his bike website saying he doesn’t use social media. He posted this for you, not me. For… https://t.co/DwWpLwlkv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSalvac @ValentinaESL @JennyVo15 @Sarasparks21 @LeoneMack3 @esljaana @gabbytorres2017 @alycia_owen @delgadong94… https://t.co/5R4lv1dgEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great to see @TylerHilton when he’s in town! Such a great show tonight 🥰 https://t.co/fo5Vy3yy1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daffodils were the first flowers 🌼Jenny gave me on my first Mothers Day 🌼 @Omadre @OccidoLumen666 @gordon_hughes2… https://t.co/1FHeXi35Zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerwoodKerby1 @CheriJacobus Which explains CNN’s fascination with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@choll12 Caroline, do you even understand what a diehard fan my ex was of Chubbies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live what you love. Have a sharktastic #MaxMonday! https://t.co/SQ9BcoNKvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pepperfire @gill_godwin @ruthmkb @TrevorsIdeas @SusanDelacourt @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @TorontoStar Any special reason?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m back b!tch. Don’t @ me h0e hahahahaha jk you know I love you @iTailynn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxycharm I love a good liquid and a cream concealer so what ever you choose is find with me guys! I sure would lo… https://t.co/SVYN3XhNIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 10th Birthday Marley Corne!!!  💞🐶💞🐶💞🐶💞🐶💞🐶💞🐶💞 #houseofthemisfits #chihuauamix #beaglemix #adoptdontshop #dogs… https://t.co/eQlpgaz6Kq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_vt16 @dcexaminer @erinelsadunne They don't consider illegals murdering Americans an emergency?  They think Am… https://t.co/9KSvXT1fEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEADASS!! literally the bestest girlfriend/bestfriend ever!❤️ i love you with my whole heart😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so damn bored i just keep walking around the house 😭 someone make plans with me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work, resilience, and mentorship in the right setting=opportunity. Great job Evan. Well done Coach McCourt ano… https://t.co/GC5LspweLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[That lady so be ashamed of herself. Taking a ball away from a little girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLOVERadio God bless you and your pastors for helping me through the worst time in my life. My mother, Mary Diane… https://t.co/3dfHRGiGmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alan_stoddard 4. Call themselves men of God but are wolves in sheep's clothing. The ppl I worry about aren't those… https://t.co/DJxxxc895F]]></document><document><![CDATA[“17% of people experience some form of disability. Something needs to change.” - @maayanziv closing off… https://t.co/BqPMlLktBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge congrats to @mattgarry_ on your new role with @UConnMBB! We are so proud of and excited for you🎉🎉 #seeyourmanseetheball]]></document><document><![CDATA[karlajoneswilsonrealtor in the house!!! Post filming our Home Buyer Series. Real Estate Agent and Attorney? Enough… https://t.co/8aJYOl615f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wish my mom would act like a mom. Or just a decent person. Shit fucks me up having NO real parents to turn to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Specialist Stampede at Tara O! #TaraO  @TaraOaks_ES https://t.co/h8dFpUGUHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marriott your site has been "temporarily unable to process requests and availability" for an hour. FYI: that's not… https://t.co/d944k4NBjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomandAtticus A wonderful memory of the bond between a man and his dog, Atticus. https://t.co/1oqgb1fZVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima just retweet this for all my friends with no healthcare/financial troubles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for Authentic Sri Lankan food in NYC? You have to head to Staten Island- just tried Randiwa. It’s delicious… https://t.co/Cke5ovjKxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey sunny. I hope the safari is treating you well. It’s cold up here. Send your rays bb!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t look now. #Pistons up 13 against No. 3 #Pacers with 1:57 left in the 4th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiteMomba If you read my tweets I have stated OVER AND OVER again that any 👏🏼 sexual 👏🏼 content 👏🏼 being 👏🏼 sent… https://t.co/ESQfGkF5VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an extremely productive weekend, but now I’m ready for the weekend again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at gregory ave &amp; northfield ave in west orange, NJ https://t.co/udeZWowK5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shemarmoore @swatcbs Can’t wait till Thursday I wish you was here in Kentucky to protect me!!! 👊🏼💪🏼😊😁🥺 Feel free t… https://t.co/uCeSRllPNl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look! My book! @ShakeandCoBooks #rockneedsriver https://t.co/Xx5lUCzAzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So ready for this one. Can’t wait to see how well they portrayed us 🙏🏻🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skincare 101!  What a difference a month makes!  Join me live tonight, 6:30 at @beckypiferjourney on FB. I can’t wa… https://t.co/UCHMzy7Ae6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation.. Worshiping Jesus and my daily readings 😇😇 https://t.co/gCMdMj7Y1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I drank half a beer at work and I can already feel it, I’m so weak lmao😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 dumbasses who dont know anything about what is happening.  And r probably pressured by  Chamber of Commerce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be easier and cheaper and probably taste better to just grill a piece of marinated cardboard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lakers Come on guys! Pick up the pace ! LeBron just take over the game! 💪🏀👑💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KameronBennett Pay off all my loans I know that’s not buying something but I’d rather be debt free]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Democrats #FeelTheBern2020  ? @JackHites and I will talk about Bernie Sanders 2020 with @GovHowardDean and… https://t.co/xR7rVubQNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prisoner of Love // Arthur Jafa #museumofcontemporaryart @ Museum of Contemporary Art Chicago https://t.co/8GwbxHlKQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachFTIII @Coach_Greene79 He should have bought the right shoes—- like Air Jordan’s. Shot happens - one guy doesn… https://t.co/HjzswC2uNQ]]></document></documents></author>