<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@twagz20 @CheriJacobus We Finally found the right man to calm the waters &amp; get things back on track]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Badgers and Nittany Lions are underway in Game 2 at Pegula. https://t.co/CmfbKl0t8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill I, for one, would love to slap that idiotic smurk off this imbeciles face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thanks for the information ! NONE OF US CAN FIGURE OUT WHY YOU’ RE HERE !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbassadorRice on the future of national security. #georgetown https://t.co/ngHZHkXbua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must be Friday!! #hardtobeme #worldtravler #thankful #luvmylife #luvjeremyslife #hardtobeking @ Delta Sky Club Term… https://t.co/2ioD4Wdmcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your don't have to be anything other than what you've been trying to be lately]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrindstoneSEO Это великолепная работа, мой друг. Красиво. Это прекрасно, не так ли?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look it doesn't affect me hurt my feelings when people call me the R-word you want evidence here one 1 time after I… https://t.co/oUrwxo2MN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello i just made this new track. Lemme know what you think about it #edm #new #song #music #track #newsong #artist… https://t.co/YWNYbuYULb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROJO36 @TheCookieRojas That guys definitely builds peanut butter castles in his basement]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am officially 40. While I’m nowhere near where I’d thought I’d be where I am is pretty good.  Happy birthday to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudaPhillis @Billfagan9 @Derameth @EinsteinMaga Yes  will it be on cnn pay per view televised]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hope is a waking dream.” —Aristotle #Hope #NYC #Gotham #iPhonePhotography @ 7th Av, 53th St, Manhattan, New York https://t.co/QjaYSIr49S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenShattuck Like Tania said, if your pan is seasoned well, then you won’t need to do much. Put your oven to 425… https://t.co/9kIZDJCeVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinniecassius @getemjcnw @newestmagazine @RealLisaFrank @PhobiaOfficial 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/SSIfxG7Rq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThunderJew1775 @mattyglesias @ModeledBehavior Which terms make it clear he’s discussing post-election conduct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lillian_Guerra @catedracuba @MJ_Busta @Adita_Ferrer Also I'd like the request a full photo of that painting in the… https://t.co/hQWeEC2Z0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn immigrants stealing the jobs of good, honest, American meth cooks #BUILDTHEWALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug Williams signed by Bobby Beathard, who was still there when he won that SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to see my neurologist today. Good news no MRI needed. Has seen a slow down of the disease since I have been taking #ocrevus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reducing infant, maternal mortality key to improving AC's health. Story by @clairelowe #ReinventingAC   https://t.co/Vq2ueHClMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#retirement #beercation brewery number 15: Persimmon Hollow Brewing Co., DeLand, Fla. https://t.co/OZAGVpkHQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnyrockhill @a_nowtime @klbkt @BobKillman1 @johnluyks @skybar01 @wildbillphoto @mez_merrill @ViktorMochalin… https://t.co/dxpCwtNpMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no facts to base this off of but I feel like his shooting percentage had to be in the toilet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @marclobliner  This epic camo hoodie and @ArnoldSports sale is live now @tigerfitnesscom and is in while su… https://t.co/ZTf9jKzYr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣 S/O to soundwellslc’s even photographer snapping this dope flick of my cutthroat Crizo and I posted up at the sho… https://t.co/RYXpH7QTTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbirch15 It’s left from time to time, but thankfully it always comes back. Like a bad penny lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10skyler @AnionSports @officialKobesta @KinGSLY0727 @Dc_Or_Nothing Yea he was solid.. what’s your point tho? He ma… https://t.co/aGF69hwE5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiPointeDriveIn Do you serve this every sunday also, https://t.co/1aLP56s99I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwistedOne96 @Jasmine8137488 @AnthonyGuidera @Real_AzKyle @rogueranger23 @Randal68052371 @RickLRobbins… https://t.co/RbIZHgMUX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHGdawn @christianllamar @w_terrence This entire charade should if been stopped then and there. He's an admitted a… https://t.co/rls2AhNkj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmersonBarrett I think that’s really cool man, I would love to see old movies and art films at the shows, way cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are never going to use the words “memorandum of understanding” again”—even tho it’s binding and legal. What an… https://t.co/yUwgS6aBcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Our Guest WDW Podcast Episode 1447 - Listener Questions- Stream the show right now at https://t.co/ZMlyv2QqIx Do… https://t.co/pxYTi3hRa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[congratulations on an awesome career toko @tu12pou all the best with the agency. If you ever wanma a chat about Rug… https://t.co/uV0J2PQn97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVS__11 But the real question is: is it a ‘barbecue’ or a ‘cookout?’ 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[buncha idiots. first of all, why you playing with fire on dry grass. second of all WHY AINT YO FRIENDS HELPING YOU… https://t.co/KyN9eErJs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cullen_p @TiffanyWatsonX Hi everyone &amp; let’s make this happen &amp; RT THE Twitter post alright thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m feeling extremely grateful for amazing friends. https://t.co/33KJWSgEbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Ted and other GOP rats 🐀 start realizing that Trump’s end is approaching and are now trying to save their hides...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damont_nelson Thats not to say his death wasn’t a complete tragedy. Of course Stephon Clark didn’t deserve to die,… https://t.co/AR4LF6EzMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sparksjls @CaptainsLogAz He did not. We knew he is stupid. This is too funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferBrinker It’s bunny time! Next time give me a heads up I might be able to sneak ya in the back room and you… https://t.co/y8fvveOMP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtmoneyadventur @JoeRJimenez I agree. We've thought about those possibilities as well. The market is certainly there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 52. Devastated. #lukeperry #riplukeperry #soitgoes @ Scarborough, Maine https://t.co/bETr8QgKqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So cool. #Chants first matchup will be against #SanDiego. #Toreros are 9-4 and coming off a 31-3 win. Yup, they sco… https://t.co/4TJRSmJtOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkrossolife Oh I hope not! But you may be right. Lol. Here’s to seeing spring flowers. https://t.co/CNeYupon9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @lilkiiiim telling me to listen “It’s a Great Day to Be Alive” in the mornings. I already feel better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferSall yeah. probably the baby. Sickos! But hey! Let’s pass the hill and all stand and cheer like we just wo… https://t.co/vm3GJNBGqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 So all you have to do to be a pedophile is claim it’s in the name of Alah. Bull shit. What if the child… https://t.co/RKWBvX1djk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSBSlade    Hi Scott,  Elizabeth ‘s story will be aired on John Walsh ‘s In Pursuit Wednesday night on the ID Chan… https://t.co/ULcnq2ZMK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you know how reporters and photogs feel when you spin us on to something after we already have a story shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[OffGuard Shotz : #sony50mm #kidsphotography #travelphotography @sonyalphagear sonyalphagallery  ☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆☆… https://t.co/8rmFLqgXJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea how timely it was that I FB tagged Boardmember @richmintz on this topic last night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @DeadBunnyFrank I got my learners permit at 15 1/2, and full license at 16. But that's just Montana..… https://t.co/1Zyzp3w454]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Might be the best ever declared national emergency. It’s a direct assault on our border. This Potu… https://t.co/qSrAagICPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OKCTopicThunder @adaniels33 Haha, awesome. I was just saying earlier I wanted to hear @adaniels33 on a pod today,… https://t.co/c2dbuuG3qE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump cspan still has House in session   And CSPAN2 has repeat of 2020 budget request from Mark Green]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minding my own personal business while nature peacefully stimulates my thoughts process. Featuring mainly.styles… https://t.co/DNSrbPpHcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson And don’t forget that @VP @mike_pence was also in charge of the transition team that appointed… https://t.co/6EKaR2m34R]]></document><document><![CDATA[SENIOR NIGHT for @MMU_BIH when they host Brattleboro tonight ...   FREE admission to any MMU HS student!!! https://t.co/ZxaryqOXN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MizzHogan Personally, I think you’re looking more like your mom each day and that is by NO means an insult from my end. Looking great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #Lent2019 I will be giving up snooze and multiple alarms. I will set one alarm and get up instead of setting an… https://t.co/Y0OHJ3NGWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLysowski @TBNSports When is there pressure to win? We're burning through years of Eichel's prime. How many 1st, 2… https://t.co/81WnY51rjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesilberman “Zionism...makes war against the saints”? What? I thought it was the referees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN So it’s hate if it doesn’t fit your ideology .... ???? Sounds familiar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcharlesworth7 Get that a lot.... lol... I just tell ppl that  yes!!! This is America... wanna speak English....   go to England ...  lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Machado singing with the Padres and Sanders announcing 2020 Presidentail run....2 bad decisions in one day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSports @NBCSportsGold @PGATOURLIVE @PGATOUR it’s about refund time. NBC Taking over has been a DISASTER. After… https://t.co/RDilMdZaoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening again. Honestly shut the F up Jerry Kill. I still remember when your “guys” stood up for Tracy Claeys aft… https://t.co/Jek0mky9d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know how our leaders see how our dear nation is falling and be scrambling to milk us to the last... Why do… https://t.co/hjQqoyjgEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In room steamer, brilliant move @NoelleNashville should be a must for every hotel! Ditch the iron, have steamers. https://t.co/5m75oluEbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[pops, it's been 9 months. 3/4 of a year... I miss you more and more each day. I know you're watching over me in thi… https://t.co/2nTurxUnfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelandLia if you’re still in the U.S. this afternoon and you have some “telly” time, you might want to tune in to… https://t.co/ZpFOcVbVTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you like alternative music, this is the best playlist 💪 go hit it up https://t.co/NCjymnZPHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a ghost in your room and it wants to be active leveling up on the creepy factor ...also it’s only a l… https://t.co/GN1Jkh48VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw @captainmarvel - so good, so timely, and everyone stayed for after the credits. Great job @brielarson, @Marvel and @WaltDisneyCo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's it, in a nut shell! End of society in a month. @realDonaldTrump @DavidJHarrisJr https://t.co/Xd3uT8CKiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snewbery1 Our friends from @UofTFamilyMed have been working on a #generalism framework that can be used in #MedEd… https://t.co/5eX5g1HHWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jakov_10 @TomNovelly @TMobile @Delta @JohnLegere Blackout restrictions like crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa @tanyaeiserer I am from Houston, I know the town well, it's on Lake Livingston about 50 miles north of Housto… https://t.co/f2brQpWFcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when this happened &amp; @aplusk got a whole bunch of cell phone numbers for his texting list? 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ball State’s K.J. Walton giving WMU’s D.J. Houston a “hell no” from the bench after both missed free throw attempts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six Straight for Coach Organ’s girls! What a dynasty this man has created. #WarriorPride @AP_Athletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed Johnson steps aside as head coach of Newberry boys hoops to prepare for his next job— head coach of Newberry foo… https://t.co/uxuZ11ysGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Frazier's on their #New #Nissan #Versa! You guys were awesome to work with. Thank you for your busi… https://t.co/oYScMU5dbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon from US District Court in DC. Roger Stone is expected here shortly, as he has been ordered to explai… https://t.co/6fA0ozQ62Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covington Catholic Teen Nick Sandmann Sues 'Washington Post' For $250 Million https://t.co/1rnAC5EvvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffHaseley @MyFantasyLeague @DynastyTradesHQ The whole convo about Davis now is pretty fascinating to me. It’s li… https://t.co/4xWjXblWNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aggie_hood @HERC_N_AG At least  Texas scored,  held them under 70 aggy couldn’t even do that in 7 OverTimes agains… https://t.co/NkfDB4TeoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like the look of @Qwilr but I really do not understand how it works with regards to clients/prospects, con… https://t.co/vbDUQBOiWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Josh Hansan I guess now that is Jerry Hansan Boy around here in Jay okla I guess now Josh Hansan works for thi… https://t.co/UAwDEFekep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APsilos @istockhistory I did read that part—and fully comprehended it—thank you, but the evidence still requires i… https://t.co/6w6pd5zX4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rVyJimenez I haven’t even started yet. I should be kicked out of the tequila gang 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[9/10 your gut feeling proves you right but this time i hope it proves me wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump 🛑THE TRUE AMERICAN REPUBLICANS NEED2 CLEAN HOUSE.AND VOTE ALL THESES FAKENEWSTRUMP PUPPETS OU… https://t.co/4zEsNJgJk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we don’t retain @TreyDeuce32RTR I’ll be so pissed. I hear that BS rumor him for Odell. Hell no. Trade a first. N… https://t.co/Yq4wMLjtU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump My father died flying a B-57 over Laos during the Vietnam War while you were dodging the draft wit… https://t.co/Oqv1QAIIcF]]></document></documents></author>