<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Nothing like your final clinical cancelling on you 2 weeks before you were supposed to move back 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Renouf gets in on the action and doubles the lead! https://t.co/qoATy2GNmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruth1_8 @mbe_fans Did u leave dool ? If so that’s it I’m finish with the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicPendragon Omg you’re dog is so goregous and so is the movie and game library you got going 😂👌🏽👌🏽👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[My blessings here. Technology has been compromised I believe. Someone wants to shut down USA. No planes, no phones,… https://t.co/vsf6NchUaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right @PopTV how did 'Clique' work out for the network?  If you're ready to crack on to the next millennial across… https://t.co/Hww1lm2RUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nobody_stop_me omg just remembered you were in my dream a few nights ago and i told you i always believed in you a… https://t.co/h8Upuejtm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty much...#gottasparkle #saylavie #maudegrahamjewelry @ Plainview, New York https://t.co/JXPw36QltV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @THSGirlsHoops Seniors!  #Classof2019 ❤ #THSProud https://t.co/TPlWgF7IMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sequencer16 @iwillhavemyday @hispano_Mex @Cjamesb4u @Enkumal @White7Mr @Tombstone1954 @iam_trump @IsabellaDAngel7… https://t.co/4SS5HNRGGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be alone I do not want anything w/ anybody - I don’t wanna talk to anybody either lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AgustinaAcost1 Necesito uno de estos bb @iblv_s2_ https://t.co/CiiqgZCY6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journey in composting manure began after @BrekerJoe noticed different plants growing after applications of raw manu… https://t.co/F9d9RbPX4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @nycjim @JonLemire @jeffmason1 Who is surprised? How is a Press pool created? Who determines members… https://t.co/XeeXeoaYwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s what I call my cup of coffee LOL!!   @Zak_Bagans This is actually pretty neat! 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey en Grey's Anatomy simplemente nadie puede ser feliz más de 5 capítulos 🙄😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course why am I not surprised? 45 can’t answer anything truthful. He lives in his own delusional world 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AynW @rudekaty @abbyferri Our guests are crazy about our dog Keely Smith. She gets rave reviews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TasteOfCountry Kip Moore @KipMooreMusic... All three... Every show is a different experience.. He is the greatest.… https://t.co/HCRB27qsjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJeffHoliday Both my brother and I have autism. The fact that they’re using this disorder as a scare tactic is… https://t.co/KXlJn9WSk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedjspecs I can’t 😭 the big hydroflasks don’t fit in my cup holder in my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was LIT, as the kids say.🔥 #sarahsrealtravels #californiacaptures #californiavibes #napavalley #wino… https://t.co/jhNQVMlIYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t matter how cold it is, I’m still ordering my iced caramel macchiato 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You are not a drop in the ocean.  You are the entire ocean in one drop.” ~ Rumi⁣ ⁣ .  .  .⁣ ⁣ #rumi… https://t.co/Svmrg9xGnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing from grief: Cleveland family raises money for CuddleCot, a device to help families with stillbirth #grief… https://t.co/lSY2TupK46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latin representation w/o typical negative stereotypes matters now more than ever! Even if you’re not Latin, give it… https://t.co/sBZ4QBgulv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@og_pdub @cinyarita Ehh yeh but the line for obese men should be at a minimum bc of this. All of y’all need to be gladiators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just made my first donation of $27. Still feeling the Bern!!!! #Bernie2020 #FeelTheBern]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @RspctNoRspct I’m sorry but that’s a dumbass thing to say]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been surrounded by girls like I should and i kinda wish I had some in my life but ya just like to turn fake on each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manegogh @dramallama32 @pewdiepie Bro someone named E Series has 20x more points than us 😭 but we’re working on it don’t worry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason I love my husband #469573: he is so dedicated to making our house a beautiful home and doesn't rest until a… https://t.co/bnNsnf4fKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 and there’s a tv show where the lead actresses and an actress in a fat suit are at a diner and the fat wo… https://t.co/M70f9b8bfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jen Johns crossed 15K. Time 02:26:17, pace 15:16 min/mile, est. finish 9:33 am https://t.co/DRbA2COumi #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyeeSTUD She’s dumb as hell. It’s her own fault for letting that shit add up like that. No one to blame but her la… https://t.co/tb0dpbJrkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyMartinCo3 @RuanAntunes7 @Lynette_50 @KingsPlayszz @pizzalover4189 @mfourie64 @dm_stp @CJG_Pokemon… https://t.co/K8gkyKs1T9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to leave PA to get back to North Carolina on Wednesday morning, but they’re calling for 5-8 inches of snow a… https://t.co/sihGwB9JkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEY!! HEY YOU!! Party people!! Nostalgic children of the 90’s!! MY MOVIE THAT I AM ABOUT TO START FUNDING FOR VERY… https://t.co/BoyusLaOv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking new meds sucks, you can’t prepare yourself for the nausea/vertigo/dizziness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even Saturday Brunch is a playground for outlaws!  Note the details @galaxygaby_art included. I bet Susan serves th… https://t.co/cYfukwYtU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onepeloton Andy speer’s HRZ endurance run from 2/27 that is supposed to be 30 mins cuts off at 15 mins and the dig… https://t.co/jrLINqZVyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So confused about life lately that I wake up multiple times a night not knowing what is a dream and what is reality… https://t.co/lnjHXK8SPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even on no relationship type shit all I’ve ever wanted was someone to fight for me aka my parents and raise me… https://t.co/YT573gWkgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 I can't "like" it, it breaks my heart! And,that asshole trump thinks it's ok!]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 days till I head to Denver for @BacklotProject @johncusack Grosse Point Blank and still hoping to upgrade to a VI… https://t.co/SegndZzhGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love a surprise but not in this category. Give it to #GlennClose. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSIPstudio @GrandGuilds Thank you so much! I'm really excited about this! 😄😁😄😁😄😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @ReneeCarrollAZ @BreitbartNews Then there's the Clintons. Bill, they seem to have dodged that residence. 👮‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A story I can relate to. I am thankful for my support group. Within 10 months, I lost both parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please spread the word. Pressure on politicians is the ONLY way for success in San Francisco.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union Cemetery . . . #photography #photographyart #photographystyle #photographylover #photographyislife… https://t.co/QM0ACjsVky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hope anthony text back I was hella looking forward to this shoot😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the guy who tipped me $15 when the overall bill was $20- I appreciate you more than you know. It’s people like y… https://t.co/a05hDp84b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don't watch the new season of #GameOfThrones then #JonSnow will always remain alive. https://t.co/H1zaY3voSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much googling today. On the bright side, figured out night sweats are being caused by #tramadol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordans plan makes no sense.She is telling Franco2 plead guilty2 themurders2draw out the killer cuz the killer will… https://t.co/fCRUoVeuTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL People keep shooting mass amounts of people with AKs and nobody wants to pass gun reform either. GTFOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep seeing pics of sam and colby and all i wanna do is break down and CRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support local businesses!!  #mermaidhair #mermaidhairdontcare #supportyourfriends #supportlocalartists… https://t.co/kSkzOBeILh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_vinograd @SecPompeo @jaketapper @CNN @POTUS How strange this world 🌎 really is they have swallowed back their… https://t.co/vgfxGWhjhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinnyGinny_1 @jrent777_james In modern times many Jewish families work hard to raise successful children who becom… https://t.co/dwty1zIC9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foie Gras is unethical and disgusting and if you fuck with that shit then I DON’T fuck with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ALASEDU for being such a great host! I’m leaving this weekend’s ALAS State Affiliates Conference feeling… https://t.co/WZZUkJKzDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you would come with me. 🤝 Photographer: saturn_addy Me at Anime Los Angeles, as Sebastian from Black Butler. 🖤 B… https://t.co/1qdLCw3qPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh 🤷🏻‍♀️He already gave them everything they wanted on their first Red Carpet Rendezvous...❓❓❓ Now what, 🙄mo… https://t.co/WalgK3N4JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neither of us are happy but neither of us wants to leave so we keep breaking one another and calling it love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[During the day Alice won’t get off my lap unless I force her but at night she like refuses to lay with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw I like you and respect your opinion a lot.  But if most Jewish people did not agree with Netanyahu,  he… https://t.co/Cw2N3iyfKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoraWil31925690 @B52Malmet @StrangeBird19 His self hate is affecting ALL of us. Like those mass shooters who kill… https://t.co/YTNBJ0W5EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JensenAckles @DanneelHarris BEAUTIFUL pic!  Makes me a little sad though.  It's like a djinn episode-a peek at wha… https://t.co/noFwsR0JUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nada peor de enterarte de lo que hiciste el finde por medios de vídeos y no acordarte 😂😂😂 #tragametierra y ni me im… https://t.co/mB0EdB3uKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEBrown003 @1776Stonewall Women rights not female baby rights because the true idol is self.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEWSTALK1010 I think it would be amazing to have @Songbird_7_ on again to spread awareness about this amazing even… https://t.co/FMXdAjCXXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa! That is impressive! Someone tell me this made @ESPNSportsCentr .. it did right? @danielleeee41 fun fun here Y… https://t.co/X2hnQVCuJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗LOVE ❤️ Happy Valentine’s Day, lovers. I got to start this divine day at THE mother church with my singin’ sister… https://t.co/0cONTbo5eW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Berns I was going to say, you can’t even send a strongly worded email at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about how mad my mom is going to be when she comes home from vacation and sees a new 250 in the garage 😬😬… https://t.co/JytxWeW7dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[... WAIT so you mean to tell me that it’s not a PRNDL cause I really didn’t know what else to call it 😭 https://t.co/CPPsEc40I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMO its one of those “it” factors , you either have “it” or you don’t.  Unfortunalty, playing with heart does not g… https://t.co/31bCbhN7uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcipolla0224 @jeffpearlman ... Zion Williamson, as he’s know outside of auto-correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bts_bighit @flame_deluge @KayluvJB @lambouh Ah, c’est celui de juste Seoul. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @justincwiekk !!! Hope you have the best day!! Thanks for making Physics class last year somewhat enjoyable!!! 💕🎉🎉🎉🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[My inner goth girl just wants to stay home and listen to Peter Murphy’s ‘Cuts You Up’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m rewatching Rebelde and I didn’t realize how bad this show was recorded. I can see the microphones on some sets… https://t.co/emecYr2XQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RoadToMiami2k19 is here! Events all Miami Spring Break 🛬 ALL MARCH! All the parties located on the South Beach str… https://t.co/XqFGKm9tNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day! #newyork #nyc #manhattan #art #love #loveislove @ IAC Building https://t.co/X2mRBg0Cr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanEibe @nick_ford13 @MLBONFOX I love the  Astros , but the Brewers is  probably one of the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[among doctors, cultural competence trainings viewed as bureaucratic training and were disconnected from how race af… https://t.co/R1Wr5fy0LL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @Z100NewYork @1027KIISFM @BTS_twt @tacobell @BTS_twt  #BestFanArmy  @Z100NewYork @1027KIISFM  #iHeartAwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kid and I trek from Palomino Valley to Robb Dr for Church. Talk about completely different weather conditions.… https://t.co/BF2aZIaf9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gehrig38 It looks more and more as if some people think that black lives are the ONLY ONES that matter. This really sickens me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have marked @amyklobuchar off my list. Her answers about #MedicareForAll were not acceptable to this trans woman… https://t.co/gneydI93zO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got a new Knights player! Super excited to see him on the 1st Line! We needed a player like him to make a deep p… https://t.co/0HJmg9j5QF]]></document><document><![CDATA[No longer listen to any judge nap interviews, always some big Trump IF, IF done it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom took me to the groomers and look at how I came home! Am I still a dog?   @SuperGrobanite @blueeyes_Marta… https://t.co/tX7NMCc8KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[WEISSELBERG.....AS GUILTY AS COHEN!  Why is he teflon??? I don't care HOW OLD HE IS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting at a restaurant with my mother and she said, “Okay Talia go to the restroom.” I said I’m okay mom she reall… https://t.co/8BERCjzkAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wanna day something ima be quiet tho ... soft ass nigga go get some money all that hatred got you dying slow 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braindud92 @MissusMelnee Yeah, I got it sorted. Redid it with the mixer on high and drizzled the oil down the side… https://t.co/13EsykCaNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump @VP #MikePence is trying to show he's capable for when they impeach Trump. I just hope they g… https://t.co/aYcLbYyOqs]]></document></documents></author>