<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Random neighborhood cafe in Philadelphia. Guy next to me takes out book. It’s the new @SohrabAhmari book!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagotribune Good actor , great singer , horrible person . It’s this kinda stuff that promotes racism , homeopat… https://t.co/gD7qd1EGBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts: There will always be someone who runs faster, lifts more, and does better than me. No matter what, I'll neve… https://t.co/R7xzpjJh52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious question since we already have one in the oval office. A person who claims his Bible is his favorite book y… https://t.co/sNRw16Dmg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[OU basketball will have a natty before that Bryce Harper contract runs out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see Lil kids getting that ass popped in public still... parents to scared nowadays 🤦🏾‍♂️ that ain't beating… https://t.co/G6EiUX3Dy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Montenegro's "Heaven" might be a dated 80s-sounding bop, but DAMN D-Mol's facial expression and emotive movements have me VIBIN with them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenScionti @politicsluo @SenhorRaposa Ron Kind wouldn’t do it; he was too afraid to run for Gov in a much better e… https://t.co/V103VZNt1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayudaizzi Cumplan ls cosas, y mejoren su calidad de servicio una verdadera pena, espero con ancias enero del 2020… https://t.co/e75tYL7LGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woe unto them that call evil good and good evil that put darkness for light and light for darkness that put bitter… https://t.co/MGjLZg1eVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have underestimated @AldiUSA’s reusable bags for too long. I recently bought two hot/cold bags and about five nor… https://t.co/k7ogN0T9t1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you actually see your hard work start to pay off is a beautiful feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnionAbuelosTra Veremos dentro de un par de años cómo está funcionando esa corporación sacada de la manga de… https://t.co/gxqLAgc3KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amateur pool player @chrisgrohusko makes one lucky pro shot . . . #billiards #pool #trickshot #poolislife #poolhall… https://t.co/Fbys9LIlbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi primer regalo de mi amorsh @lanhaz en Las Puentes en San Nicolás https://t.co/Q69yO88wLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big guy went through Lawson’s toys and came out with the ⚾️ ! Not sure what to do with it yet but he grabbed it… https://t.co/1tXNYn8CVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling up to PA to see my guy @MorganCWallen tomorrow evening and I don’t think I have ever been so hype. Hands down my favorite artist 🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_aprilgloria @Saberforge @Saberforge makes fantastic stuff and that blade looks amazing!  Hopefully I’ll see you at SWCC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met up with  great friends for dinner in LA Sara thesupercolliesmom        John @devinemag                        A… https://t.co/d4FRWAsq6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is #nationalpetday with the #islandofmisfittoys.   #treatsplzkthx treatsplzkthx #thebumble #riley #daisy… https://t.co/Wsu671IvgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sexual revolution continues it's scorched-earth policy against those who will not bow to their godless worldvie… https://t.co/sip37yjwGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't go on dates to start a relationship or find the one. dates are just fun. I like eating fancy food and walki… https://t.co/QU0o5l78ZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentBozell @newsbusters The media is a product of professional indoctrination centers aka colleges and universiti… https://t.co/XkoNkfPRqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbolanbass   Been a fan a long time and still am. Follow me back please 🤘🏻🤘🏻☠️☠️🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será Bueno El Significado De Esa Carta Del #Tarot Pos No Te Pierdas De La Sección Mas Esperada Por Los #MhoniFans 📺… https://t.co/hS9pOatpHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 jussie is no jackie robinson you ass clown. Stop smoking that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once a Communist always a Communist. Not complicate.   Nancy’s out, move over Bernie there is a new BOSS in town!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNnewsroom @CNN @jimsciutto @SenatorDurbin For cnn's dumb assed media, it is possible that dick durbin has sh.t for brains.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian_level Yo- did I see you have thst on dvd? Might I borrow, if so?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twp459 @Katiedidornot @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @POTUS He lied to Congress. Isn’t that illegal?  Didn’t Cohen get charged for that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noooo #SNOW ❄️ Yes here in #LasVegas ... Maybe I’m just having some kind of TV 📺 #weatherman flashback? How can thi… https://t.co/hYRATVJVR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[29 is here and feeling goooood!!! 😊☺️😊☺️😊☺️😊 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/2ewvlYNuzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speakingabtpain @StefanKertesz @PainPtFightBack Could using a rhetorical question in the title of your piece be th… https://t.co/VCAqzC57Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why the definition is so important. “Extra” could mean just about anything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyHeyItsConrad so when does the Marty Lunde podcast start?  I ask cause I don't want @mattkoonmusic to get the jump on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por eso es que digo, que todos los chavistas son unos pedazos de mierda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not too far off from #valentinesday i'll just leave off the wine part 😁 #craftbeer #drinklocal #beer @ Lucky's Mark… https://t.co/PSYvtM9A8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[And there's fire on the mountain, lightnin' in the air https://t.co/PutNcEkVnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the nitwits on the Left are confronted by MS-13 gangs, we should ignore their screams for help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so ready for a match against @chuckcomeau ;-) @ Greater Montreal https://t.co/AyYpVb2Fcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking in memphis • 📸: @aus10russell @ Beale Street https://t.co/fpwX618SHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I think about it the more it bothers me that they changeed Mar-Vel and did away with his death from cancer… https://t.co/TaTBlDbTC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious phenomenon re funeral directors - there are no support groups because it’s all about the client which takes… https://t.co/OuNg65hJDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Вид из окна в кои-то веки меня радует. @ Palm Springs, California https://t.co/eFa3n0IvFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baby5donquixote I don’t think he’ll do a heel turn. Maybe anti-authority like Becky Lynch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are CBD pre-rolls the new alternative to tobacco? https://t.co/KPI9GTyyA5 #cbd #wellness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mobusueyside @mamiidev Ain’t gon lie chief you gon have to break this one down for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think @AustinMillerKDE about the Eagles possibly getting Brown?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many thanks to the rather limited Jeff Zucker for his accidental admission today that, while Mr. Obama was in offic… https://t.co/8T3OfXMslg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RolfSolber45 @DonaldJTrumpJr False! But thanks for playing.  Hate crimes have been on the rise for the past three… https://t.co/2XD3xfc44U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beg1Girl @POTUS @GenFlynn @w_terrence @BPPope @davidbcrumbs @RoseDC11 @PowerTaking @Dawn_DeMore1 @busylizzie48… https://t.co/RystyrP3vM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@captdvlong @HoppyKercheval WV teachers are so UNDER paid you could "throw" 20 percent at them and it wouldn't solv… https://t.co/W8n5nZNpwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Hope You Dance By Lee An Womack  I hope you never lose your sense of wonder You get your fill to eat but always… https://t.co/JCmkZgWtYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is a GOOD husband, and he would never. But literally all of his friends are this way and it makes me nau… https://t.co/lP9eMROZ7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToonamiNews Wait, so are you guys actually saying that she already found Kazuto?🤔  SPOILERS😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FS1 What is the title of the show we are watching during this weather delay? I’ve never seen it before and would l… https://t.co/UALSnFpBit]]></document><document><![CDATA[— Family —  Launch team after party, vibes.  #PerryElizabeth  #ShepherdWest #pearandshep https://t.co/j8oAyZMkYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anannabananacan Once in high school I had to climb through a window and the neighbors called the cops. It was so thrilling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going out on a limb here,... anyone else thinking @EricDuechle of @usmlr @Seawolves_Rugby has earned a look to… https://t.co/xN8NwRzzOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at CVS Health? We're hiring in #Kissimmee, FL! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and m… https://t.co/Ufi0M8raKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryasarous Born right in front of God and everybody! But what do you like?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before and after. Big thanks to neighbor Zack and his daughter for helping me yesterday. This is mostly invasive bu… https://t.co/XiJMOSgs5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else got the limited edition inaugural @aafAPOLLOS jersey? #TakeAim🏹 @TheAAF LETS GOOOO https://t.co/RruPhjo47W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBenassi @joerogan As for his business venture. I have no idea what that’s about. I do know he has a team. Le… https://t.co/Vb3QF2H3vZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re ever just laying in bed looking straight up at the ceiling and you see spiders up there but you’re like who… https://t.co/PJdUDzeNGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoreHorror @savagedirector @Unearthedfilms Give it a vote and review either way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed the #CASEVII opening keynote from @jackiehuba on brand loyalty and prioritizing your communication w… https://t.co/NBjnBGmnqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirstenelise17 Have rules in place for being in rooms and lights out at night. If players have family’s visiting h… https://t.co/zJBGKGFHab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the votes its official gonna order a @MarcoGonzales_ spring training jersey soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJD107_ The debates are going to need a B stage like the Republicans in 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1MonsterMission @cauzin_trouble @HuntressMonster @Lizardkingfish @BamaOutdoors @BassTamer @pondpredator @panekbill… https://t.co/PYuzlrF8R0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump plans to allocate $8 billion to fund border wall, source says  https://t.co/nDebCpzojP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day another dollar back helpping the nasa boys out lol Sneaked in a few places I shouldn't be!!! Only here… https://t.co/n58uJwWt6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awade_13 @ChristayyyR I know I’m late but let me guess, you were referring to Pixar’s Oscar winning Bao?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/DL9oUYNVKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfrodriguez_ @mitchieforshort @hnnhjey I don't agree with everything he says, but I think he provides a really val… https://t.co/lKbebYX9B2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swear I’m not letting you in and going your speed to keep you from merging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was younger I used to love watching "Rugrats" but now when I watch it's creepy as fuck! https://t.co/THjHWVFs9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PulsatingShadow @ValveNewsNetwor i figure his suffering is just suffering and that by venting about it it can be a… https://t.co/DxidTUdKpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliaxogden So essentially you don’t like having a car for a cheap price]]></document><document><![CDATA[They didn’t keep up with the trends or the cuts. Why y’all still selling loose fitting jeans?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending a tour is always bittersweet, but this one was definitely one for the books. Thank you @DPageDialogues,… https://t.co/OtgJMMNVtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdardy @AiWorshiper @HarMath @johnjoy1966 I agree Jim! Now throw this out to your groups after discussing the oth… https://t.co/RIjgEfR21T]]></document><document><![CDATA[- Wee quiero unos tacos pero ya no traigo lana - No te apures orita lo arreglamos  👀 https://t.co/jtCXK218el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@papi4481 @ShawnBlymiller @realsaltlake @KSL5TV @YouTubeTV I agree we are lucky. I do know about the antenna. I gue… https://t.co/NC5ccDonNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmboccuzzi @GavinNewsom I will pay for your one way ticket out of our great state please get packed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night's #lostinlakeland adventures were sponsored by the cool and calm Southern Gentlemen of Smart Water Irrig… https://t.co/NXi8pWbnmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you 🙏 @KarlLagerfeld @CHANEL @gq #fashion #style #KarlLagerfeld #icon https://t.co/MwFh6XFI6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scroll down for @lukestein 🐚 pun paper titles. Luke and @arpitrage should offer a paper title consulting service]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ZotzCityKid Real Madrid even getting the benefit after Ronaldo is gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggioMatt @EMULSIVEfilm This is being a bit specific, but I see those more as choices, rather than controls. Film… https://t.co/1QCFq13wSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huryazarlar Eminim seçkin gazetecilerimiz çok gûzel sorular soracaklardir.😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @CBSThisMorning @GayleKing I don't like what I'm reading, the words suicide packs,when I think Azriel, R something is wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieS17641641 @lifewithshar I promise you'll be running from my tongue...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatdragmeatball Omfg I was playing HW Words today and the answer was “Cosmo and Wanda” and I was like WTF is that?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity for me today. Too true!!!  Don't text and drive!! #mirth #giggle #smirk #clever https://t.co/mS415HC1DJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnimpressedTX @BBackerman1 @brendap1949 @TxsleuthUSA @Yakekoge @FactCheckU @DaniScotchIrish @MrsPerrin @DaddyJim52… https://t.co/covvml7Rj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wire sculpture lessons still available at the Centerstage online auction. Valued at $500. Good for 24 hours of less… https://t.co/3DdmUwQKtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to one of my favorite races of the year #SpartanGreekPeak and having some fun in the snow! . . Who… https://t.co/qj3YW7hGFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random person at Food Lion: “Who do you want to win tonight?” Me: “State”]]></document></documents></author>