<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Bethel 19 Job's Daughters held a beautiful meeting tonight, honored their founder, Ethel T. Wead Mick, and presente… https://t.co/lyecOxLIvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #ByeNicki on @TheTylt—NIcki Minaj is corny https://t.co/6hRHkymIHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha see you recognize my freaking problem with insomnia you're on to me now he he he]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma get another shirt dress like this one 😁🤔🤣💥😉🥰😘🍾💛 #youngmelly #clubdeep #cinproductions #nyc @ Chinatown, Manhat… https://t.co/U692GJVSME]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @andreasavage so much!!! This scene was everything and then this deleted version just took #imsorrytv to ano… https://t.co/rd5H92QZUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep away sweet boy!  I missed the party, been doing that all my life. I too hope Luis and all have a restful sabb… https://t.co/q9fmCYHOod]]></document><document><![CDATA[You all know what this is? This is my favorite guilty pleasure in the whole world...okay maybe not the whole world,… https://t.co/jrwLKxYzXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Did you have a stroke? An emotional breakdown? This is strange behavior from someone who used to be a conservative. Get help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 SexDiscrimination Violence Against Women Pay Inequality Creating a more even playing field  Price Inequality (o… https://t.co/k49wQo0bZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houston_trill98 If this isn’t the most relatable shit I’ve ever seen😒🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessieann8213 I'm reading this now and I care . I'm not having a bad time myself right now also . ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my other dumb ass cat got outside while I was searching for her so I chased an all black cat through the yard in pitch black darkness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LANCEARMPONG @DianaKraft7 @IvanTumaJr @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump There are laws regarding mentally ill and… https://t.co/2HdVzw6Ca5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @PressSec @StephenMillerAL @JaySekulow @PatToomey @DineshDSouza @GregGutfeldShow… https://t.co/KeNgtX7kES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turfdom @NematodeGuy @BruceMrtn Majority of these are grower samples, some for upcoming research trials. I try to… https://t.co/l9uAegnx6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenealogyJude @DebbieKennett @ancestrydna I just wish I knew how to figure it out.  The main ones, I knew before d… https://t.co/bryeFACWGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need nominations! I know there are amazing women working on your campus and in your organization - please nomina… https://t.co/iaQx3Piab0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocarr4 @BendNsnap31 Agreed. There was literally only one song from Collection 1 that I didn’t download]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant Surprise to be included in NYC HISTORY on Kiosks thru-out NYC! A friend of mine was on his way to work and… https://t.co/CDK7rJKCKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a talkative nigga like damn you just can’t keep nothing to yo self ?? Huh 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly can’t like this possibly any more!  Especially on #InternationalWomenDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punched93 @Gpig666 @AxelAbysse Oh how I miss being able to fist myself. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio You are insane and despised by your efforts to uproot the constitutional truths of our forefathers effo… https://t.co/0aoxqOCZkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[(ugh witness..he keeps calling everyone involved scum and then drops completely irrelevant info like “Once [his emp… https://t.co/ak7yZVi1TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night live, we will parade tomorrow! @ Sector6 Extreme Air Sports https://t.co/AJY3Ve1C1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @jessicacline23 (get_repost) ・・・ @ Warren, Ohio https://t.co/pgBXgYbF9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not think $CNHC is done. Still up hundreds percent and still a custodian play. Chiang is working on something]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 degrees with a real feel of -1 ..... idc wtf i look like i care about being warm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know a good handful that do love us and we’re grateful for them. But yes, this can be true, especially with local… https://t.co/MGtxXOEIoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oregon Truckers Association has been the lynchpin of deisel legislation from the 2011 horrible idling bill and… https://t.co/LdiR0UHdzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTB @DonnieWahlberg @joeymcintyre @dannywood @JonathanRKnight @jordanknight what was fav it was all way cool!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EbelingArtPhoto @WestBend @VisitWCCVB @EarthandClouds @StormHour @ThePhotoHour @PicPoet @LindseySlaterTV @jritka… https://t.co/KnAiY78toP]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry for the little rant (i guess what it’s called?) but i just love ashton and he’s so fucking talented 🥺 @Ashton5SOS @5SOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple's Radical New iPhone Suddenly Takes Shape  https://t.co/UTtUpCS62k]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite east coast destination: amazing island on #atlanticocean #monhegan #monheganisland #maine… https://t.co/9NmDcLOyzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Merve_TWD @Me_Cennet @smoking_reedus @HeyMo517 @AntoniaSchmitt4 @leedusme1227 @Calisto82 @supportnormie… https://t.co/adAGgjFSGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Only a pathological narcissist would pin a tweet of himself being introduced and entering the Hous… https://t.co/sYphzNP0qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be jealous cus i got a nigga that take me on trips and i dont gotta put a dime up towards it and you jus gett… https://t.co/QZ20yAgZzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @JonLevenhagen to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews – just… https://t.co/K4hmL2r6z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say that this is generally the case for all job applications. I also think you need to explain why you want… https://t.co/JcAnVj2cen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLBriscoe @Cbp8Cindy @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @suziday123 @thatsVeryKari @FionaMorgan79 @CaththeWineLady… https://t.co/1jPw2TLjPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveDivjak He was good for a short time then was sometimes hard to watch. Nice person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenaiswriting @drewtarver @OSTtalk Crown Candy in Macon has great peppermint bark as well as other vintage sweets https://t.co/XwMtOVzklw]]></document><document><![CDATA[the on campus starbucks would rather burst into flames than me tell them they made my drink wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I deserve the last name West Coast? Well... it’s very close to my real last name and I’ve lived in all three states in the West.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conorsen @mattyglesias Tired of being disenfranchised by a bunch of racist hicks because I live in California. One person, one vote, baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stejam82 @TexasHumor I’m not sure we want them!! I got outta there as fast as I could! 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry guys I didn’t touch it. #LeafsForever https://t.co/s43JdZdGZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotOneLineFF @kae_ysh @Hade_Hdez_4 @gemdavis_ @L_Ithil @jenniclarephoto @C_licare @Absolover @Malirensch… https://t.co/UIuFRCLcBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[D-20 🙏🏼✈️   less than 3 weeks nalang and my wallet is not yet ready 😂 kailangan ko talaga ng full two weeks na work… https://t.co/YqUT3uhoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCVodkaFan I've never wanted to dick kick someone as much as I do him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nessa_effect And that is fine lol. I’m dying on this hill. Side chicks are evil ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[just watch it GOD IS DEAD AND WE KILLED HIM https://t.co/OfhoqAXQBn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louder for the folks in the back! “If you are a white person with black friends, and you aren’t getting critical fe… https://t.co/8qbbZg27fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerlingLagarde @sylvainreynard @SusieSteinle @JDT19 @PenningtonJoyce @Lorianneaton @solacemusings @Sam_Sooki… https://t.co/gzGs1P3yeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to do a social experiment where I wear my hair in a ponytail for five years like JoJo Siwa and see how much hair I lose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Careful Steven, your about to become the Lars Ullrich of the movie streaming world!  Can’t put the toothpaste back… https://t.co/xgG6jJPdXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/dBtfTKKSGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanawrites @WildpipM @The100writers @JRothenbergTV Hit the nail on the head with ALL of them, but especially these… https://t.co/fhtrnvleW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @DrDorindaCA! I’ve appreciated the education and guidance you’ve provided in Okemos and am gratefu… https://t.co/oZ2yyupO60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FUCKDEPRESSIO13 @TalindaB @mikeshinoda @AnnaShinoda That was so beautiful!! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fakest person I know right here. He judged me for sending food post WHILE I WAS ON PREP FOR MY SHOW... Now look at… https://t.co/s18rbiPlCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pregunto si la vida cada vez me irá poniendo más lejos de mi novio 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes Can I just say damn boy you look hot in glasses! Definitely a fan of the look]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk and you'll feel better. This is awesome! I can use it to make a gift or card for any occasion... https://t.co/0VfSB71eQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot even begin to describe my excitement level for tomorrow’s @MumfordAndSons concert. CAN. NOT. WAIT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pickingupthewheelchair #thegirls @ St. Clair Shores, Michigan https://t.co/IQlqJDE7PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I could be way off here, but could the lion be Rumer Willis? #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wear wigs but baby i’m not bald, i’m just lazy 😉 https://t.co/TVePdZTRAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lakemeadoverlook #playingtouristtoday #clamdoesvegas #getoutside #explorenevada #Jeep #stormclouds #naturesbeauty… https://t.co/Rd5nK16fhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our sweet baby boy is 2️⃣! From 😇👶🏻 to little man ⚽️⭐️ in the blink of an eye. https://t.co/DOnQrvVfQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I was so good in ochem last semester. I get a new professor and have no idea what’s going on and I’m about to cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[didn’t think Jake could get any more attractive but throw a baby goat in the mix and my heart is freaking overflowi… https://t.co/O3Cmqat8BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgshepherdvan You took the words right out of my mouth. Damn Detective Pikachu is going to make me give a crap about Pokèmon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YayDanielBarron @grantpa It’s not too bad on that front at all- pretty linear dungeons etc! I also play on easy mo… https://t.co/YGzeW44bfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear so many horror stories about lyft and Uber drivers that honestly whenever I have a male driver I get a littl… https://t.co/GMxHBVo49N]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you have done absolutely nothing to address the problem. Hypocrisy yet again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Fuck that wall, you're stealing basically from the govt that we pay taxes to n we don't want our money… https://t.co/tjCtJqGQI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prolepac @BernieSanders #MSNBC Funny, I asked the same question when I heard it last night. Are these ecomincally… https://t.co/FUUJJW9di4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Volzie @FLRightsRestore @desmondmeade @JessiChiappone @sheena_meade @XMccleary Love your mission!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you found your perfect Vintage Love yet??  Just scroll through the posts below to find it.   — ——————————————… https://t.co/7GxpEn7yXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next workshop is right around the corner! #backpain #back on track! See ya there 👍!! thenewtownyogacenter… https://t.co/6nGD8Sazs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sounds like something that @philshapiro could have written. Or maybe he has a Twitter alter ego. LOL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I try to buy tickets to @ellamai it’s already sold out 😭😭😭 I just wanna cry right now 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister is trying to connect my AirPods to her phone and this is what’s she’s saying... “AirPods connect” “earpho… https://t.co/m41V3mijhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National FFA Week to the Forney FFA Chapter/Officers. #FFAWeek #ForneyFFA #FFAJustOne #ForneyFamily https://t.co/jw59K4cdhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[BHS @ProStart are on deck &amp; ready to go! #GoLiberators https://t.co/2WAbPFUCla]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I said that #TSPRA19 is the place to be...I wasn't kidding!  Nobody wants to miss out on #CampCommunication!… https://t.co/Qz5d3eXnQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is midnight and this man @ivted_ really just made me get out of bed and do 100 squats. Can someone please come collect their boyfriend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I figured Pelosi would expose which sex trafficking routes she most wants to protect. Is there a comprehensive list… https://t.co/ExloHjeCNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHamilton262 @DLoesch Me too. I was wondering how I slipped through the cracks here... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[cause it’s BadBoy for life 💥🤑😈  . . . . #set #setlife #mua #makeup #makeupartist #badboy #hair #hairstylist… https://t.co/a4XcjP0XoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a difference between #diversity and #inclusion. And we need to be clear what it is and foster a culture of… https://t.co/TtObu1Aa7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how it starts I nearly lost my farm Taxation without Representation  In  USA 🇺🇸  First they come for your P… https://t.co/SIjkY0KcRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGkee @xOMGkee The original haunting of hill house movie. It scared me when I was a kid and it still creeps me out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHardstark @MyFavMurder Sweet serendipity! Next time you’re in the Detroit area, check out Lost and Found in Royal Oak. Clearly it’s magic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Should we list their names (social media handles), states, and office numbers so we can communicate our stance on bigotry?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Chilling in #PaloAlto #California😎 And What Do We Hear While Eating at #Walhburgers ??? #ForYou Then #Stiches 🙃… https://t.co/YRXlWMvA3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miamiulibraries @miamiuit @loriexlibris Library staff find your best chili recipe and join the fight!… https://t.co/3twIdoUARo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nillythesquid If Floribama wins, does this means there will be more seasons?]]></document></documents></author>