<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[*tweet blows up*   Them: “Listen to my soundcloud mixtape” “follow me on ig” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pike7464 Cool! What sorts of stuff will you be up to? Are they forcing you to move to Seattle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliant long form @JREpodcast with Jonathan Haidt that covers how micro aggression and colleges teaching to the m… https://t.co/dR8co8MLfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citylifejc @HowardSchultz Taken together with the other polling tho, very scary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna go fucking deaf trying to block out this bitch at work. We work in a fucking office. Why the fuck u yelli… https://t.co/Rpekq5TgT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ballmatthew Is it a safe assumption that most viewing is solo? My own viewing almost never is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewColler Kinda makes you realize why they didn’t talk about it in the first place 🤷🏼‍♂️. You get labeled as w… https://t.co/3lyBZSciTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying “paper money is going away” isn’t necessarily a bullish comment for crypto. News flash... most people genera… https://t.co/0SOpplMZPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to @ralphreid ! One of the good guys. https://t.co/Z4Vac6TUeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq And a few hats from your fav president https://t.co/SiXC8DXHw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliseIsWritinYA @irisvanooyen I have one out for a beta read too. I’m nervous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Dinner Special’ $12.95 at the newly re-opened 8 Immortals Chinese restaurant on Taravel street. https://t.co/HRhHzUJfR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @fox4 #Free4All tonight as @EdwardEgrosFox4 talks with @PaniniAmerica VP @sportsmktgguy about #lukadoncic… https://t.co/ipYxOzBzXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp poursuit Amber Heard et réclame 50 M$ https://t.co/EwSfc316cX https://t.co/h7LPbZxXXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transition... When everything around you is changing, embrace life and be true to yourself.  Come out of it better… https://t.co/RFRlNxbJ4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The greatest rapper of all time died on March 9th”. Rest In Peace to the Notorious B.I.G. #biggiesmalls… https://t.co/BNRoWEcefS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my favorite part of being an American. Love getting to vote!! #everyvotecounts @ Flagler Beach, Florida https://t.co/CBQFRQxJFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pointblaek @johndburger @adamjohnsonNYC How does not being smart enough to read various sources objectively before… https://t.co/HwQZ5AZTmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @steph93065 IF we had a real GOP behind our president. Now we have RINOS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abraham Lincoln knew about word thinking @ScottAdamsSays   https://t.co/5jjpe5P1Gl https://t.co/WC1pOThIAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giohio @Desmos @geogebra The slide rotation proof I did forty years ago, cutting all the pieces. It’s a fun proof.… https://t.co/HSb65KlMN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KorySouza @CartelBaggersFL #floridalife #makelifearide #liveyourlegend #cartelbaggers https://t.co/J42CMRRnxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 The absolute toughest issue I have with my partner over our daughter, now 16. Good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Do the house also, just a big redo. We need to get rid of the Democrat scum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton @ChrisCoon4 Lets all not forget a law written so many years ago called “Attorney client privilege “. On… https://t.co/lYe2OKBh3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally working out and dieting consistently, it’s been a long time since I’ve felt this good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaPOrdorica Va a decir que "ella tiene otras cifras" y que las que se publican son para "desprestigiarla". Ya vez… https://t.co/kYLuszHADL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk One of my San Marino (CA) High juniors is organizing a discussion on 4/4 (UBI in the US) and he is wonder… https://t.co/jdPDZ0otNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krazyfool4 I hope he breaks out offensively this season. He deserves it. Hard worker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[:: weekend seekers guide :: . . This weekend, shop Randolph Street Market for antiques and rare finds. Taste free s… https://t.co/polB7Hx4co]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y el máquina la cuelga en su insta. Respect 🙋🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/f9Q4Yrlr5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trill_sammy96 😂😂😂 the only call that I thought was wrong was the IT one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelheldevans F has no clue that under Caesar’s pic was Gk phrase “Son of God." “Give C his due” is ironic. F’s idols are due nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bus15237 I logged all my bus rides in a spreadsheet for 4 months, one cool stat I got was my average number of bus… https://t.co/wSh9TVbFsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PokemonGo anyone? @ New City Elementary School https://t.co/E0tOM0Nywc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quoi de plus gratifiant que regarder se magnifique paysage que la nature nous offre… https://t.co/MPAGhGKcKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDiPi @Rivian I thought you hated EVs? Please clarify your past statements or the @Tesla mafia is sure to come for you again 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Yaaaoooo " nobody's in charge of your life; so if you don't make time that's for you to decide.. Life goes fast; g… https://t.co/KNjWEFgVjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a call from “Vanessa from the Help Center.” She sounds an awful lot like “Elizabeth from the Resort Rewards Program.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[German Police Admit North African Migrants More Prone To Criminality!   That they rumbled this is a stunning upheav… https://t.co/EM4X4UfyRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What trail runner doesn't get overly excited upon discovering new trails when they are out exploring?  Found this a… https://t.co/nvsL0hX4RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music is the shorthand of emotion.” ― Leo Tolstoy.  #allanjackson #vanandelarena #concert @ Van Andel Arena https://t.co/oqgL1HYkYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the story of a new name → book two of the Neapolitan Novels.  even better than the debut.  every character a bruise… https://t.co/bj8R0jtiX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rand with all the blocks our President is dealing with?  What do you expect, the mans trying to do his job🇺🇸💯🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musicloverchick I could also see a place for 0.x. The beta test years would include Trey and Tom writing silly son… https://t.co/xxNiT42TMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Long Beach Convention and Entertainment Center https://t.co/QH9kVHICIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want @tylercowen to explain the economics of South by Southwest to us all because I am baffled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow I want Cohen to reply to these GOP Congresspersons, “You all liked me a whole lot better when I was your Finance Chair!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a amateur photography nerd, a real thrill to have Mark Seliger talk shop on this week’s @TexasMonthly National P… https://t.co/XoR6RF49fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just taking some colorful pictures with Yulia Logacheva julloganova in Miami.  / #model #photomodel #colaboration… https://t.co/uq3gDuC6Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/F6G7bZDSY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyndsay_CTV @MurphTWN #ShareYourWeather #StormHour @ExploreWR @sunset_wx @WeatherNation @KWAwesome @ThePhotoHour… https://t.co/ZLG3RS5Nzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pakman888 @SCSU_hockey_pbp @deanthibodeau @billyjoel I don’t care for that song Dean, but that’s the beauty of Bil… https://t.co/nfJrH7vRkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smile, You’re Incredible! #tagafriend #tuesday #jaycardiello #smile #happiness #jaycardielloquotes #fitspo #mindset… https://t.co/9pKfFIomyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time this girl from my high school admitted that her and her friend would photoshop their faces on other people… https://t.co/vpNp3K5Uks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep pushing toward your goals. Do not stop when things get hard. Hard work pays off and you will be rewarded for y… https://t.co/ccRdUbhivT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aidan Hickey with 2 FT's and Yarmouth has gotten as close as it's been in a while. Maranacook 39 Yarmouth 35 5:56 4th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamiSamaPlays @Niko_R6S @D3ltaforcee Too bad even the mantis couldn't help him aim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IlhanMN Oh really little pence! What about trump!! Remember these! You need to shut the fuck up or resign litt… https://t.co/RkKpXJo5Ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeignerMusic I work for a charter bus company in OKC specializing in large group moves. Been in business since 1… https://t.co/2xTUUZ7CH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cszabla @drewmckevitt Thanks. This is a book I've been meaning to read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is so beautiful. I feel every word.. I just hope she sees this..... ya know what I mean ? /: https://t.co/e26QDNRreW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of this crew and coaches! #RedbirdPride @ Collinsville High School https://t.co/ku1Y1joYmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoryMcConville2 @2000AD @SimonBowland @dancornwellart @jimboswellart Of course!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen You look to be hitting on all cylinders on this Monday. Good job young lady! 👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichlandSD400 roads out in the county are hazardous.  Be safe all! @emswildcats1 @douglane9 @EMScatsden @bjsorensen21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_mcivor @WG894 @JSportsnet Mocking it is one thing but I would love to see someone go all out and mock them i… https://t.co/eXiNhbkl11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es que la gente debe entender que la mayoría de los Animales se alimentan de otros animales. Jeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltmossberg @LaurenGoode @WIRED There’s a social status aspect to it as well. You’re seen in it once or twice, li… https://t.co/RKyl62m4a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very exciting race in @ConferenceUSA as the real fun is about to begin. The nation is now taking notice and there i… https://t.co/g95zvdiKPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[California Gov. Gavin Newsom wants Google, Facebook to share profits with state's residents https://t.co/u71TTXgiG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 5:40a, first crash on NB I-435 before Stadium Dr. Left lane now blocked #kctraffic https://t.co/jyexJ1Vtj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So,with about 3 weeks of serious winter left, we are told we have trains that don’t perform well in Ottawa winters.… https://t.co/vhtvK9Cdbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the end of 2019, will Disney own 99% of all wealth in the world?  This year they are releasing Captain Marvel, D… https://t.co/jVTV8uCjF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShutzeT @maydenmayden @ColbearGoggans Fuck all that let’s go to south padre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The best celebration for that time would be your absence and real Americans being invited. Also, s… https://t.co/XWydT9l1M2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseydDavid @mrjswaine @BayridgeSS_LDSB It sounds like you are doing some pretty amazing things with your business… https://t.co/8AUgmVoDvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pulling up on them O'Driscolls after they snaked me https://t.co/arL2YgLxPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a traitor. Hardly a position from which to throw stones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First, in order to have better, you must become better. [📸: idealistic_crown] —————————————————————… https://t.co/Xid0ucUljs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The advising center won’t give me a new advisor, so I said, “ I can go 2 more years without an advisor ”. now I’m thinking wait can I 😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProcterGamble and @M13Company, a full service venture firm, will partner to release a number products and services… https://t.co/CuydivosTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[81-year-old picks up guitar in a store, shocks everyone when he starts t... https://t.co/l8yY0z9k38 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2ndof10 the other insight.  Don't buy any KETO labelled foods.  Just eat food and stop eating carbs.  The 80% is t… https://t.co/fP2RbHDmCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[She wears armor around her heart. ⚔️🖤⚔️  @horriblyright live in Providence, RI  #Horriblyright #Conjurethecure… https://t.co/KDNr03qEFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSScottWhite @Fantrax Happy to do it, I appreciate your efforts. Would love to draft with you guys some time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LambAway Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite things to do as a scientist is meet with lawmakers and make the case for science funding.  Best… https://t.co/opXV6wUIZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIRMILES @sobeys Gee thanks.  You failed to mention that you have spend $100 to get the miles.  Doesn’t help me.… https://t.co/r4l5pTMzyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @AOC I am beginning to believe a great danger to our Republic is the left of the Democratic Party who shou… https://t.co/xebk5wmK4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassiecabbage I didn’t put any work into it because I wasn’t there so I actually don’t care about releasing it?  p… https://t.co/4MfiEZ7srA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hype to see everyone on the lineup tomorrow, but super excited to see that boy @diontimmermusic throw down! 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jporty13 Hey Jason , Chad's pick 4 tickets don't line up ,,,7th race is where the discrepancy is ,,,can ya please rectify the error ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how quickly the media doesn’t even want to mention this disgraceful , sickening, phony, famous hoax pr… https://t.co/28r9ZyuAYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bendudman1 @JamesMCritchley @hairy_n @hairyfan @Eight8ofclubs @BumsteadFan @WomensEyeCandy1 @Todd_1014… https://t.co/gqdO8yNm6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCpatriot123 You insulted me enough, so your bawling about my returning the favor is just being a cry baby. Grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who IS the handsome devil in that puddle? @ Narragansett, Rhode Island https://t.co/A2UzDXDDnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I feel at work while everyone else is out here enjoying their life https://t.co/QL0CDx1Yd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, has anyone asked the question directly that @maddow asked indirectly last night?  Is the Republican Caucus ac… https://t.co/fWp06vaZXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW55 @dennyhamlin @KyleLarsonRacin @KyleBusch I’m subscribed 😎Had to find the @purplebutton]]></document></documents></author>