<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[All these senators are from states that make the F-35 (Texas, Florida, Maine) or are going to have F-35s based ther… https://t.co/QPDeYsvyUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarjaKPTV They do that from 6am to 8 am as well! And you know I took part in that. 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordanbray_ Lmaooo id be screaming across the field “siiiiis, you will not believe what this man just texted me at… https://t.co/HvLVH69Dg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m craving nachos from Freebirds but the closest one to me is in Granada Hills 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a balmy 27 degrees here...Time for some red wine, my cozy fireplace and a good book!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meritchey @Haley_Aye That came off way shittier than I meant it! Fuck lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayAreaDebates @amber_red1 @NBCNews If it needs to be explained to you, you'd better start paying closer attention… https://t.co/pW0QFboHSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serenawilliams @alexisohanian If we celebrate love daily a special day isn’t needed because everyday is a special gift❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a funny insta post so I searched “vines about presidents” in google and only results Igor were for the vineyard… https://t.co/cuOAbiFOaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can’t afford NOT to invest in yourself!” - Karyl Eckerle @BusinessofImage #WXWBusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[#playthefuckingbassjohn more amazing #latergram night 2 photos of #duranduran in #neworleans. it was such an amazin… https://t.co/WBD916Zp14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodeGreenTV @ShootyPerson @_enp1tsu We can’t socialize or behave... AND we’re all vaccinated.... there’s an interesting link there....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge win v a very good Westfield team on Senior Noght!#mamafalcon #falconhockey @ Fitchburg, Massachusetts https://t.co/BAAd3vum0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brooke_jayy So sad I couldn’t be there, but my heart is so so full 😫♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got a palm reading by a psychic and, wow. Wow wow wow is all I can say]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadMikeyBad @0000seapea808 Why did the chicken walk half-way across my road and stop?.............................… https://t.co/kwdXc34Bop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, we should pick a woman to challenge Cornyn. I, love @KimOlsonTx too! #RunKimRun #KimOlson2020 https://t.co/p9uwUhS8gN via @houstonchron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHGOP HB 482  adds 8.5% tax on employers HB 623 increase business tax to 7.9%,  jobs go elsewhere.  NH = lower emp… https://t.co/a7UUxsvZp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Pugs Are Made - Funny Cartoon | Curious, Funny Photos / Pictures https://t.co/p9ZCipkh0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep respect for @MikeBloomberg evaluating what is best for the country, not his ego (take note @HowardSchultz )]]></document><document><![CDATA[I, John, your brother and companion in the suffering and kingdom and patient endurance that are ours in Jesus, was… https://t.co/DqI19rMRlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samariel7194 I love you Sam! Forever!!!!!⭐️💫🌟🌟✨🌟🌟⭐️ come visit us soon. We need ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my community  @CrossFit gym #KanehsatakeCrossfit 💜Tragedy struck 24 hours ago when a fire burned dow… https://t.co/l5FZxYwldP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDBank_US Just got off the phone with Leslie in Greenville, South Carolina. What a great rep you have! Way to go Leslie!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I don’t think I “know” celebs but he has always come across as really intelligent and evenly keeled. I am tryin… https://t.co/HTNAwBMNvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maggie’s doing a podcast (and many interviews) about her groundbreaking surgery. Cool! #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PillsFor @ProudResister No l supported a woman who was not bought by Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teasers for @CosmicFabric  trueandtherainbowkingdom   Commission !  My work can be found at https://t.co/zT4k3joHJC… https://t.co/odl0EKmpIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bohemian Rhapsody came on while I was eating breakfast in my hotel lobby, but in accordance with the rules of life… https://t.co/JhTIXxdtPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Absolutely, despite the fact that all women are generally shit upon, white women do share in the white… https://t.co/uFxBknzXcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[STILL CANT BELIEVE THIS IS MY LIFE!!! 💍👰🏻🤵🏼💕#Walkerdowntheaisle https://t.co/dKimf7Y5i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 Wow, report her to the school board. She should be fired. What a shitty teacher.... Not to mention a liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So....SOH Pelosi @SpeakerPelosi We The People want an answer to the burning question Why is tRump still in Our Whit… https://t.co/RhTVBKcZie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send me the best baseball valentines, i can’t find mine from last year 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kink is @ariana2525 in horse riding gear #PumpRules https://t.co/oESLgX7iLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lfzalacca @sbambury13 @elaine_erb are you surprised Anne of Greene Gables wasn’t her first book?? #obsessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do they realize how much the American public already knows? Or is it they just don’t give a damn? We all know there… https://t.co/hzpDuekeTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman HERE'S YOUR HUMANITY &amp; PRO-LIFE AGENDA AT WORK.  https://t.co/tOC3F3rXVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo many people suck at dressing themselves. Get your own style and dress accordingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristinalaila1 @KamalaHarris Kamala Harris and Cory Booker, Rush to Judgment saying it was a modern day lynching a… https://t.co/aYakQ4Cnf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So our @lyft driver asked for $20 cash and she would cash app me it back- she needed cash for the gas station I gue… https://t.co/cm1QUvooCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComoseDise For me personally, if I draft a poem and can use a line from that draft, I'm very happy. 🤣 My expectati… https://t.co/iAfTDe6Bm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN @KamalaHarris @RepMaxineWaters @SenWarren @DebDingell @SenStabenow @nytimes @maddow… https://t.co/k0YUHDHCPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlighty60 @eaton_sandy Rt. They exaggerate benefits . Yes I notice even the Ins . Co. Pushes it . What is that tel… https://t.co/jud8kD5ipK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice Love Adam. He seems more selective than the other coaches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4,363 SF Turnkey #Restaurant Space For Lease on High-traffic Tunnel Rd Business Corridor in East #Asheville, #NC: $… https://t.co/eroWCpVr3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HOPE YALL DONT THINK THAT I WAS SIDING WITH DREW PLS 🥺🥺🥺 https://t.co/8i8IqTRVOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 There’s something funny going on there &amp; it doesn’t smell good.🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amable lector, lectora, dígame usted, ¿acaso no son los adoradores del dinero los que van a Las Vegas?  https://t.co/0Qlgc3ChSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic No, the piercing isn't real 😂 Snap let's me live out another life with piercing filters. Haha! https://t.co/o0LKRk8pTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erica4beauty I hope your feeling better soon! And if you need time off take it, we'll be here when you return. 💜 keep strong]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when you say that trump supporters are deaf dumb and blind you get 6 days in twitter penitentiary. But when trum… https://t.co/WxKPmc533a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveLikeGhee Say it louder for the people in the back ! 🙋‍♀️ preach !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgrantaddison @benshapiro She is a communist and needs to go.  She does not love this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once I start talking highly about a dude he always fucks it up smh why ????? Why can’t no mf act rite. I’m sick of y’all 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliza_relman @AOC Well with only 12 years left I suppose there reasoning is solid lmao 😂 #WakeUpAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cawhly yeah like... pheromosa being like a representation of how lusamine's beauty and power as a ceo and how thos… https://t.co/hMhEkVGvC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing love to my hair stylist @ultabeauty and @Redken5thAve Thank you, Tessa!! 💇💕#UltaBeauty #Issaquah… https://t.co/NOe6Yf5eVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I feel that no one is going to love me again like Alejandro did.. *cries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrStevenCree So very sorry this happened to you. I had someone who stole several small azaleas from mine. The poli… https://t.co/okGa1xiUXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep The Faith (Ft. Aja) - Styles P @therealstylesp #KeepTheFaith #StylesP ft. #AjaLorraine  #HipHopLives #HipHop… https://t.co/1spfONG1JZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USNavyMomPA @realDonaldTrump Watch Rachel Maddow tonight very interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iona13111 @don_elswick @merovingian2069 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump 25 followers humm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four Russians attended the meeting, led by Natalia Veselnitskaya, a lawyer with known Kremlin connections who acted… https://t.co/Rba0beJFcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad just watched a star is born last night and he told me he loved it and cried akaksjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #2 on South J Street of the Street Painting Festival.  Don't miss the completed works today! @ Magnolia Boutique https://t.co/7kpaJGMnd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariecountryman @Communista2 @QuietManc @bunkybun @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @deeshanger… https://t.co/2AMYtsc7OO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new brexit will be something similar to the US and it has its own success There's always room for improvement later on]]></document><document><![CDATA[At first Rylla loves Wingates U, where genius teens research new tech to fix the climate. But when she discovers he… https://t.co/Zi0rCc20nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope so...soon  @DonaldJTrumpJr  and I feel sorry for his kids unless maybe he’s home-schooling them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@znerdforever @creolecanadian Wow, I made the horrifying mistake of reading the comments on that post.   Need a haz… https://t.co/Nc4seZrY2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ever you feel sad #MentalHealthAwareness #MentalHealthMatters https://t.co/cL162an3n5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YllekIlene I’m gone for ten days as of Saturday then I’m back FOR A WHOLE MONTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you follow me on Instagram it’s important for you to know that my aesthetic is “older mom that doesn’t really kn… https://t.co/1PMCxDvyS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOT gonna roll through that on my road bike.  😳 #nofilter #thingsiseeonmybike @ Santa Clara PAL BMX track https://t.co/Yy8ack4YZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bonniesurf4ever @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse A "Smart Wall" is needed-continued fixing/updating fence,… https://t.co/9JSui4J5nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @FrankFigliuzzi1 @JoyceWhiteVance @KasieDC @kasie @MSNBC You are the best reporter there is… https://t.co/ZoXYZpOiZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Practice compassion and tolerance whenever you see someone with a disability. Their road is a daily battle of ma… https://t.co/rAXDV491Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get paid to watch things like this. im not mad about it https://t.co/oXw6cZedGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJellyman @PizzaPortBeer @ArrogantBastard @2ndChanceBeerCo @badhopper @JonMontag @lhtetrick @Jagoff33 @cellmavin… https://t.co/sMeuJkLcjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Descendant Detroit Style Pizza - @descendantpizza in Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/AVW3BNF0my]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Fauquier County JROTC! So incredibly proud of all your accomplishments thus far. Thank you f… https://t.co/7vusEAhubT]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: it’s OK to have a life after a kid. no im not talking about you tweeters who are partying every… https://t.co/r5l0I6SoyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayoClinic The best hearing aid is a cheap one. That's y I don't have one🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore something that I thought I would never see myself in, because I thought I could never wear something like this… https://t.co/ROrjiYneeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro @SethAMandel are you serious a cry for help.  Typically liberal thinking.  He had choices he made bad ones.   Consequences dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skb_sara @bulletedd Speak for yourself. Or the overpaid CEOs and Politicians?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been in a Justin Timberlake and *NSYNC since seeing Justin last night in concert in Portland Oregon.❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I phoned my work this morning and said, “Sorry boss, I can’t come in today, I have a wee cough.”   He said, “You ha… https://t.co/mKY7DskpVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its never about where yu started     always about where you gon finish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ofbirdsandbears @pandlemily SOMEBODY TEXT RYAN. LETS GET THE GANG BACK TOGETHER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahliz92 Listen I just want to sit in a way that looks completely uncomfortable and weird but actually feels like I’m relaxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magicalmsmurphy @TpTdotcom Yes, please! My email is Miranda.evans@hsv-k12.org]]></document><document><![CDATA[7.7 Magnitude #earthquake in Palora, Equador.  I was just going to be looking right now at the maps, (and still wil… https://t.co/8ASd99sX8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more poisons! This is why @naturecide is the best vs poisons that harm our pets, wildlife, children, etc! https://t.co/TLMrZclvoO @UCLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone watch this vid of my friend who is rlly rlly good at using her vocal chords :,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 When I see these, I get giddy knowing Trump and his ilk will never, ever, ever, ever experience this.  😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mislissa0080 @Klyqueen2014 @JenniferHorsle3 @OurClassroom @Jinj_er @joshNYa78 @rwilley112 @K9Dasy @cutesydolphin G… https://t.co/q9zoCXIEbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is one of those days where I just want to curl back up under the blankets and tell the world to fuck off 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darling I'm a nightmare dressed like a daydream #sundayfunday #jumpintospring #springforward #dclingerie #boudoir… https://t.co/6tpzyiBQao]]></document></documents></author>