<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Part of me wanted Caddies car to hit Colton after he jumped the fence. That way Cassie could make his physical body… https://t.co/Z8PWHXtXoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmineZozzora @ananavarro @PatriotLA @kylegriffin1 @steph93065 @phil200269 @SaraCarterDC @michellemalkin… https://t.co/bKXWex5guk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Auburn, AL? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/NjhtancFRz #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Bernie Sanders is the Democrat’s nominee, count on another 6 years of Donald Trump as president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to this guy right here. Coach Solovi on leading the @EastHighGirlsB1  to back to back State Titles!  Great le… https://t.co/eR6Po3E5Lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingRoble12 @amydipa @SarahKSilverman @AOC @justicedems These anti Bernie people are toxic. They can't even handle… https://t.co/ydMun7PrmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iniciando el día con mucha motivación 😊🤙🏻 #EchaleToro en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/1pWegcDxkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boothman23 Both topics should die alone with anybody worried about what everybody else is doing if it doesn’t affect them]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the coolest concepts in Dragon Ball Z has gotta be the hyperbolic time chamber though I would abuse the shit… https://t.co/eFtqSOEmmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairfaxJustin When we all are in the same boat  I can't believe how they are so jealous and vindictive to constant… https://t.co/sLzWlWfTmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a sick feeling in my stomach that Trump will be reelected in 2020. Dear God let me be wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZubyMusic @Cernovich If you’re not the next woman of the year you’ve been robbed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foreal. If you don’t already have them downloaded or know how to get them you not a real one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for giving me a chance, Charleston.  Unbelievable night at the @chsmusichall  Excited to be in Macon at t… https://t.co/f1f2OKKldO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shboogies @ChallengeOvrld @indyman08 @DayDaVonne_ @MTV_AMANDAG #latenightcrew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Kenny went with the smart-tight-RHJless rotation the Nets offense has looked SOOOOO much better]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Hoodie!  #oscars2019 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/xWJqo57Q72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft and Donald Trump,   Grabbin' #Patriots https://t.co/HfWaIWorI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gonna be me with my lil Asian baby one day lookin all cute like a lil dumpling 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realmente como venezolano en el exilio me siento indignado!!!! Son tantos los personajes cómplices y corruptos de e… https://t.co/5CGGq52ZCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start your Sunday with "Come as You Are" by @Michael_Card from his new record "To the Kindness of God".… https://t.co/oV8WqvoY5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Man you are the biggest moron in the world, you took the word of Kim Jong UM, you took the word of… https://t.co/vniyGKABGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it difficult being a farcical shit sack of an organization? It has to be, yeah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found one road in Omaha that doesn’t have a pothole https://t.co/Gy20EP5Ofa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom keeps transferring money into my checking account and then asking me to Venmo money to people for her and if… https://t.co/pj8KJw9bPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big weekend for #Syracuse hockey: @SyrCougars and @SkanHockey win DI and DII state tournaments. @CuseIce won the CH… https://t.co/7TdaKPsmjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re drunk and you randomly start missing your ex. Ew, no, thank you, next!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys and gals. I'm terrified of this life. I just want to throw that out there if any of you feel the same as I… https://t.co/KUJHUSFAwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby and Cat Fun and Fails - Funny Baby Video https://t.co/vWmIS0OX01 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[having a crush on someone who lives in a different state https://t.co/ozFsWqlw7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump said he was going to "stop our deficit" and "We're not going to increase our debt' . He will bankrupt us if w… https://t.co/ypBCHbEJCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the podcasts we did over at @therapymovement was on the Kaiser Clinician’s strike. So frustrated to see that… https://t.co/CDrxJ4N8Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mas sabes que te amo y quiero que recuerdes esto Siempre te voy a querer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamLover69 @barstoolsports I have so many questions for you. but my first one is.... why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the socialist/communist regime want to do is rip you apart. But we love you Mr. President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scholbAAL @lyndseyfifield @RepSwalwell But then, #RepSwallwell would have to skip being petty and just get his coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca permitan que alguien arruine su día, ustedes son lo suficientemente pendejos para cagarla solos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Ci Tourney wknd Event 🚨 @djenvy  howlcharlotte 🌙  Saturday Night During Ciaa Weekend  3/2 Nyc Dj invasion #DJENVY… https://t.co/U7nhJZE86l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some comics are upset that Stormy Daniels is headlining the Joke Joint, but anyone who has seen Chris Kattan live k… https://t.co/2poLe1ShiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIE ABSOLUTE CRIMINAL LIE ABSOLUTE INJUSTICE JURISDICTION AUTHORITY DISORDER DISTRUST COURT JUDGES. HAVE BEEN HIJAC… https://t.co/NQmkpkr3Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[you really have nothing better to do than to tweet hate words at a senior in high school? y’all don’t even know him… https://t.co/8ObvlAAEIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's a load of crap. @realDonaldTrump held 2, 3 or even 4 rallies per day in the final weeks of his campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyGargano So proud man! Definitely made my night. Can’t wait to see what happens next!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milton Area Veterans Memorial. @ Milton Area Veterans Memorial https://t.co/rxvRqPEYOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adriana Alvarez started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/lyrro42Ou2 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMALL GROUP TRAINING SESSION AVAILABLE   12 SESSIONS FOR $200  RESULTS ARE NOT GIVEN, THEY'RE EARNED"  if you have… https://t.co/xfEjaKPOXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @CNN @Dollar_Bank @WRIGHTAUTOGROUP https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/bupaDwIyvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMackowiak The ridiculous part is that they hired an unqualified Trump shill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#timelapse of my #theta360 in action 📸 #brooklyn 🚇 🚊 https://t.co/ZWgbxwhj2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahbearrz @luckydayapp Granted you don't have to pay to play but at all it is is a scam because people that play… https://t.co/uB75WkTQYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss What do you know about the book listed for sale on Amazon in relation to Mueller report?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessmead Are you checking their designs in @tinkercad before printing or are they sending you the .stl file and you are printing from that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to Google Search, Chuck Norris, for his Birthday and this is what came up, "Because It Knows You Don't Find… https://t.co/wOlnCuVEEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonCovey10 @washingtonpost Ha! So funny. Although children, one of the main beneficiaries of food stamps, generally don't smoke or drink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concussions can present in a number of ways. This info graphic describes common issues people experience after a co… https://t.co/ynnQGMUtLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[New book, ‘In the Closet of the Vatican’, produces a toxic cloud of suspicion @MichaelSWinters @EJDionne https://t.co/vhSV6Ox4rD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivinoTormento9 No, no tiene capacidad ni para manejar un puesto de agua de coco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Attila_The_Hon @LudwigDrumsHQ @MapexDrumsUSA I got this one for rehearsals, small gigs, and to carry to the music… https://t.co/KeDikfvg53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if women had actual pockets in their jeans, their wouldn’t be a need to strap a purse to their thighs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @RJBosshart_ on earning this great recognition! Very well deserved. Show out!! #FamilyWarriors]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcneil_emanuel @mcneil_emanuel I couldn’t agree more. It was about 24 years ago this month that #CoachShanks arriv… https://t.co/uuUpv4zYQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oaktown vs Philly: AI or Curry?  Love the question but I know The Answer.  @JalenRose @paulpierce34 @1MrBigShot @ESPNNBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrainEvacuated I agree. I think nms rain could use an update. Well, I think the weather as a whole could use one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinwiddieproud Thanks, man! #DMSGens #DeepRootsGreatHeights #MUSTbesuccessful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrowder @LWC @2CuteMadi @TheJaredMonroe @halfblack your losing to @benshapiro on: The Best YouTube Politics Chann… https://t.co/ysSOV6RKyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc7breaking Seems like an incomplete story to me. What is missing here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I found out yesterday that @rembert sometimes interviews people without a recorder   That's some Jay Z level me… https://t.co/h8BpCtnHQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canto della terra - Sarah Brightmann ft Alessandro Safina 🖤 live in Vienna https://t.co/WjSyTK3xI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I didn't have it together like that during my junior year AT ALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father, open our eyes to see this battle with evil for what it really is. Bring into the light any of the ways we a… https://t.co/FBUEIAAqyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Campbell101 @Dannmace Most places use pastries here however, I have seen bacon used.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😭 mane I swear to God! Can’t breath, on the floor, stomach HURTING! We be dying mane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oh_Watup @G0nFreaks As per always. I’d love to see his music library. 💅🏽 Or maybe I don’t. 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna take full advantage of being off today . Hitting up the lunch buffet for sure .]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t ignore your passions, they’ll point you towards finding meaningful work in your life.” — I’ve had many conve… https://t.co/AnIqLa1VRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salmón y masitas de cangrejo!! La ensalada de vegetales casi lista y yo a freír mis plátanos porque todo eso es par… https://t.co/V4sI0KNUG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[REAL WORK UNDEFEATED @isaiahthomas GAVE YALL THE BLUEPRINT OVER XMAS BREAK @jalenmcdaniels5 @Jmcdaniels7 🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I seem to remember Al being a big trump fan. I hope he has seen the light?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goingglobal2 Why not?  If you have the green deal, NOOOOOO one will be working, so socialism it is, I guess?????… https://t.co/9yy8Fkyo19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewk0117 @ScottsdaleBubbe @karanjasan @WhenIs2001 @jintzie19501 @fetus413 @Mikel_Jollett @AOC Yet good companies d… https://t.co/NOH9kYa9SZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusicByTanner The song is wonderful and so is your rendition! Awesome job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support me and my team! Our latest #alita discussion is available now on YouTube:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come a long way i started in my first college soccer game last night 🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone, is on the same SIDE of AMERICA. PRESIDENT TRUMP, and Nancy Pelosi, do not Rule America, only, the people… https://t.co/JpDUfzN0OO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalcubemaster @CaseyNeistat Yeah idk and i like the colors on the white but the detail is a big yikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRMRobertBruce @KyleClark @Rossputin Sure thing, Anonymous Rob. I'll take your "perceived" dangers to the abuser a… https://t.co/Gm7vsGuUPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Jerni Kiaku  2019 Hot 100 Girls Middle School Showcase   In our efforts to acknowledge outstanding performance… https://t.co/pIfcyNNRIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[accidentally got a reg lyft instead of a lyft line and feel like a Fucking hilton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh new hair cut 👌 and time with my little man. #nottoobadfor44 #dadgoals #lazysunday @ Matt and Mikes House https://t.co/BerXrxl0f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris What about the right of infant? Don’t those loves matter. What about the reproduction rights of all t… https://t.co/WYXKP3lYTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 8 AM on a thursday morning and she’s not even moving. Guess somebody doesn’t want to get tenure https://t.co/KL7EOs3iJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can hear all the action this weekend from Kalispell on the AM KCAP at 950 AM and online at… https://t.co/zR0WYhyADM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost I doesn’t matter he has done sooo much so far that the snowball will continue to roll and the Democ… https://t.co/9gE2gX74aD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awells10000 @EconTalker Right when you least want it, because rates have fallen dramatically. I’ve seen cases of 8… https://t.co/8J4r6v4Ni6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This assumes that the @SenatorLankford plan to reduce the 30 hour rule to a 2 hour rule for district court judges h… https://t.co/D4HnN3IeS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA is nothing if not thorough. Five minutes ago the @luka7doncic nameplate had no accents. Someone just swapped in… https://t.co/Y0Zsu0PaRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyClevelandTN Any idea why the power has gone off 7x in the past hour, Chatata Valley area?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleLobdell @nathankhensley @V21collective The inside word (?) is that it began as a movement in Canadian univer… https://t.co/8SxNwHT5Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[An observation about people. @ Alloway, New Jersey https://t.co/QwF4tt8123]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @Cern_lXXl @noah_nonsense @Tribal_Eagle70 @BiblePoop @EndtimeApostasy @horusrage @SoberHootOwl… https://t.co/veBz3YPnWO]]></document></documents></author>