<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[HEMP WELLNESS , PET SUPPLIES  CBD + Salmon Oil Tincture for Pets – 250 mg  Tribe to Table’s Native Wellness Pet CBD… https://t.co/tZZQECHHAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream I went to sundara. Let’s just say I woke up extremely disappointed]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any of my #emchat #highered #scchat friends see all these @NJACAC posts and have some ideas for more donations o… https://t.co/4n7QrVWuIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga just said something bout a birthday fit in like wow that’s a thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#math # This is a great dvd with math and a review of the alphabet sounds! https://t.co/gSRyrjq7oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trmp's history of bankruptng busness aftr busness, took endless "loan$" of DIRTY MOBLAUNDRED MONEY FROM CRIMINALLY-… https://t.co/eLZl5gWJ03]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Don’t be afraid of being a beginner.” . Now with my first year of working in real estate under my belt, I wanted t… https://t.co/he2JTDtgrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleaning my husband &amp; I room &amp; i see the bottle laying around might fuck around and drink by myself or drive to the front 🤷🏽‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaDonArtest @prageru I don't see how that point connects to CNN &amp; Fox. Those two firms appear to be free to publish what they want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftw_social @robrousseau @KatieSebas It really is. Either we support the Elliott Abrams led coup or we don't. That is black and white.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dr28 @wilmu The boy who harnessed the wind by William Kamkwamba #innovationineducation https://t.co/sKNCfL1Ns5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eastercards #religiouscards #OOAK #greetingcards #handmadecards #cardmaker #handmadeisbetter #paperarts… https://t.co/YocxhTDkEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s her world. ⭐️ We’re just living in it. @ Ponce De Leon Park https://t.co/z5oN8r7c5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this evening’s #MarchForOurLives event. Local students will share thoughts regarding gun laws/re… https://t.co/sKKaTOH1OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[An article about our district made the Asheville, North Carolina paper yesterday. Pretty cool! #OurFISDStory https://t.co/S6AuniuWmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars: Henry Golding, Melissa McCarthy, Regina King and more arrive on the red carpet #Oscars https://t.co/UZD9dYY9xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[United States of America only cares about it states @OANN  @POTUS what does each state want for Christmas? Summer festival anyone!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin @Sueme39164137 WE are THREATENING Men’s ‘STASH’ by exposing one of their procurers of “Throw Away Gir… https://t.co/wqYtoudoi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish we had a rooster 🐔 crowing app!!  😂 I need a reminder that I’m betraying my Lord. @bakerpastor @eastviewchurch]]></document><document><![CDATA[in case anyone asks tomorrow, international men’s day is on november 19th but no one really seems to care about tha… https://t.co/tUGeCh38Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing day hanging themrktloft with beautiful mama’s and their babies! So fun shooting with lindsaystephan… https://t.co/ocWGCqsz4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadMellon I’m really in to that hot tub 😍 like not INTO it, but you know what I mean 😏 ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG thanks @vulture for this sweet #geek note: The #OneRing + hot #Sauron coming to @PrimeVideo Long live… https://t.co/DqzINVOrf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Shame on you  In real time you are confabulating  Ever heard of the internet ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to try floating to see if it helps with my chronic pain and anxiety. #urbanfloatrehoboth @ Urban Float https://t.co/xV7tAKSCsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are Dumbest President of all time!!  Your Biggest Fraud of the 21st Century! No one cannot beat a Trump at Lying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A full birthday weekend together celebrating this guy I get to call mine in the books. And it was perfect. ❤️🎉… https://t.co/9BPUX1uPCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to be able to live life everyday like on Valentine’s Day where everyone is expressing their love and being n… https://t.co/QB1KTEJrGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaLazos Victory funds help our school beyond measure with student and family support on campus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me caga que quiten la cera con peyote  La Leslie confundiendo las telas de depilación, con el peyote]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a society that is focusing less and less on gender all the time. It could very easily happen that we have a… https://t.co/5PNnvcZh08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Well-said. We know almost everything essential and it's already damning. P.s. You know you're going t… https://t.co/kqMZXPgDb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are returning to our communities and students tomorrow.” Looks like no #sickout on Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have this new rule where I don’t, under any circumstances, leave Columbia Heights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenAlexander @PattyMurray @SenatorEnzi Share this thread with fellow Senate HELP committee members. @ABC @CBSNews… https://t.co/1EK9OtiGU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImSo_Randie Same as when you you blink and it’s morning and now you’re already late for work lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indigenous Women's Day at the Round House @ New Mexico State Capitol https://t.co/hWil8tkqSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamAir I was a sprinter in the water,  not on land. I could have swam a pretty good forty yards in ‘96 - would that count? 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a big difference between you and I, and after all this it definitely shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorphBox @doots_goots @EYuki19 @CanvasPirate @FUNimation What accusations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifeguard 🌊 Intern Reporter 🗞  Producer/Reporter 👩🏼‍💻 Graduate Instructor 👩🏼‍🏫 Social Media Manager 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defeat insomnia and sleep better with Energy Medicine...   https://t.co/HgI0CIvHFD  #energymedicine #insomnia… https://t.co/3XGXvtY4UV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithworksVodka @blakeshelton @BellamyBrothers @johnanderson @TraceAdkins @Lauren_Alaina Cranberry works was very… https://t.co/CwnlN2h81n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeedIsMe @Briteeye777 @_IamAnita_D @TigerLetsRoll @leahbirdjohnso2 @bizwomen4TRUMP @DaveSchreiber3 @Solmemes1… https://t.co/h0LUt5wqcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Namjoons been flexing on me and I am sooo over it how dare he look so fucking good these days istg idk if it's the… https://t.co/qOrgM3j18P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinfitzsloan EXCUSE ME🙋🏻‍♀️ Did you forget we bought a lip kit together??]]></document><document><![CDATA[As this week comes to a quick end I’m sitting here reminiscing on how amazing the past couple of days have been. I’… https://t.co/AK0GXdNi7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking out the fur because it is colddd in Raleigh🧥 #liketkit https://t.co/Q9TNY7pRnA https://t.co/YT0BazLXai… https://t.co/EwxG9m9UVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC shameful John McCain would be disgusted by your actions...WTF happened to you... What does Trump/Russia have on you??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 43 of Stay is Touch is posted https://t.co/FMwcaSY2HN Kate in action The… https://t.co/HwIoiiz2pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a 70-year-old man trying to sneakily hit his juul outside of a hospital. Day has been made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid @MichaelNardozzi That's amazing! Black don't crack. She looks so beautiful still; Camden Barbie lo… https://t.co/4NNsVKaEsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t believe Charlie is bringing you guys around Roterak people. It’s probably cause I’m not there” -… https://t.co/91gXOiGObn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youngroulade every time I’m trying to have a serious conversation with him about something I need him to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonline2000 @gmizrachi El PSUV esta lleno de gente equivocada. Pero en una democracia esta gente tambien tienen d… https://t.co/dQhVVX8BFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skeletor2785 @ChrisCuomo If they were Asia, they were already here in our country through the normal visa system.… https://t.co/KJTdO9tMIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellTech Culture Code embraces our individual strengths and common values.  Global Alliances team’s diversity in g… https://t.co/2KBFMbfvcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing Day! Loved helping Nick and Jess find a new Dig in Royal Oak!!! ✍💜🏡  #newdigs ] #royaloakmi] #oaklandcounty… https://t.co/2a0p5zCFf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather not be the person who cleans the Mojo 50 studio bathrooms. Too much poopin going on in there. #WhatILearnedToday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzie5197 @msmoon61 @keeshond81872 @twittersecurity @JennyBeth326 https://t.co/wwdpSCa8Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesdays were fabulous last night at the Rivers Edge in Yonkers. #tuesdays #rocknroll #music @ River's Edge https://t.co/AdYhr54muJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body is so sore. Felt like i did 1000 squats when i only did about 20. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pascaleyees @_SJPeace_ The Koran War seperated me from my daddy when I was a child, I remember seeing him for the… https://t.co/8iVBF0wT4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their fried chicken is everything! #pittsboroeats #pittsboronc  https://t.co/NHjrPkMKyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sostraveluk @AtlBotanical @monstervoyage @TravelAtWill @FoodTravelist @MyVirtualVaca @TonyOnFood @AskChefDennis… https://t.co/bACf8tTs2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaiwyarneson @SixZeroAcademy @Coach_Creighton @CoachSamSewell @CoachCKap @coach_cristobal @CoachBobo_CSU… https://t.co/LEmgpBCEOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FortniteGame Please put the scythe in I hugely support your game I bought the whole marshmallow set and I still ha… https://t.co/gHdaIHPXcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawn3448 @jimdonovancbs3 @ChelseaWeather @ChandlerCBS3 @CrystalCranmore @MPetersonWx @DanKoob 😂😂😂🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @7Eleven in Laurel, MD https://t.co/ZTc0f3JOv4 https://t.co/xCBygV1w0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vulture @stephanieprager another thing we have in common with Jay Z and Beyonce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@volrob33 @Shawn172510 It's so weird how all of us found each other on #VolTwitter and we are all around the same a… https://t.co/uxIyU9NUOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault And then, could the cat stop shedding already and contributing to 90% of the dust in my apartment!? https://t.co/k79QK0dq59]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to hear about your office supply quirks. For example, I hate ballpoint pens and they are definitely my pen o… https://t.co/NyzGHKF1yY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been on the road all day and came home to cook. Made a bomb meal and now i get to relax and finally do this homework.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Carsen Edwards for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/jrHFMpojkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dean Graham providing a wonderful analysis of state conversion therapy bans @USDLawSD @dineenkk @CreightonLawRev… https://t.co/SC0gzblYav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching all of the schools around me close but my school hasn’t even delayed. https://t.co/CxgENnT1sU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody @SheriffChody can you pull someone's DL on the spot for going over 100 mph? I've heard that you can.… https://t.co/5L72mgQfEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to go from the @PikeNurseries on Crossville in Roswell! Be a part of the live broadcast from 6-9:00 and share… https://t.co/qyieHEZY80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely superb letter. Well done @Anna_Soubry @heidiallen75 and @sarahwollaston 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @Steven11bit shot a beautiful video of it all! https://t.co/Rqw1EhJVrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to thank @WengerJeffrey , @RobertDCollins8 , @Mntdewmania ,@dnddegenerates , @austiebosty94 , @Ebil_otter, a… https://t.co/h9WYVGn97k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson So you are okay with the giver of the bible writing a note on the inside?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, we had an NYC Celiac Meetup event at @ROLLN15 in NYC. It was a great turnout with a REALLY happy group… https://t.co/qJ1QCV4LHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEmeraldDove I feel ya. It's all so intimidating. &amp; honestly, with a full time job, who has time for all that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOX19Robert @Fox35News You will b greatly missed. But can’t blame you.... Florida go where the sun ☀️ is always shining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SerendipityDizl @tnmynatt Their masks are off! We all see exactly what they are!!! EVIL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debber66 @CherylW54985317 Elizabeth Warren should go baby sit Michael Cohen ... in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this like the "slanket" as advertised during the holidays on teevee years ago?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefanAHoward Dude don’t judge a book by its cover. NO ONE has their act completely together. You’ve got plenty to offer. Keep sharing it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody take us back on our @RoyalCaribbean adventure! I miss the warm weather!! https://t.co/3kR0DPuaCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joliehaitian79 @soapsindepthabc That’s what I was thinking.  Anna drains me.  I like Alex much better.  The way An… https://t.co/pj7FkVUBLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca en la historia del universo hay such thing as “too much Olallo” . De nuestra cuenta tendríamos a Olallo 24/7… https://t.co/U86q9Y331I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiebionci @Casey_Elekes98 @BrianaLytle17 @SkylarVictoria Pretty please 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djstef415 I wish you had mama. We raised many glasses to you today. HBD Goddess 💜🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited about this ❤️📚📚and more 📚Thank you @dukes_library @DukeCitySD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Would someone please show this asshole a Youtibe documentary about Stalin and Hitler. If he really… https://t.co/HrgFPzzkzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasmaMcCullough @keribla @HoustonChron The Judge finds PC or "no PC" not the prosecutor. The Judge arraigns the Ac… https://t.co/H1BhjifXOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeahNoPod @GoPostalPodcast @LAnotsopod @AugiePWrites @ourtruecrimepod @SpilltheChisme @peoplearewild… https://t.co/YLdL5GTWck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good ol’ @billmckibben. Thank you for the #DemUnityTwitterProject. It’s a great example of creative positive thinki… https://t.co/Hted5EQJ7I]]></document></documents></author>