<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Have extra Clippers suite tix today for the game at 12! Anyone want them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astro_luca Looks like you are in the house of cosmonauts museum. Did you buy the Gagarin photo in the museum shop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[also SERIOUSLY don’t watch this alone at 3 AM because now I feel like a hopeless romantic gn 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are not friends on FB. Too intimate. I just go and look at her page sometimes, like you do]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does a Vegas trip with the boys mean? Half of them didn’t even make it to the headliner and @IzzyHere__ went to the hospital.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveWestly Instead she should start with a living wage law. To give gov’t cash to working poor family is to subsi… https://t.co/FamU5yoFYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another blatant LIE by a DESPICABLE acolyte of Trump! https://t.co/fyFsW6lCTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cameron_Gray @WalshFreedom But crustaceans make excellent border patrollers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently my wife booked a double queen bed hotel room on “accident.” She said, “look we can sleep in separate bed… https://t.co/j71hXD0TU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una vez le envíe a una novia un ramo de flores 💐 y en la tarjeta le escribí “Yo soy el Diciembre de todos tus años”… https://t.co/bVoL3aQksC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSScottWhite we have our draft scheduled on the 24th.  Just realized there are 3 games scheduled starting 20th.… https://t.co/Wtlx78mB5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@permoratorium Bro I wasn’t sure if my girl was human then she let out a big fat wet one and I knew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sapinker @AnnCoulter @dpreview I have tattoos. I like tattoos. But, pretty soon the unique person will be the one who doesn't have one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLBlackStar Relax! Always been a few that worked in the WHITE house 🤷🏾‍♂️ Django Ass folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't stop watching this video!  #USpoli #Trump #ThrillerDance #ZombiePOTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having the right mindset is important.  In fact, just the way you look at a situation can be the difference between… https://t.co/d0gKpEisTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valavb @nytimeses Los hijos del padre de PZ tienen entre 30 y 40 años, eso fue hace añales!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbarmyman2 Few things bring me more happiness than helping others. We have the power to change the world for the better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it yes (@ San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/CBDapEzEfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeSuisBernie @ninaturner @dccc @BernieSanders That’s the 2016 agenda. Must have been written by @neeratanden]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarveyLevinTMZ Truth hurts... Should she have not have them on and just let the lie continue?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnStolnis Well Cozen’s can’t play, and I think Williams actually has value on the market to put together a solid… https://t.co/oRrXiHiYYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't call me a 'hater' but I'm still waiting for Weber to do something .. #goHabsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a good game for so many reasons, not the least of which was spending it with my good friend @CenterIceSweety .… https://t.co/vlcZS870fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BrookdaleBobcat and @MWwolverines families for adding stories to my classroom library for 22 years. Ray… https://t.co/evY4X8laxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanadaNATO #bring #Him to #Me #I need him for #Questioning have #ALL #Civilian #Government #Workers and #War… https://t.co/E9wz2niyS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Folks could be using their time to promote their music or askwhy certain people have a critique to I prove their cr… https://t.co/WNm5Wk23NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyB371 @kimfreethinker They should tie his bitch ass up in a house a set it on fire!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow If you hate the U.S.A. and you hate @realDonaldTrump , you gotta love the fake news media!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s my thing about the opt-out rumor: if only one person gives out information, and nobody else of credence back… https://t.co/D4szrSpb8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨MAY I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION PLEASE....@_angelaprice10_ is 5/5 4(2B) HR on the young season. 🚨🚨 @KUSoftball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tide gets leadoff man aboard for 3rd time in as many innings as @tjr1_ plunked to start the 3rd. That man,… https://t.co/Rz38Rq4UZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyDeRosa Making him fight my M.U.S.C.L.E. Figures like I was taught too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up at the “Butt Crack” of Dawn. #oceanlakes #surfsidebeach #mrytlebeach #atlanticocean #vacationmode @ Ocean Lakes… https://t.co/EyEfADdseg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veramagalhaes Enquanto isso no microfone da jovem pan, Vera Magalhães! 👇🏼 https://t.co/3vN1wfnIXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have Wolf/Greninja for mains, but now I can't stopping labing pika and ICs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only way Utah come back is by gettign to the line. ASU has been impressive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian The world can’t comprehend how much I hate you much less how you’ve become the definition of the wor… https://t.co/goK6EnTSbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This zoning hearing board was originally Jan. 17 but overflow crowd due to intense interest led to it being resched… https://t.co/cOeH2mfNcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny she got her pic taken when booked without a head cover. How come she couldn’t be sworn in to The House that w… https://t.co/TmbJCeeqnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morterenatus But if it wasn’t paused it wouldn’t be right? Because it’s basically hi lighting the power bomb for w… https://t.co/FDWR2FmKIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport If she doesn’t like the second amendment why have armed guards when she goes in public]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJayapal @MalcolmNance @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi @SenatorSchumer  @GOPLeader  The real crisis at our Southern border!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gotta keep reminding myself that all I can do is just try my absolute best. I can't keep stressing myself abou… https://t.co/H0NkiVrYFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting an awesome corporate event at @pinehurstresort #carolina #travel #photography #photographer… https://t.co/ipyinaDbiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarrettSallee @SethOnHoops @SXMCollege Did y'all talk about if Williams' play was a foul? -or- Did y'all talk abou… https://t.co/WfDImLmw6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s edit list. Pardon the sloppy notations. https://t.co/GFfhrDC4X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robin Miller says Pato declines 8 races with Andretti because Mike Harding would still be involved? Yikes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[dads that are about to go get some milk be like https://t.co/ZEvwqg7fgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mistake on the back line of Madrid and the misery continues for the Merengues.  However, if the result holds, Real… https://t.co/ObEK3OeIWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betofloresRG690 @LuchoIbarra690 Lucho siempre a dicho ke Pizarro no kiere estar en Rayados, Aurreta y Medina ni ha… https://t.co/V9a40GI9Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, tuck your shirts in. “Mistakes Guys Over 40 Make Trying to Look Youthful” https://t.co/1ym24ZmL4E via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jimi_Jammin @SheilaPierce51 @Hippie_of_Love @Berthagoodlovin @HollyRoseMyers @JamesHo03148924 @happygolfwidow… https://t.co/IAhDjiP6RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennedyNation @LawrenceBJones3 @RepThomasMassie @kayleighmcenany @gayletrotter @tomshillue @KatTimpf @FoxBusiness… https://t.co/4AMC09ASgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicitaciones al excelentísimo constitucional presidente de R.D Danilo Medina por el excelente discurso de Rendir… https://t.co/ir146o38UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You always know when you’re in for a customer service nightmare when you can hear them coming with the “clip clop “ of important shoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chilltowntv 17. I can't verify it but I think I met a dude, y'all.  Not that there's anything wrong with that if t… https://t.co/5D0kk4ZNLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look at this lovely, two-story St. Louis home- cozy and spacious! #realestate @ St. Louis https://t.co/JuXMGDlZpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Not switching, that ain’t over yet, just adding on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida Snake hunters from India tackle Florida's python problem https://t.co/tKMp3zNUEi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bloodstained: Curse of The Moon - First 3 Levels Thank you to everyone that joined the stream. Much appreciated🙏🏼 C… https://t.co/pJWY37gvfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARedPillReport He should get the Flynn, Manafort, Cohen and Stone treatment and then go to jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess #bloodboy from @SiliconHBO is really catching on..🤔 https://t.co/AkmzTpcEri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry University FL Sat Mar 9th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 75 SUNDAY Chance Of Showers Hi 81]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz And your solution is to elect another billionaire who is completely out of touch with the electorate… https://t.co/z45QJOkMwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MonDAAAYYY!!!  #SpringBreak2019 for @ProfHankLewis #BrewCrew ☕☕☕  @DarbyDouglasTV  @MattGranite @LauraScyrkels… https://t.co/KIlTrCy9Je]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller @weedmanhippy needs a couple 💯 ft extension cords &amp; a couple 6 ways!    We love cowboy john Brad!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna be your ex, we way too good at being friends. Can we still hangout? On the low, get wild I don’t wann… https://t.co/tGEOlrwCJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought Sox fans, including myself, would have been "over" the MM signing by now. But, my displeasure for the Whi… https://t.co/mN6fifuafb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once a lively home with two cats.. now there are none.. Poor Phoebe.. you will be missed..  sorry that you were so sick..]]></document><document><![CDATA[too much Yesterday criticism on the tl, all of which ignores the basic reason this movie exists: it's time for a mo… https://t.co/XTfd9pHc8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatkid_diff @Jared_Carrabis @playoff__b He ain't going anywhere lol.  If yankees really wanted to pay for a 3b th… https://t.co/7ZXjdLX6In]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods I’m still trying to figure out why cheat on you? My wife is the closest version of yo… https://t.co/oMlPGijQei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your love for yourself is down right creepy. Like its ok to love oneself but you go over the top w… https://t.co/n0vd83OyuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankie1g We SHOULD'VE done that. There are other cases where that's been done, but we were a bit ill-prepared. HO… https://t.co/i7Zlkwjnmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgmstl_dan @charliekirk11 Listen bot, the internet has all the information you seek right at your fingertips. I no… https://t.co/q5gPtQ6niw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. In fact I’d like a third slice because fuck this kind of attitude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bastylefilegirl Lmao you served me... no cap  But seriously, that documentary was trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new film “Straight outta Riyadh”? Nope, just a bunch of people with a poor appreciation for the laws of Physics… https://t.co/MmZZ9ct2Kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some ask where is the black men fighting for equality? Tupac probably said it the most eloquently, you don’t see an… https://t.co/hVh6RcIZYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided this will be my personal account. I kinda need one to vent and recapture my passion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low-key shade catching a TD in Oakland with AB in the background. Well done, young man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaWarfield No and proof is lack of morals in the Catholic faith.  Look at the priest and the many child sexual… https://t.co/Tm4GyFRvrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_thisiscarter @zetaraffix @lizpeek @AOC The crippling of the economy, or her lack of knowledge?]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 hours of #Seinfeld starting now on @TBSNetwork ,,,,, @JerrySeinfeld @IJasonAlexander @OfficialJLD @ImJohnOHurley… https://t.co/xpeEschKII]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Democratic Party’s idea 💡 of civility. Literally unbelievable what they have become. No ideas 🤔 just: obstr… https://t.co/5XCHmKjC6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Why don’t we has not bee man ten yrs that kind of colusionwould just get someone not a Clinton suidcided]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NuestroSpotify Comparemos juntos la música que compartimos en Spotify. https://t.co/ddekJXENS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And he tweeted this 3 days later https://t.co/STuTFHTnG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazerMazur19 stays 🔥 knocks in couple more, AC now leads 14-2 in B8. Bulldogs are 🔒 in at the dish, now have cracked out 16 hits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was living on my sailboat, before I retired, every morning I would walk about half a mile from my marina to… https://t.co/2wHyI6lI05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotwingo I hope they have the manners of this guy https://t.co/PFJryg2G3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValaAfshar I kid you not. The machine I'm running right now is using an Atari 800 computer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My doctor when I tell him I’ve cut crack out of my diet https://t.co/8ag9LfZUYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this kid. She may be dragging me around the floor (seriously, parents, where do they get their energy?!!!) B… https://t.co/BINxYNT2u5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp Why the fuck do u guys have the subscription continously on for? I dnt need 72629292lbs of protein(even… https://t.co/pMdFvXfiP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessings upon blessings and Glory be to God!!! https://t.co/NYbznKvBYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to protect your team culture. This battle is waged daily.  –  Doc Rivers #PowerofLocal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sera? Ahora resulta que para tener mas sexo hay que ser Grifo No.....pos....nomas no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is total insanity. There are many chikdless couples who would love to take the unwanted child that you have be… https://t.co/sE3XaK3VYn]]></document></documents></author>