<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@wildwestpie @SopanDeb Well, an indictment &amp; criminal charge are usually the first steps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking bets on what lap will be the BIG ONE and how many more cautions we are going to have within the next 23 laps. #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished off an incredible weekend sitting next to the most precious 6-yr-old on the plane. Reminds you of what rea… https://t.co/inMXWeYInG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sound-mind Saturday ...We become what others want us to be until we discover our own identity ©️2019 LWB Butterfly… https://t.co/ieJEsDb2l8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sincerely disappointed in the lack of snow storms... get to work Mother Nature, Times A tickin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nephew had me blocked from his snap stories but not my friends🙃 I thought I was the cool aunt????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to announce that I will be interning in Albuquerque, New Mexico in June photographing the National Senior Games Association!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charges need to be filed! @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @GrahamLedger #DrainTheDeepState]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO if you’re seeing lil skies in south padre tell him i love him cause im crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy culpable 🤣 me da confianza y me dicen que como quiera estoy hermosa y pues 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sorry to read this.  My thoughts and prayers are with Jason's family]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had such amazing customer service @HomeDepot that I walked out without my purchase 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcoming this new week with hope, encouragement and God’s promises to be fulfilled. Happy Monday y’all! @ The West… https://t.co/RDXVpxIR4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have A Blessed Beautiful Wonderful Day🎉HE IS ALIVE!!! Our KING JESUS Is ALIVE!!! Go WORSHIP Our KING JESUS SMILE😄❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldClark @dylanwiliam @RevaFish @natwexler @DTWillingham https://t.co/oHoCYL8kte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 ...And why is he on CNN...no wonder I don't watch this channel.  The new FOX NEWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[how single am I?   i’m currently sitting at a table BY MYSELF in a bar ~sober~ while my friends are at the bar taking shots :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abel2j21 @Jillymoe @360red_ @MichaelAvenatti They do. Just want to cover for trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Days off = cuddle sessions with this little fur monster. Got some freelance work to do... however currently stuck..… https://t.co/unP3pOMIPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_laTodd @kokotwist @camdasilva 30 million goes quick when you're paying the hos and  partying... Not to mention th… https://t.co/JWk70aMXAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this what’s passing for Woke these days? I’ve displayed my ... GASP ... bare legs on tv before. I’m certain the… https://t.co/4Ty7vNVf2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump also like, what’s the Connecticut dig about? You know you’re also president of Connecticut right?… https://t.co/kNW4lHppPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning LORD JESUS Thank You, It Is Your Wisdom With Understanding It Is Your Grace Mercy Empathy Daily It Is… https://t.co/gCyEN7luxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want twitter to know that I’m writing a research paper and instead of typing “getting his wife pregnant” I t… https://t.co/D9wT7za2MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kulang Joy.. Malandi.......KA! Miss putukan na! Tigang ka b dyan sa Taiwan joy? May cobwebs na ba?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysterygirl_hs @mariareiner26 @stylespromoarmy @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday with the boys @NJDevils #PruPics #BUFvsNJD #NJDevils https://t.co/mY3iNFqYuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a horrible horrible country to be doing this to CHILDREN and their parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dancing my little pink heart out for the Night Owl video ❤ @ New York, New York https://t.co/nwmMiNyrYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It ain’t pretty but it’ll be yummy. #chickenpotpie #homemade #nom @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/aVrURPwpJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not saying u ain't make ya own money but never bought u shit lmaooo dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary Hard to believe! 🤣 https://t.co/GvZqMg4s4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[You snow what time it is!!! She's still not feeling it. But he LOVES IT. @ Ferndale, Michigan https://t.co/MgzPEoE0FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest I didn't do anything but walk tonight, but going to get back into everything soon. I've missed, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hammetjohn @sparky1florida Do you know what the English word ILLEGAL MEANS? please allow yourself some time before… https://t.co/cYuyvZBfL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adapted Phys. Ed. PD day. Getting our learn on! @cburgelem @TcboeE @TCBOE https://t.co/P91LietXQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A must read on this Sunday: @elizabethjdias examines the contradictory culture of the Catholic church and the secre… https://t.co/idCNsY07ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notwithstanding ye have well done, that ye did communicate with my affliction. https://t.co/tkWtT9icxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blove65 @velvetrose15 @SavvyHuman @Tierrah46 @thetoyman1 @BillPeriman @sholzbee @mommydean74 @ScarlettDear1… https://t.co/pXnOWuHWMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaJohnCagle That is awesome news. I look forward to learning what you find. The admiration is mutual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyTabbbb @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett So sad that Jussie betrayed his own black people, LBGTW people, and mos… https://t.co/dXOoVmDTzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to tell my dad a story and he goes “instead of talking let’s just watch family guy”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into Ken Jennings! If you don't know who that is, then you don't watch Jeoparugh [enough]. Awesome guy. 😊… https://t.co/GaOMCCkqVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did anyone else have to watch Mac and Me in elementary school when you had a substitute teacher? Maybe it was a Nebraska thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doug_Zbi @ChosenOneMike @WalshFreedom Michael attended Trump University.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders @BernieSanders the true socialist living the capitalists dream..sold out to Hillary after the rigged pr… https://t.co/JQTHRwtaAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting that gold ring to match next szn . With all that smoke .. thats all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sl2016_sl @StromfieldAdvs @Sostraveluk @monstervoyage @Adventuringgal @MadHattersNYC @thethirstytales… https://t.co/8MnJsHKZia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victorlopezrico @Cuervomk @lopezobrador_ Beca de Porro de seguro sí le ha de haber tocado al macuspano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittnyreneeXO_ @katherrinemarie Yeah I don’t think they’re beautiful and powerful 😂 I hate them 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lion - Rumor Willis, monster - Cee Lo Green, peacock - Donny Osmond Rabbit - Joey F.   Bee - Patty LaBellle #maskedsinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov @Chrisconsrv1776 They voted against it but they don’t have the votes to end it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the actual fuck do you keep making plans with me and then ditch me EVERY time. I deserve better than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoiled with this Dominican treat. My fave mangu con bacalao 😏 @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/MMXequlnCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[But like she said.. it took 7 years. Majority of illegal immigrants try to become legal but the system is fucked up… https://t.co/GJKFtZmmtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of Pub Days to you, @alysonrichman. Looking so forward to this read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, when you are cranky AF, the only thing that helps is playing fIREHOSE really loud and singing along. Tha… https://t.co/LomM1F1XRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump News Conference moved up from 4AM Eastern/4PM Hanoi time to now 2AM Eastern/4PM Hanoi time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry kids, Forrest stopped running a while ago... We love beautiful Utah. ❤️ A place where there are endless explo… https://t.co/mLY2SYJ5za]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beerfonz77 @Roosters Roosters is fucking nasty and DO NOT COMPARE CANES to that shit show]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think if he’s proven guilty he’s gonna have a bit of time to consider the fact that you reap what you sow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 Perhaps, you all just need to watch The news for a week, then report back to Bernie your findings, The… https://t.co/ZkHbxe4YSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattbc same place I get my check from Soros: Beautiful Lake Never Gonna Happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[u think u know someone until they lie to their mom about u..smh some people are so threatened]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday, Always praise! When you feel like it and when you don't! Get into a local church assembly. #pushthrough… https://t.co/wD1jbz9rIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[But WHERE can I find this?!?!? 😻😻😻😻😻😻😻😻😻😻😻🤤 never seen anything MORE beautiful 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[We healed the bay today. @healthebay napakettu7 #nomoreplastic @ Venice, California https://t.co/6mUqeeiw9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little boy who has my whole heart. Forever and ever ❤️ @JamieDawnPhoto1 @ Thunder Bay, Ontario https://t.co/fsyswDsQp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carnaval #ensenada #confetti en Riviera de Ensenada https://t.co/55jUX77jp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[every year my niece gives me a valentines day gift, and she knows I’ve been a little sad lately, so she handmade an… https://t.co/0F9u7ZgmCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FLOTUS: Agreed, the press needs to cover the opioid epidemic. I understand you spend some time in Palm Beach. Hav… https://t.co/g2aAPruScD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@democracynow No entiendo como ustedes se prestan para el juego de maduro. Cuantos venezolanos más deben morir para… https://t.co/2Z8U9JRklW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, Evening and Afternoon Worldwide to my Instagram, Facebook, MySpace, Twitter, Google, Snapchat, Pinter… https://t.co/2FBaMgp7yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathryndennison @WKRN Plus if kids don’t get their way or if a parent doesn’t buy them $500 tennis’s shoes or a ne… https://t.co/oTFfltCwdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little salty that people are bashing Mother Monster for trying to ruin a relationship and crossing lines. BRADLEY… https://t.co/02ZRI6XGIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff__thegoon I know man. We’ve all been here. We are gonna rage some pain away this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone compliments me and I flick my hair back know that I don’t do this sincerely. I have anxiety and for so… https://t.co/xaCpf9FeIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC And for anyone to trust them I'm sorry but you are a fool! Look at Puerto Rico!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You two make life so much sweeter 😊 #auntlife @ Walt Disney World https://t.co/Mpzks56l8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: Bernie’s platform is amazing and would help individuals debatably more than any other candidates… https://t.co/V18LdXZkui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great running into you a few moths back at our @World_Wildlife event @pcousteau and have an exciting opportunity wo… https://t.co/j1Xd77IIKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if baby goth has ugly feet. Mostly because she keep choosing to wear fucking white socks while be half nak… https://t.co/9fBhEEc2CN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joker fans: One of the happiest moments in life is when you find the courage to let go of what you cannot change. 💙… https://t.co/923ltovPkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my husband both working full time and being full time parents is hard work, no sleep, but so worth it at the end of the day 💸💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 1:21 am and I’m thinking about him. Yes him,,, Louis Tomlinson https://t.co/h4yi8saEcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“attachments YOU created” ..... this is so important. https://t.co/giyTTd0jev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @corpsejackx thank you for always being an amazing friend and one of my OG supporters I love ya! And… https://t.co/zXd8vnGjDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now playing on Starfire's Country Music w/Trisha at Night Wave Radio (https://t.co/OI5xIMNO2M) @nightwaveradio1 Gre… https://t.co/RyuHY8BHRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when mfs text me I just wanna be like...  Idgaf... I'm taking a nap  🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Buffoon -not true and been repairing with funds from the Obama administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently #childrenofadamband visited the #Trenton365Show for a #recordedperformance and #interview  . This 10 piece… https://t.co/UOlCEZSo0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the story has many different beginnings it always ends the same: me with a cracked iPhone screen wondering wh… https://t.co/bBCdfjWBaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Diva's Headquarters in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/SZehDvzqtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardyBloodNut Honestly I’m thinking about it. Festivals are not usually my thing but I am thinking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us remember that this is how we succeed. Let us stop stepping on other women to forward ourselves out of insecu… https://t.co/S7HGXCsaKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the upside, that means it's time for a new bus read, and I have plenty of books waiting to fill the position.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolf744 @eduardodeamaya @JSaintPastour Ud se  contradice, si fuera sincero, no estaría abogando por el voto nulo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ala_Camillae My first thought was gorging yourself on sexual partners, like a sex demon or Bilquis in American God… https://t.co/zIueCFZCVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl This is performance art, right? Isn’t this the part where you cover your face with Marshmallow Fluff an… https://t.co/M4R4itaFvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so much natural hair in this venue rn. I absolutely stan. @ThisIsTheRead]]></document></documents></author>