<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure what improved (sleep quality, quality food intake , fatigue management) but I felt fantastic this morn… https://t.co/4dqCYE303a]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Nashville Lady Eagles vs Greenbrier TONIGHT at 7PM!!! @scorejammer @SportsNashville @MainStreetPreps… https://t.co/ClP3qzy8eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah that sounds about right sweet dreams everyone 💤 😴 🛌 goodnight @ Lebanon, New Jersey https://t.co/5eKpr2GxI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TueElungJensen @Michael_RM @DalGren @FaithNaff https://t.co/lfwHqjUsGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I mentioned a few days ago in my story, ignite has brought me on board the creative team and I’m pretty damn exc… https://t.co/kcMyoxH0Cr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo si realmente es necesario tener que ir a hacer trabajo en equipo, o seguir durmiendo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump you are such an embarrassment to the United States. There is absolutely nothing you could do to save yourself… https://t.co/IJ2KvkV8Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy...baby almost got hit and I’m sure that dude in the green got hit.  https://t.co/AdeZQ0cPZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from last eve's fabulous #ClemensBusch Riesling dinner. #naturalwine #MoselRiesling #winepairing #wineislove… https://t.co/zbqHbefXml]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is not true. He did have 54% of white female votes according to CNN. Yeah, there wasn’t a larger turnout compa… https://t.co/ZI1rTdT9Nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BfloHealthAtty No one expected Buffalo to make the playoffs, most media I’ve talked to set the bar from at 85 poin… https://t.co/wQoiMNd9Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how you talk values when the President talked about grabbing pussy and not paying taxes]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key is the Padres can’t stop at Machado. They have to commit to signing supplemental free agents to compliment… https://t.co/3RFCL9Qfg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe some clarification needs to be made as this comment is talking about possible future not factual present.  Th… https://t.co/toVW2Sty8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Change the locks. Arrest them both at the airport. Put Nancy in charge now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does sen sanders wife get a pass on bank fraud and everyone else goes to prison ? Interesting !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Honeymoon 2. Born to Die 3. Paradise 4. Ultraviolence 5. Lust for Life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshua_in_AZ @clevelanddem @eriknichols73 @williamlegate @PressSec Exactly]]></document><document><![CDATA[green day’s american idiot. opens tonight. @ Forbes Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/eyVniI7ESg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dedbutdrmng Skulls are the decorating accent that never goes out of style.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Back9Ben You may be on to something. Played a doozy of a par-5 17th today. Forecaddie said matches get insane on t… https://t.co/nrBj77x4yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A stunning finding that should reassure students &amp; leave fancy colleges questioning many things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atención, Atención... 📈💯📈      Hoy zoom  1 hr antes que lo habitual  .  Disculpen las molestias!!! en Mexicali, Baj… https://t.co/OFZfwHQT0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget the little children being snuck across the border to be sold as sex slaves...THAT’S the worst!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine FBI MULLER CRAZY AS HELL..LOOKS LIKE SOOM OFTHEFBI WILLBEFACEING LIFE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PozitiveVizion @markneefuzz @noNAMEtoby @jahdoughboy @Unsucchiacazzi @HulklingAwYeah @Charles_Savio @broyea… https://t.co/KZFuQGOz9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Fiel @lithium66 @WorldsendNow @jockosrocket @PassiValerio @justfordreamsxx @SAMCRO1968 @Ts_Lolita… https://t.co/xk6Hmd06Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUMP Making America really shitty for U.S. and our troops while enriching evil corporate oligarchs like himself an… https://t.co/9uvEJKZGNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson The party that thinks the world will end in 12 years if we don’t convert everything to wind power sho… https://t.co/K959N5sgx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gilbert bloops a single into right field, State has 1st and 2nd with no outs for Rowdey Jordan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. —Michael Jordan  From the Daily Quo… https://t.co/HLWrALJBc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Apple #skyline #NYC  🍏 🇺🇸 @ New York City, N.Y. https://t.co/wmX8eI4Hoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marybar41015771 @eugenegu @AnnieOhAnnieOh @realDonaldTrump What do you believe Mary? That there is no creator no h… https://t.co/w8hlaMttyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ljjones_95 @BiggerTen Probably time to find another one. Indiana for the BTT &amp; maybe a team like auburn for the NCAA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 6812 Augustine Way #Charlotte #NC  #realestate https://t.co/LkEKBn2lUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we wait, scheduled delivery is at 8:30, let’s see if it goes down on time. #deliveryday #SentaraObici]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rodney3810 @GrahamAllen_1 @AOC @greennewdeal What is favoritable about that?   Where there is high speed rail air… https://t.co/FSzRP2Vk8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just paid @RiebelFarms69 to put my clean clothes away. That’s what level of ‘staying on the couch all day’ I’m at. https://t.co/K6uY6asHib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take away it’s broadcast license as a threat to the norms of what the mission of a cable outlet should be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of good - and inspiring! - things going on in Albuquerque today.  @RepDebHaaland is making some history (and h… https://t.co/3rKJRjQxvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbieBarstool has always been my favorite writer there.  Rapper Denzel Curry's Cover Of "Bulls On Parade" Blew My… https://t.co/VRqDSCQmYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛑👇🏼👇🏼🛑 In order to be filled with the Holy Spirit you have to empty yourself of yourself to make room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiseryHighlight @TTonyhenderson @RantingGAPeach @pretendmunchkin https://t.co/ZWgaTR7sCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you don’t get what you want and end up feeling like a failure #currentmood https://t.co/ePUt8OZzqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kluttz_fan Not saying it won’t be Dodgers, but I can still see someone coming out of nowhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@descifradocom Confirmado: En concierto X Maduro también tocarán: Los tambores de Tocoron Las flautas del FARC  Los… https://t.co/r1rLoWuJxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it isn’t renewed, I simply won’t renew #Netflix. I’m not joking. Like the original, the reboot is relevant telev… https://t.co/E1fRc9JdXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Streetcar has a sequential cluster... @ The Matisse https://t.co/vEcf7MNowB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tilly01215337 Hola from Nuevo Mexico. Hope your day was great. Just waking up to light rain here. Good for our dry desert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/o7jokphWLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerroldTimes It was like two titans playing chess. Neither wanted to give an inch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carinasimone @joncabotc Also, he said we tweet each other too much for people who barely see each other. He’s coming for our brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second day in a row I've gotten up and forgot to wear my fitbit. Damn, I even walked outside to get the paper🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRIPMOBB Not gonna lie. Thinking about going. Probably wont cause HARD Summer but Hella females in their feels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith Looks like @PatrickMahomes got the last laugh #ChiefsKingdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReliableSources @Olivianuzzi And there you go folks, today's line-up of "Unreliable Sources" right here on Reliabl… https://t.co/NpIiEp2DIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgay Same. Lately, it seems so confrontational and it immediately sours my mood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Sen. Jeff Merkley opts out of Democratic presidential contest and will run for reelection to Orego… https://t.co/ude1cREdbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSHSCougarsXCTF @CoachClarkTF That Coach Clark doing what Coach Clark do!   Don’t be surprised, y’all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamVanderbilt @salewis27 @Harlan Trump lies so much you can’t believe anything that he says. I only believe what he actually does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Morning Superstars..!! 🌞🐯🎸🍒 Have a Stupendous Saturday..!! 🥞🙏💞📱 Don't use the weekend as an excuse to give up… https://t.co/cDk0amm4Ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see what this is about #haMILTOn @ SHN Orpheum Theatre https://t.co/603Y3yXhqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great dude, always a great laugh 😂 #tylersbarbershop #stgeorge #stgeorgeutah #utahbarber #stgeorgebarber… https://t.co/iZUxR8DOm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna read “You Gotta Play Hurt” cover to cover on this dark day  RIP Dan]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😩😩😩😩y the fuck these lil fucking dogs so aggressive. America scared of Pitts. What about these bullshits. They… https://t.co/VIXTOf0HRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind rTumpy getting rolled by a kid that should be locked away for his crimes against humanity. Hard earned… https://t.co/RbjOZrKTiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @WestYorksPolice America should think soberly on immigration policy. Thankful for my time in Europe befo… https://t.co/FKQxe8szgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceWolfChi @DanProft Economic stagnation ambivalence to decaying neighborhoods black “leaders” fealty to the 5th… https://t.co/k8sTXlI8RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmabo @ericgeller Also is he tan? It's like he just got back from vacation. So much better than his cyber zombie usual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxing4free @EditinKing Idiots like that kid don't learn from anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanucksJays @botchford @BasketballPhil Are you arguing that he’s terrible?  I feel like you’ll probably lose that debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilar_rod La izquierda comunista en general adoctrina a sus hijos desde muy chicos. Todo a pura envidia, odio , me… https://t.co/R8qrse8JhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrell64542980 @shiftershifty @sok2nvme @PatriotXr @coach_weaver @DanaBashCNN DHS ? 😂😂 I mean its not a secret you should know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited to see you in studio Lenny boy. @DinardoLenny #BringDonBack @DonOrsillo @NESN @Jerry_Remy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum How about @Scaramucci saying @realDonaldTrump could send a perfectly spiraling football through a tire..… https://t.co/GvkMjRcmvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msmithpoker @ThePokerBoss Ya I agree with you. And that’s definitely a good point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking good on @News12LI @stonybrookalum @WeatherGeoff with @jackielukas . And how fitting, he’s got his… https://t.co/2pemZ1n1Fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drivers! #selfie #driveteam Presenters! #frc #firstrobotics #waterburydistrict #omgrobots @team178 #nefirst @ Water… https://t.co/MF9e5j90pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klzdad3 I’m not sure what motivates offensive linemen. They are a strange breed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[we’re living in ashton kutcher’s world and we’re all getting punk’d eventually]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalSports @SnapFlow69 Rapport blew this one  You like him.   hes done this thing before  hes off more than he is on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrettRuby Thank you for the follow, I look forward to your Tweets.🌊 #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure okay don’t be creepy #midnightash #catsofinstagram @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/Qm3UXOP9eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo this man luisbermudez769 is trying to kill me with the new shit he got me doing! I’m not gonna quit though! 🤬 @… https://t.co/hnwdtkei1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you think we’ll see the actual phoenix again in #DarkPhoenix? the promotional material so far kind of leads me t… https://t.co/57pCaScIGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin @JussieSmollett You should reconsider your friendships. Bad judge of character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CCPS_WHS_OWLS dealt with a different 'brand of basketball' in Saturday afternoon's Class 3A West Region final aga… https://t.co/aS2uii6IDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm...maybe a better question, legal or illegal pitch? Hard to tell nowadays. Wouldn’t be called until the playoff… https://t.co/7sQv7q0Y15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im Off The Pack I Could Not Wait My Shawty In Trouble Here Come Alexander The Great]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Vara's Lounge in Houston, TX https://t.co/Xq4ac57LlX https://t.co/ew9SMNuyS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSpeedMcNeil @Donna_Barr @ColleenDoran  you three have been a guiding light in my life (and now, my a Daughters) f… https://t.co/F24inl6NBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora que no hay luz me pregunto si se van a cancelar las bodas, 15años, bautizos, etc que estaban pautadas para el… https://t.co/HqkNH4ADe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claylude @heyyrandi @CopierCollin @AstrosBill @mhg76 @OxLyles @rrfosho72 @iam_workman @morasee @BobChoate54 Think… https://t.co/3P717nnBNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I predict democrats will find a way to take his campaign contributions. Wait and see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristinalaila1 @LatAmFr @gatewaypundit "Monarchy"? I think we need a new term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tastes like a true Mexican mocha chocolate coffee. No real mango flavor to speak of, but that's Ok. - Drinking a Sc… https://t.co/GuAnxUJ7ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pczapla @Cuddlyhugbear Money is the root of all evil. Blizzards are the root of all things good in this world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The all star game is a complete joke! It’s just a showboat game with no glimmer of defense. LAME-O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skillsy75 @cmace30 @Bradm14 @wildthingz80 I remember when I was in Bridgestone Arena and these guys behind me duri… https://t.co/SoYjAPLW2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Week of vacation with terrible weather is over. Now it’s beautiful but I have to go to work in a few hours and coul… https://t.co/41wovFaYJ8]]></document></documents></author>