<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Best wishes to our @CentennialMBB_ team as they compete today in an @TheOCAA playoff qualifying game vs… https://t.co/ef2xpvx1j0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_ei8ht @Ginger_Lyn_66 @readnallthetime @SharonLynnCald2 @CunningSq16 @Cha51brolll19 @_monzon322 @strom_annette… https://t.co/AU4luoClrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PT109S I think just typical delay and perhaps related to making sure they respond to concerns fully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeggieTart @paula_prplmrmd @hutchleah @robinmarty The church is certainly not above reproa h and has noooo moral a… https://t.co/JPANNFkeq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me if you want me to give you all my time, I wanna make it good for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lvlupvideo You are THE best!!! So ready for Tour Finals next weekend!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Librarian says she was fired after reporting her son was being bullied: https://t.co/MKIBmjn0cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is 3 kids to stay in the house you think the FBI care shooting military weapons into the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EVargasTV @jaketapper My daughter Ava showed this to me today with a huge smile on her face. Love this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Unbelievable. A black guy who burgles a candy bar gets more time than Paul Manafort got.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeLong22 @GroupHomepage @Janetjo53678621 @fedupcitizen16 @riley_momma @AnnThacker2 @HLAurora63 @Lori_B_777… https://t.co/um2AmjNXb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello yes, on this women’s day I just wanted to say publicly, I’m a talent recruiting god. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe we live in a time where social media is available for us to reach out, connect, and associate with… https://t.co/iFNMKdLIJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 9th birthday, Ethan! I love you so much and I’m so happy and blessed to be your momma! 💕☺️👩‍👦👪🎧🎮🎂🤳🏻👨🏻‍💻👷🏻‍♂️… https://t.co/JoUjUXUNIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I am a college student and yes I will be fan-girling so hard at a Jonas brothers soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the music, @MtJoyBand and @michiganderband! @thebluebirdbar https://t.co/4Gm3fNu0E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp just watched 1st time your CNN show due to my love for @MeghanMcCain   I’m conservative mostly but open to… https://t.co/Kdvl9sTJJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This wild wind blowing thru Cincinnati is so unusual, and I love it. It feels so alive and I enjoy the sound of it… https://t.co/czOwrfTZRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Only Florida would elect someone like you. #SHAME Jesus wept.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be in Cali in less than 3 weeks &amp; I can’t wait 🌸☀️ my baby daddy really out did himself a this one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes if I could get my bachelors and masters at a community college I definitely would have oh wait I can’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful Craftsman style home has almost 2400 square feet, 4 bd/ 3 ba and seasonal lake views. It features ha… https://t.co/TdkFa3HI3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullock_baker @woahanass @krassenstein @ilmgal @GeneralFlynn2 @TheDemocrats Now shoo! Go play with your slow, Clos… https://t.co/Qnbnp7x74D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel a huge part of the marketing for this movie is making everyone believe and love their chemistry. They did gr… https://t.co/dHOCDDDx9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn’t find this out until this year and i legit have the tetons tattooed on me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I’d be here, drinking @koolaid out of crystal glasses, eating beef jerky out of bags, watching @boburnham on Netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of 7 nominated by @TheOfficialMrG. One of my favorites. Now I nominate @jscottyes1 https://t.co/r5UcXgBSGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay Binge watching Hells Kitchen😳 I’m on season 8. I’m shook but also a better cook now 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[80 degrees with a breeze. 🙌🏼🖤✨ #floridaliving #mymoodyflatlay @ Forest City, Florida https://t.co/8MSHuNhZlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_RomayMua @GSLEcouncil DM me your email address so I can email them and cc you, please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kausmickey Go online to. https://t.co/XFLQzggOj8 and email the President. Tell him to veto the bill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyNY4Ever @JDHardin1 Congulations JDHardin! On Reaching 10k!!  Way To Go!🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko My favorite pokemon type is fire because they are strongest and my favorite non legendary pokemon is mew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r0ckar0lla Also I have more on my insta                   Dragon_Art_EH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at CROSSMARK? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and informat… https://t.co/9HIAh5e73K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have this much fun at work is it even considered work?! Days like this remind me why I do what I do.… https://t.co/VnvulJsVHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun and creative way to help students make connections!! ~I loved the nostalgia too🍯]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:33 PM Central. #StarFall. We are gorgeous. Let Us not look at ourselves as victims though in their eyes we are p… https://t.co/rw6LgnJH7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sandal always leaves me in awe because of how low some people can stoop (cough trump)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KleinTrottel @derekkerton @blvdr @ToddHibbs @r0wdy_ @ashleyfeinberg @sarahjeong Yes! And deserve to be represented… https://t.co/TcZEuqagAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just got invited to a facebook event called “vape swap” and i think i’m having a stroke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "Noncertified Nursing Aid-1" at Laramie Care Center by asking for referrals. It's a… https://t.co/FFSuryooO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #AllStars4 winner @RuPaulsDragRace @LatriceRoyale #AlwaysandForever https://t.co/DzzXOMJ37b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to worry! Once the #Millennials grow up, start making mortgage payments, etc., they'll think more like #Boomers… https://t.co/wSi6TZoVpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofballgeorge @KellsBellsSC @onew1tchyw0man @patriot_billy @Patriot988 @PatriotJeweler @PaulieD55 @Pawleybaby1999… https://t.co/ozr1iWFMTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldnorthbear @newmanjam @huntershea1 That’s an awesome one! I’m so excited for the TV adaptation that’s coming!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejacksonlive @realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Literally not a rhetorical question!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night, Tweeps. Tomorrow (meaning after wake-up time) we start the #WomensHistoryMonth series in the format ala… https://t.co/bY6DQXS8NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting.  So, next time you get a scratch or a cut are u gonna smear it all Over your face? You look like a scar… https://t.co/eS7n8NG364]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I believe our actions are products of our biology (hormones, genetics ect.) and our circumstances (who we are rais… https://t.co/Q3orAOYrS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please vote and help a sister decide: If you had the chance to attend the UK 🏀 game tonight (2.5 hours away, starts… https://t.co/sPrfewIHUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitchhh i hate traveling by car during the day. i’ve passed like 10 cops and i’ve been on that road for an hour and a half]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeCalderon @CartonCalderon Gracias a ti Paco Calderón, y ¡muchas felicidades!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asiwome_ Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ_Cox @CalebJHull @DonaldJTrumpJr I’m in SoCal and every station ran it nonstop!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill So many problems in our country right now &amp; this is what this idiots worried about!Poor excuse for a leader!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_so_soft Still feeling pretty lousy this morning unfortunately but thank you, I appreciate the concern!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who didn't get struck by lightning when she walked into Church? THIS GIRL! Yes I got Mom to take a selfie too… https://t.co/oSU0d7E20n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday mornings with Revit... that’s all . . . . . #architecture #structure #revit #bim #thestruggleisreal… https://t.co/y0rkEBtZno]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lehigh County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/gPGXuIhbqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresBillMacohe My flight leaves at 9:30 am or otherwise I’d put it off to the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesvarlack Because the world has changed. You can't do what you always did because our children would not be abl… https://t.co/MtQwevWtHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I smell smoke or something burning, only emergency lights are on and my train is creeping to a halt. Lawd plz don’t… https://t.co/iuElR6yExi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m telling you this movie and scene really hit different. spoke to my 8 year old soul or somethin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday Jr, beautiful peeps! #SpreadKindness ♥️☀️ https://t.co/H5oFooIEUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to see Coach Goff inducted into the RPS Hall of Fame last night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Superfluous Nomenclature by @wbwbeer at @wbwbeer — https://t.co/aJf6lKNQ4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine getting on al gores internet to yell at a woman in all caps saying “yOU aRe thE rEAsOn My faMiLy bRoKe Up”… https://t.co/NLQ08Ibp3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can't wait to here Michael Cohen this week tell us what a crook you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who talk loud during lecture are mad distracting. If you want attention that bad, go to the club or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lucky to have this extraordinary woman in my life, my daughter in law, Clara Kwon @kwonzabonanza standlandscape… https://t.co/05SUsgimmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have any reason to stay here anymore so like.... I really want to go home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabulous @WDFosterGraham1!!!  Love your energy!!  Meet my amazing friend @DearDean22 🥳🙌🏻🤩 You two should connect yo… https://t.co/Aw1vYlSu20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though , it’s awesome to have a gym partner ... but they act like a emo high school kid ... like.. I literally… https://t.co/qzOPulxiV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what these words mean; does this mean he has the ability to leave but hasn’t decided to yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im always stuck doing tavos shit this better be the last ticket he gets bc these defensive drivers classes are long and boring 🤬🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @cmafoundation for all their support! Without their donations and support the students would not have a… https://t.co/D6MuYr8aj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XgGamergX_YT @scopely @YahtzeeBuddies You know if he did it to me, he probably did it to countless other women as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchAngelNeko I got an extra S rank classic Yokai to trade for him! Just let me know when you would like to trade… https://t.co/9AgYELenJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #InternationalWomansDay my bestie @Samantha_Lacey is talking about her report on fighting climate change by addr… https://t.co/lF9eJAHpPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARedPillReport @IWasHrren Does it matter that they have assignment surgery, they are still genetically men! They a… https://t.co/3r7LaU9pDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the one lying and you are a disgrace to America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrie4502 @Travvie_Dearest Me too so glad I’m outta that game and on the bench]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating art with people who ARE art is my favorite hobby. https://t.co/eWD5Nghwtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney Princess 10K  #MNadventures #run #rundisney #AliceInWonderland #Disney #WaltDisneyWorld https://t.co/zyFYRYZsQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cat's name is Potato Salad.  That is all.  #Meow #FortCollinsCatRescue #Adoptable #KittyCleaningLady @ PetSmart https://t.co/xye9xcKA9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericamgoodwin @iancron @SuzanneStabile @TypologyPodcast Started @TypologyPodcast this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonatha97947998 @PatGrant7777 @lr3031 @MiluRamalho https://t.co/nWgZJ4z65Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this Molly feeling @JengTheVirgin @SimplyKim143 @patriciaxyee  😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the Morning to the World 🌍 Believe in Yourself and your Dreams 💪🏾💪🏾💪🏾#motivation #dedication #determination… https://t.co/gruc7lcfz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I use this for work? “They are nocturnal I am not!” @SirenTV @FreeformTV #Siren]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t been to Ohio and had Jones salt and vinegar chips, go ahead and do that. It will change you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paging Dr. Reynolds you are a GREAT friend even if you don't feel like it #NewAmsterdam @jockosims]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delainemathieu Isn’t this what parents deal with when they just want their kids to take one bite of their vegetables? 🍅🥬🥦]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍❤❤🌹🥀 #12Pink #1Red2 I LOOOOOOOVE FLOWERS ❤❤ #BirthdayGirl https://t.co/aBmjCVrhpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was stopped just now on my afternoon dog walk by a man coming from across the park asking a favor. I immediately… https://t.co/pznMt5SXGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaWiggins Well, delaying isn’t ALWAYS an option for various reasons, but hopefully it won’t be necessary. Also… https://t.co/jSkNksmKCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t know why they did this to her.” The family of the Cobb County woman, who was found dead in the woods, reac… https://t.co/APqhlChnOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter! We need a new, affordable shower curtain for a bathroom with black and white tile. Can you please help me… https://t.co/G5klc2K78x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cee_Kay_ astro twitter over here! 💓 personal so far but working on small content to post too]]></document></documents></author>