<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The Floozies throwing down at Vinyl! #PassTheGood #VinylMusicHall #TheFloozies #Pensacola #Florida @ Vinyl Music Ha… https://t.co/FVNx4DA5wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haymarketbooks Were they not asked the question; or was it decided that nobody cares what they think anyway? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little bit ago @morganprice got me thinking and wondering if teams actually gain an advantage by pulling their go… https://t.co/9MPamhNcJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferm_q Any analysis can be misused. Its imperfection in practice isn’t a very strong argument against it’s va… https://t.co/1lNMZOOphv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougBurgum it’s never to late to admit you’re wrong. Can you imagine what conditions would be like in rural North… https://t.co/lGfdZpF40r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arensb @JuiceCupSQ @AOC Never once have I said taxes are bad. Paying 60% on taxes is dumb. That's the whole point I'm making]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailykos Disgusting and un-American.  Where the fuck is Mueller?  #hobomessiah  Enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rinconderufo Uno ganó el mundial y el otro no esa es la gran diferencia]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’re trying to impress Maverick, @EagerThomas and the rest of the staff. But worry about them never while… https://t.co/x889ywdROu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Daniel Giese My age is over a quarter I was born with lots of questions I like to help people answer the… https://t.co/muxD7B24Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @WCCO memory of February 2019, snow removal #MyMorning https://t.co/lRBvdq7oOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never given anyone a solid reason not to like me that’s just how it goes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMAckerman @LeonKrauze @AmbJohnBolton @SenSanders Socialism is a cancer !!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This doesn’t get old. #SECSD19  #ButTheyDid 🏆🏆🏆🏆#UnfinishedBusiness https://t.co/zU5vCkqv74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA I’ve been kicked off a college campus for political speech.   In a GOP stronghold.   They actually told us… https://t.co/sAn3F2gzix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_bennett_1   He was smart to  go to Philadelphia to avoid state income taxes.  All California, NY, and IL tea… https://t.co/mDfGCEwZnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1TimothyA @BadgerMHockey They can't call a penalty on that replay situation, only take away the goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows we know that you and 45 are best friends, you should never call anybody a lair. I’m sure you got the hint liar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newmusicvideo of me making live beats with my Maschine and Korg Controllers. You can find more videos and free mus… https://t.co/JLSwEboylH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Massacooramaan I got offered money couple years ago and i still said nah. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyomingpd @BuzzFeed I am assuming that an article titled "37 outdoor things NOT to do while Mother Nature reminds… https://t.co/C1abf5L8nK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardoHq &amp; of course cue lacey evans theme the sassy southern bell lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_December_86 I’m so glad everything worked itself out with you two. Love wins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up this morning to the sweet sounds of The Allman Brothers Band. #RockSolidAlbumADay2019 https://t.co/LdleJMnjEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theupsttrs @BerlinerinPoet @bihhimacow @AbuYoshi @Jellis1snv Or he could simply go to the dean and report the teac… https://t.co/CQfx42wGDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is this even possible? Why is the @GOP so dead-set in protecting a system that allows this to happen? Zero taxe… https://t.co/zUjOcpWyHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/fJdifGUq8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to see NKU break into the win column against tough pitching . Good job Norse !]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t do this work alone. We’re all in this thing together. @Joe_Sanfelippo #maesp19]]></document><document><![CDATA[He had the money. He could get help. Truth is it was a political stunt. Had nothing to do with drugs. Prosecute his… https://t.co/AWVlIiO4So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/Pjj4gR3o1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SouthwestAir! What a pleasant surprise! https://t.co/7ubbWRS6SH]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of third, Cumberland Valley leads Wilson 42-41 #berksgameday #upsetwatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was just offered by #Bama Saturday and he discussed that offer here: https://t.co/Je5GmXJjjr @Corey_Bender]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russwest44 is 🗑. But sure let’s talk about how only fans are the problem. For really threatening someone and his w… https://t.co/3JocwMrRc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArashMarkazi They’ll still finish 3rd at best in the NLW. I just don’t see Manny being worth more than maybe 5-10… https://t.co/JHaJsUIVPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Red by HyunA on Apple Music. #kpop #EDM https://t.co/u86O1dI0Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTMarlin77 Yep. I like to put value on middle relievers, since many are better than lots of “closers”. I don’t lik… https://t.co/RR1fdWEKR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently forcing down a beer I hate because I bought it and I’m too cheap and stubborn to throw it away]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK #OneTreeHill #TV #Pilot #Script #ChadMichaelMurray, #JamesLafferty #SophiaBush #HilarieBurton #PaulJohannson    https://t.co/6xdLPxVZ7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Bedroom 2 Bath Great Location Watertown , Newly renovated, parking https://t.co/UfIb7i4oF1 #watertownapartments… https://t.co/izeAtF4TeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy that my old self showed up in #AlitaBattleAngel . It’s an amazing movie!! Go see it!! #alita… https://t.co/Dlyy09HDny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Costco Cortez is dumb. NY was not “giving” $3B in cash to Amazon.  They were merely giving  $3B in a tax breaks to… https://t.co/yxZLXcozqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[298-200 S Lucerne Blvd 298-200 S Lucerne Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90004 https://t.co/NFnZXx1FPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future is mine! Check out Acorns Spend at https://t.co/iosayOjguc #GrowYourOak https://t.co/LiqYsY8kHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InspectorNerd Last part - reaaally blows my mind that thinking still exists at all. Kids definitely have trouble s… https://t.co/0p6HfKm8o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brittany_Geneva @AmericanAir @Delta I think it’s the “Boeing 737 MAX-8” and Delta doesn’t operate any of that particular aircraft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cdnpoli I’m forwarding this to @cafreeland. Just in case the “minor league imperialist” has not read the UN Charte… https://t.co/tQWpXYFlaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first 60 minutes are amazing. The last 30 are gratuitous and boring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth on growing your channel https://t.co/q91uFVSujk via @YouTube https://t.co/VYm775wxSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few of the new comics that came out this week that are on my pile...  #Avengers #WonderTwins #Superfriends… https://t.co/8dwxhZcXpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPSHelp so why exactly does my order say it was delivered and signed for but i definitely never received anything… https://t.co/gqOTvBfs6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stand seein a bad bitch, then you look down and she has some Reebok classics on 🤦🏾‍♂️.NO!.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I’m playing a game called HQ Trivia. You should play too. Use my code 'Hey, I’m playing a game called HQ Trivi… https://t.co/T8BRnG9k0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay in 1936 the world’s first superhero #ThePhantom, a cartoon strip by artist #LeeFalk, made his first appe… https://t.co/AG6xKHmi45]]></document><document><![CDATA[#funfact Jussie Smollett was in Mighty Ducks.  The things I learned when I listen to @katienolan https://t.co/Ts598lohiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Vietnam trip should put the collusion narrative to rest once and for all. Trump genuinely admires dictators li… https://t.co/zMRPe4Li0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was exactly this. Like I said not over the top but he wasn't joking about it. It was received well by Mejia also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, @JamieMauracher for your attention to this important road safety issue. https://t.co/FNrHYjTrAj #toronto #potholes]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/z62Hjg6wXg @KeithUrban @KeithUrbanFans I like your version a lot better. Thanks so much Keith! So I’ll… https://t.co/FOKnjX4A77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretBaier @benshapiro How can people not see the injustice of allowing this to happen and not do anything about it… https://t.co/wImuDZ0m7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do ya find it unusual that aide is for central America. The countries sending invasion force.. To ironic dems fundi… https://t.co/JK4oFZ8Xop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zcoh5 Color scheme alone gets them in the top 5 https://t.co/yjiueQiyhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep looking at that last @imoss38 shot and seeing... https://t.co/jq3eDPf013]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivien2112 @RushFamTourneys It’s the first glimpse of Alex Lifeson‘s  versatility. Good evening Vivien. I wouldn’t… https://t.co/4oPn5jW01I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeavyseT330 I'm mostly retired from Challenging People To Brawl-For-All matches on any sort of active basis. It's… https://t.co/N4ZrqQF1H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HankFox29  @LucyNolandFOX29  @KathyOrrFOX29 I think i wore the captain's hat better https://t.co/N3OCzVLDMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only people who should pay for reparations is the Democrat Party.  cc: @thecjpearson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed are they that keep his testimonies, and that seek him with the whole heart. Psalms 119:2 KJ… https://t.co/o7tRX32cw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[LINCOLN HAD A SECRETARY NAMED KENNEDY! KENNEDY HAD A SECRETARY NAMED LINCOLN!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blankkRL @eSportsBSU So cool yo see you all on stage! Thanks so much for making it out our way! Ggwp!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1933, año que Jimmie Foxx (Americana) y Chuck Klein ganaron la triple corona de bateo; única ocasión.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Representing ‘Bad Ash Cigar Co’ at the Atlanta Mission 5k for the Homeless @ Centennial Olympic Park https://t.co/aPDoQplq4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlynncarte Great call. Couldn’t agree more. I’d even be okay with penalty more severe....but for everyone. Johansen 10 games. Malkin 5. Etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeResistHim @welcomet0nature Well it's not a ewe. It's a spider. A lovely spider.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@No_Displace_IND @adamwren It will be interesting to see if Home Place being incorporated into Carmel will drive up… https://t.co/3FqfTtrVPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gelbach @jciv 1. Everyone on earth, including based on statements of public officials and former officials of Jim… https://t.co/r93VpwCTsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I am jealous of Giants fans for…They still have hard tickets   Mobile/print at home tickets are stup… https://t.co/7MK0V6xad7]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s literally a coordinated campaign going on at HCDE right now where someone, I can guess who, lined up taxpay… https://t.co/vfKeb4shEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealK_K Lmao yes. Or the perceived notion that you’re racist if you support trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikk15795488 @Dansgaming Again, that's corporate's choice. They chose to sell access to the "full game" to their p… https://t.co/4xgEyP4Oxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabyJuarez @GameOfThrones “Game of Thrones &amp; Chill” https://t.co/ixghxTLmT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ski jumpin in Brattleboro, Bubs is not impressed. #babynuge #smileyoreilly #brattleboro @ Brattleboro, Vermont https://t.co/sjDD5Ps2y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rather late; but, as my grandma taught me: “Better late than never since if never comes it is too late!”  A Squirre… https://t.co/sUyB8q4pd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadeaFamFuneral was a super #funnymovie and heart felt film about family! Check out #MadeaFamilyFuneral I loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan The past always has a way of coming back to find those things. You don't believe Cohen and there are a… https://t.co/tMelLRGUFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunt_Rob @Mikeb1961sports Best record in baseball in 81, but no playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m enrolling in a Roman Catholic University so I would like to actually get accepted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grrlpowercomic Dave, if Cora's ship can accommodate 80 crew and guests, why are 37 refugees being housed in temp s… https://t.co/g96A7JHmmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gorgeous townhouse is now open! Sat. 3/9/19 from 1-4pm.  4 bed, 3.5 bath, 2083 sq. ft. Two years old! 21401 Da… https://t.co/IierpEWM1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[This economy is arguably the best it has ever been, and yet Democrats HATE President Trump for it.  Employment oppo… https://t.co/iGbSCAWCSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #NorthWakeCounty on I-540 WB approaching Falls of Neuse Rd - Exit 14 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snacchinedges @BayleighDaily Are you insulting me by calling me Nikki lol , firsy my grandma called me that and it… https://t.co/dQG8ZQdPpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megh_wright @crushingbort Thank You. I feel ugh for sending this to someone. Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand your desire to stay on the pitch and I respect it, but if you showed that you were injured 2 min befor… https://t.co/DAij0j25MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are far too many people who have had steady employment since 2015 that Jason Kenney is lying to Albertans abo… https://t.co/99Zcl7YrYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look to get long $ES if it goes bid above 2787.50 or if the A.M. open is above 2787.50 and goes bid above the open.… https://t.co/0rCBdQWRlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilIrishGrin @realDonaldTrump Actually it’s not. Instead of calling the guy names throw some facts out there to r… https://t.co/anDBMI0mk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a night!!! @muse playing knights last was the fucking best!!! https://t.co/AGrXfNmWDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJonathanCain @ndccOrlando Found it on ndcc page: https://t.co/HTvzvH628E!!]]></document></documents></author>