<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tengo 19 años y no puedo comerme una bolsa de cheetos flaming hot de un jalón porque me arde todo mi estómago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Mini Back To The Future Reunion Happened At A Fan Convention' https://t.co/6GlPECe4Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJeffHudson Chat with us instead.  I’m either super fun or I will bore you so badly you will fall asleep. Either… https://t.co/ETGKCQNGwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: i'll leave early so I have plenty of time to park and get inside the Capitol.  The universe: no you won't. https://t.co/gG1hleBesV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah!  What a game! ⚾️🔥⚾️#thanksTitansforagreatwin @FullertonBSB @Sahidv04 and King Jairus! #teamtitan @csuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saddee2 @joshgriffith59 @YandR_CBS @YRInsider @CBSDaytime #YR. #FreeLilyAshby #LaneArmy #StrongerTogether]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soccer Playoffs continue as our Bears face off against JPII this Friday at noon at Clark East Stadium in Plano.  66… https://t.co/flkVG1STNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenToomey @phillydotcom So grateful only sanctuary city immigrants assault children. She says dripping sarcasm!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m very happy opening up about my male to female transgender identity. I’m no longer ashamed of who I am. In fact… https://t.co/q0Av9HiTem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaHannigan Join a critique group. It’ll give you the incentive to keep writing more pages. #writerscommunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjaime95 @LauraGrider_ I’m sorry hun! 😿 Well we are here for you, always. 💛 https://t.co/CqF3tWY5vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to run away and all I took with me was a single can of spaghetti-os. I only made it two blocks before I had… https://t.co/qmRAzkR1xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I advocate for a client and get everything I ask for &amp; more 🙌🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @Jose93571656 @roberta_lanzoni @AnaAndrade305 @gabryluce @ElbaklySami @SimySemsem @carolina_smal… https://t.co/9gRZSjPZND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reepal OMG thank you for the bowl cut comment! 😹😹😹 I prefer anime haircuts more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it sucks that i could never hold the attention span to read comic books but i can appreciate them and their influence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOOS ON THE BOARD!!! After a Logan Michaels double, Nate Eikhoff is able to score on a Duke miscue  Blue Devils lea… https://t.co/SdYBlcELzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwoodall79 @ATCanonymous 🔊@jwoodall79 Say it louder so the people in the back can hear! 👏👏👏 If ATs expect respect… https://t.co/WSjEpfN26B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Wrong flag. He needs to be hugging this one. https://t.co/TAiCg1HPKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I think he’s a crafty old turtle who wants to punish trump for th shutdown realizing th DJT veto won’t b… https://t.co/nQgAFgOjvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this laughable there's something wrong with you. The Very Best of You Had One Job Meme - Snappy P… https://t.co/296MjYLvB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMorgster @ETClubHQ Morgan! Did you ever see the 30 for 30 on The Boz?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I take Kypreos' 'insider takes' with at all times. https://t.co/9bqDZVtjgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revisando mi Messenger y morí de risa con esto !!!! NASTY 😹🤢 https://t.co/8nyve1zWrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[AWE Board Meeting. #womeninevents #eventprof #eventprofs @ Mandarin Oriental, Washington D.C. https://t.co/CEgAOwqWEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennifer60182 @KaraLandgrebe @G17Esiason Amen Jennifer! And I’m of the opinion that God picks the BEST parents for His special little ones!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trapped inside a #Seaworld San Diego ride for hours.  "A couple of times my daughter was crying I had to calm her d… https://t.co/zzRfAS5mET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to this gal...my mom Lynette L. Olson who passed her real estate exams and who is all done with cla… https://t.co/4HhomaILSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[GREAT! I'm crying bcuz I'm so happy!! He would be POTUS now! Imagine how much GOOD #Sanders2020 would have done for… https://t.co/kV9HENnOQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man. Another @labattusa Buffalo Pond Tourney is in the bag. We won our 3rd game 22-17 today and finished 2-1. No… https://t.co/jeYYF01X3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec Poor Laura. Everyone hates her. Even the righties. https://t.co/btLZUPCrpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pappiness I am just happy to know there IS a line!!!! I was really beginning to wonder!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Graton Resort &amp; Casino - @playgraton in Rohnert Park, CA https://t.co/4OTr6JnRjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Except his hair has never looked that good. Lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get mad when my internet is slow like is that’s going It go any faster 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historysandoval @RoniMacD @stacyyung It’s sooo true! I just wish I could be there! https://t.co/Z8Z00lBl1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like my Valentines outfit??? Yup this is how I’m spending my valentines evening..... with a kettle bell workout wit… https://t.co/pCgCf5THjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itzbryan20 happy birthday!! thanks for making my girl so happy ;) don’t party too hard 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24newstime @SteveJSTL @oldbaldeagle @Onlyknockme @lp398vc @Trish24382029 @Patriot_Mom_17 @JohnMcL94552489… https://t.co/FeFWfzoPWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer    Win $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/47uIfzCvfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if @Kehlani and @thegreatkhalid put out a song together ..... 🤩💭]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a special place in the gym for the people who pick up weights WAY too heavy for them, pick it up on… https://t.co/SHDGnGR0Ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Please stop calling her Alabama Mom. She may have lived here for a while but we don’t want her in Ala… https://t.co/Xq6U3uXANR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGowdySC son I wish you were there today questioning colon I mean Towing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me you are not impressed with the performance of these Tesla vehicles on snow and ice and I will tell you I do… https://t.co/atcDWVAIO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does she have to be so damn pretty... like... it’s not fair. Oh and I’m also trying her Starbucks drink today a… https://t.co/4QuaC5yx0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want 2 see what true, authentic learning looks like? Look HERE! Bird kids worked w/ Henrico kids 2 show the world t… https://t.co/R0Ht1C6CbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect breakfast of fresh khobz, olive oil, and honey we got on the side of the road near the little middle Atlas… https://t.co/MBEBayvQWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree! This needs to stay alive! Crimes against some seem to fade without resolution or public outcry. That needs… https://t.co/jZSquMB8wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACLU This exemplifies how America deals with problems - *after* they occur rather than take the less expensive rou… https://t.co/Cp9OTvSNrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full on dreaming about my return visit next month to @MontagePB resort. The view from this bar overlooking the brid… https://t.co/pRCbyctAGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tybrodylogan @thecoachkj @KennyBattle33 @KendallG13 @stephenbardo Happy you handed it to Bruce Pearl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loudlearning Assessments in kindergarten are fine. They are a useful tool to use in teaching young children. But a… https://t.co/e48zAzykhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas you have been amazing back to New York for a few hours now then home time ✈️ already excited about getting ba… https://t.co/qaA2piTWcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaAn10TV @petescalia @AshleeBaracy @MollyBrewerTV @LauraBorchers1 @DGCrutcher @LSnowden @MaryPo10TV @Todd_M_Ward @Kirasic_Park @10TV 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been using my walking desk more. Today, I walked back-to-back hour meetings. Best part? When the ‘mill automat… https://t.co/bvy1iXLZUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find one of your besties at the library🙌 Squad goals indeed #lfk #seawitch @ Lawrence Public Library https://t.co/pIaeEmG46l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamandColby @SamGolbach @ColbyBrock Jake was possessed 🙀 https://t.co/imAEKyjsIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, may I, ________, act justly, love mercy and walk humbly with You. From Micah 6:8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VarshPrakash Honest to God you Purity Trolls wear me out. AOC craps out a propaganda piece and you use it to demea… https://t.co/ACHlqbQ10w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #UPDATE #FicInProgress Chapter 58 of Stay in Touch is posted https://t.co/iL7XphIpI9 Lymon Foster's dil… https://t.co/d9VDC8xVRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[you also, like living stones, are being built into a spiritual house to be a holy priesthood, offering spiritual sa… https://t.co/I10uRvP1eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TJWatt Kellogg’s, Rice Crispiest Honey Nuts Cheerios, Frosty Flakes and Fruit Loops]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙋🏻 W h o R u n s T h e W o r l d ? G I R L S 🙋🏻  #womensday #internationalwomensday #march8th #8marzo #lottomarzo… https://t.co/S32DZWnWGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Germans have no problem equating Trump with Hitler. https://t.co/K2GyVyQQto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono @Perrydigm @realDonaldTrump Polar vortex  is real cold. Real cold freezes everything real hot heat dry… https://t.co/b16u4XmJ7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was smoking inside my car just chillen when I realize there was someone next to me hella starring like damn want a hit ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#totallyreadyfortheairport #6amflight #whothoughtthiswasagoodidea #needanewtravelagent @ Bethesda, Maryland https://t.co/yI3OZPTi9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @carol08156 @eepeters_ep @Peeperpea29 @MarieSoapFan 😘🥰🐕❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the glass company was supposed to fix my Windshield last monday, changed the schedule to today, and just changed… https://t.co/PdJcwzienn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NC4LIFE74 @ReneeLibby2 Why do you want to? I mean your friend. 😂😂🤣😂🤣🤣🤣😂🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[huwag kayo magulo, that movie ‘Alone Together’ is now showing here in LA, so sshhh I went straight here to the thea… https://t.co/nB3SgjIodZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @jeremygibson54 You have the plague running around in LA rats garbage shit and needles in your sta… https://t.co/LlhJV9cZ2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! Thanks for more amazing music @alkapranos @thisisallweare @SpeedyWunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisshipitv An ambassador who has the ability to bring a smile to your face is one worth having. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! My mom lives with her gal pals and our boutique senior living setting. They helped her immensely in her… https://t.co/6Nd8jGfGVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met and listened to Mr. Billy Star - the founder of PMC. Inspiring! #PMC #waters https://t.co/WVw8CIdsW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen this photo before, adorable Rod..Thank you for sharing again, But what are you doing there? The Penguin l… https://t.co/hXL2dCMLXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that mf assume shit. And I cant wait to prove what u think you know. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be cleaning , moving furnitures and setting up for the next two days shoots. Lots to do!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally cannot wait to come home from work and wait to crash the fuck out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CD release: Cycles of Eternity In Mulieribus; Anna Song, artistic director Features premiere recordings of many new… https://t.co/4Y26WVTRHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterwashburn @mraspinall To sort of quite @sylviaduckworth You’re not bad at math, you just need more practice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may be March, but winter is still not over. Bundle up CT! Temperatures are taking a plunge the next few days. https://t.co/jPNJS4jk3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO Khloe is the furthest thing from a single mom. She has tons of family around to support her child literally al… https://t.co/njPR5YbQZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebelousanagram Well same actually. Yung ending lang yung ok for me. Pero yung story mismo meh. Di ko nga nagets m… https://t.co/I830tFJtB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[She swore that she loved me, no, never would she leave me, but the devil take that woman!!!🖕🤘 @Metallica]]></document><document><![CDATA[#greattimes #friendsarefamily #hombreslaunge #❤️❤️❤️ #🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈 @ Hombres Lounge https://t.co/MzHq0KzJR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRamiMalek I just finished Bohemian Rhapsody. I can’t stop bawling your performance was out of this world. You a… https://t.co/nV0r5rtiO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Typical democrat socialists communist party member hippocrite on every level !  Vote no democrats 20… https://t.co/mmGoOPZicP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robgee704 @cspanwj Why can't you understand that was their own money America had stolen till we returned it to it'… https://t.co/fyZQOkmNCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Just like you said you believed Putin over our Intelligence officers, just like you said that some… https://t.co/LZP3jgbrAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[had him gun point band she does not know how many men there were but Ronald Harvey who is Frank Miller has no busin… https://t.co/J56TMg02Yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our video submission for the Samsung Solve for Tomorrow contest. Link: https://t.co/a1OyqVvg7E @ Cave Creek, Arizona https://t.co/Mgk84gpPuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You touch me once and in an instant we knew that there will be history with the way that we're looking at each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Grow a backbone, trust your gut, and know when to strike back.” https://t.co/Rn8qJuHmLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Wizards' World of Harry Potter: Diagon Alley https://t.co/oaenJsUJNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are people in the habit of eating raw chicken fingers??? That’s a big warning. #onlyeatcookedfood #ThursdayThoughts https://t.co/hwvTVP1taM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The saddest part about your tweets Mr President is, most of your supporters believes them to be truthful. SoSad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kidsmathtalk Excellent nuance to pull out! Is it a do-over of the same kind of lesson or a different approach to t… https://t.co/Xre0Rdq7Ji]]></document></documents></author>