<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer Please keep your big mouth &amp; wallet running.   Trump continues to trend higher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents of #NVTeenDrivers have a conversation with your teens about the importance of allowing extra time to get to… https://t.co/WJZYCCPUJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[US admiral warns of Iran's advancing naval capabilities: https://t.co/sXfC7vgXjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerSaidWhat At least they standing up for something. It’s fun to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last two functioning brain cells after playing Apex Legends till 2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieDurdaWPLG @WPLGLocal10 Gooood morning Julie :) 😀❤️Happy Valentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m supposed to be getting Noah and Mia ready for Disney in 6 weeks, but must we wake up at 6:30 am to watch… https://t.co/VXVvNtsx3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjlamberton1 @iam_workman @astros_dude @NombreEsJustin @morasee https://t.co/NlsrghBHVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[These power structures should be confronted on every level. There’s millions of folks out there whose talents and v… https://t.co/n1kYKUb3ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realBethNeale @Trump454545 @realDonaldTrump @OANN @WayneDupreeShow @SidneyPowell1 @JussieSmollett Here's better qu… https://t.co/He6Cf9EXzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me take that back lmao. the few i have are people moving forward in their life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BLF77962711 @wbz Hone of fake Indians 1773? Also got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/… https://t.co/HgEgCnyLGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jentaub @OrinKerr @michaelmorley11 Many states and most democracies allow videotaping or live streaming of some ki… https://t.co/xtmZwM1kws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ian_leonard @Purgatoryarts Remember when we used to #BlameJerrid you’re going to have to start falling on the sword for this Ian!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have important work. Work across the isles and get things done ! https://t.co/jgbv1n202C]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best sports reads in a while. Ready for the remainder of the stories to drop now. Love that @Cardinals 2… https://t.co/DgPxnxH7AF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Pelosi is dumber than dumb. You’re biological clock ends at 80. Wtfu  resign dummy, you don’t need n… https://t.co/LOa3Njdz9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLCanes @breakingtco Donate some money to the Impeach Trump fund...Cherry would REALLY love that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaireCervenak @Me @adamdovico @smgaillard @PrincipalKafele @JWilliamsEDU @ARHasanEdS @brewerhm @karadowson Well, c… https://t.co/xlnrWKMGl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you say it: yes, I'm aware that confronting triggers is an important part of healing PTSD. Trigger warnings… https://t.co/odICOrobOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imprisoned Minds - Brenda Walsh Ministries Daily Devotion: https://t.co/r8EGqXbu6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidleAgeGambino @PlinythaElder @UberFacts He is doing a play on Stan from Eminem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that's a flagarant foul then we should just cancel college basketball right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name me a better sports town than Philadelphia at this current moment in time, you can’t...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did a great job right up to the point of shadowing the #deutschmark! #nigellawson @hmtreasury @ASI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa @realDonaldTrump check it out, that’s like Obama inauguration-sized crowds! 👯‍♀️👯‍♀️👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson learned again today. You can’t have a decent argument with a liar who makes up more lies to try and cover their original lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar I listen to my iPod at the gym and it's all songs from 1955-1966; lots of Elvis, Wall of Sound, one-hit wonders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have post Antonio Brown syndrome.   Definition: The fear of falling asleep &amp; missing out on NFL breaking news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writers #poets #teachers #poetry #poems #writing #books #college… https://t.co/MU0EBsbd1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to the @IrvingChamber for visiting your Texas Capitol today. @TerryforTexas, @juliejohnsonTX and I w… https://t.co/MezCGgoNZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarnabasPiper God gets no glory from this it’s absolutely tragic no matter how you slice it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A co-worker said I looked “dapper” in my tie earlier today. I let her know that is an old person term…]]></document><document><![CDATA[But y'all are tactless and want me to like you without knowing nothing about you because you like me and only seen my ass🤔 no bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbradfor42 @KansasDems With that being said, many have purchased tickets and give them to individuals who wan… https://t.co/fLBl53v4Ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing’s better than having someone match your energy you’re putting in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC You been a little off since the passing of your guiding light]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump is the disgrace of our country.  His hitler style, power grabbing mob tactics are ruining ou… https://t.co/9EvRkacZcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom If @JoeBiden enters the race, he will split the Democrats between Hillary supporters and Progressives an… https://t.co/8Q7VvCysN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please please please take me with you!  How ya gonna say no to that?!  God bless this journalist for this one time… https://t.co/v9bDnuryop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of meeting a Legend, former World Kickboxing Champ, @LouNeglia owner and promoter of #ROC… https://t.co/MarI0mwf6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Boston @celtics are a bunch if fucking cry babies. You have one of the most talented teams in the league, JUST BALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zenzurzb24 @glasgow_bruce @p_ganzel @InvajyC @bhatanagarntn @OohLaLaLina @67Mandie @gloriajkenyon @bionicanadian… https://t.co/YkBRuGXwB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[call me a Grinch but I dislike Valinetines day so much. #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretStephensNYT I just love the religiosity of the Fox “News” so-called anchors. https://t.co/frl1Q19r6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se equivocó @danielaganoza cuando vio el PRE estreno de #rapsodiabohemia Oscar merecido]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIGHT RAIN Sounds for Sleeping BLACK SCREEN | Sleep and Relaxation | Dar... https://t.co/w3jyYJEmBT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This person with the meme that says it all. (That face haha) 17 Of The Greatest... https://t.co/6NUWhTB8di]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firtyfreefousan @RachelBoundy1 @HackneyAbbott @sajidjavid What about compassion for the Manchester victims? You kn… https://t.co/hT9Z6rBG8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[“when you're searching your soul when you're searching for pleasure how often, pain is all you find but when you're… https://t.co/puXJIwBUMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbleTitos @ZackMeisel You don't get to the World Series as a "small market" team without a little risk. Trading… https://t.co/6BxbQxRQXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homicide: Life on the Streets did an episode based on this case.  https://t.co/N0Aul3vdDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't know how you predicted this but that is impressive https://t.co/PrxWsoNwqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perspective on who the @Suns drafted in @DeandreAyton   @NBA centers drafted #1  Shaquille O’Neal  David Robinson… https://t.co/fNOpvqHqBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmelgarejoc @Giants2019 @Giants Not necessarily. The Bucs aren't drafting a QB. Winston is their franchise and Ari… https://t.co/44kZD2WmqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars out here trying to save #BlackHistoryMonth https://t.co/vhPjKY2qfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @LindseyGrahamSC He’s trying as hard as he can to take over the number one spot of biggest assholes from… https://t.co/7RsD9CXpW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately she is the leader of the Dim Party and this is what they are about! WAKE UP AMERICA!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HMLoeschMcK I get so disgusted with liberals. I joined the Army served my country and was fortunate enough to have… https://t.co/2dZySCM4cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[MH370 search will continue, Malaysian PM says - CNN https://t.co/6vqHFQUOQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes He Should Be McConnell But You Know That All The Democrats And 10 Or 12 Low Life Republicans Will Say It Wasn’t… https://t.co/l13Dt0hvAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My art card! #art #artistsoninstagram #artist #artcard #designer #graphics #graphicdesigner #business #trendingnow… https://t.co/TSTjzNXukp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept 16 hours last night. Sick. Got up. Took a shower. Just slept two more hours. Lord come quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stellar graphite and silver leaf work by @andrewkcurrey in now @laluzdejesus gallery for #laluzapalooza check it ou… https://t.co/9QfnTq6t6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reshiDFS I cant believe you didnt play your favorite goalie Holtby even though i faded and took Brossoit against Carolina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theDISTANCEnoah Success of a player is based on how he impacts the game and how impacts his teammates. When on the… https://t.co/vMxhR1lk8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to educate themselves on weed before talking down on the actual plant and people that smoke it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget To Use My Promo Code On My Lyft Ride To Work... Could’ve Had For $4 Off &amp; A Free Ride 💀 Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegates approve bill to allow more money in state politics https://t.co/SXa24QUW9x via @WVNews247]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Fish, Two Fish, Red Fish, Blue Fish Sorting with Google Slides https://t.co/1dyr4eRHbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelpreaching @TheJohnDiMaggio 71’.  For his age he’s nearer to bleeding heart lib at the time.    People don’t r… https://t.co/CGF2pf5AkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re the James Dean of your generation, you don’t have to share the cover of a magazine with anyone.… https://t.co/b8YWhnJ9CP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laynemerchant @UncleDrewGB @ the other replies.. https://t.co/gU92cJATNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @PGuey88 You don't have to prove it. Anyone with any level of intelligence can see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I guess “just Tweeted” can refer to something that happened 14 hours ago... https://t.co/QCICAgR546]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sundjohn @NDSU No way! Hopefully we’re grouped together. I’m suuuuuuper nervous 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4loko4president @isaiahhickland I can count 15 we all on the same ~wave~]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, yes. Because Wayne Simmonds would be the difference between #Isles making a run this year or not. C’mon, stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LinkedIn now drives over half of all social traffic to B2B blogs and websites. https://t.co/ylPrwseECB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemard10 @apo4lif3 I like Kobe more than lebron but I know that lebron is better than him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertarianBlue @BreitbartNews @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Hmm 🤔 #FreedomOfSpeech abused by @instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bitprophet FWIW I was kinda pissed when I got a crown that when they asked what color it should be matte black was not an option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition If you ignore a problem, @FloridaGOP @RepMattGaetz promises things can only get better.  @FlaDems… https://t.co/QUBn6xQcKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to see @jamiegraceh live again &amp; catch up...been a min 🙃 https://t.co/v7NQYpJRcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don't tone it down with these games, my Gamerscore is going to make it look like I actually play lots of Xbox.… https://t.co/T2fiTATnZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevonPuglia @SteveSinger10 And I think it’s very hard for middle-class people (especially the liberal wing of… https://t.co/GfrGTa1Aa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarnetBlackTrad @GamecockBasebll Xl sold out already? That’s what I need]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athens_lawyer @llewokj @DanCrenshawTX Nice retort, care to elaborate? I say you're wrong, is that how this works?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant Williams is such a mature dude. He still falls on the ground more than any player I have ever watched, but he… https://t.co/csCWIIu7XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews What u call overreach some call oversight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluecollardaugh Hard to say, but when your job is life on the road alone, it's probably what's familiar and comfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1untamedbrain @billmaher @BetoORourke Actually you are right.  Or even Beto/Klobachar would look pretty good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystinaArielle The male doctor who laughed was very unprofessional.  It is there profession to take things seriou… https://t.co/Ihc6ufjolu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schrempfblogger @chriseatscheese the all white hickory are best jerseys they’ve had since flo jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How many times have you watched @theofficenbc “?    https://t.co/0LMjfAnGBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just blasted an hour and a half @trvisXX set in austin while Joe Cav was dead asleep it’s lit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all dumb af if y'all thought he was a surgeon ..... like jus look at this clown .... then he said 1 down 1 to go 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terilyns68 Phils signed Harper and half the radio talk was still eagles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warriorsworld @SteinmetzNBA He hates this team there’s no point arguing with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few boogie men @BernieSanders has called out tonight: Amazon, Walmart, United Healthcare, the “military indu… https://t.co/yoLUDuSYS4]]></document></documents></author>