<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile the chick with the fake Louis thinks she’s making a difference when she pulls on his belt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the season begin! ⚾️#SpringTraining #GoNats https://t.co/ci53iee7py]]></document><document><![CDATA[Molienda "El milagro" preparación de melcocha, sembradío de cañas y en la cima del cerro una 🐢 #mocorito… https://t.co/H3y3AALfVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better then kisses and beers #kisses #couple @ Richmond BratHaus https://t.co/PijAdeMhIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS Really, have these idiots not been paying attention? Sorry, educators.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your daughter likes markers, you need counter clean. #amazonrain #scentsy #countercleanallthethings… https://t.co/ApzoBRqvea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqtrivia Second win ever! Can I get an extra life https://t.co/V1PfKEVSgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorphBox @minto7_minton @EYuki19 @doots_goots @CanvasPirate @FUNimation He's right, we all just got to have faith]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quickest way to fuck up your career 😂😂  Convington is such a bitch tho,  “Stop recording”  *does as he’s told*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encantarme tu es poco me fascinas  sin darme cuenta de la gran intensidad que se nos viene]]></document><document><![CDATA[@350Mass @EdMarkey What a sad man you are GOD is going to punish you remember your old and god is watching you. Sor… https://t.co/tsTAPblQfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost from mrslin   Another big day for @maccosmetics this Thursday, March 7!  Be blown away with your natural se… https://t.co/KOUM6Nmslg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opened my OCT magazine and saw a familiar face! Congratulations @tina_zita ! https://t.co/6Kmr1OukA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I mock my husband's voice, I start out sounding somewhat like him and always end up with the sounds bur bur bu… https://t.co/MXGRWwRvzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComedyCentral please let me do an episode of drunk history I promise it will be a glorious spectacle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman in cot testifies to Congress on opioids, chronic pain management https://t.co/yE1nxIVW5T via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wet weather in Coos County causes floods and county concerns https://t.co/6rpq4J0laB]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% sure this isn’t what he said this is so click bait of y’all. Where is your source?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicOlague ¡que lamentable! Espero quienes votaron a favor puedan hacerse cargo o por lo menos, ayudar a muchísimos… https://t.co/BqhSi86dXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raaysamachado Eu quase fui presa em Dallas por causa de talco na mala. Pó branco em bagagem de mão não dá né lkkkkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being spontaneous at times it always creates a new adventure. Don’t knock life until you actually try it. Live!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And awesomely, ichthyosaurs were viviparous — they gave birth to live young. Soooo cool-n-weird.   For more dino ne… https://t.co/HSDF2NUyzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes Mondays can be pretty... @ Grace Hill Winery https://t.co/USshrkiR8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mae_phillips @crocker_kris @ansleygrace16 @caroline_chism @Carlss_98 Kristen will be here &amp; ansley may be here too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Community college for my gen ed requirements did me just fine and then transferred to a state school… https://t.co/XyRNC0UMjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD FOREVER BLESS THE MEMORY AND LEGACY OF THIS GREAT AMERICA HERO! 🙏♥️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself I have been going to the gym.  I've been swimming due to a variety of health issues I like to swim u… https://t.co/94TDIWZw9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiding for the next three days to get some serious work done - and at an absolutely STELLAR cottage. #winning… https://t.co/TBNh7PbwXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Investigate Nancy Pelosi’s dealings with the Mexican Cartel @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @SenateGOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta escondido en Bélgica el cobarde por algo será @MashiRafael vió q le caminaba cerquita el diablo y salió corrie… https://t.co/Khgt7orFCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[He had no idea what my shirt said 😂😂 #FreemontStreet #AllCaps #DistrictOfChampions #NHL @ Fremont Street Experience https://t.co/wgyttXykqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you play RASH in #wordswithfriends and can only think about Mary from @TheEllenShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocoabriel @keedypaula Lol I had this exact convo with my sister actually  Well I hope she gets where she’s goin cause this rn lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriaAlvarez85 No se oponga al matrimonio gay!!! Ellos no pueden reproducirse como los políticos corruptos 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 100% convinced that central Montana has the highest caliber sports reporters in the nation. https://t.co/UAVxF51zHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina blue skies at The Needle. Go Heels Beat Dook! #goheels #rivalry #uncbasketball #UNC @ Space Needle https://t.co/uGYcKsYBAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta enfermedad se llama corrupción Senador y lastimosamente está atacancando a Los Altos Magistrados del cartel de… https://t.co/mrBZNbbiTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiBianca @lovemandi_ Yep. It’s common after for sure. I hope the postmeno stage isn’t awful for us. 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[High intensity interval workout to great music coming to weekly We'd. 5:30-6:30pm March-May. Reserve your spot now… https://t.co/rFRI0Y5v9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d always thought i needed you, but look at me now, i don’t have you &amp; i don’t need you]]></document><document><![CDATA[My negative being perfectly put corrects our climate and eliminates harmful extraterrestrials. That is completely i… https://t.co/Kfn4aIkiTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wyer222 @Prince3eb @DarinColville @JCoker13 @spiritdance33 @Vickivbreezy @528ILoveAnimals @FaithCampbellJ1… https://t.co/Crx7MrN9Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbamok You and Michael are arriving flight twinsies! 😊  I will be at Mandalay, and I’ll save you two seats!!! 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what’s happening to me but I now look forward to lunch so I can eat my avocado salad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Why on earth is this child being listened to. As a Republican I hope she keeps yapping... it is good… https://t.co/k3Bn6ylTWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finished New Girl and now I'm onto Arrested Development and ahh I love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black history program Bessie Coleman Middle School https://t.co/XZRckYVgOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The smile says it all. Thank you @LouieVeganyc for making me sweat! At his new weekly residency #Expansions. People… https://t.co/egpJpNKjq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llijbe @HashashinTag Ummm... that is not... what?! I could see you spinning this as the French made bidets after c… https://t.co/pDJdoXVtdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can relate: finding it increasingly difficult to talk sensibly with my trump-supporting family. Trying to keep my… https://t.co/hOO1gkvb9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algún día haré el perfil psicológico de mi ex, lo distribuiré a mis amigos y así se terminará la eterna discusión de porque lo aguanté.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the CUTEST boy came into tavern for brunch and chatted me up AND THEN told me he’d make this his new spot to come o… https://t.co/HQn1vLiPSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharper_brain Sorry I think you are a typical entitled ass. You shouldbhave https://t.co/P4KHLZ7puU right away. I… https://t.co/AAQNXkn0PX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m seeing reports that it was a crash near Chatham square, which would make sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[me logging into kayla’s cc to see what people sayin abt me https://t.co/WiTvxUaVGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ifgirlscollide How the hell is ‘cinnamon sugar’ not a choice in this poll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[99 Cool But Hot Shots Of Ice In Black And White from @viewbug #photography https://t.co/qPHQbZILp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarateacher27 @bj116 My pineapple wasn’t ripe enough will try it tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherFrogger72 @Annendil @Z3RoForksGiven @jlwesterfield My sis had the eight track lol I know the songs. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd @IlhanMN I agree and why isn't the statement by Jim Jordan anti-semitic then?  He uses the $ sign for… https://t.co/4gSq38VNMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie at Fernbank Museum of Natural History with the #dinosaurs and #dad. More dino photos coming soon. #Atlanta… https://t.co/SaSn25SWJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPACSports @Hastingsbroncos @cunebulldogs @dwusports @nwcraiders Lady Broncos stomp the Bulldogs Saturday at 3!!! Momma Beacs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of #PlannerCon 2019 #franklinplanner #sweetstampshop (@ Hyatt Regency San Francisco Airport - @hyattsfo in… https://t.co/snBups00p5]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗We were goldensoiree event  with @phoebetime and @HeatherChadwell. . . . . .  #hollywood #events #party  #girls… https://t.co/p2dVsxFJ5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang playful. teen fashion | Tumblr  waaaant XD #funniness #giggle #grin #farcical https://t.co/1IxOSIoNBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinamash That is what a true representative supposed to do. Thank you for representing not only tue republicans… https://t.co/9pillpvaWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKlemens your voice just started randomly playing on my phone when i had no apps open and my phone was on the… https://t.co/9r8n8It5pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[surprise her with lingerie you wanna see her in then rip that shit off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when someone kept spraining me with fake trump supporter calls and threatened to kill my cat. I was terrif… https://t.co/dkfQFv5NO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao heres the thing my chicago vacay is fun and fine but f*cking  so L field]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you met these dynamic leaders yet? Their name gives you a chance to know them more. They are here for some 💥 c… https://t.co/3ekG37u6Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_deeminceyyy Ben10 was such a trash cartoon and  does NOT measure up to these other treasures 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonTracy @RaminSetoodeh @nigelmfs @hunteryharris @kpfallon That's crazy!  I love getting on set and being told… https://t.co/CbkpSpBng7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods SNL... Weekend Update: Girl You Wish You Hadn't Started a Conversation With !!   compare her to AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 shot on Syracuse’s South Side (witness video) https://t.co/3J7o0QYTM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @markgeragos Media "gang bang" @markgeragos? Nice choice of words, bahahaha! DON'T DROP THE SOAP IN PRI… https://t.co/Xt3rEIBTPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Texasbears @TeaPainUSA @joefaz @DanRather @TheDemCoalition @stucam7771 @stonecold2050 @ananavarro @CyrusMMcQueen… https://t.co/WfjjFSswlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @VP @KellyannePolls @PressSec @seanhannity @rushlimbaugh @marklevinshow @RealJamesWoods @Education4Libs… https://t.co/g8q8YNnBoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @CPAC Please let's organize groups of CEO's who have come up from their bootstraps and invite them… https://t.co/bXfxLTQKcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bugattiBLACK 😭 that’s my girl. Just let me know. You know I’m old and need to plan shit anyway 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @FionaMorgan79 @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @cowineco… https://t.co/v5fc70ZDc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNerdinaSkirt @PascoSheriff Also, I love "caffeinated candy juice" as a descriptor...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipfranklin @eyelovehorses In 1970, I asked my Social Studies teacher what, exactly, the Pledge of Allegiance mea… https://t.co/Hfa09JLsKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HerbJWesson is a great sport and settled our Super Bowl wager with some of the best LA goodies! When I was at… https://t.co/t18OUZ6aD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting with the WHY rather than WHAT we’re changing—-Blended and Personalized Learning @LearningAccel #SXSWEDU2019 https://t.co/xQDbSrcJA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@187k87k Excellent verse. All social media users should read.(Actually vrs 8-12). May we all try harder to not trad… https://t.co/VHSPSyBzhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[flights booked! A quick little trip to New York in April to celebrate our 4th wedding anniversary ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunsenbernerbmd Polaris says happy snow play Bunsen and dad! https://t.co/R1pJoMmPNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a fab weekend❤️ #Sedona #AZ  #girlsweekend #MyHappyPlace https://t.co/BwaGFvuFYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeRangeKids @LetGrowOrg This is so great. We’re homeschoolers and I’ve been worried about letting my 10 year old… https://t.co/Egb3CEo9pj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just before sunrise at the Meyer Amphitheatre and the weather is perfect!! Join us for a day of fun at our Wal… https://t.co/hmcxomelL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm confused crossed rn... But I'm sorry, I won't let a person continue to use someone against me and think they ca… https://t.co/lwE7X9H92u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbhiGTweets @RanvirShorey What do u mean season. Is it a show? Oh then i must have just watched the first episode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danibby0611 @jordancoates10 Why do you care so much what other people spend their tax returns on? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a plan fits perfectly on 1 sheet of paper 😀 and that plan is backed up by a pile of data and research 👩🏻‍💻… https://t.co/zW98Z7gLqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was buggin that my boss wouldn’t let me leave work early to drive up to Asbury Park since the concert date got move… https://t.co/HPScZ5ukzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emmyroots Las balas perdidas de este amor, prefiero no verlas en mi piel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wamaunderwear I am fine with avocado but I avoid bananas &amp; kiwi &amp; jack fruit too.  Jack fruit makes me naseous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGHurcomb UMKC Photography 1 Lighting and Still life Lab 3/4/19 #umkcart @ UMKC Department of Art and Art History https://t.co/Mvc0iCOt2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[His graces come to us through our cooperation with the means He has given us. These are the three pillars of spirit… https://t.co/EkuL7h8wCZ]]></document></documents></author>