<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I agree @jimcramer  I have watched their accelerated growth over the years and always think it will stall and they… https://t.co/wnJiiVjQIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASPEN.... XTREME.   We just dropped a collection of ‘80s ski long sleeves. Hope ya dig. ⛷🎿🏔 https://t.co/cTkZQnmyOn https://t.co/uNt7MyFcoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny you should mention "cut." Dem girl scout cookies have Planned Parenthood's baby blood on them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@griffin_poppe Yell if need help feeding! So if you need a new scale scaletech has neat new one  make jump to @PerformanceBeef]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 minutes into “Abducted in Plain sight” and I already hate everyone involved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally everyday and now I’m crying w a degree bc to do what I want I need another degree]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @LordByronEmpire (get_repost) ・・・ Even in the morning snow, the Cosmo is ready to cruise.....… https://t.co/tvdtyfufP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Navigating Payer Challenges @KLASresearch blog https://t.co/1U38XW7ZMg #KLAS #hcldr #healthcareIT #providers https://t.co/lmJi6Xi1v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankieMazzilli Take a look a Tulo’s back foot in slow motion ... my fears are legitimate https://t.co/nAvuFenGm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent study that should confirm that the effects of calories vary depending upon the state of the body. The bod… https://t.co/BQzHXu88fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny a lot of the people complaining about them thinking bout lowering the voting age in Oregon don’t even vo… https://t.co/4OrAclzXwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching the renaissance faire episode of king of the hill again. alan rickman was a gift to us all. sup tom keiser?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fengcha friend order MILK foam tea. Got tea with no milk cap on it. Was told she ordered something else. #WTF… https://t.co/tsD7LEXCMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[To My Future Wife...  I promise, I’ll propose to you at cnco show...  #Piénsalo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Block the deal...HE GAVE IT TO THEM #Moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning Family and Friends. Be Blessed! @ Browns Summit, North Carolina https://t.co/eoM7rAl1j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donttrythis They are not threats, Adam. When the fake media is writing stories that are more fiction than fact, th… https://t.co/0sG7Kxx5a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBreuer Killed it and made the day for a lucky kid at Metallica world tour #MetInIndy https://t.co/vSIv5oZEwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish @amazon @Allbirds @CNN @cnni Your guest is smart enough to take advantage of a cancerous polyp of the s… https://t.co/xY0lNPSjwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crislopezg Okay my Asians, time to get in our lions, Voltron up and rocket punch this gasbag https://t.co/sq1i6H6Q7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drsosterer All well and good; my tl;dr version: Law is being an asshat here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should lose all federal Aid and be held accountable for any related crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend of the show @cobeselfmade dropped some new 🔥🔥🔥 today! What y’all think? #HighlyInappropriatePodcast #HIP https://t.co/IQwf9O3kBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall got 1 Week to get ready for tommiee_ At Cove 51! 😎 @ Cove51 https://t.co/vr03dQPVjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcoren I am remembering the 47 girls raped by pedophile Father Charles Sylvestre, who was allowed to continu… https://t.co/54GQIHRqQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No time like the present- Happy Saturday 🌞👍🏽💯 #saturdayvibes @ Blink Fitness https://t.co/KqOvcjJpRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and Quinnipiac owns it against Harvard. Cup can be shared, seeding of course is a different story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodfatherRiley Didn't Magic just have 6 players on a plane to New Orleans...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msexcel Excellent, used it to modify a list of data which, if done manually, would've taken hours on end!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterMOFAD @JPVMan @HammerBDX What “promising result?” Is ‘promising’ our new word for unmitigated disaster?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 59: Wakeup. Eat. Workout. Repeat. #fridayfun #earlymorningworkout #meditate #workout #pray #swimmorning… https://t.co/3gKvcgZ14y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @newbirthmbc ! We are listening to your pastor @jamalhbryant for #LeadershipTalks @BeulahHeights]]></document><document><![CDATA[So frustrating! And, of course, you’re right. The next chance we get, we are right back at it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[312-34 the @AkronDerby took down @chicagooutfit at the Knight Center!  What a game!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoplifters won’t win in the foreign language category, but it is a magnificent piece of film.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeslaBand Been listening to this "track" several times today. See what I did there? Good job! https://t.co/83SQz8Xsnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a terrrrrible Bill for Americans    It’s only great for democrat politicians because it’s a train wreck of fr… https://t.co/dt0sOGugR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smulpuru It’s hard to imagine we will still go “shopping” for detergent in 10 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #Nursing job in #Austin, TX? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Regist… https://t.co/Zo8OdgiIvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queenofspring @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Maybe go with pg 1 any school USA. I got fake news,calle… https://t.co/YWyAUbCg8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha, Charles is on a roll...                          https://t.co/YOVkmUuzU6 @ Cardinal Nation North https://t.co/609GpuC4dj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertTornabene Agree. Hats off to you and the entire department.  Prayers for all to recover.     Great job handl… https://t.co/Tg3nHDBdNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBookOfNick @xan_desanctis @DavidRutz Negative, Ghostrider. https://t.co/Sx4CzaXFaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Jim Jordan is really trying to take Cohen out. Pity he doesn’t work as hard to call Trump out on his “misstatements”!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo una duda a alguien de ustedes les gustan las tortillas de harina Tía Rosa ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tchaiko @Nikyatu I had nothing on anything when she hired me I was a student with a script she liked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Urgent: Protect the North Arm Trails! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/Wd7N5XLYWL via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjizzles @JonathanPaviaaa yea big facts, get ur degree then drop out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dorian Electra was so sweet but if made any sense whatsoever I’d be surprised @DORIANELECTRA https://t.co/V2P1OU5vcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still grinding. From 50.  #HershBrothersKicking  #TeamSailer https://t.co/w1NtkWD6w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cromulons! . . . . . . #jasonmontoyaartist #instaartist #instaart #drawing #artoninstagram #handdrawn #artlife… https://t.co/oqWGDVDQxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamVingan The team never got hot in 2017 and went to the Stanley Cup Finals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my colleague tried to check me for using all caps to emphasize certain things in my emails...   baby boomers get on my nerves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSchifo @JerodLycett People will find ways to make the Bible say whatever they want. Always have. Right now th… https://t.co/66zUQckVqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acton flys out to left and the #Gators can’t take advantage for the third time tonight. As we head into the fifth,… https://t.co/QZfdunlj9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[He who lies and know that he lies defiled himself. He who condones lie and knows that he is condoning a lie defiles… https://t.co/RnwxcFT9E8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFaustoXXX @hankeystoys @J_E_F_F @mikey_dxxx @ffistme92 @A_esposito_xxx @SlackJock @actinido Nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight on her show @maddow raised an excellent question in my opinion.  If Michael Cohen brings evidence to his op… https://t.co/sg9BXO4B2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILLADELL Word you loose how you got em ...even more crazy is that tristian baby mama name is Jordan lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo.2013.02.10 18.43.05 Bennett Hill Preserve on 2/10/13 https://t.co/6Bvpaeg2X7 https://t.co/vLSocx2tnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I am so proud of President Trump and his administration! Great job! Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustA_Scrub @RockStar_Rams But it goes both ways. It’s not just white people doing this as it’s portrayed. The the… https://t.co/VY4n38VBDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m was in disney for 6 months and the closest i got to seeing a celebrity was some guy who kinda looked like tom h… https://t.co/w71w8Jb6iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[1916 Early Spring on Little Cauchon Lake https://t.co/J5EY9FBoGK #tt1916 https://t.co/kz9ghtcaWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xrey1 @ezvic420 Im sorry...I Assumed you were paying attention as YOU LIKED several tweets in the conversation...… https://t.co/LcXsVB45CC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthamptonPage @HolyHojbjerg @Twitter Why Hughes wouldn't play him just don't understand!😇👍🏾🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody has to clarify whether they’re a “socialist” or not. Just give us the details of your platforms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo La Batalla de Flores puro Carnaval desde #Barranquilla por @CanalTelecaribe a través de @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea about the laws of copyright pertaining to photos online. So glad someone made mention before I got to… https://t.co/6957PveLx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @RepAOC Damn good job and use of the witness’s knowledge. You’re a sharp cookie, AOC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo this should be a good film@in my opinion. But I’ll throw it out there. If they have Koko B. Ware or The Junkya… https://t.co/h2ZwXEIj7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaavoInc 27 minutes ago: Your new remote was delivered! Now: We're gonna spam you with stuff we think you should w… https://t.co/nAQOJUfwic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillPlaschke Gee, that's too bad.  Course, the important things to Lebron are his talk show, and Space Jams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami-Dade’s “half-penny” Transportation tax— not enough to expand Metrorail, but a roads wish list is almost compl… https://t.co/stDd0FPivJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadian roads have been cleared and schools are open today.   #backtoschooltoday📚😌✌🏼️ #toomuchsnow #lifeincanada… https://t.co/7EH0TCTSSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Echoing @BarstoolJordie, this isn’t right. @Tehoka1 doesn’t deserve this at all.  Scott Marr said it best: there ar… https://t.co/4xzjknHDyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do something and do it HARD. Read. Attend meetings and seminars. Meditate and pray. Share your experiences and lend… https://t.co/c4cKTIeDNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX You are turning a blind eye to a lot of warning signs about trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanWurtzel I don’t understand this disrespect for the greatest living 20th century President. His brother just… https://t.co/FodxETOwJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is after I was cracking the fuck up because she lit a cigarette in my non-smoking building and didn’t give not… https://t.co/uqW2TxStGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amie_Just RV....I think you misspelled Trailer Park for those two schools!  @tcraigschilling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siege_Boyle @1HappyJan @dragonflie5874 @arsenault_judy @HienPhuongHo @sf_mom3 @Rosekeepr @ladychryse @RachelMaytum… https://t.co/vukjRFjFrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry She’s debuting her summer bikini line. https://t.co/dFEBxGV6oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Wednesday, it’s #AustinTX #QueerRide, off n away for hot chocolate.  #LetsRide @ Texas State Capitol https://t.co/oulzqHGTwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I guess I've got to give @Target credit for their #BlackHistoryMonth displays, whomever thought the Superfly… https://t.co/maW2cETAmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do drive thu’s put there hours on the window at the end of the drive shouldn’t be before]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the nigga you fuckin Don’t gaf about you and that shit hurt the most 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazon how is a private residence closed?  Especially when you delivered a separate package #noservice,… https://t.co/3CfhJMg2IO]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, The first 3 weeks are over at The District. 3 more weeks to go. https://t.co/lLqGj5AqBu 💣💥 https://t.co/9iBJValJYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ticket lines extremely long in San Diego after Machado signing https://t.co/fIWioy55zI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our team does the design and layout work for every issue of the DuPage County Bar Association magazine. Several mon… https://t.co/KA35CDj8AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter clearly knows we’re bffs @MiliVGonzalez because it will let me know about every single thing you post]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett wouldn’t be in nearly as much trouble if he was a nobody I think. Fame got him right in the poop ch… https://t.co/FIYMd8V3qK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffJacksonNC This is not a judicial ruling it’s a judicial hack. If you agree with his ruling every bill passed i… https://t.co/p8w34lti5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_coppola @yvonnewingett @azcentral I see the pro-plague people are at it again.  Tragic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjgranger1 @roaddogger @kathylandb2 @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends @WhiteHouse LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 10, 2018: See my pinned tweet? Why is Region of Peel/Dine Safe Peel still hiding info about the Dec. 2017 con… https://t.co/dtEPIFy2B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random s/o to @JustinPeters_FS for being awesome!!! Everyone get u a Peters https://t.co/66CO5BzOqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a meeting of the "03's" at Cochrane Yard April 1, 2016. On the left is GP9 1603 purchased new by Ontario North… https://t.co/MNoGOiLmWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[District 3 Wrestling Tournament. Day 1 good luck Daemon and Bronson. @KDHS_Athletics #ramspride https://t.co/IswFpl2mTw]]></document></documents></author>