<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[⛳️At my new listing! Seller is the photographer 🤣 #miamipetfriendlyrealtor #miamirealestate #kathyhidycares… https://t.co/R8VaBB3Zsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anton47492193 @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @Southappie… https://t.co/4WJNHEif0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thebadmf_ ... airborne bacteria lmao. It’s literally taught in elementary to not brush with the toilet seat up bec… https://t.co/QDk6hchgKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perrydrake @MelissaJPeltier @thespybrief What a relief—Rodman’s got it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MujerInparable   Visítanos en Rosales #105 esq. Monterrey col. centro  Tel. 2121270  Whatsapp 6622686821 #HazTuCit… https://t.co/eGfA83tMDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JCPSHS zone schools take a look at the recent updates to the backpack: https://t.co/g7hhwOcHC7! I have also shared… https://t.co/QTZpZelRwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajaja así yo ahorita que ya me chingue la quincena 😂😂 https://t.co/EQ2Ci1akO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who schedules a Thursday night concert? A great new artist that can sell out even on weeknight that’s who! @lukecombs #tiredbitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's some laughter. SUB PLANS: In your sub binder put the book "Miss Nelson is Missing" and have the... https://t.co/pewzZ8RyEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to church, (a)près-ed for powder 🙏🏼❄️❄️❄️🍾🍾 @ Aspen Highlands https://t.co/D7QVRLXIL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foul on @jgibby1121 at the line for three! 51-51 tie game. #GoQuakers @SFSQuakers https://t.co/Df5kdBCLdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattRenoux @9NEWS @ColoradoDOT Keep updates coming for those of us stuck on Vail Pass !]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing like finding a $100 bill in ur pocket that u forgot about]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 great presentations tonight at @BF_District Community MH Awareness Night: Common Mental Health Disorders in Child… https://t.co/uloX7buHvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the scenic route into work today, down Meridian. The fog over the water and the green, lush canopy was a remin… https://t.co/PGb8pmNNBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Willow Grove Mall Water Fountain in Abington, PA https://t.co/jeBsvmQuea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linslawre @used_bandaid Haha right? About to smack him right inna face 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritesJodi Yes, although it doesn't always happen to ME. (I do, however, believe I'll get my turn eventually.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulosophia Stand down Trader! Americ's great leader's are working very hard to protect America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKayMSmith The saddest thing I have ever seen. My Father was there to help liberate the people who were left. He… https://t.co/ZoPHpbk72Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else like to just drink coffee and listen to the rain/thunder ☕️ 🌧]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many “San Diegans” who never venture this far down south to recognize or appreciate the communities th… https://t.co/GU9mLovxBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've got a @GooseChaseEDU going right now to learn about banned and challenged books.  Watch out Grandville High,… https://t.co/WMKoEWEgsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day 2019! Explore powerful words by women &amp; illustrated by women from around the 🌎!… https://t.co/oPxUUfbdc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airvooocht @realDonaldTrump Are ya trying to be Moses ya stupid idiot. You lock kids up in cages and make them wor… https://t.co/yO371ADqaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bf was doing the dishes and while washing my FFXIV minions mug it slipped through his hands, fell and the handle br… https://t.co/vUJ2jpydiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenAlexander Have you been to border? Have you spoke to border security? Have you spoke to the people who are bein… https://t.co/0WNgHHnORT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My emotions are all over the place right now @LaurenCimorelli song Flames is so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my first day back from spring break: busy, but at least I found time to eat two meals today instead of just one!!! #progress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPRverlee This reveal is basically what #coleg Twitter is living for at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_keesmaat As a pedestrian I want to say that tinted windshields are criminal, you can't make eye contact and that's life threatening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the ring master @IsaRossellini Today we chat with the star about performing on the @gatewayshows stage. Her do… https://t.co/Yz5k7xTHPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sorry if it’s sitting in your fucking store how can you not know how to check something out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Called my supervisor and let her know that I’m going to be late to our meeting bc I’m locked in my bathroom... I’m… https://t.co/tw4qkAdSnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unconditional love 💕. Soul mates. By Lake house. https://t.co/FrjvYquAxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Process can’t be the end but the means @ernestmorrell Give purpose to Ss #TALE2019 https://t.co/gmrLv1EK0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so grateful my nephew loves Sesame Street, and not Caillou like some sort of terrorist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oyebee SLOWLY TURNING INTO A FOX RELOAD. TOTAL SILENCE ABOUT THE USA REPINOCHETIZING LATIN AMERICA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i kick my vans off my feet all the time and let me tell you they do not land right side up everytime]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son Jesse ll and daughter, Merry, are waiting with me at Dade City hospital as my husband Jesse gets his surgery… https://t.co/Kmy6aNF00U]]></document><document><![CDATA[100th day- man these kinders are looking old! @WVEOwls https://t.co/lyWqIyRGan]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't the full push or the only car we moved today, but it is proof that our retreat was eventful.… https://t.co/KZQqUrmHm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your stylist receives a visit from a Presidential hopeful and then gets a shout out tweet.  Awesome. Proud of… https://t.co/zq9An28wag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrtablaze @frespirit01 This woman is such a danger to our country! WAKE UP!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this little family! #reynoldsfam #emmagrace #beckhamtroy #jacksonscott #babyjackjack @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/yyaLHO2gei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerryECooper @juliesteinberg4 your twitter feed is amazing at finding funny GIFs + memes to go along with your art… https://t.co/1tZtgO78qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karina_escaping @MattsRoadTrip @Sostraveluk @HHLifestyleTrav @GailBenzler @dsouzaashayne @OdetteDunn… https://t.co/8UG7Zzyqti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Ya think? Dude get help. Don’t use getting help to get by the judge. GET. HELP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH ALSO, re: #networking, please note that I'm actually a little shy and overwhelmed by large/loud gatherings. I wo… https://t.co/5ykL1xs5KI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah — HELL YEAH!   I hope/pray every sharia area is rooted out, banned and the enforcers of such laws incarcerated… https://t.co/lgMhzRd4cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: please for the love of god use the arms of your jackets, they are there for a reason #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman @pam_houston Ohhh! I love her and meant to go see her Sunday @NorthshireBooks but could not make it due to ice! Lucky you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theunbigoted @Imamofpeace So America is all about its citizens when it wants to be but cuts them loose and makes t… https://t.co/Rmx2iyvTR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[black ice getting down to school. roads are NOT safe ! https://t.co/0m0a1EdhKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing my nana like this is truly breaking my heart pls make it thru this nana I’m not ready to lose you ....like this  💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheActOnHulu @JulietteLewis Can’t wait. @PattyArquette I know you brought it...🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall Don’t assume that just because you cannot ‘reach’ all of your students that something is wrong with the… https://t.co/if32xtpSN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinBrant93 @mattheldstab @VMwareHOL @VMware @VMwareHOL has lots of dashboards for that though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[enough with Smallet guy, too much news coverage about him, it is annoying, most of us could care less about another publicity hound]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all men are trash, you just pick trashy men and blame everyone else but yourself for your problems 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[POLO • @WorldPoloLeague •  10am • Beverly Equestrian vs Smithfield (8g) @GCPC 4pm • All Star Challenge Final WPL (2… https://t.co/VSjdHWUAFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my professor was discusing mindset, and while speaking about high-achievers he said “sometimes their A-ness g… https://t.co/nsZaDk8l23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson Unfortunately kellyYou know fake news in the media it was all over Facebook and people are going to… https://t.co/cfa8MaQsFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So his apology is supposed to make the judge feel better?  Fuck Roger Stone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yusuf_VI @SenSanders I try not to piss God off. It's always been a bad situation that only became worse. I believe… https://t.co/OHVUFbb7kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veggies do a body good #healthy #diet #sexychefwendy @MichaelDinich @MorganStrebler @DaleTheMoneyGuy @MichaelDinich https://t.co/IWT7ByIAAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's @damndarian birthday I love you 💗 many years ago darian sent me the risque outfits from princess maker and i s… https://t.co/siyDonlVwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Oh thank goodness-he needs to be held accountable. #LockStoneUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@altmaralago @youroutervoice I must say I’m enjoying the humor today!!! I always said that is all TRump has been good for!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever been home alone and randomly start hearing shit and then start blasting music 😭 im shitting bricks rn!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUSHED OFF a SHIP IN MIDDLE OF MEXICO ! I WILL NEVER TAKE A CRUISE ..............https://t.co/J0v6hur4qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safetyabby @fayfeeney @safetypam @MMurraySafety Oh wow, that would be an honor, thank you for thinking of me! I’m… https://t.co/P8D5gFiAI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to enjoy yourself. I deeply want to enjoy myself. But I am terrified and hide and just watch everyone wish… https://t.co/4GC6Dq9iIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of Friday Night to kick off Spring Break, dinner, drinks and great company!  #GolfMoms ⛳️🦅💚 @HailiMoore https://t.co/sVM2zDZnun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went out shooting the other day with a friend and found these amazing leaf prints on the hood of an old car. Love a… https://t.co/iTcJvqHjdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter legit made me get a new cell number because they suspended my original acct wayyy back over hating on Golde… https://t.co/mncgIDMdRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo Ladies Day annual tradition minus two. We shopped, we boozed, we froze our asses off. Will someone please tel… https://t.co/P9hLuWIYh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another amazing south Florida weekend 🌴the Honda Classic and Mets spring training never disappoint!… https://t.co/kjykIMkhNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nieves_rd Esto es el colmo que venga a destruir lo no ham sembrado en un país no es el suyo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mary_Nam Put it on while you’re still damp from the shower. Your legs will glisten and your cuticles will stop pee… https://t.co/0LOtVPIskw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveFenberg @SierraClubCO @Tracee_Bentley @APIenergy @COPetroCouncil @kcbecker There’s a new sheriff in town.  Hi… https://t.co/chcy7lk43c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate when old people stand in fields like u look like a ghost! Get out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl Were you “punished” for orchestrating the Tawana Brawley incident?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachealwilson @chrissyteigen Ohhh, I'm sorry you just broke my heart sweetheart! I literally have tears rolling dw… https://t.co/4eV2SOldt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetKat111 Dude don't come to rural Ga we like our guns, you will find https://t.co/miprPrBhyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s on beat. the flow changes. it has internal rhymes. and she’s prettier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m already crying and this is just the promo! This show reminds us that Love Is Bigger Than Anything In It’s Way 💖… https://t.co/5euvmZTkgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our students LOVE to get active in the snow, or should we say ice??? @wrdsb #wearenotcold #canadiankids #activeplay… https://t.co/g1qNX3yQKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I was reprimanded by a patient’s son for getting it “into my mom’s head that she’s in charge of her own heal… https://t.co/0zEKsoEkge]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Blue River Community College Student Lounge in Independence, MO https://t.co/fsywnGcv4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJeffries @SarahBCalif Dumpty projects onto others that for which he is truly guilty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidgeLee619 Subscribing to that theory that “all publicity is good”.  As a human, it amazes/bothers me that there’… https://t.co/Fijs4biYv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said to me: "It is done. I am the Alpha and the Omega, the Beginning and the End. To the thirsty I will give wat… https://t.co/eQyhOPXPYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is spending evening in #Chantilly #Virginia with her girlfriend. https://t.co/dweCEGpKG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have absolutely no idea where this came from 😂.  @EllieFuson @budderbrojoe ??? https://t.co/g9j3LGXuH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We the People will not forget these Baby KILLER'S, BOOKER, GILLIBRAND, HARRIS, KLOBUCHAR, WARREN AND SANDERS  ! ! !… https://t.co/M6GzDgyW8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TManitowoc @Cultgti It’s the only thing he truly had an association with, so they hold on to it feverishly! It’s j… https://t.co/S5owS2QlMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature HBD, Arthur. My dad was a WW II vet, but my dad was with the Army Band. He was a trumpet player an… https://t.co/C1erprTjrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ivan is one of the most hard-working, passionate, and driven people I’ve ever met. Voting for him would allow WSU’s… https://t.co/xUlqawXxeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt I am all of your sure shows will be sold out!  Don't forget to Rest!]]></document></documents></author>