<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NFFNetwork, thanks for the invite for  @EthanHan_  @PVPHSFootball. It was a great year. https://t.co/fjF0kMfUSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off my 2 weeks home with a nice soak in the tub! It's wonderful to be able to relax, even with my kitty me… https://t.co/ysthKsXeIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was excited to see @MariandTorres is joining Wicked tour. I went through my yarn bin saying “Time to make 2 new hats!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[My youngest daughter, animal lover &amp; vegan 💕💕💕 https://t.co/tsWl2K1rG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@groundedeffects @IndyCarNation @elgordo99 @Meeshbeer @Fieldof33 @sarah_connors @Erock_in_Indy @15daysinmay… https://t.co/N1wYk2dqnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I was gonna go pick up some of God’s green earth today and then found out that event is all the way in Friend… https://t.co/5jdhF0qZ3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillBox_27 @jundaykel was trying but we were too close it would’ve been too obvious. 🙆🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NanInKansas @PatTheBerner He moved the entire nation to the left from his 2016 campaign (which also included his d… https://t.co/Gko2AGqUSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is hard for me to wrap my mind around Sr Night. Our last regular season home game.  Each of these young men are… https://t.co/hz17sS2J8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so excited as a Randall Swope, one of our Head Coaches for Major Force Lacrosse and Head Coach for our  2021… https://t.co/QL7JJ1Nh39]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate that i’m exhausted all day but as soon as i lay in bed i’m wide awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[and if you’re going to do this anyway, please do it the whole play instead of fading in and out of it. 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachelorABC @colton What a shame he can't see that she is not worth the fight.  When you're in it, you're blind to… https://t.co/MEj3Rvu2xM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaveyDaniel when I wore that sweater half off half on it was a bet https://t.co/SY6Dx6S8VW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am low key PISSED that i didn’t get to drink one of my favorite drinks on its national holiday 🍹#NationalMargaritaDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAINN That’s how Mom began to suspect something was going on. I had developed anorexia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part of having today off is that I don’t have to leave the house OR shovel my car out of my parking spot🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is literally why driving at night is my least favorite thing to do ever. i can't see even with my glasses on 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What a hoot! You ignore the Constitution and any rules you don’t like on an hourly basis. You make… https://t.co/SAPB3c3h4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a year when all my friends and family OWE tax $ who have never owed before, this gets a big, fat, "Duh!" 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mowsyling @AmyWishman Hey! Fellow 36 y.o. here. I am super happy to know I'm not alone in this fandom. I guess we'… https://t.co/xRGrNZ2hFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to @legends_stars and fully representing my teams and guys there signing with a Bills hat, Sabres jacket, and… https://t.co/qHwfRcPBGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says you who has a picture of Lincoln! You are very confused. Bernie is greedy! A rich man condemning the rich who… https://t.co/eQqItrgLkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog Isn’t there someone who can take McConnell on in his next campaign and beat him? He is the one p… https://t.co/72llG4gZj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m gonna need to take my ass to bed. i was tired before i even came down here but i got like 20 minutes of studying done. go me]]></document><document><![CDATA[“How does #poverty influence #learning? Poverty-related factors that intervene in students' ability to learn includ… https://t.co/UEOuYQb0Hi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really has evolved a lot, love it!! It’s nice that Joni can zoom in on your face, so much emotion, you truly are… https://t.co/zOphuO5Okw]]></document><document><![CDATA[R Kelly thinks he’s victim and actually he is. However, like other victims of child molestation , he has created ot… https://t.co/NwPxlnGxFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[BITCH, I got my fucking lips done and these bitches are going to be SWOLLEN for three days &amp; I have to work!!!!! WHAT THE FUCK 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring back Frank's East Blvd. Its patrons were so depressing that it stayed a good, cheap dive in Dilworth.... Albe… https://t.co/quMSN1cNLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARTIST SPOTLIGHT👀 Let us introduce Ms. Stacey, an art teacher from @edwhiteneisd who painted this beautiful piece r… https://t.co/FM8R1CUr4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using Arts Education to Help Other Lessons Stick https://t.co/DEj5yDPemg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teacher voice should be included in every discussion affecting their profession and livelihood.… https://t.co/vFciIl1vlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to fucking hurry up, and I need to fucking remember to pre-dose with nausea meds. https://t.co/UVAOUW0CLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danagould I’m pretty sure I’d say, ok honey, that’s nice. Now go play with your Legos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 All my thought &amp; good vibes to your Grandmother. Blessings to you all...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s raining so hard and I would sleep so good if I didn’t have to work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What lawyer?  No one is going to take his phony case unless it’s to place him in jail!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jose_Jalepeno_C @ashm0nsterTV @gglindsayelyse @GrimisS @SirCapObvious Fuck that looks like into the blue!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KnightsR7 GREAT day for Wellness. @drkrauseashley @KnightsR7_Supt @Director_ElemED @KnightsR7 https://t.co/8uGuXKv2Lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JaguarNation. Make sure you're putting #SouthernU_RYS19 #RYS10Strong in your tweets!  EVERY vote counts!!! 💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calientesports Desde el cielo una hermosa mañana el águila descansaba en El coloso de Santa Úrsula, descansaba par… https://t.co/cnrAzw7gEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about how #traumainformed care intersects with how we should approach the #opiatecrisis &amp; #chronicpain #pafpcme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc if I get my tax return today or not. Ordering some more Jeffree Star brushes today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP YOU LYING SACK OF 💩💩 PEOPLE ARE PAYING TRIPLE IN TAX FINES YOU DAM LIARS! You CANT FAKE THAT ONE AWAY I p… https://t.co/3NWcVLwJUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day on the mountain! (@ Vail Resorts in Vail, CO) https://t.co/JW7dnBIMCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer I'm a single issue voter, and you just lost my vote. No pineapple on pizza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day of bowling! #BestFriend #Boyfriend #distancemakestheheartgrowfonder #EaglesClub #Muskegon @ Muskegon Eagl… https://t.co/5kq3D1T1OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpu6600 @EdKrassen Tax disclosures should be a must! Also, an elementary level reading test!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been seeing so many Roselle girls flourishing on my TL lately and I’m just so happyyyyyyy for all of y’all 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__james__dean @Dodgers @Bharper3407 It’s almost 9 pm on west coat and almost mindnight on east coast they would an… https://t.co/9YDpPmfRoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janet_sd @nicnak423 @countryknights This was wonderful it was a great show and awesome concert a night to remember indeed!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t go out ALL the time. Sometimes I stay up til 2am reading articles on Stevie Nicks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that happened here.... I promise I would do that.  And I’m talking about me, not my dog.  Although I would invit… https://t.co/tVUieXAfFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus was their teacher and was delivering them from slavery to sin and bringing them to the Promised Land of grace and salvation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are really looking forward to another “wine down” Jazz night at Whistler’s Knoll this Friday at 7:00! $5 at the… https://t.co/UG5ykWmHYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was dumping all day. Skiing with these two was a blast! #aspenhighlands #dumpingsnowallday @ Aspen Highlands https://t.co/7Z0TbrIn9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vanity Is a Virtue and KEY Survival Skill When it Comes to Facing Age Discrimination #Psychology #beauty… https://t.co/oCuc9AaaSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Superhoo I was getting a little crap for the junk on the table, which I cropped out. Who knows why there are t… https://t.co/yfLOanM8ux]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I need to just get dressed up and go have dinner with the gurlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virgiliohernand @ONU_es @MashiRafael @Lenin @EcuadorRC @CompromisoRC5 @ForoComunes @ForoNacMujeres… https://t.co/ANByHlRL5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Model Call: Maternity. In search of pregnant mamas to model fashions for a leading maternity clothing company. Bump… https://t.co/1udHBLVs0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#T3Learns at #T3IC some tools we use as Ts to reach our Ss with #STEM ...hooks and stories... https://t.co/oDo1vvfhNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laurels News headline.. coming soon...'FEMA camp welcome centers coming soon']]></document><document><![CDATA[My entire childhood we weren’t allowed cats because my dad was allergic. Cut to him calling me after we had all lef… https://t.co/S0vSyjZqRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m listening to these Twilight soundtracks remembering exactly where I was when I heard these for the first ti… https://t.co/ZH49mzc67B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you guys imagine Raiders Twitter if they would cancel this trade???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas  felicidades  a todos #AmarAMuerte @AmarAMuerteOf 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏 https://t.co/N4qrlfZHUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaihumphries I did! Keeping it old school (I'm just far too lazy to change everything to my Gmail. I have a Google… https://t.co/AHBWr9pzSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Old_Hippie @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews She's very uneducated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oldfriendsfarm Happy Birthdays! May you both have many more years filled with health, love, lots of peppermints and carrots. 🥕🥕🍭🍭💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend just sent me this pic of my husband encouraging me through the CrossFit Open workout today, and I burst in… https://t.co/xFNq0FY9sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saylavii1k1 @jacobpounders @frankthorp Keep speaking up!!  No one hears what doesn’t get done after the “promises… https://t.co/DHyRK8N15Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[👓 Aurora Borealis, a natural electrical phenomenon, also seen in #Alaska, my home state!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elementary school teachers who don’t know the difference between there/their/they’re, your/you’re, etc make me neve… https://t.co/oszAFUaOn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before International Women's Day ends, I want to acknowledge and send a shout out to my hero, @HillaryClinton . A w… https://t.co/Il2b0jtoDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just downed this jack n coke as if It was water...um... I’m I ..... back? ..... ;lol now I’m in the mood to go out… https://t.co/P3ggh1hoPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthaus_CNY @CuseMLAX @ArmyWP_MLax @CNYcentral As USMA alum that has played in the Dome this is very touching and… https://t.co/UAHkbg6BoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSF_en @BBC The US dictator will NEVER condemn violence on journalists or anyone that does not pander to his hate-]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find out some of your closest friend's mom were talking shit about my mom behind her back, and when she fi… https://t.co/4BImUC6u5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheeto377 @IJasonAlexander Oh lord I’m 🤣 ... Maya Rudolph’s composure and expressions during this skit was classic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I so love Epcot!!  💙 🌍 ✨✨  . . . . #epcot #epcotflowerandgardenfestival #epcotfestivalofthearts #epcotfoodandwine… https://t.co/EIsAzUEAw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t complain without an effort to do something about it.  We need consistent compassion, action, love and contrib… https://t.co/8FXa8C2YcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought Laura a shot of patron and she only took half and I've never been so disappointed in a friend. She poured… https://t.co/Q2mOY8ts1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I can fw another Libra nigga .. it’s just annoying or maybe it was cause he just annoying af]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear my Groupon listens to me, yes I want to go skydiving but even with your coupon I still can’t afford it?? Wh… https://t.co/mD2zpG5oAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDavidFisher @girlsreallyrule @McSkooch It’s almost like he’s an unwitting assistant... 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Benji @BrooklynSpoke Clearly the other message from this photo is bike lanes need protection especially in urban a… https://t.co/hmnqGu0Aus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking green so you know I'm not mean. #greenlife #greensmoothie. #raw @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/pMWsCWlnd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phenylart I’ve made the waitlist in the past when people drop out, but I don’t want to count on that. It’s fine. C… https://t.co/HATcVeBzUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynn lead the path to an amazing @CobbAlp program of excellence! Well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleVillage What can afrofuturism mean for business and industry? For instance, how can my business support its… https://t.co/dZ7jT9cQmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engagement session in Hanna Park | Jade + James {Jacksonville and Ponte Vedra engagement photographer}  https://t.co/RlrSCZvyv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving to different facility today. Heard mixed reviews about it. So very apprehensive I'll let you all know what i… https://t.co/T8r8tN5itp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nervesnnibbles I'm #veggie and traveling to #Amsterdam next month, I'm definitely going to try this place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Climate change is a world problem.  Until it is discussed globally there will no great improvement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s it is! The face off with whiskey.dream and kweeen_yassss!! Had a blast!! Inspired by @jamescharles and his Y… https://t.co/Drvl5ocRW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full Dress Armbruster Chariot Owned by Gloria Austin https://t.co/UfDKE1uXkM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular tweet: them fancy ass cupcakes do not be as good as they look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urknighterrant @apeirophobic @magi_jay If you despise people, because they don't draw the same conclusions see  yo… https://t.co/YmwaRzuxnG]]></document></documents></author>