<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @SteveO3570 Yep.. I want to  know. I am one of Clinton's deplorable. I am 61 year old woman building… https://t.co/f0Rcmshu9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[A los que pensábamos que a los 20 ya íbamos a tener la vida resuelta JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[On some nights like this, i can’t help but think of us, I’ve been reminiscin’, sippin’, missin’ ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ken__stern @JoeMart45807348 @abigailstern1 @VABVOX @PWM62 @SallyAlbright @MrDane1982 Your opinion he was worse, Fa… https://t.co/loG48QKQDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is it any more illegal than all the acts you @realDonaldTrump have done while colluding with Russia🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpMyPres @RebeccaFaussett @gatewaypundit This is America who cares about Pakistan laws, I am so glad we have Tr… https://t.co/1V5L61bRM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m to the point where Im over social media, why do I need to keep up with peoples lives that arent in my life ? Ho… https://t.co/BoNgex1ChD]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to show up, speak up and, as I sometimes do, cut up when necesary, @HouseDemocrats @HouseDemWomen… https://t.co/ZolCPMku3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @SpikeLee on a long-overdue Oscar for you! #morehousecollege #AtlantaAfricanFilmSociety #DoTheRightThing @… https://t.co/0WOvxFrtK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there's anyone who had a Birthday while I was gone, Happy belated Birthday. @ Newark, Delaware https://t.co/s8lfoUfnfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#G4G_LA supporting #foodforwardla 3/16 #OurTownLA https://t.co/Wrz64Qg9Do https://t.co/z0opVWXEui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who getting spanked? Who getting rubbed? Who getting ate? Who getting left? Who getting me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was gonna try and not drink caffeine during the break but i’m only on day 2 and i’m struggling]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quiet beauty ❄️🌨 of a human and a dog walking together through a snowy forest❄️ * * * #Snow #instanature… https://t.co/I26jqzU3wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve tried to take so many girls home and it’s not working #SquareWheels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @TheDemCoalition @mattgaetz Incredible how unprofessional and childish the party of Trump is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSpringer12301 @_MerriamPark @icoachleff @intheKDallmanMP @TammyMotti @mepottersmsd @medeange @MsScarlettSPED… https://t.co/gDVfyq33JO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to kickoff @CEDNC #CEDTechCon! Looking forward to some great networking and learning about rising innovative… https://t.co/xbykSnoWxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of judging those how about you learn how to be fucking bilingual and try to lead a different language estup… https://t.co/c25iKQmIMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sreeja2k @rodgermaIik He was agreeing with Niall you must have read it wrong cause Roger supports Niall  as well h… https://t.co/ZCD1Tsyn6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeauxScalise Bless you and your family. Thanks for supporting our great POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasantly surprised to find hints of other books I’ve read in the ones I’m reading now. ❤️ @StephenKing #theOutsider #FindersKeepers]]></document><document><![CDATA[White Ribbon Night Gala highlight days ahead starting with today.  Showing love and appreciation to the Ice Cold Br… https://t.co/1rAa7jOvOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the first day of Lent. What will you add or give up for 40 days? https://t.co/UEHlbMvrVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a child. You are a mother. How would you feel if your daughter made a mistake and some 34 yr old is attack… https://t.co/DhMHi4GEL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING show @bijoutheatre ! @ErickBaker KILLED it ! 10/10 would definitely recommend! 🌟🙌🏽🥰 https://t.co/GC4HlC1qUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I died my hair blue and it died part of my skin around my hairline and face too🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump I know!  But we need it.....  burn areas, slides and potholes are a mess though.....  but we need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI! I fully blame this one on the #FullMoon! #SnowMoon2019 #ChrisFleming #GayleWatersWaters https://t.co/t64Z6IeDEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 Mom because she was there for me.he was too busy planting his seed]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a disgusting pedophile  perverted phuck up for a President .. Congress get him out of our WH, What an Embar… https://t.co/sgdR8gmbvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to go to city hall during lunch today and really don't wanna https://t.co/3Le2pHLnQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 These signatures are the same signatures as those on the Michael Cohen reimbursement checks for Daniels’… https://t.co/Pkl7PAQ1wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanSciNbanjo @cyn_brooks @RaquelGarciaAnd @eventbrite @latinorebels @LULAC @BarCrawlLive @Latinos4MediaEq… https://t.co/dVfP9SG0sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to see @Sendhil_Rama and @KaviLadnier tonight on #HateF**k!! And meet our beastie friends @DPCeleb and… https://t.co/hjn7evUv1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[While millions are dealing with snow in the NE, a significant severe weather threat taking shape today in the South… https://t.co/BHjughaS2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melwin7777 @tictoc Damn, just tweeted then saw yours. Great minds think alike.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man. I took a deep dive into some very angry “goose the Flerken from @captainmarvel” threads and damn. Men reall… https://t.co/XVCGFLf2VT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it to @TheOfficialROW . Thank you @BookerT5x for the advice and words of encouragement. Absolutely loved it!… https://t.co/1JAOW7AP7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last travel club soccer tournament ever for @samanthakuhr 😭😭😭😭next stop college soccer!!! Two days, four games..bot… https://t.co/xvyxhPZaOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Well he got his "calling" from Mohammed in a space ship (twice) so he's geared to the "out there som… https://t.co/8Kvr9Murfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Stand tall Khloe - sometimes the hardest thing to do is to stand quietly in your trut… https://t.co/DxTVeLuIn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CICsal  buen día vecinos quemando basura Calle 19 y oriente colonia vista hermosa https://t.co/NevRVD21FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's weird that #primeclothing let's you try on panties and return them if you don't like them.  Also, panties is a strange word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz About the definition of witness tampering... "Witness tampering is the act of attempting to alter or … https://t.co/M3RXQa3Zsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou to all who care enough about #humanity , about #freedom , about #Venezuela #FueraMaduro #FueraCuba… https://t.co/VrO7Y6qHDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[But wow Jamal really made me believe it was real smh I just don’t understand why]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodo Awwww! This video truly warms my heart and soul❤️🤗 Storm, a rescued #Pibble is such a love bug! Bless her ama… https://t.co/ztSL5T5apu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should presidents be able to excuse all crimes of their admin on the way out the door?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earth_to_sammie I think so🤷🏽‍♀️ haha I mean it’s all good, I get to see all the photos and videos of Levi from you… https://t.co/F8yTyTGl44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@recordspapers 😀 I tried! And then I was asked me to include my voice instead of text on a project. Important as a… https://t.co/kA2aEIlJhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasticWonder As soon as the cat quits playing with it. Haha https://t.co/sPIFysfmFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Escucha a @liliana_sosa 19 hrs. @AlexDominguezB 20hrs y @azucenau 21 hrs con la mejor información en #MilenioRadio… https://t.co/HuPG4YK03Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What math Rob? White, Christian criminals/rapists get every advantage. There is no hope for our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for the flood waters to recede. #floodwater #floodwaters #water @ Wickliffe, Kentucky https://t.co/wb3KenTHH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStarBrahmas @suede__3 That’s my guy @suede__3 doing his thing! Keep going kid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fixed the backdrop so its appropriate for the occasion! @BDillon04 @mamashark11 https://t.co/hXxAFzAKJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenWing19 @JodiesJumpsuit Nope we have it on occasion also have tuna melts, tuna casserole too. My mom also made… https://t.co/KkYgIAFkTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[quick question: why is my tuition 22k but the toilet paper here is 1-ply]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like ...just thinking about how cute jjongs enlistment pics would be Idk I'm just tormenting myself kfjjf I hate th… https://t.co/MR6vWExNdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to heed ALL THE WARNINGS  ...   WE HAVE A NATIONAL EMERGENCY, A MORBIDLY OBESE CRIMINAL HAS DECLARED WAR… https://t.co/IwesiEzPKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattapanviv @bostonpolice @StreetsBoston @MassDOT @bostonbikeunion @WalkBoston @walkuprozzie @MassBike… https://t.co/cKx7Z0K6BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dreading the Women Tell All tonight. @caelynnmk already has me heart broken from the glimpse of her crying croc… https://t.co/rNzTIcYvpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie rally in Brooklyn right now. Nina Turner tote it up! 😎❤️https://t.co/TvFC8JA1fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howard closing time (@ Provenzano Law in Plymouth, MA) https://t.co/SpJeC3TpvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisyortiz95 Thank you !! And school has been stressful this year :( are you going to be traveling soon !!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blueyeyes524 @matthewamiller @zunderwhelmed Yes!  This is all so exhausting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me jump off this #JussieSmollett hashtag so I can keep my peace tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet He is right but it won’t be trump going down. It will be those who tried to set him up with the Rus… https://t.co/Vfolm79Wg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[holy shit i’m sorry i’m late to the party but lonely codependent is a fucking JAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jayssun_ Prolly cause I don’t post my nudes on twitter for attention lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC_Breaking Since Jordan loves to say what the American people think. We think Jordan is a HYPOCRITE  that is l… https://t.co/xhGXPv7P7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nevada is not a place to drop bombs but to pitch a tent and enjoy a starry sky - @nvlobbyist during #AJR2 #nvleg on… https://t.co/Sn6WkDoApY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #WebDesign job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Java developer at Cognizant #Charlotte, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeWhoWait1776WW Knew they started in that region &amp; were brought in by Jezebel after she married King Ahab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Do not pass go, do not collect any American benefits.  She needs to be at GITMO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Op Art Students traced their 1-point perspective lines and started coloring in a checkerboard pattern to create the… https://t.co/OdHESrluj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lion's mane to Manageable! We donated 8 inches of her locks and still left a small puppy on the floor!   My thick h… https://t.co/ZoGbH81Jgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamWolfMoon @thegirlpurls @flyingleaps @esp1371 @realfranco @tonichelleak @msea1 @akpups @BlairBraverman… https://t.co/edB0x9OQwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowWatching Godzilla the reboot. Those shots of fighter planes plunging one by one into San Francisco Bay (followe… https://t.co/fsu4ZYeXKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Escarcega @SGVNSports Very proud of our 2 boys qualifiers, Trevor and Bradley and our 1 girls qualifier, Ver… https://t.co/cECYd52is0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gramchats @RoseLaoutaris She has blocked and unblocked me 3 times lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosmarin_ @ildivoofficial I'm finding myself and being is a big part of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have 18 more minutes to see him jump and fence AND have a fantasy suite w hannah ?? #TheBachlor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which one of you decided to take their new souvenir for a joy ride?!?✈️🍆🎢 🤣🤣🤣 @ Boston Logan International Airport https://t.co/LkmW4x5X01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go UC! @UMich should follow suit! Open science for all @ORION_opensci @biorxivpreprint @_open_science_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarvalhosa @freddymylovee I second this! Favorites are some of my go to videos to watch. Those and empties!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just going to go live life... ✨ @ Fifth Avenue https://t.co/WyZZHyrZ8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anti Nmdar encephalitis antibodies test needs to b done in any case of swift neuro- degeneration]]></document><document><![CDATA[We see thousands of trucks on the road every day BUT there’s a huge shortage of drivers.   Ahead on @ABC57News I’ll… https://t.co/6Qeg8kBUa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positively interested #BettinaHubby .@KlowdenMann. Need one of those #EyeMasks girl .@HubbyCo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love reading all of these articles about “changing the clocks” for Daylight Savings. Does anyone even have a cloc… https://t.co/FVoMf2ISQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsVanBalkom Set an alarm, @MsVanBalkom!  Totally ok to pop in as able. And remember that #BoostingAchievement chat… https://t.co/elkHMBheF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I looked it up on twitter just now  ..  .. thanks for sharing that info]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so excited to smash some chicken and dumplings in my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow @AlanDersh Alan, Alan, Alan! Remembering who you used to be...confuses me with respect to whom you have bec… https://t.co/7CCEtQRK5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if there will ever be a part of me that doesn’t want to watch Harry Potter when it’s on TV?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broganlovesyou Well we’re almost done with formula thankfully just a couple more months but he’s on no dairy no soy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spaurromance @CarrieAnnRyan You have something great to look forward to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be fair, there is no evidence to support the claim that if a member of the #Trump family lies there are negative… https://t.co/A6wl04GvQw]]></document></documents></author>