<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ShotgunSprD1 @StJohnsBaseball @USDbaseball Definitely a power move that’s for sure. I respect it haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoPunIncluded Maybe I should make a game about theming games and inventing time machines...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: wow I actually got ready in time for school today 🤩 My dog: y’all mind if I run away real quick https://t.co/Up2Cs4iMB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please for God's sake if i was happy 30 min ago and I'm sad for no reason rn please don't take offense I can't alwa… https://t.co/tXD5tBcwwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOregonRA @TR0771N @Carterdsc @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/gFExK6k0mK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live shot of Mr. Kraft having his massage suite raided https://t.co/fN6yfxlMDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[More adventures in exploring Portland’s coffee culture, but this time it was in Beaverton. #portland #beaverton https://t.co/TT7YadT82O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when wake forest starts flaking on these demands by ARC for POC’s to simply be treated as human beings.… https://t.co/l6T7rf3BhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sookright Think those vatos were hoping you were single 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/PPgMulbYx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is saying Giannis and Luka but I’m repping #kubball. Giannis and Joel Embiid, all the way. #comeonson 💪🏼😤🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 guys is one of the most trash burgers and 5 guys hype just shows  How bad America’s cuisine is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to both of our Moms in heaven and our amazing wives that do their best to be the “rose between our thorns… https://t.co/ItF7aFAs01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsG_ReadwMe Michelle, thanks for following! Welcome to an #AwesomePLN Congrats on the 1st chat! My first did not… https://t.co/4owTiY6kA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice little show of personality from Keith. Understand Spence, who has been dying to fight him, not being so amus… https://t.co/62s51izzpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you fix s poorly designed Massey Ferguson oil motor?  You replace the whole boom with one from a Case. @ Log… https://t.co/FHiD7j4zdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iSpeak4Jesus Idols. The flag is an idol it's part of a pseudo religion mixed in with patriotism , the whiteness of… https://t.co/BOLuk40fqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me know when it’s nearly done so I’ll know where to escape, since that will be the only way in or out mkay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman there’s a person on twitter named Joel Gendelman and for split second I was like “did I just discover josh’s burner account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rellsestev The rockets have a contract with att so just to watch them u have to either have cable who has att sout… https://t.co/YQMcwhGJ7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't freakin miss open net opportunities in this leagur, damn it!!! #GoAvsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was buried underneath me and I was on the edge of the bed.. where the fuck they do that at ?! How we have a kin… https://t.co/veU2aDlCUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrinconSiderate @maniamorxxx Damn y’all Gassing this shit to the max... who cares!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback THURSDAY!!! IN THE DUNGEON AKA "CALLIES" THIS MORNING!!! LEGS! SHOULDERS! BACK! BICEPS! #BULLDOG4LIFE… https://t.co/8e8dcRoE08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway countdown clock at the s/e stairway to street at 30th Ave not working—showing time and date]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligé la guerre entre fcc et cach c'est le pays qui perd . Le camps doivent mutualiser sur de principe de bonne gouvernance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Jimmy Carter only Democrat not currently running for President in 2020. https://t.co/dehAZMfqKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexgracia3 Welcome home! 🇺🇸 I'll be in San Antonio soon I'll hit you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 more days in this incredible City.             3 more plays in this incredible show.         Let’s make the most… https://t.co/4M8aabVtLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like all these two guys in this supermarket have too talk about is there kids...meh man I miss my guinea pigs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a song I made. *link in bio* I hope your Valentine's day isn't lonely.  🖤💜🖤 - #lovesick #valentinesday… https://t.co/09NugahYUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for @YouTube grateful for absolutely everything and when @OWNTV #FixMyLife @IyanlaVanzant said to the youn… https://t.co/T7QapMh9Vm]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA is not equipped to handle rain...traffic lights out everywhere 🤦🏾‍♂️ #LArain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bham_United still planning on playing this weekend?  Lot of out of town travelers. https://t.co/LxBbZ8pgdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotoGP kicks off the weekend at Qatar 🇶🇦. Love the on board cameras and telemetry data overlay on @beINSPORTS .  W… https://t.co/YeEIdSz4ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N0mad805 Yeah I kinda knew but it’s been a long time since I’ve been. Sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people applauding at Joe Biden European speech as you can see were democrat representatives and senators from t… https://t.co/vHpxGzPwZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JobberRobb @RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE Not complaining about the story line. However, what was tweeted sounded mor… https://t.co/ePqNWeWiRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenny2Hugs @ConstanceM2015 @ArmorocCA @TPSOToole @arek_janula @lisa_kirkby @BrentCushman @AnonLadyCop… https://t.co/T1ryHxrxRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙄 whooooo, #FeelTheBern2020 Heartburn. Bernie won't stand a chance against 3-4 years of #Trump's economy....  Berni… https://t.co/HY0tNHnimc]]></document><document><![CDATA[...as I was waiting some Scottish guy came up and they wouldn’t let him in and he tried to head butt one of the bou… https://t.co/gFfAkg8sn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karma_Rx Karma can I get a follow!! Wanted to tell u something. Not being a wise guy either. Something positive!! Im serious. Thank u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new sleep schedule got me FUCKED up ... I’m fully rested and it’s 2:20 in the mf morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArsenaLos @UnaiEmery_ I'll put it more on the ref who got all the big calls wrong.  And on our two strikers: both… https://t.co/dX0zVLMc2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[At some interviews in OCI, I was asked why they should hire me (from Rutgers) instead of someone from Penn.   “Beca… https://t.co/ToOCILV68L]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damnit @clydetombaugh        “look, look, look” I just started to like you! HUGE loss, #RIP @kevinandbean]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MAGA movement actually got far more political mileage from the Democrat led Congress NOT condemning Omar than if t… https://t.co/WgLwv7RQd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday June 1st ACC is back in action at the arena at the Westchester county center in White Plains NY for more i… https://t.co/sUkEzxK7Fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vintton @JsnBlackwell1 @AiG As I said you have intentionally preserved your ignorance. That is the only thing that… https://t.co/kQkeedOWQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropping some tunes for #Miami Sexiest Event @modelvolleyball ☀️🏐🤗 #model #volleyball @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/OiUPdtDvCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessiStone @steelyonsports @AndrewGilmanOK @FranchiseOK At the office....sometimes. https://t.co/NvvGbjs7WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryMil26845169 @jaketapper Or as Reagan when said   it's that so much that Democrats are wrong all the time  It's… https://t.co/C4QB7D5XSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brucefalck Well done.  Best leaders in the long run recognize they have 2 ears and one mouth and capitalize on tha… https://t.co/FCIZ08MnkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlicjaMiaa Tak. Masz zapewne rację. Zatrzymane w kadrze . Czasami tylko tyle lub aż tyle ... https://t.co/vRVXT15AOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to down a 5th of whiskey in 2 days: a novel by me https://t.co/xP34oWdeai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebequewest @ThePlumLineGS Remember. Russia and Saudi Arabia are out there trying to divide the Democratic party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rickyh24 @I_AmShe__ @ColeyMick Clearly you’re right as the Celtics beat GSW and the sizers list to Chicago - smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoburnJunior @CTVToronto @VeteransENG_CA @tdsb @LC3_TDSB @paonessaspeeps @JungchoiP @woburndonaldson @schan_tdsb… https://t.co/vFWY3qHzid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude these safe auto commercials on hulu are fuckin hilarious. "Give the sandman your sedan, man, with car pajamas" 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm... what made these fresh tracks in the marsh? #MyMaine https://t.co/7hlxDv1esc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my favorite canine clients! #rafduran33 #dogwalker #dogsofinstagram #comedy #sidehustle #actor… https://t.co/9r8lv4IX5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[True. Remember when he said our ecenemy is in great shape. Immediately then the Great Recession]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has there been any actual evidence against Jussie Smollet shown to the public? Maybe I’m tripping. I just keep seei… https://t.co/5ZBQn8X4Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussiette Smollett crisis acting career is over. Don Lemon will cry on CNN in his Beer. Another Tawana Broley hoax.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“......his first trip......since she...” @GuamPDN is taking this non-binary thing to a whole new level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuky_diablo @unttalhanckoc @manuel70m @davidant264 @ElPincheJuan4 @Gamborimbo76 @maskarita4 @pelon_73 @cero3801… https://t.co/Ql09bQKwm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[BitterSweet...🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽 #SEC#Champions#GEAUXTIGERS _______________________________________________ #Repost… https://t.co/U4dMh4D88S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett Adam Schiff is such an effin idiot and he proves that every time he opens his mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are going Dancing! What a season @GWU_MBK!  @GWUSports @gardnerwebb   #SkoDawgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartburn won’t let me sleep so I guess I’ll finally watch the new Beauty and the Beast 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachB_Sibley @BigB1ue9ation Keep dreamin brother 😂😂 that's why no one answered your top tweet 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I want to share how much I love certain songs but they’re DEVASTATING and then I worry people will think… https://t.co/wOfvtUtsfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@low_nascar @RyanSiegRacing @JClements51 @BrandonBrownRac @XfinityRacing @JCR_Clements51 @KEMMOCupSeries… https://t.co/4BP8N9ASO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Author_PCorrell @BuffaloGregNY @LindseyCDuncan @MarcusCVance @RjSorrento @Michaelbigchees Thanks for the shoutout, Patricia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another veteran piece to the puzzle...he gives us some size to throw too... 🏈🏈🏈🏈🏈 #Colts #ColtsForged #ColtsNation… https://t.co/TJYwKp5vAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is God Damn good right now. - Drinking a Barrel Aged Reboog Vitis (Vanilla) by @GaragisteMead @ Garagiste Mead… https://t.co/yHP9y9YuqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CremasTotal Y nosotros?? Con las divas @rodrisaravia6, @AlexLarin14, lombardi, han pasado más tiempo lesionados, piernas de cristal]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a sound of heaven coming down.  Sound always precedes manifestation!   https://t.co/FjpEoFhzYT  #sound of the #Spirit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tupacarnal @RodriguezManuel L@s mandrile no tienen idea de Cuba, repiten lo q le dicen los medios controlados por… https://t.co/WJIqUSB9K5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karla_agc Estoy igual de echo me molestan los grupos por eso siempre termino saliéndome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This in an article on why we should imitate Germany. Sky high utility bills ‘worth it’. Up next why sky high crime… https://t.co/kxIWfQpbCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve decided to continue the sale however you will have a chance to vote one what part will be on sale for Wednesday 30% off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howiemandel @itsgabrielleu @juliannehough thank you for congratulating me on stage on America got talent on Facebo… https://t.co/k4Tduiq4GO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is @YaOnlyLivvOnce the youngest member of the current women's roster she's the cutest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chat with Steve @jonesysjukebox and #VinnyAppice today on @955KLOS lastinlineofficial @ 955KLOS https://t.co/JUENlgkW3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve long been in favor of legalizing most types of prostitution. But not if it involves kids. Never, not under any… https://t.co/7j1ZycV7lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passing by the Sir Francis Drake Hotel.  Always makes me smile.  Great lobby bar.  I foreclosed on it once.  (When… https://t.co/xaTpqJYVPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have siblings but sometimes I feel like this when anyone asks for a piece of what I have]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @LAFC why’d you guys never came on @935KDAY I had been listening confidently I was gonna take some of those tic… https://t.co/SiXifCk0jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElyseDehlbom my fiancé wants to know where you got your statement dress?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 Failure to accept responsibility, too lazy to take on the the requirements of the job...and always the… https://t.co/zvQJ4tw9A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulgarian Split Squats 💪❤️ . . . . . . . . . . #fitfam #carterfitness #carterfitnessrules   #TrainHard #Gains… https://t.co/7XUkk9EP4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oklahoma City's Diallo leaps over Shaq to win dunk contest  https://t.co/yEsaaBrb2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0ZNeyPuqBO My Location. Rex Is OK, I'm Having A Great Time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middleton gotta force their hand put their best offer so it puts pressure on them. 10yr 326 with a 5 year opt out.… https://t.co/XqZpvOh1Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been long time no cooking😢💔. However,today I made a great dish which is called OZY, decorated the plate with a… https://t.co/iaz21oNNoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like Hitman’s energy, but I feel like KB would catch him with a meat hook and knock him out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. @CruzPerzCuellar , la estrategia de intervención militar en 2006, el número de homicidios dolosos aumentó de 1… https://t.co/9HNWWu54f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s win, Sharks! (at @SAPCenter at San Jose in San Jose, CA) https://t.co/EWx7HgiTP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattzollerseitz @baddestmamajama @DanaSchwartzzz Tried to kick conventional soda (diet or otherwise), made it 2.5… https://t.co/zVF8l0edPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look.  We know there are plenty of idiots and morons out there.  They’re the only people who come to your rally TV… https://t.co/cqzN5hfo9u]]></document></documents></author>