<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's finally here! Our most powerful elixir to date - Ultimate Supreme #DualElixir. Formulated with camélia oil, ar… https://t.co/WIBl5bYSSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamShowtyme_IG @PFF Great question.  We have 500 people working for @PFF so we can do live grading with multiple… https://t.co/FyKb9QYfCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber praying for you hun always fall back on God when rough times fall into your life God bless you babe l… https://t.co/zGmEMLsUew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean @HarperCollins Janice i saw you several times on fox news today. Omg you are fabulous. I have been home… https://t.co/iMfeGwgmWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not attracted to Gillian Anderson I don’t even know what to say and I’m borderline ace at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I crying because I’m tired or because my soul is tired?   Did someone press pause or repeat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent all this money to go to the eye doctor and I can see LESS than I did before https://t.co/POOI4mGlqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@25itsjustme I might have autism and I have anxienty and had a hard past life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to feel like a sexy badass warrior goddess ? Take a Buti Yoga class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current lap situation. Just living my best #dogmom life. #allthesnuggles #houndlife #houndsofinstagram #beagle… https://t.co/lorCKEZLOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[the financial aid office puts you on hold forever bc theyre all spitting at a picture of u for bothering them #fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can admit that sometimes there’s episodes of shows that I like simply because my OTP has moments in it and I’m no… https://t.co/QtNvhBz6NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally obsessed with him. I was so excited to watch him live at #UFCPhoenix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin and you'll feel better. So, you hate me when I'm drunk??? Well we're even then, because I hate you when... https://t.co/KrK44TRMDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little ball of sunshine has taken over the station today! Meet Soleil, a sweet girl who’s name means ‘sun’ in… https://t.co/mtgLXwzg13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love weddings that get ratchet at the end... Salt shaker. Bend over make your knees touch your elbows. The filthier, the better 💃🏼🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Latina elected officials in San Francisco! And tonight, about to talk more about leadership development within… https://t.co/kCF5TdsvUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benradigan @CornyLink667 @MarvelStudios Or maybe it's just cause they dont have a thesaurus... https://t.co/UivhGb4vBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man reminded me why I fell in love with him in the first place today and it couldn't have came at a more perfect… https://t.co/SYJ9tLeJmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doug_Lemov Actually what helps me process the best is those things plus I make a slide deck as if I was going to p… https://t.co/WEFgTlML4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s literally a #snowstorm in #LasVegas     Crazy!   #LasVegassnow https://t.co/CoCSqJH36G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beverlywilshire #beverlywilshire #beverlyhills fendi #fendibaguette #fendi @RodeoDriveBH #rodeodrive @mrchow… https://t.co/QXbCmqJVTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st Rangers game, lots of excitement!😁🥅🏒 @ Madison Square Garden https://t.co/i2ayNmEq7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must look outside the box to find solutions on how to alleviate and assuage the current problems we keep facing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aubinfrancois68 @Olivier_Brett @GeorgesLaraque @919sports J’ai raté ça !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @JussieSmollett 2) To add fuel to the fire. But well, when it comes to Turkey, for a start there is n… https://t.co/GvWPz6zhAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary — and it was even earlier on my @CreativeSage… https://t.co/fUEi7qaHps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sedan Service Number (703) 459-9666 Call us to Book Sedan Car https://t.co/Ry2U72ncRw https://t.co/vFiUv0yNw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyPeakChallenge I’m 71 too! Still in the foundation program but I’ll get there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanson Well the whole “I’m crawling in my own shit and vomit” message in slack made me miss you less. #tansontales see you Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchingWhatYou Gee.  Jim must not listen when Trump talks, because he doesn't open his mouth without lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marco Demaria - Breast cancer treatment increases cellular senescence (aging) and higher levels of cellular senesce… https://t.co/Dc2M4Hxwpf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love the outdoors, you'll love this house. . . . .#newenglandliving #southshorerealestate #norwellrealestate… https://t.co/8vo7RWkAbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very true - just off my @heroicspeaker training - and this is exactly the message we heard from @neenjames last nig… https://t.co/BReJKJE2EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[These olds in the back all signed releases how satisfying!!! #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemajlak Omg I haven’t used Facebook in almost a year I bet all my friends think I died😂👌💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cold February afternoon at the Newton Union Cemetery, established in 1854. Newton, Iowa. #cemetery #graveyard… https://t.co/dImgzDwRI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished hiking 1.03 miles in 1h:03m:35s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/DvVIeQbwNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I do know is I will vote for whatever Democrat runs against Trump in 2020, no matter how far from mine their i… https://t.co/nRwTfCPkbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomgreenlive Hi I’m new to your page, but I just wanted to say Congratulations on winning the Favorite house guest… https://t.co/VrsuyQAWdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read the most eye opening book after the successive death of my 3 siblings - The Denial of Death by Ernest Becker… https://t.co/loxSAMHQEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that being unhappy with myself was just how I would be, as everything I tried just didn’t seem to work.… https://t.co/3nhAXy3XyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give, give, give! Still 40 min left in #ChicoStateGivingDay and you can show that #CatsGiveBack - help us unlock th… https://t.co/d64Xg9jqmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Friends &amp; Happy Thursday!! 🌸 . I’m excited and honored to be this week’s featured guest host for… https://t.co/k2HH3FxKHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cindylou178 @bbbtmenw I love expresso I love the taste of coffee I really don't care for too much sugar I just lik… https://t.co/C45knuydts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenLong1967 Oh I agree that for limited purposes govt is required and does good. But asking schools to take on the… https://t.co/rViaR1ofIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooked out steak. Couldn't eat it. Tried to eat a Reeses egg &amp; couldn't Am I gonna die? FML Lmao 🐬]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwbackthursday to my book launch for The Secret of the Codex, exactly 6 months ago today!! (Shoutout to… https://t.co/MiDWsr0R0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIPS ON LIPS TOMORROW #TiffanyYoung  #BestSoloBreakout  #iHeartAwards  @tiffanyyoung https://t.co/S0U3JfGhO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Oreo Cookie Day and pre-happy birthday to Kinsley!  #homeroom #pacerpride https://t.co/d5BmDoIeN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your brothers hate groups texts so you just text them all the same thing 🤪❤️ https://t.co/X7MCiGSsF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my comp "Chivy" will be performed by the East Central Univeristy Flute Ensemble under the direction of Alexan… https://t.co/mpZpBJ0s8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MXYZ_ @cnalive @matthewschmitz Again: Melbourne, Australia, Feb 25, 2019 / 06:21 pm (CNA).- Prosecutors have aband… https://t.co/2JD08Wa2x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss She has a painting in her closet that has deteriorated bigly. (The Picture of Dorian Grey).]]></document><document><![CDATA[He sure does know how to use map quest to find his way. He sure is faithful! To golf.🏌️‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Case Keenum to the redskins... I’m gonna start praying for him now. 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful jog by the Halifax River... over the bridge twice... Happy President’s Day  🏃🏼‍♀️🏃🏼‍♀️🏃🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/BPT3qBm0u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @realDonaldTrump Dirty Harry was as crooked as they come and being ill does not negate all his evilness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently Kayla is a rock star. Rock n roller coaster take 2 but as single riders this time. @ Rock 'n' Roller Coa… https://t.co/7aIyw7gcFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 2 have a big ask: if you enjoyed Life on the Leash would you leave a happy Goodreads or Amazon review? Postiv… https://t.co/I3LbrmEHJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #InternationalWomensDay! I'm celebrating all the strong, amazing, kind, and compassionate women around me—incl… https://t.co/Yj5rTB1jTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D0R0THYGALE @harlowdeco AS IF you aren’t one of the four we were initially referring to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Biden Beto ticket is my choice.  I think they can beat Trump together!!!👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @CNN @NewDay Thanks for the heads up.  I never watch CNN, but because you'll be on, I'll make an exc… https://t.co/J54kVYIJzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crayons_coffee And thanks for giving my other one some extra TLC yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont usually overthink, but when i do, its when i have to be awake in 5 hours to drive 4 hours home and spend the… https://t.co/Kb27b3wiLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyMila @GeneralHospital But I think that was a clue Drew. Because he didn't push Drew. That is what his mom's… https://t.co/86E5fIi8cJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdetler @RachelintheOC @sugarbeatbc @HMJonesWrites @annerallen @TheRuralVA @fahma311 @jonathabrooke… https://t.co/wIi6alGkEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[snicker for some stress relief. #funniness #tee-hee #smile #amusing https://t.co/Lx6WJnWK9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wait, what? You want us to paint over our pastel colouring in black paint !!!??”      #artclass https://t.co/Dtkt18wbrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been applying to jobs as an RN and I’m trying not to freak out about being an adult https://t.co/msH5HccGau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Chris3BM @courtneym8216 Good morning friends. Here comes the weekend! Spring ahead....🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am speechless, what’s up with teacher pushing their views on children #WalkAwayFromDemocrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HHypocrisy101 @AngeleStar11 @jack The music group REM is raising hell over it. Not sure this one is Jack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me a bitch but I’m kick people out idgaf if you’re naked you gotta go]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom surprised showed up at my gig tonight and when I got offstage she said l, “you were fine.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is There More to Love Than Just KALEIDOSCOPE? https://t.co/WbmUbRwDpm https://t.co/fFmwBlkGfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[(\__/)     ⠀  (•ㅅ•)      Me making a decision 　＿ノ ヽ ノ＼  __    /　`/ ⌒Ｙ⌒ Ｙ　ヽ   ( 　(三ヽ人　 /　　 | |　ﾉ⌒＼ ￣￣ヽ　 ノ     ヽ＿＿＿＞､… https://t.co/DcJ7EDL4u7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u have to add a link to your old watch&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't think I was going to complete my first Mahashivratri but here I am with one more hour to go. Thank you… https://t.co/eUuwvn9ZSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linda took on Eden like a pro #edengroupies @ EDEN https://t.co/F4FzjMJvbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthhill74 @hallmarkmovie @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott My favorite mystery! And yes that look said it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesse is scheduled (for the 3rd time) to get his much needed gall bladder surgery tomorrow. Keep ur fingers crossed… https://t.co/1h2qWbIz1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ironhorse76 I blocked her, but viewed her tweets and reported her. She needs to be reported by everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving #sxsw - such a great event for networking,  innovation and ideas. . . . Also helps that it is warm and sunny… https://t.co/ldWxqoytx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh goody! I’ve been going on and on about how my neck had gained weight lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haiitsaubree I have a Michael Kors tote to carry daily. It’s more structured and water resistant. It’s on year 2 o… https://t.co/YFRQWTy0dL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp Meghan Jones here at @CPAC I wanted to show you this I wanted to see if you read my letter to Kristen gav… https://t.co/qBsdgGXkGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wellhaythere RIGHT?! Did you read the responses people have had to the article? I cannot believe we let these people have children?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor Anthony Steven Evers: Remove Angela Sutkiewicz from Steven Avery case - Sign the Petition!… https://t.co/rqTLhPtSdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatssohawke Thanks! A lot of this was the culmination of months of work - with the framework laid things came tog… https://t.co/60iPRDGGmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still going strong at 116! The oldest living woman is Kane Tanaka from Fukuoka, Japan, according to Guinness World… https://t.co/TkDFXtJPX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Lindsey, you need to see a shrink as your positions change hourly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher Really! I know no one that wants to be you! Get in real touch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen: *lies*   Republicans: He’s not lying!   Cohen: *gets caught*   Republicans: Lol  Cohen: *confesses, says the… https://t.co/Qbn3hDAAEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basser069 @WPLGLocal10 And I when I worked in California ans Arizonia I had my fair share of forecasting snow &amp; severe weather too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurnie234 Yes me and the other advisor say we watch to make sure ",nobody runs off to get married" 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[YSNCMAFAKP!!!!!  First person who can guess what this stands for correctly wins a prize. I’m still debating on what said prize will be.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting news!! Congrats @brave @attentiontoken @brendaneich and @TAPCOIN    I've been a fan of the Brave browser f… https://t.co/KDVbuNHqlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summit helps LGBT businesses reach new heights https://t.co/VPgfXv9FKw https://t.co/aqAGZ0C127]]></document></documents></author>