<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@eusouabal já lembrei uma coisa que ficou no Brasil. Meu difusor da Deva. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarajevo is my favorite song by @gwatsky and @camilarecchio vocals killed it. 😋 https://t.co/1CjHeYt25l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude on bumble thought brockhampton was a “his” ... its over thank u next https://t.co/B2qQDhPOUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you GE for a fabulous picture and we are excited to collaborate in our Journey for Renovation Lifestyles!… https://t.co/Zn3JLVKml2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephJFlynn1 @Truthplease5 @BarbaraRedgate @GenFlynn Blessings ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!  This is a great idea so people willall day to vote and not worry about being late for work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of us actually have good personalities unlike the pretty sassy uptight bitches 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️ looks aren’t everyth… https://t.co/pxPqMXj9iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinOropeza Don’t know if you have tried @Blabberize, it is similar 2 ChatterPix. 🤷🏽‍♀️What others have you tri… https://t.co/ORPGG7XjAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deanodon I do feel like the only good decision I made was to avoid Logan. 10 minutes from my car to the gate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePatriot006 This is so insane. Neither the gazzelle.or.the.leopard have access to guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ofctimallen We bought tix in Columbus, OH! You are worth the drive from Cincinnati 😃😃😃 Thanks so much for coming t… https://t.co/k2sn4Jlswv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I see now why @BillyforPhilly has a Facebook page full of praise. He just blocks anyone critical of him. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Sara for your passion for our kids and the important work you do! #NVLeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all Sorors to the floor! Subscribe to the #DeltaBox and save $10 using my referral link!  https://t.co/70EWS9NET3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do think the way Patti LuPone says “We’ll... You’ll be handed power on a plate” in the Evita Tony broadcas… https://t.co/QhM7URoFlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backstreetboys So when are you going on tour together again! #nkotbsb? 2.0 ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swiftlyshannon So there’s a surgery called rotationplasty that some of my pediatric sarcoma patients get that take… https://t.co/yl3g4x4m3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy llevaré a 3 de mis sobrinitos a una fiesta YO SOLA.. espero sobrevivir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah flowers are cool for valentines day but have you ever heard of a chimmy bt21 oversized pillow]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Breaking News 🚨 Sending a big 🗣shout out to my #GoldenScholars in #KinderCollege @ClevelandHCPS 🐾 for taking and… https://t.co/fm4SHNL0mY]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUSH TRIAL: Details from that day are intricate. To further clarify, the belt in question was the subject of a tran… https://t.co/gV93DB3vnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Malinda_Hodges The funny thing is that announcer probably mispronounces his own mother's name. He was pitiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skgates So sorry for your loss of your beautiful Oscar. That last photo is absolute love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I look forward to EVERY year on my birthday, my @Twitter balloons!   Something I JUST realized:  You can… https://t.co/SOv4H2L2PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgalleg4 Which I think is wrong. If it takes two people, and the fetus has 50/50 DNA, father’s should have 50% say… https://t.co/RAHzkeuTJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gooooiid Morning💋 #TampaOutcall available 24/7🌇🌃 #TampaIncall only at certain times🤷🏻‍♀️ I travel all over Florida🤗… https://t.co/8IIAJnSjHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yayayayayay!!!! #BroadwayBackswards2019 is going to be wonderful! Come one, come all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your website had a smell, what would it be? What was that one elusive scent one can never quite match in airport… https://t.co/rRwmQXZ7M4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuggleNet ...the only Stone currently in existence belongs to Mr. Nicolas Flamel, the noted alchemist and opera lo… https://t.co/0UP4rLT7pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mary___LA @StillJohnCA @goodnewcatchy probably a bot who couldn't see John's profile pic complaining about a "too bad, so sad" tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauliCat3 @SHi75333764 Hi to both!! Happy #Caturday!! https://t.co/Yo4fl2MZvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contemplating on getting a GoPro for all the crazy shit I’m about to do in Germany]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like Valentine’s Day when I’m single cause I have zero disappointment cause I have zero expectations 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeTheBlackCat Poor Tortie, no kitty deserves such horrible treatment. I have a Tortie and she is the love of my… https://t.co/8gEa2dMc7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msinsulindpndnt @tweetybirdnnc God Damn Pharmaceutical Companies! 728.40 a mo for insulin! This is not something a… https://t.co/JHE9bGwZhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to “speak books” to our students— read what they read! @pernilleripp #MRA2019 @LarsonMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought myself a promise ring and I couldn’t be more happy for it to come 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qanon76 @realDonaldTrump This Russia thing has gone way too long.  No proof Trump colluded Russia.  How much has t… https://t.co/j8foXLBcLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenngranzin @SeiIlMioSole18 @kaylovin__ @ChelseaHouska I’m glad you got to have that moment. My grandpa passed awa… https://t.co/4Pl8hzVwRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliCann1 @MbQueenbee3 @army_bc @DKNE4Sure @EmmadeeH @Susanne09248043 @TerryannScott @blondedolphin17… https://t.co/37ZYjzQ2x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i want to punch my boyfriend in the face because he literally does not ever ever reply to my text messages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Snapchat #PlayingAround #bored @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/HeuTYB9N6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmgivingsoul @RunhappyKat @runnergirl1612 @MelissaKahn7 @JustJane2019 @Dracaenawines @Cbp8Cindy @KellyMitchell… https://t.co/cYW9Vy97Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biiankizzle I hate Gatorade. You know this. That eliminates me from your suspect’s list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yell0wheart Are you on the patio? Him: wearing VGK grey October 1 sweater. Me: wearing white Route 91. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binghamology @ALLTRUEMAN1 I had to end a relationship with a man over this once because he had my prayer life unde… https://t.co/m4I4uUvlJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooo Ludas early music was the shit. I remember wanting them air force ones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfonsoDurazo Alfonso porque celebra?? Con que van a combatir a los delincuentes de la Iztacalco?? Con resorteras?… https://t.co/A1sOsU8MZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew she was going to be a girl! I called it and if you don't believe me check out their maternity blog post. Lay… https://t.co/HMGlIMYA80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally ended up listening to a few more songs than the couple I knew...heard the whole thing and ❤️ it! https://t.co/GvInJnv488]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: *retweets something at 400 retweets* *tweet jumps to 18k* me: *gasps* my impact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews @megynkelly Please call for his prosecution to the fullest extent of the law. Wasted resources, cri… https://t.co/XeXQa8s47f]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTW @clydetombaugh, my 8yo is totally infatuated with @GreenDay. Knows every word of every song and can't believe t… https://t.co/dD0hzVObFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonsross And the teachers are burned out because they are having their pensions stolen, putting $100s of their… https://t.co/tzb7ytMzuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just sayin... if there’s no worship today, I’m not voting for any of y’all @_nia_carter_ @belijahneal @carter_haupt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nadinereigns You’ve always been so damn positive and up beat! Keep fighting. There’s always a light ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be fooled by how datacenter are fueled: Greenpeace calls out AWS and Dominion Energy for its ‘dirty data’ cri… https://t.co/FXSZ8yNPzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad day for Indiana. We need to do better by all Hoosiers! Not just the ones that look, pray, and love like you.… https://t.co/wYlH1pVqpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorLankford I'm sure that was your excuse. However, Trump authorized the Interior department to allow drilling… https://t.co/87B3lIrQsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIRD COLLECTION: available now on site (link in bio) @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/OOPTXX1Z9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[i remember when i got starbucks w this guy and he ordered s Strawberry Açai and was making me carry it because he d… https://t.co/Bq8P2vDVUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVH516GIS @FoxNews @foxnewspolitics Same reason fellow Ken Starr elf Barf Kavanaugh does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just click and follow me on the gran... no need to go search for me.   https://t.co/INo2wGKUwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto He shouldn’t be treated any differently than anybody else who would do such a stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalishChannel @Spice5400 I knew Squidward was a bad clarinet player... but I didn't think he could kill Freiza...]]></document><document><![CDATA[faux should be destroyed. The garbage they spew hurts americans and they only care about money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVW5 Why are you giving a voice to this piece of trash who voluntarily left Canada to support an ideology which p… https://t.co/RLbPttRuLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just going to leave this right here! Say their names @AOC @AyannaPressley @RashidaTlaib #RepresentationMatters… https://t.co/wF1kagpl96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikaelahelane Now understand why I’m not huge fan train travel especially a young woman alone? Because lawlessness… https://t.co/Ps0xXxOlS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz @BuddySchweitz I have never seen a dog do that, Buddy Boy is too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[The soundtrack for this movie is 100 times better than it should be and it makes me so bad. #ElyssaWatchesFSOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the fathers &amp; all the the sons on the globe should be forced into a theater to watch @Gleason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyChamp7 Not what i meant to say.  It is the other way around.  Did not proofread before sending]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to have been the person behind the camera interviewing Brian for this. Life is epic. What a moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the man on HWY 13 in the right lane with your right turn signal on... please don’t make that turn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iMikla @MLE_Online @RueNahcMohr Big thing with machining stainless a lot of the alloys work harden rather rapidly,… https://t.co/fXyEAw1mPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[yesterday was full of great moments with my @MaryMMouser , but this one had to be my favorite 💕  #bestfriend… https://t.co/Rp0k6UoGn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[(deleted previous because I just woke up and therefore wrote “write” which is not RIGHT)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMcMullin No. The coalition of ppl who want ACA, gun safety, climate change study, fair wages, voter rights, ge… https://t.co/OxbDIH9waV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSugarLily @Maggieb1B @1RealLori @tillmantweets @JoeBoss1020 @Boyd_2650 @busylizzie48 @Kellie2727Paula… https://t.co/GznGxBq6ZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erika_cortez8 But it’s getting played out or I am probably just hating because I can’t party 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any man of mine...❤ #ShaniaTwain #anymanofmine #KaraokeNight #nashville https://t.co/bmguspMjVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought morning skinny was a myth but I experienced it this morning; the key is to not wear your glasses while getting dressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul The problem is your bill won’t pass. We BOTH know that. Rather than stand with POTUS you want to make the… https://t.co/5oIYHId8iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GroundBreakingNews The 1 on 1 BIZ CONSULTS with Lady Bizness are back just in time for Spring! Let me help your bu… https://t.co/d9O5brqfdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer I no longer say "How dumb can you get?"  Some Republican always shows me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini @iamAutumn61 @realvickimars I adore her as well , she cracks me up 😂 Good for her for going to school 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attn: Today is National Drink Wine Day! I will celebrate by drinking wine like I do every night 🍷 Cheers 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading in to #NYC for the @gaaaysinspaaace viewing party. https://t.co/Zxq6gRcvM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caesar_is_home_ @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews I speak with the voice of the popular vote: something your Comrade Hambe… https://t.co/MWI8Xn85us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders I did this. When family was coming over on Sundays for dinner, my mom would set the table with one of t… https://t.co/wH0p8prtDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVNDO209 Ilovemakonen is a perfect example 😂 nigga got signed to ovo then the fuck drake tweets came up]]></document><document><![CDATA[#4725 has this contest on lock down! We are ALL in!!! #hd4725 #wehaveyourback #d39proud @TamaraRoden… https://t.co/rswQNteWvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monthly Horoscope - March Monthly Horoscope 2019  https://t.co/CDT8dTx9Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobconrad4 @nytimes Shameful and untrustworthy person I have ever known. I mean his best friend is Rush Limbaugh,… https://t.co/jxM2MMLUvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin Beck showing off his speed! Beats the throw and collects a hit and an RBI, driving in Jeremy Eierman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clear your calendar! When We Band Together Pop-Up in NYC next Monday- #ZoeBands #KeepChildhoodAlive… https://t.co/DFZXyOCR06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun times promoting Pork at the Iowa Speedway 🍻🐷 https://t.co/nJwr0l95Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between watching Abducted In Plain Sight and keeping up with this Kardashian drama...there’s no way I’ll be able to… https://t.co/Arz58QHCVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a great experience at the Nora @INBMV! Thanks for making something adult and boring not so bad! #indy]]></document></documents></author>