<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump How bout #ImpeachTrump . Like that better? If even 1/3 of the testimony of Cohen checks o… https://t.co/aHBIZ59X9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[when my mind really wants me to realize something it just keeps repeating in my thoughts like an alarm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolls_ross77 Hahahaha damn definitely the wrong day to tweet this but come onnnnn this Jonas brothers reunion is about to be unreal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenMcLiteracy @HeatherPiSTEM Me too! I’m super excited to have some then to bond with/mentor my group.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystiChan @broadwaybabypod Agreed! I was absolutely planning to watch and it’s gone!! 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night networking with NABE key presenters and President, Margarita Pinkos, Alberto Carvalho, Miami Dade Super… https://t.co/KeyNUM9Wdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Softball play a non league competition at Pacifica today @ 330pm #Saints @SCVarSoftball @schs_asb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh...4-6” more snow tomorrow night into Sunday. Blizzard conditions.  I need to check my scotch supply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luceroo_mariel Omg chikistrikis means that?! That’s my sisters dogs name 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over halfway through the third quarter. Only four points total in this stanza.   Waynesville 28, Purcell Marian 23 - 2:45, Q3. #cincyhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaBrownCNN What the heck is happening! Congratulations on your baby ! And by the way u look terrific ! Thanks for the great reporting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love asking all the faded guys at the house for money 😂😂 they all bust out quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great article about a great human being! Thanks for sharing it with us @KodwoGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Yet DT is silent on the Coast Guard terrorist, his ties to Epstein, the 12 dead yesterday in Baltimore. Hypocrisy]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, how was your Saturday night?  @KISSOnline @genesimmons @theforum #losangeles #Kiss #metal #music https://t.co/rY1DrzQ3vT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles fuck anyone who makes you feel inferior. i speak with a lot of history of self insecurity, depression… https://t.co/wksTng122x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PanamaGold Lmao I bet! But God gon bless you for giving that lady a sandwich!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faculty Mtg diving into ESSA data using Data Wise! I noticed... I wonder... https://t.co/p11OrH5vWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool project! 🦐 Can stocking re-establish a sustainable amphipod population and help restore wetlands?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want someone to look at me the way Bradley Cooper looks at @ladygaga ❤️ https://t.co/WWGaXEDTio]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been sick for the majority of 2019 and I ain’t taking it no more so I finally brought my lazy ass to urgent care 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[An extra cheesy date night with @clintjames_1 at @TheMeltingPot 🧀 https://t.co/2n2ead5KZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always follow your bliss. I did 16 years ago when I left corporate America to become a Realtor. Best decision I eve… https://t.co/ViL1xh0QZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I moved into my dads today!  Hopefully things look up now, and I can enjoy my senior year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know how fast you truly are till you have to make it from one end of the airport to the other to catch yo… https://t.co/THDYPKaNXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @fabnana74 Huge hug &amp; congradulations coming your way. Thank you for living.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee I don't know about brave but I agree it is a new world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loves_nra @PaulaLanier54 @USATODAY It's amazing how #Democrats #persecute everyone who they oppose before a fair h… https://t.co/ML5m3hfbVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many more times is this gonna happen.   I fucking hate cops.  Only assholes want to be cops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what will win, but The Favourite or Roma are the ones I’d like to win #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHELLAheartyou @LetsGetLexi I wish you were!!  Maybe I’ll get to see Lexi and Hunter though!! Well send you a pic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please please let this picture go viral I want to see this on the local news I want to see this everywhere cause it… https://t.co/sLPazn0KBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SageHillfarms I know you don't. I also know you do the right thing if you have to. We all be here for you either way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWJaneTheVirgin okay when raf’s dad died and they said i love you for the first time it was so mf amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[All i want rn is to be at Disney with my love eating a cream cheese pretzel. 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaShanneStokes Rupert/Roger Ailes started the ball rolling, chump just turned us into Humpty Dumpty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverRadio @RMGduji Eating too few carbs puts your body in a state of KetoACIDosis... your body becomes acidic and… https://t.co/UNzSYN4TAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 That is true, but if we don’t start taking him seriously as a candidate, he will be the worst 2-term President we’ve ever had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend @samiam6202 just sent me this - happening on Markham Woods rd now @WFTV chopper launching now! https://t.co/XTpmJTomAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__BlackPyramid i want to become a Neonatal/NICU nurse because i love babies and knowing that i helped them get a c… https://t.co/Gw9APZ5vcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍✌️✌️🇲🇽🇲🇽 _jacky234 #roadtrip #mexico @ Pancho's Bar https://t.co/hiB99eR1lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from the “Tweet Deck” perch during the @UI_HPG symposium. We were so busy capturing all the advice and lesso… https://t.co/A2mIpeq7Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaireCervenak @ChrisQuinn64 @dbroaddrick @mraspinall @ThirstyBeesNY @BiscottiNicole @bbray27 @JayBilly2 @brewerhm… https://t.co/t7fFkCi0xW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie @BernieSanders At the very least apply the same scrutiny to him that you always have all things, Clinton. Just be fair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for all of the gen ed teachers working on their #ESL endorsement pathways with U of R that started today… https://t.co/lW9pD4l8x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a teacher is going 12 hours without using the bathroom quite by accident.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with my forever valentine ❤️ @JawwadJLove  #theloveconnection #ValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/CFP2D75BcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg my cramps are the worssttttt currently dying at this beautiful wedding hahah. 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is what you make it! Choose to make the most out of every day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have trust in our leader at Rosa Parks because she has been our leader for 20+ yrs and you tried to blame her fo… https://t.co/OF9tWXONCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badjamjam If they are receiving vaccines, you can bet the taxpayer is getting the bill !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScrubHill66 @AndrewScheer @PierrePoilievre @CPC_HQ Lol. Yeah ok.  Upstanding antics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @accpchest Friday (2/15) @ 12 pm CT for the 1st LIVE episode of The Inside Scoop talk show! Join for a chance… https://t.co/HVa8yaTPx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_brundige @Jhogan552 @sealmh @resister_mike @StandwithNathan @goldenrule_247 @Mysstyblue @BruhManInSoCal… https://t.co/4ycyxuL0UH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorneZiemer @MSNBC @mitchellreports She is old and losing her grip.  W/O Hillary to follow around, she has no motivation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are unrelated to the safety dance although i dont doubt that i would go that hard to the safety dance. https://t.co/QJquYASIRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnfollowTrump WTH??? When did it become racist to advise folk to vote?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at TSHA: therapist appreciation goodies from the most awesome company... #weareT2K #weimprovelives  #tsha2019… https://t.co/lpVDezuBen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deej2771 @AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN Defending genocidal maniacs is not a good take.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DefLeppard WATCHING YOUR SEXY ASSES RUNNING ALL OVER ENTERTAINING YOUR FANS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptrzykd It isn’t weird one bit 💖💖💖💖 it’s my inspiration to keep going even when I don’t feel like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ BobGoff for this encouraging nugget. https://t.co/j1l9DGYJMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who was wondering what’s up at #ChezStacy slash #BriscoeBistro? 😉🤣 So glad you asked: pan-seared halibut, white cau… https://t.co/0VX9JDl088]]></document><document><![CDATA[X 401 was such a good place for me. It served its purpose and I’m grateful for that. I’m going to miss it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EderinhoGaytan @grillomachine @mediotiempo @XgenMty 😂😂😂 https://t.co/bq7QeWJF4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a ball at the KNK concert tonight! Glad to be a supportive Tinkerbell! They crushed it! #KNKINCHICAGO #KNK… https://t.co/UUg56wKoaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joke - Schiff wants to know what Trump and Putin talked about!  Why don’t they go after Obamass when he clea… https://t.co/bRBuy3S6fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow was cleared enough for me to go into third gear so that’s monumental]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southernvl1 @Dj_Gumster @PrtyCentrlRadio @sheri_lynn95252 Thanks Sweetie! It was a fun project! She's so talented!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytdavidbrooks You overlook the biggest challenge we face — Climate Change. It depend on where you live, but here… https://t.co/f3BriBBT8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coryrbenson Omg that’s awesome! The second owl creeping in the background is hilarious~ thank you Cory!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5b20be6386164f8 @castellanosce This is the most beautiful thing I’ve seen all day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenSoutar1 @Kaled1974 @Cosmonautdude Gibby was good at managing veterans, so it made sense to go in a different… https://t.co/RdJGk1YzHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My therapist reminded me of how much growth I’ve had in just a month. I’m so proud of myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While a little outdated, I still stand by this video as the best way to learn the presidents. #1850ReallyNifty… https://t.co/PadoH458O7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Trump: Kraft has “proclaimed his innocence” A familiar phrase from @POTUS. Trump dismisses the seriousness again!☹️😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley environmental horrors they've committed in the name of lining the pockets of the already absurdly… https://t.co/Jy2H3H5cr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Low carb chicken strips with cauliflower mash potatoes and sauteéd beet spirals! #fitsciencellc #wnbf #wnbfpro #rgv… https://t.co/sj2w2hhkP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickenboo23 I will always “appreciate” the umbrella/singin in the rain tragedy, because well, they really went fo… https://t.co/s2OAw7vO7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@octaviaspencer @kylebuchanan I loved that you were thanked a billion times last night! 💕💕💕 You are an amazing inspiration!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Americans need livable wages...We got Part time min wage jobs up the wazoo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a WFR is really strange because I’m certified to do some things even EMTs can’t do but only in the fucking wilderness lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a manager I can complain to about the fact that DST is forcing me to lose an hour of sleep literally two days before my defence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl @ my job today was crying about no one picking up her shift because she had homework, WE ALL GO TO SCHOOL… https://t.co/dBSxyQ0Lir]]></document><document><![CDATA[The judge is seriously pissed off. I'd be surprised if Stone isn't locked up after his next court hearing.  The fiv… https://t.co/E5Q5koeSTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendyhowell711 @WeAreCisco @gigiwang1019 @taniakatan Is there a RSVP link?]]></document><document><![CDATA[me ‘n you babe 👻  happy love day 💕 from this silly turtle 🐢  . . #ValentinesDay #SingleAF #still @ Vertical Networks https://t.co/bipo9tL4ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these student leaders and their commitment to @FletcherCollege students]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamknott777 @BlakandBlack @Watershedd Its been broke for a long time...Greedy Polly's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight me and my fam decided to randomly get a hotel at 8pm to go swimming and order pizza and it’s been the best time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just walked around the floral department for 20 mins and left with nothing bc flowers are so expensive :c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She’s definitely ready for retirement not work !!!! Democrats will want her to stay on the job even if she’s dead....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have some Chiclets Foster can use for a while? 🤪🤓🦷🦷 @ Greenville, South Carolina https://t.co/slApwNRs79]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to complete the #MuellerInvestigation Join me in defending our democracy #ProtectTheInvestigation https://t.co/0gE7xLG2qG]]></document><document><![CDATA[some people legitimately have ZERO consideration for others &amp; it’s repulsive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home now and showing my boyfriend some of @RealPaigeWWE’s best matches because the magic of Paige can’t just be exp… https://t.co/QFi0ExF5QT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case you’re all tired of the Valentine’s Day posts and need a little break. ☀️🌊 @ Venice Beach, Florida https://t.co/BKEdybS1nU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRamirezBoxing Hmmmmm You almost soubd like you night have enjoyed the BEST bout of the night😜🤷🏻‍♀️ #BestBoutofthenight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigimn37 @WhiteHouse Gun violence is worse in  places where Democrats are the majority. It's not the guns, it's the people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today I tried something new and wore a bun. No one said a word. https://t.co/ndmbE2uASH #ifyoucantsaysomethingnice]]></document></documents></author>