<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Search me, O God, and know my heart; Try me, and know my anxieties; And see if there  is  an…… https://t.co/q4NXACpNr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Well, the Sexual Predator is known for lowering the Barr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 30.029 in, Steady. Temperature 55.8 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 97%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @BetterNikeBot @njsneaks @tclicK_  ran BNB on my iPhone 😂 https://t.co/oh7PIV15Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ManicMonday  with @michellebb10  will air LIVE Tonight  at 7pm ET/6pm CT/4pm PT @RadRealityShow  Special Guest:  M… https://t.co/XOjAzAoLAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanGSN He can’t do this in the nhl. That’s the same amount of goals he had in his ten games here this year. Rather see Otto and bellows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help my writer friend break a personal record for preorders.  He's nearly there.   GINJUH: A Gay Coming-of-Age Tale https://t.co/L6P9Es8DRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great first year for Pepperdine Head Coach Lorenzo Romar.  Coach Romar beloved in basketball community / phenomenal… https://t.co/77IqjTx5nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sparkyscrum Note 9 is still there, just further down. It's still an interesting choice because of the S Pen and no… https://t.co/rW3MvPVzya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyJeans Glad I could make it!  Always on my calendar #ImpactMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person is playing at the @BookHamptons tomorrow. Y'all better come by. @ BookHampton https://t.co/sMChWYKW98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detective :“I never did find out who took 2nd place in that turtle contest” Police Officers: “Oh Slappy” Music outr… https://t.co/FnTEZzIu1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 @latina @latinas… https://t.co/dAnl5wJHeS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmarisJessica_ Wangs, it’s either there or BWW. You know I stay over by Dwight’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essentially this is @reckless admitting to abusing the @YouTube copyright system and thinking he can get away with… https://t.co/NQH5rvySb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos queriendo ir a un concierto de bad bunny, anuel a,  etc.  Y yo aquí queriendo ir a uno de estos 🙌🏼 un día... https://t.co/RJaKtgOC15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldeHippieDude @JaniceHorton @OrderofAnton @HeikkiOjala @eroticCJ @gloriajkenyon @perthtravelers @ARPearson2… https://t.co/TpQ9uyhqem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Donald Trump IS NOT a king. This is the death knell of the @GOP.  https://t.co/4lVPFt2twb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Pelosie is going to protect what or who ever agrees with her demonic agenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Money management skills wouldn’t hurt.  Live within your means just like Brook Street Publishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also cool to see klout mentioned in the piece. Always was funny to see the people who bashed klout the most were th… https://t.co/OHPbpOamjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathis290 @DaneKuiper14 @claypatt5 @mathis290 congrats on a great career!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbieBarstool The fact that they’re using this match as the blueprint to the Kofi and Becky storylines five years… https://t.co/MvDLFU7HdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was AOC and other Dems point in blocking this deal anyways ? What did they accomplish other than job blocking… https://t.co/y01YoiAAvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casey Cizikas is unhinged right now. Number 15 on the season. His second 2-goal game this season. #Isles]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I may need to shave cause my phone won’t recognize my face anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Spinning: Talking Heads - Speaking In Tongues #nowspinning  #vinyljunkie  #talkingheads  #davidbyrne @ My Big S… https://t.co/0kxvgWcK0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[After admitting to my wife I was late to work because I left at the same time the neighbors were leaving, so I didn… https://t.co/PWKUZmr7Im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UDeportesRadio HACIENDO UN POCO DE EJERCICIO..SALUDOS A LOS 3 MOSQUETEROS @lamanodeldiego ..@quintanillajc… https://t.co/6T1MAEvFbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheZackFalcon @monasfineart @RealDrGina So you voted with your intellect this go round?😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebiblicalskep @NickSoutter @Lead1225 @OceanKeltoi @AaronTTaylor1 @GodlessEngineer @YouTube Acts is accurate on 8… https://t.co/7QMmXRyL9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport Yes he will. But it sounds like you have made his iCloud account (Pages, Etc) inaccessible at school. Can we disable this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKingofDC Had similar reaction to @PodSaveAmerica interview: https://t.co/pvV6KJAhR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yankowitz: Can explain a lot of the twist behavior in the linear T regime in terms of electron-phonon coupling, in… https://t.co/1BO5sGrhMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driveway is clear. Which means the Street plow should be here any minute.  #Snowmageddon #onlythenwscannamestorns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson I’m hearing that Schlapp has the same definition as Santorum. Schlapp! Now that’s onomatopoeia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7GenFund #shameless #revisionisthistory #williammckinley #belovedpresident #belovedman #godresthissoul #liberalshateamerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeharvkey I think he’s trying for Brando, but he’s confusing late burn out Brando with early brilliant Brando.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day and another round of snow❄ in Flagstaff, Az☃️🌲🗻 https://t.co/v8mJO5HgX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It always has, I've just been late to arriving at diagnosis. I've always had ADHD-PI, but was only recently diagnos… https://t.co/bdukqUcqz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedufflady Our uncle who took us to get ice cream but also co-authored mass incarceration???]]></document><document><![CDATA[MacArthur is having their way with Santa Fe. #PrepHoops #okpreps https://t.co/MbqsCYu07t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TubalTec Then you might like ComicLab. It’s basically the same show with me and Dave Kellett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @IvankaTrump Hi that's great ! Listen to Ken Dulin Vote #Trump2020  Impeach the #CrackBabies of… https://t.co/sFqbgFB8ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ The way he stutter and fumble his words. 😏 You know that Trump dose the Financial relationship to Ru… https://t.co/UJvVOHX1Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Cienega FFA Horse Eval team. 1st in State AZ FFA CDE Day. Team: Megan Dailey; 2nd, Hailey El… https://t.co/VSjosdEEmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I’m up to debate or discuss this article if any are interested even if people feel sensitive about it💯 https://t.co/fdDcFumc0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeFastNFL Thanks Mike! I used @DraftNetworkLLC mock machine. It’ll be interesting to see how the rankings change post-combine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[white ppl at ucla don’t ever say thank you so I just stopped holding doors open for them and my life became 100x ea… https://t.co/XBibpcBrbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me dijeron: “Quiero aprovechar tus poderes de influencer” y yo WHAT? #NoSoyInfluencer #YoSoloQueríaSerLocutor https://t.co/N6lZ3uQQzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: made it back to Austin (finally). Now time to teach myself organizational behavior for my test tmrw 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. It’s day 15 of the General Assembly’s 2019 session #kyga19. Here is the daily legislative calendar:… https://t.co/JvdcyKUfvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roberthamwriter One thing we know for sure is that that picture was not taken in San Diego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[to lembrando da minha despedida e da cara de pau de umas pessoas q se diziam proximas que colaram, nao trocaram mei… https://t.co/VBlhjHWu4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the bottom of the funnel is broken, fix it.  Don’t pour more into the top. #salesgenius #salesfunnels… https://t.co/SkVdfmGgR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundaycoffeeandmusicsession #nowplaying🎧 Maiden Voyage - HERBIE HANCOCK with Freddie Hubbard, George Coleman, Ron… https://t.co/hf5U64EBGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Calm the fuck down okay” is how I’ll be responding to all arguments for now on 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i rewrote the second verse 3 times and ended up sticking with the first one .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Zen Garden by @clownshoesbeer @ MyZoomZoom — https://t.co/wSh6mEKIHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite type of pants but I’m always cautious of the type of girl that wears em.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad to see this re-tweeted so much.  No one is more deserving of this than @ryansickler .  Love this guy.… https://t.co/d3ydXvlXHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 2019 remember what these two assholes did! I want you to tell your children what they did!#Neverforget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline @kharyp So... he's testifying.  Do you think he's smart enough to know that lying to Congress is a… https://t.co/rnxACuDDd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALSO FUCKING LITERAL TETRIS BATTLE ROYALE THAT WAS A MEME IM GOING FUCKING BATSHIT INSANE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoSportsJB @FPOnTheDL Funny thing was they were pleasant unlike one Leaf fan who was clearly drunk where he g… https://t.co/9GcArfnS4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaReef70 @jsmith10575 You missed my prior conversation lmao read my thread on @jsmith10575  tweets jordan is def… https://t.co/KpeuPmGwGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultrarunmike 1)Vikings  2) Bulls 3) Hawks ???? https://t.co/K6UMWzcEVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAURABARRANCO @jenarovillamil lafelipa ADEMÁS DE SER LOCA CUANDO SE EMBORRACHA, LAS DA, ES ASESINA DE MAS DE MEDIO… https://t.co/rs1WLbk8Hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalenbridgess @Zyon3Dobbs @p_laxton15 @jones_dasilas @fshsbarstool @LoopParkLoonies @WDTVSports @12SportsZone… https://t.co/xPgwnQ8ZV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Teach your dog that focusing on you and listening to you is beneficial to them..... Then and only the… https://t.co/G6MknXahT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deansleckie @vnbateman She's making serious points and you're thinking with your dick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi my name is Gordo... aka #Santapaws ... aka #fatcat @ Suffolk, Virginia https://t.co/f772nVoq0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrothaLynchHung my dude if you ever come to Cleveland I’m the first one there. Spittin every lyric with you, well… https://t.co/g07tnJ90Gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone playing #CrackDown3 , I feel the need to plug in #AgentsOfMayhem. If you like Crackdown 3, consider supp… https://t.co/OIUYR8iN1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeeBoykin I PROMISE YOU I'M NOT YELLING. IGNORE WHAT YOUR BRAIN IS TELLING YOU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just restarted Friday Night Lights for the 5th time. Top 3 favorite TV show of all time. 🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OddRomo @Kurosaki_Gio It’s a shame this retweet ended up on my timeline, but there is absolutely no reason to be t… https://t.co/iPCDEAsLzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigestVenezuela The Maduro Regime is capable of anything at this stage. From hiring armed thugs, to using inmates… https://t.co/xub0B5Uguy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful having a chance to hear a behind the scenes perspective from the three of them! #PLScholars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old and young Calloways @ Wethersfield, Connecticut https://t.co/WBohm4BlUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody (@strawshopsea) #seathtr (@ 12th Ave Arts in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/5W6NBe6AS4 https://t.co/Jc6eUVSoxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice easy drinking blonde ale. Smooth light brew best enjoyed while listening to "Harper Valley PTA" - Drinking a V… https://t.co/bxMpjCkDJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Weather Advisory in effect from 6 PM CST tonight to noon CST Sunday. Up to 3 inches of snow and a glaze of i… https://t.co/JMpEON2jKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adi_AdityaGupta Excellent!!!!** dear brother Glory Hallelujah👍👋🌞😊😀🙏🙇🎶📖⏫☝]]></document><document><![CDATA[A president that mst fight our own gov to protect us from traitorous politician’s acting in their own interests and… https://t.co/qO5kB3IoMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t what scared is until you get pulled over by Auburn Police Department 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Killed at Venezuela Border as Aid Standoff Heads to Critical Moment https://t.co/qM3rTbqHRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can argue whether Laura's prodigious giving to Dem causes and candidates should mean her removal as well. I woul… https://t.co/a53MmKMTgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a BotanicAles - Lela by @tapbrewhub @ Children's Miracle Network Hospitals of Greater St. Louis — https://t.co/PpYiWnAQEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Turnout at the Bruton Terrace CW #ActiveNeighborhood @RickeyCallahan @DPDPage @FiteDPD @DPDWalls https://t.co/AytmksGxzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenbrotS @piratefoxy @MaggyW5 @BandieraNancy @10MinutesaDay4U @media_auntie @wildweezle @SaneSophisticat… https://t.co/tPtoRORTRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThndrP15113 @Enes_Kanter @NBA @kaj33 There’s only one person in the picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl @TIMOTHYJOHNART @IvankaTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump @realDonaldTrump @EllenBarkin @Rosie… https://t.co/vcHwdBdE9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just hold on. God is working. It may not be exactly when you expect it but it will be right when you need it. He's always on time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried significantly more than Sarah.   I am still crying.  She was worth the wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewkimmel Please more horse race. We don’t need to know positions or temperaments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one who once in office assumes she is of the ruling class rather than a legislative class]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Not RACISM that's Killing the Majority of Chicagoans that are being Murdered! We Know who's doing the Killing!… https://t.co/na71DyxbQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[in apush today, “ohio gang” was mentioned and someone mentioned jake paul b4 i could 😓😓😓😓😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The one constant through all the years, Ray, has been baseball...” https://t.co/C8k0ElU81c via @WSJ]]></document></documents></author>