<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BiggaBoss_Biggz @_Thirst22 Nah it has to be balance.. I can’t be welcoming women into my home if you’re not allowi… https://t.co/XnaUGRWXME]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud to work for such an amazing congresswoman! @allison_kerman  I didn’t know your congresswoman brought this… https://t.co/h14KNRxQsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a big Valentine’s day person, but there are a LOT of guys on the El tonight with flowers. I can’t help it. It is very sweet 💐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great discussion on #designsystems in the enterprise tonight at the #DesignOpsnyc meetup @lifionbyadp with… https://t.co/m3JdJBYmte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sugdendingel @PattiHavis @dayzedconfuzed @hoosiergal86 Throw under the bus? Haha. Claire has reason to start the fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting really bad heart burn and it’s reminding me of the time I told my mom I needed to go to the ER and she laughed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tú eres la luz en medio de la oscuridad y fuiste creado para vencer los problemas.  #7minutos7días #DiosEsFiel… https://t.co/38Wj6fKPNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I mention #Pirlo, Cabs the bartender at @McHalesPub51 , my #soccer local in #NYC, just casually tosses out tha… https://t.co/CNdpGWlVU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoureA311FanIf you always try to buy 2 tix to every show so you can take a friend who's a @311 virgin, to show them why you love them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sb67Steve @29POTUS @mwilson1212 @RepChrisCollins https://t.co/lEFAyk2LwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogChurchWork @DearAuntCrabby @TheDemCoalition @DanRather @amvetsupport @Alyssa_Milano @JustaSlob… https://t.co/Tx71a0p1ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Look at her picture! She fucking crazy or high on crack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyValentinesDay #HappyValentinesDay2019 Have some dark chocolate 🍫🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai Official Trailer #1 - Christopher Lloyd Mo... https://t.co/zlqsihnb8o via @YouTube #national emergency 🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching family Guy. Shows the bomb brah. My home life's so like that. Jojo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadgirlWRX I know. It’s absurd and reckless. The existence of these diseases are not up for debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aftertheflash Aww hopefully next week! Have a good night #RoadTripChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houseofcubs up high in his tree with a roll once he climbs down. Very vocal this afternoon! Sorry for the screamin… https://t.co/0quf1VdhcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fracking kidding. Such hypocrites, the #TrumpCrimeFamily! By trump’s account, Hillary’s big email crime was play… https://t.co/IDMfO8LnoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #presidentsday ! The hat looked a lot better on George Washington.... @ FOX 29 https://t.co/k68OucB8OC]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeah i wanna speak to God and ask him why he took my dad from me so soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[In order for the #Flyers future to be successful, it all comes down to what we’re doing now. @AnthonyDiGrazio knock… https://t.co/Xu0AVrP4HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍Indianapolis, IN  Excited to represent @KU_Football at the @NFL Women’s Careers in Football Forum!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found a pair of fishnets without rips are u all proud https://t.co/LusagHl1pU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @davidsh01060735 @LouDobbs @RandpaulS @POTUS He is a RINO. Vote him out]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is a very unfriendly wind” #walking #neighborhood #floridalife #windy 🌴 @ Lakes at Boca Raton, Boca Raton, Fl… https://t.co/s1oG4acRJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever felt the need to be on stage again? Like after 7 years I would kill to do Escapade again. Senior year… https://t.co/eTcU7VbVUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow up in North Las Vegas by my fam bam..keeping them in prayers.. She said its not even the worst..that part is o… https://t.co/xV6DeEnvrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are my Valentine ♥ Forever together ♾ #RussellMartx #HappyValentinesDay2019 https://t.co/KZ8ioQWOTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @donnyosmond for signing all the bags for me . 😘😘😘 c u next month with dogmom23 . @QAbugger and I had a f… https://t.co/vpDaKb7lmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacopoVeneziani @paoloigna1 @albertopetro2 @MariangelaSant8 @PatriziaRametta @BrindusaB1 @GaiaGaudenzi… https://t.co/U0vv8pFnBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! It's John Glenn Day! 57 years ago, Ohio's native son blasted off into orbit and into the history books. https://t.co/140VtzJviZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨NEW POST ✨ Two days in a row? Say wha? Only for Valentine’s Day! ❤️ 🥰 Today we are heading out of town with some f… https://t.co/cnL4Ky9KnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I send Will pictures of rings all the time, so when the time comes he knows exactly what I like 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukester_cycle @PriscillaCalvan She's not been hard on Bruce she just trying to figure out what's this thing that… https://t.co/lP9EgAK6kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoongi is on live!! Thank you!! #VLIVE @Vliveofficial @bts_bighit @BTS_twt https://t.co/vsfmKqUbe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNS15141 @Mac_Vegas @003a04f8c2054b7 @KevinHu63682270 @Terri101092 @FreebirdAmerica @kathy101252 @kgo2017… https://t.co/ndF1dHWeDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haaaaaaate when people snort their boogers or phlegm. It sounds so disgusting. 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hollyyo1 @gillian_biss @MommaMurderino -look ladies, the masks worn by serial killers from 9,000 years ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My problem is that I get lied to constantly... now ask me what’s wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woodard4Kansas Total crap!  Their argument is options should be available to kansans.  Wouldn’t Medicaid expansion… https://t.co/xdfRCLBmWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Farrelly, Rhode Island is proud of you. Congrats! #Oscars19  #GreenBookMovie #RhodeIsland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimas2107 No sé, había un gran Acapulco en su momento, que murió junto con la popularidad de Luis Miguel. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current inventory of "Love" Celtic Crosses. #danishheart #celticcross  #wildflowersofscotland #lovenotes… https://t.co/mp4EyMiee4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easta_5 @MrsH_Murphy_KG Thank you for inviting me, it was fun to see another LIM school in action! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lincourtp and I having a great chat with President of the National Association Puerto Rican Hispanic Social Worker… https://t.co/hIMYJQfVqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#selﬁeoftheday Tonight I worked the Muse concert. What an amazing concert!! #muse @ Talking Stick Resort Arena https://t.co/G56pdDt0Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart hurts so so much for the person I was at that time. and I get so emotional on the other side when I recogn… https://t.co/XSzPFWzJyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖 #365DaysofGrannySquares  🦄 #yarntopia  💖🦄 @ Lancaster, California https://t.co/0wqBZlSABU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in MA, check out this #CustomerService job via the link in our bio: Field Engineer II at General Electric]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have more going for you than you will ever know or realize. You are the power and you are the strength of your own Soul and Spirit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC You and your show should pull your heads out of the corporate sand re Omar (and Corbyn). You are way off base!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthSpader747 @ThomasOtterman @locknesss456 @KnotsThoughtz @Schmoeness @GanglandLegend @KarlWPickup @NYounker… https://t.co/KQobrVwdh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad and I are jamming to HSM in the car after realizing a mutual live for the franchise so how’s that for a Saturday night? #winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never do this, but I turned the Kentucky game off in the eight minute mark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyDaPuppyCat @lathomas_lynne @RhondaHendee @livingroomlions @TheRealOtisFuzz @RudigerTheCat @Chrissy7115… https://t.co/ALusHOOKSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll take “people who demonstrate courage, dignity, and self-effacing humour during a difficult time” for $1000 ple… https://t.co/0cuPN3Wp9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBradJohnson @AASAHQ Absolutely! I am in my 5th year at my current school (elem, and Reg Ed, I was an EC teacher… https://t.co/agI1SYIlpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAMinneapolis is this thing even monitored? People are literallly BEGGING for your help and y’all can’t even be bo… https://t.co/2w4g5PEn7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rojomo85 @Tiff_FitzHenry Yes I think I do remember that her mom gave consent! (Zip my mouth!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get your solar and save yourself some $. Making California a leader in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy$]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the newest episode about one of the docs we were lucky to watch during last week’s @truefalse  - @MBrgger… https://t.co/kzChZxqX1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhnguyen141 TY. Nothing about this album says Houston 😂😂 people sucking Dick over street names]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stomu @therealjoebob @EndlessNightPro I’m the lone Mail Carrier for the entire Drive In...I gots lots o’ground to… https://t.co/WwozPISOLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Jussie stuff is super weird..... the story changes everyday like what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los pancakes o panquecas, entran en esa categoría especial de desayunos, son fáciles de hacer, puedes variar ingred… https://t.co/Nu0AwYDRRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariahgrooms97 Keep your head up! Your mood will change soon ❤️ you and @kate_bate123 and I can all get lunch this upcoming week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way he is sitting reminds me of a Corgi haha! 😂 #stubbyLegs https://t.co/OIEXb2aVnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that I can down vodka with no chaser but I can’t down cough medicine without being a little bitch?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#datenight #tacopanda (@ Taco Bell in Brea, CA) https://t.co/YLrqeTufNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to be able to do this ONCE.  🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾. If it had not been for 3 ACLs I would have done it 30 years ago.… https://t.co/dEmLptO8wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I can’t understand are the elected Republicans not being united behind President Trump-failing to be part of t… https://t.co/CglNSe0ZJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dimafadma Awe!! I’m not sure your situation but believe in your self. I got to a point where I stopped. Don’t ever… https://t.co/8uKc6T9E8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[💗 Lucille Ball 💗            Available for purchase!                 Follow my Insta:… https://t.co/oN82nG3GRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika @JoeNBC Dr. Khanna is too smart for this panel. #lamebrains]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love going out with @RFWill149 because he always gets recognized and he always lies that he’s not a big deal 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might need your sunglasses for all this shining 😏😎  #beauty #beautyblogger #youtuber #blackexcellence… https://t.co/kroEuFqdKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it astounds me just how true the philosophy is that when you begin to do more of what you genuinely love,… https://t.co/f3RlSIuntj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone pls take away my laptop. So far I’ve bought a swimsuit and screen protector for my Apple Watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepNewsTeam hooray, state of emergency, #BuildTheWall it's what the American want!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews North Korea is rebuilding because trump couldn’t do a deal. Trump failed with North Korea big time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @McDonalds I love that you are back open #wenissedyou but one question, where did the kitchen go? #behindthewall… https://t.co/TjSfydaHv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @LAMOONLYNN Florida would welcome Amazon HOWEVER we will not give our state taxpayer monies of bil… https://t.co/Lf0xFk7a7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone, I hope all is well. Have a blessed day @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/mQPV8DckzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can't there be an #oscars category for Outstanding Boom Mic Holder? https://t.co/zazQRNeEaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That is BS! Talk about fake news. Trump could give a master class in lying and BS. No wonder he lo… https://t.co/alUVcQCQ8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Canyon employees discovered 15 gallons of radioactive uranium by a popular museum exhibit https://t.co/Jvsa9J7IK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s sooo HOTT 😍🥰 #ArianaGrande #Arianators #GirlCrush https://t.co/xI3yq68iL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristineduguay @YouTube @youngthegiant This is a different version, give it a listen! I love it 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realMattGarwood @LynnAnnZill No one debunked anything. You should know the reality of your cult]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schoology Do you have a grading platform on your site that can connect to standards?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to be back in #washingtondc for the @nkf Kidney Patient Summit! As the NKF Kid Ambassador, I’ll be m… https://t.co/mtvE5WPwMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sh7CEQDpNq #art #dance #photographs https://t.co/uzLbx0WFWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dice Alicia Ortega que el aplausòmetro registrò 125 aplausos en la escala de Richter. https://t.co/1L5oezq6sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to speak to someone immediately. @uber does not seem to want to deal with customers. Why is there no way to… https://t.co/m74ioP7Sz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got off of work at a decent hour and all my girls (Melly and Ale) ain't down to have a girls night :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who dare me to not go back to work n just drive off 1 like n I’ll do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so the lesson Desiree needs to learn this year is called “Scissors are NOT therapy! A guide on how to not do a… https://t.co/7Xbe7oEJt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbullard41 @markwahlberg Hahaha! Just did that was perfect 🤣🤣 “white people showing support for 21 savage”]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. I’ve brought you all here today to remember the late and great President Rutherford B. Hayes]]></document></documents></author>