<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Out of nowhere I found myself thinking about Josh Hamilton this morning.  I’m hoping today is greeting that dude in a good place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVShannyLeigh Wrong! 1 + 1 is totally 6..... 😉😆  PS - What are the 10 NHL arenas you haven’t yet been to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PepsiCo @CARE @DukeFarmsFdn @DukeLawStartUps @UN4Indigenous @OFIDnews sounds great. @swissolar_d @WEFBookClub https://t.co/Aqr9SiALqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to shovel in order to get my car out of garage...leave...hour later come back and entire drive is plowed...do… https://t.co/UkuyAHV74W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-posting this showing pic from 6 years ago, and wishing you all a Happy Valentine’s Day! ❤️🛁😂 #valentines… https://t.co/ykissU0b4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatFlippen @edtechteam @CoachHuskey I’ve already started fixin’ my drive #EdTechTeam #learningisfun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedDeutch @RepCicilline After you take my AR15 how would I prevent you from taking my other rights also?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colin Kaepernick will be the QB for the Hitabuckta Flingers.  He will have a salary of -20 million a year until he… https://t.co/COjUaqAkuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKBHD @Tesla I want one to smoke #weed inside it. @Laweedaloca 🤔😆🤣😂🇺🇸 #teslaweed #teslamemes  While parked, of cou… https://t.co/1E0WZs533B]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the second year of covering this event and it is an incredible joy. I hope to come back as many times as I am able.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmorey If you need someone to sign a 10 day contract I’ll do it for $5,000!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessLynnMoreno @DrDP14 @brandonbphd @Peter_Grinspoon Yours is the most sensible approach I've seen to date. Please don't change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mierdafavorita @AmA2jena1 @maryjanesosexy @candi_smyles @OMGitsVanessa2 @KittyTheCather1 @Arianna_32xxx… https://t.co/LBOfbAMEEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is "National Napping Day." Unsure why this requires an official designation as for me, every day is napping day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkmanDonovan @LHtheVO This is the email I recieved this morning. https://t.co/S7b2RnMzrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[THERE MORE TO BOEING CRASH  THE WE CAN UNDERSTAND=ITS A SHIT HOLE COUNTRY\\]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @lauren_upper hope you have the greatest day 💜 love ya 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[True friends are in it for the long haul. Even when you’ve fallen—or agree with you completely—a true friend is in… https://t.co/5d6gtkuJeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stairs to the Mayflower or the dungeon where the government is keeping El Chapo? https://t.co/FKgk5gb8AS]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those slagging #Islander fans ... sports fandom is not a business partnership, it’s more like a marriage. What w… https://t.co/QyPK0gETDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samesfandiari i say yes, i think he wants to open Chase, try for a 4-peat. he’s in the ideal situation, i don’t re… https://t.co/YEcDR4dzW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever think.. that you’re the bad kid that all the #DARE programs talked about? Except you don’t go around offering… https://t.co/DWin2belbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me for....Feb. 28: NJ Institute for Social Justice to Celebrate 20th Anniversary - Insider NJ -… https://t.co/WmRhDgc3F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[An empty room.   Me: omg Ellen you didn’t.   Silence.  Only the vague buzz of the lightbulb overhead.   Me: Oh.    (She didn’t.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Mexican El Chapo will pay for the wall. Mexico will pay by absorbing migrants who do n… https://t.co/DzNv3rYxOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los valores de igualdad social y humanismo, fue la bandera que enarboló toda su vida, el líder de la Revolución Bol… https://t.co/4L6lp3cUlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bb_referee @AppreciatedSD @KeithOlbermann If they follow this up with Harper, then leverage that farm system to fi… https://t.co/v4Tn5ZjGZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress should STOP resisting it’s Constitutional responsibly to secure our border, fix this shattered immigration… https://t.co/dxcz6QIq9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear about Brody Stevens. If you need help or know someone that needs help PLEASE call @800273TALK  Com… https://t.co/1ocPeWXDmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more mind blowing facts for you @Noggle_Farms there are 16 ounces in a pound and a pint is a pound the whole world round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bturner23 Every KU fan I have ever talked to agrees that he traveled. How is this still something people care about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the menu for this super cold day: Homemade French Onion Soup with crostinis and melted gruyere https://t.co/9QeFLzpYDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heifer, I don’t care if Jussie is the biggest liar in history.  You have no moral high ground to claim, trick. Shut… https://t.co/09ro8HzgPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornerTom @acanatconf Everywhere you turn there is live music - world class and no cover charge. Every bar we’ve b… https://t.co/BMo4GqhCxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Robyn so good that I just bought Pitchfork tickets? https://t.co/5Dqk7F0SDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LStoneWNDU @MMcFaddenWNDU @CClawsonWNDU @WNDU Where's Mike Hoffman? It seems like he's always gone this time of year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grand Opening weekend. Dark brown, licorice, spicy - Drinking a High Seas by @reveriebrewing at @reveriebrewing  — https://t.co/YKPk26wZ3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtmdiamond @RosedaleClubFit 3 strike rule.  I'm paying top dollar to my gym. I warn the front the first time.  I c… https://t.co/9buWRPKAzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin Are you interested in criminal corruption information in NJ Ag's office? obstruction, cover up bidding laws ? with evidence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO EVERYONE DID YALL HEAR ABOUT THE PUPPIES THAT WERE RUNNING AROUND THE HALLS OF CONGRESS AND SENATE. THERE ONE… https://t.co/zZbhIXluIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ai voce chega pra imprimir o ticket de embarque no guichê @voeazuI e não tem um misero funcionário se quer pra aten… https://t.co/Fn5F4fpJ4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gaby_Miro Gabby you always have a great message. I appreciate you for that. Thanks Girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC Salting now got to go. 8am we out🌹😘🙄♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️So in love. And man that tweets you day in and day out non s… https://t.co/VCO1WBYOmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick reminder that the right will always call any pragmatist running as a pragmatist in our pragmatic centrist par… https://t.co/3ndKviWL8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone out there vlogging? I'm looking for a camera with 4k capabilities and an external mic input.   Looking to sp… https://t.co/MK58u7eDAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing the stupidity of the leftist liberal Dems; do they think the American people will believe this bull crap? N… https://t.co/57F25PRTuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RazLPL LMAO YO i was thinking about lupe and us legit yesterday. I was thinking Lupe was dabbing before it was “co… https://t.co/7HNiOxgkWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson As a watcher of the Bernie effusion, my favorites were the fanatical declarations of H.A. Goodman, w… https://t.co/h73SHyqsuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@universalhub Absolutely 100% and add angle parking on one side - safer street more parking and the double parking ends!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two-pad #TuukkaTime stack! Glad I wore my Reggie Lemelin Jersey in honor. Even the #GoKingsGo fans were 👏🏻’ing… https://t.co/JEbEuansKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thin film interference is fucking cool. @ Pixar https://t.co/QSmmnhC9zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Used to be a bunch of assholes that lived in this part of the building here. But we systematically removed them li… https://t.co/ajNVtJzJZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanScherr @womaninmedicine I’m a 23 year old who just graduated college and works in financial services. Don’t lo… https://t.co/sbQmtrQIwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caleb had the best time at Delta Downs! A day him and I will never forget! https://t.co/2DBvRjwFH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pellomaldonado @krek9 Ya todo lo que digan los tigres después de la final regia los rayados lo toman a mal. Frustrados nos dicen 🤦‍♂️jajaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I figure out what are the target demographics for "Now! That's What I Call Music!" and who is actually makin… https://t.co/x01FpZEjTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[... And then I listened to the @CriticalRole One Shot with @shukrani. 🤔👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give it up for @netflix and there part in giving creators opportunity to achieve #Oscars Level status https://t.co/3xmkY4jmj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bob_Boyer I recommend it—got one for Christmas, and it’s been a godsend and a joy to use!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonronson Awesome - thank you!  Don’t suppose you’re planning any shows in Toronto any time soon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran three miles yesterday in 40 degree weather in the rain. Fuck California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old dude at Goodwill is chilling on a sofa here curling a 5 lbs weight. He's probably like "I ain't paying for a gy… https://t.co/8iDC4ETTTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got done training as the sun was coming up🙏🏼☝🏼 Blessed beyond belief to be in this position. Can’t wait til March 1… https://t.co/HFVm7vl9oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@braunold Started with Barak? It is been an inherent characteristic since the founding of the state; of course, Rab… https://t.co/EZFaigBEQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RexGrumpy @IlhanMN No , I judge the barbaric Palestinians who go around blowing up innocent people  having lunch a… https://t.co/j7Eu0qtZnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEStatePatrol Be careful out on the roads tonight troopers and motorists. https://t.co/care3AYsD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeMariePosts @klyphnelson @NNorma192 @MCW16591775 @MeaneyJim @BonnieLCarter @plumbkeith1 @RUalreadyawake… https://t.co/qga6qAUa8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanLeigh @Star64WSTR @FloFC_ It hurts the growth of the Dayton/Lexington/Etc fanbase which is very, very important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaehvogel @goldblum_zeno @KamalaHarris Do you disagree that 500,000 people were apprehended at our border last yea… https://t.co/3MsJbOjGic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All Volunteer State comes through again, Remember the Alamo, Thanks be unto GOD for sanity and the protection… https://t.co/XiKtlo06cD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cucogzz1 Todo bien gracias a Dios, espero lo mismo para tí, un abrazo. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PAlterBoy1 @BradSchrag @Dribelo1 @AltUS_ARC @miked194765 @rln_nelson @JamesRider3 @HeisenbergErwin @BobGreene333… https://t.co/HAKbr5wzrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicing Shot Put-Warrior Pride takes dedication. ⁦@The_Mr_Dalton⁩ ⁦@LCS_BC⁩ ⁦@LJHSWarriors⁩ ⁦@alexrbrunk⁩ https://t.co/jbD6utWZLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BullScripted Now it has the whole thing.  Weak is right, but he had already gotten at least one warning and I gues… https://t.co/JGBQZptQJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhnywang @alanhahn This story is such malarkey, it’s not like we’re one of the 14 teams that passed on him]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you can’t remember the passcode to unlock your phone  https://t.co/cqZj8ba5te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetStork @HillaryClinton @EmergeAmerica @emilyslist @runforsomething Also Hillary actually achieved things in Senate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GasCanSquirrel @kenthovind Yes evolution is s fairy tail written by Erasmus Darwin in poems he wrote three books l… https://t.co/187JgdoH2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_F_Kennnedy Ee are calling national emergency mexico was caught using artificial intelligence weapons systems… https://t.co/qdib2pRggu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started a new blog on my website! Would love y’all to check it out and subscribe! https://t.co/oOBqDwyCc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the walk in clinic with a sick son...he is in town for reading week- happy to be with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The official fast food French fry power rankings - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/qF6VklA4KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferStPie13 @michaeljacole @GeorgeMonbiot Absolutely, would love to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pʟᴀʏɪɴɢ ᴀʀᴏᴜɴᴅ ᴡɪᴛʜ sᴏᴍᴇ ᴏʀɪɢɪɴᴀʟ ᴄᴏɴᴄᴇᴘᴛs. sᴛɪʟʟ ɴᴇᴇᴅ ᴛᴏ ғɪɴᴀʟɪᴢᴇ ᴛʜᴇ  ᴅᴇsign ʙᴜᴛ now I ʜᴀᴠᴇ ᴀ ɢᴇɴᴇʀᴀʟ ᴅɪʀᴇᴄᴛɪᴏɴ ᴛ… https://t.co/y1TlA9ZyWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lost @_joshblack_ twice in this subway car if you wonder how we’re doing this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes people spend there whole life without meeting there soulmate. I’m lucky. https://t.co/xv09I6Ms4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because we all have to have one of those Sunday shirts.  :) https://t.co/HFDRvU5dTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby cousin called me yesterday screaming and frustrated. Hung up. Called again within 2 mins and said he was fine. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorPastTime Not sure if you have ever seen these but Clint Hurdle has a couple daily emails you can subscribe t… https://t.co/8zeo2uFbKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then, I’ll see a roadrunner in my neighborhood just chilling on the sidewalk before darting off just like the cartoon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's all stop talking to Lydon unless it's about early PiL, huh? Please? Listening to an Adam Ant rant would be be… https://t.co/C4kigpE1ZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My doctor just asked me how I’m doing, stress wise, as she sees architects as her most stressed patients.   Me: https://t.co/C2nvoWioSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atlanta United playing at home is the equivalent of Tune Squad when they drank Mikes Secret stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJeremyGardner The entire sequence is infuckingcredible, from Silvestri's echoing piano heartbeat during Bud's sw… https://t.co/kbIT5tOmOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ole has managed brilliantly again tonight. Got more from less, plus changed shape to see it off, and now gives youn… https://t.co/IuGn3LSxuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m looking for a new show to watch.  Also me: *starts The Office for the 12,378,912,516,715 time https://t.co/HXyYz5tSAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me who you were before you came to this earth. Tell me who you worshipped fore they came with the church.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was asked to talk to the Mead HS freshman and discuss my life and how important is to take advantage of the secon… https://t.co/MWHmbYs9zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aprilhenrybooks The state Motto is “Equality Before the Law.” Not sure what that actually means around here but th… https://t.co/9dfx7ALN7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrnEyedMandy Supposedly last month. Still not s real Democrat. #NeverBernie]]></document></documents></author>