<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Fabulous #poets fantastic #poetry #thankyousomuch @EthelRackin low._.rainee 🙏🏻✨ it was a #dreamcometrue tonight!… https://t.co/GTa3Fp0uvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[senior theology was really out here trying to tell us we were all gonna get recruited into cults in college and we just let them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the beauty of this gorgeous heron! @ Lealman, Florida https://t.co/W2GlcHCgJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sami_Alabami @JtmYd @ramin__alizadeh @SandraB16901827 @sami_ Thank you 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tzalikowski007 @LizKotalik @SteveStaeger I like her assistant, carrying the box on his head 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clay_mckinney @cashmeauney @GriffinSmyth @MLeFaveinTx @LordOfThePogs @leeleebb21 I thought they grew on potatoe trees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A semana tem 7 dias. A neve podia ter caído em qualquer um dos outros 6 dias, mas não, ela resolveu cair em plena s… https://t.co/hPogWtfyYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I gotta say big Sean really dipped on Jhene ... he gotta be the dumbest man on the planet ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never give up on the things that make you smile. 🙅‍♀️👆🏻👩🏻 @ Statesboro, Georgia https://t.co/l6r4qQnwRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nymphfatale Hay una cascada super bonita cerca https://t.co/tilfanGJsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just accidentally showered myself and my entire kitchen in turkey hot dog water. Happy Valentine’s day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PurpleReign14 It’s pointless! I haven’t had a good conversation with that demo at a front door in I don’t know how… https://t.co/pd8CtEOjoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassanmccan @HonestLeYo @_lightbrigght_ @DearSpecialK Oh sweetie I got it Don't think that other one saw you WE GOOD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPsy1010 Heinz did the wrong thing by stealing the drug. There are plenty of other ways to make money quickly. Ste… https://t.co/eHXGsO6cbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcanti @jaewav fuckin hell I need to reread that stuff ty for reminder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poontangpie666 @yashar @KFILE I support Joe Biden because he can beat Trump. He will be good for the country. He's… https://t.co/U657CZNdaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Castle memories keep popping up! Watching #CrosswordMysteries : A Puzzle to Die For, and I spot a familiar face--t… https://t.co/m2nbpdMUBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor’s Fellows Program-2019 Rising college seniors, graduating college seniors/enrolled as degree candidates in… https://t.co/QSZpzxNeGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[hmmmm let’s do it again. frank loved his #puppuccino and the #walk was pretty nice too. 🤷🏻‍♀️❤️ https://t.co/dyMiiEOpMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Padres win!!! This should be my new tweet when the boys win! 😱🤣 #PadresST https://t.co/zAN8VoBNVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some hilarity. #mirth #laugh #smile #merry https://t.co/MXEfKvbjwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[LET ME FEEL BETTER DAMMIT. IVE BEEN SICK FOR OVER A WEEK NOW AND LITERALLY EVERYTHING HURTS. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏻 High fives all around. You’ve survived another work week. Day 52 is under way. Both Judiciary and Finance are in… https://t.co/oBaKWCZzWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[my phone gone die soon... my charger in the room... &amp; i gotta pick chels up at 10 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being the cute bubbly chick next door.... and then there the days where I love when you make me your nasty l… https://t.co/0uHAAp5PkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truce is the only song not certified bc it makes everyone ugly cry and vomit when they hear it I’m sorry but we were all thinking it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/1DnzNoPRzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're dumb enough to talk crap about @aaroncarter  you might want to check your sources because trust me you do… https://t.co/DaQgGWrL6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna Not nice for you @lisarinna to decide what @LisaVanderpump should say or do during her grieving period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just was informed there will be No graphics or prompter this morning...happy Thursday friends #amnewers https://t.co/311DAkoS3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a GREAT idea for Twitter translate options. #twitter #TwitterVoices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gaby &amp; her new baby bunny toy. #starcatoftheday @ Star Cat Books https://t.co/TxlPX18LuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepMarkMeadows this is SO weird. notable folks in DC call you “Moscow Mark”,  just like we do in #NC11 .   why is… https://t.co/wa9FcdVzrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandicarlile @kelly_clarkson Omg!  Amazing!  Both of you are incredible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbzegarcia99 Check it out! I think it’s safe to say you made a good choice for your kids! #ESOL #literacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything better than throwing a bunch of stuff in a pot for soup and tweaking it until it’s amazing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A topic that got brought up at lunch with coworkers- In general, does social media create more of a positive or negative impact on people? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m wearing my “Dog Mom” shirt today and I couldn’t feel more myself than I do right now 🐾❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russia must have been listening. Now if you can find out what Hannity and #cohen was up to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNLVgirl I’m sure there were plenty of other seating options available]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t always a judge a relationship off of social media. there can always be a dark side that no one knows about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLoulouC Ma mère était artiste peintre, elle avait des livres avec des nus, mais c'était de l'art]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I had two students called on stage in the same event. When they got off stage one of the boys ran over t… https://t.co/tgROhv7EUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️ games today - Nutrabolt field starting @QatarW0lf #workhardplayhard  💚⚾️💙. brant.roberts @ Nutrabolt Stadium https://t.co/1mNy0r2B7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a good time to remind me that if you didn’t vote for @HillaryClinton you’re dead to me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are your candidates asking what you want for your town, city, state, nation? They should be. Throw out the agendas,… https://t.co/mBVrFpBUdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@win_miz @se4realhinton @carrieanninaba @kirstiealley @AnimalProj Ha Ha Ha!!! 👍🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhIoeK Jordynn said she didn’t sleep with him.  The spent the night at his home,a mistake she has owned up to.  Ob… https://t.co/4P9lqH8fF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We accomplished so much, knocking on tens of thousands of doors, building friendships throughout our community, and… https://t.co/0bvKoUNbtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts but it’s okay because the sophisticated lifestyle wasn’t meant for everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaySain Lmao. But then what happens if your phone rings when you do that then?🤳🏾🤳🏾🤳🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[QUE CHINGÓN SIENTO CUANDO MI HERMANA ME PLATICA DE SUS COSAS Y DE TODO LO QUE ESTÁ LOGRANDO ♥️👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlantBasedNews @VeganBlogger78 We've been vegetarian for ages  but try constantly to go vegan. Living in New York… https://t.co/nIc6fdLKcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents of our #TCEcardinals - let’s recognize our teachers of young children! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still Iron Strong!!! with you all the way @aafiron !!!!!! #ForgeOn https://t.co/4cL384Qlk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in West Palm Beach, FL, check out this #Education job via the link in our bio: MS Langua… https://t.co/iJ1QNgFc3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Song of the day (because baseball is coming even for non-Redsox fans) Sweet Caroline  https://t.co/2qFeGZo2qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roberto_ruizg Que lamentable situación! Que está pasando con el mundo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @beaglebabe48 Anyone who could do this to an innocent baby is capable of much worse on a not-so-in… https://t.co/hqo3a8X1OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRCC No. We need more personnel, better technology and our immigration system overhauled. I'd be happy to help any asylum seekers as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill What is this bullshit? You call this news? Every mother since the beginning of time hopes their child find… https://t.co/5NO8M8yK4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aidachavez @sunrisemvmt Sorry, I do not know what the Green New Deal is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday- Phoenix city council did not vote on the rezoning case for high end condo project at 7th St/Thomas. Inst… https://t.co/x3JeGyosfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyEGoodman Really get to put those “all seasons” to good use https://t.co/fGETzaoNgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so sad when young kids take their own lives and my heart is so broken for my brother right now. 😞 Send prayers to the Simms community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProjectLITComm A1: We’ve recently finished Wish Tree and A Long Walk yo Water. Both amazing books!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an outstanding (free!) conference opportunity for undergraduate students! And was the first conference I ev… https://t.co/fwM7M0N0Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I supported my local animal shelter just by walking my dog 2.06 miles using #WalkforADog app. Get the app at https://t.co/m6ZGen4K6Y.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A note to all my girls out there this Valentine’s Day! Let’s get focused on real beauty! Let’s also remember that… https://t.co/CEDy1a2YU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosGphoto @sarah__mclellan @StribSports @StribMultimedia Love how happy Parise is!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved spending the day with my favorite niece and her parents today. #JosieToulouse @ King City, Missouri https://t.co/PZJhfXzmUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somesingsfishy @AmyMek I went to school with 2 of his children and they were the most hateful, evil people I had e… https://t.co/JKYFSS1GIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do schizophrenics talk to themselves? Because when we talk to other people they pretend to listen because their… https://t.co/4gUnOl1GqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannongailmc @halladayfan32 Was I supposed to think it was lipstick? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MrPickles &amp; #PrincessPintsize approve of my new #slippers from #greatergood Get a pair… https://t.co/JH1HMJyjIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree @avrohomg. We need to have a balanced conversation about #AI and #employment. #FutureOfWork]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salty @myfabolouslife ain’t perform , but that bitch was definitely GOING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake Shelton you have a twin an actor by the name of Dale Midkiff what do you think?  @blakeshelton #VoiceBlinds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porking the fork, one customer at a time @ Rantoul Foods https://t.co/zLVvCcEN8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveAdams54 @SouthwestAir I will! I’m escaping the endless winter in KC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @janahyde1 @curley_jake @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/bifDglTVsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy belated birthday to the boss! @ Wildfire Chicago https://t.co/QHQzgWTU9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s incredibly sad to see the Labour Party descend to this point and I fully respect all seven splitting MPs for m… https://t.co/FqY4iyGI2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You think treason is hilarious? When your father is found guilty of conspiracy to commit treason Sh… https://t.co/kn1YazBEYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t mind washing, drying, folding and carrying laundry to my room - but why is putting it away so hard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t flex on someone who doesn’t care about what you got going ‼️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas that think you gotta prove yo gangsta onna internet to show people you not a poodle be the biggest poodles o… https://t.co/SwmkUOLgVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need good crime documentaries to watch y’all... Netflix, Hulu and Amazon are all fair game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Francamente bicho não tenho mais palavras capazes de expressar a repulsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bell12804 @netflix @AJ_ThompsonJr You have to take that up with Disney. They own Marvel and will soon have their o… https://t.co/ofxFonkmWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@van_her78 @XoolYvonne @guss2421 @Josefa_GBOM @JLozanoA @fernandeznorona Y las guarderías tipo ABC que había?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the Take Stock Run &amp; Event at Main Street https://t.co/QkQqJ7o4Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj We have a whole year before any one votes...I'll watch and wait to see who survives till next February, while Donald plays golf]]></document><document><![CDATA[told my brother i wanted to do my nails and he sent me 200 dollars if this is not mvp idk what is]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3atAkUvTxR https://t.co/RmvQ9LZYdB https://t.co/dMW9hZ1Uca   https://t.co/RmvQ9LZYdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#felizdia #diainternacionaldelamujer #diadelamujer @cassandraEspir 3235217721 en Campton Hills, Illinois https://t.co/6zbk2Bg60M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins Good now you know how the DNC felt, as well as Podesta and Hillary when their emails were stolen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere in this timeline is a tweet not understanding what the “hype” is with   “The Big Lebowski”]]></document><document><![CDATA[they’ve become so entrenched in the pursuit of wealth that it has altered their moral compass. Whether this is true… https://t.co/zDVGXJhC9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimash_official is not only the best singer in the world, he is a true and proud ambassador of his country  #TWBDimash  #WorldsBest]]></document></documents></author>