<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What is the reason for the confusion about human rights? It is bc we have forgotten the foundation of human rights.… https://t.co/qeoZnET6vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[No entiendo porque es raro oir a un arbitro, creo q se deben expresar mas. Los comprenderiamos mas y dejan de ser s… https://t.co/DlNQu4mEWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Miss Abby from the Bridge to Books Foundation for visiting and donating books at TMES for Read Across Americ… https://t.co/oAPH8u5HJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHammActor @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @hmgivingsoul @linds4fins @JackConnie @ja2cook… https://t.co/WKOwXz9Ku9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady GaGa, P!nk, and Katy Perry each need to give themselves a good ‘ol pat on the back and retire the mic… https://t.co/zEs7PGPwxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylah is a business woman! Selling girl scout cookies at Epic Arts Entertainment. Come buy a box and sign your chil… https://t.co/zLg2XFFngI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate an entire sleeve of Girl Scouts thin mints for dinner and I feel zero shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen can't thank you enough. Please keep fighting for America. We need you now more than ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeReady #concacafchampionsleague #ATLUTD #MLS @ Kennesaw State University https://t.co/03gFrsYGVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[These amateurs really think they can challenge the funniest duo at LCU and get away with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the work y’all do! I am pleading for more services to cover all of Harris County and not just Houston City Lim… https://t.co/VcCpV8N4St]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto the man is a traitor. He is quick to believe and support Dictators and Despots but even more quick to c… https://t.co/1isA3hppeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mangtizzle Honestly been trying to go to a rave for the longest just haven’t been back in town for one 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t need known terrorist in the US no matter how ‘sorry’ you are. Geez actions have consequences. 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @60Minutes So do the American people we are tired of this charade.  Its costing tax payers billion… https://t.co/547XvFig1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyyE_Redd Listen don't let him be bearded and light skin .... https://t.co/1T2FOaArqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of all the people in the world.... Guess who I just HAPPENED to be sitting next to watching Drag Race!!!! For like… https://t.co/1JaHNhayW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KiKi1185 @capeandcowell @yashar It's the same ending in all the versions]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many people in DSA who really, genuinely believe that socialism is whatever the majority of the people… https://t.co/bFUMdKHnTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strawberry waffle at Café Princess 💕💕💕 @ Cafe Princess https://t.co/FHJlwGJKFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maggie Rogers NYC concert tickets are $250?! And this is exactly why I never wanted to share her music with people back in 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SindoniRachel @MrsSlatteryBHE Miss playing soccer so much, and most importantly miss you!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAMPAOfficial it was so good meeting you last night!! Keep chillin and killin it! https://t.co/P5gUWRyPzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga YOU ARE FREAKIN AMAZING IN A STORY IS BORN!!! Love the brown hair. Watching it now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aviean @donovancurry_8 @TarinWestbrook @DonDon_Bailey7 So proud of @donovancurry_8 !! I hate I couldn’t be there t… https://t.co/7vCTswFD9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suggest you fly to DC. I haven’t bought tickets to LA yet. I will. But I don’t know when.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why you don’t fucking wear a MAGA hat,especially at the mall. you know something’s bound to Happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR It's just a lie a minute with you and your 3 kids.  We are SICK of it.  Get out of OUR WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cruisenorwegian best bar tender is senil fernandez on the Getaway!! Having a blast at MiXX. @cruisenorwegian https://t.co/cpLxDFhn2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it funny how la has 2 nba teams but local news talks about the lakers more]]></document><document><![CDATA[love Chicago Pd!!! One heck of a team who knows how to get the job done!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got some good feedback from my SWACUHO presentation. 😁 happy for my first one. Do i need to improve my presentati… https://t.co/c01RgLgqla]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t hear from #iconswim soon I’m going to be pissed. I placed my order on Sunday....3 days ago and haven’t r… https://t.co/7xNwpsvsy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KookieBae26 @JessicaKostele3 @Lilajev @nenny21 @nicsit2003 @browneyed_nuna @Luscious206 @jkannie1 @claypot77… https://t.co/RpV3gXAaUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Perorationer @Glorygirlone I love Engineers. They have all the answers ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[just some crazies @ Seaside Heights, New Jersey https://t.co/aPxelJUQX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barnascombe @AmerAcadPeds @leotrasande @Google @facebook @Pinterest Please read Dr. Paul Whiteley's blog post on t… https://t.co/aWE1zqbmxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonMom98 @SabreKevin1639 @SandiMarie79 @lno09281978 @MsAFromBK @suej104 @KevinFcBayern9 @rjflesher @jimmyreu81… https://t.co/teNzJr5NOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @SpeakerPelosi The country is already divided. How could impeaching the corrupt, bought and paid for… https://t.co/ZlDq2t9O2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealFatCrow how thirsty were you drink that whole bottle of water? 🤔 #Aquaman #robVSroy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Family Day!  Weekend fireworks @bolermountain A perfect end to a perfect Sunday!  #LdnOnt @weathernetwork ❄🎆🇨🇦 https://t.co/XNIh6MQ3XS]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC knows. This is why New Yorkers, Liberal New Yorkers go absolutely crazy about Tatiana when I visit. Traffic sto… https://t.co/KBeA6K6SlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RightWingWatch @TwiHusband Jim Bakker is an asshole who wouldn't know divine righteousness if it bit him in the ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr BS... she is a traitor... she needs to stay wherever she is NEVER to come to USA again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need some good news? I talked to a 91-year-old man who retired from hauling mail after nearly 70 years.   https://t.co/Elkbhl919u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman jumping barrier to wild animals is surpassed when attacked by wild animal. Oops, you forgot your selfie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No —WE DO GET THOSE INTERVIEWS...But Ours Are LEGIT &amp; YOURS ARE NOT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never hit a cigarette once in my life&amp; I plan to keep it that way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RanaAwdish @asmbs @ConscienHealth @NeilFlochMD @ObesityAction great weekend to  read the book “ IN SHOCK “ by Dr R… https://t.co/4MeDW6n7or]]></document><document><![CDATA[i couldn’t find a ticket to see elton john for under $350 in the whole stadium. do better @eltonofficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been to bed BUT.... I studied(a lot), researched my family history, planned a new tattoo, cleaned my apt,… https://t.co/hh7y909yoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrawberrieGina Was that you, contacting me on Instagram?  I do not use Hangouts, too many scammers. Feel free to… https://t.co/Fv3KTTfvou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vancitydwell @WienerDawgsRule Hahahahaha!  You can tell she voted for that pig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol @GTA_Redhead @madsatan6969 @MopedTN It was like a switch flipped and I was a different person 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benito Mussolini and I will just turn the place into a dictatorship - problem solved]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between getting a little too drunk Friday night, daylight savings, and putting in an unexpected 12.5 hour day at wo… https://t.co/Ig8ZidBtBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do people still have the app that tells you who unfollowed you on IG? Because i unfollow people all day long]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DID I START WATCHING FREE SOLO AT 12:30(?!!!!!!) was all set to go to bed but have now prepared myself a snack… https://t.co/TdsytfZj71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump There is no such thing as good institutionalized child care. How about having a forum of Day Care work… https://t.co/m8FfIIxahx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSherryPagoto @McLNeuro @darakass @choo_ek You are an amazing leader Sherry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🌀Heightened tornado danger to accompany severe storms in southern US into Saturday night https://t.co/gF8tV5ACnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stopsuicide #suicideprevention #beheretomorrow #bethevoice Join us THIS Saturday at 9 am to walk for suicide preve… https://t.co/KWDSnZZrMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AURORAmusic We Will all miss you here in Minneapolis till next time . You were perfect. How the wind flows around… https://t.co/DWQnlnoteB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s happening @iovation. #RSAC 2019 is going to be one for the books! #authentication #CyberSecurity… https://t.co/NzR77YvDYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[After yoga water. Yes really. @ Dinghy's Restaurant &amp; Bar https://t.co/5YVbHvWz0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @__Zimtsternchen The only wall being build is the one that exists in your Alternate universe. Exis… https://t.co/KirmB5Y87S]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Moscow-based businessman, Geovanis worked with Trump in Moscow Tower in the 1990.   He is also one of the bloc… https://t.co/is1wfv8K7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGravel Love love love @jillian_papa I will Venmo for one for Chris and I!! Long sleeve!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorrorAllDay Just don’t talk or befriend his family...stay out of Haddonfield around Halloween but Michael.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your response to a question about rampant sexual harassment in your candidate's campaign is to attack the woman… https://t.co/bFKer0MY7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK! NOW! THE REAL REASON FOR ALL OF THE UPBEAT , FUNNY LITTLE ANECDOTES AND POSTS, FROM ME, FOR THE LAST FEW DAYS!… https://t.co/XwxnwehEzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thelmaandlouise no sleep and getting on a plane ✈️ that will be 4 shots of espresso please!!! @ North Kansas City… https://t.co/1KhabuTgBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow Wickstrom Ford is a poppin place on a Saturday morning! And now we wait...#oilchange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliemason susan Collins plays Lucy to the Democrats’ hapless Charlie Brown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spoke with Montrezl Harrell about the #Lakers #Clippers rivalry: “You can respect the past history of what the La… https://t.co/vkf4BwxxWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidneyPowell1 BETO He is just a guy hand picked my Satan Soros to blow hot air filled with lies and manipulation u… https://t.co/Y7iBKMS7Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoratiousPowell @CrystalBeebe3 @Madonna @dubstarr73 @MEDUSAS_BROTHER @Sheena_655321 @YantisaJ @JamesTConleyII… https://t.co/3tHAIdmDvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm super hella Excited!!! I just made my brand new furniture purchases at #AaronsFurnitureStore!!! They get delive… https://t.co/nIviQKSC5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ughhh thinking about Beta Bae I would see omw to my 8AM class sophomore year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning feeling like it’s Christmas because...it’s game day. 🙌🏼 #DukevsUNC   https://t.co/BixyYHhAGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish they would stop saying TN is being man handled on the court....call it what it is. Foul ratio is ridi… https://t.co/hlERRCHx6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[got jax some new outfits last night so i gave him a bath this morning, dressed him, and just caught him checking hi… https://t.co/IzamzyNF5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Junior, if you had an actual job, you would not have the time to input your snide and worthless comments on twitter 24/7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @sonablast and Howard &amp; Nancy Bruner-Wilson for supporting the release.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valentineee @LanaDelWeirdAF You get a powerup for the Animorphs mention tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @JoeNBC Including the day after day free coverage they gave him by having him on and letting him ramble for hours...]]></document><document><![CDATA[👑Enter for a chance to win a #ForeverTotes @readforeverpub care package curated by Katee Robert, author of The King… https://t.co/0l4lB3TGmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe cabin fever is setting in from Snowpocalypse because I decided to brace the cold to deliver a very important… https://t.co/eFoLuZ4FKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[aight twitter friends lets make a poll, this is for my bachelor watchers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCBS12 @BillDeSteph @chortletown @irishfox1949 @SusanDuncanolp @LindaLeeKing @LoveDVoiceless @rissalipstick… https://t.co/9DD5cU6bJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work in progress — Seahorses are one of my favorite creatures in the ocean... they seem as magical and surreal as m… https://t.co/6pG9910Y8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_pniewski I’ll be there!! ☕️ Will there be a playlist for this event? Magical lights?  I’ll grab my coffee ...… https://t.co/JZqlTfre1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving my dog is honestly the hardest part of every day. #aspiringstayathomedogmom]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we come into the home stretch of Black History Month 2019 still time to expand your knowledge of Canadian histor… https://t.co/Y7tMo4n2J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Too bad the number of @GOP polled was smaller than your pitiful inauguration, smaller than your ti… https://t.co/ADjeHoviel]]></document><document><![CDATA[And as I’m trying to prepare for a presentation she sends me a photo of a flamingo with the caption “I put my leg u… https://t.co/RUn0FqMJYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omgosh mine too!!! I finally ordered one in November then days later got email from @taylornation13 that they were… https://t.co/KxwS95AK6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidlangford73 @AndrewRappaport @D_B_Harrison I thought the same thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystynaGadd @hjarche @Josh_Bersin @MarcZaoSanders The other day I just started claiming things. Like, I invented… https://t.co/L5Xi83fwRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUSINews @GavinNewsom Let me add that if you speak to 100 San Diegans, my experience is that at least 50 of us hav… https://t.co/sXx0D6V5LK]]></document></documents></author>