<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[El we que se iba a levantar temprano pars edtudiar bien chido se acaba de levantar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tsjennajam @IloveShemale44 @jockosrocket @SHEMALELIST @Tgirlfan69 @lithium66 @TGirlsAddict @kittysilk7… https://t.co/rrD7H6Pspj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This only works if there is a thick slice of cheese between the bun and pie. Maybe on both sides of the pie?… https://t.co/11URnCW9uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Kendall: scattered clouds, 71°F 100% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarreHouseknec1 Thank you for capturing the moment, @CarreHouseknec1! I really enjoyed this #nctiesunplugged poste… https://t.co/SV8ABjInoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus the breaches, plus Bitcoin, plus moving the prime meridian to heal the ozone, dumping tons of snow on the Sier… https://t.co/yEsnPgL4NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[He made the one who did not know sin to be sin for us, so that in him we might become the righteousness of God. - 2 Corinthians 5:21, CSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having a really hard time deciding what to pack...haven’t packed a thing yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluetoothCavity @bkohring1 @ActionBastard9 @ClaireEdwards88 @Rialisms Dude if you don’t support your friends uncon… https://t.co/iqRuS7n2Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalloryNoePayne Real consideration for me. Glad we had one, but part of why we're not planning another]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LevitatingYogi I go to bed shortly after sunset so now I can see music again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday Feb 16th, check out  aaroncbell93 in #AtlanticCity for the philadelphiacomedycollege Alumni Showcase… https://t.co/UbqVn5NuWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTD_Global Exactly my point I do not believe if not staying somewhere for life then a 10 year deal isn’t even good… https://t.co/CwLvcKbnjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Just because you corrected the spelling, it doesn't mean that you or Sean know what McCarthyism means. Ha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ofctimallen Love these tweets of yours...thanks for the backstage views!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neco_ornot 20 washcloths? For what? To knit into a sail in case of flood?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Saturday morning drive to Watseka will begin at 7:30 am. Heading to firemens retirement breakfast with dad Stop i… https://t.co/l9jc3oUATL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOFSpodcast @CCinemaPodcast "Phantasm" puts a whole summary of the movie on the poster. https://t.co/YP9GWX3cmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardwood mulch loading crew!!!! @Bronco_Band https://t.co/dIWgzS8bfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big day ahead.  ⚽️@Lionesses to get it done v Japan to win #SheBelieves ⚽️Tottenham to do the biz against Dortmund in the UCL 🥞Pancakes...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidtabrown @MLBNetwork @Eric_M888 Who’s left bidding on his services besides the Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmeliiitiiis Yo llevo el.control sobre lo que descargo sobre todo en esos grupos de hombres en donde mandan catálogos de avon 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Medea funeral- I would have loved to been lobotomize than ever see this film ever again.   Easily one of the wors… https://t.co/KGXyxzZkia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me:  My dad:  My mom: “I wonder if there are any dead bodies in the woods near our house”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the wettest Valvoline Jacket, I’d wear that bitch if I still had it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[L'avion transportant les 113 Québécois coincés en Haïti atterrira à Montréal vers 21h13. Le vol est retardé.… https://t.co/NSStdMtPFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fought the pain for a long time, I tried a lot and I failed. But now it’s time to excel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sean_lukasik @creagentmktg @TBEXevents @FLXWineCountry @FlyBrother It’s definitely on my come back and body - and… https://t.co/XUzyFbXyrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kc Airport Cmte approves ordinance for short term loan of up to 90 Million. Motion includes estimates cost(includin… https://t.co/AnrwGACGC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like if we just met and we don’t know each other anndd I don’t have any interest in getting to know you, PLEAS… https://t.co/gR3LQs93NE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington State Man Arrested After Threatening Pro-Gun Sheriffs https://t.co/8LB60Di0Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAST A DEADLY SPELL is on &amp; I’ve put everything else on hold for now. https://t.co/8HIfoqRWMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fcps1 will operate on a two hour delay today, 3/4. Offices will open on time @FCPS1News]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente @megreenwell Thinks he's doing something special, now that they made it a "golden ghetto" Would've… https://t.co/nLnlnVr0Ly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust the Process @CrossFit @CrossFitGames #CrossFit #19Point3 #InTheOpen #PaytheMan https://t.co/lOlwGTMt9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmaciasGdl que personal con tan poco sentido común al no venderme un medicamento controlado solo por que no tení… https://t.co/OCz4B08SC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is going to be so good next year https://t.co/g3ShZEkiFe via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Baker, thank you for all that you have poured into me in the last 6 years. You pushed me to try my hardest even… https://t.co/QHORhwb6CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[love my taylor mutuals, we can talk shit about each others faves n still be friends. thats what stan twitter is all about😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Darren Dreger,  Brady Tkachuk is a leader because he plows into goaltenders and he’ll do it again if h… https://t.co/OjdSoYzJmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @e_poterfield won his seat by 6 votes last Nov. blind, not to an accident or illness - has his ass who… https://t.co/P4s2vOea26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCoy75 @robpowellnews @SkyNewsPolitics So all Tories who are against Brexit should resign and seek re-election?… https://t.co/JQ6WccaDAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okdiario QUE DEVUELVAN LOS 75 MIL MILLONES QUE ESPAÑA LE PRESTO A CATALUÑA Y DESPUÉS HABLAMOS DE INVERSIONES, ASÍ… https://t.co/RHhmOimkhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek @realDonaldTrump Farrakon and his partner Maxine waters are the biggest haters in the country 👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said I was hungover and wanted to go home, and my co worked said “Isn’t that every Friday”  💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero esto no lo dicen los periodistas mediocres de televisa y tvazteca, ahora si que los cometortas del pri pan nes… https://t.co/rhClRdqabE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @NASCAR Since no one was hurt....  it was awesome to see live.  My first ever NASCAR event.  I will be back for more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseBoogie__4 I feel like he’s always posting other shit on ig. Not saying he’s not focused on the game but I fee… https://t.co/SuId9lB1iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N2NOther @scottEweinberg If it was legitimately one of the best films of the year like Roma was, I can’t wait for… https://t.co/tHHjjWBvCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRYALL140 @OzzieZuniga @smillerdegnan @HeraldSports @NFL @CanesFootball Do some research and see where Temple head… https://t.co/zfnLokYM5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Called A Violation of the RICO Act, basically an organized conspiracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Wieskamp is talking that talk following his game-winning three. https://t.co/jD99f8ddLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamera_faulkner @KING5Seattle @komonews @KIRO7Seattle @wsferries Thank you!! :) Such a beautiful location!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any artistic people want to help me with a tattoo design? Simple as can be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone please give this a listen and come back to me with your opinions. https://t.co/yokCwT2xcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the privilege of cataloging Dr. Carver’s rock, mineral, and fossil collection at Tuskegee for the NPS when I wa… https://t.co/mSnqXqPE6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoselynCanoo Good Morning Joselyn so Grogous and Sexy you are Breathtaking ❤❤❤❤❤❤❤❤😘😘😘😘😘😘💕💕💕💕💕💕💞💞💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andre05_02 @covfefecomic @mymynags @John_R_Berna @Aug1405 @PamCapitanini @Hulk4Trump @Lathenerd @SealeyGerald… https://t.co/oEQG3dFdef]]></document><document><![CDATA[CICI May As Well Give Me Her Twitter . I Doubt Ima Get My Account Back 😂 .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goon48 @UNDmhockey Thome looks susceptible to the stuff. He gets out so far to the side of the net that he can’t m… https://t.co/cu2RImUxXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECLSrick @Delta @greenbookmovie @TiffanyHaddish It’s really not very good - definitely not her funniest work - but… https://t.co/1F6H98Jcux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHoppeNHL @TBNSports @SCSUHUSKIES_MH 13-23-7 and Housley is still a coach in the nhl. Mind blowing !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 years of L ❤️ V  E with my bestie #happyvalentinesday 💋🥰💋 @ Dunmore Town, Harbour Island, Bahamas https://t.co/dB0aB3ai5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Premier always has a choice; that'swhy he's the Premier. #AutismAwareness]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Piano Trio in E-Flat Major, Op. 12: 3. Finale. Presto by Beaux Arts… https://t.co/dV3u1jotYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how much better he has been last 3 games with a different roster.  Just sayin. #kubball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Merrimack, NH? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/ZoUboQCVkM #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love March sports on , between the usa and european soccer, Australian football preseason and March madness, who… https://t.co/bEqhwDzniU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We for the can is yes and message Twitter night can we it just get https://t.co/eW1LUFNone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevvscott @tveitdal @inkl Pretty much, just look at healthcare here. Treatment not preventive. We treat, we don't… https://t.co/16UFViurze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSeatBlogs I would have rather invested some term here on McQuaid than trade for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ducks #floridaphotographer #florida #swfl #swflphotographer #waterbirds #birds #photography #wildlife… https://t.co/npZ3N7U3C0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatPeterG With me prolly when I went to take my clothes up to load the closet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing my glasses every time I travel.  Maybe I should put them on a string like my ear buds.  34 year old dudes we… https://t.co/YIcL8dEYDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bwhahaha Just call me the mouth of the south 😂, I’m clearly a big deal. Or I have no life it’s debatable 🤷🏼‍♂️😂.… https://t.co/C9j9Y3y18w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelBreed I agree that whatever Matt paid El Tucan was between them. I do think that El Tucan despite not being… https://t.co/oMYKZCRQMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastienlevert @AzureDevOps When it comes to task/issue management I'm with you buddy. Builds and releases, there's a lot of work to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Stones back to stinking. Waaaay too many easy buckets in the paint for a half of hoops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riverside Bulldogs having some fun taking #PhotosWithAlbert https://t.co/zmP2mfkSEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaywardWinifred @IlhanMN Solidarity with a Jew hating Islamist. Great friends you got there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving his baby straight BARS!!! TALK. TO. THIS. BABY!!!  (Son cheating for laughin thru his rounds tho.)… https://t.co/AIY4xli13b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss What happened to PM Theresa May and Great Britain?  O right:  she is not a murderous authoritarian dictator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elijah #4 playing in the tournament this past weekend.  #🏀 #basketball #cla #christianlifeacademy #lions @ Athens I… https://t.co/q5VGE7OOFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow that Niko Price vs Tim Means fight had one of the best rounds I’ve ever seen! Price landed that hook outta nowh… https://t.co/uv6gzNCGzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my mom ask me question after question after question after question https://t.co/89B05glFSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When an ice covered tree begins to thaw.  #MyMaine @wgme https://t.co/Q0Pa8TJNS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love science  I’m no fan of Science  Evidence comes in all forms. Studies done by and on OTHER people are just on… https://t.co/CaEZd7MStn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rasabatino Súmale a la simulación este hermoso detalle: https://t.co/IwpLk4NSre]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then do NOT check that other box, DO NOT then have to suffer yet another term of crooked liberals and their sca… https://t.co/YgYgVrGJCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fans of @CurseOfOak Look familiar? It ain't Smith's Cove, but it's a sure sign to me that Tuesday is right around t… https://t.co/KHtQCEFAIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes............ when I laugh I sound like a chainsaw and I find it hilarious so I laugh harder then it just sounds like a lawnmower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BuenasNoches amigos hoy fue un día de mucho trabajo, cómo les fue durante este día de #frio en la ciudad de #Monterrey 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday basketball stress reduction strategy:   Watch the 1st 1/2 of the men's game. Switch to watch the rest of the… https://t.co/wNi1mzEzyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kat1567 @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @WMALDC @LarryOConnor @JudicialWatch @POTUS That makes me so angry that these… https://t.co/ZjsW0qxclH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarsynElledge3 @KarsynElledge3 Hey...Good Morning and #HappyValentinesDay Keep up the good work at @TBMotorsprts P… https://t.co/Bu71x29yLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is almost here. I know because I just paid the annual dues at my golf club @coppinwoodgc. (the BEST club in… https://t.co/QRYEGHcAx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FLYHIGH #FLYHIGHENTERTAINMENT  #WhyFlyLowWhenYouCanFlyHigh  #TheSkyIsJustTheBeginning  #SMOOTHDRE #BIGC #NANI @ Vi… https://t.co/2xMWn42dJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakerho1  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge me all you want but I seriously can’t wait until Toy Story 4 comes out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscarcarrillou @ari_alvite Viniendo de un apolítico que hace comentarios políticos esto es un halago para mi.  Besos.]]></document></documents></author>