<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So much tonight at tsun! @CoachVic_MSU @HailStateWBK https://t.co/ztfrUnw3ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet IQ45 probably trots the #fakeflotus out when Melanoma tells him to fuck off]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be teaching a simple meditation technique at 11 am @Icenhauers this morning on Rainey street. Come by and visi… https://t.co/6BugITqVTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 good morning!! @RobNelsonABC7  @mcharlesworth7  you all looking great!!❤ https://t.co/EMA1RtHD0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris  Yes! Just stop thinking it is going to happen over night.  If it took 2 years for Trump to totally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rome was NOT built in a day.  Building will take time.    #npcbikini #npc #bikinicompetitor #mastersbikini… https://t.co/i07M1aTw2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump administration’s cruel new family planning rule threatens access to contraception, cancer screenings and othe… https://t.co/xQyy0YMluk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow: “Bee blames wife for making him shave off his nasty-ass beard disguise.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s in doubt I suggest a rewatch, as I am doing, it’s very enjoyable. It’s not fair to say this show makes me l… https://t.co/v6uFesVbAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO THIS IS MY MOM BRO. I MEAN I DONT LIVE WITH HER BUT STILL DUDE LMAO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We broke out to reveal our new book club title!  Fenway and Hattie!!  #WeAre44 #BFBluejays https://t.co/jJK7VATS0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, looks like we’re in a pretty standard fantasy story here, so we need to prepare for everything that can go… https://t.co/5qVDC2C91q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@visible where’s the closest charging station to JW Marriott? #sxsw2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CortneyKuehl @heidnicolee Oh I’m sorry if I exposed you https://t.co/GK4ZBdVIpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino This after licking Kim Jung Un’s boots and disgracing the Warmbier family for absolutely nothing. Ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it still cold in Nashville??? Why did the groundhog lie to me???? . . Drinking ALL the hot drinks in this co… https://t.co/GiRsvQ7Y5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[My questions surrounds conducting trials that tests models of care, however, how do we push innovation forward when… https://t.co/NyjXNwwGDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 109 Wapiti Lane #Loudon #TN  #realestate https://t.co/t8ClFaxSKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch. (@ GU Ramen Taps &amp; Tapas in Long Beach, CA) https://t.co/kczH1uUPpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielmarven Pregnant women got their bellies by swallowing a watermelon seed. 🍉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenCogar apparently, i mean i’d rather work out &amp; achieve my goals that way but i mean that’s just me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisanne120287 @DanComp02107462 It is normal to wonder why all of this is happening to a precious little one.Yet… https://t.co/tsA1Fia10x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abgutman @WethingtonPaula I write about #diabetes, #nutrition, #fitness and other heath topics for @EverydayHealth… https://t.co/ZAiueSuWeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham He's justified but shouldn't have got a 16 year old pregnant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan She's Muslim what do you expect ... what's so confusing about why she says what she says???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 28 but they want to give kellz 70 years 🤦🏽‍♀️ #contextualdiscrimibation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight pool hopping 😂🥰 OG suit 👙 @vandal_a @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/tj6ybysEQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudeMike2 @justinamash @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @GovBillWeld Trump 2020!😊❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Grace made the OHS Lacrosse team and today I sit in the cold on metal bleachers in support and adoration of my b… https://t.co/ahjvVCP9v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basicallyhalie @ParkerMcCollum @GGilbertMusic @michaelasgio Thank you! Best purchase I’ve made in a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport The main problem is that she was wearing sneakers, so she was 5 inches shorter than normal, plus she… https://t.co/KGGutmXeD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at my Dapper dogs y’all. They got new collars today. 🥰🤗 #goldenretrievers #puppers https://t.co/bJWqIi7HnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little update: Took my child to the park today once the rain settled of course.  My child NEEDS a haircut. He just… https://t.co/CKoWMg6AdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi my name is Taryn im 14 and i want to die dm me reply my tweet or follow showing i should live]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the press box at T-Mobile Park and hear someone in the crowd shout something about the ump checking his… https://t.co/BJ1eUneUrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today one of my classmates couldn't find childcare for her 16 month old. So our instructors told her to bring him t… https://t.co/twdkQHx5nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris @CAgovernor @GavinNewsom @chrislhayes You do great going up against trump. Consider running against… https://t.co/SZpddyhHJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs Guard you &amp; your home. My 130 lb doberman was Qualified more than this Racist Freshmen we erroneously elected!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain't seeking these type of thrills at all just so the homies know count me out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter The QAnon is the code name for nazi and kkk. They are the 1488ers and they are a threat to these United States]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly but we need to turn them around, and stop detaining them. Turn them around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the father of a beautiful baby girl... I absolutely cannot rock with nor co-sign putting hands on a woman in any… https://t.co/mfUf0vC2Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCTAL_Cos awesome Promotional Board for @SkillsUSATexas District Competition 👏good luck today @KregerSteele… https://t.co/jBJ8mLBSfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lordsofacid #prettyinkinktour #seattle #showboxsodo #band #concert #music #tour #againstthegrainphotography @ Show… https://t.co/XGrEVKHdFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimeses @jorgeramosnews Esa debió haber sido la última pregunta, no la primera.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McSean17 They wanted to raise German Shepherds and they had to choose between views of the La Croix or Shoreview]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanaLin4 @sannewman @kpmalama1 @washingtonpost She provided two who have already denied it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly—@TheDemocrats &amp; @MichaelCohen212 MAJOR COLLUSION PREPPING FOR “ATTACK TRUMP HEARING” #EndTheDems… https://t.co/fWA0zeccS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[R e t r o V i b e s 🤓 . . . . . . . . . #retro #coffee #saturday #saturdayvibes #brunch #ootd #ootn #houston @ Cata… https://t.co/fUAjqInkaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devin_Gibson15 chile i got this on repeat. when it started things i imagined back?? PHEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big massive, incredibly gigantic thank you to @newcountry94 @Bexxterz @MaOnTheAir for VIP tickets to the… https://t.co/WeEIUCp81I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My loves ❤️💗 (except Richard  @sunshizzle4) saying a final farewell to Michael Jr. 💔💔😢 #foreverinourhearts… https://t.co/sWnewoJDUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellaschwartz @kathyiwanicki @bloomsburykids Fingers crossed, would love bookmarks for my students 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrikeoftheMind @EWErickson @MarkBellingShow Excellent comment, thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Trump will win but if he happens not to win.. He would never act like you democrats..Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoAnnDwyer5 Guess you didn't watch it with me. Huh? Buzz off go mess with people you don't follow. I no longer follow you. Bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby fever is SUUUPERRRR high rn. Also seeing a lot of pregnancy announcements😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jenniferrothschild Are you where you want to be today? Check your thoughts! https://t.co/MEyHzzLMTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowledge is power so the more we know, the more we listen to others to learn more. #MondayMotivaton #Inspiration… https://t.co/MThCiSAkBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallHerVixen @SoodTheDude708 Have you been peeing a lot more than normal too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on a big #cosplay haul delivery... I can't wait to actually see what I got!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This had me rolling. Charles Barkley SAVAGELY Roasts Jussie Smollett on NBA / TNT Highlights Show [Video] https://t.co/5iOHujEMvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I think I’m going to transfer to a community college. I might stay in Delaware, but I’m looking at some community colleges in Atlanta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryRGrayJr @ValeriaBrownEdu Jealousy? This is a thing? If anything I feel pity and sympathy for my fellow profs!!!!🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy #JeopardyAllStars I don’t know about the likes of some the top game show critics on social media right no… https://t.co/eYwam4MOji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking 5 minutes to read this was the best thing I did for myself this morning https://t.co/G8H05zyMAa via @iimag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooooohhhhh you can now catch my show #cootercatwalk at marysdenver EVERY SUNDAY at 8pm. 21+ To kick it off I have… https://t.co/UhnkCwrwc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have spilled approx. ten gallons of bbq sauce and I have yet to be fired. so i guess i’m a good worker or something]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sami1206 Girl if you had done that.... you would just have really hurt yourself 🤣🤣🤣 maybe at my old place LOL   P… https://t.co/4gxetpQ3K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean... Come on! THIS is how get someone's attention! What are YOU doing to shout out our #ProductPricePromise an… https://t.co/9yJoDIbb0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS NEWS HAS LITERALLY MADE MY DAY, WEEK, AND MONTH #hellodarkness #myoldfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have a hard time trusting someone who doesn't turn up to Baby Shark... https://t.co/I76UeQ2uAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sleeping very soundly, now I'm up having an mini anxiety attack https://t.co/aZ6UunKffy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jitobear #GISHentinesDay #SorryNotSorry #spamming https://t.co/ij4kb5LnLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished hiking 4.40 miles in 1h:30m:14s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/WTQLSRbGiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders of course we can improve aspects of our country but it is the best place on the earth just as it is!… https://t.co/MV8oot62JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍Beilers Donuts, Philadelphia  . . Elvis Delight (with bacon topping) and Nutella Donut 🍩  . . Very creamy and swee… https://t.co/enMtXTwKhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleornls Cero aguante ya lobu... no fuera a los 16, porque PARTY ROCK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gorgeous JoAnn is lucky enough to grab one of these cute little star blouses right out of the box! #prettygirl… https://t.co/YLt48R3pGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama Court Awards Aborted Fetus the Right to Sue Abortion Clinic?! https://t.co/qTtK2sHhhc via @RollingStone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super impressed by @CITGOiaOLLE students who created a whole marketing plan and delicious product. @aliefstem… https://t.co/cIlqWDdCdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Happening Again LEGENDARY LINE-UPS every time #6950 https://t.co/cv81uzVSoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No new haircut, but trust me, I do have other ways...😩😏🤦🏾‍♀️ https://t.co/X4Yj2F1Qgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wofstargirl. Hi Ana I was wondering when is the upcoming event for Lucy Liu's star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?… https://t.co/LzcBwniWgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ImHappierWithout Dairy. If ur near me u r 2. Makes me gassy. #lactose #dairy #milk #vegan #vegetarian #]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidarredondo Lol! He was trying to say that you can hide the truth when its staring everyone in the face. I think he was wrong :S LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was definitely tired. Definitely mentally exhausted coming in to this event. But I guarantee tears I shed last ni… https://t.co/ShAkxt4zli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britbristow @hallmarkchannel @IamWillKemp @IamLaceyChabert Me!  20 minutes! Woo Hoo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you all.  I was only sharing what I have learned from my own experience.  Satan and his false Christ are tak… https://t.co/exLZEl9hPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WISH YOU WOULD BE AS HARSH WITH EVERY ONE WHITE PERSON WHO CALL 911 ON A BLACK PERSON WHEN THEY ARE JUST GOING TH… https://t.co/vLXird5RTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamGuertler Twitter keeps playing with my emotions. Please don’t get my hopes up only to break them 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck @IlhanMN She understands the English language just fine when she says the Jews are just out for the… https://t.co/eZpbAVszcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Ann Conway really opened my eyes last night as she must have repeated herself a mile a minute how McCabe is a… https://t.co/s0xFXis8NU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#8thgrade Ss in Mrs. Plamann's #art class created needle felted landscapes based on a pic of somewhere they have vi… https://t.co/VSHg6fHWl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paris Jackson Breaks Silence On ‘Leaving Neverland’ Doc: Stop Taking My Life ‘So Seriously’ https://t.co/6VL4J3L7mu via @HollywoodLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS Friday March 8th  STAFF VS. STAFF B-BALL Red Team:  -Jacobo -Porchia -Ruiz -Patton -Archie -Danny V.   Blue Te… https://t.co/kLH4BO4cQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[II think that more #WomenOnBoards are needed to advance gender equality today. Do you agree? #SheBelongs… https://t.co/5qbjc2tpAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I don’t fuck with Vegas hosts on so many levels right now. These mf just discriminated against half of my crew.… https://t.co/DEslb6jvUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[This episode hits close to home @TheSimpsons. I took care of both of my disabled parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a victory donut for finishing the nursery today so I guess I’ll eat this apple]]></document></documents></author>