<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I accidentally went to class a little tipsy and my professor asked if anyone here had problems with being motivated… https://t.co/hHVzHJO0DF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews A different culture? How does that work? Is she ignorant?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma be sad when I’m gunna have to take my nose piercing out for a job 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @mrs_freer to post covers of 7 books I ❤️: no explanations, no review-just the cov… https://t.co/bVrVEdgy5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROCKTOPICS @barbiejoy Mama don’t mind the envious, jealous and ugliness of loser haters...  You’re a Boss Woman wi… https://t.co/vhBGypRpQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmanuelMacron I had a very difficult time, Sir, explaining to the Dove that she is a target and that it is my fau… https://t.co/iRdRyZSrMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 30 Day Challenge - Week 2. I wrote another 7,500 words in my writing project. I still want to increase that rate… https://t.co/DcPWLDdc15]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF 9th Annual Echo Awards Spotlight February 15, 2019 TMP's Best Musicians Of 2018 Michael Brü… https://t.co/ZK7FnjySY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Minors and “ADULTS” please report as it is stated. Don’t fall into the Cupich’s consensual sex bs...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re attacking a man who retired. And who is also dying of cancer. You are despicable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hkerkhofs @maxarmstrong @IHboog @jwolf7447 @TheChadColby @DerekHarms4 @FarmChicJodi @JenSchweigert @plowwife… https://t.co/McXLPvq2vJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell me that at a Norwegian Coaches Conference for tennis the term “Fjordhands” was used. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BardCoachTurner It’s sad, but you’ve got a point. I’ve always been an LBJ supporter but this side of him is hard to defend as a fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phil_petty @philadper2014 @SpeakerPelosi If this is true. It will catch up to her eventually. As the rest of the h… https://t.co/GbfX43FiHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laptop machine fixed  I’d say it’s about time to go check that new @VelaSeff out (https://t.co/sX43Dy5sA4)]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Matthew 12 we see Jesus heal a man with a “withdrawn” and withered hand. As soon as Christ heals him he’s met wi… https://t.co/julPxnoGk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Return of Achievement Radio - Late Thursday Night Special uploading now]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does this mean ? They get 1 day off when it's St.Jean Baptiste Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll ✏️ #pencil you In this #saturday , Confirming You’ll #skirt Any #issue Beautifully @byronlarsbm !!!   Inbox 📨… https://t.co/q2xiNvcfs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite podcast episode to date 🙌🏼 I love how EM is full of skeptics. EBM is about doing what’s best for the patie… https://t.co/g06GdvZ7RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WshSportsDude @NatsGal @dcsportsbog @ScottSAllen They BET NOT (that's right BET NOT) get rid of Joe B &amp; Locker!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatasthaGhoul Usually would of just passed by this but that’s exactly when you push it your hardest and keep perfe… https://t.co/JPrsRlsHjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice day for baseball practice. Finally, I get a chance to relax and just enjoy the day. @ City of Martinez Joe DiM… https://t.co/2pXra1PYp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This gay bar started playing Shallow and then skipped to another song... electric chair !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanSileoShow this has become an awesome Monday Night Tradition listening to you on @WEEI! The Boston vs LA rivalry… https://t.co/jvfSvvV74t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops extra late on feeding the trolls lately. Is it even happening tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out our former @BrickMemorialHS student!! 🐎🇺🇸 CC: @Brick_K12 @gdalton_BTPS @MsMac_BTPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love her more and more. Decency, common sense and compassion, @NicoleArbour has it going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tresmonsieur201 @arcp_ @kim9973 @GrayzoneProject @jaarreaza @VoluntadPopular @JulioBorges @jguaido @dcabellor When… https://t.co/LxqDnSIabh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skeeter_f @BrianLaslie Right. U were right to espouse your war mongering. U keep telling yourself that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate Republicans need to get on the right side of history. They are presently supporting a criminal in the White… https://t.co/w2sTirl6oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strystyl @andrewwagner29 @scott_jasonandy @Bourland_T @daenku32 @Clarknt67 @brylockvonrock @ToddOnFranchise Potent… https://t.co/0unmesdmqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mountaingal456 I tweeted this earlier today loved her she made that show!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone from work adds you on twitter dot com you should get a notification that says “Becky is now watching you”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d be lying if I said I didn’t miss y’all. @JohnnySmiley33 @MurphyPowell]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think by now we are used to it but every time the machine beeps saying I’m almost done scares the crap ou… https://t.co/GmIKNdSmxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evandawson Wow. Wow. I am really shocked by Feinstein’s tone and responses. I think she could have handled this si… https://t.co/lEv5yeoT3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I'm good, a couple of mistakes early the team will get it together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Reezy Yep,  our single 'The Airbrush Wizard of Heaven' was number 1 behind the iron curtain for 5 straight we… https://t.co/8HW9zgfme4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JT16283803 @bschaeffer12 @Tolcou15 Oh no, I fully understand.  But to say the Jays should call him up, makes no se… https://t.co/9n71PEBkA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats girls 2019 District Team Champions.  #goboats⚓ #AllIn⚓ #dont✔the☑ @ Robert F. Busbey Natatorium https://t.co/1ze34ENf4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbaileywnct @pirateradio1250 @JonathanEllerbe @TroyDreyfus @tweetingclip https://t.co/dNi4RYZXR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY SUNDAY EVERYONE!!!!!!  Today is a very excited day. Working with emsavs_ and piotrekhightower today on an awe… https://t.co/LouYVDb139]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t appreciate the solution until you appreciate the problem - Power of Moments #npspowerofmoments]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron Stan’s can’t deflate his stats long enough to realize that his numbers don’t equate to winning ! And that’s… https://t.co/sxFTQcuneC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevDon It doesn't matter where the cruise ship goes. If you're with the wrong guest, 7 days is too long and painf… https://t.co/6aGPPbTuqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @emfvet78 @gsteck74 @fortressfin @gopoundsand1234 @Jenn198523 @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs @mymynags… https://t.co/khMfeFh6ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #Clayton on Government Rd &amp; Jack Rd near Barber Mill Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[For people of a certain age... Ever play this drinking game in college when you watched 90210? @andshewas and I did… https://t.co/n5hmcqn0gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bIakejmorgan I love how people are trashing 2014... that team holds the all-time Georgia record for scoring. Also… https://t.co/n6YD9t4JvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods bwahahahaha @JohnTRourke @jasmaxwell @BajaHoncho @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support Pres… https://t.co/QJ3sCPgd2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever written and done the layout for 100 pages of a graphic novel before you realized you had no idea what… https://t.co/cRPAG4Ttc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[2A 126 Spenser Harris of Newton-conover finishes a brilliant HS career with a 7-1 win. Will get third in this tournament, 64-1 this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shamusroan13 @lisazumba10 Why because I have my hair and your a bald ass fucker😜😜😜😜😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is March 6, 2019 and no one has a problem calling an undershirt tank top a "wife-beater". So that's where we're at.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Broncomaniac58 @ShannonSharpe Let me tear your ACL, or break your foot, or injure you like he was and tell me you… https://t.co/uICXGIbfJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlamandGore It was a great video. I was worried it would be preachy... It wasn't. It was informative. The stats di… https://t.co/6aNp0yMLws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/gUFNzeIA4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suntimes They are backsliders .....Return to your first Love Jesus Christ ..... The Real Jesus Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for Aladdin dress rehearsal! @FRApanthers @FRAHEADofMS https://t.co/l895glaeUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioCavalli @kevinsjuts @Notorious_JRod And all that being said I do realize MOST possessions would not be affected by a 40 second clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recap from last night with @downlinkmusic and the doom system tour. Just wrecking idl ballroom so much that the cei… https://t.co/jIOu9wVij9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The princess bowl seems wack #stayinside at least I was with these cuties https://t.co/nzzCxP5m3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[MJs dad murdered and estoban loiza dealing coke. @thekapman @chrisbleck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @BY1959 @politico But also they're saying he didn't, no special treatment, nothing to see here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 God bless and keep you Dawn And your mother you are still in my prayers I hope you are feeling somewhat better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to move on it’s obvious he’s trying to find reasons to not have to come here #phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, another most happy of birthdays to our favorite meteorological prognosticator Tom @Skilling! Definitely not gr… https://t.co/n35rGGrNfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand Chuck has taught you well. How to obstruct and keep your gravy train going. Useless tick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyMRosati @watchkeep @UT_Grad_Amy @letterofmercy @ML05781542 @juleswoodson11 @writer_dee @wartwatch… https://t.co/kgktrGgFqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is #InternalFamilySystems (IFS) “Parts Work” Therapy? I think it’s easier to explain if you have seen the chil… https://t.co/KXR9bLPmoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to preach @PotentialSC today on behalf of @CASAdoption ! #gospel #adoption]]></document><document><![CDATA[Civic duty day. #downtownsanbernardino @ San Bernardino City Hall https://t.co/afyEtbtSVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yourallyjohnson @KevinKleinLIVE @ZackGalafanakis Wow heidentical tomybrotherJerry(looks)my yngr bro by 2 yrs...( h… https://t.co/Xxseb99yps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Parkes @AndreaLoken It’s the duty of care aspect that this motion violates in my opinion.  The directors have… https://t.co/7zgIjMpePY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachcecil7721 And only 3 times since Mark Few became coach. 42-3 in the Few era. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katthyaaa @mgpe_rd @transparenteSon Te podras tardar pero la verdad llegara...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marshall9News @hickenlooper Well if bad Kiss cover bands and the people who enjoy them are a potential voter base… https://t.co/wxiAS9DLxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have I changed in the past 3 years? #Gay #GayMan #GayBoy #Homo #Homosexual #SelfPortraits #SelfPortrait #SnapChat… https://t.co/eJQPC5RHdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayeljac @myserenity69 @CoryBooker I get what you’re saying but, what got Trump elected was the fact that voters o… https://t.co/CCad8zFPY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun licenses should be allowed just like driver's license, The bi laws says we all have a right to bare arms but we… https://t.co/4As5Wt8GTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdkitkat129 @luvnewinfo @Georgiapinecone @GATrumpTrain @ga_kag @gakagtrumptrain @TruthMaga @full_mount727… https://t.co/7H56aSFZFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Tic Toc!!! How’s that dark money doing Alex!! https://t.co/eNceXeA2P4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Florida, #FSU dominating Mens 60M final... @TnFjunkie @FloTrack #NCAATF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Anyone can sue anyone for anything, Charlie. Trump sued Bill Maher for millions when Maher made a cr… https://t.co/D4mxnlk91Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @AOC @RealCandaceO How about a "white" New Deal also. We've been getting screwed for decades now. I str… https://t.co/4ITN3Stxr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Diego just crushed the much larger Gall. Can’t count dude out. #ufc235]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nut_history Dodger Stadium Big A BankOne Kingdome (gone) Olympic (Expos) Stadium (gone) Memorial Stadium (Baltimor… https://t.co/9A8TCzjgPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @LIBREinitiative had the opportunity to bring many Dreamers to The Hill to share their stories to members of Co… https://t.co/FzS4C6wMin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kryptonlogic @YoPaulieNJ @westcoasternet Neither does toxic masculinity, but they keep on with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats    on her first online session!!! She did a get job and  the passion of getting results is amazing. Till n… https://t.co/P7kqRIYncS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceWyattRoss I think the words you are looking for are "child abuse" and "dehumanizing"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN She is being targeted because of her comments and behavior. She brought it on.  You and her… https://t.co/oMRRDMVLdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CraigSBPA It amazes me that the media do not condem this HATE speak!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard from a reliable source that there is going to be a Jaxxon series on Disney+. Spread the word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesseawayne1 Your the one that’s going to hell the flu that you have is more than you think it is. I’m just a guar… https://t.co/VSQjl7lS66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Red Go Tutu 5k run this morning in #Gainesville. @ Shands At the University of Florida https://t.co/KU1i5s0UMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amoldeshpande78 @FBNFarmers Hundreds of ag shows a year and singling out Commodity Classic? Doesn’t say a thing ab… https://t.co/Mv7d3sCsdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Senate floor, Leader McConnell says Trump will sign the funding bill, and will also declare a national emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) Interesting to see leaders of the Conservative Resurgence (CR) being falsely accused of liberalism or being soft… https://t.co/Vcx4BukEXi]]></document></documents></author>