<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@SenFeinstein: Oppose the Trump admin's changes to Medicare Part D to protect progress fighting the HIV epidemic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg idk y ppl keep thinking you’re on the show.. I’d know your singing voice immediately😂😂#TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could tweet this every minute: Why are Republicans not in the least bit concerned about a president who secretly… https://t.co/NBIlxnWLEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty Woman (@ Nederlander Theatre - @nederlanderbway for Pretty Woman: The Musical (NY) in New York, NY w/… https://t.co/TBwLs1z9Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish they had phone plans with unlimited data and streaming and all that but like 50 minutes a month for the phon… https://t.co/nf8uVzqA0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is a cheese lovers onion soup! @ Le Rivage https://t.co/anaQoQtKpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANTIGOPMVMT And he had the *gall* to be insulted.  What. An. Ass.  He deserved all of that X’s triple.  #Swamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prince_petty_ Ewwww fuck that guy. Mance does this with another fan at Unsanctioned Pro and I think it’s all in fu… https://t.co/udrXrgHOFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Justin  @Esther188rod  HELLO JUSTIN GIVING US THE WEATHER UPDATE SEEING THE WEATHER  JUST NOW AT 5:15 PM SHOU… https://t.co/B31Hb4LAs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slim_Goody_23 @LcDeLo22 @Breezy5312 NUMBER ONE??!? https://t.co/ZFJ4pJZHPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyavila71 @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 @realDonaldTrump Completely unbecoming of anyone who claims to be a member… https://t.co/1VVWxCc6MP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisalibrarian No... But what is to stop the publisher just creating more and more and more journals "to be convert… https://t.co/wSnvGG8Qzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayanna Pressley gets up to SMEAR the President. Congress shuts her down! @realDonaldTrump @AyannaPressley must GO!  https://t.co/CRFwYITkZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumphreyBarry @kyhighs @KHSAA The Catholic schools do not have “entrance “ exams. They have placement tests. There… https://t.co/zGCLFt41rF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sagman_39 Hang in there! I miss your face in the Halls. Hope you are being the best you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Darlin knows that her mama comes home today! @ ms Nieuw Amsterdam - Holland America https://t.co/6fAnaYIK1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Pugs Are Made - Funny Cartoon | Curious, Funny Photos / Pictures #hilarity #chuckle #grin #hilarious https://t.co/kONyXaxtg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone meet my dog Mia. She thinks she’s a human and sleeps in between @KlecanA and I with her head on the pillow… https://t.co/EkTzUcNHxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why would you be proud of this? Can’t you see how hated you are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me siento plena que los clientes me digan que les encantó sus llaveros. Gracias por la preferencia, besitos❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a ball (pun intended) covering women's h🏀🏀ps this season! These ladies are so much fun to cover and the ones I… https://t.co/pvEbtZCA4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amestris_star This and the Google most asked questions interview are my two I want the most for Tom to do. The sof… https://t.co/dnoTjTUu3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re someone who’s not in a relationship or have a family - you have to understand that as you grow older, you… https://t.co/w3itcVjbkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bkrayder @etnow Humm try again it's not about him not winning. He was happy for Cuarón and Roma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling at this lgbt cafe. They have bunk "beds" (more like cubicles with cushions to sit on) and I'm squatting on… https://t.co/EtQFHeOPz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it is important to you to see this homecoming, DO NOT rely on a 30 min to 2 hr heads up from social media. It is… https://t.co/cd2V0W27xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabei de mandar 12.000 reais pro meu pai, eu vivi pra isso.  Obrigada Deus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta Let the man Rest In Peace. It is disgusting you’re saying all of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linzy happy in love spam! #MyPerson and my #BFF and a #Murderino 🥰😍🥰 #HappyIsNew Thank you for loving me 💙🖤💜🖤💜🖤💙… https://t.co/YsjAlUL2xB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and I are literally texting about our credit scores and our favorite paper towel brands right now and I’ve never felt so grown up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ty has never been so happy to go on a walk. Love having the #OneWheel so he can full on run. Clocked in their speed… https://t.co/dyG53WStbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JIBRALTER I worked at BK in the 80’s. So food with mustard lettuce and pickle!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doandrad JAJAJA me inspire de su amigo Hideki habia que hacerle homenaje]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is always so much to be grateful for. Just because you don’t have it today DOESN’T mean you will never have it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up, this woman had the personality of a lettuce sandwich. Wow. I was devastated. So fast forward a year an… https://t.co/jjwCfRvUOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Museum of Illusions New York https://t.co/qAZKDzTbiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talked to my little brother tonight on facetime, we talked for awhile before he asked me how work is. Told him its… https://t.co/RNeSJny6pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdgarIrene I personally over-think everything! Lol! I can still hear my mom telling me to quit projecting on what… https://t.co/95SJbqLbYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealJBGoon @rickygervais https://t.co/zIczImwun3 ironically post this 2 days ago on my Facebook page for this reason! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DIRECTVService we just ordered the movie The Favourite via our Genie Box. The message came up “preparing for playb… https://t.co/Ejg9cWVYlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes That’s nice. My parents never bankrolled me for college or anything else. What are they learning by parents doing this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlacklionCTA @SenSasse I got nauseated just watching it. These people are ghoulish murderers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I love KND and I ship 3/4 I will never forgive them for that god awful zombie kiss lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyfromteenmom My grandfather is Morton Eugene III , they did it thrice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin’....Breathing....and Stretching with the GMU Wrestling team on a Sunday afternoon...🧘🏽‍♂️💪🏼🤼‍♂️ ❣️What a gr… https://t.co/G2yFXK3FgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has saved us and called us to a holy life—not because of anything we have done but because of His own purpose an… https://t.co/UyW3eoApLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Springfield Gardens, Queens https://t.co/aWzndUUXTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarWoodhouse That just left the grossest taste https://t.co/eGCbdtKmwg my mouth 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[1,159 page “compromise” completed? Did they list each food they shall feed the detainees? Did they detail each 1/2… https://t.co/TOBPOmZr1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordonhardy @MalcolmNance Maybe he will treat Trump just like family!!! 🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom Petty and The Heartbreakers - I Won't Back Down (lyrics) https://t.co/GKAachay23 via @YouTube.  OKC Thunder Anthem!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotiUno La Sra. Ramírez es una de pocas figuras que defienden la estadidad que gozan del respeto del pueblo. Un ej… https://t.co/w8cBhpDbY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreggDoyelStar @AllenBourff @HSESchools I hope you’re not done! This is becoming a pattern with @HSESchools.… https://t.co/AiweUDRFsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/6X78Jvtgn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and now we have old white men from the #GOP explaining twitter to us #CohenTestimoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have certain people on my Twitter that CAN NOT WAIT to copy others, start all the drama, and try to hard fit in w… https://t.co/GLpR4ObtVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman @AOC David let me tell you what happened when here in Ontario Canada our minimum wage went up. Firs… https://t.co/BCywZO1pGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why you don’t cheese people or animals. Or use cheese as a verb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARLOSEES @elrenecito2 @JavierEnrikez @tonymarquezroon @luisaguilerahmo @drmonteverde 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says creeper more than "liking" someone's random posts from a year ago in the middle of the night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you make a comment, you’re supposed to let your words pass through three gates: Is it true? Is it kind? Is i… https://t.co/zwRRxyLo9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, the founder of the world’s premier environmental organization took the socialist to task for her ridiculous Gr… https://t.co/lcBnBJ0NKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arrowp Me senti até culpada agora por estar trabalhando para manter possível o sonho de chegar no primeiro bilhão.… https://t.co/NR9SYp5AjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister got a new car Sunday and hit 100 miles right meow. How??? Where are you going without me????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @girlscouts I learned a lot from being a Girl Scout. The most important being the Girl Scout Promise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamás entenderé eso de leer teorías de GoT. O sea, ya me pasó y quedé muy moleata porque me arruinó toda una tempor… https://t.co/H34Qd3e0e2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Happy birthday big brother. Keep breaking barriers &amp; speaking truths.   Have yo day yo way P 🍻😘 https://t.co/N2R2o4AUbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some cougar on IG been sending me nudes every morning and I’m not complaining, she fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthem getting mediocre reviews big fucking yikes https://t.co/5r9bWEwpWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of y’all gon get your feelings hurt trying to stay down for someone that clearly doesn’t give a damn about you or your feelings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's day is they day to celebrate loving yourself.  Others only get to participate they don't suck.  Unless… https://t.co/l8VJ2fodwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my oil changed is something totally new and I don't mind the waits -thankshunni #needyjaguar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chiefjocelyn I’m watching teen mom.............it’s a sad night for me 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I wish I could give each desendent of negro slave 5 acres and a home with 4 bedrooms and two baths . To live a… https://t.co/0CINLvM5tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GBPNews Refuses to Broadcast The #Murder of #MaryGreer   Orchestrated By The #Kemp-#Abrams-#Trump-#Carter  Mother… https://t.co/7zKFAvI59k]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve Been Waiting For Like 3 Months For These Stupid People To Come Fix Our Bed, &amp; They Are Finally Coming Tomorrow!!! I’m So Excited!]]></document><document><![CDATA[overcast clouds -&gt; broken clouds temperature down 57°F -&gt; 54°F wind 11mph -&gt; 3mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh heck no. i f with his music, but he DOES NOT deserve to be outta this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Proudbearof3 @AmberScholl oh my gosh, these are actually so gorgeous! thank you so much, i’m going to look into th… https://t.co/jZa2JknnkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iwas challenged by @CLSGirlsTennis post covers once a day of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews.  Thi… https://t.co/QcmDwPgc0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol at the $10 umbrella I just bought that broke instantly 😭 I should’ve known better 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Project-Based Learning: Benefits, Examples, and Resources https://t.co/fsBqjyglpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[lost my best friend today. don’t have words for why this has to happen. but i know he’s happy and healthy in pet he… https://t.co/2mmBprK5YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poptivist Woohoo!!!  I actually listened a couple times. On first listening, it sounds kinda sad, but really it's… https://t.co/zs4DuPPBk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Oh, surely Mitch can, and will.  He showed us who he is, believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerriski @Nationals @whatwouldDOOdo @EireannDolan @masnKolko @Ploger @TalkNats2 @FightinHydrant @NavyYardNats I’m… https://t.co/StcJrJ0X2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[He asked to go to school in a “big boy button shirt” and wanted his tie to go from plain red to Valentine’s Day the… https://t.co/2mOT2aLAuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how loved I am at work! I’m constantly told either how cute or incredible I am and it just makes everything at work more pleasurable🙊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even really thAt into fashion all things considered but I’m sad about Karl :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katjutras tellement: pour celle de 6 ans suggestion jeune gardienne payé pour animer!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh pedicure, red toes and freshly washed rope drying. #Femdom #fetish #ropebondage #footfetish #FootWorship… https://t.co/PpVNOhreuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I already know I’m off for St. Patrick’s Day. Who wants to go downtown with me to the parade?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol this sounds so sad that I'm only 20 and I'm saying this, but it is something I had to learn. But, seriously yea… https://t.co/PZAsuaYLum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourNerdWonder @petersimeti I love this ❤️ Peter, thank you for all that you do for comic readers, for inspiring s… https://t.co/mQAK9mLMwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can truly say the power of a "person" to persuade a crowd of 25,000 to leave their Christianity, values and yuk i… https://t.co/XZD825UAfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Ojalá porque que se sepa hay un montón por ahí viviendo la buena vida en casas de millones!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you want #KennyG in your living room on Valentine’s Day? I’m discussing this with @DesireeMWiley and… https://t.co/4Lj2qSUWbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want Donald Trump anywhere near the Presidency. He is a criminal traitor, ignorant to boot. All this is a n… https://t.co/PlqTmELYj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blazer_85 @CFL_News @InstantReplaySA Seriously! He’s gone. Done. Don’t want to know (never did).🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trinity is excited to announce new members of our staff leadership team. Welcome to Caroline, Sharon and Jodi! For… https://t.co/mVkPCntXmS]]></document></documents></author>