<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[While I agree with her this time, remember the stated goal of Muslims is to take over countries. She will run over… https://t.co/Ed3PDjDMES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the 7th Grade Lady Titans for their tournament win in Washington today!! Great job, ladies!!… https://t.co/YRAMzN2bAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[my kink is not being able to decide between 2 things off the menu then always regretting the one I chose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting organized is exhausting. Plus once I start to organize one space I get distracted and start organizing others. #squirel]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re telling me jensen ackles is bacchus at this year’s mardi gras and i’m not there? rude but ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a difference Caroline Novak has made for public education in Alabama! So grateful for her steady, selfless vis… https://t.co/1oE0TUNQjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylabryn Hehehe hasnt he!!! Girl he’s still half his expected full-size weight which is absolutely nutz🤣 They’re… https://t.co/gdm3dgLhFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being blamed for someone else’s inability to be responsible &amp; set their alarm for work. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Good Lord no! You can like certain things about others and overlook their faults.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon @chrisparente  you'll be with Natalie again  Photo taken 7 years ago https://t.co/6t8I30vOiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apposed to me waiting for Cassandra Fabs Jayme Makayla Leilany Esme Jackie and Diamond https://t.co/nqIEPiU1zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[karl lagerfeld was blunt n harsh n opinionated n controversial but if we can free or mourn rappers that are rapists… https://t.co/LRzuYlL27V]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a perfect day for GOLF. #nofilter Salon and Spa  . . #trump #golf #miami #salon #spa #beauty #beautiful… https://t.co/E4Q3X2ecSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi someone recommend me some good ppl to go to for lip fillers!!! Preferably Oregon/West Washington area !]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great!!! My kiddos love our SEL time together every day. I have to admit... it’s one of my favorites too! 🤗… https://t.co/Aya1pQveul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePuglielli This is a great idea! Our customers def have responded well to it - moreso this thread was about all… https://t.co/fqQQh5n1r1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#minnesnowta welcomed me back hard this weekend. Ugh. I love me some snow, but come on now...  #mn #minnesota #snow… https://t.co/R8CP38zog6]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY SATURDAY! What are you guys up to? Did you hear temps will lower next week? You better enjoy this gorgeous we… https://t.co/i43WSMETd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattiebookittie He is such a fun student!!!! Always willing to participate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @joelbreakstone for spreading your word on FakeNews. #FakeNews https://t.co/RFIf717jJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUST LISTEN!!  Your ears will thank you.  (So will your soul. And bank account.)  I am getting endless positive fee… https://t.co/J8UAnqiVPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to “The Ones that Don’t Make It Back Home” by Justin Moore and realized that in between scenes of first r… https://t.co/r2DRhB1TZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sker4Lyfe @Tsiser45 @epitomee @lynnv378 That is a Viewmaster that shows three dimensional images. Atari is an earl… https://t.co/tdCEYqk14z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaFincher @gwoman9810 That is the worst. Could they possibly get any worse lighting??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bellagio Hotel &amp; Casino in Las Vegas, NV w/ @viivis @dani_l_c @alxortmusi https://t.co/m3Okgjkwpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan To make us “eat our own” has been their tactic for years. I have an idea:  let’s all agree to support w… https://t.co/8oAsZ958jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy @Away_Team_ @MJtheProphet @Phil_Nourse @ElPatriotaA1776 @sharrond62 So we should ban all talk women. Great plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-SXSW fire inspections are underway at 120 bars, restaurants and clubs in downtown Austin. Last year… https://t.co/l7bBD7NjSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADDcrafter @jimbcbs4 I thought it just meant someone who enjoyed smoking some ribs “in some peace and quiet for once”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Birthday Tribute for my baby girl❤️ 🎺 🎺🎺🎺🎼🎼🎼 @ Greenlawn Memorial Gardens Cemetery and Mausoleum https://t.co/IhwmlOgE7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Disagree - this is Not about Dem versus Rep. The guy occupying the Oval Office is a criminal. That’s… https://t.co/YFPnJIJINs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @andrerucker51 @keanothedog @JayValenz67 @hey_butter @terry313401 @delgeo1 @poppij @MarilynHallett… https://t.co/iiPrhjoMPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great to meet you tonight @SheriffChody!  Come visit us at Jarrell High School sometime! #LivePDjunkies https://t.co/yzEZZt0ZLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalism  History  Capital has existed incipiently on a small scale for centuries in the form of merchant, rentin… https://t.co/xFuNQNVaQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoOneIsAboveLaw Americans paid for the investigation. We deserve to see it, all of it. Any thing less and no one will trust the results.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dem's are investigating things they brought up meetings and the Spineless GOP voted them down everytime over the last two years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's good to have a deep thought before saying things like this one. At a glance even without much thinking I have… https://t.co/vueDWlqhht]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to look like @JLo when I am nearing 50. Pero me gustan las tortillas. 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mohennessey i legit spoke out loud to my self the entire show. Someone was like: WE FELT GULLIBLE. I go: NO SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victor e muito fofinho, se oferece pra ajudar em tudo nas tarefas de casa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Inflating assets to win a newspaper is not illegal...” No, but it makes you sound petty AF. I love that little jab.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OklahomaPatrio1 @TammieCroft @unbrokeMs1 @SafiMaasai @BlueTsuni @Tonia8675309 @zazzybritches @HondoResists… https://t.co/wjtgillrDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindalu827 @CherylArgenzia2 If you don’t think the Devil is roaming free, think again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady bo$$💰🌟 . Leggings: @ultracoractive Top: @Alo_Yoga  Shoes: vans  . @ Equinox East 63rd Street https://t.co/dy8n0rWLSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹 . 📷 @can_share . EOS Digital Rebel XS f/5.6 | 1/400 | 280.00mm | ISO400 . #RawPhotographers #mylife… https://t.co/aX8nDLy683]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kameron with the win! Russell High School eSports team celebrates with him! Game night #4! #latenightatrhs… https://t.co/UNtD3qWbOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rollin up to work with one eyelash on and hungover asf, no fucks given on my behalf today😂 I just wanna stay in bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crew Carwash is hiring in #Indianapolis, IN! Click the link in our bio to apply: Night Time Clean-Up #FacilitiesMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleri__ Like it's an a b conversation 🙄😂 I even understood what you meant lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dankennedy_nu This declaration is testing the limits of executive power, which isn't the case with legislation. Al… https://t.co/5Ku5zZQimD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snapcrackl_POPS @bsegodnia @TwitterNYC I can't believe I never told you! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl payed her friend back for her mg and got blocked my ex sis same with me demi never payed back than she used… https://t.co/t514MMjZ64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met a lovely 13 y/o girl last night who declared "I'm never getting married or having kids" and with my husband RIG… https://t.co/kCsfnN5xt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[In dire need of coffee.   #nolisafilter ☕⚡ @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/QgAq9AxwYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[just got a call from doggy daycare because Joey got bit this morning and needs a bath. he's dirty from blood. Excus… https://t.co/1ww55xD0lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[28... 📸 studio901__  #valentinesbaby @ Los Angeles Fashion District https://t.co/owIFJKLVeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP KILLING OUR BABIES!!! STOP INFANTICIDE!!!  DEFUND PLANNED PARENTHOOD!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Patriots must stick together!  More of us than the ones who want to see our Country become a shithole!  Anyone who… https://t.co/d0JGCKbMXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some cool ship art I took pictures of at the Channel Islands Maritime Museum https://t.co/Wfcmsf3W9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the480club @TGIFridays @WaffleHouse @MontVillageMD We were just talking about SWR the other night. Place was so good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🚘 Cedarwood Road #U2 📸 #myphotography em Miami, Florida https://t.co/oul05CaDZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎀💖What I Got For Valentine's Day Haul 2019!💖🎀 ✨February 2019✨ AlyssaMarieDeMeoTV  https://t.co/EGbGkUuK6e  💖Februar… https://t.co/CjAHKyt7KN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heather_desorbo @TrippLite Congratulations to you and your students ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally the first thing I’m doing when I go back to miami is getting a chicken tender pub sub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at our happy place! Wish you were here... 💚   #LakeLife #LakeChatuge #vacation #mountains #nc #georgia… https://t.co/t4jTubqPrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_lilRanga @zanzibubz @_butterflyjessi @GamerTakes Kind of funny to think they complained about it to commemorat… https://t.co/4f17iEwtWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyLennarLemon #RealEstate #ClearEnough4u #Lennar #LennarMultifamily #Realtor #LennarBayArea #ILoveLennar… https://t.co/I7y2IvbOsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zzyzyvasmay All of us, you know, lifers...do need to take a stand, as it were, and not go along with this.  Do not… https://t.co/WsbhPy5EJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[let’s go get away  .  . . #seattlewashington #travel #20thbirthday @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/4nkauayJEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ContingencyFee @HowardSchultz Me too. I wonder if their store revenues are down since he starting running. I used… https://t.co/HwkynownKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 Rise &amp; shine. It’s 8 am here in New York. 🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼 https://t.co/GHoRwcZWVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m learning how to turn around All the voices in my head I think I found my #favoritesound #AMusic #saturdaze… https://t.co/J5aOex164U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow on #SuperstitionMountain #Arizona on 2/22/19 https://t.co/fN76HX1K0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not surprised that RH likes a character with heart and imagination. ❤️📚Thanks for sharing. #HeartGreatBook #QAE… https://t.co/PTKZTdhTPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gopoundsand1234 @ctanner3 @jonz970 @ImpotentR @Melisa94361674. Following all &amp; RT'd!🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[so this is what two full days and two full nights of no sleep looks/feels like. oof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Fish Frys! 🐠Interactive map: Find a fish fry near you https://t.co/2O482voIL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot road warriors you did your body good today, we did both 😁🏃‍♀️#addisonroadwarriors]]></document><document><![CDATA[#notetakinggoals When your notes are so pretty the teacher posts them to Instagram. @ La FeriaHigh School https://t.co/XQLHnhhPTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kassidy literally puts up with me drunk me more than anyone she deserves an award]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houstonusa6 @stripedbanana3 No one knows if she is alive or dead. If she cannot or does not perform her duties as… https://t.co/KNyFTCCdhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Rexy! #nightatthemuseum #besnstillermovies #travel #movieslocation #newyorkcity #nyc #nyctravels #travelgram… https://t.co/Y3Pz1VAbIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steph8469133320 @ponytail122 @realDonaldTrump IT’S  FELONY  FRIDAY !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 24, waking up full of energy...watch out world.  #SundayFunday #AlmostOne #MommysBaby @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/5lba6fSxLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherrilizabiff @YNB And they feel the need to reason their way out of racism because they’d rather it not exist bu… https://t.co/AKc1tnW0Yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[there was a “fight” at the park across the school today &amp; someone started pouring hot cheetos on the girls 😂😂😂😭 https://t.co/YgYuoUIWld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TizzyisTizzy @abitchingwitch @AOC Yeah that has nothing to do with her error.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes us feel guilty and complicit in the artist’s terrible behavior, while also feeling stupid at having the wo… https://t.co/AGzsX9e3Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izenku @tenaprelec @Vijesti_ba Thanks for the clarification. If comparing to the EU, its easier money in that ther… https://t.co/Y8WLNOCs4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Avila46170601 @macabeso @barbara_lopez21 Exacto, por eso no quité esa parte del tweet. Ahí vemos reflejado el impa… https://t.co/Zo5oi21uyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard about this last week.  Crazy. I hope there trying to find the person doing this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fsnorth @Twins I didn't see @toriihunter48 listed. I love his playful style.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a stressful dream about a dance competition last night, but not about actual dancing (which is a REAL TERRIBLE… https://t.co/vfFilymi5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garth Brooks is the best performer ALIVE!!! Such an amazing experience! 😍🎶 #STL @ The Dome at America's Center https://t.co/qMym89lLmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @gabryluce @GizellaGerics1 @roberta_lanzoni @mich_onelove @Jose93571656 @consuiglesias… https://t.co/hy9vB1HNRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND I’m sure Atlanta would be the first state with more black owned dispensaries than any other state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#culinarycontest #secondplace 🏅🏅#hummuschipotle #shrimp #cod #friedveggies https://t.co/TqvNlVTr1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Omaha poses a few driving challenges - from geysers to car-eating potholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRamiMalek Congratulations Rami! So excited you won! You’re fans love you 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroFdezW Rendiciòn de cuenta de obras desde el 2012 hasta el 2018]]></document></documents></author>