<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JENisJUICY @hgtv @CastleHouseJT It’s a work in progress. More pics of @CastleHouseJT on @instagram (at) TheCastleH… https://t.co/BTkNrKRKoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCCoach910 Relationships inside that locker room that will literally stay with you for life. 25 years later, I sti… https://t.co/tgKB3Wl1Ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s keep it real for the lifters on Valentines Day!  “Dinner date? No time for that..” #ValentinesDayWeLift @ Uni… https://t.co/hRv1a1sJjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillGrayGC You look like you're old enough to remember second string football players didn't play until the fourth… https://t.co/jKIbaf93ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15thRegionZone And the coach who won the first? Hillard Howard. #OldGuyInfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caruddy @SallyAlbright @YvonneMullet @soith_feargach @kristheywood Are you even sure what your point IS anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Come to Haywood county nc check out North Carolina laws crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing fellow Cyclones in LA! Proud @IowaStateU @ISUSOE Alumnus! #NASPA19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SzewczykKathy @GabriellaR613 @JamesBr68146064 The @KamalaHarris way! To the top!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer I remember when people tried to tell me Flacco was better than Ryan. https://t.co/MzrubRTnCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Panthers and NFL head into free agency this afternoon. @JourdanRodrigue looks at what fans could expect from Ca… https://t.co/uaBYdzmhmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come eat at Freddy’s tonight in Norman and support the @alzoklahoma. #ENDALZ https://t.co/EW5qhKA5ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elwafflesss Ya quisieran los gayados tener esa afición en todas las ciudades del mundo mundial 😛😛😛, pero no al con… https://t.co/73h0lR9Z6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Massive pollution problems makes Russia vulnerable. Pollution is a security threat worldwide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HoLA (@ Los Angeles International Airport - @flylaxairport in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/tH4HjoRodz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated SWAC bracket with quarterfinal game times and streaming (no word on whether Texas Southern will have a stre… https://t.co/usPAizJfE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabino_Iglesias Bad day for chargers. This morning, I experienced the silver connector separating entirely from the cord. That was new.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i was tom brady’s son atleast i would get a kiss goodnight every tonigut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its cold AF, but we’re here anyway talking BTC at the MIT Bitcoin Expo #bitcoin #mitbitcoinexpo https://t.co/yQLdn16JEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surfcity64 Chargers have to rebrand themselves and downtown was plausible but again money and SDSU had a big part of the move]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Markomaralaw Sir, Forgive him...for he is an idiot and will be old news by next week. I think he is down in Hollyw… https://t.co/AnWK2FBY6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rod007Slick @ravensnook @placardabuse @NYCMayor It’s a state gov’t car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccgrime @_Alberto_Nunez_ Also don’t forget that they finished 1st in NL for 6 straight years w/o a WS. 🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/EC4P4V5ehE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from themercedesbt  -  Spent the morning with some epic writers  @BTF_Collective Harlem Writers Work Group… https://t.co/0Ua6Trwzbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good sequin clutch?! Available now in my Etsy Shop! https://t.co/1iviAflmhD  @etsy @EtsySuccess https://t.co/EdPclTrynN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grambear5 2). But I also think that a good compromise could be having other bits of info: Plaques and historical m… https://t.co/gEmR98JKiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandaorson Have to promote, it definitely doesn’t just happen. There’s some FB groups for buying/selling domains… https://t.co/NLd889E1iA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They contend that you cannot legislate morals. But while it may be true that morality can not be legislated, behav… https://t.co/bkVvIGuXce]]></document><document><![CDATA[“M’lady...we humbly submit our sole wish that the earth NOT be ravaged and sown with salt for future generations.”… https://t.co/RjNoGYAgnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see a pic of @TheLanceTaylor tv room! 6 TVs sounds like a dream! @JOXRoundtable @jimdunaway @RyanBrownWJOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning!  I am guilty of this. I stayed up watching Papillion on TV and didn't realize how late it was.  Prett… https://t.co/oZGz5SYsI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor @DLoesch Great! I hadn't quite thought of it that way! But accurate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tia_goat All I saw was a great player getting a minus defender to bite on a shot fake and making him pay 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[main reason for Brexit. In the United States the federal government never tells a state what it can spend or how mu… https://t.co/31gPo29S8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kino_x3 Nah because caring for someone can be shown in different ways the same for loving someone. Flowers may not… https://t.co/5MJgLIciBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoxHunter @TTremendous350 Y’all forgetting the classics like Stricken and Indestructible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palomaa12664363 is the best person I’ve ever met but she has the worst twitter handle ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[To say your sole focus on decreasing the impact of #PFAS is drinking water is blatantly short sighted. Animals bioc… https://t.co/GY9VJVMT1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight we won 2 awards for our branding efforts and I’m really proud of all of our hard work, and how I’m a part of a team like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing helps @CB_Icicle_Invit athletes recover faster than a bottle of @OakhurstDairy chocolate milk from our spon… https://t.co/FI38wW8r1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azcsports @kyrstensinema @jeffmetcalfe You go girl. Congratulations!!! Proud to have you represent me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkidunn7798 @Chloes_HoneyPot Definitely beautiful! The both of you defiantly are! The two of you! Look like you… https://t.co/4hYlCe5S3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryRootz Y’all care more about faux locs in the natural community than actual locs]]></document><document><![CDATA[And... the season’s over. Nope. Don’t need pitching. Don’t need Bumgarner, don’t need Cole, didn’t need Verlander,… https://t.co/GBbeStNw0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I toke 1 day rest from the Temp Agency. Curating now @SoundCloud tracks, thanking you all for ❤ the support.… https://t.co/kRJvBzLPhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that puts a damper on my proposed trip for next Fall🙃 If we go up then sure I get it, but not if we are stuck… https://t.co/xu3fAURnC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: USC's Bennie Boatwright mostly delivers, but not at end against UCLA: Bennie Boatwright’s senior s… https://t.co/LtFryW9s4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisdanbell I’m currently looking at flights, my heart is racing, omg ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroMtzMed Pues no seria un regalo,es dinero que le ha robado al pueblo Méxicano con su pinche servicio telef… https://t.co/rSuDNzjVRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drmiller166 @oalejandro69 @RapSheet @NFLTotalAccess put it this way: let's say he did leave the A's to enter the d… https://t.co/ttPLqsISHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We didn’t do anything to deserve Lin, and yet here he is existing. God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, I wanted to fucking cry with this song @trippieredd  @xxxtentacion https://t.co/gzyymUBbKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/ukMTELRdNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #BuffySlayDay, everyone. That show is so deeply bound up in my experience of grad school (we had watch partie… https://t.co/34xwxt6ucg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevinhaime Burned and sold as cheap - that won’t go away anytime soon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just played against a kid in SND that had a seeker, body armor, a spitfire, and a flashlight shotty. What a fun experience Treyarch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKarol @ElizabethDrewOH Could be similar to when Teddy Kennedy sat out Watergate and wasn’t on the Senate select committee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood One of the few single hits that breached the unwritten 3 min. or less FM rule.Joined other classics s… https://t.co/mGekR2cmtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DionBrazill Can’t compare the in two different categories in my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think @DukeMBB misses #ZionWilliamson? Favored by 26 points -- 26! -- #BlueDevils hang on to edge @DemonDeacons in… https://t.co/CN88Ql0WI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Man with knife at Oakland airport wanted to kill officer, police say - San Francisco Chronicle: Ma… https://t.co/3MYCULecgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s not necessary but so welcome to hear from the customers that you’re doing a good job running a cool bar a… https://t.co/woPQC5oIb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet the stat guys there in Houston have just given a bunch of extra assists just like they did for Stock 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know that this guy is a top PG in our league than you’re just arrogant]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be so cool if Vietnam has a law against orange skin. Life sentence .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost So we’re calling criticism of an apartheid state anti-semitism now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise this morning. @ Pleasantville, New Jersey https://t.co/pRTU2qnpK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[He looks so awkward as he waits for the applause. “Please...somebody clap or he won’t let me back into the White Ho… https://t.co/qCQHmtATiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you keep Ss focused and engaged in lengthy informational writing in Science? Make it authentic with Google S… https://t.co/xxebUpCTY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysbookman You are and always have been a race baiting idiot. Now your party’s mask of anti-Semitic is coming off. You dipshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Up next for the Ducks: Friday vs. Montreal: When: 7 p.m. On the air: TV: FS West; Radio: 830. Upda… https://t.co/t9eK9SJyNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @SenatorCollins nothing You do will make a difference for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarsonDaly  Carson you need either a sharper razor or a new electric shaver! Looks like your sporting a Hitler stash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kurt_Kitayama @TaylorMadeGolf @adidasGolf @WeAreSBX @Kitayama11 @realjcdeacon Way to go dude!! 👊👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! #TheEnemyWith @nbcenemywithin by @enemywriters premiers on @NBCUniversal ! Don’t miss it 9PM EST! https://t.co/91UmXSs9Ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) why does he look like a 7 year old pouting? 2) that’s not Melania...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett I know, right? I knew you were lying from the beginning. Now you’re going to prison. Damn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctsuj just another example how the rich exploit the poor in a fair wage senario.  Would he have done this in the s… https://t.co/qbNjfSp14d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me in congratulating @ProfJonesMusic on his offer letter!  You deserve it, Jeremy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also been talking to this really cute girl who I'm finally hanging out with tomorrow! Stoked !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Springfield, MA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/yYVnqP1wlZ #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN Rep Omar your the problem not the man who was being asked questions by you. You people are all the same… https://t.co/zIklJ6h8Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billholtzclaw Tax on Food, a tax on gas that will continue to go up indefinitely, state income tax, property tax o… https://t.co/6yfuItki8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patience. . .   More Photos Here:  https://t.co/PdRIivF8cT https://t.co/U5Vblv13YS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevCumming @Nightwyn @David56798816 @TheFilmShredder @skipwiley11 @DTMoszkowicz @RepDanCrenshaw You’re posting a… https://t.co/iJgyFkSM71]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m playing at @Article24boston this Friday.  Hope to see you there!! @ Article 24 https://t.co/STxvknA8U0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars people still don’t get it, make it quick! Be organized damn it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone stop what they are doing and go check out @paigevanzant Instagram story. You're welcome in advance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier well I think all these people should just do the world a favor and drink draino]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powder puff is here. Pick up registration forms in AP office. Form and money is due Wednesday at lunch! First come,… https://t.co/LpjZf3WawT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does it make sense to kill local economies to help oil companies profit while we still give these oil companies inc… https://t.co/4KOcsd2nmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh for the love of God. Hey @MarkMeadows? Do you think that was a tad racist?  I was hoping you would blow an arter… https://t.co/BrtXg15Q6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SageAdviceDnD in the necromancy school when it says “when you kill 1 or more creatures” referring to the Grim Harv… https://t.co/oarrduDipa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MysticaIgirl_ I had mine in Taco Bell 🛎...after tearing up those quesadillas...lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec Once Trump sets this precedent, think of all the glorious work li… https://t.co/iuRvDOc3qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼🥁🎹Mashup📻!🤠 Joseefus , the #hillbilly #banjo player joins the California Raisin 🏖 🍇for some #rootintootin fun!… https://t.co/V6eKEZIK6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyKHLiu more playing time? he was sucking wind after 5min when he was on the Warriors, did he want to have an as… https://t.co/H6ptyn0dsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The spirit of lack will trick you into believing that the success of others reflects failure in yourself when the t… https://t.co/qGUfbRqYmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many social media peeps commenting on my diet lately and saying it should be more balanced. I eat deer, fish, pi… https://t.co/RSXqFF5BZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryHelmerWCPO I stood in it for two hours at FCC practice. BRUTAL!!!!!]]></document></documents></author>