<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Life is good. #furnieces #Fenway #Panama #dogsofinstagram @ Hoover, Alabama https://t.co/U0aKLknSZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter and I are registered! Very excited to attend this event with her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ry! We are so proud of who you are and all you do! Keep working hard! https://t.co/L50l3hhgKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/GCbPkqUG8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amahnke I hate trolls. I love what you do. But I don’t have my face on twitter cause of creepy people. Hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t even get to spend time with my baby girl at all yesterday. She slept from the time I picked her up at 8 un… https://t.co/eO7JyyrHnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denouncing white supremacy is exhausting, but I can’t imagine how exhausting it must be to actually spend that much… https://t.co/pIUtzj59E2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to make a very beautiful life for myself no matter what it takes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really sure if you can tell how excited I was to meet the cartoon characters that I grew up with😂😝 • • • •… https://t.co/xmcL6R7hWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “play some Frank Ocean” My friend: “I mean that’s pretty sad but ok”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, trying to watch and actually understand Love Island: https://t.co/ndb97gfsQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[For fifteen years this man has shown me nothing but kindness and love. Thank you Mark Sheldon for the photo. https://t.co/rkvZ0xGTP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s late but I hope everyone is living their best life and loving themselves💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennieGThompson Obama cages 2014 ! SAME Photos REPOSTED DATE CHANGED TO POTUS TRUMP TERM! https://t.co/K5QGAOCQxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[PMI LEADERSHIP INSTITUTE REGION MEETING DAY 1 Reporting live at Omni Hotel Atlanta venue of the PMI Regional 3 day… https://t.co/JGVwr7BbHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was really about to go to sleep and have a normal ass day tomorrow but now it’s gonna literally revolve around Gaga huh 🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tallahassee Mayor John Daily welcoming delegates to the AGA Tallahassee Chapter opening Day. @uga_serves @CVIOG_FMP… https://t.co/bkUn2Z3ZsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s CRAZY I used to let a boy track my location and tell me who I could be friends with lmao, character development is beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@better_delhincr @Jungle_View @ajitsinghpundir @MengiKuldip @PNRATHOD1 @nirajntsh @AmreshwarS @25rubybaruah… https://t.co/rjjsWkRjol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also Owen and Betty’s parents don’t seem to give a damn about Betty. Only Amelia does. What’s wrong with them? #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrgasmsAreUs @JNasty3x @Baby_BreezyXXX Damn I need that shit in my life right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJSenatorBooker your upset about Manafore sentencing? We the people are upset Hillary Clinton and Barrack Obama haven't been sentenced]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miren lo que es tendencia. Ese 4% para la educaciòn no està dando resultado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie’s dad just shows up in Portugal... #TheBachelor https://t.co/4Cp2dv9ggz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JNeuroscience interns: for your entertainment. (see? musicians have cat fetishes too!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[God took some people out of my life and replaced them with some pretty awesome human beings. He Amazes me every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to #win a #Step2 WonderBall Fun House for this week's #FanFriday #Giveaway!  https://t.co/37hbwp6Pql /]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katehopeday Of course you did. Me too. Sometimes I would play Eliot reading that poem and the @GratefulDead 's ‘ Dark Star' simultaneously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toronto Maple Leafs vs. Chicago Blackhawks - Scotiabank Arena Wed, Mar 13, 2019 https://t.co/PRO9b1qDjJ #TicketmasterCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young people?  What about older people who have lived here their entire life and can no longer afford it. That’s De… https://t.co/TT5RfCUkop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well,  by 1145  we had better shit to do. Btw-still waiting for the men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the #disney photogs capture the shot you didn't know you needed. . . #wdw #disneyworld #waltdisneyworld… https://t.co/mvXMO1Vjez]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story came from my curiosity as a new Austin resident. All these activations downtown come and go so fast, so… https://t.co/tdhO46j8vO]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night at the bar at exactly midnight the DJ started playing man, I feel like a woman by Shania Twain, happy in… https://t.co/h36iD5x4Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adnazteca @Jcchavez115 @regia_fer Hola Sr. Julio mi campeón favorito por favor dígame cómo puedo hablar con usted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiMorales2 @realDonaldTrump Stop with that crap! The kids are well taken care of and coyote ‘s bring them in to… https://t.co/0J287s23df]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanmoore @marklevinshow It’s sheeple like you, who believe this stuff and react this way, who help the spread of #FakeNews hysteria.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to buy, sell or lease? Let’s talk about it! Check out my site and give me a shout! #lovewhereyoulive… https://t.co/EEJ7QFygzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to write and record an entire #podcast about how fucked Transformers: Beast Wars was and how I’ll never be the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RenInTahoe @FOXNashville That’s exactly why you extend GRACE to people who act crazy on the road! You never know w… https://t.co/PFLUwcGtWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Segar Final Tour.  Spring Break 2019.    Thanks Boo! @ Ford Center at the Star https://t.co/gXHGcrPJSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futpicante @manoloml1973 @amarchesin1 @ClubAmerica Que si se proponen son campeones jajajajaja pregúntenle a Morelia 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pulmon_de_Susan y dímelo de frente, gordo e mierda” suizo te crees huevón! Se quiso pasar la fila y le reclame y es ahí donde me insultó]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OluyomiOjo @seunonigbinde Yup don’t be mad the next time he says he fit cut Africans 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WomeninPRcanada we would love to have you join our event for #IWD2019 Help us run, walk and work together for equa… https://t.co/NjdzoHmxWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you want - I’ll get it for you, whatever makes you happy , I’m happy 🔐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Colleen Sheehan asked me to do a joint project with her. I am screaming. Holy cow. So exciting!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEG DAY!! #ithurtssogood #ifeelallmybuttmuscles #workoutbuddies @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/pPPbli84W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annahaddenn I’m about to 😂 I feel sorry for girls who think they’re too good for Walmart shit bc I’m about to save… https://t.co/APgkuMAoQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo hoo!! Congratulations, Jayson!! 💙🐻🏀 @BJUBruins @BJUBruinsMBB  https://t.co/RxgpO60ESp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering GrandMother Josephine after the #greatlakewaterwalk. A kind and warm soul, a woman on a mission. May yo… https://t.co/GFGSjWXEa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevens Brody Stevens was a series that made me want to pull my hair out. And I couldn’t get enough of it! 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be sleeping but God’s love is pounding on my heart so hard I can’t close my eyes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: calls doctor about back   doctor: you might have the flu you should go get checked   me: *feels fine*  manager:… https://t.co/7dnXaCsTHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at T-Mobile &amp; BlackBerry @ College of DuPage (SRC/SCC Foyer) in Glen Ellyn, IL https://t.co/GdELXYlQG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuilliamsDeann @MrsSladeLMS @JDSterba It won the Pulitzer and he went to Bowling Green. So it’s a win-win. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenluluthepug Guess you need to try harder unless poppy know the look and is just ignoring you all together Lulu… https://t.co/DGLjPUaZsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the dog resort I’ve sent Svenska to doesn’t send me pictures while I’m gone, do I get a refund?? I am INCENSED,… https://t.co/lD9lR7iaTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenevilletwin It sounds silly but lay on your back on your bed, with your shoulders on the edge and your head han… https://t.co/vAm24YRGQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If women had a dollar for everytime we are mansplained by someone who doesn’t even have a degree in our field the g… https://t.co/vuLnQz9lrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really don’t get the point of posting “dhmu” on your story..? like, okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malawi Boy Who Saved His Village From Famine is at the Center of New Netflix Film https://t.co/mhIhlFiLrj #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Craziest thing walking though a mall in Billings Montana and seeing your best friend from 3rd grade out of nowhere 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlishaGrauso As someone who didn’t grow up with money, I don’t think I could spend it on anything frivolous at all… https://t.co/JCBffI8jUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto x #QueNoTeFalleElCorazon  con  @AlexisMusicMX para que ingrese en  el #TopPacifico @SAPSGrupero… https://t.co/vAry3rQRi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried taking a pic of the patchy fog and this car drove by and created this panoramic fail 👍 https://t.co/sKmdpN5ztx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bettiebloodshed I genuinely hope u feel better bc ur wonderful and so beautiful and creative 💖💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyFavMurder @KarenKilgariff @GHardstark listening to icebreaker episode again screaming they do make an American c… https://t.co/reu2apAbbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as expected:  Our “free thinkers” thinking &amp; spewing their garbage freely.   #GraspingAtPaperStraws… https://t.co/zzaBeAI2iI]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it fair that some people actually get to live here and I have to go back to PA or Germany. Why can’t I just stay here. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandMaidensLamp Just purchased the Kindle version.  I have one book I self-published.  Here’s the link https://t.co/CsR7DmBPQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been waiting for this movie for so long but I was not expecting the way this movie made me feel. It was amaz… https://t.co/4iYzQWHTSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfie’s attempt to gain attention and play in the water with the #canadagoose at #riparianpreserve in #gilbertaz… https://t.co/Pp1anE6n4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: @AACOPD are looking for 17-year old Jamari Hammond. He's wanted for attempted murder among other charges… https://t.co/PwgYnfubox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC CHINA - THAT'S YOUR TICKET !!!  Now go it in the corner until you can behave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpanbergerVA07 @WhitfordBradley This is always the plan 4 the #GOP. Obstruct so they can turn around and say Dems… https://t.co/P0WNNM0usP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed_by_design @LindseyOwn @TheMoth These folks were @sxswedu #dtk12chat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some bitches may have tried to clip my wings/cut my legs off.  We're cool though😉 They were just quizzing me😁❤… https://t.co/RJqF97hZL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neylandmafia Respect Mike Young.  He always has a team that comes to play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did not enjoy the fence scene in the bachelor as much as I thought I would 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Owners of 400-year-old bonsai trees ask thieves to make sure the trees are getting watered  https://t.co/DoyJ5jsFBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[New episode of #HurricaneHope is up NOW! Take a listen n let me know if there’s any topic you’d like to hear me tal… https://t.co/blUP7R72oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I fear I don’t have what it takes for my desired career path, but I want it so baaaad :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PdxPatriot1 @MagniFieri @RandPaul Never trusted him, this is the lamest excuse I have heard yet. Wished I could tr… https://t.co/L5J8fTcuLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bleach &amp; botox has gone to her brain. Botox is a poison injected to the face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sa wakas makakanood ako ng live! Watch din kayo here https://t.co/xLdQzCogy0 #BOYBANDPHXPromDate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bvanhool Don't let his poor tortured body dir in vain.....Pass Tommies Law...in every state. RIP sweet boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When its been a long day already and it’s only 6:30am 😴🙄 #CanIGoBackToBedYet]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you’re worried about your kids, you’re not going to do a good job” #Childcare4All @PattyMurray https://t.co/UaxDcr8ikM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win A Trip to Our @iHeartRadio Music Festival Daytime Stage! Enter for your chance to win a trip for two to our iHe… https://t.co/btpQ6mvqpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s is over bitches. NYC, 2.25.19 @ New York, New York https://t.co/T7oVjZk99L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swilkinsonbc I will vote Dem, but I've been disappointed by Dem candidates I DID like (Warren). I'm turned off by… https://t.co/bDRRNTUph1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanSowards I literally just got 3 in a row. All from my home area code. So annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[KJV Verse of the Day for Saturday, February 23, 2019.  "For the law was given by Moses, but grace and truth came by… https://t.co/Y0eIe1kTRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rschooley Or the one where the paranoid, hate-filled bigot shrinks down to Two Feet Tall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrannanJulia working &amp; reading doesn't mix when one wants 2 figure out what happens to Sarah &amp; Lucy.  Dag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AnaheimDucksGoooaaalll #UncleRicoAgain #NHLDucks up 7-2 #nothatisnotatypo #LetsGoDucks #MTLvsANA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me think of the time I walked into the bathroom in elementary school and seen a turd that looked like it… https://t.co/CjLqIfJkY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was so much fun to watch the growth of @JaspersMBB this season. I’m incredibly impressed by the job… https://t.co/7lnExg01Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago today I watched families fall apart and a community mourn the loss of their 17 friends. 2018 will fore… https://t.co/SrvKW484vq]]></document></documents></author>