<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[En el grupo de whats de vecinos las mismas mujeres satanizaron el hecho de que la mujer trabaje y no se dedique a t… https://t.co/YOq1STEpBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my son and my little brother enjoying some sushi @ Hello Sushi https://t.co/i7n9cNlejM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump - what's your problem? Lying about your height on your health records. How small can you be! Note… https://t.co/Uyy5YOIA4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, he admitted to lying for a liar. Pretty screwed up. #DrainTheSwamp the #ShipofFools aka @GOP needs to fl… https://t.co/2MCwZgi1IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch LIVE as activists stage a protest on Capitol Hill demanding Trump's impeachment and Rep. Rashida Tlaib announ… https://t.co/5tzQ6o3AAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[All locked up, rolling along! (@ Oregon Weigh Station in Huntington, OR) https://t.co/xYDUOUqO6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THilalMD What about fresh fruit/vegetables/meat? Do they cost the same from Walmart to Walmart?   This is indicati… https://t.co/ZWqmGQsjwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all, so I don’t have that many friends into what I’m into but if someone tryna come thru w me lmk I’ll get you a… https://t.co/ZnYZT8CwxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to Receive an offer from Utah State University!!⚪️🔵@CoreyFlagg5 @JoeCarroll_25 @coachgcross @CoachJP3… https://t.co/GyaptoMH8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katalin_pota They say everyone has their price. @chrislhayes is no exception. Anyone that follows #inners conversa… https://t.co/mnh9hu8yn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvin81156899 @JoniMullock @davematt88 @PressSec @realDonaldTrump Pathetic reasoning from a complete asshole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyPascall They need to look at Tampa bay and say to themselves “what do we need to do to be as good as they are?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because I'm a fat kid that like to do fat kid things. @ MTO Café https://t.co/b578WrN7tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took everything I had not to touch it; The security guy knew it too..😈 Call can’t wait to show the kids… https://t.co/8OzHguS7Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I’ll never let a Title get to my head never forget where you came from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to an event this morning that advertises a, “significant brunch.” Me: https://t.co/CC9pF2dfSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder where this leaves #McGregor in terms of visas for future fights  #mcgregorarrested]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful Valentines Day! @ Parm Upper West Side https://t.co/OHkyL89qpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoffRBennett @NBCNews @WSJ Let me see if I got this right - the most popular characteristics in a President: a ma… https://t.co/lSlRqQFoLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all you assholes who are asking who Olivia Colman is, turn off the Oscars and go watch Peep Show, Broadchurch,… https://t.co/coiU96DBI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eminence Hill screen grab of the moment Quincy is informed that the restaurant will not validate his parking.… https://t.co/jHrRuGb3Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acrossunvrs I loved ASIB but it was SOO over the top. Almost every scene someone was having a mental breakdown and… https://t.co/MyS0gEe9UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarubioCinthia @noroestemx @QuirinoOC No entiendo que tiene que ver si lo he vivido o no, me manifesté totalmente solidario. 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of your political affiliation, this is great news for the city of Milwaukee and the state as a whole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gktrocks This is actually Griffin's long term career plan: 😜😜🤣🤣 (In all seriousness, I love a good one man band ac… https://t.co/xmGIPQIjL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Baystate Health? We're hiring in #Westfield, MA! Click for details: https://t.co/1fD6LIqspV #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluppfisk @NYCNavid @Sophiecat_luo @joshrogin @DavidNakamura Well here in the US: https://t.co/HQkxIPT0hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStarVarsity White our the gym! #OneMore #PlainsmenHoops @montereyhs @MontereyHoops @pchristy11 @806hssc… https://t.co/E0BvRBdeDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Steph... everyone in the building thought that was over. No one lights up an arena like him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s been kinda ass tbh. But at least I made 97 dollars in a days work🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ali_heston: Advocate, tinkerer, and designer - but her best quality is that she speaks up for her ideals, while re… https://t.co/34TjBsITO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A mi me gustaba mucho Janis Joplin, said my dad, reminiscing about the 1960s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rae woke up to nurse just now and as she was finishing up she stretched her whole body, put one arm in the air and… https://t.co/eheIXZw6wD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 291 gifts away from our goal of 1000 donors in 24 hours. Make a gift and invest in what matters to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinLea7 I never had money when I was in grade school. I had my sack lunch maybe milk money and came home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it 🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀🚀 straight games of 30 or more points for The Beard. @HoustonRockets #RunAsOne #MVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Car and SUV collide with serious injuries in the 1000 block of W. Galbraith Rd in Springfield Twp. @WLWT… https://t.co/AFuy4ANb6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spirit airlines wins in the best legroom competition..... @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/YePorQAuf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckythecyclist It just underscores the reality that the plan has nothing to do with sexual ethics or “faithfulnes… https://t.co/Gn8hnQmLKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeMOwens @ItsSamG @KayEmily2 This is exactly why I search everything on urban dictionary first to see if it’s saf… https://t.co/RKbUuvt23c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriminallyVu1ga Yeah honestly I stayed away from it because I figured unless it was literally by sex workers it wa… https://t.co/nyY0Ecebme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Philadelphia @Eagles Ron Jaworski receives Francis "Reds" Bagnall Award from @MaxwellFootball Club. https://t.co/yk2ZLvqHWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@putemupcdukes We got in a 310 mile ride to Andrews NC through the Mountains, the sun shine was amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Baker Truck Corral Restaurant in Baker City, OR https://t.co/UIxr62NK84]]></document><document><![CDATA[#F3 Day 210 - 8 at #ManU for a @abridges79 shoulder burning merkin fest in the chilly gloom. @F3RockHill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Beshara I am pretty confident in #NewYork we call what I see in the picture #Rats , and they actually are NOT… https://t.co/AqyVP0E81k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mosaic IPA by @CommunityBeerCo at @aacenter — https://t.co/HrUrTg87XN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's a sneak peek at Nintendo's future when Reggie Fils-Aime retires as President of @NintendoAmerica and… https://t.co/8d5Vh3VPRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[2110 McMillan Avenue / $559,000 / 3 Bed / 2 Full Baths / Craftsman / 2,090 Square Feet / East Dallas / Dallas ISD… https://t.co/MrnISPErdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once when we were at this water park a boy my age (12) kept following us... #comedy #giggle #smile #absurd https://t.co/h4Og9umWM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump And Jesus...don’t forget Jesus. Dude is modest, but give him props]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcamposss_ Bien pata porque luego piensan que uno fuma por el olor a cigarro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dad2136 @tallman_1_ @Rifleman4WVU @AllProAnalytics Haskins back up in NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive,,. Always.. Wondered..., What. @cher opinion,,, on,,. FURRIES⁉️,,. ❇️✅❇️ or?; 🚫❌🚫 https://t.co/SrMELKzgbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be a HUGE deal for Erie NFL fans. Would mean potentially when the Bills are on the road, we would still… https://t.co/bfBpOsf85S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Magic flower power  #supportlivemusic #supportyourscene #livemusic #gotoshows #lafayette #louisiana #divebar… https://t.co/HnLNwwMDSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late nights like this got me looking forward to breakfast in the morning after my 8AM cuz ya boy out here hungry af!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaswhitley @TrinityJoy Or if you have multiple sets you can keep adding to that. Maybe that’s why I’m slowly losing my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019-02-28: @monsterscruise #MORC #MORC2019 #MORCFamilia #Miami #FL #jamaica #labadeehaiti #2019Gig34 .… https://t.co/h87ZctHsXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFAN660 @WFANmornings @MikeFrancesa Is this the best NJ has to offer for sports betting? Good luck getting paid ou… https://t.co/f9zhH2kR8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MishyFishyWhoo Desk bartending... never thought of that! Would be so much easier on my feets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reinsdorf waiting for the right moment to snag Machado https://t.co/ye8uUSoNkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Potatoes au gratin or whatever your favorite preparation is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WisconsinPS just received my magnet today. Thank you! https://t.co/KoKJZwLgQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HellaSpring Update: @JoshPhegley just homered down the right field line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelSchilling @RuthHHopkins My amazing wife (Northern Cheyenne) is graduating medical school. Just wanted to share… https://t.co/rpJESsuDLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hasan Minhaj: I’m sorry I slept on you, but you’re like an Indian Richard Pryor, like the first of you’re kind, not… https://t.co/5tlJUmBpMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[An alleged sex act at this fast food restaurant - now police are investigating whether the same guy was involved in… https://t.co/yPQJkrKqv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farmnvol #stillhavemine #aintgonnabenopicture #thatsawesome ##bluejacketproud #ffaweek  #ffalumni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson In Italy for 2 weeks, FoxNews only US channel on. Daily w-out time corresponded w/your show. Was dum… https://t.co/0YgjADiCzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTLug0 || 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beau… https://t.co/D8ZZmcL9u7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hothambone Hey that’s awesome! Glad you had fun. Yeah, the bar team there has always been some of the best around.… https://t.co/vqW0E0eyvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our little mic tape cup is coming to life! #Xanadudes #XanaduPOV #DCPAXanadu @ Denver Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/bKEyyTfcaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @charliekirk11 I know. That’s why I wondered what the point of posting the high number of illegals apprehended was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KNayyeh Tomatoes from my garden make everything better. #BurgerIssues #TomatoToppers https://t.co/ydWip6fhnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[آجکل ریحام رمضان عرف ریحام خاں کی کوئی خبر نہیں آرہی سنا ہے ایک اور کتاب لکھ رہی ہیں جس کا عنوان ہے   ناچنے سے لیکر… https://t.co/cR8h5D2QEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get rolling to the Civic Center for tonight's 7:30 D1 regional girls championship between GlenOak and Eastlake North]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimKim Biscuits are bread. Flour is biscuits.  Rolls are dough. Dough is money. Money is evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@islandguy0307 @BretBaier We get the leaders we deserve. If the gop voter would simply tell Trump they will not sta… https://t.co/stUV8lOekx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d be the guy retweeting a bunch of animal videos, but if it’s amazing wildlife footage like this an… https://t.co/57jdmpUobE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iconic word/moment of the day: Charisminum by @plastiquetiara   We don't deserve you my queen. 🙇🏻‍♂️  #DragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing like sleeping 4 hours and then being wide awake all night. love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badatgaminggrl I think the environment looks really beautiful, but it’s going to take an adjustment to get to used clay chibi Link.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn_on_Games Talking about the whole ‘the senate gives all power to Emperor in exchange for promised safety/this… https://t.co/0CZKC72CQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDeptCT @StateDeptDSS @ForeignPressCtr Maybe he's in Algiers.  You might find him at the mall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Zander has a great #Valentine’s Day. #ZanderJames https://t.co/LJ6KtK8ssh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PVDDR @hylkyhopea @SaffronOlive To build rivalries and story lines to make the games interesting to watch. Think l… https://t.co/CQTWNr8EkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time to start getting in shape physically, mentally and spiritually is now!!!💯💪🏽🏃‍♀️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃🏽‍♂️🏃‍♀️  #carpediem… https://t.co/aXeedMOMmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donald2979 I am sure someone will come up with the proper rulings. I would think Natural Emergency would “trump” anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But we got way too much in common So what's the point in fighting? We got way too many problems if I'm being honest… https://t.co/9175O5k5kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Problem Gambling Skype Meeting this evening with seven people sharing with and supporting one another to furt… https://t.co/q36rHeas1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirmaEspn @vikingomartell Repetición de  mentiras. Parece que @kenneth_garay está buscando trabajo  con el vendedo… https://t.co/iBTUzd7hgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow Predictions for Tomorrow  MSP Airport-7.5 NWS Chanhassen-8.3 Duluth-10.1 St. Cloud- 4.7]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise here. Congrats to Jayson and the BJU program @tonywmiller @BruinsHoopCoach]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continued support by the GOP is the only thing keeping Trump in power. Remember this in 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to be half way done with getting ready for work, and instead I’m still on Twitter smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody in a corolla with a hole in the exhaust pipe just revd at me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze This lady is the gift that keeps giving.  Please Dear Lord let her run for POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeliciaRose But you deserve happiness or something close to it 🤷🏻‍♂️Something like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[DeWine Will Ask For Gas Tax Hike. Now the question is how much. Analysts are saying may need to double current 28¢… https://t.co/ogbpDjrTKh]]></document></documents></author>