<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu @RCDobbs Because he's the brother of Betsy De Vos. Neither one of them are too bright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first car died in the middle of nowhere in Ft Hancock TX.  I was driving from AZ to VA, getting ready to be stat… https://t.co/qCUmfOuc2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosieIsTired @BernieSanders I am a woman supporting Bernie for President 2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else miss the simple days of upside down crosses and galaxies and triangles???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Because I already want Season 4 of @OneDayAtATime. Rewatching Season 3 so @netflix can renew it for Season 4.… https://t.co/ncmE3oGnIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[funny how my @the_wing calendar gets me and my energy this month ⚡️ https://t.co/7zmqnNr0Ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence So sorry to hear this. Prayers for speedy and complete recovery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Yes to the real women who work hard, educate themselves, have a healthy self-esteem and don't sell themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t other bitches on here mind their own business and drink water let them be fuck man 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[bonjour je m'appelle Hazel, j'ai quinze ans, je vis à Lakewood dans l'Ohio avec ma mère et ma sœur]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a rare 16 yr. old that doesn't spout their parent's view, if they even know what politics mean. The brain does… https://t.co/cW6v3WYdOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericwbailey @marcysutton I can’t agree more! And I’m also stoked to discover two new typebuddies. :)  And along th… https://t.co/zkFjPhf8Tt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreyDeLisle "Hello. Thank you for calling our brand new customer service line. Please listen carefully as our options have changed."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this one may be the one. Take a tour of one of the houses 🏡 on our home buying list. https://t.co/tsjkRkENGO https://t.co/CEx1VChTvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @sharontuckerlps to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no review needed. I will challenge… https://t.co/wzuVtKoBWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget today is national discount candy and flowers day! Go save some poor roses from the trash and load up on Hershey kisses #Feb15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dshafik I literally am ashamed to admit how much I spent on that small amount of food. I only shop there for these… https://t.co/F4D2alSt5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started out the morning by letting a man know that he was about to miss the elevator, ended up being the head of co… https://t.co/yEoDhl5HXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm eating a left over chicken finger in the bathroom because this is what this job made of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day!  Here is to all the women who are making things happen in their own lives and out… https://t.co/fsTsSkscBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS MY SCHOOL BACK HOME OH my god 😂  The fact that they got Mr, Rhodewalt to do it is.... iconic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayCockerill @PuertoRicoOpen @GolfChannel Hey Kay ... wanna switch locations for the weekend? 😬 I have some articl… https://t.co/22qy2nL6Qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is afraid of MOMO like they were afraid of JESUS. MOMO was sent to us by GOD the LORD hath sent MOMO to us… https://t.co/hlXw9beEe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariade_lourdes @FedericoArreola @garcialcocer @CRE_Mexico @FelipeCalderon Él mismo lo aceptó. https://t.co/ke94lhbGpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #vinman #valentines box. #4thgrade #party #hockey #hockeyvalentines @ Paint Creek Trail https://t.co/Fydh4Lnryk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kokomen Spicy Chicken #Korean Ramyeon Noodles (꼬꼬면) with grilled adobo pork. 🍜  라면 #FoodGasm #FoodBlogger… https://t.co/m4PnTKvheF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, #SidneyPoitier! Rare, Early Glimpses of Sidney Poitier   https://t.co/Y5hdEzAZeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekillahBEE Whoo Chile use the hopper app it'll tell you when they're going back down]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're #praying on my #downfall  I'm Praying you get on your #feet  #wearenotthesame  #sd #sandiego @ San Diego, Ca… https://t.co/Ay6u03GjvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although #SageSummitUS in #SanDiego is over, #SageU is always available- access training and certifcations any time! https://t.co/CvwHd2QYyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my children meet or exceed their goals, I feel rewarded #LoveKohls +  🙌 + #sweepstakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookyBandit How much do you charge for a picture of multiple characters? Is there extra charges in order to make t… https://t.co/9XaCOlTIrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly PMSing because I was crying over some dumbass and now I’m squealing and screaming because of The Twilight Zone remake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viajamos hasta Atlanta para conocer a Ignacio Montoya quien estaba a punto de cumplir su sueño de convertirse en pi… https://t.co/Kakm6KbL2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is now almost 2 am and I can’t sleep...currently in my living room on here and IG liking alllll the pics from th… https://t.co/ETGNdg9spZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResistanceGold1 @ransomedpatriot @paulpuckett911 @WHurensohn @BarkinDavid @TrumpsAlways @debbz8 @dmon4ever… https://t.co/OF6GRTXDZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you following @TeachAPE 's daily tweets of book recommendations by African American writers?   Start! So many g… https://t.co/xa8uVRlRWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few years ago, on “The View,” Barbara Walters warns of the disease called, “The Shingles,” what’s the Shingles, y… https://t.co/fOClZ5XSOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[izzos has played two twenty one pilots songs in the 30 minutes i’ve been here. my New Favorite Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a tourist in your own town 📸 Any chance I get, I'm planning my next adventure. That could be anything from a chi… https://t.co/wGgzT8gEzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the many cool things about https://t.co/YHNlqEXe6V, is each month, Halloween Corner and Christmas Corner, al… https://t.co/NcZVL8xhGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s my night night off. Can’t sleep anyway. Got a kicked up sleep schedule. Always have!!:);) https://t.co/qVCj2oaPIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsDarciLynne @AGT @nbc You are absolutely an extremely talented and beautiful young lady! God bless!! 😊❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[We bought season tickets two years ago in anticipation of tonight. Wasn't sure if it could live up to the hype. It… https://t.co/8MOxR0Ll5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re the liar and the truth will come out you’re horrible and you will be gone soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may feel it, But I also need to be able to accept it logically. I need to challenge and defend myself internally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironically, this the first Valentine’s Day I’m not single and it is the first Valentine’s Day I don’t have a valentine 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kisseso3 I AM CONTROLLING THE NARRATIVE BC IT IS MY OWN DAMN NARRATIVE 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my girl @GinaIsber !!!!!! can’t wait for this weekend, ily💖🤪🤟🏽 https://t.co/35hnWGIbX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marjani_Mj: one time my sim died from laughing to hard. It was his little girl’s birthday party and all of a sudde… https://t.co/1DPHYQtt3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPhamK @janellecj @KishaKBird Oh I should also mention I left at 10am today 😕😕. But I hope you guys have a great trip!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day snuggles with my favorite 4 legged animal!!! ❄️🐶❤️ #snowday #furbaby #snuggles @ Island Heights, New Jersey https://t.co/9OdJRxEJJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn how weird, awkward, and random I am by purchasing my Diva Diary from Highspots. Thank @NINaylor for always br… https://t.co/OJwcKMQdql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gayle King watching R Kelly dig his grave deeper and deeper throughout this interview: #rkellyinterview https://t.co/ufGNspqFyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a theatrical whiplash. First, @MyFairLadyBway with a flawless, joyful @LauraBenanti. We were front row ce… https://t.co/tL2s6WDcAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trudeau Apologizes For Canada's Mistreatment Of Inuit With Tuberculosis https://t.co/DOjJ9GenRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything we fully do is an alone journey. Natalie Goldberg  This is Valerie June. She came to First Avenue last y… https://t.co/d5LYAMgjeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates Heres my Lucy ... @littlucygoose on Instagram 😄 https://t.co/V0Obk9miCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sebauyanet @lenfestinst I don’t need the money right now, but if they want to throw $5 million my way, that would be cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*idaly &amp; i singing to moments from one direction * i look over and she’s literally tearing up 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[for lent im giving up being a sad bitch so i can get my life together. and i’m giving anyone permission to slap the… https://t.co/XAyIOZ66YT]]></document><document><![CDATA[RHS Alt-Ed student Drew Altom graduated today🎓 🔔 🎉. Drew finished his core40 3 months early. @JoshAmyx… https://t.co/vzrrAuoFlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica My signature cocktail is called the Cantonic. A shot of canton (ginger liquer) and a shot of good g… https://t.co/X1qdb52mrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys this is how I’m trying to be!! 💍@ShayHunn @TristanBeal96 @CierraTurk @carlyjan127 @West1998West]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sesame Chicken Saturday! Or just a good Saturday for all things China Gourmet! 👍😋👌 @ China Gourmet Restaurant https://t.co/9gZSW0eIPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[And remember when Bill did just move back how you and your friend try to convince him I was cheating on him with so… https://t.co/8mIpWTaZPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heppoco01 Though I'd probably insist that I didnt like being a girl. XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aquietstrength LOLOL that was me tonight. Me: I'm on the verge of passing out bc of my illness. 1 1/2 hrs later co… https://t.co/rk6GqkjbZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umbyrella @ChrisSturr @XCleXo Darling, she not running! No need to post *anything* about Hillary unless you’re kee… https://t.co/LD9NWhjxjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[TJ’s in the bathroom and all I can hear is the faint singing of Livin’ on a Prayer 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a news story yesterday from Seattle Public Schools that they WOULDVE opened schools earlier this week BUT t… https://t.co/mIUOthwNv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s National FFA Week so what better picture to share than the ultimate FFA member?! https://t.co/mZLtR3S1uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dozing off as I’m half way through chapter 2 of my book lolol. It’s time to call it a night, gudnight my friends 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I missed the Oscars and had to look up this whole Bradley Cooper/Lady Gaga performance... next to his girlfrie… https://t.co/sSkI9YlN3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Shuttle Driver - Caspian, MI - https://t.co/kC5nZALoUh #CustomerService #Caspian, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJSchauer Have you thought about CBD oil? You gotta find a real source that doesn’t water it down. I think… https://t.co/0U1Ux0bG6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop wearing the suffering, cruelty and torture of violently slaughtered animals so that you can delusionally  conv… https://t.co/j97JYbpXf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow The show is bad because everyone takes themselves too seriously. It’s the Oscar’s not the Nobel’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw @ThePromMusical and I don’t remember the last time I had this much fun at the theatre. Please go support t… https://t.co/sRR6yRFmm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly. Next he will sell ice to Alaska!   Go TRUMP!  🙌🏻🇺🇸❤️👍🏻💪🏻 https://t.co/lJ1hV8LwKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmaooo i was on the phone w my friends telling them to hurry up &amp; get ready but i’m butt ass naked in bed but they have no idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's a harder day!! 10 days without you here and it feels like a lifetime! I miss you 😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cariisss i’ll learn one day. until then, someone else can fight with it😂💀😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would get rid of the term ‘catastrophizing’ it’s become a catch-all term that suggests the patient has lost persp… https://t.co/F3SHoymQ1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @thedonaldwall @realDonaldTrump @MariaBartiromo @JudicialWatch @FoxNews They were instructed not to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[that three by duquesne womens basketball to tie, and then the near buzzer beater at half court. okay 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Blackhawks, #GoStars, #GoAvsGo, and #AllTogetherNowSTL play one another several times in the next few days. Th… https://t.co/0pj1hNuV2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enrique_Acevedo Jorge Ramos tambien es Ciudadano de los Estados Unidos.  Lo dijo en el famoso encuentro con Trump en el 2015.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥎 is now full time! 😎@LalondeSoftball @coach_lalonde @StriveSoftball @jaegersports @ConnectSports_ @SoftballConnect… https://t.co/CzM5qj9Ma0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staff meeting at Esten. A time to bring us closer together to share our worries and our goals. We are stronger when… https://t.co/WrpwkljawT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strategies To Foster A Sense Of Belonging In Your Classroom https://t.co/sL7kYNuuKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ba9MMX1DfT This is the 3 ed day this has been in newsfeeds. Move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AZSuperstitions @KimStrassel That's like the fox programming the look on the chicken coop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing Beyond Skincare, formulated with all-natural cacao ♾ Enhance youthful looking skin and lift your mood w… https://t.co/F8Zvsv1p6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Countess Elizabeth Báthory would love her .. perhaps they are related]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAALTA official meeting!! Connecting and sharing ideas with other Latin American language testers #LTRC2019 https://t.co/SrSiPVXfnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Walmart Supercenter in Ellicott City, MD https://t.co/bivu9kBHNB https://t.co/cZ5zWZHQDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I did use the word ‘psychobabble’ to a therapist once and it wasn’t appreciated” #mnleg #outofcontext]]></document><document><![CDATA[Campaign volunteer Denise Alcauter said she and other volunteers have slept maybe 8 hours over the past few days. https://t.co/Q11UuPSiL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrbanAchievr BECAUSE IN THE FAMILY VALUES PARTY YOU HAVE A LOT OF PHONY PEOPLE.  MATT GAETZ IS ONE OF THEM.  WOULD… https://t.co/ABtxN5L1sX]]></document></documents></author>