<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi This will not reduce crime and buying of guns. If you got the money there are numerous of places you… https://t.co/8NZfsNGA1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ana_hunsicker I’ll pray for you and ur family I know a littl about “tuff” times God is good 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jaycox Road south of #Electric Blvd closed due to tree limb down in #AvonLake https://t.co/KGKjV8r5zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aún y con 5°, los festejos y las sonrisas no faltaron tras el triunfo de tigresfemeniloficial ante clubleonfemenil… https://t.co/OP59m27veZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You know who else didn’t go to war against Vietnam and chickened out by saying he’s got bond spurs… https://t.co/xfQTlb8IEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survey says I'm 24% more likely to get laid tomorrow. What the survey doesn't know is that 0×24 is still 0😂 #nonut2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[2021 6"0 Olivia Miles , Blair academy  Best player in 21 class hands down . Athletic , passes like magic shoots like steph . Rare talent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering these are two different issues, with wildly different statistics, what would prevent a future president… https://t.co/2vOXVtQY1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cool is it that arcades don’t experience inflation?!! The coins never lose value. Allan Greenspan should incorp… https://t.co/Zf3mzvy9B1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Huntsman Oatmeal Stout by @relicbrewing @ Wood-n-Tap — https://t.co/ReCDbfF3sB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost I really don't mean to be rude but after seeing your picture I seriously doubt that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today truly was a MANIC Monday but the work day is over and girls we’re seeing MNEK tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_McPommell @lexiabrams4 Yes Nick. She's got a lien on her car now. My people don't mess around]]></document><document><![CDATA[U r painful with questions about events u were no where around to comment on. Just remember ur people were instrume… https://t.co/cQeg3TI0hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are those pimple popping videos so grotesque yet oddly and morbidly satisfying? https://t.co/xztWS4jBy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJerryP @natesportsguy @Brian_Haenchen Nothing crazy about the point system at all. A team should be rewarded f… https://t.co/fWoIkRbMGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @SK_Buckley @niamhwade27 @cmcgovern_ @iamshirtacus - miss you guys! https://t.co/GDbAVeIgX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of @Hickenlooper's 2020 kickoff speech: "I’m not the first person in the race or the most well kno… https://t.co/eMYkkqSK0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been listening to "American Nations" on audible and I've noticed the can't say Appalachia correctly.   Him: Ap… https://t.co/nrZq531PMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Konspyrenayko También hay gente que está deseando que ganen sabiendo que son bulos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianklaas That is why he will die in prison. Trump only hires the best...hardened criminals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people talk about Lebron and somewhere around the corner, you’ll hear the “but he’s team sucks.” At what p… https://t.co/0QPDaSkWr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JannaWilkinso69 "W" lowered the bar to such an extent that OBAMA looked "Presidential".  As Governor, he actually… https://t.co/w73HQfLEpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggadventures Not if you get me some Lawrys, onions and some lamb bacon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a chef is easy.  Chicken is bland? garlic salt* Subpar mashed-potatoes,garlic salt* Average French fries, gar… https://t.co/rFXgLXxevS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavy contingent of Russian or Eastern Europeans on this train.. and they say this is a commuter Amtrak??  Hoping m… https://t.co/DPETbTnsQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to giggle. Karan Brar And Cameron Boyce Hanging Out Today (October 25, 2012) https://t.co/Oo7wCWJQTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam Reunion waltdisneyworld Resort Themed Magic . . . . . . #tourbreak #fam #famreunion #wdw #artofanimationresort… https://t.co/7atPHazLuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonSiriusXM I don’t care about these types of initiatives...I care about HEALTH CARE, EDUCATION REFORM, TAX RE… https://t.co/WoOOYckiHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! Started covering Jaheim his freshman year and he’s become one of the best in Georgia. He’s worked very h… https://t.co/M4F2kzMZnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cities_PDX It could be a random ‘disaster’ that ties up traffic for a year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unions are the backbone of the middle class. The middle class is the backbone of a strong economy. The economy...we… https://t.co/jLJvmLvCLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely pulled something or popped something out of place. I have no idea how, but this pain is no joke.  It’s… https://t.co/UNFqLN8psO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted today for public advocate. I voted for the conservative Manny Alicandro. He supports Trump. Eric Ulrick the republican flip flops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you wondering, it sounds like the aim for puck drop for #NHLJets and #Coyotes will be between around 8:38 pm CT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ballad of Ira Hayes https://t.co/fkeCzflYs8 via @YouTube In memory of the raising of the flag at Iwo Jima 74 years ago today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virgilian_ @thronesfacts Yes. I forget who was talking about it but the Mad King put barrels of that stuff under K… https://t.co/zCIwhrZ6gH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burgerkimm Char lang saken ha baka mamaya you believe na I support incest. Hindi po]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #Tennessee #Titans / #Houston #Oilers from 1965 on.  https://t.co/RCMZtWZKwW … … … https://t.co/I3mTJ5Ze6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrapAndFamous @realcrookedtie @Dgfria2 @MarthaMad99 @realDonaldTrump Just record employment numbers record unemplo… https://t.co/r290u3uELV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wealth_Theory I must balance it out for you somehow, right? https://t.co/qOFA9BrET3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Part-time Instruction and Classroom Support Technician I - Culinary Arts (Cuisine) -… https://t.co/KtSkyoFopm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant say im this die-hard Jeopardy fan.  But Trebek is such a stud.  Imagine hearing this news and giving a state… https://t.co/0jQDwIDHPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fresh Prince of Agrabah...  There, I did it everybody. https://t.co/iiqpP0Cfbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorginaHolguin Gina , te ves preciosa y súper sexy en Expreso TE AMO te mando millones de besos 😍😘😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Veeterz I loved the 1st and 3rd game when they came out. Never played the 4th]]></document><document><![CDATA[The partnership between @ptc and @GroupHowden is incredible, and with the new #Hololens2 it is even stronger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally done with inventory (@ Shiki Japanese Cuisine in Half Moon Bay, CA) https://t.co/TTRYp2nAwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tenhill and would love a #K9Lor shirt @JamesCraigmyle @GreeneCountySO @gototheshack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorrorMovieBBQ But his wife put him on blast. It'd be one thing if TMZ discovered it and everyone wasn't respectin… https://t.co/T1LMTM6XyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mandalay Bay is pretty busy hosting a pet convention #dasvegas2019 @ Mandalay Bay Resort and Casino https://t.co/rn43SoxYpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here with my Baby Girl. (@ Brow Spa in Clarksville, TN) https://t.co/OcKsxpiunW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty stoked to see these boys coming to Charlotte  #nowplaying Sleep - Sleep’s Holy Mountain (1992) #metal #doom… https://t.co/6SyRbiKktp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Aerial / Timelapse short film coming soon :D https://t.co/Te2CN48pmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ This is hilarious. A multimillionaire buying full page ads to influence politics supports her cause.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Letters4theLord @kyreOhani @Bryan_Duncan @JeremyKappell @caseytduncan 🤔 Seems to me your phone needs a #Timeout 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pope1849 @ErnstPauli88 Makes me want a cellophane canoe of my very own]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corpse_Husband Not sure the time zone with you but good afternoon, and have a wonderful day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, now I’m wondering what he’s smoking. I think it’s cool too, but did this tweet just come the Oval Office?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trains don'tmake sense in America Until we increase density 900 percent]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get how the Red Storm can come out like in front of a sold out crowd hungry for a big time win over Nova.… https://t.co/cG8ubrLQHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAtheist The religious or non religious beliefs of citizens are equal in the eyes of the constitution and a… https://t.co/boONOQajyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it wrong to invite your mother in law over for a few days just so that your significant other will clean the house? #AskingForAFriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Argument could be made for Anthony Jordan if you’re just looking at the impact each player had on his respective te… https://t.co/ohUSrlXQZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[DLCH😠😠...por quedar mal conmigo, quedó mal con otras personas y ahora me la tengo que pelar inche gente VV😠😠..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC So the nearly 63,000,000 people who voted for Trump aren't part of the "People of the United States?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the morning drum session @PaisteNation @evansdrumheads @YamahaDrumsEU @ribbonmics @InnovativePerc  Rock and… https://t.co/CcA06bQ3QE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MachineryPete @AgDayTV Not much emissions on those!! I imagine that’s some of the reason! I have 8230 . Good rigs.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ever out in public and think, “I have to be on fucking Boiling Points right now!”? Just me? Ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ian_banks95 I knew he had a job there, but I'm surprised he actually had to do anything. He made UT great again. Firing him seems wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanholladay @petermckinnon @BladeHQ Make sure you give him a coin in return or the blade will sever the friendship...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncurtis @rosswil I think it is more than being effectively stopped, not doing one more clearly indicates your i… https://t.co/yDouD9PvMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how protective Steve is of Wanda when he sees her upset. Respect the Cap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frank_Frangie I think the Jaguar fans are tired of having a bad team. They’ve had one good year and a lot of very… https://t.co/F9qKqGrbgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @harleydavidson chandlerharley_davidson  FXDR and FatBoy ( romeogolf62 )hard parked at @MerchantFirearm!… https://t.co/uzdtE8kMTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/X0JO56wqo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sinatra_Jay That education you think they are getting isn’t all that it’s cracked up to be in some cases. Some sch… https://t.co/r6CkJsE4vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[At #WTFest19 and want to discuss where from, why here, but hard to approach me. They see I’m blind. Hope walls come down for us all. Say hi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#epeeps bronchial injury with Cryoablation in the LSPV. A potential under recognised complication causing post op c… https://t.co/8M1TtLjv96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Is to give you a little education president Reagan to go over the worst economy since Barack Obama and turned… https://t.co/rpFJ5kxvTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Where no oxen are, the crib is clean: but much increase is by the strength of the ox.” Proverbs 14:4 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The science is not clear NASA reported the earth cooling for the last two years.the ice sheets are expanding.I trus… https://t.co/cIHO1FMESu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest fear? Who will take care of my son when I'm gone. Constantly trying to idolize the gifter and not the gift.… https://t.co/D3O9GYHOis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amanda_Kerri I think one reason Jon Stewart quit is he came to realize his snarky analysis wasn’t really helping.… https://t.co/qQHrKsNe44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love when someone spits on your car at a stop light because he wants to hate on all electric vehicles. 🔋 ⚡️ D… https://t.co/ggz8MVIeQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump I bet he is real mad while he’s tha president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey, Valentine. Didn’t see ya there. Come let me dedicate love song after love song to you tonight at Cineplex V… https://t.co/Alf6n1tsaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump You have got to be kidding. You believe that liar. You have to gullible person]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zach_Brach @Apple I’m gonna wait til this one dies. There’s honestly no reason for me to get a new one right now..… https://t.co/kur9vzW4gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really think I’m bothered by their opinion about me. Y’all just my daily entertainment when I hop in bed 😂👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to do football drills and competitions n’ stuff when it’s nice out DM me if you wanna join]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timk1208 @TheMeadowlands @DaveLittleBigM Use Siri and the microphone! Don’t type!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trashygaytweets @GavinLee784 Two separate issues. And if we keep muddling all the worlds problems together nothing… https://t.co/pseLl903fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisforce75 @ZacStevensBSN @AndreSimone I’ll concede to Zac if it means I don’t have to do any running 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S HAPPENING... Sean Hannity: "The Deep State House of Cards -- Mark My Words -- It's About to Come Crumbling Dow… https://t.co/lI4Ps4sHMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley Lol that's NOT considered snow...its flurries dude https://t.co/MkSLuBzJvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@King_kevvoo Have yet to see this “football side”. Definitely familiar with your “IR side” tho!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even tho it's in the East and not the South I'll take it. UVa as the 1 and Houston as the 3... I'd take it in secon… https://t.co/G5F97AU8hG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rileyrussill @AlexHonnold Me the last 20 minutes... https://t.co/fGH1bkzCq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshcopen @SlowToWrite I’ve read and listened so some anti social justice people and while I can admit that things… https://t.co/6NEPj1g5vi]]></document></documents></author>