<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey there folks! You should check out this awesome event going on tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onhi I will be seeing cranes at a gathering in 2 weeks.  I will post pics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Greatest former President ever and arguably best human as President. #hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSXYZ9 Afreeca had so many chances to put themselves ahead and just never did, so what a surprise griffin picks a… https://t.co/WhP4NH3PfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle @MSNBC @SavannahGuthrie @Yamiche @clairecmc @BarbMcQuade @MariaTeresa1 @gilliantett @Peggynoonannyc… https://t.co/IqKtdxVEYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t expect to make it out to Frankie’s this weekend, but it was a welcome turn of events! (with non-IG Bill an… https://t.co/49e0mGiYDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess there are some benefits to having to wake up early for your daughter's sportsball... https://t.co/vWjnpyA2Gi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #KuwaitNationalDay. See you next week 🇰🇼❤️ “ya a7la bald” https://t.co/f7kZalMi7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have @ElixirOutlaws, Fots LaCroix stickers. Fine me. I have crutches and a Nemo bow tie so it should be ash to fi… https://t.co/L87jl90CRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @ArianaGrande would love going out on a date with me. The only thing missing is her following me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UprightSpeedway Jeff Havacko and Rob Pfetzing at IMS in San Bernardino and probably in 1980.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colulu1991 @BeeMissa Kids are a good judge of a person. I miss this man and his leadership. I tear up looking at a… https://t.co/zxZYdFJpQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Panthers @run__cmc @gregolsen88 @greatness_16 @AndreSmith_9 @Jay_wright4 @ShaqThompson_7 @kk_mr93 @_DJack01… https://t.co/Uvqo8ZXIu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Fudge Cookies Made with Avocado!? | @tigerfitnesscom @MarcLobliner @KaraCoreyFit https://t.co/UucTw9NSzR via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget ghosts that won’t leave no matter how many times you sage the house; the only thing I really have to fear is myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Holy shit, Donnie - that's some socialism right there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penguins gotta figure something out soon... we need to get back in this quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringoffireradio @farronbalanced Boo hoo, guvnah.... https://t.co/568lRC8dDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's wrong with the MAX plane type @Boeing? Two crashes from it in the past few months???]]></document><document><![CDATA[#potus, President Trump, you cannot win in congress due to the corruption on both sides. But you can win with the A… https://t.co/rFj8u6o0AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple weeks ago, I drove home three elderly ladies who had just seen Jerry Lee Lewis perform at @peacecenter in… https://t.co/Jm1hZaZMMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bi11ion18 @Brad13___ @Chargers They did actually had the game sealed when brady threw his 3rd pick late in the gam… https://t.co/Ulhy0k1mTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winterlovers❄️ #instawinter❄ #lakelovers💙 #instalake #tbt #bluesky💙 #instasky #instasun #sunlovers☀️… https://t.co/KAw6M11vhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday’s Work. Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch… https://t.co/jrI3Pv1JwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericbolling @AndrewBreitbart @LarryOConnor report to trump with asymmetrical face for mockery of disability]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellzfan01 And when did you discover that a grand jury proceedings is secret, ge I don't know that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZionistGirl18 @GoGreen33333333 Oh God, oops i mean Allah, he messed up his hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glenngabe Half your recent posts are basically slide subjects from here in Portland. In particular the JavaScript one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPEZZARONI Too large, Whataburger overrated, Ted Cruz and John Cornyn are evil people, abortion, etc etc etc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePunisher is a Good ass show @netflix you guys Suck that's why I just stopped your service 3 days ago now am rol… https://t.co/BGthH6GVie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMathews21 @CNN @CillizzaCNN When she blows herself up at the state of the union]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackNFrank Tough to pick against Beard or Weber at this point, although I do believe this was the best coaching jo… https://t.co/VZDB0Kg9hO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbarro The full gamut of human emotions from these members of Congress. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope rises from the Darkness! 🙏🏼❤️✌🏽 @ San Diego, California https://t.co/NSSOQIXkOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how social media can connect people who are present (virtually or in-person) at conferences and still… https://t.co/9ZgbHCZqyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 months ago I had just an iPhone for my camera and VSCO for my editing... guess this just the beginning of my work… https://t.co/pX1wNc54di]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you do for your love ones or one's today stop for a minute think of what they mean to you ,make sure what… https://t.co/mbNf8Jwlor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I’m reading Virginia Woolf in the airport. Yes, I want people to know I’m a feminist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy March 4th. This was the area where I had my first ever sectional for the good old BOM back in 2014. The “next… https://t.co/FzTzcZdqhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[That makes sense! For your last-hundred-meterers, for sure.   But boy, you should see my friends: They got *nothing… https://t.co/m2lPKQm9y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hollywood Walk of Fame in Hollywood, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/bnJIHedh8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erin always had to be first ... just like her mom! LOL!  Love you, Erin. Hope you have a great birthday. https://t.co/g0xaA1svFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its my birthday today :) can someone please get me a GTR R35 Its all i really want in my life😩😍  please retweet thi… https://t.co/vg4rsmgaIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We did some serious calculating with our co-conspirators this morning! #stem  As always, thank you to 1A for hostin… https://t.co/SQ8QmInjJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every reason to be grumpy this morning as I head to Chicago for the week.  But, my attitude is a choice.  I choose… https://t.co/hZL0XaUddZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Marcus Jewish Community Center of Atlanta in Dunwoody, GA https://t.co/TnVQrTEoHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefjoseandres @WCKitchen Muchos muertos “extra oficialmente” en la travesía a través del Páramo de Berlín, sin du… https://t.co/IussZ1iAth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naturally_ee @paulhue I agree but disregard The Who question for I misspoke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarettMansfield i don't know if I sent you this picture before. sorry if i did. with  him at the helm anything is… https://t.co/pdt2xDaBO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSteegeNFL @piatz1019 So we forgot about what Nick Foles looked like when he didn’t have one of the best Olines in… https://t.co/Ty1TnfgF5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger Kentucky’s drug problem is astounding and openly visible to anyone who visits Louisville.  And many… https://t.co/b4TLYr5Qda]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ENTÉRATE Así comenzamos hoy @noticias62tv #11pm desde #losangeles #california hablando de @YalitzaAparicio y… https://t.co/C5PoN4ZBYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristapley @jehorowitz We need new, competent voices.  Change is possible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tarasenko scores, Allen solid as Blues beat Kings 4-0  https://t.co/oWD4noPRC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you needed to know what surprised me on Valentine’s Day. #aviationgin https://t.co/37mG1bTmUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that remember the midterms. You’ve lost mine and others trust. You’ll need to to do some work to earn it back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always the prettiest girls trying to scam...  talking about “you could make $2,000 in minutes, do you have chase?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AlbrieLeavy_ @PaperPowerPussy @alanahamideh And I don’t care if he doesn’t like it’s fine he was cool when we wer… https://t.co/dDa6ojbMUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TotalFurthMove @WelcomeToDot @BillForry Given how hard it is to find a place that will take appointments in Dot, I… https://t.co/SaFGFdamgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConservativeTht @marklevinshow @DennisPrager @MedvedSHOW Picture of 2 demons]]></document><document><![CDATA[[3/6] #SXSWMusic X #internationalwomensday: @tinashe at @800congress for @sonyelectronics’s #LostInMusic 3/15/17. 📸… https://t.co/IBKCfX7ozS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USRNRadio @calmister2000 @skywalker42811 @OwenParkin3 @malleychristian @CBBonUNB @IESportsRadio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellowkelow Report for what? Stealing money from Hal? He certainly isn’t reporting to play in a Baseball game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MeSaleElDiabloCuando escucho veo a alguien hablando mal de los demás... https://t.co/SVSQEBv1mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ogitte225 @670_is_trash @AdamMKaufman He has talent but IMO he is not a franchise type player]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy from the night cleaning crew 100% just saw me sniff a candle after debating whether or not to get it, say “… https://t.co/iDnbJ2FiEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imispgh @LawOfDriverless I did, the first time you posted it. It doesn’t apply to this. They’re not doing remote o… https://t.co/Ze0KYPCLOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naretevduorp I blocked the Orange Jackass on Twitter so can't see what he's been saying. Feel so much better now.… https://t.co/57JBO435Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJs_Restaurant Bar and Grill in #Bayville presents Karaoke Tuesdays from 7PM-11PM! #Barnegat #BayBoulevard… https://t.co/8YODebYkeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sums it up. There is no other way to spin the reality of this. Well....... I’m sure there is a way to spin it… https://t.co/gI2oZaBTJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s the day. My time to shine. I’ve been waiting for this moment. LETS GO!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how millennials think. 80% are dumber then a box of rocks, and what's really dangerous is they breed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad said I need to be on the track for this to be considered “seat time” 🤣. #MyHappyPlace #MySeatTime https://t.co/ScdSCaCt1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amateurs built the Ark, professionals built the Titanic.  I had to read this quote about 3 times to understand the… https://t.co/aP8v74Dm6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpachov Substitute statistics for ML and I think it is literally the same so I don't see any difference. The curre… https://t.co/LpcUUXvoZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖕She is number one in my book. Ya right  She's out I promise you that fu#%@&amp;! #RHINO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukas_scott33 @WSHS_Colts @CatawbaFootball Ain’t going to lie ! You will be missed here . I know you will do great… https://t.co/WA1Fq1g6OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[off to new york i go 🛩  #goof #lair #leica #nyc @ Lax Airport https://t.co/RAuTUm5SzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakewillms17 @wilkswilkss I think that time will tell. If Apex can survive after the initial hype and continue to… https://t.co/9jAJqq1Tvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalfEvilPope @HALFEVILCO @parkersabsent @ABSENTCLOTHING @augst Whoever can get me a size L!!! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night of food and fun with the family! #theshed #familia #family #santafe @ The Shed of Santa Fe https://t.co/TThPiJZTpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvorakoelling @realDonaldTrump @dvorakoelling , your ghetto lingo betrays your miseducation.  Praying to God for y… https://t.co/WBl4YFYqwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aqui a foto de amigos que fiz na viagem que me mandaram com o Chavez e o Maduro observando... eu acabei não indo ao… https://t.co/acRHpX2duy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch I hope so! He’s a fucking crook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobJack83120905 @PremierScottMoe @ezralevant @JustinTrudeau Very mature and totally wrong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How far will the @Yankees go this season? #LockedInn https://t.co/Ah1UyqZ4Cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so fucked up! It’s so sad I have to worry about my daughter watching this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moderate to High impact snow and ice storm expected on Wednesday for Berks..get the latest and expected snow accumu… https://t.co/iJofBrcO7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is Thursday with big numbers coming. Not surprising to see #natgas moving up here. $90.9 is my next mark to buy… https://t.co/G1VIQRKVsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EarBlowingAudio Another one of those "easier said than done" helpful phrases. 👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen The larger problem is why do the privileged get away with these things time and time again. Corporations… https://t.co/vsfC5LshlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuanceBro @ChrisCuomo Some of them simply weren’t jokes bro. You can hear it in his tone. Especially his comments… https://t.co/sWxcZHsb1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget that you can Pre-Order “Unveil” by @joncegan today! You’ll receive “What You Said” when you do. If you… https://t.co/J3xny2KHB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crusting it? See we got sum things in common, come on now n slide into my DMs lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the douchebag plowing our parking lot who dumped all the snow in the handicap spot so the poor elderly… https://t.co/SVuRXCtVmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold What is it with @realDonaldTrump and golf courses, anyway? A few answers here from @ilyamarritz or… https://t.co/ik1e25YHJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morten @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Roy Cohn Was The Devil Incarnate https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since when in the United States of America did we have to start making these kinds of statements? We are a Democrat… https://t.co/AhfSyMi09P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antid0teee I guess it was all funny jokes pissing on those girls in the shower back them huh? This dude is a peace… https://t.co/cI57JdWleR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olivia Coleman wins Best Actress!! #AcademyAwards https://t.co/L201aL2TBX]]></document></documents></author>