<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Yogirljackie_ I believe you, but when they haven’t written it down in my experience 8 times out of 10 they mess it… https://t.co/WU548jSquM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phenomenal edits of Sam heughan and Caitriona balfe  Credit to @GinaPustorino #Outlander #loveforsamandcait… https://t.co/R0jiMpgrPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got chased by 4 dogs! Not one, not@two, but four!!! #imok #instarun #running #runninglife… https://t.co/T9eC81TS2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlockWagon @TrishDukes1 @karnasoar @lucky_deviant @SimonSaysMoo @FinallyEven @CieraMiller19 @Anaba_theLEE… https://t.co/WYyQyQPJVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow pup. 🐾 #lutrathewonderdog #cockapoosofinstagram #bestcoworker #certifiedtherapydog @ McGuirk Alumni Stadium https://t.co/SewOTLgBMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monkeypaw @JordanPeele Please check your DMs representatives from Howard university are trying to contact the company and @JordanPeele]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungdoublecupp Yes, watch the door when you open it 😆 they try and book it every time. Also get one of those play… https://t.co/yfXDYswZr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to know why luke hemmings hates me and ignores me every time he comes online 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @fawnpnguyen had been my teacher, I might have taught Math instead of English. Check out her website at… https://t.co/ZEZCnBqdd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[New stuff in the light of day.  #resin #resinmolds #resinart #resincasting #diy #witchy #glitter #sillyputty #bats… https://t.co/K0qhyjs34N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrganicValley #OrganicValley #EggWhites 🥚 + @dietpepsi #DietPepsi (@ Westside Market in New York, NY) https://t.co/msUyfpNtEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisBergHD Awesome! I remember my Diamond Celebration with The Conyers Team I will never forget it! Thanks to @JPatton89 @kjfritz84]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3yo crashed his 10yo brother’s friend’s house tonight. Stopped at the liquor store on the way home... I’m offic… https://t.co/pUHvsPmRxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am seriously cursed. The fact that this can happen to me TWO TIMES. Holy shit #ForeverAlone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheena___V @eschoenTHD @MNevesTHD @THDJon_RHRM @THD_Alexandra @islandkemper @lennyatdepot Hilarious 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Concord Swim Club and Mya Lynn!!! Swim fast today!!!! #warmups @ Concord Aquatic Center https://t.co/hlTZ7sRKua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a great session on Achieving Equity and Empowering Students with  @dr_lillian @SXSWEDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t think straight 💘#valentinesgay2019 need me a girl :/ https://t.co/NApILFJnRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you doing for Valentine's Day ? Any plans yet ❤❤❤ . . Note this is not just for couples . Any plans with y… https://t.co/kYaISBGu9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you still carry around a wallet? I do when I'm hauling my big purse, but if I'm going out, I just grab my ID and… https://t.co/rLgDPtbEBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magssca @CompaTiger The only way to get rid of demons is to throw hands 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jd_morganne @DoctorJAuthor @AndreaPatten @dbmoone @DawnHosmer7 @JennMaloney042 @PCWharton @KelvinROfficial… https://t.co/1yufkEx3z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaSokol Please be with us now! On earth as it is in blahs, blahnik, blah...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobunruh Girls?! That’s unusual.  The crew at Moore/Mustang game hardly called any today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Out85Strong facts. logging in to make a payment was pissing me off too much lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your favorite part of the weekend is nigh! Meet n' eat with 40+ makers tomorrow at #IXFarmersMarket from 9am-1pm. -… https://t.co/iSdfPRcrpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnPtye @dbtjenn @DebKurenaiValo @YoshikiOfficial @PBS @ThirteenWNET OPB schedule for Friday... https://t.co/xvmigo2raD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to check out @kenjeong New Netflix comedy Special, he’s hilarious 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Netflix se ha topado con un hallazgo sorpresivo: pese a un aumento reportado de nacionalismo en todo el planeta, m… https://t.co/EEC1wxl21m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xkhdc @Runlittlefox How did you know my mother was born in Paris?  Je m'appelle Jacqueline. 😸]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a lovely day in #Dallas #microhistoriasdelaquevuela en #Texas #wanderlust #eatpraytravel #instatravel… https://t.co/biYhBzMYXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It snowed last night and it is a holiday today, so rather than going to the gym at butt-early I sat at my dining ta… https://t.co/hKzlLM91gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coworker said Vincent Gallo movies are good if you have time to watch a guy jerk off for 2 hours and my response was “I do”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtd_gameon12 @KatTheHammer1 No he needs to hold acct the murder of innocent babies before he considers the tearing… https://t.co/G8VRnKaShV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to all of my beautiful and outstanding women!!!!!!!❤️🙌🏻 Above all, I love identifyi… https://t.co/ChoyUBFJmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @MalcolmNance @crooksandliars Sean Hannity is the poster boy for White Privilege.  I can’t think of a s… https://t.co/sYjM698RTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Wow talk about mindless banter! This bullet train was a bonehead idea created to screw… https://t.co/MH5InEt3Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all starts with a concept and #inspiration !!! A little here... a little there and viola! Check out our favorite… https://t.co/lg97lcnrKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a terrific movie, and Bradley Cooper is a criminally under-recognized talent in everything he does, probably… https://t.co/5U8Q0cbosq]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤❤❤❤ Eustace and his Valentine! @JonathanJ254 @chris_breezy27 https://t.co/MR955z36lX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma - assistance to rebuild.  Tomorrow Big Line Key #comminity #kwislandgirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I always weird loud noises when I’m the shower? 😫 (I live alone, no more animals)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not superstitious, but... we couldn’t bump that up a bit? #oneaday @Bayer https://t.co/Px6aJ0mtFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby all up in the @CAMMHS pic        @CSen19rs @CAMMHScheer @CAMMHSAthletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Colton   Put on your damn blinders and stop looking at the shiny things. You’ll know who’s legit.   #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLNTV @DonnieWahlberg Wait they forgot producer.. Wahlburgers Co owner... Defender of #BHLove ..AMAZING ASS... I'm… https://t.co/WtZ83pjpQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇  Cl… https://t.co/HyhW1EAdry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vasilevskiy is the first off the ice this morning after practice. Presumed to be the starter tonight against Ottawa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate that I keep waking up and this damn cough isn’t helping either..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday "Bean"! Love you Buddy!  Mr. Kendall James is Paw Patrol Wasted! #jessieskid #mycuz #wecoparent #lol… https://t.co/EVcFmNFC7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kohie’s outfit I ordered for his first birthday should be here today!!! Ahhh I’m so excited! Even though his birthd… https://t.co/j8Vjb3GGZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I booked a flight for 10am tomorrow but I actually booked 630am why am I such a consistent MESS??!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go teammarylandehl and what a beautiful PP goal Connor!!! @EHL_Hockey #hockey #powerplay @ Piney Orchard Ice… https://t.co/LuRQ6b8rcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobDMaxwell Loved your rendition of Delicate by @taylorswift13 I hope you go far on The Voice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechubbette (At least when I went) there was an annual football game against a rival state school every year but… https://t.co/CMSy7Qi0LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilybell @starisbornmovie 😂  I kept trying to turn it off near the end bc I knew what was coming and @lmower3 was… https://t.co/lSQJ0s2kju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dewan298 @PostMalone @TrackBangas @TylaYaweh @rriproarin Hands down. Beer Pong lol. I’d whip his a$$. Lmao Hail to the Pong 🤗🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FancyFranziFfm @robertcarlyle_ I’m Jewish! He scared the hell out of me and they didn’t portray the worst. My relatives were lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support Repeated they had no information. I want to talk to an American who speaks English clearly. Bc there’… https://t.co/plytlhjJO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s because Dave Grohl is a talented musician who TRULY cares about his fans and gives his all during their conc… https://t.co/AeCT143QaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially putting my name in to run for mayor of Kansas City. I promise to immediately fix every pot hole on 35 hi… https://t.co/Q7FiMComHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaHeaton @Oscars2019Live_ Greenbook, so glad it won!! I see around 60 movies a year at the theater and loved… https://t.co/smIZNlOpPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteGloriaJ For a small dinner like this, Matthew would do it all, then the Governor and First Lady would wash dis… https://t.co/lB2wWe6G2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[SpaceX just launched a rocket that orbited earth and landed back on launchpad in under 10 minutes live!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson White,white,Caucasian, white, not black, white, white, not brown, white, white....]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just feel like this is something noah centipede would say  https://t.co/KyIhHrJ9lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinky’s up! The best way to enjoy the weekend with a hot chocolate after a beach hike in Cape Cod! #worklifebalance… https://t.co/yN9pxBagF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_RossX @JimC267 Mike, my family history goes back so far in England's history it boggles my mind.  Sir Cyril W… https://t.co/FS23CwLz8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M2Madness @cezhere Fuck you and the crippled horse you are riding in on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a good time this evening  officialhampton_mainstreet celebrating another race weekend and welcoming our… https://t.co/w6pswNAskF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Faustotweets Lmao dude they are it triggered me because it reminded me of high school and I hated it! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night .. with these two!! Fantastic evening hairbrained_official awards #HVAAwards2019 @HairbrainedME… https://t.co/LeeYqTR3Im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump The News is Not the enemy of the people!  They are on the side of truth and are tired o… https://t.co/jnhTr9Kl3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceBartlett shouldn't quoting Mussolini be grounds for being stripped of his authority? Geez Lousie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charles Daley Park ❤️👀 #boardwalk #pier #park #beach #winter #perspective #distance #lake #roadtrip #Ontario… https://t.co/BfnPfusgy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl Just bust through there &amp; always remember this: everybody’s rooting for you &amp; really wants you do a good job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just so NOT into going into the grocery stores that I can’t even fathom having to stop for even one thing. Fuck… https://t.co/gBHmWzqFcq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool that ur allowed to rip cigs on the subway now thanks president trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophia Shalmiyev's Playlist for 'Mother Winter' by Sophia Shalmiyev https://t.co/LkbFDO4mxH @Powells Music for the book!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BentStraite I’m not mad at Kareem as the 🐐. But be completely honest, no single person on earth would take Kareem… https://t.co/mB61VtporW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashley_edes Ah! I went to EFP in Rome a few years ago - it’s a wonderful group!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could just fly somewhere right this second. Pick up your passport and just go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardA_Esq @bridget_joy_ Well, he knows the price he’d pay. Vlad don’t play that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a Veteran or a family member of active duty...hell, no matter who you are, watch this salute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Good Luck to you John Schneider.  I'm dedicating the song "Backwards" just for you!! https://t.co/DTkrDPrFwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhHeyMrJ @drewabides Oh geez! The school week starts and I totally lose track. Posting mine now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I'm overloaded with the amount of work I have this week, so when talking about work at the end of the year, or wor… https://t.co/kuLrvMJsbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debratankersle1 @confessions_cup @melanie_korach @TheAngelOrsini @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie… https://t.co/ymmkW6cnRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few more shots. #ScottieBlackHistoryProgram @ Sarah Scott MiddleSchool https://t.co/gS9iDeyrJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna play the Mamma Mia soundtrack during my work out today. But instead I forgot my headphones.  So now I'm… https://t.co/gXUKF1i1xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAFromBK @DragonMom98 @lno09281978 @SandiMarie79 @NashBillsBackrs @ByCharlieRicker @JustPlainT @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/LBWFHTfT3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember at the beginning he told me he was different it’s a shame what a show these boys play after time😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KimLovette #TybeeIsland #BirthdayBehavior #SAGEligible #ActingIsMyPassion #ActingIsMinistry #AKA1908 #AKA… https://t.co/NLv6cBoIJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AubreyWollett Congratulations! I will definitely send a vote your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to a beginner yoga class tonight and I felt like SUCH hot shit because I was “the best”. And then I fell on… https://t.co/WgQAegK6EK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamb83 @ShefaniAFRICA @blakeshelton You can only get it in Virginia I heard? I hope not!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oblivious. Only?  I’m alright with a slow burn. Congrats, @KaceyMusgraves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok.. why is google showing me ads for a face serum that I have in my medicine cabinet but have never looked up onli… https://t.co/vkrP4m1nVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commissioner Tom Dale points out rescinding the resolution doesn’t commit the county to any further interpretation… https://t.co/0qoksGJ1F3]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing like feeling it after half a beer bc all you had was a cake pop]]></document></documents></author>