<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/gyL8nd3fma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AylaForTrump You know, I don't give a fk what anybody thinks about me. Sht like this is  SICK  AND  HASTY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta LOVE this time of winter 🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀 NJSIAA Playoffs... Let’s Goooooooo💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Semaphore89 @Kellyann_Dupuis Supreme Court needs to establish legal age status of a fetus, not life, but legal age… https://t.co/KhO2bgUrbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Citra Single Hop IPA by @seapinebrewing @ The Hop Garden — https://t.co/29vEIeeDxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swierczewski07 Well to start, every MCU film has been good. Like even their lowest graded films are still very goo… https://t.co/MzuvYPBuqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XTRASports1300 @Globies @bworldarena @Lili_Thompson1 These guys were the real stars, their talent far exceeds that… https://t.co/lQ9Z2OvXvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met a guy tonight.  Thought he was cute.  We played beer pong.  We won.  We talked.  We laughed.  He says to everyb… https://t.co/ZU0hksH34z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Responding to @CityofWichita  The Hackathon of 2016, in which WINTA garnered 4th place out of 13 teams: no funding… https://t.co/nYoknfrUIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly it so hard maintaining being a college student when you just want to party and not be stressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Nefarious Purposes by @Race_Street @ Sideline Pizza — https://t.co/4B4GaH1R5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madShana @G792Mike @nysportsfan2015 @NickM538 @EastBhamKid @DiStitz @_WeAreND_ @Zalman888 @LifeGal4 @Amber00924… https://t.co/l4fKDLoYHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J9Talley When you're famous, you can do anything. You can grab them by the moobies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garry_keller @JL_Braden Would be interesting to see if a law society would punish a lawyer for violating solicitor… https://t.co/XwEHO4RkbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA *gasps for brearh* HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAA https://t.co/QdRRoLW8Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennieology This part makes you an exceptional person IMHO. Standing up for the downtrodden in that environment wa… https://t.co/rn1UttyULr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalNiederman @DanJFederico Macnow just said on WIP that Bill Goldsworthy was a supreme jackass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianWinn @BryanNews3LV If there was anything you could change from your comment, what would it be? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[This new Deadbeats episode makes that last Forest payment not seem so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are no words to describe how thankful I am for these two incredible couples right here (and of course “Sethy… https://t.co/e2ePG10Kv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you very much Jenna. I really appreciate  your offer to help thanks a million.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTLug0 || 🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MO… https://t.co/DBrOIZUKLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apex queues get so sweaty and boring this late. People playing edge of zone and third partying last fight like it’s PUBG lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@labboypro It's often both. Civil disobedience is usually illegal. For some of the classic theorists/practitioners… https://t.co/y28K17sw2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Book. I liked it a lot, but what an underwhelming winner for Best Picture. I thought I would be happy to see… https://t.co/ugsLS3SlS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekDrewes @lincolnwayne_ You didn’t pay for admission so we can disclose any information. Venmo each is us $10 a… https://t.co/8hWA12p63V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Doug... it’ll be a lasting moment in my life... can’t even imagine how the Stdnt Aths feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEN MARCO RUBIO confirmó que si alguno de los 6 jefes militares venezolanos principales desertaba (Vladimir Padrino… https://t.co/QpAjLo29QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisella80 Y se pusieron los chalecos amarillos!!🙄🙄  Pense que era broma. Wow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking hate when people jump to say who wins a trade on deadline day. Let the trades pan out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprised that Americans still talk about socialism as if the Soviet Union were close to invade the US. We are in 2… https://t.co/me0NUYwHsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jordan, Loreena McKennitt, Jerry O’Connell, Denise Richards, Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Lou Diamond Phillips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy mush day to my amazing wife. @ The Gourmet Pizza Shoppe https://t.co/oERExlNJTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update in Lynn, C4 reports fire is in a large brick commercial building, fire started in the oven, extended to the walls and up to the roof]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your buddy asks for a google review and gets 5 stars with a complimentary Rick Roll. 👊🏼 Book caffeineandgasoli… https://t.co/ePdH98XfOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josespinoza10 @mundodeportivo El mejor jugador de club de todos los tiempos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElJohnny95 @CAGOP @millanpatterson Agree 100%   Life is sacred and valuable! It ought to be protected.  Patterson… https://t.co/t7uBgL7oN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[A college student’s best friend... 💥sugar-free lasting energy 💥increased mental focus 😜🍓🍏🍒🍇🍋🍈🍍🥥🍉 https://t.co/498mTISd0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited about this! @Chelseaker @paulbaloche @michaelneale @robwilsonmusic @WillisCaleb @Spotify… https://t.co/bQAg1jNoz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erik_Guzman09 FOH that boy Lavine was legit flying! Windmill and goin between the legs ? From the line?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palita_40 Muy buenos días PAlita y feliz martes para ti también saludos internacionales y cuídate,!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kstojwwe It’s just “ putting over” the new talent. That was probably the deal when the powers that be gave The Revival the Titles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The majority of ppl would admit that they dont teust their government or what it does but it will be the same follo… https://t.co/33tVDiQvy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlaPanthers teammates cheer on Derek MacKenzie as he takes a final lap in uniform. He has been out since opening n… https://t.co/aaulHwqBrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akaWorf Awe, you guys are the best! Wish #StarTrekNextGeneration never had to end!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I get fries with that? @BobLangert provides a chat and expert from his new book of his 35+ year career w a glob… https://t.co/0hY9qTgLcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[are we still sitting in #sin, or worst just being #silent, not sharing the #goodnews not going out there?  are we t… https://t.co/d5hbCUhH15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/mEszqfP647]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soju_warrior That’s well put man. I totally agree. Idk why it’s that way but seems acceptable. They could afford t… https://t.co/EKcBQ9O8Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a fan of Wang Leehom. #NowPlaying 大城小愛 (Big City, Small Love) by Wang Leehom. #mandopop #ballad https://t.co/TOXd9QQjK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[With colder weather moving in, this was definitely the highlight of the night for James. #ZBB #Zamily10years  Thank… https://t.co/Iqw4a4oDbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCSDSuper @RyanBJackson1 @LakotaSuper @GLSSuperFalcon @cooperlearns @npolyak @BCESCsupt @DrBTroop @mikelubelfeld… https://t.co/KwSV4gubEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same old same old Acosta and left touted Texas town as one of safest cities in America, NY Times just uncovered ram… https://t.co/rkuRzNpLJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyWot No I meant matchbox 20 but I also second creed coming back as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a guest speaker today at work so I decided to get my #spartanburpees in before work started.  24 drop sets =… https://t.co/KvJXNCFgwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValorCollege @aaroncrabb79 @amandascrabb May God bless all of this and near or far everybody that loves this feels… https://t.co/morPZuSuBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA #MAGA #BERNIE #BIDEN #JusticeLeague #CoryBooker #Warren  We have a formidable enemy. Why go it alone? Why n… https://t.co/GoSntmgD4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakeboughie It would be perfect if we didn’t have to go down a flight of stairs for her to use the restroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future #Historians will caption a chapter for “The #TrumpPresidency: From Moscow to Migration to Migraines” And… https://t.co/UA8ZmKAv7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[— “Stay Hydrated, Stay Extra!” 👌🏼  This your daily dose of #CappuChiro , and now I wish you a wonderful day! ❤️🤣 (P… https://t.co/Bfi91t880b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It turned to a rant on college professors. Dr. Crowe's reaction: https://t.co/29jxQBMeeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeonnaPurrazzo @MartyScurll Also, that face you make when your friends want to go on the scary ride again, but you… https://t.co/G4L8MuVDiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano This all starts at the top! He has made it ok to be this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent planning time with the teachers at Sunrise this morning. I can’t wait to see the activities they have plann… https://t.co/SNx5jtcpM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Says the idiot who just voted to allow illegal immigrants to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor says #StephonClark death wounded Sacramento, calls for $200 million community fund (via @sacbee_news) https://t.co/jbqnMOjM08]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess it’s not so tough to go first. #3pointcontest #NBAAllStarSaturdayNight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasTribune @marfagringo So the bail system is the fault of republicans because democrats have never been in cont… https://t.co/aF1CpINn5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jic_tvasports Sprong est pharmacien ?  quel lancer précis une pilule top lucarne]]></document><document><![CDATA[The content that @denny_thompson and @biggamejames36 on @sportsDen_live is 🔥! But the music in between is always 💦💦💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blaireinfeldt @1000HolyPlaces @RichBeeker Good times!  I enjoy the debate]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #InternationalWomensDay (founded by the Socialst Party of America, but that is for another tweet), I want t… https://t.co/bF2kKKcJj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman Shatters The World Record For Burpees In An Hour While Also Doing Zero Burpees https://t.co/TB2gnXKOCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@filmphreak @e_mgarcia2002 @davidpakmanshow @realDonaldTrump That’s stupid!cohens going to jail , that’s who you Ike? Haa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamToddyTickles If I were you I’d try being nicer to people online, also maybe try and understand why so many peop… https://t.co/6zmUOU9wmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liljohnsonn ayyy I literally don’t think I own pants with belt loops 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apollo 11 on IMAX is something certain people will really enjoy. If this is you, we should talk about space stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all y’all saying #captainmarvel was trash really out here lying. wasn’t perfect, but far from trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceMatthews_ A great way to foster reflection, critical for facilitation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best wishes to all @CCSAthletics1 teams that begin play over the next few days. 👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew3sixteen Perfect. And if you need unreasonably strong opinions about Houston as the best food city in the US, I gotcha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKChilds If parent engagement or classroom instruction strategies do not explicitly address and foster parent und… https://t.co/AOinra5mjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenzo99 @shark_helmets @redbull @chupachups_es Those colors should look great with your new Repsol kit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby’s about to take the stage, and I’m about to throw up because makeup made her age 5 years...  don’t know how… https://t.co/XIjrcfrhah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great work. I'm glad I voted for you and will again next election]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedStryker @megmyers So Am I @TedStryker! So Am I! Let’s Get That @megmyers Interview Scheduled My Punk Rock Lovin… https://t.co/ozlq8mMARW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClassicFM973 Dionne Warwick Bally's #LasVegas  April 4th-6th,11th-13th, 18th-20th,25th-27th… https://t.co/UO2lcRi70Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mside_Baseball Love @rooster_O5 in left but when will he get his chance at catcher, his natural position? Also, di… https://t.co/yofXOYRSnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Innocent employees turned over a new Leaf all you poor bastards! Did it ever occur to you that there are o… https://t.co/jc8RtWbMI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9CShbvsyXq Ok...so we now live in a fucking world where there’s a ‘Copycat Doorbell Licker’. What in t… https://t.co/C2KnEHFbAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m guessing this guy became a Sixers fan again as of last year too... If you weren’t with us at the bottom then we… https://t.co/VEPUC6Todr]]></document><document><![CDATA[✅ Creating Syria’s first women’s soccer club ✅ Founding a library in a refugee camp in Turkey ✅ Building a hub for… https://t.co/lr6pXRfkb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got soaked with green tea... who knew I was on the splash zone of a Seaworld themed flight. Great start to my fligh… https://t.co/DJXbbrblyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTimbersFan Ha...no...other than DaMarcus apparently has some sort of Fountain of Youth thing going on. Not sure… https://t.co/rzx8fcAoZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN zero tolerance = zero intelligence. Not all rich people are bad. You should embrace those who are progressive in their thinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitol Hill Trump Republicans, just which country on  this planet did you take an oath to serve and defend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[film twitter trying to say glen close was robbed,,, have y’all seen the wife? Such a predictable plot with Glens ch… https://t.co/chL85p780O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BulldogPlayerDevelopment here’s a great version of #SimonSays 👇🏻👇🏻⚾️😊⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think for me it maybe was too realistic - there were some minigames but overall it was a lot of walking and talki… https://t.co/Do0gpjvKfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MTA Subway - Court Square (E/G/M/7) - @nyctsubway in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/g2GrdwALvN]]></document></documents></author>