<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey Toronto (especially those who are cold-weather❄️☃️ sedentarians) 👇👇👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping #ThankYou to all… https://t.co/nbpr4xYYVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uncgsports @UNCGBasketball Let’s GO “G”!!!! So proud of the Spartans!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can I not love him! Always making me feel like the most beautiful girl ever!!!!!🥰 https://t.co/a6aItepMZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dialect is a variety of language with a consistent set of rules, spoken by a certain demographic or regional grou… https://t.co/7ew1HNIvuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama @MichelleObama Yes beautiful and wonderful first lady ever. I miss her in the White House. We need you back President Obama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Too bad you don’t have a decent bone in your body, Eugene.  Did you feel bad when Dirty… https://t.co/qk5SWzKm43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avoid Las Vegas Blvd. and Flamingo just saw  police drama and really bad traffic jam on news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gowsy33 Ha, they both have one by that title! I HIGHLY recommend the Siddons one. One of my top 5 haunted house bo… https://t.co/M24iXOGH6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wyvern's Boysenberry Wheat by @LabyrinthBeer at @labyrinthbeer — https://t.co/AtJdiRKxaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets involve our rural schools in this experience@HamiltonMusical#ALL KIDScount#passionateadvocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whiteribbon @munkschool @shereenelfeki @MichaelGLFlood @GenderEQ Thank you for setting the stage, and your (seemin… https://t.co/lREwtrRgIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennSp33 @AndrewReyes3 @DrLeanaWen @PPact We see this totally differently and will never agree. Have a nice life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from the @KutztownU Annual Eductors Job Fair! KU Students: Stop by and visit Booth #87 and… https://t.co/eo7kCqgyrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC First off I thought she was retiring but I guess that $200K is going for a tanning bed, Botox and highlights!… https://t.co/yOuGOyty7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand how you could make your son go through so much pain and still not get him vaccinated...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colinodonoghue1 Great throw back. I've still never seen this movie, but my friend says it's great and I remember y… https://t.co/t280Z6JBaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my music randomly played the A Seat At The Table album but honestly not complaining, I think Apple knew I needed this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyPhilipps A while ago I decided not to be disappointed when I hear stories about men doing this, even if I admi… https://t.co/HzvbVJvvSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago, @BrianFox46 and I set out for Montreat, NC where Rev. Billy Graham spent his final days. Rest In Peac… https://t.co/k21MrLwX6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[people are saying that halsey downgraded yet g eazy cheated on her???? downgrade who?? fuck cheaters, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guzdial @diane_levitt @dianafenton1 @professorpetty5 @aderbenwick We talk about careers &amp; people @NCWIT… https://t.co/MdpExPfoTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve worked in entertainment my entire career. It’s exhausting loving Awards season whether you’re in the thick of it or not. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melissa71349052 @PrezHillary17 @Bravewriting I simply cannot understand that example.  I have lived among people w… https://t.co/GeoW6cg9sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest Thanks! I've made all kinds of graphics over the years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God blesses those who patiently endure testing and temptation. Afterward they will receive the …… https://t.co/v31D0TOZIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Irwin’s videos inspire my daughter to learn more about animals, their environment, and how to protect both. H… https://t.co/SPYNTrQbhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is insanity!@Headerop1 @BlogChurchWork @DearAuntCrabby @krassenstein @DanRather @JustaSlob @openpodbaydoor_… https://t.co/F3tH9mYoFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Zion Williamson for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/FJR3l4E6k0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentinesday vs Anti Valentinesday collaboration 💞 With the amazing @bossdivaanita  👉 I used all Avon makeup for t… https://t.co/ibDKrUv4Jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ploya29 I’m still shocked that’s SHE’S shocked. Like did.. did you think he’d be any different with you?! You reap what you sew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Influencer marketing now involves AI powered technology. It is no long a novelty - @ChrisDetert 🤩  #BISummit https://t.co/8MQ8CiLMvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great events, added to the SF Irish Film Docfest on March 2nd @sfirishfilm it’s going to be a great month!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! Why does @RHOBHLucy Lucy have a twitter page! Its like the dog that cant find a home for real! Did LVP do this… https://t.co/iD5e2YvbW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danidel62 @LeafsgirlSteph @WardenOfNuts @Zinaa008 @PaulaJR34 @IKRAVEMUSIC @TMLGAL @ericagnandt @hotlipsstewie… https://t.co/427xvbQHm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cori Jean Ice Cream Cart ! Back in the Park! Sweet Calm Day !  Super Sunday In McAllister Park ! —- Cori Jean Ice C… https://t.co/8v9fEYVTT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I just realized I haven’t had a “valentine” since I was like a sophomore in hs lmaooooo or was it senior year?… https://t.co/tRh3ar23T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I did my hair all through hs, I’m ducked up by both hs.. but anyway y’all aunt Sarah’s be hating but ima show u… https://t.co/cYITLTdOJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinnelonPSD Ts and Ss are we ready! Great opportunity for our students]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when people that took me for granted try and hmu again https://t.co/ZALGGvNsA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI, @benshapiro, the likes on your Media Matters article are not being documented correctly. How #weird.… https://t.co/QEHTXM7NFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EinsteinMaga @Aug1405 @aj2657 @Vizzpat @Briteeye777 @usanovak @CensoredC1 @Jdv74D @RealTT2020 @JulieReichwein1… https://t.co/zXpYYbyHcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intente ondular mi cabello con cremita para peinar y pues nada no se quedan 😭 a pero la señorita se echa tratamient… https://t.co/QV6PQPmTo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ultimatecircuit #studiofitness #fitfamforever #515crew #smile #getsummerready @ The Extreme Studio https://t.co/DRrvmKYTNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackTheLEOs @lt_kennedyfanpg @OfficialLivePD @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @FanpageLivepd @LivePDNation @LivePdFans… https://t.co/X4LlAiajgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day 💘  If you're 💓 secretly in 💕 love with a house on 💖 the market, speak up so I can play matchma… https://t.co/n5AgBDXYpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is in Portugal &amp; I’ve never been more jealous of somebody else’s Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[My MySpace tagline used to be “beast in progress” &amp; I really wonder when the progression stopped 🤔😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao @ paying $700 for ANYTHING that’s going to be done to my hair 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journaling is critical in getting to know yourself and hear your inner voice. Hear it first, then take action on it #MillennialTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[They got lucky tonight but they will still never win the championship they have no clue what team ball is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! I got my machine going again! It's the little and Huge things, lol! #sew #sewingmachine #mytherapy… https://t.co/cBPQKRk2j1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The tweets on this page are disgustingly disrespectful to Our President. Low info folk. So glad th… https://t.co/qJBLKEXsJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nick_lindquist Probably not but I’d FOR SURE want to know if a prospective employee of mine were a flat-earther, so good on him]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRAND NEW VIDEO 🚀  “Gotta heal my pain, gotta heal my pain..”  https://t.co/jHeJHrsyKE https://t.co/p4M8Gx5jxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydortiz @xMzAnnx @ohfloy @Chelsnii @Annjelife @Cinnpie @ohfloy needs to post the video 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burner2047 @PrimeVideo @neilhimself What do you mean by no offense when that is your intent? Jackass. Offense intended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctorsensation Yeah!!! Common sense has prevailed! https://t.co/a4rthbxu9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racist anti Semite filth.  Donald Trump’s long history of racism, from the 1970s to 2019 https://t.co/ClZcrUx4uI]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all our @UVUcomm peeps have a wonderful heart day. @UVUPRSSA #ValentineDay #Valentines2019 #uvu https://t.co/QEahHMnoTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaomiEsparza4 @catherinedoc12 @YsletaISD @MarioLu60247032 @CSeda3 @rita_tellez @swoo888 @adbrewer @michele82300765… https://t.co/BL0e6dc3iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure it is, for me! Put a smile on my face to see some unusual weather here in San Diego ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The refs here at Lipscomb love calling technical fouls. That’s been the case since Thursday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@60Minutes They like Russian it’s no us we never did that we never was there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timtimmons Thank you for inspiring me, filling my heart and inspiring my soul @Leavener this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could wish for anything it'd be not to be so sensitive to smells bc I went to bed at 7 and still woke up w a headache 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a few left, these botanical earrings. These beauties are inlaid with pink onyx and pearls. Available at… https://t.co/3lw4fgwRKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Cisco for sponsoring the @SiriusNews #SiriusKickoff19 What an amazing @Cisco National Team! That’s some… https://t.co/7HKp9oUJJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article. Challenging our thinking on ”what a school administrator /teacher is suppose to look like/act like ”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Nashville #Lexington #Louisville #Tennessee #Kentucky #WestVirginia #Arkansas #Alabama #Austin #Texas #Michigan… https://t.co/hJuPxk6D96]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t remember the last time my dogs shit outside 😩😩😩 # https://t.co/EM60NAm9Bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[GO AOC!   Ocasio-Cortez hopes to 'break this fourth wall' by responding to 'bad-faith attacks' https://t.co/mblP24AcUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop looking for excuses... Find reasons to improve yourself and achieve all your goals 💪🏽💪🏽💪🏽  #topeka… https://t.co/AW91frIMWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re here, after 2 days of being on the road! With my family — I’m happy!! Don’t quite know if I’ll be styling… https://t.co/75C4bD57GE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bipartisan public lands package (S. 47) would protect more than a million acres of wilderness, over 650 miles of… https://t.co/6SXvaYHPrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the airport. Probs not a good time to ask if Mexico has the same outlets as the US:]]></document><document><![CDATA[#babyboy he has to have his music @ Irondequoit, New York https://t.co/WJ8Qjm54Ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority just watched your appearance on The Mark Levin show‼️‼️‼️. Great job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miceli556 I really think your height hindered your professional scooting career, so I think maybe he doesn’t under… https://t.co/4ECp0LK59o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper were going to kiss after that performance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, says the gal who is teaching a “Make It Rain” workshop today... (That’s my “living a professionally creative life” workshop)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephPetticoat @CGage44663269 Sure, would you like to check out my new website?  Just one large painting sale wou… https://t.co/J7QAd1cizb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron 'Throwing People Under the Bus' Like Never Before, and NBA Is Baffled  https://t.co/utqE419UVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigcountryknox1 I don’t watch any of that garbage. I haven’t even watched the mainstream channels in 5-6 years 💩💩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen testified the president told him to make hush money payments to Stormy Daniels and he brought the rec… https://t.co/8p0ySR8O53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoDiscussions I never met the 4th, but I’m sure I would’ve enjoyed traveling through time &amp; space with him as much as I did DW10.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuroraKaril @adeladessire Ese pajarito se está gozando esa agüita de los dioses. Simple y hermoso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My crew! ❤️A quiet weekend away is just what I needed! #family #familydayweekend @ Fenelon Falls, Ontario https://t.co/J1SWTBULzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haar18gh Figure it out lol, but it’s ok though I’m just keeping my fingers crossed 🤞🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CV5sYpYp8V #betteroff by @Ookay was recommended to me by @marshmellomusic and it's a really great song to vibe out to! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[#❌marksfraud #nsnfraudsquad shutting 👇 be4 u can scam any1 dont know why ya mess with @kennychesney look at his tri… https://t.co/xIZKECUwfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Lift each other up, and know you are not alone!” -@gerri_elliott Register today for #WOI2019 #LoveWhereYouWork… https://t.co/haYQzD5fsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[La música es el lenguaje de Dios para conectarnos los unos a los otros de una manera sinigual, no importa de donde… https://t.co/WsOjETmU26]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending a great, big heartfelt thank you to @one_more_paige for inviting me to come read to and sing with over 200… https://t.co/ROQ9gQHkfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being straight is really hard to deal with. I wouldn’t wish this on anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not take me to the comfy theaters with the recliner chairs. I WILL fall asleep 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ONLY part I miss about being in school was seeing @sdanielleduncan @KAiLYN_ELiSE and @cdn_98 everyday 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ ITS HERE!!!!!!  💜💜💜Remember that awkward teen phase we all went through.... well these… https://t.co/gwzmQdwBO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans looks like we got the same sweetheart https://t.co/kKk0BxwwaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a woman and a feminist who has been working on opening up my concept of my privilege as a straight, able bodie… https://t.co/5v17jd1bfi]]></document></documents></author>