<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[NOW WHEN THE SAN DIEGO SHERIFF SET UP A BUMP AND STOP MURDER THEY BROADSIDED ME ON MY MOTORCYCLE THAT COST THEM OVE… https://t.co/I1QLNwoHY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RAMIREZBOXING talks @_garciapita @GarciaBoxing @ChonZepeda @mightymohooker @RPrograis @VasylLomachenko… https://t.co/114hSHBB6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[La verdad socialista de @petrogustavo   @hermanntertsch @cayetanaAT @cristiancrespoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWCEexpo We have a booth MCT26! Excited to attend! Come check us out. https://t.co/UOANwkJSGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A Game of Pool” S03E05: A bitter pool player gets a chance to play the ghost of the greatest. Better to watch as a… https://t.co/nemWbX0iUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Do as I say not as I do. True fascists dictator in the making. Grown &amp; raised by the leftist nation in the U.S.!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's becoming clearer and clearer EA pushed Apex Legends out early (and it's totally killing it btw) since they nee… https://t.co/g8n8Fs7ppo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Walt Disney Concert Hall Box Office in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/KcpbYkDo98]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I ordered chicken tenders today for lunch. It came with THREE ranch dressings TWO honey mustards and ZERO chicken tenders😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyfactor What the fuck dude hahahaha this is great. I want it so bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Why is he asking?  He does not need to ask, he can simply transfer funds from other allocations. Is this a… https://t.co/CNSHAKzB1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcgeorgemd OCT again after aspiration? In Europe, would this be a good case for coronary DCB?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrkevinconnolly @mirtle @NHL @NYIslanders #Isles fans couldn't find the high road if you drew them a map. Is a pla… https://t.co/8Lzr8YMbzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@migoodridge1 @cannaworldsite @Bklynbby @Raymosaki @Smokette_ @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @james_bong13 @_jena4n… https://t.co/UthnvzVVkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think some of you think you can uplift yourself without bashing/speaking down on another group of people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodrigothemexi @megynkelly She really should go back to her comfort zone Fox.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewT61830774 @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow Genesis 1:1 NIV [1] In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Democrat majority on House Oversight is really seeking the truth, Michael Cohen would be the last person they would want to hear from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot Valentine’s Date last night ⁦⁦@ChipotleTweets⁩ with ⁦@bethketz⁩. https://t.co/Ja5LrVq3mD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ce n'était pas parfait mais le collectif semble avoir fait un 180 degrés cette année, c'est prometteur. #imfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Renea_Rose @itsJeffTiedrich There was a group of people who all killed themselves because some idiot told them th… https://t.co/G8PerKSYyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think one of the biggest problems these days is that a majority of people want to get all the respect without giving any]]></document><document><![CDATA[FEC gives Jeanine Pirro 24 hours to stop flouting law and come clean on 14-year-old campaign debt https://t.co/PGnuhJCQPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohio’s 44th Congressional District should be beaming with pride — Rep Jim Jordan epitomizes everything wrong with w… https://t.co/MetFtP7Snt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisSeveren I agree with @marcfbellemare. I received precisely such an appeal as an editor, changed the decision… https://t.co/mabMc11o0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriciajaniot @jorgeramosnews No le hagan propaganda al progresista Jorge Ramos. Ese puto ha sido una piedra en e… https://t.co/f7GL6MeO8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson You are compromised Donny!   You are unfit for office !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The extent to which you care for your employees is the extent that they will care for your customers and each othe… https://t.co/GcylQd702G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BKBoheme Cognitive dissonanse is a powerful drug. So set against the overpolicing of black lives, that she'll defe… https://t.co/W1IFpFFBD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats "Speedy" very proud of you #RustburgPride @ Rustburg, Virginia https://t.co/fw1DEKb0XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could get a picture of a sign I just passed that said "stay behind plows and spreaders"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Days till Captain Marvel: 9  Days till Avengers End Game: 57 Days till Detective Pikachu: 72   #CaptainMarvel… https://t.co/YEj4e4CnjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @RonDeSantisFL This is a real governor not like the dopes in new York and California proud to live… https://t.co/F3itmFjlgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored and blessed to be part of the Pinnacle Family👍💯🏀 @PinnacleBball @SpencerRattler @niccolomannion  https://t.co/XbB2wjmeou]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Giants’ Stephen Vogt thrilled to play in his first game in a year - San Francisco Chronicle: Giant… https://t.co/89QN23PVAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penotpa On a lighter note, you just made “like buns” my new favorite thing 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the goat @Brandon_Koch12 Best pic of us that I have... https://t.co/YXm9QspmKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/vFANs2R5rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mississippi / Alabama State Line in Cuba, AL https://t.co/GnLW8IoYkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoodleyDownard @wiaawa Girls like to roll their shorts...why would you want to??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylamb8 @DavidGPuppet Once again, how do the best teams manage to lose away games?  Must not be very good teams.… https://t.co/bdRYEY9LXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[my injury really set me back emotionally and mentally. I’m glad I’m back in El Paso so I can recoup, get healthy, g… https://t.co/M4n4aC23as]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltzVegas That’s incredible. What a rip off. $1000 just to watch a game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMO: u know what irks nee today. the music people bump on the block, on the streets, out the jeeps, i’m sorry shits… https://t.co/lBfU2L3zjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirenmiren Thanks! I’m basically an old man! 😅  (Note: this would literally take me 59 years of growing out my fac… https://t.co/sqjcn4QBNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Duro999 @ManUtd @premierleague Un sacrilegio no ver al equipo del DT que “inventó el fútbol”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatVince84 @LadyLondonnn @__Ardyy Bro I been tryna marry her for the past year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brad_Hope @580Sportstalk Jerry Ford was a former Michigan football player.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuandaryMan I saw it once. Shared it. A few folks showed. It's all Sam L's show. I dug it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hillarynkirby bah! well, if want to go real big, just do Canlis or the Herb Farm over in Woodinville. On the more… https://t.co/mKywh331on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WXgage Them cowboys of Oklahoma be like giddy up https://t.co/gzmsQ2m91i]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my bday!! Gained enough experience to level up. Let’s see what new adventures open up! #blessed #31yearsyoung… https://t.co/IyZwsTGs91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewasears That relegates each to propaganda, with negative value for humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsKristinaHo I missed it for the 2nd week in a row and I actually tried getting up early to watch it but I was so… https://t.co/tSlhy8RqA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Seven Dwarfs Mine Train - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/SQ5bOJ4kyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laura I’m a fan of your show and laughed my ass off tonight. You spotlighted our couture. And that’s cool. I’m so g… https://t.co/aDmCYx6sjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[As freshman, I had a pretty good idea these @NessCityMBB seniors would be special, simply from their work ethic, an… https://t.co/gaPHTl94UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up everymorning at 4:50am and I sleep at 12 every night pero aki ando al cien 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wcXfYkBxvh #HollywoodRockStars #JamesPaulRowland #MotownNow #HazardousMusicPublishing #DopeGurlMusic… https://t.co/KQfn6H7d9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reboot What if Siri and Alexa actually encouraged us to unplug?! That’s the premise of our new parody, launched in… https://t.co/XEmCic2TUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heavens declare the glory of God; the skies proclaim the work of his hands. Day after day they pour forth speec… https://t.co/nBVSHFknuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdarrenwhite Get back on your meth habit and kick the tired in the pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was real Philly! Until next time. @ Philadelphia International Airport https://t.co/HowqxrAhzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjaniCarter3 @Ezmoneyquez @stacmaycash @JaayUpNext_ @JetJt50 @rayganryaan4 @KarienHoward1 @ballout_gyasi @cdotcaash_ 💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micheilemmett His biggest thing besides the concussions was he wasn't the best skater right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed Captain Marvel! I am so glad I got to see it opening night! And I'm glad I got to watch it at Alam… https://t.co/kWiKWkETDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[hahahahahahahhahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha the steelers with one of the pettiest moves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peep my New song “All Night” (Prod. By mellowthing_ )| Dedicated to that special someone that get’s your pants tigh… https://t.co/VO9h4sxRcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got Leia! | Quiz: Which Woman of the Galaxy Are You? | https://t.co/1ctuVj0XoG https://t.co/cnPg3ND2Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ewarren is a thoughtful foe of unaccountable power. The digital-social platforms have metastasized into just that… https://t.co/FsvZtxRMjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremiahHorriga @RawStory Any sentence that begins with "Susan Collins may . . ." Is not worth reading.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Trump say ‘true’ when called a sexual predator in 2006 https://t.co/Q1AuS3UIN2 # via @HuffPostWomen… https://t.co/Ihv9etV8yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi As usual Senator your lying needs to be fact checked. Congress gave him the power. How c… https://t.co/0tKGe7JDoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rokjohnson @erik_engquist @AOC @amazon I’m assuming you’re just applying the NYC income tax of roughly 3.5%, which… https://t.co/9ry5FeClIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hmfaigen Nah Caruso is very good defensively.  I would love to see him lonzo and Bi playing defense together.  Maybe next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Westgate Entertainment District in Glendale watching and listening to the Brightside. https://t.co/hiXGWtNZmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You sure if you are missed out on this week's episode check it out right here  https://t.co/3fJs9ufAre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t sell them this asset in the first place. They really are not a true ally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adnlewis @RadioGunk @PageSix He listens to a radio guy and thinks hes making a difference but all he does really is talk shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritta_oh Excellent!!!*** the reason most Believers don't enjoy reading the Word is because they really do not kn… https://t.co/8kU1fuBJZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would fuck the Cash Me Outside Girl right in front of you and not think nothing about it no matter how old she is… https://t.co/ujDnJ5jx7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is, A GoodDay, In WISCONSIN..🐺🌹🇺🇸 😇😁😏.... Hmmmm.... ? @ Veteran's Manor https://t.co/CAXZRTHRTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Party Bus VIP Party Club Tour for all y'all 3 Clubs 1 Night On Party Bus with Free drinks Going to Hexx Lounge, Tao… https://t.co/3PonLRCbq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just kidding more players are filing out. Looks like power play units had some extra work before practice got going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattScalici @AaronSuttles @HunterLJohnson @Ascot_Friday This is your fault. That’s why they call you Scamlici!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_suigeneris Nice and healthy yes, but you gotta think about it sometimes boys can get picked on at school for h… https://t.co/ENp0GdWZxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit I like the way. they always catch this photos to make people look bad, your kidding me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir messed up my reservation so bad that I had to request a full refund. I called multiple occasions and m… https://t.co/KmU7CN1O1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I have an alternate version of his statement. Justice is closing in, your time is near, sleep well… https://t.co/bCei8hSVMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuggieSmith @anylaurie16 And this supporter of your comedy remembers you making fun of Tom Griswold for assuming a… https://t.co/pcOQbjkuRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_feral1 T. is very diverse-so Native racism is low on the radar. Ppl here pride thmselves on being on "THIS" li… https://t.co/kcfozmOrgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soccertvblog @Fanatiztv @beINSPORTS Wonder if Fubo is happy about that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We shouldn’t be debating anymore about what’s happening with climate and weather...we need to build on our track r… https://t.co/yCh2g8JO2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you pull to the house blasting Chalino Sanchez and walk in nobody wakes up! 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savvyconsumer7 @jonz970 @MagaHansen @Ken19512 @Sequencer16 @annmarienyc @scallawag3 @Crusader_Miles @John_R_Berna… https://t.co/aWeKrlwEcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @BillWeirCNN CNN no they are not. Only those paid by the Mexican cartels don't want a WALL like CNN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dig if you will #snow #toronto #dammit @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/F4iqzrpo4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight while riding the train home a group of people started kicking around a bottle cap that was on the subway fl… https://t.co/PXBBjrUi7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djcarisma  -  2019 is all about giving respect where respect is due!  @djquik @tunein youngcalifornia @ Burbank, C… https://t.co/Jmycf1cqAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKRobinsonEDU @Coach_CGreen @westlakelions @FultonAD_crafts Congrats Team!]]></document></documents></author>