<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[There is not much better than chocolate milk in my yeti to get me ready for the day. #nopenotcoffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally warm enough to get outside. 😊 Been a long winter.  Ready for spring. https://t.co/2RE05JAKTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Dawntless_ I like to accept that it doesn’t really affect me...😅🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The actual term for morning wood is called “Nocturnal Penile Tumescence.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the 2019 ncaatrackfield Indoor #TrackAndField season comes to a close, it's so cool to see the immediate impact… https://t.co/KDOctCNqdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a joke, right??? If not, can someone explain to me why people are getting kicked off Twitter for saying thi… https://t.co/GY57uqjGbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFC_Airborne51 @CaptainFutureee @BeauRogers12 @thehill We can, we just don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It blows my mind how insanely good @billieeilish’s music is. Music industry please do not ruin this incredible young woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrienneTarth6 @RSun82 @hotmess50162764 @EmmyStar79 @seraphicpetal I got you Brie you already know..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sixers’ Joel Embiid and  @BenSimmons25 playing in #NBAAllstar2019 is proof of The Process at work https://t.co/cdQMvVIuuR via @phillydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enholli Not me but a couple of my friends do that. I think they usually put in one that has a small opening so the… https://t.co/Xbj3Fvm4Ic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassiejobe Go to the zoo. The snake exhibit there will be a lot cheaper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TourSportsman @AlexMyers3 And I've seen a DQ for this exact thing. Happened 2 years ago with a guy in my 3some, st… https://t.co/UCikK8BhTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[this was probably my favorite song a few years ago its still good https://t.co/vcmS4NWw4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[After careful field research, I’ve found that binging a TV show with 20-30min episodes is waaaaaay more dangerous t… https://t.co/GYDP4BMy2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We need to stop the CIA from having a regime change for oil.” Via @FluorescentGrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNMOONCHILD @DollyVol @GTA_Redhead @Santa_Vol @GoVols1914 @GoBigDamnVols @Smokeyholler @Nick23929445 Thanks buddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtsandClouds @YouTube Thanks @ArtsandClouds the process is dehumanizing Workplaces and creating a level of Social… https://t.co/PfxQEMJrXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom @netanyahu buddy @realDonaldTrump is responsible for this. Like the anomaly of "Pro-Life" Trump @GOP Re… https://t.co/0E7vxxvqXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper has a number 1 on the Billboard Hot 100... something Nicki Minaj has yet to achieve]]></document><document><![CDATA[New @dabombfizzers #bathbomb thanks to reznin @ College Park (Orlando) https://t.co/rdehZDLJb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what! @Skyleigh_Ann and I started a podcast! Here’s the first episode where we brag about our long distance r… https://t.co/n7wpWuBBXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might’ve gave my son up for adoption if I was to see a video of him like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staredcraft @tristen_just I think she is just too toxic at this point. Honestly would seem like a big Fuck You to… https://t.co/Ol0R8zSWMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumps lie for the day: Democrat Party is anti-Jewish Party   What a propagandarist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, you’ve got to have Deflated balls after a prostitution arrest. Deflate Gate The Sequel. #DeflateGate2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow We could use that money towards Wall, instead robbing taxpayers money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #MalibuDanTheFamilyMan And I don’t want to have Mac &amp; Cheese anytime soon... @DavidARWhite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pplscourt @KFCBarstool Cowboys haven’t really been winners in his lifetime lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJSmith53533 Turning off lights, picking up trash, petting the dog, scratching my own back, taking food out of the… https://t.co/O7UtWxQlQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @MarkWKSU for taking a Silent Disco tour of @playakron with us. Stop by Art x Love’s studios at 157 King… https://t.co/DiFGkPDQFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Cats fuel on Michael’s secret stuff in the second half playoff win. Helping Walker to pull away for a 55-38 wi… https://t.co/9efH59tGig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime in Emery...SD Region 5B Tournament...Bridgewater-Emery 35 Irene-Wakonda 30...With a 3pt basket in the 2nd… https://t.co/5QbPDNwGeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[📱📱 Tired of scratching your thumb?? 📉📉📉 Need your iphone fixed for the low??? HMU we have the lowest prices in the… https://t.co/ygIiAbRLgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching a British TV show and they just found a single shoot gun with 5 bullets in a suspects home. The police… https://t.co/ahevpLVf2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Chcago Institute for Vocal Care for the great info on voice care for while traveling. #vocalhealth… https://t.co/VKUhQLsXhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHappyMargarita Dona no está mal, es el informal de done. Sí es gracioso. 🍩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna fight each and every one of yall that told me YOU on Netflix was dope. https://t.co/XLNeBmxwYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/XsCxng6KK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JariedScantron Not really, once conference play starts most every game is pretty fun to watch wether it be ACC, SE… https://t.co/DkoUrOEHuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikschlitt Played 30/32 games the past 2 seasons was surprisingly nice to see.   60 catches 600 yards probably wo… https://t.co/TzxoiWECZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to become famous so I can convince the media to push my anti-coleslaw agenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of Western Washington University's most famous alumni are teaming up for a stacked Civic Stadium concert to be… https://t.co/ulfXCoUUrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews @RepMGS Rep. Scanlon, I still have concerns over your hesitancy to support #NetNeutrality legislation.… https://t.co/f6hw6DJtjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlucas405 @sjoblom_erik @OKCKaraLynn Who cares!!!! It’s just fun anyways. 🤪🤪🤷‍♂️🤷‍♂️ And it is “He’s” or “He is” and it is also “Didn’t”]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOLF EYES = HIDE = DAUGHTERS = MASQUERADE ATL 2KNIGHT!! THE GOOD TIMEZ THEY DON'T STOP FAM https://t.co/4E7lmJG5Nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squadron Leader Hassan Siddiqui in a Hot Scramble - JF-17 Shooting Down ... https://t.co/WRyKMJXBoP via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnThacker2 @wrs1260 This is truly truly murder and democrat support it because they want to control how many vote… https://t.co/gxnn18VRbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[That wasn't a prediction it was a spoiler by @JCLayfield @JohnCena album you can't see me did indeed flop #SmackDown299]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFLMAVERICK I love how the organization appreciates what there doing. I also love, How It’s Built. I can’t wait to… https://t.co/bnOVRtZan0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How ANY advertiser can put their brand behind this cretin is astonishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetJonesPHD @RealLifeKaz Yup. No one buries their talent that they're simultaneously trying to get over more tha… https://t.co/HiQUMDok2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotoriousStephs Fukking ........thank you !!! On curtain aspect fukk yesss]]></document><document><![CDATA[The super soft wide neck women’s “eagle and rose” sweater🦅🥀#ironandinkfitness  https://t.co/F42oZk1TQ8 @ Minneapoli… https://t.co/DtNndu75Ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kruppe_ @stevegress19 @BenLeid @Taylor_holder11 @walkerriney Eh, I bet you guys will be able to keep it close for a few minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you in Philly, and in Brooklyn, and a few other places if I can help it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kailyn to Maki: "We do not volunteer. (To go on the block.) We don't do it."   #BBCAN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patimoma56 Muy buenos días para ti también Paty y feliz jueves saludos cordiales y cuídate mucho,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for a pizza. This works... - Drinking a Stone Tangerine Express IPA by @StoneBrewing @ Golden Crust Pizzeri… https://t.co/ZG2liyfv8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorBennet @GovofCO @COAttnyGeneral And yet you support the red flag law. Feel free to choke on your hypocrisy.… https://t.co/Oqho7qbvYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black students protest in the student center and get suspended without any of this “investigation”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints - Siloam Springs AR https://t.co/dPEfRVspZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarsen I agree with you. So yeah, beyond my point of needing very advanced maths to push the industry forward, som… https://t.co/HcMwGOrbNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimension7films great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my latest horror film review PSYCHO SHARK https://t.co/KQQWhoAmGr https://t.co/hc7onvljg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re currently living in a 21st Century Mexican Film Renaissance. 🇲🇽 🎥 🇲🇽 #Maestros  @RealGDT @AlfonsoCuaron… https://t.co/s7JUkqSs08]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Island City, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/NoYzb1eWBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ratio of people who are alcoholics is comparable to those who are on sleeping 💊 pills @say_blk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAntWright Ehhh. MSU switched on the PNR. Half the time, you had a guard on Teske. They didn’t throw the ball do… https://t.co/x2t09MjA2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of 1 (Solon district semifinal - Division I): @raidersofshaker 17, @TwinsburgTigers 10 #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyEPIP @DecolonizWealth Send me pics, Tweets, videos and IGs!  ;). Seriously, I’d love to hear your thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 305 DAY TO THE CRIB‼️🏝🌆🙌🏼 #OnlyONE #InventedSWAGGER #BuiltDIFFERENT #MakeTheCribGREAT https://t.co/nGfcWg7ieO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexican and Asians babies are Mexicans real shit. 😂😂 when u go out just peep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeRealTV @budcrawford402 he's going to KO Kahn! Body Blow Body Blow Jaw!!!💣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is barbaric!  Please sign this petition!  End the trade of shark fins in Canada, Now! #care2… https://t.co/HiFJx7bUqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Dusty - his legs stopped working so my dad made him this thing #AmericanHero #birdperson https://t.co/StTP3JxWae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never mind "Send that to me. I'm going to cum to it" definitely takes home the cake]]></document><document><![CDATA[The game didn’t matter because this picture was all that mattered today https://t.co/fGbCWFWvjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Guest Services Representative - https://t.co/uExYRJHzAy #Simon #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my best buddy Marie are going to bowling as our hangout and played three games from Saturday @ Auburn, Alaba… https://t.co/JXvrzzSW9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aseguró que le va gustar correr 🏃‍♀️ 🏃‍♀️ 🏃‍♀️ came on came on en Vero Beach, Florida https://t.co/PbkD2YPJPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Honest question.... What’s the point of any FI doing their job correctly if they will just hand a TS… https://t.co/BVHqd19F2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Ophelia #TheBand #jamband #southernrock #NCMusic #NorthCarolina #supro #fender #tele #cleantone @ Southern Pines,… https://t.co/DXm8uDkvNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaneStephen @DTV89 @nrbauer Oh I’m here for it. Idea 1; there needs to be a small group of people that never let… https://t.co/66g2RUfa03]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awakening leads us to a calm self-awareness  that naturally gives of itself to others.  #awakening… https://t.co/IlCJ9O6fCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRachelGeller @lifetimefitness @ABDollyPlus Holy Moly Rachel I think I just dislocated my hip looking at this pic !  Amazing job !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice thread on comical “science” in a real journal (with the upside of showing how small n when there’s plenty of d… https://t.co/l6oAcFFpFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you to Border Patrol and ICE – we need to give them all the resources they need to do their… https://t.co/iled47kQIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannimalStyle @GeorgeStrait @bobbybonesshow They was very accurate for us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BangerFilms Any update to offer on the Triumph documentary? https://t.co/nphjDK7q1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlband777 @KurtSchlichter No one is defending the remarks.  We're defending Tucker from the quote-mining outrage… https://t.co/1fa06OhQLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RingFalcon @smarktodeath @OldSkewlPantz @JustJeremyHeyYo @ImmortalOne76 @RudeTexasKitty @Jrpwain @kirkjoh29180161… https://t.co/QqsMoCG4S5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CRichardNM @joyousgarratt Nope! I wish Rep. Garratt well and hope she does a tremendous job for our district. But… https://t.co/IXEckl7ZDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FollowFriday @TasiaValenza NY, New York's gorgeous actress with the gorgeous brown eyes! #AllMyChildren #StarTrek… https://t.co/ZtpFSsTdMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm thinking Scottsdale should own at least 1 snow plow.  Pictures been Pima/Cave Creak to the Bartlett  turn off a… https://t.co/oihxk5wpLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueWave2020NY @armandodkos Oh definitely. She's the perfect social media social democrat. A big reason I back Klo… https://t.co/3bTrCRNBcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthernlionLP "I also don't enforce them, I just make arbitrary utterances."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaux Bridge leads Bossier 27-15 at the half.  @OTBSports_ @PrepHoopsLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Dr. Seuss! 5 life lessons we learned from the author https://t.co/30A9kBCQqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Drum Heads Hosting Carlos Adames in the segment “A day in a percussionist life". (Performing on @tocaperc Custo… https://t.co/pTZdtnmPIO]]></document></documents></author>