<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MrJerryOC was so good to see you back on Wendy today! Loved the red suit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no way that I’m opening an email from 1969, especially if it isn’t from somebody I know. #getout… https://t.co/2xhWgttHYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darylsturgis I can’t believe that there are people now who don’t understand how bonkers it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive Affirmations Almost done with this beauty 😍 #blacklove is the theme for this one. Wanna see more? Check… https://t.co/sQc0Vm4sfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our THS Noys Bowling Team 2019 Regional Champions 🧡🖤🎳😊❤️ https://t.co/AR5bvur01t]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year difference. Same friends different outcome 🤟🏻 https://t.co/zd1mR8uQY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chanstormAD @PRMTrailblazers @ChaskaHawks Awesome crew and even better peeps!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is about reveal everything He spoke to in private!!!!! Smile.....He trusts you &amp; He chose you!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was suffering and in pain. So I went and had the most amazing #acupuncture treatment with Danielle at acupuncture… https://t.co/CHtVphj80F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it runs. And I love it. #golden #co #latergram #oldtrucks #iheartmountains #mountains #jacksonhole @ American M… https://t.co/UfzaFp4PIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encaustic class today - I have room for you too-See what you can do with encaustic wax!! Join us today in my studio… https://t.co/Zy2kJutcsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey I believe @SenFeinstein has written an actionable Bill for the Senate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes that is what you need.  ✌🏻 @ La Canada Flintridge, California https://t.co/cfI4rJZQ2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #shutdownstory for Scholastic News Kids Press Corps @Scholastic @KidsPress by Maryland reporter Grac… https://t.co/CzERJqf28U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then I take a look at the FB pages of diehard Trump supporters. The takeaway: Trump is God’s anointed… https://t.co/txv4b4LKOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@313Mikal @davidhogg111 if @davidhogg111 said that then I'm very disappointed in his tactics-a shame since always a… https://t.co/JBphvzUmhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another get up and make it happen on the road kind-of day and so grateful to be in this beautiful place… https://t.co/YWUccrhPAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[200 years from now when they dig up HER bones. They’ll discover SHE gave birth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WAS THINKING OF GOING TO STARBUCKS TO GET AN ICED AMERICANO AND THIS POPS UP. I’m just... https://t.co/qmCyH1vhHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i’m ever laughing for no reason it’s probably because i’m thinking about the episode of the good place when elea… https://t.co/8psz0mR1Ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past year has been a curiously inspiring one. I’ve travelled alone quite a bit. I’ve gone out by myself quite a… https://t.co/HSzaQJlqoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr And the Trump's should be held responsible.  He lied and crooked deals with your father punk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aférrate a lo que te hace diferente. Si esperas el momento oportuno, es este.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed home with our little peanut... Can’t even imagine the adventures that await! 💕😊🥰 @ Union Hospital (Indiana) https://t.co/PX3oH2NfGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Will MEXICO pay for it? That was the campaign promise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasHumor Yes I want 4 spicy ketchups.  #mybackups #eatingasyougo #workfromtruck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT my WatchTV  doesn’t let me log in? #customersupport https://t.co/08lx1sKl2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Democrats want to get rid of the electoral college -- OMG. They are so corrupt.  Hiding their true intent… https://t.co/meC8V0gbBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use this link, i get points and you get a free week at edge fitness... Win win!  https://t.co/k26is8f4OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParadisoPresent @Insurance716 @MikeStromsoe @DLYother And massive thanks to you @ParadisoPresent for all the value… https://t.co/5y7oOSIueq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlanketFortBlog It's an app called Dollify! 😍 it's like making a Sim of yourself but with doll like features!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I said “no, actually none of you guys tipped me, but if you’re here to give me something I’ll take it” and he di… https://t.co/L4syy845ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Javier Camarena @tenorjcamarena en @MetOpera: un orgullo de #México. https://t.co/OTjGTe2mRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like a band called @themaine, pink boba, pink hair, and Sundays. https://t.co/4wCalyiDpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneyellis @aprilfiet @srdlobdell @annawoof @AymieJoi @flemingrut Received!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a difference between a girl that wants your number and a woman that’s your CALLIN☎️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaMonsta1980 @SheDatWeDat @technics117 @Ballislife @shaqtin That's because he cares about him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wweevolution #tonistorm #tonitime #wwe #wweuk #myc2 #maeyoungclassic #astormiscoming 😍💋🎩🕶 #progresswrestling… https://t.co/nLV4GinvF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Yes.  And he's the white supremacist... so why arent the left screaming immediately for her to denounce this!??!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bishophilliard always knows what we need #firstfamilyconference #aim #aimstrong @ New Light Christian Center Church https://t.co/CAi51OVjda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrHosPITTality @duntaej Come on bro, I gotta eat my food and finish my meal!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[why dudes get so aggressive when you turn them down? Like shit you wanna fight? Cause we can]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were in middle school in the mid 90s - early 2000s you need to watch PEN15 on Hulu right now. 🦄@pen15show… https://t.co/sLJNbhY1tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenDippel @ajholda @HKorbey @jwaters1607 @NYschoolSecrets voila! https://t.co/f20SjzyVTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernardoFarina @RevistaLeyendas @Facupy01 @CamisetaGuarani @CorazonAborigen @soydelaborigen @Aurinegro1903… https://t.co/sfrIEqFd5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody ever notice when Nancy is speaking and holds her hand up in gesture they often do the Spock thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Umbral_Ice You know you still have my number and are welcome to use it at any time... right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gage_kristi @RealDeanCain Yes, truly precious!!!  Thank you fir sharing and making my morning!!!  🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷👏👏👏🌈❤️🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[my uber driver missed every single turn. but sang george strait with me the whole way. five stars for u !!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @krassenstein He’d be more safe with a lobotomy. He’s a vile traitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some great new music man!  Vivian’s solo is awesome of course. That man can work that ol’ Les Paul baby of his. Enj… https://t.co/KvsTNx79AB]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this laughable there's something wrong with you. #funniness #giggle #grin #comic https://t.co/MBfgwGYsvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What keeps us tethered as teachers? What keeps our Ss tethered?Thoughts to ponder!! Rick Wormeli  @GAGCGifted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonhider @JoseGonz321 @pavsaund @pryelluw @ReidNEvans @Odytrice @rick_pack2 @raelyard @pepopowitz my hubs ran outs… https://t.co/1GEYQpyvyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs My guess is they will all be Democrat Liberals...but let's just wait &amp; see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We make a living by what we get, but we make a life by what we give. https://t.co/pGBm92XmKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSmartChic Happy International Women’s Day! Have an awesome day Cynthia😊 https://t.co/FUFcP4tDcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyGuerin3 @ShawsvilleMS @MCPS_VA_Gifted @MarkMiear Congratulations 🎊!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 He can make up any crap and R’s just clap.  And Rupert spews hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALRIGHT HANDLEY FAM!! Tomorrow’s the last day of Read Across America Week and we defs gotta finish strong with “Oh,… https://t.co/wiEbRpbH1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Ilemona EVERYONE can thank Buhari for corruption tyranny economic failure and no electricity The investors we… https://t.co/U4wkocWGdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eerie looking sky in Mount Juliet. #Flood2019 #Nashville https://t.co/yQ18ZTjs7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Leaders goal: Always be learning, never stop growing, keep on forgiving, stir up your envisioning. The BEST is yet… https://t.co/usMsaZZNlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to welcome the newest member to the club!! Reddie legends keeps growing. 6 years = 6 legends. https://t.co/at4UDQXi0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lecture this afternoon given by #DavidKaplan, an award winning legal affairs writer at the O’Donnell auditorium… https://t.co/CUR0qL7R9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five Female Superheroes Who Deserve Solo Movies  https://t.co/ZVsF8PP1aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenGoruk I switched my phone to British Man and it's very calming.  I can't get mad at Siri when he's all Brit… https://t.co/ueRJ0WtftP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaSilvaFOX5 @FOX5Vegas Yaaaaay, I get to freeze in my room, yesterday our cold air kept blowing all day. 😰 Well time to get ready.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AmityRegion5 hey it's Suzanne from @News12CT. Still trying to reach your superintendent for comment on a story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone come to my job and get your washed, blow dried &amp; styled for the fuck fest you’re going to have tonight 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2_vigilance @JAMenziesAuthor @nytimes The taxpayer has no place in this calculation. Don’t even try it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexiwah I never said you were wrong 😂 Take it how you want it. My entire point is that everyone is going to call i… https://t.co/B24vvGbkRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago and today! Same place! #acuatica waterpark Orlando ❤️ https://t.co/TXyFixhZIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Influenster @lushcosmetics Cup o Coffee is my favorite scrub mask ever! They make the best bath bombs, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morse109 @enneazetton @DC_ARVSgt @libertyhq Enz needs to go hug a tree ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today years old when I found out there’s a joe dirt 2 https://t.co/Vot6IU7zfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for my daddy hat to come in so @danielleybellyx &amp; I can twinnnn👯‍♀️👯‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @VOISINE01 @JussieSmollett Where is Hollywood's hero #EllenPage? She needs to apologize to the Vic… https://t.co/mx9T1I4bxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing that hour of sleep is actually killing me on the inside right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanmcsorley @tara_atrandom But jobs won't do good if there's not enough resources for us to eat. Thanos said ther… https://t.co/My40vWRZjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaLuizito @rosecooleredboy @MariaEd07812623 @GuilhermeBoulos Dukevir(sec19):"Não tem jeito pq o público (maioria)… https://t.co/oiES4HuGKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[CT Flower Show- excited to be here in Hartford as this is SPRING #ctproperties #CTflowershow #hartford… https://t.co/hxe6Y2qssp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colfer36 @EricaRN4USA @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump No, only his daughter is Jewish. That’s not how it works with bein… https://t.co/Vf1DYGwaoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We dug deep into The Old Well to pull out these Air Jordan IV UNC Retros. #AJ4 #1989 #GDTBATH #GoHeels https://t.co/cv09Fqf6Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wir sagen:   Mehr Feminismus wagen!   #weltfrauentag @spdbt @spdde #mehrdemokratiewagen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbelanger12 But why do I need someone to help me rise up. why should I need them why can’t I just be able to rise up if I want to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t even know how much I can’t wait to see @Carlie_Marie15 again😭💙   I LOVE YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLinWood Goodness gracious, loooonnng time coming, to correct  reprehensible behavior! ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[oooh if there’s good music in this one Jay’s gonna be hating me for a while]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone who is always promoting the importance of #MentalHealth this disturbs me to my core.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my Dad’s legacy and the opportunity for transplant recipients!#denverfoundation #organdonation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats #ChicagoPD for your diligence uncovering truth. "Unfair to true victims who don't receive same attention a… https://t.co/rYWy55XoYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to hear the birds and their territorial calls in the morning, even with the windows shut #Spring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec why do you persist and pushing these lies I thought you were a Christian 👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @graceann297 very deserving!! Thank you for being a great mentor to @laurenelise211! 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resumidamente: ela é a minha parceira de viagem, e toda viagem que a gente faz juntas e perfeito, a gente da certo… https://t.co/Fwp676BzAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrezHillary17 Thank goodness it seemed confusing to me especially after all the anti Semitic crap and Israel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSMT88 @GMSarli @TrulyRowena @SallyAlbright She's not hiding Anything. Ask kamala anything and she answers with out obfuscation]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOOM: America Gets The Last Laugh After Father Of Alabama ISIS Bride Sues Trump https://t.co/SqezQEJAoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liberalsblow100 @ReaganWorld Now time magazine is controversial? When did that happen?]]></document></documents></author>