<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at Ruby Buffet International Style in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/S4AzEug0d5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoItsFredo @AGBecerra @realDonaldTrump I'm done, but I'LL add this cause it looks like I'M a great deal older than… https://t.co/lr7CDHpuX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jykrgr @JonBoyDavis @CaptainBetty @LeslieTeston @mattdudleydrums @rbeef81 @muxmike @EmptyPageStudio @PearlDrumCorp… https://t.co/jZt25GNQDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in stock! #who needs one of this in their life? #rmcdesign #cruzmadeit #woodworking #cruzwiththegoodwood #slg… https://t.co/NaTS60BpRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youreanyaway @sightDOING Will you be there for 5 de Mayo? If so, Puebla has an amazing parade and festivities for… https://t.co/rI90CCxcDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews All of this was done to me in Bedford Pennsylvania with sexual abused mom is Donna Day step father Jes… https://t.co/EVKKBE2ExW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Nicolle, I'm putting this squarely on ur shoulders. I'm missing too much work because of u. I have… https://t.co/6t2B0RR1p3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to have received an offer from Michigan ‼️@Coach_SMoore https://t.co/gpF8dXZGN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fun thought😀, the 81 letters sent by the house to so many Trumperos💩  has increased the the number of arrows Tru… https://t.co/YzufyWuPkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dems are in the middle of a tantrum right now because crooked Hillary lost and they just can’t get over it, lik… https://t.co/oXnt279Pt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[She donating her Willie Brown Knee Pads for his Prison stay with Bubba new cell mate]]></document><document><![CDATA[👁 This eye was 3-D printed! #HealthTech @IrmaRaste @eViRaHealth #3Dprinting #HIMSS19 https://t.co/8yPR9bB80p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pac-12 basketball, Utah at Washington State ... on Pac-12 Network. #GoCOUGS ! https://t.co/vbupoZr6Oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shortproof @Jdclout I would love for the app to be able to know my phone’s Quiet Hours setting or Do Not Disturb and just respect that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikebasketball might wanna start sending the college programs the “high grade” material like the league get and no… https://t.co/qwZbYUz3lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_lysss_uh @elliswes Sorry boys but she’s already taken so don’t try any funny business or things may get ruff..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took a shot of mezcal called Montelobos y prefiero tragar tierra pinche chingadera tan mala.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debostic @TrulyTrumpette @MiesW @nytimes @TwitterSafety @williamlegate Yeah but you also don’t have prove that it’… https://t.co/VnhppMPTZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack Keep reading this stuff and believing it if you want to become a mushroom growing in the dark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tamar making history tonight. First African American to win and broke the first to enter curse 🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌 #CBBUS2… https://t.co/msrPJoNuhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIIAmericanGirI @BreitbartNews I dont watch her shows now, and i never will]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dual Agent - first time representing both buyer &amp; seller...and things couldn't have gone smoother! #SOLD… https://t.co/ifBtKsbf07]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewryce On the bright side if you were sending demos to him and that happened... bit of a compliment ? Makes me… https://t.co/tes1WNnaBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDXDiamondProj Good thing I brought the hoodie! https://t.co/QBYSOXUGj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAMattK If he's cheap. I don't like giving up a significant asset for a RB rental unless it's absolutely necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two things; this is a HS and one of the teams is their scholastic bowl. Tip of the hat @BburgHSBruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredcwilson I ran into Phil Keaggy at O’Hare one time years ago. He has been a big influence on my Christian life… https://t.co/AgKj54rIwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatNeshek Hey Pat... not many of ur cards kicking around Canada... Do u have any extras for trade for signed hockey cards? Cheers...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unttalhanckoc @Gamborimbo76 @pelon_73 @manuel70m @maskarita4 @SoloPHombres @ElPincheJuan4 #odiamemas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatest encouragements in ministry for me: 1) pastors and ministry friends 2) kids 3) senior adults. 4 realz:… https://t.co/zsOs8QLlva]]></document><document><![CDATA[Step 1) get vaccinated against them.  Step 2) don’t let immunocompromised people near those with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_me_and_d @MrsTyler78 @KristinaNadia @LifesStyleBlog @judyohtweets @iluvtacos822 @AKAMOOOOOM Rest is overrated, u… https://t.co/QBcXoXUsXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Volkswagen Touareg V8 TDI Has Over 600 Lb-Ft of Torque https://t.co/85PTx1CZ6w via @jalopnik]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominos trash. @pizzahut trash. @PapaJohns trash. @littlecaesars trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Can he be excluded, based on his previous cheating? I think the election board should just declare Harris's… https://t.co/F1MsTAMh7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathandensley @manda_friedman @justinandgreg @GoldenKnights It’s still sweeter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night we dropped our first podcast! Check it out and go follow @BayfrontBoys  https://t.co/LNJlMkpRPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué es esto?👇🏼😯 Qué le sucede a esta mujer con esas declaraciones? @jesusardgz @senadomexicano @Mx_Diputados @gobmx… https://t.co/ys6e6CMs61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanessajhons @pssvbtch @hotmodelsxxx @IloveShemale44 @jockosrocket @Shemaleporn1983 @loretto5000 @PassiValerio… https://t.co/efYOp5ylzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_story Everything just gets dog slow for me, even though I gave docker more memory/cpu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you're Lyft driving and after dropping off a passenger and you're not sure where you ate, and then… https://t.co/BoMaMzKvdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers @NewDay @CNN Perhaps Twitter should just be outlawed? No, I don't think TV personalities would like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Let’s see if Robin Roberts on GMA ABC does a 16 minute interview with @SarahHuckabee or maybe… https://t.co/LvG4r9iNM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest Valentine wasn’t one you found on tinder, a college class, or even in high school. The greatest Valent… https://t.co/PBagE3GtQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSurman5 @NJ_2_FL Right. U didn't hear how USA began 4days ago. Not 1word I got fake news. Most valuable thing… https://t.co/vePqoWZL1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshStein_ Agreed. We can’t expect better of our future generations of we do not put in the resources. I can’t beg… https://t.co/tBXGswwjCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlieByrd I like History enjoyed reading The Bully Pulpit by Doris Kearns Goodwin.  I am following You. Please fo… https://t.co/4wH9gtzJSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practical #contech applications of #machinelearning and #NeuralNetworks Circular Saw Kickback Killer via… https://t.co/MYjbTJAemS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish I had some friends in Orlando that wanted to drive to Miami next week. Or someone going to Miami could stop through Orlando. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @robreiner @FoxNews @Disney @BeachesResorts @SandalsResorts @ChoiceHotels @TIAA @alincome @PetSmart… https://t.co/vyN3yVOOzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I’m still going in @TwitchSings! Let’s chill and have some fun. https://t.co/8RvT4DxWvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has the coach of the Canadian WJC team, ever gone onto being a top notch NHL coach?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know Houston full of thots lol it can be 44 degrees and they still gonna show up to the rodeo in booty shorts a… https://t.co/fO6cyNtB3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of the empty human ant farm that I stumbled through last night. @ Ballston, Virginia https://t.co/5XIvYeuRip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please give Kukan a chance. I'm tired of watching Harrington make mistake after mistake defensively. #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the store about actor/singer on #EmpireFOX #JessieSmollett  about making up the whole attack, then the old sayin… https://t.co/cqxgYtgjlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[supper #bestdadever @ Rocky Mountain Chocolate Factory - Ridgeland, MS https://t.co/fTXqbUcky0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sold for asking price! Thank you for your service 🇺🇸 I hope you and your family love your #newhome @ Oxnard, Calif… https://t.co/FxQ4DUUwF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @WhiteHouse Too bad 3 of her Most known Speech’s are Word for Word Copied From Michelle Obama Not Original… https://t.co/atB931dmgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know anything about this youngsta? @rjnotrj https://t.co/U9aLtryPX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll probably be pretty busy at work today which means Antonio Brown will get traded, cut, signed, traded again, re… https://t.co/Lp6kBs8kHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gracevilches But aren’t you glad you saw it? It was won of my favorite movies of 2015]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for my dad’s generosity and numerous contributions to schools throughout the metro area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonymurabito Tony I hope you are doing good. Quick question for you .... who won the game last night ? I didn’t pa… https://t.co/gpQgdBwTXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si Cristiano le mete más de 2 goles hoy a el Atlético me compro la camiseta de la Juventus con su nombre.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MexicoEnTweets @AMLONEWS @lopezobrador_ @lopezobrador_  @AMLONEWS  si alguien de su equipo que cubre esto de los m… https://t.co/YTRHCTBMuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t mobile order chipotle or starbuccs instead of ordering in person, you’re a weirdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When asked if this scandal warrants a confidence vote in the House, Scheer says Justin Trudeau should do the right… https://t.co/jdRzR006xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atasteofkoko @KerlinBBQ @la_Barbecue @veracruztacos @Joesbakery @fresaschicken I think you should include "Where t… https://t.co/rdmkYHILtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pat: I don’t like that guy. Me: Who is it? Pat: Idk, but he looks like Kyle Busch, and I don’t like Kyle Busch. He’s a whiney bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGreatBolo @thebrettclark Was looking at Crosstown tickets to see I can make that so I can say I have been to Wr… https://t.co/Hn9jWCXEMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Do you think he’ll ask for a tour of the POW camp where many US service men lived, like John McCain? (I… https://t.co/x8mWf9mASy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BrooklynNets gettingkilledon glass, missing open threes, playing listless D, and #CarisLevert just doesn’t loo… https://t.co/4UcrCSzERr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethgunnar @ChillyMostFresh @Smitty1915 @LukeLapinski @JaimeEisner https://t.co/Lc68sT8uJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! Here’s an app idea, Poketasks “gotta complete them all!” 😅 (excuse my dad jokes)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F_S_Adventures @Ta_TaForNow @ninawwd @Alphatraveler1 @chronicles_yaya @HappinessSweetT @TKMaxx_UK Good Morning fro… https://t.co/F8aQMMz3wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyberNihilist @NRO @benshapiro When an allegation against you is debunked, the accuser proven to be a liar, you're… https://t.co/mToQ0hZHR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque Correction: The Boxer rebellion he lead! There's a picture. Just one, though. He did nothing for those Boxers afterward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went up to Carver’s Gap on the TN/NC border for some twilight birding. I hoped to see (or hear) a Northern Saw-wh… https://t.co/SF4Kfj4djx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Tampa, Florida https://t.co/tjBFCC3i8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this means @MELOD1P  can enter the draft this year if they take away the 1 and done rule. ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/6eCsx9aD1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Why is God wrathful? Without mentioning sin, which is transgression of the Law, the idea of God be… https://t.co/QqwB5k5cdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to add a @VentraChicago pass to my Apple Watch. When i click “Add pass” and tap my watch with my credit card… https://t.co/yVFigk8U52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwaithBall @MustiiDmr @KlairhA Some of them went even further and included Hattians, Assyrians and Sumerians to th… https://t.co/iWJIjaNrpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #Finance job in #TheWoodlands, TX? Click the link in our bio to see it and more.… https://t.co/eXLUo6HeRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaleekreider That degree of fluctuation in one month? I agree with your late term abortion reference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mickey Mouse Says hi! 🤗😀🌅 @Lionelitu2 @carolyn660 @CarolynNewsom @Kreditrechnen @cynthia_lardner @JjbattleC… https://t.co/pVqg9NMJ05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctoraSexual Hay doctora como no la conoci a usted antes de que se casara.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadityyyB Yes!!!! It shocked me at first and then later the next day ! My mind didn’t know how to take it, you get to brain storming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulvt @linesbylyons There are two possible spots in north ish west (not been to either) one at Oxford and Wonderl… https://t.co/Y2QrJXOBs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isn’t everyone talking about how much @CoryBooker loves @BetsyDeVos , he apparently owes his campaign to her. H… https://t.co/S6grwTwTej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markrmcqueen @NTBasketBall Should I call off my U11 press conference re: "culture reset"?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARCis2Loud Bro box office numbers do not mean best film. Shitty films kill it in the box office all the time. Bla… https://t.co/UGb7lmk7x4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmares72 @yusuku13 It happens with a bunch of stuff. But we get better stuff for it from Japan 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, who is this?  “This is the Minister of Finance....” (Hmmmmm, was not expecting that response)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draco613 That's what I'm telling y'all that's exactly what Vince is doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[people get annoyed that I’m “always right.” while I enjoy being told that, I am not always right. I’m almost always… https://t.co/d7TK1jwXYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legisladores instalan la Comisión Bicamaral de Seguridad Nacional | El Economista @eleconomista  https://t.co/ysNbP1p4wS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings, are you really this stupid? You’re just another perfect example why the @SenateDems are the party of hate.]]></document></documents></author>