<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What did you do Saturday morning, we trained UFC Bro!                                             #martialartslife… https://t.co/00aP61yamq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been living/traveling in a van for over 4 months now. Finally, got around to filming our van tour video. Chec… https://t.co/RpstyWmNRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot Breakfast run on cold day! (@ Jumbo Donuts in Whitinsville, MA) https://t.co/XA1S3vPq5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans should be following these developments.   I predict Trudeau's departure and, despite that, an Alberta sep… https://t.co/M5EpfbuL4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Adrian McCarthy hits a 3 with .5 left in regulation. @KearsargeCougrs up 50-49 over @ORHSBBall @seacoastonline… https://t.co/xLhDmFt9cV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buster_ESPN Another miscalculation by Boras I guess you could say Boras is still effective for about 10 to 20% of… https://t.co/Qa5FmFxwNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Detroit! :) #Sunrise 07:21, noon 12:46, sunset 18:11 EST (UTC-5), February 20. Day length: 10h 49m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest crime Smollett committed was he required the CPD to commit massive resources to his mentally unstable a… https://t.co/C7lRifI8VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Untappd is having a beer fest at Bank of America Stadium and I want to go so bad 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KOE_KINGKAGEUFC @theterphouse here’s another #biztip 😎: copy and paste your caption on here to Twitter too.. that… https://t.co/UlSpmDcjDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Panthers have hired Jake Peetz as running backs coach, the team announced. #KeepPounding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost You got a real Winner Winner Gas Gussying Dinner NYC. The rest of the USA think she is an empty pants suit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A manuscript written well over a year ago is hardly "just written." The reason why I'm willing to… https://t.co/XmwRkEKTme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at @HS_ingenuity the class of 2020 were able to gain knowledge through speaking with faculty from @UHouston… https://t.co/aJ8fd4e4Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @classastudios!  Thanks for letting me be a part of your vision!!    My first cameo in a movie!!  Exciting… https://t.co/Ez3w1ZGHkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Cassius Winston for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/t1zgiAXV61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @rdrhwke @DavidSicilian @pcal4HIM @DLindsey2 @chilllingwithme @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs @mymynags @RL9631… https://t.co/tCn5jHJvay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly tho, who gave words their meanings? Like why is a rock called a rock?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one amazing girl. She has been able to experience many new things over the past year. She has handled every… https://t.co/AIYamzpOdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MettaWorldPeace @YouTube Wow! Enjoyed it. If u don't watch yourself you are gonna be on a network doing shows. Keep it up bruh Metta]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @AccidentAliens Anthology JUST went live on @kickstarter - Get in on this book!!!  https://t.co/7zBGRTq8vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful Prints by award winning artist Gary Kelley available at https://t.co/WINHkMCWSD @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/ySjT0FNLyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pYkLyLlrXw Texas Tech now controls their destiny in the Big 12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nastytwitlicker Make sure we get married too so if he wanna leave after he blow up, I  get half or have his ass pa… https://t.co/TmQLYwVsmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 inches of #snow in about 3 hours last night #PAwx #thatescalatedquickly #timelapse #snowfall https://t.co/z3KlLFNJcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PTPJacob @buffalobillspop @masterspenceiam @Dragons_Quest Coming from a Florida Panthers fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NL is getting to be a tough road. Off the top of my head only 5 teams didn’t significantly strengthen their rosters… https://t.co/WEqt9fwOiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the death anniversary of my mom. It’s been 9 years since you left this earth. I grew a lot mom. I hope I made you proud. love you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorTwellman More drama than keeping up with the Kardashian’s and any real housewives series.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone told me “Money is replaceable, but Time isn’t.” but if that’s the case wouldn’t I need to spend Time workin… https://t.co/5R02DZmKzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a haircut today after a long while. My hair was long. The lady cutting my hair was about 5 minutes into cutti… https://t.co/ytO3I4Gmfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it rain tonight at rachelspalmbeach!!!  Drop "Sean Reb" at the door to slide in!  _______________ First i will… https://t.co/p6dBAnj8DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the pups on about a four mile hike yesterday in Cherokee National Forest up the up Coffee Branch to the Chestn… https://t.co/4z6iz7QF3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwiss There was a brief movement earlier this season than said he was good. I’m not sure where that came from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@um2girlsmook24i @pinchehilaria two words. ZION. WILLIAMSON. https://t.co/LKXJoXHAc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really that's awesome maybe when you're in New York i might bump into yahhhhh LOL😁😁😁👍💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[George W. Bush Center Slams Trump’s Plan to Boost Jobs for U.S. Graduates https://t.co/3ULA6uNhua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC It's Ridiculous that people do not want a better standard of living, Affordable Healthcare and less restrictio… https://t.co/FAFTpXPfAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillwindsor It is a fever dream which means it's not real. It's just a movie. But I hope we can have a new Rocky a… https://t.co/T53MUvNYzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RL_Bynum Are you counting the games played against Trinity College or just after name was changed to Duke?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFRGFrogatelli My son... who shall remain nameless.. takes 2.. one at night and one in the morning. Just wonder ho… https://t.co/SJPOej0243]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I attended @sabr meeting in Durham NC via video chat.  Even made a presentation!  Thanks for invitation,… https://t.co/XFpTFkmAVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY IS PRESIDENTS DAY!  IF ONLY WE HAD A PRESIDENT TO CELEBRATE IT WITH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on my way back @ Puente Los Tomates, Matamoros https://t.co/BIoRGnbNAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfobioq @MicrobiomDigest Pictures of a few tumors is the data?  Isn’t this just qualitative?  I’m sure it is hard… https://t.co/NFNZiv26c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benj_fry If you want to make $300,000 a year in IT setting up sharepoint, go work there. Never seen a startup blow… https://t.co/IEsNJJ6icO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judyposton22 @MaysDaizy @thedailybeast I was uncomfortable seeing Mr. Family Feud have his picture taken with trum… https://t.co/ahLq6e5CRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Forever Loving Jah by Bob Marley &amp; the Wailers, Bob Marley, from… https://t.co/tRUBNIBwLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceHallman @libankerDC @jdawncarlson @PinkPistols One way to think of this is as complementary to understanding… https://t.co/9Xbcl8LTAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaannn listen.... ✊🏿✊🏿✊🏿✊🏿 #TearsFloweth #DailyLaugh #LMFAO #Funny #Comedy #Hilarious #Jokes #Flatlined #LOL… https://t.co/bG3A3hRtEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m going to make it really hard on these guys. Not demeaning, but demanding.” @VCU_Hoops regular season @A10MBB c… https://t.co/FR6AcBSu0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bugsbunny2062 @DudaPhillis Cuomo's gun laws violates the constitution, Bugs Bunny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee @MartySmithESPN if there is a better opening song to a show than Waylon’s - “Ramblin’ Man” I haven’t hea… https://t.co/JM2cuFEHAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[ETERNAL COVENANT SECURED: This is merely a hint of our night from a few  who sent me pics.  It was an awesome celeb… https://t.co/VVL6g8k2H0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man is in critical condition this morning after being ambushed inside of a car at his home. Police looking for wh… https://t.co/72xL4RCyfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBiancaa Last week’s lecture was based on sleep problems and disorders...  hope this helps https://t.co/OdR89QE8Qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @eddiek005 @realDonaldTrump Keep em in chains of hatred ‘bishop’. That’s what makes you rich. Your ‘co… https://t.co/WhHIb05FrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump @GovIvey Right on time.... https://t.co/Nb1px44UoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShamanicNights @BjornLomborg @ClimateRealists Computers make people dumber. Climate scientists come up with a prog… https://t.co/elMnJngzAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin @Kelly_reSister #Trumps Boyfriends need the money . He and Republicans get their campaign money from… https://t.co/6XYOHpjdfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ketapaapi @jess22bess Bruh... girls are just following and liking pictures. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you young weed smokers. It fucking smells. Your parents aren’t as stupid as you think. They just hope you wi… https://t.co/zHg0eKtoTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manny got what he wanted. Opt out after 5th year is important to note. Will be only 31 then if he decides to opt ou… https://t.co/yYVBrkemfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafaelmarquezal @brenzambranoc @Cruz_Azul_FC Por favor póntela siempre que juegue Cruz Azul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports Training Available  ⚽️⚾️🏀🏐🏈🏉🎾🎳🏏🏑🏒🏓🏸🥊🏌️‍♂️🏌️‍♀️🎣⛸🎽⛹️‍♀️⛹️‍♂️🤽‍♀️🤾‍♂️🤾‍♀️🤼‍♂️🤼‍♀️🏆🎖🥇🎖🏅🥇  RESULTS ARE NOT GIVEN… https://t.co/dcPmCXADVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStation having issues getting into PlayStation Network. Tried DM you and no reply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You believed in me, even when I doubted. Gave me love when I felt I was without it. You remained committed though I… https://t.co/GkNtzAAoBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s so great about Chyna, but we have seen this so many times after many have  unfortunately have an untimely pa… https://t.co/hz0TDdz3vF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Wheelsup #KC via #DetroitRockCity @GearBoss_Wenger 1st Class Upgrade @Delta! Shoe game upgrade courtesy of… https://t.co/OTtwMJVqOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[imagine breaking up w your girl but y’all still have to live together this is awk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Australia. Who wouldn’t want to go to the land down under?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallCoyne If you have a speed skating competition between NFL linemen... he’s my pick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you’re a twat sellout trying to stay relevant. Does that count?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellinidata @pcatapano @katie_honan If the reporters spent more time reporting and less time inventing scandals the… https://t.co/7PhdmIqQhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Facts Don’t Change People’s Minds. Here’s What Does... #truth #media #news https://t.co/Zd7hwYRbM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSteensma @DanaFarber How about draining ascites or pleural fluid? It is sad to see them suffer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton " If babies should not be in detention", maybe they should be left @ home! DUH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You get drafted based on your offensive skill set. How many lockdown defenders going in the 1st round every year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristenschaaled You do realize that the same processes that made all other life forms onEarth,  made us.  We are o… https://t.co/VJ5pAldvqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool Hand Luke and The Finnisher. So close yet so far. Damn. #NBAAllStarWeekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reviewjournal I don’t like this plan. I have a rights issue with this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a dream come true having our newest release of “Tough Luck” from “Old Habits” on some of our favorite playl… https://t.co/9fM4lvbnWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy estuve en un museo donde había un pedazo del muro de Berlín. Al lado un reportaje sobre los últimos días de Nor… https://t.co/lm4FCslY99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not teleport me while I'm sleeping at night like I am some dude in the Prairies where you can just teleport at n… https://t.co/lRxDhuFPto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @stoolpresidente @TuckerCarlson Like I just said you look very uncomfortable in a suit and tie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed @EthanJSkolnick  Lineup of:  Winslow Waiters Richardson (LeBron) Adebayo   would definitely be top 4 in West… https://t.co/Yrqgi78nUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismcquarrie Had to to my friend’s brother to rent it for us from Errol’s Video in Northern VA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be the only peep on #Twitter who notices that there are zero (0) #characters remaining almost every time be… https://t.co/LnvoGgpQTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HistoricCore @laplphotos Hopefully, one day, it can regain its former glory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmarx Just when you thought Richard Marx was done writing cheese 🧀 lyrics. https://t.co/DFYDdHpX29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danstringer74 @jennablan Any evidence to support your claims of "mortgaging personal homes to the max"? I didn't think so. smdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simon_lindsell @ShaunGunner @LOTRonPrime I dont think we are getting deep history, except in tiny spoonfuls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khelgen @darth Spotted a Canadian Lynx in the Yukon in 2006. https://t.co/CeAURqimZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the bottom of my heart; thank you so much for giving me the wonderful chance to be friends with all of these p… https://t.co/sTVMkkPwZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who’s in *charge* of whether we a snow day or not but if they make us go to school tomorrow on a full day then… https://t.co/kmLNlhvJzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now the Pens need more forward/defense depth. Hopefully we make a move or 2 at the deadline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Len1776 @realDonaldTrump I was going to say 3rd, teddy, jfk, then President Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this your mindset dont fwm, if you one of those who is always on your phone dfwm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[mr_mackie since u cant remember seeing me at vice_htx here is a pic we took 😂😂 #alcoholink is still #undefeated  🍹🍹… https://t.co/XVa64tnk8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Solo documents the first ever “free solo,” or completely ropeless, ascent of El Capitan. In trying to explain… https://t.co/WWT2ljNEPs]]></document></documents></author>