<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s really amazing how many business owners really don’t understand the marketing funnel and internal planning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriennelrupp Did they start to use the ladies’ room like we do when the men’s room is empty but the ladies’ line is 20 people deep?!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I see it, I like it, I want it, I got it...” 🍔🍟🍕🥪🥙🌮🌯🥗🥘🥫🍝 #arianagrande #arianator #thankunext #sweetener… https://t.co/Z5ZqzGs40P]]></document><document><![CDATA[My customer kissed me on the mouth today..... She was 4, so it wasn’t totally weird.  But a little weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AZ Loop 303 and W. Glendale Ave. in Goodyear, AZ https://t.co/bpur95jSet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orlando passar a ser a nova capital da FL e tirar o posto de Tallahassee?! Wowww!! @orlandosentinel https://t.co/wVM3x4UcBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris You work for America citizens..   Stop fighting for Illegal Aliens Undocumented immigrants rights!  F… https://t.co/xg6vEzxzpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone uses cbd oil?  Compare your ingredients to ours? Now you see why ours is the best https://t.co/355cRVHtJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inertiauk Hell no! That song deserves to be somewhere around GOL &amp; FTLG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RutledgeWood @Blaney @chaseelliott hey Rut, why don’t you take them to @Hooters for lunch today? I hear it’s https://t.co/7n1jVTZwj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been working myself hard for almost two months. Ive gone from being dead after one climb to regularly doing 15… https://t.co/CyFQNBQ90D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flower Show #Philly2019 #philadelphiaflowershow2019 @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/TEw7cql2ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkinMoms Just started watching this and I can’t stop laughing 🤣Brilliantly written and acted. My wife told me to… https://t.co/hx1FK54FBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jiggycomedy Hey Jiggy! I’m listening to your Tastes Funny podcast with Alexa Matthews and you’re talking about Ube… https://t.co/DPiLowgiy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NEW “Gripping, intriguing, emotional and spellbinding!” “Another thoroughly enthralling story by Penny Dee” Brothe… https://t.co/iQy56xemGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enmarket and Healthy Savannah Invite Public to Kick Off Sixth Annual Encourage Health Educational Series… https://t.co/YgObmovne0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix to open dedicated production hub in Toronto https://t.co/22F6gE5SuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ish102066 @j_yanez55 Happy Birthday,  Joseph!! Hope it's a great day and one you'll look at back on with special memories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been collecting data on this story for months, because the prosecutors office does not keep its own data. Qual… https://t.co/GfuaclLmDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiDC4L @valentinifrank @GeneralHospital If he has such range why does he have only one expression in all his sce… https://t.co/gMO1DaZZRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harryrose670 @classicalbeat Harry- I think it has more to do with the fact that the style of production seems to b… https://t.co/BtZZtm6TOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Memo highlights the fact that few urology residents feel prepared to handle the business side of practicing ur… https://t.co/76VFgZD4mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The fact that the media holds you in account does not mean it has changed. It means that you are a… https://t.co/ZwC0VKfp5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdimples0005 Good luck getting the tickets, the queue is moving crazy slow 😔.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone keeps beeping like someone is pushing a button? Phone hacking? Gas lighting?  😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurynnorton @LaurenHerschel Yes it is a good match.  Having the visual of the ball in the box and the pain button… https://t.co/ehFSrAoSTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a big fan of the Golden State Warriors and dream of some day attending one of their games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st time posting a pic after strength day f45_training_portchester  #iameliteny  ❤️❤️❤️ #thankyou @ Stamford, Conne… https://t.co/csPBjYGpPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyRenner @cherokeesher2 @MingGao26 Yes and I don't care who brought up the 25th they were not wrong to do so we… https://t.co/jRf8TJ5z3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missed this ethical theory clapback earlier! (via @DillEPape) https://t.co/GzpqQ3EnF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I apparently just loooove waiting until my stomach is literally eating itself before I order food. And now I have t… https://t.co/PEws351cz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is day 3 of morning rush hour problems this week by the way. It’s unacceptable. #Astoria residents deserve better than this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my interview in the latest Arkansas Business-pg 10! State of recycling. #arkansasbusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[The company SpaceX has successfully launched, with the help of NASA, from Cape Canaveral its first commercial capsu… https://t.co/HvEafBZUjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ MY NEIGHBORS: STOP REVVING YOUR ENGINE YOU’RE GONNA GIVE ME A HEART ATTACK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usedgov Why isn't DeVos removed yet?  Yesterday cocaine trafficker, Devos said "We must be removed then, we were p… https://t.co/TsrJXc3N3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psyched to have met @deepseadawn tonight at @williamandmary for the #100YearsOfWomen lecture https://t.co/6s8rN3y4O2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lanterns #vegasstyle @ Encore Las Vegas Hotel/Casino https://t.co/XAqTM7gAyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatBarrell @realtimrozon @MelanieScrofano @DominiqueP_C @emtothea @WynonnaEarp ↑ Let me know if you need a Doc Hol… https://t.co/iPrNKf6vmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day out with my babies ❤ @ Red Robin Gourmet Burgers https://t.co/THN7Idsf5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[boba rankings:  1. boba fiend 2. tutti fruitti boba 3. cha2O boba 4. boba tea house 5 any pho place really  and the… https://t.co/jwqkGGXiZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to sum up the education positions of the mayoral candidates in 4 minutes... there’s a lot of them so it was… https://t.co/U09SCVddLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieTielker @uhaul Huh. Thought y’all might have missed the flight on account of a GoT rerun, a perfect restaura… https://t.co/EV72nKN5tE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow I believed he looked handsome and distinguished. People should be worried more about integrity!!! A d… https://t.co/QpKNHeSlPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence She’s come out of the closet and is a self proclaimed racist hate monger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo! Murderinos of Twitter  Which are you? A @GHardstark or a @KarenKilgariff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwikWarren 2.6 for the win. As others have stated, he didn't earn it, he was helped along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Yes we do, people have the right to vote without obstacles... It should be a day off.... Fully support that]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a new post up here this morning! Head on over to https://t.co/l2lxbGpeGD to see a little recap of the begin… https://t.co/Y8nfJD19p6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademiaHell I saw this too! My slides weren’t from a text, but a variety of readings (some even online) for which… https://t.co/t9lAtXXs6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up to what I thought was two cats fighting outside my window. It’s just the wind. #ohiowx]]></document><document><![CDATA[New school partner highlight! @StAloysiusAcad students learning how to #code in an after school program with… https://t.co/otLK84MBlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It still amazes me that ANY of them  can claim to be victimized!! Not to mention pathetic....]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is National Colorectal Cancer Awareness Month and The Bagel Rack in Lebanon is making special bagels and a de… https://t.co/KivZyBmeYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us at Spring 2019 #ApacheSpark 3x30 in #RTP #Durham #Raleigh #ChapelHill #NC! https://t.co/JABbrtfGtP Great sp… https://t.co/qw3URm77u2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephanie_chae_ Thanks for suggestions...I've listened to all of up and vanished.. So hooked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody at my box is saying how easy peasy 19.1 will be while forgetting the fact that it’s a 15 minute AMRAP. We… https://t.co/PEUtPWGbju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paradiseivy4 you already know! #ChallengeAccepted to post 7 covers of books I love--no explanations--no review--ju… https://t.co/hYow7q3PiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BR0C I’m more on the “holy shit. human trafficking is the fucking worst. Is this the Kraft Mac and Cheese guy?” train.]]></document><document><![CDATA[University of Missouri, MU Hospital, and now MU vet hospital.... thankful for them all but 🙈not looking forward to the bills!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Yet you support a man who has a history and future full of lies. You post videos of pretending to opp… https://t.co/bYLu1V6ZGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFleegle @ShoremenBball Turning on alerts cause I wanna know how this goes down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I'm remembered for anything when I'm gone, I strive to make certain friends and family remember my #kindness . https://t.co/f0MoP4ZrgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did some electro shock therapy shit on my back &amp; now one of my muscles won’t stop twitching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone does something wrong, don’t forget all the things they did right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re getting old when it starts to become a habit to watch the news and wheel of fortune every night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillsPointMS teachers learn how to #ExactPath ly get the data @WillsPointISD #EdmentumTX  @edmentum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some (of us🐓) have been waiting patiently for Brexit to go away so we don’t have to figure it out, like literary th… https://t.co/gHxYRcZZSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yinzstillers @StormIsUponUs not in California the Dems cheat with illegal votes. if they don't win they just start… https://t.co/VqjKZc1y3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mpls Public Schools referred to employees as “redlined” just this week in bargaining 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @RobBenedict / @LoudenSwain1 - Salute to Supernatural Nashville 2016 #spnnash #nashcon #nashcon2016 #loudenswain… https://t.co/QAtdKRHjgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheypretty Agreed. Not using resources and not networking is where people feel like they’ve wasted their time. The… https://t.co/WnVKfgWdze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrillSince93   Thank you for liking my tweet. Let us discuss your mobile app development requirements here - https://t.co/9FCwcjAIYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[God dammit that typo. Never MISS an episode, not “kiss an episode”. https://t.co/YyTHESjm6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Omar does not stand in support of America’s long-standing good relationship with Israel, a country who has sup… https://t.co/OEWr3PFupN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Monday  and #Tuesday I will be marketing, promoting and sharing this author's #book via my platforms in the plight… https://t.co/MrY9sYh2EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When 6 of you travel across the country to reunite with your bestie #squad #california #santamonicapier… https://t.co/WDuwsfdDoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien Why are people forgetting the TRAFFICKING part of this story??  Somebody like Kraft could have a nic… https://t.co/zH9oa8WFxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahharas22 Search the name and then hold down on it and click “more” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Charles McDowell Rehabilitation Center in Lyndon, KY https://t.co/0JleFvikiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatnerdsarah Am here if you ever need to talk or just someone to Listen! 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know socialism in America has already been done they didn’t call it socialism they called it something else but… https://t.co/zCTzS1aVxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A candy store for those with an eye for space #urbanamericana #warehouse #furniture #design #interior #vintage… https://t.co/49efJEPjiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntLopezfit Early morning traffic is a treat yes?!😉 Have a great Monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Sunset Pointe at Fly Creek Marina https://t.co/xAyynQVtWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy @MJtheProphet @Phil_Nourse @ElPatriotaA1776 @sharrond62 This supposed advantage hasnt shown itself in a… https://t.co/2BiQntDTIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews GAME OVER: Chicago Police Reportedly Believe Jussie Smollett Paid Brothers To Beat Him Up https://t.co/bBVQncxZYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabaluCat @frankfortsports Those were suggested times for 1st round. The two teams playing had final say. Our game willl be at 7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve just got over my jet lag and it’s gonna start again tomorrow night 😭😭 send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speakingabtpain You're right this definitely a thing in the pain space. It's big in the psych space too. Interesti… https://t.co/NllFOFp21c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my Boyfriend 30 chicken nuggets from @ChickfilA bc nothing says 4+ years of love like giving your love their fave food ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPMinfo @SPMAthletics @SPMGirlsHockey @SPMBASKETBALL @spmbaseball @SPM_HypeClub @SPMNHS @SPMGuardianFB… https://t.co/s3AWTOCeE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The clock is ticking on a stormwater drainage project for a Midway neighborhood that was devastated by the 2014 flo… https://t.co/Bv8KrkCdOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Putneyman @EvaShadowgirl18 @kev13F 😊👋👋👋raining here now Dave, just lightly at the moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why on earth would Whitehouse admins suggest @IvankaTrump ? She has no qualifications. This country doesn't have a… https://t.co/trupfsGRLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us in Westlands. Student Sit-In #SLC50 #50YEARSOFSHAME Click for information on WHY we are fed up!… https://t.co/Nslwt7St27]]></document><document><![CDATA[People swear they never say anything then you talk to the person they weren’t supposed to say anything too🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bop for today (and everyday): make a pop rock wanna be my valentine candy @walkerhayes https://t.co/fHUlo0hzJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coco_l0c0 If you didn’t tweet that we wouldn’t know. Judging from a far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevLaurieinLex I mean, if you're both off of work that early, go for it!]]></document></documents></author>