<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Looking for a #situation #detroit #psychogeography #pattern #illustration @ Plymouth, Michigan https://t.co/Fl8m6gs3Oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t even get me started on how sublime French fries are dipped in mayo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenChuckYeager @JunkYardCard @jgrahamthomas Gee I was terrified on Space Mountain in Disney World cannot fathom how you guys do what you do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Não me preocupo com os falsos Subo nas coisas porque eu posso Faço dinheiro porque eu posso🎶 https://t.co/HoBdPRtogA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martingeddes Wait until they find out 70% of their government are pedo's!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found it! 💙 . . . #blueberrywall #epcot #disney #disneyworld #disneystyle #flowerandgardenfestival #acolorstory @ B… https://t.co/td3dyTRzrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me trying to calculate how to get enough sleep for work AND also watch @TXT_members debut this morning https://t.co/MsrOdCPaOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuidedbyGeorge mom. Chill tf out haha stop fighting ppl on Twitter this is a community for funny memes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeseEvon @nightwing2525 He was. My nephew was one of the security guards and got decked by Ronda Rousey. The one… https://t.co/9UTJ8Jmeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell that Department of Justice Head from Illinois to stay away from my family and I. I don't owe him anythi… https://t.co/yP9nQRPp7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lowkey love that people still ask me to proofread all of their official (or unofficial) writing. My double tour o… https://t.co/q2KtakGuCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never know badassness like these guys.  @brothersosborne https://t.co/3txKX4TkX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was such a rough day... it was even harder to look people in the eyes and tell them that I was okay instead of telling the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was awakened by Satan’s cherubs, to a personal hell I never could have imagined — on repeat #makeitstop… https://t.co/zuEFDXyi9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I KNOW that I talk a lot about my haunted apartment. But tonight? I’m staying in one of the most haunted hotels in… https://t.co/CkWbgyohnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished Second Hand (by @heidicullinan) in 3 days.   I really need to learn to pace myself better. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Sis for showing much love as always😁 #face❤️ #husband💙 #blessed🙏 @ Pulaski Hall https://t.co/HdiCJK9S8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we outgrow people because they weren’t growing, and that’s okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @LindseyGrahamSC already has you see him crawling out from under @realDonaldTrump desk daily along with @seanhannity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbuYoshi notifs are on so I can see all of the updates lol https://t.co/vYsmWSC8M4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports Now apologize to Hillary for hacking on her daily "But her emails..............".  Constantly.  Ne… https://t.co/fvnLJXtLdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump @kw1979 They want to be stay home moms apparently- not a problem if they didn’t impose their choice on others. But they do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for following along with #mariebakes today!  I made Hawaiian buns! 🍍🍞🐰 I followed this recipe from… https://t.co/YqDdqpSYpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laker477 @barb71 @OldSmokeEater @TeriHentschel @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong @FMedic921 @bluefamilyprays… https://t.co/lWoOgyTl22]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it once, I’ll probably say it another 600 times. Most people who drive in the lair are a special kind of stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@im_bad_luck Yep, just wish i left him in the long ago past instead of trying to be friends😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luchavino @VinoSocialNancy @cotebonneville @SeattleUncorked @Wa_State_Wine @YakimaAVA @DivaVinophile @SteveKubota… https://t.co/1Fbzi6u6Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[An ideal concert of mine would be: Mazzy Star, Cigarettes After Sex, Tame Impala, Beach House, Mac Demarco, The 197… https://t.co/fUSjLa44vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctoralexa a job, then no matter what color a person is-deserves said job. I just wanted to thank you for being r… https://t.co/2N7gZjnYwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #AnnaHowardShawDay https://t.co/tCuVkjUFZz https://t.co/oFiPMx6uZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photography: Real Estate Home Staging Stager: upstyledesign Marlene Boney Photography 📸 @ArtistYvetteM designed for… https://t.co/9q29Uh8nDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE TEA HAS SPILLED at #beachesweho Get here early to catch #RPDR11 with host #barbiesaddiction SEATING IS LIMITED!… https://t.co/N77ezyGOtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Frances of Rome, wife, mother, and servant of the poor, pray for us! @ Madison, Alabama https://t.co/vnOUtfuH3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BengalThinker One battle at a time! I’m glad .@SpeakerPelosi isn’t breathing fire! This is why she is more effective! #MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianmilonas addresses his #AtlanticProWrestling future when #DemonOrtiz interrupts @ Newburyport Elks https://t.co/BYZqfJwSiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoanneLevy @bloomsburykids She keeps running in and describing her favorite scenes, which is like her stamp of app… https://t.co/LtSHfPHFgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else having trouble getting the game right now???Shriners College Classic https://t.co/AvXzOpIvlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassytxchic @Untappedtalent2 @Carlarussowoma1 @GobAbiertoBOL @HillaryClinton So just, what? Fuck those women who will die? Cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did my neighbor, Charlie, change his name on fb to Cousin Eddie Drake tho?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland He has one and it's deflated.  My kid is sucking down Helium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJConsulting_CA A.2 Homemade chicken soup is my way of showing my love and concern to family and friends. #LoveCDNChicken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united I have been told TWICE today by two different “customer service agents” that bc I used #UnitedMileagePlus p… https://t.co/oW6Gr6p7gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could you trust somebody when everything they believe it has no value]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would just like to say that I obfuscated on my insta post. I’m still on the dumb red line going home. I will be sleeping soon tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickkidtchThoer @CNN Those days are waning after tax return truths. 💙🇺🇸 #UndoingTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got some damn bad intentions I got some secrets I forgot to mention Haven't learned my lesson]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on day 3 of being vegan. I’m having crazy detox symptoms so I’m seriously hoping things get better because I would like to stay vegan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[and none of the girls who blocked me are even pretty so stay huuuurrrttt 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ca1ty Hahaha no worries boo, I was just saying in case you want to delete bc blank tweet 💖 you’re always welcome t… https://t.co/h7zuCeHqIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna be the woman that this little girl looked up to. 💕☀️💛💯 and so much more. https://t.co/Viy7DGwsA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alentejo_1970 I put a honeymoon couple in a suite here :) they loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[XCentium Launches Flex Accelerator for Sitecore - A SaaS Solution for Mid-Market Companies https://t.co/avTlWWPQ0K # via @benzinga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anonymous_78 @gamegrumps11287 @pkmnsnaps @PokemonGoApp 😮 you’re so lucky. Been trying to get one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlsdRtheChzmkrs @TheOnlyEdAsner @realDonaldTrump And the liberal media is helping them. Every freaking show on MSN… https://t.co/1RJjvKgPap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottjo12268543 Good morning listen I’m new @ Twitter finding you was a adventure good lord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to remind myself of this continuously. @ Mental Health Association of Nassau County https://t.co/rnlbSL2Kat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Among the mundacitity of Sunday "chores" I sprinkled in brunch in a favorite spot with new vegan options, a plan to… https://t.co/qP7kvRpQuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[With some of refund money I’ll be purchasing a replica championship belt for my wedding entrance. A bit conflicted… https://t.co/95s0QxdmnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracie sold this cute arrangement @ Gracie James Company https://t.co/wnU5iu8iEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl used to tell me how cute me and my man was now she’s tryna get with him I CANT WITH FEMALES 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[An evening musing . This weekend was difficult and nothing seemed to go with right from painting to packing to work… https://t.co/JKwrGsJxq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill More ignorance from Cortez.  The gift to the GOP that keeps on giving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for featuring Marc! Thanks for your hard work &amp; CONGRATS on your award!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4) one example - AR/VR can provide safe, realistic learning scenarios for students w/autism. Current research is fascinating #EdTechChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotableDesister @aytchellesse I grew up in the mid hudson valley so was accustomed to stunning nature from age 5 u… https://t.co/ILhN91vS51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aacrimony @BROWNGlRL When I had put my two weeks in apparently everyone thought the next day was my last day and went with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped my makeup holder. Bye bye Bronzer 🥺 I didn’t check anything else because my heart couldn’t take it this e… https://t.co/x3VvHOZ0or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating impact - huge shout out to  @mobilizemichael and Krista Jensen for all their hard work. It’s the beginning… https://t.co/hS1NEefmEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[it really doesn’t matter what time i wake up, i always wake up hungry smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CincyPD need your help finding a man they say broke into our home on South Fairmount and left his wallet and medi… https://t.co/t2PVkQ1Zcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allbsallthetime @kimguilfoyle The 32% on the post what an embarrassment. He was a rambling old man with no substan… https://t.co/tUS3KQoyqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TheSHLNetwork Semifinals. @GBNhockey and @RamblerHockey at 4:30, @YorkHockey and @newtrierhockey at 5:30. The universe hates me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabpan01 Girl! What?!? I’ve never had them like that but my mouth just watered 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always thought this #pizza protector was a mini table for my dolls 🤷‍♀️ https://t.co/ww2KJBGeIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's an excuse these embarassing and disgusting feminists use as an excuse to murder full term babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelBruner @sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein Additionally it’s like a group of kids telling a plumber how to install a si… https://t.co/2QE8T6yDVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to rally for #IWD19 with @DCCADV! @MayorBowser, to make sure we can #EndDVinDC we need a #FairFY20 that funds… https://t.co/80AcKfakBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm learning slowly that this is true leadership. You're gonna fail so many times and then get back up a d try agai… https://t.co/fPvdOSMyvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I woke up like @VINNYGUADAGNINO with some #pinkeye I have never had eye issues in my whole life. The fuck is this shit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love her excitement and words that a film about menstruation won at the #oscars   So very empowering and it’s a f… https://t.co/Q3KcMEaHrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GustavoDudamel and @LAPhil dedicated this to #Previn tonight and my god did they play beautifully. The audience wa… https://t.co/3rAGtt1ZPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nous aimons ceux dont le comportement est plus gratifiant et ceux capable de nous soutenir pour atteindre nos buts😊😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy Christian worked by himself to build this awesome marble run. @EileenKearney1 @ConnorCougars https://t.co/1Xe0BoSmz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll never forget when Mr Hooper passed away, still makes me Teary eyed.   https://t.co/Uqe4YpyBVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalFamily @KensingtonRoyal @ClarenceHouse I️ wonder why KP is so worried about the Television actress is receivi… https://t.co/8XReCHQWO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_L2 Aw! My heart!! It’s okay sis, they’re ignorant to the beauty you have! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[41 days till my soon-to-be roommate is here to apply for condos and get us a place to live and I can’t wait #April9… https://t.co/klXZUO0QR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karinayebra4 @gerbss28 Why can i hear u signing this but yelling at the same time ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow @oliviamunn Please Please Please. Would love a #TheNewsroom reboot. We need this reboot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClintRiddle6 @CNNPolitics He received tons of money, which tuner ha it that he saved should he decide to run for President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCLASemelFriend im sick and tired of beimg told im delusional or crazy because of narcissistic people who think th… https://t.co/t6Pawsub2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @WashXC to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews - just the cov… https://t.co/EDZpalrOyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough said?! Truth?? Do you agree?? .  Never let the opinions of people who are in the cheap seats of the stands c… https://t.co/fKFXUmUJ4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @SouthShoreTwit The problem is you have FOX News praising him and putting him on a pedastool and his ba… https://t.co/O7lpS3AaKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunhappyKat I’m loving living vicariously through you Kat! All your pics are great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#firstladyofsong #queenofjazz #bebop #swing #scat #isitliveorisitmemorex #ellafitzgerald #badassblackwomen… https://t.co/gW4FKvMU4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Hint Hint* I would LOVE this #GemstoneHeart necklace from @kayjewelers for Valentine's Day! https://t.co/gSwiBJUEC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@221beees Still not here. I’m already 30 minutes late to work https://t.co/MNFJq25ty6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Angeles is lighting up tonight!   @ABC7 @abc7weather #eyewitness https://t.co/1amOzClDq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Queenniy girl it’s the worst!! I try eating just a little bit, but that never happens 😩😂]]></document></documents></author>