<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[just because I fly halfway across the world &amp; tell everyone you’re my boyfriend doesn’t mean we’re dating !! periodt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having some good conversations (and some fun) at this year’s Legislators’ Forum II @hrccredc https://t.co/XoHUPALaJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly what I have always said and have felt.   #truth #motivate #smallbusiness #entrepreneur… https://t.co/YISsNKylz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @stellahrst! I created a YouTube group chat so we can share videos more easily. :) Join here: https://t.co/3YfXiA0KTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No, I’m gonna be in there...” *points to venue* “...rocking and rolling.”  A response I just got when I asked if t… https://t.co/GKWZXyfmck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraDawn4 Yes we r already engaged in an ideological civil war. These magas r scary..some ould be glad to see dems persecuted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgieiscurious @realDonaldTrump I couldn't bring myself to justify this with a response]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, I've got this one covered. Been talking shit since they took their first breath. 😅 https://t.co/1Z7nu8AyPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Excelente pregunta! Así queremos que respondan, con logros obtenidos! No que se defiendan con descalificaciones si… https://t.co/JrBIDTCkBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t say rip when I die i’m not dead i’m just living in another alternate universe 🦇💟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradHales10 @taylorswift13 Google the theories people have been saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heads up for tomorrow:  it's National Margarita Day, so I expect you to all celebrate in style! https://t.co/mjDYVVmKYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Bedroom Duplex, Camolot Lane, Columbus, IN  References are Checked! Contact Denise Eckelman 812-350-1864 #forrent… https://t.co/vBclI54Dik]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Washington’s going home! And just like that, after 75,000 guests through 32 performances,  @hamiltonmusical… https://t.co/dBz1L14YQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@submx8ch @niclet @MarthaMad99 @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Sweetie, I can only answer for me.  I was not ignoring… https://t.co/rW2QN1pPuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 5th grade, a girl in my class gave me a lecture about how to be cool (guess it was super obvious to her I wasn’t… https://t.co/1DRuI3jQoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subway Deli in England have stopped serving Ham because it was offensive to the Muslim population.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pacastr Hay que ser chica de Hotel y no de Motel, se lo dejas claro desde el comienzo 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 29th birthday to my sweet boy! Love ya! @ Conway, Florida https://t.co/0cBMu4FXXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomArnold @Kris_Sacrebleu @GeraldoRivera @Rosie @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Dude, there’s no rocks big enough here for… https://t.co/Tsbm05lbiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadToday I believe they can. I suppose it depends if they are a good/clear communicator or not. Sometimes with to… https://t.co/zsslDzMggH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a lil part time gig so I can make more money to launch my business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11thHour Remembering “Lock her up!”......Karma, Karma, Karma!.... what goes around, comes around, often on steroids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. Just because something is labelled "therapy" doesn't make it therapeutic.  Kids "regressing" once institutionali… https://t.co/tOuG9RWkeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliadavidovich @SilenceYrMouth Maybe for Alyssa’s bachelorette we all go get these?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps, there are some adult staff that would participate.  @firemanoo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #ColtonSucks on @TyltEnt—Colton Underwood is one of the worst bachelors ever https://t.co/m8M6Futzi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[New report recommends ways to prevent depression during pregnancy and postpartum for new moms.… https://t.co/JLAsSlhfuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught a FABULOUS exhibit in nyc this sunday at @NYHistory !! not pictured is an equally stunning (and informative)… https://t.co/5AofJM6uuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerryJuDo4ever @KateMansi @TeamChabby @CarolynTopol @billymflynn @4KimmieBee OMG, I don’t usually get a bit sad ab… https://t.co/MPJOevUpBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShinyGyaradoss Wow that’s a let down I was hoping alolan geodude was gonna be shiny there’s enough of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[me being passive even when I know I shouldn’t b https://t.co/lyoS9rpFxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresRobinson RJ is so amazing! I wish I could reach out to @hollyrpeete and get some insight about autism, my g… https://t.co/pPqXXtSqjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @VP until it is criminal for the male who made the pregnancy a problem , Shut up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro the gym smells like dirty vagina and ass, I need y’all to get it together]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how these girls played fast and hard tonight!!! Keep it up!! #ladyads #tts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol, not only did they go down there unarmed, but without an extra set of batteries? 😂😂😂 #Gotham #NothingsShocking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desayuno antes de bajar de las montañas @ La Cabaña del Abuelo https://t.co/DdMyh6vSfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humanworkplace It is always reasonable to know what the pay rate is before taking a job. Whether new hire or exist… https://t.co/zm0o0U1NFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdelaineMorin I’m Annie, from Nashville, TN. ❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/cu4m5KGaK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerHuckabee @UnvirtuousAbbey It happens to be at the root of all religion, too. Money rules it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Why are the GOP so afraid for the public to know what we already know Trump is a liar and why do the GOP l… https://t.co/YW5sx1P5lr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rreagles20 I really only went there to drink, because they want 10.00 for a tiny bit of wine st CBP. I’ll have to… https://t.co/ybGHQYCwMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonteDurham You liked that? 😟 That dress is awful and does nothing for Maya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw #captainmarvel⁠ ⁠ Thought it was a fun ride. Thought Ben Mendelsohn stole the show. I was in the mood for… https://t.co/cGb6oGXk8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacBee_JoeD what’s your opinion on Cassius Stanley playing HS ball as a 19 year old?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far... The best thing about today... Cockatoos Rock..to Elvis!!  and she's like..😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iXTo_ Exactly. My friend wants to be a flight attendant and I told her people are going to be worse than they are… https://t.co/j2tqhz3s15]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little #ThrowbackThursday for my Twitter followers😂🥰🖤 I was soooo darn cute! https://t.co/GnmE4XLcIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAJAJAJAJJJAJAJAA las patillas de Kevin lo eran todo jajajajaja y esos chinos de nick 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is WWE’s last chance to show they actually care about Sasha &amp; Bayley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dredd_Cruz @meggomeggo25 or it's twice as expensive because it's better]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what Granada’s neighborhood looks like today: https://t.co/2OcSo7MxVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelm1976 “You said you’d feed me wet foods at 6:30 but only got home at midnight; we’re going to need to have a chat.” 😹😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between 2016 and 2018, there were about 21,000 reported hate crimes, and 50 hoaxes. That makes it 0.2%. Don't let J… https://t.co/uh3oW4EwjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a few hours away from going into full Doomsday mode. I#Apocalypse2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such a fantastically crazy time last night at the #kdancebreak with kpop757va. I learned so much about putting… https://t.co/t6AGO0aqIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WithConEm I didn’t realize that was you! I’m so bad at recognizing people from the internet 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe #HelloMagazineUK made this huge error in their print magazine...read caption to see that the man… https://t.co/vHHXVngUGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoApp just a rant post. It seems like the shiny rates for these mini events has gone down. I remember when… https://t.co/Tp3K3omlnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Veronica_sphynx @rogelio11025708 @Angelic86416803 @monerorape @V_TrujilloM @Milenio A poco la tuvieron los prianis… https://t.co/6frZDDEtHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh! @NaomisLitPix will you draw fireworks on my contract cover page too?? Pleeeeeeaaaaaase?  (Or hearts or stars, w… https://t.co/aeR65scvfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting Results! NOW Pending in The Concession | $3,275,000 Listed | To discuss your real estate goals, visit link… https://t.co/xyAbh1Zwvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, I guess this is more appropriate on Valentine’s Day, but really when is it not a great time for a classic… https://t.co/YfMZMzG33o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see my home friends like every 3 weeks yet I still miss them all the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@findingfletcher makes waking up at 5am so much better with these midnight drops 😂😂😂 #Undrunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mflynn1954 @TwinCitiesChick @mena_ganey @AidenWolfe Congresswoman Omar made the comment about the Benjamins, not AOC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting paint off of my paint plate makes art itself https://t.co/Wm83RvV5du]]></document><document><![CDATA[i local just asked me how much it cost for pussy and to let him bust in me 😫😫😫blocked ❗️❗️❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTattooedProf In some circles, the concept of “respectable businessman” seems to have little to do with how you… https://t.co/5eyWbeh9xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Then start working on your strategy to get that report out. We have a right to see it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 Wonder what's causing it? that's kind of troubling. 🤞he'll be OK in the morning. 😟We just saw a ga… https://t.co/64AQIdaD9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celticriverside I enjoyed reading this and now have a deeper understanding of yesterday’s conversation. You have t… https://t.co/rKzgsMX4DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharonainvegas @ronniemilsap @PamTillis Yeah it was going to be amazing. People suck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im positive the smoke alarm is broken because this place is a smoke house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jayne79 URGENT NOW!!!This pup needs someone to get her now before its to late and she is killed please ADOPT/RESC… https://t.co/rVqqopkiW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS I wish I lived in your fantasy land. Where you live are there unicorns? If so I’m in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Choconananut Pie  bobchinnscrabhouse for tiffipoo225 bday!! @ Bob Chinn's Crabhouse Restaurant https://t.co/bcO0sBwpyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robportman @LindseyGrahamSC @POTUS @SenSherrodBrown @Jim_Jordan @MarkMeadows Which side will you all choose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fanoffuses @KiritoAntares @Michel4PTG @DaynaCymru @MrBroBotBrian @WrecktifyLive @Misty4PTG @acampy @CarlForrest Better Man - Pearl Jam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mnbeckie @Maionegg @stevalley @DebHarkness @SkyOne @OJACKSONCOHEN Ooooh. I could be alllllll for that. #TeamGallowglass]]></document><document><![CDATA[979 Ocean Avenue, Mantoloking, NJ https://t.co/yMCddfBz7U https://t.co/fFNxeok05i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TammyMc94077689 @2boysandmeCc @SykesCharlie @RadioFreeTom @BulwarkOnline Here's a fact-checked write up on the NY… https://t.co/hvPBpvUE9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never been more impatient waiting for a text @LucyCalkins @TCRWP @HeinemannPub #ilovelucy https://t.co/guFlCCW4Ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badger8350 @WisBBYearbook Agreed. New Glarus had an incredibly tough Sectional and came out on top when many predicted otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[tsa agent: “have a safe flight!”  me: “yea, you too!!” https://t.co/fqXitEtdXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[committed babies needed,No sex or nudes. First 3 people who reply and Retweets gets $7500. PayPal and cash app. No… https://t.co/JaO0x5dR4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a waluigi sound while going down on my bf and he laughed for like 5 minutes straight]]></document><document><![CDATA[just be aware and manage your expectations of what you can do after getting tattooed! if you're going to get it and… https://t.co/wqlMk0JYyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kev_johnson @michael_rudloff @jameskilbynet @thecloudxpert I’ve been stuck in hotels without my luggage for an ext… https://t.co/Ws5rlBqd83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @shanemcmahon  turning on @mikethemiz. Why am I not surprised. #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew We know you have a lot on your plate. When will the investigations begin regarding Wilbur’s shenanigans… https://t.co/bmb5uT8O5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las masas hablan por los líderes que se catapultan. Quiere decir: las masas necesitan a ese líder.  Están ahí en el… https://t.co/AeObuwLEJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[They came to fix the doorbell and of course Luna is being her scandalous self and she scared the shit out of bane 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_Coffin @CardinalMahony @LACongress And 🦗 will continue...they must please the bisses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans want to know who is responsible for the murder of Ms Horsford, a Black Mother of 5 during an adult sleepo… https://t.co/RBYdGJOAAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob keeps farting and he’s sleeping on the floor next to my side of the bed 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynnoftrumpland @SandraKayWard5 @DianeLong22 We must design a petition to remove Sharia law from America’s soil https://t.co/RJYTr3WNmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMCTalkingDead And everything she does is so eloquently.  She  didn't even flinch tonight. I loved how casually sh… https://t.co/ttytVLYl5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maaaaan I wish I could wear lashes but that shit would not work with my glasses]]></document></documents></author>