<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@richdemuro Is this Griffith Park? Also, are those the Galaxy Buds? I'm thinking of getting them both since Samsung… https://t.co/xnHbfzZLM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this statement in @TheTechRabbi book #EducatedByDesign - “Outside of education, failure is not an outcome, but… https://t.co/0OG9CugS31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RFriend2012 @funder I thought that Trump and Putin were buddies, unless things are changing because of the power g… https://t.co/sw5q3byKzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night I was Kylie Jenner’s new bff and she let me hold Stormi and while I was holding her she tu… https://t.co/CK0NRGkwiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’M SAVING LIVES AND TAKING NAMES Join me and thousands more in ending death and injury caused by Takata airbags.… https://t.co/vLuFogtHHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KALSKingdom That... isn't what it means at all. It is 2019 and this person doesn't know about Urban Dictionary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m mad he thought this was okay!! #MobileMardiGras #MardiGras https://t.co/U8spVsAmCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just a taste of a fantabulous interview I had with @apollo11movie @neon @CNNFilms Director… https://t.co/aTOGSct1oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to know I’m not the only one who deals with this. @CaPTaiN_Chhun 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else getting geeked over this warm weather and shopping for swimwear? #bikiniseason👙 #lookgoodnaked… https://t.co/MK61rw0Yca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of getting up early to head to the #Ymca #getit  #weightloss #goals #ValentinesDay https://t.co/N0f5YZt3m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is actually never appropriate for anyone to say, "Well, you know women are kids on their own these days" upon le… https://t.co/QVv1s9PrBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killer new lineup #flyerdesign for #comedyattic 🎙 Tickets on Eventbrite 👩🏼‍💻 #flyerart  ・・・ Tuesday night comedy is… https://t.co/T0fqbAScWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake eats Taco Bell 4 days in a row and gains absolutely no weight  I just look at a McDonalds cheeseburger and gain 4 pounds   🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliannebyGrace @DorisZelaya5 @RevLDReed @beverlyfelix3 @endtimeslife @alvin_manova @Bijomjohn1 @emmanuelobi476… https://t.co/OQjf1IVb89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWyden @lindawallner @senatemajldr McConnell is as unamerican as they come. Shame on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Great watch! Liberalized by JFK! Oh, how I miss a real functioning PRESIDENT. Haven't had one since Obama!♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brian_Mejia2 I totally agree! Transparency is key when marketing for a sustainable brand. No one is going to belie… https://t.co/h5T2HqMCby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who do you think you are kidding? You are supposed to be everyone's president. Grow up an act like… https://t.co/T4XedBYu3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't like the taste of burning rainforests in your @KFC and @PizzaHut? Sign this petition to demand they crack dow… https://t.co/VfcKjFbAmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPaulNassif I watch them all Paul, the only thing that would make me happier is to meet you in person and be luck… https://t.co/X8Y5CFnQyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Nothing like trying to divide us as much as possible. Jussie Somollet really is every liberal at heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xiankiefer Ugh that is all you need. Hope you don't get it, too.  How is baby girl doing? Still going home soon?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanPritt No, Ryan. No.  I need an extra weekend day. Before I start Sunday. But I like the effort. Get back out t… https://t.co/DfNt72yMVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah this hits me hard- I’m proud to say that I took a Sunday afternoon nap today even with a to-do list a mile lon… https://t.co/1guznAvy0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattiMurin you are winning Twitter tonight and I feel like you are my spirit animal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some Kaka on my nailzz. Getting my length back, naturally. 💚 https://t.co/dMIv4menE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryKayH188 @marykk196051 @KarinGFB @ernest_barath I love him! Thanks Mary Kay!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 1 in 5 Children Live in Areas Plagued by Conflict and War: Report https://t.co/oWTmhGRDuZ #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama got a fresh mani today💅🏼 from plushwaxandnailbar 💕 I’m loving this @OPI_PRODUCTS color: running with the infin… https://t.co/adJa5a7tb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@X0X0KAYALEXIS @Chance_Riddle nah say it kay, why don’t we just make a gm lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rough night followed by an early morning.. #momlife https://t.co/9ix5LDEeTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_cmt1489 @jasontes5th @CoreyAnnHaydu @knott_michele @Kpteach5 @IowaAmberReads @KReilley5 @erinvarley… https://t.co/HVYNmgjcMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG it is to cold, I'm awake but to cold to get out of bed. I don't live in the North Pole but it feels like I do.… https://t.co/iuPOsneCRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tattoos really don’t even hurt I’ll never understand how people react like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol my doc just straight up asked me if I’m mixed with Asian 😂  It’s been a fat min since someone has second guesse… https://t.co/fvSpCxM1kD]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Jasper, IN! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Sr. Customer Assistance Repre… https://t.co/SQtXph7LGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una imagen ya NO dice mil palabras, al contrario, hay que poner en duda todo lo que dice. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Ann Perkins said she wanted a trash bag full of mashed potatoes, I really felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s meet week when the group chat is blowing up with everyone’s weight cut updates and water intake amount so far today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big titty problems: resting ya titty on the table cause it holds them up🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo Just like Obama reading off the teleprompter. Without it he said uhh, uh, well, uh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Sounders! (@ CenturyLink Field - @centurylink_fld in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/OvK4MzrEdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn is worse! We been known Tristan is a POS cheater so we’re not surprised at all. Khloe was the one who gave j… https://t.co/yPFDfuxT84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mumford &amp; Sons last night at the Q @ Quicken Loans Arena https://t.co/CeXCHI9jtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching a beautiful documentary on Amazon Prime, "The Babushkas of Chernobyl," about a community of… https://t.co/DKx1nleXRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 "Let's"???? YOU tried to intimidate Cohen; we didn't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kellyann Conway is throwing more shade then a tree on @CuomoPrimeTime 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaidaberd Yesss!! I went in with high expectations and was still impressed. So well done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta You are a sad, pathetic group that pretends to care about animals, but only when it suits your narrow minded… https://t.co/IOJdYANzs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacksonville, FL, Early Voting begins Monday, March 4, 2019!  Take 5 people with you and #VoteAnnaBrosche4Mayor! https://t.co/5rrioUhyq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hubby won—so we are watching the #Oscars. 😣🙄It’s making me feel 100 years old; I don’t know anyone. Who are these “moviestars”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are you talking about your imaginary “people” again? I think they’re standing at the border making… https://t.co/USyyHx2Ijq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonallendc Both parties are bought and paid for. I am done casting a vote for the Democrats. At least the Republic… https://t.co/VaXTF3F7dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want send a Big shout out to my son's BFF!!! Happy 16th Jacob!!! Enjoy your day!!! Your the best!!! May the future… https://t.co/pQ4CZygWPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad has such good luck playing those slot machines next time ima tell him to play with my money 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The defense is up for cross examination. The attorney says as you know I’m sorry for your loss. She says thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle you did that. I appreciate black men using their platform to combat violence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateHarding Amen. She didn’t run into an elevator to avoid them. She stood with them and had a good discussion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look ma*, no spot 🤭 #dropback #defineyourwill . (* aka bomchicka_wawa - I admit I did cut the end of the video wher… https://t.co/782Mmfd2ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@east_pccs @pccs_official 275 grade 6 students with well-thought questions about #stolengirl and… https://t.co/Lzsf0lfAJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[going out of my way on another week long training in akron to eat at rasing canes]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lifesum app was so heavily advertised on YouTube but I actually love it for tracking my calories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyV222 @Jacqueline4927 @News3LV Boo! We may get some more Wednesday or Thursday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m here to tell you that hand written thank you notes have not gone out of style. I’ve gotten a few after interviewing people- classy move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up @ 1 AM after SNL!! The Grand Finale 🎮 Who’s taking it? #NorCal or #Socal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was talking to a friend the other day about aging. She is fearful of death and is afraid of growing older. I was… https://t.co/RGp4xxloxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garcia_prisci @MartineYesenia lmfao they be having 2 different conversations too 🤣 one on Facebook one on Snapchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[People find great joy in betrayal and snitching, somehow they think it makes them superior]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother came home from his mission today!   Two years apart, and we don’t look much different! https://t.co/ZM9rO82gtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@costadaniel @joncoopertweets It’s always the same stories, women who are tricked into coming here for a better job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to save without thinking about it? I started using Digit a few years ago and it has quietly saved me thousands… https://t.co/9pRGMI3OxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoda24man Thanks for the fun evening bro. Thank GOD they won and I didn't bring them bad luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i gave my opinion in class today and someone else spoke after me and was really rude and basically said my opinion… https://t.co/9lJ25XSTAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @tribelaw And only if the @vote himself is not complicit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here waiting impatiently for @dustinlynch to perform tonight!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Makes me sick! That keeps me up most of the night, and the first thing I think about! How can they thi… https://t.co/STKvdHGNiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[40lb difference and a whole lot happier. 💗 #gainingweightiscool https://t.co/EZl1Isduag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassieXXIX LMAOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO havent laughed that good in a while thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dariophoto69 No! Nike addirittura ci mette addosso solo leggings leggerini che ti tengono asciutta se corri😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women’s day! Did you know that this was a day started by socialist? The first place it was decl… https://t.co/6buVQd0pjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The roads aren’t bad YET, but who knows what they’ll be like in an hour. Who knows what they’ll be like for me comm… https://t.co/J9ImPbLTOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearby at a cast party (@ St. John's UCC in Northampton, PA) https://t.co/P4sSEXZHWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Society Fam 🤞🏾 Great event last night martin_soaries , cant wait to see whats next ! 💪🏾 @ New Brunswick High School https://t.co/jKmjUZf89b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidMora @RexParade I love Rex throws but didn’t make it out this year. Next year!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A thread of Hicup sitting on me whenever he wants, starting now: https://t.co/eq3naA9BaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaceyyylynnn @LessyFromCali @tajahhhh I need to see that more jacey!!!! Forget a secret weapon you got to use that mf lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockstardust784 @mochipark99 Shy ka dyan.. ako na.. anyeong rockstar :) https://t.co/MErKGlfS6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Eddie has lots of Mickey Mouse and Bunny Boots.  We ended up with BOGS because they are lighter and taller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnlauren1421 You can bet I watched this the second it came out this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's quite a guy. He's quite a character. Isn't that how we would all describe a murderous dictator?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @AstateAlphaGam and @cori_keller1 for the lovely cookie gift and the thoughtful card. I am grateful for a… https://t.co/FtIq6VlMZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We are certainly playing with fascism when we allow our elected officials to usurp their power...,” says protester… https://t.co/3tQEckrToe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all get that tax money and lose all ya sense until it’s gone 🤦🏽‍♀️ Y’all know it doesn’t last forever right ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my first ballet class in 6 years, feels really great to dance again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t smile at your phone around your work aunties, because then they get to doing the fucking most.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking back CNN has failed on many issues. I am surprised anyone even watches this channel!  They are on the wrong… https://t.co/7mCOZHkD6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next 3 days I’ll be working 10 hr shifts but then I’ll have 4 consecutive days off 😭 I’m already looking forward to sleeping in !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryan19621963 What do u mean cause i wanna meet Paulie hes my inspiration hes everything to me i know people hate… https://t.co/YUKQEclwsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbrito93 After watching all of part 2, yep. It made me believe MJ is guilty, no doubt in my mind. Not fishy in the… https://t.co/Y1F7bcrpYX]]></document></documents></author>