<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GreggLintern @JasonThorne_RPP @oaarchitects Clearly a matter of public interest as evidence by built form being a… https://t.co/ECzjb6qiVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Block by Noel, transition lay-up by Westbrook and we have ourselves a game again. Thunder down 3. 6:26 left in the… https://t.co/60vzZbzB5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was another great day for #NKOTB and #BlockNation. Super busy and a long day for all of us- that means yo… https://t.co/xLyTPJiQ6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts and prayers to the Bokus family. Ben openly spoke to me about his battle with Leukemia. His bravery and po… https://t.co/LG9tq1tCcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thorn_john, I'm assuming you're familiar with this from 1884... https://t.co/y2VSz9TI02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau @OECTAProv Please stop avoiding what Canadians want to know: the truth. The more you push it aside t… https://t.co/i5Hy6SMdOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa. After the first season of @serial, the story of Adnan continues. I've got to figure out how to watch this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7: I have accepted a challenge from @MrsSagerSays to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s)… https://t.co/bnKwB5U1no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anastasiaselby I’ve also muted people like Seth Abramson who people constantly retweet into my timeline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaX_xxx @mattyfacial @Cheyenn52006508 I’m sorry that offended you and you’re correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan this morning as we are leaving for work, “today is April Fools day!” Either she is playing a long joke or sh… https://t.co/PDaC10O9Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spanishcvndy You don’t want a lot of titty meat cause when you get old they be hanging real low]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have fuzzy throw pillows on my bed, just now my earring got caught on one and it's almost 3 am, I'm alone in my r… https://t.co/Bi4i5HelDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[One can’t be a true Christ follower and not share one’s faith (Matthew 28:19-20) . . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in my feelings today y’all                     Alexa: play @Kehlani Nights Like This 😭😭😭😭😭😭🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GC_Bands with a great performance!!! #GoCougars https://t.co/nvmedYWXel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goo3r @SenToddYoung Goo, you missed the point of my life lesson. Someday, you find that you need something $$$expe… https://t.co/hyUAphhOvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikiebarb @GooglePlay I restart my phone almost every morning to get it to show up in Google podcast. Thinking about changing players]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubyRiottWWE and @SonyaDevilleWWE are as ready as @SashaBanksWWE and @MsCharlotteWWE was during that hot potato game two years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kareem_manuel @pray4jgivens I hate you! I’m still recovering. I just fucking died.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowco2525 I used to work at a radio station wherr the engineer didn’t want my cords from a retailer. Heat by the M… https://t.co/gIcfmL6zkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinpurcell Love Trumps Hate. Or maybe. Stronger Together. Oh wait ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelHenrich @boston25 Welcome back big fella!!! Glad your on the mend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I take you out to a nice restaurant, and you get chicken tenders and fries, I’m getting up and leaving you there. Bill and all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellegenerico_ Arsenal’s defense is the wall Trump has been looking for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowmorethanever I’d also have to figure out a way to put Willie’s in there. Maybe it’s “Best Hangover Food”’or “Be… https://t.co/rsHmhn32Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnarlyharls I’ll wave at you from across the water https://t.co/J5GMDW728n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC says she’s for the people but I guess she rather kick the #homeless to the curb and have them freeze outside.… https://t.co/yfcFZSo1Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are these Republicans so obsessed with that damn twitter account #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy your evening #culinaryambassador #luigidiotaiuti #washingtondc #dceats #basilicatadascoprire #igersbasilicata… https://t.co/E9vExvhQN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @walker_sherri to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews-just… https://t.co/pHKVLXhqJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently New Zealand was the first place women had the right to vote (1893). No wonder it keeps getting left off… https://t.co/fWPdSY4HBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have that fucking muffin song in my head all the time. Idk why. I’ve been brainwashed. Fr fr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man #MLSisBack and @chicagotribune isn't running like a single story on @ChicagoFire wtf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiki_f_baby_ @Ohluisluis @dan_20 C and I are also in! So I am excited for you guys to meet C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only if the event was held next weekend I think would have put my name in the hat for this! I'll be visiting Margar… https://t.co/sgA3CKafyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greengrows @montanaisthebes Run as fast as you can if you see Tippi Hedren]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigHarroldWA @pretapartager @DJ_brown_town @TJCarpenterShow @OssiansFolly @ophiuchus_1 @thenation I always thoug… https://t.co/gSxk4zO0av]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining my colleagues from across Indiana learning how to better educate the whole student.  #Wholechildsummit2019 https://t.co/0XEFwmy2Mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Wedding Made In Heaven...Or Hell? #chavezhighschool #classof2005 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/eeGBpZVNi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Predictions are hard to make, especially ones about the future.” Yogi Berra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLSPilotHockey finishes off a 3-1 win over @SOUTHBLUEDEVILS and will advance to the #MHSAA Regional Semifinal and… https://t.co/l6Fs0o3FmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MQuigley1963 @KathleenHarrym1 @FDS_NaturallyMe @MillieThom Thanks, Melisa😇🌹 3 movies no explanation  1 Jack Reache… https://t.co/RC4QSMwMOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz i believe you have daddy issues. Your love for @realDonaldTrump  proves it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting a petition to put anybody who eats this on the other side of trumps wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoBellTeam store #24827 allows their managers to smoke weed with minors but fire people for ciggerette breaks required by law]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tubaman2020 @SarahGregory02 @ChatonNyx Prayers for you special ladies🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[My highass really gave the cashier 20 to pump in my tank &amp; i literally got in my car and left without pumping 😂😭 lmao i came back tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like some cops just got bullied to hard in school. And now they have power and they be doing to much  cause… https://t.co/jzBEB18qMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total scumbag creeper pedophile this guy should be in prison right now I have no idea why we're talking about this… https://t.co/uPyQXGYrkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a must ! Coaches must put their athletes in every possible scenario . If you don’t do it practice you can’t… https://t.co/yk9bob4RLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Well I hope he knows in the words of Yoda. https://t.co/6TDBPsVfcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my Charleston SC peeps. This Sat I will be in your city. We SOLD OUT! this show last time @keithdcomedy knows h… https://t.co/AzhVJ87cEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked China Crisis back in the day but I have no clue what any of their songs are about. Maybe that's the appeal? #Forgotten80s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanSheput Debes unirte a @AlanGarciaPeru y formar un equipo de eruditos en materia de buen en gobierno en temas d… https://t.co/B0vUKRQYJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[O sure I’m the attacker because I cried last Thursday to every boy calling my idea stupid. Every time I tried to sp… https://t.co/0kBxdn38Dx]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now an old man raped her??? This is all over the place   I’m done live tweeting this movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #WestJefferson, OH, check out this #Healthcare job via the link in our bio: EMT, Para… https://t.co/GnZ394TONx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsambleaSV Por que poctas,NO SACAR UNA TABLA DE SUELDOS PARA FUNCIONARIO SI FUERA POSIBLE PARA LOS 3 ORGANOS DEL ESTADO]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/5Q3f7ctHL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The train could cost as much as $100B. The wall will cost at least as $7B. You might want to check… https://t.co/QaYrl3g4to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vjphotos17 I will play around with it this weekend and upload some stuff from it. It has built in IR LEDs and an I… https://t.co/nagqDAbrIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClimateBen @nadiabaltimore That seems like about 95% of global population.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a finish at Vegas! I was hoping Jones would put Ford in victory lane, but how can you not be excited to see… https://t.co/Dpd4cTmgRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One session down... 7 to go 💪 (@ Westchase Fitness in Tampa, FL) https://t.co/L3vSf6IYa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comienza la Cuaresma, tiempo de arrepentimiento y conversión que nos acerca a Jesús y nos mueve a renovar nuestras… https://t.co/PTIkLi8ngH]]></document><document><![CDATA[OL/DL LOOKING FOR A SCHOOL. COME BE PART OF SOMETHING SPECIAL AT RPA. WE ABOUT TO DO BIG THINGS AND IT STARTS WITH… https://t.co/t6vB1l4k4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaBartiromo We have Communists in Congress imposing their ideology on companies all the time..That's what Commu… https://t.co/HnzLmXdY47]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little office magic at the offices of Condé Naste. #california #hollywood #losangeles #magic #magician… https://t.co/eMKrxvN0BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 Your absolutely right! Our generation was blessed!! So sad to know that my grandchildren will never experience that same life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People like boarder patrol, police, and fbi etc. it could benefit all of America in the long run. BUT I DO NOT AGRE… https://t.co/dsu03lUCjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Nebraska basketball fans and historians, this is an awesome archive of information. Well done @OWHsports,… https://t.co/pbopyllDex]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HowToTrainYourDragon is airing on @NBC TONIGHT.  Join @DWAnimation for their #DragonsChat as we watch live togethe… https://t.co/ihROyxwvxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m guessing Louisville will be working on breaking the press tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a time when I had ranked what I considered to be my favorite 5 musical geniuses, but all of them have sin… https://t.co/nq3sshADyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to both Grapeland and Shelbyville tomorrow.   Reg 3 will be represented great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple of achievements on @Minecraft bedrock that won't trigger for me even though I'm doing them. Is there known b… https://t.co/xanZWtK92b]]></document><document><![CDATA[A note I found nailed to a rafter of this old garage. Why it was all the way up there, and how, is lost to history.… https://t.co/0unEhKPaLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you visit your best friend from high school, and see yourself well-represented in her photo album. https://t.co/cQjjfoYwAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1fragmentedmind Nope,  i wish i could favorite peeps so i always saw their posts first @TwitterSupport are you listening?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pandora ad: “this is five finger death punch and you’re about hear our new song Champaign”  Me: *heart beat intensi… https://t.co/ehV4sGWpI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleansing the Soul #tednugent #mostwontunderstand @ Mentor Headlands, Ohio https://t.co/J7Z3VrzLTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today i becomes a godfather again and i couldn’t be more proud. I’m racking up god kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New sky survey reveals hundreds of thousands of galaxies @CNN  https://t.co/8TJAknqgWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDVR Yet again the Dems ignore our state Constitution (TABOR) by trying to call a tax a "fee", to avoid giving VOT… https://t.co/EpbyE9k1N6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jfigs28 @NickEvershed25 @yaniboy2310 You can always suck your way out of any situation my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to really stop playing and get me that privacy screen ... My social media is just way to much ! Lol 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warsaw and the admin’s performance at Munich: back-to-back embarrassments.  Do these guys have no sense of the worl… https://t.co/RIy67DkJw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah. @KingJames delivered on his promise. As a loyal @cavs fan and Akron native, I want Lebron to succeed wherever… https://t.co/zLGc51FRhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jachillcphotos @rockthatcon @msouth1 @jennlewisphoto @SAJORFFEJ @millerslab @FundySoftware @17hatsHQ… https://t.co/g2ZyT7X9XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayMcCaffery1 @10NewsBrandeis @10News It was pretty cool seeing Cheryl post pictures of her butterflies in Austral… https://t.co/Ydkq2GdtVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I21cHealth Please watch my video and retweet if comfortable: https://t.co/PcXJLPWolm I am a stage IV HPV tonsil ca… https://t.co/hmP1hRqdi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Launchpad1307 @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews If you think the God is for the party that has legislated #killing over 60… https://t.co/4LvsmjenpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosenbergradio @WWEDanielBryan @TrueKofi I honestly can’t think of a bigger moment or pop at Mania than Kofi over… https://t.co/Ew97qBuqGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSchultzChicago @Lawrence @AriMelber @StormyDaniels Agree. They have a lot of viewers because they’re the only big… https://t.co/fTGlZHYSvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Other then letting us know some nazis are good people, what have you done besides pretending to pray...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bulldogwgr Cool. I'll be on the look out. @TroegsBeer I feel is a sneaky good label. Not quite @SneakyJoeWGR good,… https://t.co/54XKPJgUQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VANS_66 I hope you take action and fire the employee cursing at children   Until Yao, my 3 kids are banned from your stores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MexicoBeis @LigaMexBeis Felicidades a ambos, @gordoa_luz y @bluejr6 Dios los Bendiga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six days until my post #MardiGras book signing and writing workshop in Mandeville.   Will you be there? https://t.co/YtrR8g22kt]]></document></documents></author>