<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Helenhs These idiots. Very scary. We need to get control for the sake of these weak minded falling for this BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're going to want to have our Severe Weather Team 2 app handy as heavy rain moves through metro. Get the latest… https://t.co/meELhGUx3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toriiicooop Way to go @CarolDaHedghog , we are SO PROUD of you! Keep up the GREAT work!!! ❤️🦡🥎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbouzy He thinks Clinton is still running? Or does he think Hillary’s spirit has possessed Kamala’s body?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SVTuri_ @patsygee_ At least she HAS A JOB you don’t even work. No mas estas echado con el culo arriba 🤦🏻‍♀️😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @JenniferAdams to post 7 covers of books I love—no explanations—no reviews—just the… https://t.co/uRSENh8fih]]></document><document><![CDATA[another 4 times after this tweet. then called my crying bc she loves me.. THATS MY BESTIE!!💓💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OraliaAcostaG @LECHAMPS55 @lesliegastelum1 @NeriaLara Tan Bello es tener un hijo. Factible fuera el aborto tal vez… https://t.co/yJumVApI4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[The catalyst for problem solving is always leadership. A leader has the courage to challenge the status quo and to… https://t.co/yS5xvSg0Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come check out Architect Coffee Company, opening next week! @ Architect Coffee Co. https://t.co/eGWBe2EE4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll always remember you by Hannah Montana really be hitting hard these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not religious, but if I was, there’s no way I could give all the credit to just one god. Earth is so incredible… https://t.co/n2cnDjNToJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love @CiscoWisco. i love him a h*ck ton. that’s it, that’s the tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting outside in a tank top and shorts. The girl next to me (who lives in Vegas) is in boots, leg warmers, pa… https://t.co/Oyhd6OxbSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claborn_berkley i think the point is,, men shouldnt be able to decide what women can or cannot do w our own bodies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@langsciencebes @ItsOnMyList_ @librarygal67 @gatorphimu @kggreen59 Low battery, but a great walk with my girls❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/HFAHCMYPMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I thought for sure the Pine Creek Canyon was closer than this...”. After a trek, it is far!!!  Literally the deser… https://t.co/AfucaHudHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanmasolari111 @josuefumero Eso en papel suena bien. La realidad es que la plantilla se ha ido debilitando los últimos veranos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to say that my extreme unwillingness to leave for the airport any earlier than necessary is out of cont… https://t.co/FDNaZS2zcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the #IrishtotheCore #Sweepstakes daily for a chance to win the grand prize and instant prizes up to $100! https://t.co/3aSRkRdceB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@april492018 @MoniqueBonner13 @eliznoelle @ReddStatic @DougDavidsonYR @JordiVilasuso @YandR_CBS The Mal Young addit… https://t.co/SXl3cpG9nj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @AOC TEAD AND LEARN. HIW SBOUT A DEBATE W CANFICE LOVE TO SEE THAT GIRLIE🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got super high and ate shitta Girl Scout cookies and croutons last night? 🤷🏻‍♀️ Idk man. Low key dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there anything that Charles Barkley isn’t allowed to talk about? lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun with Marie at her Dream Board workshop 😍 @ Hoboken, New Jersey https://t.co/wF1LNEkgnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southyarradan @felixgonzalez_v @marcorubio #USA is the best Country in the world and we are fighting to save it from the left]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANTES ➡️ DESPUÉS Rinomodelación sin cirugía + Aumento de labio 💯 📣Pregunta por las promociones que tenemos este mes… https://t.co/6KXVENeOt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[U N S T O P P A B L E  “Therefore let us be grateful for receiving a kingdom that cannot be shaken, and thus let us… https://t.co/Z0r7oEUFMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN PARENTS: Are you looking for a day care? Already have one? An Oklahoma mother is urging parents to research da… https://t.co/bDdtmjMLsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Brick House Tavern + Tap - @brickhousett in South Plainfield, NJ https://t.co/bn2xkmhnjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom broke up with budda and I don't blame her. Communication is valuable in a relationship. She's happy with her… https://t.co/2PM9FQJDQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanOBoyle I am my love!  Quick break and then into tech for Admissions and Emilia. Would be great to catch up xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying Galentines with my sweet girls🌈🌺🌸🍫🌹🥰🥰❤️❤️❤️ @ Higher Grounds Coffee Shoppe &amp; Bakery https://t.co/ejvU791eHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[from this point on...ima be honest with my emotions because If I'm being honest, I done been through way too much..… https://t.co/IgP7nbREpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarnGin @seanhannity @HillaryClinton I don't want to see that. Knowing it exists shows @realDonaldTrump is no bett… https://t.co/EbazZPZCuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Texas_Dexter Haven't seen that view for years.  But I can remember how it felt. Thanks for doing the video. I'm 69.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO @GoodwillIntl I love u and want to work for you so bad I’ve applied to 6 of your locations in the past 2 year… https://t.co/oylCNdv0RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcpoll I just don't understand how there is this much a morality in his world? What is it? My mother used to speak… https://t.co/WEaLWVkSjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We run into issues as we age, finding a job at our experience,finding friends after moving, understanding Medicare… https://t.co/L4qBZ9lDA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only think keeping me from not vomiting in this Uber is singing.. Work It by Missy Elliot just came on... please pray for my Uber driver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guterres submitted the report - which is based on Syria’s charges against Israel - to the UN Human Rights Council (… https://t.co/r4v1wWh23s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homes are selling faster than we can list them.   Call me today at 267.421.4531 and let’s talk about adding your ho… https://t.co/H4iROkgzcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[never in my life have I had someone make sure I made it home safely, makes sure I’m never hungry, calls me througho… https://t.co/7nbNsNpuzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I’d have to see snow again this year and I wake up to it SNOWING in ARIZONA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time we reconsider lifetime federal judicial appointments Judges need to answer to the people  I propose a 10… https://t.co/MTXwsyIsFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav little dude from El Salvador needs a kidney transplant due to kidney failure plllssssss keep him in your pra… https://t.co/CcCsEKF9jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Colin Kaepernick is an embarrassment to the NFL &amp; a joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieXHunter Ad tempting as it is to make a comment, I won't directly respond about him and promote his disgusting diatribe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelackmeyer @NewsOK Would be such a shame to destroy this historically important OKC structure.         Yet und… https://t.co/iEgEIflPVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beetlenaut @wackyvorlon @TooManyScooters @RueNahcMohr Sounds like you need to build a dangerous tube synth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammy_jay294 really gets me. He woke me up with breakfast in bed, tea and a soft whisper in my ear saying “let’s g… https://t.co/TK526XgrWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[when he hasn’t kissed anyone but has a 6 year old daughter. https://t.co/xlbJ6tpGUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever have a girl I literally want to name her stormy bc I think it’s so cute but then again everyone will thin… https://t.co/FZbtodMmfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjsvids @LindseyStirling @evanescence I think it’s just park admission. I honestly haven’t paid for a theme park t… https://t.co/gcceApfCXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or it could be my last look at Hollywood’s Sonic the Hedgehog. #notMySonic]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have contests on who can #sleep the most. So far, I am in the lead. #leo #leothecat #mrcat #mrman #mrmeow… https://t.co/LTx8u7LndM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstbornDan You do not need to undergo a background check if you buy a gun online, through a gun show, or through some private sales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mariela_Isabel Bitch it’s free food and a reason to go out lmao sounds worth it to me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley @DebraMessing I’m exactly the same way except with pencils. I’ve corrupted my children too. 5mm only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstrosAngel10 @WCW_looky Don’t wait for the man. If he wants you he will show you. Not worth putting energy into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Trump e - prisoners will have their right to vote re- instated . He's done so many good things for our ec… https://t.co/4ZfdU6UJVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophie knows her mama doesn’t feel well cause I’m getting extra cuddles ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[l seriously believe she was put in senate to deflect,  look what we all talk about...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bad at Twitter. Those young activists are @IamxDaance, @Vandii_M, and @kae_elms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurleyWpd Great interview today with @LivePDWestChat 🖤💙  Could I plesse get a follow from you?  Have a safe nite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom’s the oldest of 5 and the only girl lmfaooooo my uncles be mad scared of her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer and warfare are two separate and distinct activities. Prayer is towards God and warfare is toward the enemy.… https://t.co/pVbcBOKGYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei For Trump, any time he doesn’t get his way, it’s a goddamn emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stand corrected, 6th straight Prescott player selected MBC player of year! Parker is the 6th!!! Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @taylornation13 @taylorswift13 @LongLivedDreams and me @enakj need follows!!! Please and Thanks!🙏🙏👑🙏🙏🙏✨🌴✨💙💜💛… https://t.co/KjCEmjSYc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[No words. What did we do to be blessed with this kid of ours? So proud. #UofA #UofAmom #UofAdad #Chandler #AZ… https://t.co/4exoHr8ezk]]></document><document><![CDATA[a few months ago i could hardly tolerate beer now i refuse to go out to eat with my friends if there isn’t beer on tap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyleMSpencer @AOC Me too. Especially now that I'm old enough to finally appreciate everything she has done for our… https://t.co/t9PMHuF0qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlosfnorena A very nice slave who has really just been misunderstood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joegeezi actually @fivepointspizza in Nashville is better than both 🤗😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorkymum @FAWCCapeCod @eastendbookspt Yes! Every day for a year, Ross Gay wrote an essay on something that delight… https://t.co/i1UzBG0CyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future Freshman Night- Welcome Parents #cte #findyourpath https://t.co/Q0OyD063eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu You are unworthy of ever having any kind of woman in your life ever!  I INVITE women to make their… https://t.co/unolvJKqAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acompañando a los jefes! 🤯🤫🤭 (at @Apple Somerset in Troy, MI) https://t.co/o7ZO1t3Vhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our very own kind, caring, hardworking principal @ConnorCougars @SuffernCSD https://t.co/6a7eQavkpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s about that time to make some moves off the tablet lmfao https://t.co/UVu8kBuWii]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a fact that You only get charged for extra sauce when you’re ugly...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that @DBHIDS shifted that conversation with Journey of Hope and led to housing and moving away from the ‘care… https://t.co/jlZ8BeywWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cowfish. I really wanted to sit on it, but the saddle was all wet from the rain 😕 @ The Cowfish - Raleigh https://t.co/yxJudY0WxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My room was too hot, so I went and fell asleep in my back room! That doesn’t mean much to most; but I own my home,… https://t.co/emnayZ80ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aneerinyourear idek, bruhh . . but that was real ballsy of em to do . . smh 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair @GMA @RobinRoberts Thank you for sharing your story! ❤️ I have many friends with MS, one with an aggres… https://t.co/P3fRDtnp1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamaPKL @sweetgeorge48 I watch football, but I agree with you on not disrespecting our Flag and the National Anthe… https://t.co/SW2UFF2pRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for @JRMotorsports in the #eNASCARHeat Pro League Draft! Go to https://t.co/JoKy52ll4n to cast your vote for JRM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS NEVER surrender, NEVER give in! @VP @KellyannePolls @PressSec @seanhannity @rushlimbaugh @marklevinshow… https://t.co/IFuSJFCjVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally did a grown up thing and scheduled my eye doctor appointment 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyStrang I'll pull out the boat. I'm pretty sure we've got some decent flows on Lake Erie right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS More baseless Fox Deep State crap from someone who should know better. He ma… https://t.co/Ax4F6xohRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Types of Subtle Workplace Harassment That Should Be on Your Radar https://t.co/CP37MnpBl3 via @ELI_Training]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jowrotethis Jon's death was significant for two things: Ollie and Melisandre.   What about Brienne and Jaime's hot… https://t.co/MmHiXYrVkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam and his friend were hit and spun around tonight by someone who ran a red light at the intersection of Cherry Rd… https://t.co/nkp7HHR8RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Where is Bernie Sanders saying anything about this representative; he is Jewish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only chic at the gym on sunday! There is vacation time but still some space to workout and lock some time for w… https://t.co/iSQxL2xUdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTBus where is the Q59 that was supposed to be at Grand &amp; Bedford a minute ago?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BebeRexha Like I said before He will ALWAYS be your “Daddy” and you will ALWAYS be his little girl !! Anything pos… https://t.co/rN3VuZNk4u]]></document></documents></author>