<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that judges a restaurant based on if they have the “good” ranch or not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[science in India? Claims have included that ancient Indians designed jets that flew on donkey urine. It gets 40 mile to a gallon of urine]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun is out in Texas and the blue dial halioswatches is looking fiiiiine!!! @ROLDORFco @jamesstacey @redbaryvr… https://t.co/yUXDrJrWZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never Thirst Again🌷  The living water that Jesus offers, bans thirst in all who drink it forever🌹  Jesus satisfies… https://t.co/IJFu1fnuHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday  Feb.18th @ 12noon est  HPB from A-Z Call 1st MVP Executive Dalianna Rose Host Director Charles Stout .. 774… https://t.co/EVLKUTHw36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Violet Ray by @relicbrewing @ Steelton — https://t.co/pd7UArNIxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not impressive start to the #1 team @Vol_Hoops  I figure they be up by 10 by now over a team that the #2 took to th… https://t.co/dLPxaXPJqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even 10 minutes into the game and I’ve already seen Benn make two dumb plays.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbyjamesnv No, I’m no longer with the company, but I’ll still produce some content stay tuned here for details]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new FOX show @InnocentOnFOX gives the legal drama a twist -- focusing on those wrongly convicted in our justice… https://t.co/nYTtPU61aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 mile training #hike this morning. A few flakes in the air... #backpacking #outdoors #Hiking #philmont https://t.co/8R6cn84C0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aspleenic @srhtcn WAIT! HOLD ON! I see a few Latin America flags, but I don't see #PuertoRico 🇵🇷. 😉 Would you like… https://t.co/Tt2An2cFge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenJenMichelle @briantheguppie Bischoff sold it so well when Austin came out.  He had the Oh S*it look down to a tee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew_harto @croberts19791 @JoseRolon2610 @colton_kennemur @Tyler_Karam @ChicopeeDepot21 @DanielleKida1… https://t.co/asfelFIoKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know sharing is caring but man does it get old sharing my $300 textbook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is 2:15 am and im drinking a spacedust watching coco... life is content rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very fine and smooth sour ale. Not overly soured or hopped. Yum! - Drinking a Juice Boost by @VictoryBeer @ Southea… https://t.co/xFHrXazKP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see a lot of bitches who say they down for me ain’t really down for me. Then when you try to ask em about it they… https://t.co/31iPOs8UlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m predicting the trending color of summer 19’ and the rest of the year will be Orange. #hearditherefirst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylansGotTweets Why would an audiophile give a fuck about a momentary text to a friend to see where they’re at in the venue?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncle Brian had a Marvelous time watching Captain Marvel in IMAX at the Irvine Spectrum today with @millerseffect F… https://t.co/Fyjzwyj8w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empowered by #MeToo, a new generation fights sexual abuse in South Korea's schools: When students reported that a m… https://t.co/owmDgCr5sT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrookedIntriago Ain't Honesty a Bitch sometimes!!!??? https://t.co/bMqCtj5xEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practicando para el cumpleaños de la banderita en San Nicolás de los Garza https://t.co/vgSthIa4KY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Certified_TonyG @sportsmockery Great article!! The new players added to the elevated play of stars Kane, Toews, Ke… https://t.co/KGF82FzZJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindyWbal Yup, the dismantling of the broken franchise ...... heartbreaking to watch and endure]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @SarahDOdom to post the cover of 7 books I love - no review, no explanation. On day 2, I challe… https://t.co/r05oq8sIj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Def Jam Fight For NY (Request) - Team Match at Dragon House (Hard) https://t.co/yC2kTYkTH1 via @YouTube @defjam… https://t.co/mIM8xZ7QQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date night with mommy at the Charro Days Gala!!! Moms a lifetime member of Charro Days Board and the first female p… https://t.co/vnIZ2jdo9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNC These ill advised, unfounded, disgraceful attacks on @Ilhan will cost you. You will lose 2020 and beyond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The records this kid is bear is ridiculous especially when you take how many minutes he’s played.. get 30+ rest of… https://t.co/frZODF1cxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxgarciarivas @waltervitiok Como quisiéramos tener en el plantel actual, mínimo 3 jugadores con tu mismo perfil.… https://t.co/7kVgX1h76V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone a happy Saturday morning. It feels so surreal to be waking up knowing I will be having my first sh… https://t.co/WuzEX3CABE]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there a single politician who has felt the need to condemn @IlhanMN who doesnt take money from aipac?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanMacAlpine @KingstonFronts @PetesOHLhockey Another rebuild. Is there a worse #chl franchise?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey This is hilarious. This young lady and her students have… https://t.co/foohVZz9aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo shutangina 3 pending papers ko sa psych at 1 sa human dev ano asan ang pag babago?¿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winner winner chicken! Nice little break from work! #backtothegrid   https://t.co/32Mla9Oxg1 https://t.co/WNuQtTXR4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t see how yll sit around in dirty ass houses and be comfortable with it. I used to get my ass beat for leavin… https://t.co/dPOJLC6POa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisschrismcgirt @DylanMcGirt @BasketballDMHS The Tarheel day!! The best! https://t.co/ycBpRHAzR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in Tulsa, and you like free food, do this. @TreysTulsa https://t.co/jxiL0GCUiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @sweet_baby_j_21 @realDonaldTrump Being black doesn’t mean your not a racist though wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re a parhetic, criminal loser and hated by most of America. It has nothing to do with Spike Lee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids smoking gas in illegal states be like "through the wööds we raaaAaAnn"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting and telling piece by my former Post colleague @HelloLauraKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know some of the country wants to send Florida adrift...but when the invasion comes, how will they counter this F… https://t.co/j5SCwexkQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay safe - see you on Tuesday! @ Johnson Middle School https://t.co/Dtdt3QY6QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParadiseWC_ @CR_Vulcan Chris wouldn’t have joined anyways. He was too busy watching one of the top basketball play… https://t.co/WcCVsGxq5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started the day cleaning up Archie's shits on the stairs. At least it gave me some time to listen to a podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first Bodybuilding show, way out of my comfort zone but felt great. Huge thanks to coach jbjackson42 and my wife… https://t.co/O62T0YIDCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nima1007 @FollowYourHeart is really good, @FieldRoast chao cheese is really good, @MiyokosCreamery and… https://t.co/ZJxRMdCuMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squatcharmy @FrankenCap Dude complain all you want, your defense of @TuckerCarlson is evidence enough of your support of #ChildBrides]]></document><document><![CDATA[High winds, storms, and other sudden danger to physical property, owned or leased by #entrepreneurs, command on-sit… https://t.co/ExQDDCn0oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xsnyderman Since Russell is an all star he's moved his target to Marks He literally wanted to trade Russell for the Isaac kid on Orlando]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/zynN5U9Sjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 3 - writing tools. All I need is my #typewriter, paper, notebooks, and an inspirational wood cut-out for… https://t.co/5dHWPc4dAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The H.D. Woodson STEM Academy is seeking volunteers to conduct mock interviews with the students to prepare them fo… https://t.co/usQREGiNqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aj_youngwatson hey man. We seen you HYPED up for our bobcats yesterday. True class!!! Best of luck in your future]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeDanWeber @rsdisco_ron @adeleshiv @ShireenQudosi What is the Goal of BDS and i'm talking the actual Goal and no… https://t.co/0xtFrGHEDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went to demi.mpls for Ela’s birthday round two and a late Valentine’s Day. @gavinkaysen served a delicious menu:… https://t.co/WGowIhsl19]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Kerouac, Palahniuk, and Bukowski.  Ask the Dust, Infinite Jest, The Catcher in the Rye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @PFTPMPosse The @PFTPMPosse has decided that my appendix is named Stats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meteorologist45 @ferrazzledazzle @Jamespelirojo @iget_buckets35 Yep. Coby’s stock has sky rocketed. So he should g… https://t.co/xR058fe2Md]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeFGabel @ColdHeart_Prj @goldfinches12 @IreneWoodbury @JayJayjay2683 @kimberleycale @lamarjackson2 @littlefabshop… https://t.co/yc8TtVTgYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna be the first English teacher to never assign a paper because grading S.U.C.K.S.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my co founder and I have been running paid ads to generate leads for @liverecover the last week or so and grown our… https://t.co/8DVNMEnM39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCannon Just got these off Amazon. I even copped me the wireless earbuds as well. And I don't even rock wireles… https://t.co/dxj35JT3z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far the Dems in the House have offered open borders, infanticide and anti-semitism as their agenda. Not to menti… https://t.co/dyKvXiXZql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Five billion is five billion more than Mexico paying for it. When does that start happening?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, let’s take this momentum to Purvis tomorrow! JV at noon, Varsity at 2. #bringtonightsbats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuddyGoodboyEsq @GracieLynx00 Workplace proposals just seem like playing with fire, on a lot of levels]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is calling for sanctification. Saints - World = Separate. https://t.co/qgpoQ7xXUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewicki_mateusz @Tash_Witk @bikerider1485 @urwis1977 Tam byl https://t.co/v2Vz0StKft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar Castaneda owner and pastor of the Kill Bill Church! Thanks for showing me around and telling me the story abo… https://t.co/YZuuk6aMu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWynalda Really 2 questions arise: Why flick his ear? What an idiot...And in what world does that cause you to… https://t.co/cjzGYF6Bdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Starbucks in Dubuque, IA https://t.co/8BP07RizbX https://t.co/bDfZtnSLBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darelightx @LockrCockr Well gave you all choices.  Enjoy your lock time]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost @holainspiral ・・・ Terminando de grabar un nuevo promocional para niños!!!!! Con nuestros talentosos locutor… https://t.co/exWSSnj2NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pitch 25 Beer Park - @pitch25htx in Houston, TX w/ @dutkae https://t.co/LZNGVbW3fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram… https://t.co/mxpSKUn0Cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow our minds think a lot alike @risaaguadalupe_  Made this earlier Great Memories  Happy Birthday @DoloresMya  Luv… https://t.co/O24MuYUqC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenRosatoABC7 I watch abc ny almost every morning. I live to watch gma as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDRedBull8 @MiserableSDFan @Zippy_TMS Aww I threw the BP for the 25-50 try outs. About 150 pitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__jube @StephKaylor2006 @daxshepard I do. They’re all stoked too. In fact, it’s my girls who get most excited abou… https://t.co/E9U9xtHmOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPac94054821 @DaleJr @KyleLarsonRacin @KurtBusch @CGRTeams GM miss K you off today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a month away for my cosplay photo shoot events  #cosplay #cosplayer #cosplayofinstagram #redlandscosplay @ Syl… https://t.co/Tsb1SDdcVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodishely @VMwareTAM @vmwocto @raminder01 I see some familiar faces. 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winterfest2019 @ TopJump Trampoline &amp; Extreme Arena https://t.co/zxvslDg8T8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realcindyg @Melonhe35859244 @DonaldJTrumpJr They have, Al Franken for one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth0505 @JaedenDoran @HandsomeLatania @jenny1027 Good morning. Deep freeze in Illinois. Not much new snow and tha… https://t.co/Jf0ZYGpxmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Banana Spamcakes - Jack Johnson #RuinASongWithOneWord @jimmyfallon @FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:38.7°F WchillLow:23.5°F Wind:0 mph Dir:W Baro:Rising Rain2day:0.00in Hum:61% UV:0.0 @ 18:00 02/21/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdyPackard @notwokieleaks This is actually in the middle of what's been a 2 year straight tour of her dancing, bu… https://t.co/1Yp092vB2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RG_Notorious @RotoGrinders I want to give a shoutout to Noto for still being a solid DFS analyst. I’ve been away f… https://t.co/IfWiDrj6Hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of a week of solo parenting while @meggrob is out of town, and I spent it with this guy having to stay ho… https://t.co/8gyxM9UCua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Premier Doug @fordnation, Attorney General @C_Mulroney, and Minister @SylviaJonesMPP for introducing the… https://t.co/WUBv84vwHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealScottWolter Just wanted to add my congratulations on your show being picked up by @travelchannel — am a big fa… https://t.co/0MHiIbUwly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a visit to my ol’ stomping grounds at Sebastian Inlet.  #Florida vacation #sebastianinlet #floridafishing… https://t.co/or0xNnZBXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Having a vocal ALLY is desperately needed by everything we all are. We are ALL everything.... there… https://t.co/guDxGVdCfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep...this #quote sounds #quant, lol...but it's full of #DYNAMITE! Yeah!  DY-NO-MITE...]]></document></documents></author>