<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I miss Brassard... I miss Hagelin... I miss Grabner... I miss Miller... but none have hit me harder than Zuccarello 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEPOTISM. I don't care if it's a good cause or not. But also, I wouldn't be surprised if it ever came out that the… https://t.co/CKOWffvXtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been here for almost 2 weeks and there has been so many earthquakes waking me up #earthquake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 3, your down on points. Time to come out swinging.... #winthefight  @jeremyIFM https://t.co/XP5xFlj05N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman Presidents don't have that kind of authority, but dictators do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Michele obama is fake nasty and ugly a mistake in america now the left calls her rock star,ha,put her… https://t.co/H15c66elX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daem__ Bra glasses flew near da microwave had to tell em like bra yo shit right over here👇🏾😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[imma scream and shout for what I love.  Passionate but I don’t give no fucks🖤 https://t.co/c3qoLV0oK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will now be replacing calling people assholes with calling them “fucking ostomies”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! How are ya? @JeffreeStar approved pink. They should be delighted.  https://t.co/0kIWykjOSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole body hurts. I am very tired. There is mud and glitter in all of the unexpected places. Already planning fo… https://t.co/YQGlnRYwDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol this is just funny #comedy #tee-hee #grin #merry https://t.co/2HpzBCE2y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nystacey @TheLizLincoln @GretchenRily Ugh. I was almost 30. *goes to die of old age* LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some women fear the fire. Some women simply become it 💜 vapinsin #grape 🍇 #pandorablue #vapinsin #vapemodels… https://t.co/hELg0Wdy3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “I’m just gonna have one more...” *hits bottom of Milano bag*  #guesswhoneedsadiet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dramatic digging...Advantage Menu!!! #ronwillsurvive https://t.co/QaAbAh0WAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrieksada1 @LVNancy @RepJerryNadler yes he is Nadler and Schiff are both going to be exposed this investigation… https://t.co/YI5N1iC5RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time I compliment my boyfriend he asks me if I like him better than I like Gritty and quite frankly I Did This To Myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️Catching snowflakes❄️  #julieteveleigh #winter #snowyday #snowangel #snowflakes @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/qC0vYvKURU]]></document><document><![CDATA[[#FFCC]  Join me next Saturday for a 90-minute charity ride @burton13_dc for the hopkinskimmel Cancer Center. I'll… https://t.co/BGkSXFHh4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol that’s true! Just finished an excellent book called Daughter of War by Brad Taylor and am currently reading Amb… https://t.co/nKSCAyqoLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiedetore @K_Schweigert @themcconicowire This entire thread has made me so happy! #scrapsfordays]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Erie County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/PrecQmIhZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[First steps toward adopting #bebrave   #bekind classroom norms. Appreciate the takeaway #tdgmath2019 @MandyMathEd https://t.co/L1RaKAdqQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dp779e2017 ¡Como quieras! ¿O tal vez comentarios en la página YouTube misma? así otros podrán leer y añadir sus sugerencias o ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A reminder of a time with more expensive hair bills https://t.co/M5sGusMVvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indydunn78 @LasVegasLocally @Palms This are steep needs. Haven't you heard of the new luxury outhouse? Only $20 an… https://t.co/PkFdmqVaTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many new construction homes built in the last 7-15 years have the wheat colored walls shown here. Painting a 2000+… https://t.co/IifvUv8b4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAY GOVENOR LOOK AT UR 3RD WORLD STATE.FILTH + SICKNESS HURTING REAL AMERICANS...RATS OVER TAKING UR STATE  HOW MAN… https://t.co/i6ow9CHuZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[*tap* *tap* 🗣️ @bikemorebmore just won advocacy organization of the year at #bikesummit19! Thank you @BikeLeague fo… https://t.co/hKmGBK47JH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished binge watching Russian Doll. Two thumbs up. Now I’m tired 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bayhill Enter to win a once in a lifetime Bay Hill Experience at Arnold Palmer's Bay Hill Club &amp; Lodge! #APInv https://t.co/SbfZHBjKfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s Hip Hop Day for the third day of Black History Month Spirit Week #wearewayne @WayneTwpSuper @NorthWayneElem https://t.co/IGw7QQ2BQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pence is the Evangelicals equivalent of trump...he’s awful. He was our Governor when we lived in Indiana. NO Pence… https://t.co/vYyKA8b2hY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ridgio__ did a fantastic job tonight on stage. He had the audience participate and I learned it takes lots of air… https://t.co/wThuthLbZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 things— 1. I need hand lotion...like all the time now. I swear you give your hands an inch and they take a mile (… https://t.co/UNkk1sjiNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so difficult for me to be on time. I’m either way early or late. Today I’m late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was ringing up this mom &amp; son at work today and before i could say anything the boy screamed “I HAVE PINK EYE”]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night I've actually been tired this early in a while and it feels goooood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stronger is better, but allota people thing bigger is better. Know the difference 💡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andre Dawson 4 card lot $0.25 each   (Please check my pinned tweet for sale &amp; shipping details. Thank you!) https://t.co/udb7cnrQkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just clocked in and out systems are down 🤦🏽‍♀️ that means manual receipts and annoyed customers all day. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at LIRR - Rosedale Station - @lirrdeals4u in Rosedale, NY https://t.co/YjzaUiVj44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe he didn’t even have a choice... maybe Jhene wasn’t fuckin with him. Lol 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep ~accidentally~ eating @FaithSniderr’s grapes because she’s an idiot and left them beside me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day!  Always a good day with the best associates and Leaders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “You do realize we have to buy it?”   Wife: “What?” Listens to a couple of seconds.. “Oh yeah!”   She was grown… https://t.co/iFO7cQbyWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This uber didn’t pick us up after two calls we fucking found him HELLO BAD REVIEW YOU FUCKING ASSHOLE.... IF I WERE… https://t.co/LSUfEue0Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlwithnojob Me. Me. Me. Me. Can you interview a Stale Toaster? 👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻 I would love to interview you and Jackie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, cauliflower can become a pizza? #WhoKnew #rockfordrealestate #815homes #815realestate #mindblown @ RE/MAX Pro… https://t.co/EragFQIqnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newsbabe1530 I know, it’s awful. Yes I’m okay, but it was a tough night. Thank you for asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello solo mom   I am also hungry to learn and become my best self  Celeste London  Holistic Solo Mom Coach… https://t.co/gVRSmgBLax]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day, mommy is so proud and little boy so happy!  @BauerHockey @CanadianTire @firstshift #hockey #canada… https://t.co/at4JymGkUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Arbor MI Mon Mar 4th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Snow Showers Lo 6 TUESDAY Snow Showers Hi 19]]></document><document><![CDATA[map apps really needs the option to check for most direct route unless delay is over 10min. Or even 5. Just dont se… https://t.co/OF4F6wcN84]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀Con Sue Photography and Design🏀  🏀Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏀  🏀This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/sFb6PeNZdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[should have gotten a large coffee this morning, what was I even thinking 🆘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Dems are refusing to honnor the man we elected. Those Soros voting machines are stea… https://t.co/c7b4fvnWbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHimmmm If it is who I think, I agree...how is she even invited to these events?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS they loss me from day one when Reese took hope and Liam baby and give her a dead baby I just can't stoma… https://t.co/P9rKtObp6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiTexasAngel @realDonaldTrump This is odd. I just read this. Is tRump talking about bandwidth?  https://t.co/wKfa8P4Y4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibe_erin Heck I teared up seeing them come out of the locker room hugging their fam!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly The Dems must think we are Idiots!!! They are pushing us to the Brink with their insanity!!!! People f… https://t.co/p6cSZ9J8RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨OSCARS Night✨ Serving you head to toe LEWKS in my betsyandadam gown @louisvuitton bag and vintage hat. 🥰😘❤️ ➖➖➖➖➖➖… https://t.co/SQkkONJ8NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to just focus on God and self more. #SelfLove 🙇 https://t.co/nsLi1MpQK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ColdinLA better be on the 8 letters tour set list😤😤😤 #coldinlaoutnow  @jackaverymusic @SeaveyDaniel @ImZachHerron… https://t.co/9AizyinXpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everythingloria I just want to bring you bottles of water 😢 dream crushed. I’m being sincere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump claims he never called Tim Cook “Tim Apple” and then tries to convince us that he did it to save ti… https://t.co/O0oaZ0E76W]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 more days until we move to North Carolina! @ Surry County, North Carolina https://t.co/jrsFjagw3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tink57usc @DisneyD23 That’s such a fun way to show off your membership cards!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulnixey @Patmeister You were in some delightful company, as I recall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsJeanDeaux What they really need to do is pay you. Clearly you putting in work. Cashapp shorty $25 and say “kn… https://t.co/X8I2PL9cbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetrayedVal I was just watching him on Fox and Friends and was thinking the same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While many representatives sleep in their offices because they can’t afford to maintain 2 households, @aoc moved in… https://t.co/4UzDWoGsO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else noticing an issue with their iPhone losing its gps for a bit? Happened to me yesterday and today, th… https://t.co/737ZKa1TOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: In Problem-based Learning students learn about a topic while solving problems and usually work in groups . In P… https://t.co/THCM4sLYZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_USO @USO_SC @GarySinise Loved the tribute by the “stars” honoring Gary Sinise -  so special and such a genuine… https://t.co/4xPcPeBBHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up around earth sign women. My mom is a Taurus, my grandma’s a Virgo, and my sister is a Capricorn. All so s… https://t.co/3G5hY0EqyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Great book!      Proof of Conspiracy: How Trump's International Collusion Is Threatening American… https://t.co/DCs3Ba1EAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needs to be somewhere for 11...still in bed and haven’t moved a muscle to get ready. #nailedit]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits .. #vegas #iftheshoefits #iftheshoefitswearit #cosmopolitanlasvegas @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/G7DeAvijav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache I’m a 60 yo white suburban mom who lives with her 31 yo daughter. Chronic Lyme disease. Lifeguard. Writ… https://t.co/PDeOSd3tnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmackTalkmma @eddiebravo I’ll look into it. Synopsis in the group thread. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate Virginia...their state leadership, their basketball team, their beaches, the way they are the only team to e… https://t.co/3jdiN4KK40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/EdM0oUmKgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra The collusion delusion has gone on long enough and these people need to get help they’re a danger to… https://t.co/2THWIvdQUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahbrennan98 I'm a little late but I thought this was perfect fot you. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsskinnyg @LIBGyal Come with me to Miami babe!!❤️  you’re gorgeous !😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser Real q: Are his returns really any less disclosed than the average early primary prez candidate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithChann @MrKoz31 @nearpod I can help with that!! https://t.co/YIdp2M0S5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when Aubrey O’Day was having an affair with Traitor Tot? Yeah. She’s live-tweeting the… https://t.co/FiI7wGjHmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did three pikes just request to add me on snap, which one of y’all is talking shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nezetseguin @philorch @MetOpera @AcademyAwardsHD Great Picture Yannick @philorch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh some people piss me off. Don’t look down at me because of where I work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden’s definition of America: possibility. 🇺🇸 @JoeBiden  #TheSoulOfAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulletPeople @jaspar @BridgetPhetasy No. Trump supporters are all still assholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit is so edited nobody can see your skin let alone your makeup let alone your actual bone structure. Nice fr… https://t.co/bZ5ghoClEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I seriously gave you the best/ longest foot massage expecting you to pull through as well and all I got was a… https://t.co/dq84oUNaaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackBornstein @alutkin I waited until the 5th guy in my 30s, so does that mean we’re cosmically meant to be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump He does not..your living in your own little world..you and @AOC. You're green world. Just… https://t.co/mi8FpM1ZFB]]></document></documents></author>