<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[She knows what she’s doing! Don’t let her play “the dumb” act again! This bitch has an agenda and don’t forget that… https://t.co/pl1IHFX0fJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I get to heaven the first thing I’m asking the lord is why he saw it fit to not give me a booty. What was I su… https://t.co/GQeIjU7tmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRJohnson @realDonaldTrump There is another story we will hear the truth eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeyAndNight that's what i thought too?? but i was reading an article last night and it says it'll be closed sundays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karam1ll3r @Ernest___Perez @ChilisJobs @fisher_jeanine @Jahir0323Jahir @kathryn_ransom @annessa_arsola… https://t.co/nBO1kwBrd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used some of the Calm Camp techniques I learned yesterday this morning. I had a good breakfast, put on my walking s… https://t.co/6EpnAHGPDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twlldun @ComiskeyNathan She rented a flat. It wasn't given to her. What amazes me is how long she staid in Labour… https://t.co/0ZDTEUwuYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMickyDolenz1 @Papa_Nez what a great show tonight in mexford! Thank you! https://t.co/ToDWrK7G5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@germano____ @NPR @NHLABOR_NEWS He got more time than Manfort. Do you think Trump will pardon him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[and if you’re all that w good music taste and i like your voice i’ll eat you alive lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really did not want to start smoking cigarettes again but here I am 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep while Alex and I were texting so I wake up to use the rest room and reply to him and this is what I g… https://t.co/xNwLXKRQRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonySteele3 @realDonaldTrump Lol.  Really.   Let's see what happens over the next 5 yrs!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I said I’m sensitive it actually meant watch your fucking mouth I get mad real quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guys “one more beer then I’m coming home” is the equivalent to a girls “I’ll be ready in 5 minutes” 🙄😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭 when you say what you want regardless 😂 and I dare yall call my momma 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[National #InvasiveSpeciesWeek brings attention to the impacts, prevention, and management of invasive species. As b… https://t.co/y8E4m8DA9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing mesh leggings in pouring rain and wet snow probably wasn’t one of my best ideas...10/10 do not recommend #imcold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoupGargoyle I am very happy that this is how my tweet is being received.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaddenX @colin_dunlap Gentlemen... this pissing match is unbecoming. Stick to reporting and analyzing sports.… https://t.co/Hq9DUx5O6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love our President and his family!! I can’t wait to vote for him again!! #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to snag a selfie with @kvpalooza at the Women’s Foodservice Forum! 🌶❤️🌶 #WFFConf #WFFLimitless @queenpalpal… https://t.co/ADuefRjdDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was deadass in the middle of a heated argument with Anthony and this mf takes off my glasses and says “your seein… https://t.co/NWnMJbErjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishannfl1 @glen_gould Thanks Trish! Thanks for joining us tonight! #Cardinal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joined @CP24 to breakdown #LavScam developments and the existential crisis rocking Justin Trudeau’s government.… https://t.co/NmnvAaV5RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Job should be enough, a new campaign message. @MeetThePress  In my state, the minimum wage is $8.46. We need to… https://t.co/9UG3823S6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS ....YOU ARE A 'JOKE'...USING THE THE WORDS THOUGHTS &amp; PRAYERS...HOW 'MUCH LOW CAN YOU GO ????!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 essay done one more to go. I started to get really overwhelmed but my prof cancelled Tuesdays class and the hw ha… https://t.co/V11SJf1ZCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KansasCatholic @jdflynn If you truly believe that, then you believe your own anger and not our Lord. There is a ve… https://t.co/kbCz9YYy10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherman769 @SuperGrobanite @Ragnar11V @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/5IcnlgUTXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXIScott My joint got a little over 3". Give or take. #MonValley ❄️❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this from a president who saluted a General of North Korea at his last meeting with their dictator in chief. Tr… https://t.co/oHcdE275Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattc665 @realDonaldTrump Number 2.  Therefore only Jews are Jewish. Jews are called "the people of God."  Jewish… https://t.co/Snru8IbNm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me guess on the old comedy scene wow even stonings are going to be cool no so I'm thinking that the daily show… https://t.co/7qSpJ4n8c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People equating verbal critique with bullying did not attend public high school lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelMadden @benjimadden I see you Madden Bros and I get happy. The end!!❤💕💖💓❣🤩🤗 https://t.co/nlFHZzWIbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husselius LMFAOO stop hating cause you from Birmingham &amp; im from Chicago 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Sorry Bernie. You are not as young as you use to be and would be mire hurtful to democrats if you did run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharnaBurgess your shop link isn't linking so there's no way to buy your new Cha Cha workout video. Could you prov… https://t.co/ULoo8IoV9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[What bad quality did I pick up from my most recent ex you ask? Well narcissism and a stupid walk of course😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s hard to pay attention to a movie with Matthew Mcconaughey in it bc i can’t stop drooling. look at my man]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have just discovered there is an official #MonsterMask valentine, and my day just got a little brighter. Happy Va… https://t.co/7C1wFINkBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fock2lovroc @SforScorpio But that’s not ok. There should be NO discrimination in the USA. We are all immigrants. W… https://t.co/yjWErM5rxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight to @erikacostell and @erikacostell only!!! 🖤🖤 https://t.co/RZ06tdCWP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, she is. Our churches are strangely silent. I’m going to get involved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...behind the scenes...filming my music video...in french... @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/VDC0DrlJQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 13 will be the world premiere of the new single @EnriqueIglesias recorded with the participation of the singe… https://t.co/pqU7FncGmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmorris011 Imagine doing this at 3am. In your own home. While already late for the morning shift. That was Wednesday. #blessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneDuesterberg Jane, I have tried to speak with both sides of the debate equally. I would consider Owen a supporter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everyone can be like me sweet and friendly! Lol! We love you @806hssc man I miss football!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contacts come in handy after years of networking. You learn to use your resources very well. So you always have two… https://t.co/d7DZglL5oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For him to leave Washington, D.C. and come down to little Beauregard says a lot about the president.”  Read more h… https://t.co/qT5kabKyEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several departure cancellations at @Bradley_Airport. Check with your airline before heading there. @NBCConnecticut… https://t.co/9DKhDHiP23]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fun ❤️ (@ Connects Workspace - @connects_golden in Golden, CO) https://t.co/xpYZinLwJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[So who will win between NU and UE? Haha. Parang interesting yung game next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 6:41, I just got home, I saw the most stellar sunrise, I got to hang out with my friends I haven’t seen in mad… https://t.co/fWqlTerFQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this comprehensive resource from @verainstitute on the role that prosecutors can play in reducing mass incarce… https://t.co/vfkkv1T0b6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashep__ He was the monster on The Masked Singer! Look up his performances on YouTube he was really good!! By the way I guessed him right!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAOOOOO i was nothing but good to homegirl but she out here talking mess making me look like the bad guy :/ BIEN pendeja que estas jaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyArtist56 There's my Angry Birds OC like fall in love wih Willow https://t.co/pFIkX4Y6mF]]></document><document><![CDATA[tee-hee and move on. This dog. | 50 Most WTF Animal Pics Of The Year. This is awesome, will definitely make... https://t.co/A6R1yVrPEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2qHqGjmLe6  The Amazon Phone Number works via our toll-free number 1-855-431-5111  #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[don't listen to me im just grouchy and awake bc of my neighbors watching their tv at the loudest possible volume lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things to help a "worried" student in the classroom. https://t.co/nXCIggzTAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connected to lots of people working at small businesses in the CEA and biofertilizer space on LinkedIn. Now my Link… https://t.co/OjrJODbXlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to go on a really sweet date..... ugh. Like I need over the top mushyness.... only bc I'm feeling kind… https://t.co/TfqT1eh4zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland My REPORT is WAAAAY better than Mueller's Report. https://t.co/XpGMFkqkz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear it reminds me of what my name is 💀 but I fucking hate it when he doesn’t call me princess or baby 🤦🏽‍♀️… https://t.co/4RaPdYI95C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do so many girls put their hands in their hair or behind their heads when they post selfies? It’s awkward as looks really stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I completely agree that our jails are a reflection of a #waronpeopleofcolor What are we doing about… https://t.co/iQr3Zqo4Fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so excited to kick-off 🎉(along with stephaniemaypotter ) our third women’s health coaching group beginning in… https://t.co/FxpZFZmr21]]></document><document><![CDATA[To help battle deforestation - drones are firing seed pods in to the ground to replant trees all around the world.… https://t.co/nNEcty1VOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristybelle88 @brittanyrhoads2 @virtuallywilson @EdwardLFinchEd1 @kay_heater @eeskinders @lisa_kepner @TuzzaJ… https://t.co/JwguE895ZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogDoPim https://t.co/rfSVIZ8akG ASSISTAM... COMPARTILHEM ... MUITO SÉRIO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoCoHowie Pulled it off pretty good yesterday too. Ended up in wave 2 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so heartbreaking as a queer to see that entire thing was a setup. there are so many black queer men who have t… https://t.co/6daNH6Ja4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not slept UNDER my covers in 6 months. I sleep on top of them with an extra blankey. Spoke to therapist abou… https://t.co/1THTJfjZid]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼 Almost sleepytime...we’re knockin’ on heaven’s door 🎶 #mommydaddyduet #babyevie @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/Sk6HgUAutW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nayibbukele @AsambleaSV De acuerdo todos estaremos pendientes, pero habrá medicina para el estómago de Quijano, qu… https://t.co/AyIJyQkvwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What this state may lack in size is outweighed by its indomitable spirit! https://t.co/UowLmyVUEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t expect life to come to you ... raise the bar, set high goals, find your purpose, read the Bible, ask the… https://t.co/U9kDZf5iHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib @CardiBFranceFR We want to see you on a tour this year!!!!!!! https://t.co/kxgvm1dBR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @chucktodd @Jim_Jordan He for some reason is trying to protect Donald Trump. I wonder why ? You know… https://t.co/EePh3iSeyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegAndy76 @neuroticjomomma @LBuckeye77 @lifewithshar @leelee1873 @littles_mom @mjs03093641 @tenacious_tiph Reg is… https://t.co/9TN38q8PEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[tried to make depression popcorn. and i. burnt all of it what kind of sign is this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ_CMICHAELS 😂😂😂😂😂 my music taste hasn’t changed since middle school obv🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wrangler lancia la collezione unisex Blue and Yellow ispirata alla gara @NascarVictoryLN https://t.co/91ACUwaX0V https://t.co/GcZQ8nYMLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Bias/fake news stories which continue to divide our country..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to go sleep for a year and a half. Today’s been a really shitty day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls are so soft 🙄 I’m happy with my small group of girl friends, and my guy friends. I love all you bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TickedOff6 Same here. Last night was even worse then usual. I had RLS in my legs. First time in ages. I caught a c… https://t.co/NqFgcT1F1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain And stop  worrying  so much  how can u be old  ur 36 God it's that thing teroisising u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bro_Charlie_ @Ada751918 @ZubrodRob @Vickeywoods @Investi83659952 @Porthospirates6 @LogicallyDelish @Rbigzs… https://t.co/B6ZwQ2Z9ZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[live now doing a singing stream with @THEalbertchang &amp; @LilyPichu! https://t.co/FbHmJhyu6x https://t.co/kdS6dYepyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chic_cocobelle I can afford to travel &amp; not interested in the moment. I have other goals. Them countries ain't going nowhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Never forget that a touch of sophisticated humor can spice up the past.” #RIPKarlLagerfeld]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all know how extra i am? i will want him to text me saying he too busy to text me that “i’m busy” tf. 😂😂 ain’t no… https://t.co/8pRmmiURHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbanny @SouthWildcats @AnyssaJones3 @WSladycats You are an amazing announcer.  Thank you for all your enthusiasm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[university hacks: "you don't need to memorize, you just need to understand the concepts"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team cleaned up today at the 1st competition of the season. WTG Lariettes!!!]]></document></documents></author>