<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Reaching my breaking point. Just want a decision made. Either rip my heart out and stomp it or hold and protect it. #lost #waiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a chance to talk with @m_bows4 a few times.. Met his family, too.. Just a good guy from a great family.. Had a… https://t.co/wS87DKIZBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSNGolf @MikeWeir @WebDotComTour This is great to see. Always has been a grinder!! Would love to see a solid weekend @MikeWeir]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Friday night’s fun and frivolity....the Drunk Driver walked away from this: https://t.co/YzdnhYw1WQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/1rkHJPUBGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkySportsPL @DataSmith101 Imagine when lanzini comes back. Him, anderson and Arnoutovic will bring us top 7 (if they step healthy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both my sessions including "Intro to Bot Framework Enterprise Template" (@msbotframework) have been accepted at… https://t.co/T30p0l300r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great innovation at #DMV-based #AR pioneer @upskillio | congrats @BrianBallard723 @neverest5 &amp; team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiceSing_3 @AmericasCenter @StullySTL It could host the big one. Probably 70k at the dome. Has convention center a… https://t.co/vsj7QPt7iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone in Miami feel the need to get a white Mercedes with a black roof and darken taillights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSHanford thunderstorm just east of us at bear creek fire station in Springville. It is pouring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeatherReusz Highschool me is freaking out now! ... Who am i kidding... Adult me is freaking out! https://t.co/jHZ8SgBswY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ti-  what is the worst part about politics? C- I would say lobbyists Ti- why? C- needs to be like nas car.  Make th… https://t.co/mGplREL70j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same thing we do every night pinky...time to #getafterit #roadwarrior #hustle #upbeforejocko #soe4life #cm4l… https://t.co/5zui8zuZQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I was coasting through the semester and then this week decided to drop a heavy ass load of work🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awaiters86 @rvaisred @ChrisHSport @IronPonyChef @USLChampionship They were almost comically inept at times. Couple… https://t.co/b60F18GSuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall be careful in Dallas we just got followed to our car buy some Hispanic guys who pulled up in a truck and got out for one to follow us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exhibit #1. This is why you don't dance with the devil. #Putin #Trump https://t.co/IKDFKdqALX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suntimes @NeilSteinberg I doubt I will read the book. No animus towards Michelle. I think she is great.  Your review was great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clayster Someone could film my interactions with cod talent and it’d truly make an award winning comedy show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important question, What will happen 2 a #RAD converted property that defaults on its @FHAgov mortgage? What pro… https://t.co/MyrRydplBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Está claro que Sacha Sáez ya no fue......a darle la titularidad de ua vez a D. Valencia, juvenil de la casa.....… https://t.co/wpC21SKq1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so privileged to get to help Sharon Gardner a wonderful new home in Winder. I would love to help you.… https://t.co/lMACPBd5qp]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Books in 7 days, challenged by @shinebrite71 . I'm sharing 7 covers of books I love, with no explanation. Each ti… https://t.co/y31HGLzupa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckresc I’m a little late but starting the chamber now!! So excited!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opportunists seek short cuts while bosses pull their own weight; choose wisely. #Floss #ManOnAMission @ Buckhead At… https://t.co/05CjjCme3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to spend a snowy afternoon. 6.18 mile hike. @ Westminster Ponds Conservation Area https://t.co/YuIthZ6Szk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when I was a conservative evangelical I supported marriage equality, because I didn't think it was the governm… https://t.co/GeTC81So0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globalnews @globalnewsto Nope. What’s the difference with peer pressure to drive a car under the influence and cra… https://t.co/qKwM0YTKPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescma5 @APrivitelli @canuck2usa @Benzinga @JulBonse https://t.co/ISXMn2Zleu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidniteKittiKat @peytoneshk Wait really? How do I not know this already?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine tweeting something like this less than an hour after your team got mopped by the suns? The GALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped by one of my favorite brewerys. I couldn’t leave empty handed. @ Red Oak Lager Haus &amp; Biergarten https://t.co/PoLdEmgnsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So gone couldn't tell you where I'm at. Maybe New York, Philly, maybe Pittsburgh You wanna find me, hit me on Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunking @RashidaTlaib Omg racism cries everywhere!! 😂When someone doesn’t get their way the worlds racists must… https://t.co/JY5JBajJwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Interleave @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump You’re right to this extent: I have not looked into the dynamic of the 2… https://t.co/KkcQPvV245]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beermiscuous @Sketchbookbrew I would be just as excited to try this! #craftbeer #drinklocal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trabajaron y trabajaron y trabajaron ... tuvieron sus chances y ahora están abajo ... #Dynamo #ForeverOrange 0-1 vs… https://t.co/AaYkl5rfvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lvandenberg Ms van den Berg, this series is a wonderful tribute that I’m sure your father-heck, any father-would b… https://t.co/OygqueYM88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJillStein @Clever_Hans_03 Have you ever had the chance to study the destruction and the suffering of the Venezue… https://t.co/vOmWU3jz2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recordemos: Las grandes mentes hablan de ideas. Las mentes promedio hablan de cosas.  Las mentes mediocres hablan de otra gente. Abrazo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I'm 100% sure is Jay Z is Worth a billion doallrs and 100% sure he doesn't have close to that amount of money on hand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commercial Property for sale in Downtown Minot, #NorthDakota. 🏬 Unique downtown building offering three streams of… https://t.co/K8s5mPrumZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta My boyfriend's flight has been delayed in Orlando until morning due to a technical issue completely within y… https://t.co/BMXAnBFsw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qualified on the pole tonight at @newsmyrnaspdwy !!  Will be starting 4th after the invert for the 35 lap feature 💪🏼 https://t.co/Y0nVgKEQtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might get my annual pass for Disneyland under one condition. If I get a thousand dollars by the end of May. Which I hope it does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the novel???   Charlotte Independence makes an official announcement on signing Andrew Gutman on loan from C… https://t.co/xJlO4Ksvcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[During these times, we are either reviewing the crazy stuff that Trump and his gang has done or some brand new craz… https://t.co/WUGxwG54qB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny Mauer is like the girl that never gets asked to the prom and hates the prom king...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwaykippen @FalsettosBway Seeing how so many young people connect with this show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IsBetterThanUsingPlastics Transparent Alumina, Not invented yet. Common composite in my time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tryna see @ParkerMcCollum who's gonna be my date? https://t.co/MVXaKnVQkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not a sissy man 😂😂😂😂😂😆😆😆🥺💀💀 Noah is fuckin funny and lowkey goat 🐐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter followers make sure you check out this amazing film I worked on while living in nyc.... it really is the be… https://t.co/AlKU4hXPGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoWashington @Abe_Lincoln @TheBushCenter @JohnFKennedy Impressions of #USA #presidents. Not perfect; just an inde… https://t.co/n9ryuBmm2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lacrosse Practice Canceled No Problem #WallBall #CoyotesYouthLacrosse #Lax2019 #U12 https://t.co/v1chdtgBQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manfightdragon @elgatogaming I don't use pass-through on any of my capture devices. Not worth the hassle. I have m… https://t.co/L9ZzdMbMcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell Do...do some of you think this is a real thing that happened?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iowa State is 17-18 all time in the BigXII Tournament, 4 Titles, 15-13 all time in KC, 2-3 in BigD, 0-2 in OKC, own… https://t.co/jpKzMW2a49]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been doing so much self searching the past few years and once you can accept your flaws and understand you aren’t… https://t.co/j04f0HNi7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Tucker always told us that we remember all definitions and proofs for the day we’re on a deserted island and ha… https://t.co/xecAGGFvO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xan_desanctis When pro- life advocates mock and discredit people by calling them baby killers and accusing them of… https://t.co/pnw0bfqPBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JavyerMinogue @Steveonomics @taketheturtle I weigh myself everyday now.. 15 lbs down...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dsteele67 @Nascar_Brackets @KyleLarsonRacin @kylelarson_kyle @42kylelarsonfan @KyleLarsonCrew @McDonalds… https://t.co/ifhNL9Z1aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BXHy3b7lZG Forget Homework and High School! Helping @tanamongeau win the #ShortyAwards is waaayyyy mor… https://t.co/2qYuKAShbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[supa clusta lookin when the sunlight goes through it 💫 ((still real pressed plants as always)) https://t.co/xEJ0iINOr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. The Price Is Right 2. Double Dare 3. Wheel of Fortune 4. Fun House 5. Family Feud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a wheel similar to this obevin a museum. Mine is well used and has a smaller wheel to counter rotate too. https://t.co/uFaNinKOaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MuMenWrestling and David Berg on his Natty Championship win 🏆   #NAIAWrestle #WarriorNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Parade Day Lager by @flyingfishbrew @ Blakely American Legion Post 570 — https://t.co/zEszhfI8kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigiAdams @WalkerWizardsLJ @jenneubarth @MrsCook_RJ @WEareLakotaTech Thank you! Glad you enjoyed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backavar One might think in this modern age sans a true Praetorian class that the only thing the separates this my… https://t.co/gPg6C6SpSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice-T was apart of an exotic cars rally. To prove that his custom Range Rover Autobiography could “keep up” with th… https://t.co/FJCxbZ9421]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pulledmoose So long no one gets hurt this is great for the league. The league wants rivalries, well one was just b… https://t.co/7TkUEy07Ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeVacc I was at the 4/22/70 game, a chilly April day, 4 months back from Nam, on leave from Westover AFB in Mass… https://t.co/Nmca9JwjNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 1st?   What did the groundhog predict?  #snowyday #notspringyet  #outdoorlife @ Gamber, Maryland https://t.co/mVcoNcnWpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Negilla @AngelGutie3 @Chemicalblaze So after the NE/Bobby Brown miniseries, everyone’s getting a biopic now? What’… https://t.co/iWBL7bvrCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BronsonAP 48 Hours by William R. Forstchen. Your character range is great in this one.  Especially enjoyed "Mr. Science".]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this is an unlockable gun in #farcrynewdawn and the description is my favorite thing. —————————————————————————… https://t.co/LD5QPlGVLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_honan I think when he landed a police helicopter in our park in Hunters Point South. Police cleared out all… https://t.co/LQX40yr2bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you feel that being dominant and egocentric to those loved ones around you will make you happy then go for it. B… https://t.co/7WSjWFxRLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing has really changed, they are still a top ten team in the league, and players don't make career decisions mi… https://t.co/uicXaQhO9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter You are Amazingly STUPIT, You even Believe your own Lies and Deceits. You really need… https://t.co/KB5BVzyVbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls are super pumped that we are in a hotel at a mountain!  Just might have to get “sick” for an extra day 🤔🤧😷😉 @… https://t.co/IMy0NO2Pmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren A fundamental change would be for little girls to stop having babies by cowards that run away from their r… https://t.co/6WnFAwd4aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's genuinely weird to be like "Oh shit! I totes forgot about when my car was mortared by terrorists!" But yeah. Oops?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glassbottommeg My local coffee shop has rotating video game sketches on their cups. This was their GOW week. https://t.co/LUgvg5Nwph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BEyes60 hi robin. how are you feeling. hope all is well. going to snow this weekend in ny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RecePickle @trayok10 #facts bro I don’t understand why it takes that many guys to put cuffs on someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric ⁦@luttrell_music⁩ packed ⁦@qnightclub in #Seattle for his #IntoClouds show⁩! Such a great set. He knows how to… https://t.co/dAhrvJAiPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr // Southern Border being besieged, Border Patrol Agents plead for help - where are Senate Republicans ???   #cowards]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I went to the Wayne Medical Behavior Center in Lyons NY. then I went to Walmart and buy a ear bud connector to… https://t.co/2mZC2EkkPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaginawBay I’m sure that will help you in the tourney just like the last 2 years https://t.co/X62MPpw8Od]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, does Joe just kill everyone? This is like that terrible Black Mirror episode where the lady kills anyone… https://t.co/37qOZTdho4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This world would be a much better place if everybody minded their business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When researchers compiled a huge database of the digital habits of teams at Microsoft, they found that the cleares… https://t.co/aUHnR7OcM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s one thing I’m terrified of and that is associating alcohol with being an answer for feeling down. It is not… https://t.co/QBsbvKmNR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandieCroshaw Too many evil doers to chose from. https://t.co/2us0Sg6sSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s fine if Botterill doesn’t do a dam thing this year, but if we’re in the same shit next year at this time, yo… https://t.co/3t2X2lp1VH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost my phone in the field. Pretty much had a heart attack. Carried on training. Found it back at the start point w… https://t.co/vBNregALJk]]></document></documents></author>