<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JevJournalist Lmao dawg man dem weh make my uniform used to generous with the material. Bless dawg 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt richhomie.wayne ybn.wayne my handsome son 💜 @ Jersey Village, Texas https://t.co/PGOC1xU5l9]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol i wonder if caelyn feels weird sometimes that her bestie Cassie is w Colton hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probablemente me quedaré dormida, pero de corazón deseo que @haashoficial nos lea #QueremosGiraHaAsh2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I'm with you. Making California a leader in alt energy. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg @HowardSchultz Tell me, how do you plan to do financial stability for all?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aerosmithmech @FynKaren #ItsNotJustASD #AllkidsMatter #NoChildLeftBehind #NoMoreLabels #fundtheneed #endtheneglect… https://t.co/wzXYtLIiL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If getting interrupted every 10 minutes anytime you try to get something accomplished sounds fun than being a paren… https://t.co/RGHjm9b35g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the early vision and commitment of @lomondtrossachs working with @STARDevGroup in 2001 to develop the fir… https://t.co/lI4Voumgf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this article: Get Perfect Skin with Lyft by Nurysh! / @NuryshR- https://t.co/aRe3KWrTUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I regret wasting my first opportunity to vote to vote for this guy. I can’t wait to get the hell out of this state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am laying in my bed, not ready to get up for the day. Alarm clock went off at 5:45am and I am laying here like I… https://t.co/BkQ2Ymm2pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, #Buffalo. The fight against the #opioidcrisis continues. @SavetheMichaels is getting aid in it’s batt… https://t.co/uhq7Lca5Xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 💓 this song,didn't know black Label Society did it https://t.co/S6ZAobNPig]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my Uber driver “gotta get that bread “ and he looked at me like if i was crazy lmaooo nvm then tf 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Madison! I think she did a great job on her art for the HCS Art Expo! Her piece was sold and a reproduc… https://t.co/VJxa2UYGNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Valentine’s Day so special, why we can’t get a day off from school? 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gogf19sqK4 sometimes I look at houses because I’m saving for one and I find one that is perfect and wish I was a grown up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueIrishAngel @ChicagosFines19 @bobbyfo16078346 @OldSmokeEater Jermaine is Awesome!! Such #kindness goes a long way!! ❤️🙏🚔💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eaner0919 @PonySportExpert But he still hasnt lost his numbers!the girls just a tad upset 🤢🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanDon @bamaral44 @NewsProvidence @DanBarbarisi @TimWhiteRI I don't think I'm in that photo, but my hair has always been fabulous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuttyboi219 It’s ok I already got them 😩 but thank you I’ll check next time 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read the Book of Acts 14!    So much has happened since Peter got out of the boat!  The Spirit of the Lord led this… https://t.co/71zOIhtzYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our @SpringISD_CTE Technology Specialists shows off the cool things you can do in CTE when you put Math and Science… https://t.co/aUktF6198U]]></document><document><![CDATA[This.  Is.  On.  You.    Restore the balance or lose us all.  The entire middle.  Gone forever.    If it’s not too… https://t.co/Pqla1v9YLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the Papa has lost his reasoning ability Pope compares child sex abuse to 'human sacrifice'. https://t.co/UsbUwjYoCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrElnora I have learned that,no weapon formed against you shall be able to prosper,you also confirmed what I belie… https://t.co/dhj6f0TQcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #GalentinesDay Ladies❣️Uplifting and inspiring each other is what it’s all about! CONGRATS to my boss babe an… https://t.co/rgjQsfcWeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MalaNocheNo  @Verovision  #ChiquitaPeroPicosa en Hollywood https://t.co/g9klCRhjvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[White sand, blue sky 🐚 @ St. Pete Beach, Florida https://t.co/CLiuopCcO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ariana grande tried to get a “7 rings” tattoo in a language she doesn’t speak and got “BBQ grill” instead. but don’… https://t.co/yiPWEgRQ81]]></document><document><![CDATA[One minute I’m talking sensibly to patients and co workers, another minute I’m talking shit and being reckless on twitter. Balance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iloveme1185 @TheView Probably on drugs or their family is and drove them crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I changed my mind, ie I remembered today a #classic.  #thelmaandlouise I always think of it more as a female modern… https://t.co/S5YT4aiXNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReallyR47200785 @mikebwonder @LarryHu16683289 First u have to stop laughing at her to vote for her ...NOT EVER VOTING FOR OCASIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarinaBland @azcentral Can’t you just take us all out for a glass of wine and tell us what’s on your mind?]]></document><document><![CDATA[its because you are the hardest headbanger i know and THAT is why you are my best friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WineOhTV @chasingthevine @OMGwine @esully @ricasoli99 @amylieberfarb @beckhopkinswine @damewine @WineDineWanda @christineniSF 👍💯🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[so, I guess we are who we are for a lot of reasons. and maybe we'll never know most of them. but even if we don't h… https://t.co/5JqBrmDh6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lpguyton @HenryCountyBOE I had a wonderful time at Smith Barnes this Morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s actually scary how i find out everything, like even if you think i don’t know TRUST ME I KNOW ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, yiu eill mit even beiieve this one! Someone needs to find truth here. Chipping away at Dem lies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian And if wasn't Jordyn it'd be another woman. And its NOT your fault. You and True deserve more. Next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #BTSARMY for #BESTFANARMY at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/zGgeaY57Te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss The water in Flint, Michigan. They’re still drinking bottled water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌛Goodnight Moon!🌜✨Goodnight Stars! ✨#goodnightmoon #goodnightstars #goodnightviews #goodnight🌛 @ Scottsdale Mountai… https://t.co/KYjzFIgYAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBloods_CBS thank you for how you treated the officer with #MCI tonight! Well Done!@DonnieWahlberg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating bridges and not walls. Bringing people together and not shutting them out. It was enlightening to hear fro… https://t.co/NdptHUX0WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love it when a good horse trains you💖 Savvy and I learning to lunge 🥰 Roxy makes it’s easy on us😂😂… https://t.co/wEdb1whAwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing like aggressively trying to pull your contacts out of your eyeballs when they’re actually already out]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The President had no involvement pertaining to my clearance or my husband’s clearance. Zero,” Ivanka told ABC News… https://t.co/OBDgvQGcxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_taaaylorrr The Jonas brother were for you what Zac Enron was for me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally stayed like a day after I figured out what happened with this man, and he kept asking me why I stayed a… https://t.co/Lxuuon57T3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t have taken that nap... even my cat is side eyeing me like bitch go to bed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IL SENTIERO E’ DENTRO DI VOI.🌾 La percezione che provo quando mi addentro nei boschi è difficile da interpretare se… https://t.co/UtwAOqcmp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must have #RBG—&gt; @USWNT Honors Inspirational Women with Names on Back of Jerseys at #SheBelievesCup https://t.co/csFDtgcZmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bre_88 😂😂😂 that is alarmingly smooth and stealthy, barely touched it going over...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forward motion and more hope for more children living with #Duchenne #MuscularDystrophy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XandersEdits @NICKIMINAJ @TwitterSupport Yea I didn’t get the post notifications and a bunch of barbz are being su… https://t.co/SAU4GSFBoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Famous Mansions No One Wants To Buy For Any Price https://t.co/xht4uMRA6l via @YouTube.  I would buy one or give it… https://t.co/4WUCTlAVmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanmcadory The addition of a kitty makes the title look even more appealing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask him how he treated me when I told him I might be pregnant with his child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @TryAgain78911 Now @TheDemocrats are going to open dozens of unsubstantiated investigations into the… https://t.co/3OC4WjzCZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think these DRUG CARTELS ONLY CROSS AT BORDER ENTRY = YOU MUST BE A DUMBOCRAT ! MANY ARE CROSSING OPENINGS W… https://t.co/zRZZElPNdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys! Tonight @TheBundysMusic did PHENOMENAL on @NBCTheVoice Congrats guys! Seriously so so amazing! #TeamKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trudeau says “these are questions you’d have to put to her” (Wilson-Raybould). Good - she should appear before the… https://t.co/dWpTE2rknp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatAtDisney Isn't this the type of shopping habits that Wdw was revoking AP passes for???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aeduko @just_Mooya He  is Jamaican, her mother Indian. He did it because there are ignorant people out there who d… https://t.co/OY5eukikiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@florceleneeee No one relevant. He got tossed last night. I'm not bout games in 2019. https://t.co/Xl7N2KNKvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesrhowe6 Set up a color scheme before you start, so you can figure out what you need. I use @coolors_co to find… https://t.co/fHgRfe2SfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How To Show Off Your #Disney World Spirit in Rose Gold Style https://t.co/gLbJezGRXk   #Disneystyle #NowMoreThanEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[youtube now y’all see they tried to do everything they could to make YouTube Remove My Song But When You Got That P… https://t.co/N6Q2EmdqXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck yeah @sargzem breaking it down, manager editor stylez for @ArizonaMFA peeps this snowy morning #TucsonLyfe https://t.co/B182kjodqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a sneak peek at kerrid80’s new headshots by @RNashPhoto!! It’s so hard to choose favourites!!!… https://t.co/Kfo3D7FBD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A big concern for many of the foreign workers here will be how they will be able to support their families back ho… https://t.co/bfDmbFZx8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream last night that I was on set for the new 99 episode that @Lin_Manuel is going to be in and I got to m… https://t.co/jlH9R5IwJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA She definitely deserved jail time,but 2 years at least!!!What a witch!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend i was lucky enough to get to go see my love in his city. I got to meet his awesome friends and walk ar… https://t.co/GcHsmlfwOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I just want to chop most of my hair off and then other days I love my long hair and want to grow it out e… https://t.co/f5t5P1k66k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to South Park’s Tino Tutich and Maura Huwalt!!!!Good  luck in playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from @MODMomsLLC Meal Prep and have a new recipe to try out!!!  Thank you maryanndemartin for all of your work… https://t.co/ohio7oszpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally calling it a night at 2am so I get up at 8am to be out the door by 9am so I can head to campus and keep stu… https://t.co/E21ELZNgrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lovemypupper @RobElgasABC7 @EricHorngABC7 @CharlieDeMar That’s what I said!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love those friends who give you valentine gifts when ur single as heck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungSc0e It’s 2019 EVERYBODY with influence and power know wtf going on out here ...ESPECIALLY when it comes to h… https://t.co/u0Aa5EHKza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nashvl @jj_fedigan No he didn’t bring back Otto, he brought back a man that was beaten, and about to die. Trump di… https://t.co/XimPjIKInm]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!!! I'm Died With That Sexy Low Voice 💖💖💖 #ButInACoolWay💝 @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grammys just released that 19.9 million people tuned in to watch, sooooo, they’re all excited that 1/2 of the popul… https://t.co/pNjC4Yo1hV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing reports of an officer involved  shooting in Des Moines. We have a crew on the way. We’ll have updates and l… https://t.co/nxoq2mlZXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m confused isn’t this the party that doesn’t  believe in the death penalty for murders? Give me a break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can’t help but be the person who simply comments: *to or *you’re #noregrets #grammar #spelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallJenner Omg! Congrats to ur sis. Umm cant believe the amount of haters. This was hard asf work. Paid off and… https://t.co/LJSqkpKtt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I just get three calls on Nite Flirt when it's set to away. Wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone tho is thry are hot shit. I can’t have one icjihgv hung in this world .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angel_auras except that's what I love about our little community, so many of us are in our late teens/early twenti… https://t.co/Az0O9XOxQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least Kim Jong Un has a killer fade going on. We have to look at a #POTUS who still hasn’t realized that a muskr… https://t.co/swE8CEBZ8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s the night and @LakevwMSLib is the place to be for Family Movie night!  We’re watching “Hidden Figures”, a… https://t.co/CzX4t26mvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBLightning #LightningStrikes #bolts Tyler Johnson https://t.co/J0NDu9KrnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carleana shares a birthday with @PascoSheriff’s Shep, just so y’all know 🐶👧🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekPa56710094 @marvil296 @BabyGo2014 @jill_magnussen @letgolifeflows @pratoshnivedita @HarcourtDoug… https://t.co/pORqzaF9um]]></document></documents></author>