<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Sjeutc5QBt This idiot thinks this is a game without consequences, she needs to be taught a lesson impe… https://t.co/ymSCIhgn4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[A much better alternative to $15/hour minimum wage in this state would be free community college and technical scho… https://t.co/F2GdAcSIRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He lies like the proverbial rug. What does he have in common with Trump the king of pathological liars? Simple… https://t.co/aLiXcglJQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felix1351 Solo confirmaron: Serenata sin Mayonesa Los tambores de Tocoron Las flautas del FARC  Los violines del E… https://t.co/RMQPLZBAx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Lock her up.  She would put bullet in yr head in a Newyork second. Stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @RepMarkMeadows They would as the lot of them are not credible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see some of our @ontarioreign guys make a difference in tonight’s @LAKings game. Let’s go, boys! #GoKingsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beyondfinances Having gone to college here I can say that’s not out of the realm of possibility, but managing the… https://t.co/OzTbgA3sKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sodjacket @sn_nfl As opposed to 100 percent if first team to touch scores TD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHermanCain @ZigTj All about Dems looking for any way to impeach @realDonaldTrump, including using very mentally… https://t.co/76zGsqQAyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinese red chicken-char sui. Chinese 5-spice brussel sprouts. Grilled mixed peppers. Salad. studiokitchensp specia… https://t.co/kDRXLBPWnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very blessed to have my Christian Music now being played on Sunday mornings by 🎶Big Time Radio🎶 BTR International.… https://t.co/IM3bnJfXj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilkXnikolov @leeleebb21 @WordPoor @bigeby13 Yours too. Man among men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m such a homer that the idea of a motivated, pissed off Pip coming back for the A10 tournament has me interested]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $3,081.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/eqPYER1fSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JClarkNBCS @Eagles @RealDGunnNBCS @NBCSPhilly @NBCPhiladelphia @JasonKelce @bbrooks_79 @LaneJohnson65… https://t.co/23SMTpto6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[to be able to laugh so hard you gasp for air, to be able to argue but never forget the love, to be able to hear the… https://t.co/wVQ12P6c21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rod_villa1000 y no solo eso el issste no ha recibido presupuesto para ejercer 2019, los muertos por esta austerida… https://t.co/lxVtsfHdRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saybeller Thanks Sayword! I'm just a microscopic part in such a terrific community, and it's WORTH it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostMcHistory @BlackburnReview @theUDbattleship Frank Z needs to wet his beak!! https://t.co/nB1oeRUNaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleximusPrime @MAURICELAMARCHE I am trying to have it done to ship to @BABSCon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayhawkTalk Ku has been pretty impressive at home this season. Might be the only team to go undefeated at home and not win their league.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tim_cook Curious as to why a financial calculator was never baked into iOS? There are a gazillion people in bankin… https://t.co/w5usmRzfIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyHaverly Oh I agree but that wasn’t in the cards tonight #bedtime. Plus my writing is so poor they may not know the difference!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PCF Triggers Paparazzi Firestorm at JFK On Way to Mexico to Celebrate 2nd Birthday with Entourage… https://t.co/sB2ZxDYjpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to all my happy singles and couples that just want to vibe out through out their day.  #HappyValentinesDay  https://t.co/A5N9MfpTsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justin Williams scores -- but the play was offside, and a wee bit of a rumble breaks out. Williams called for unspo… https://t.co/9eSBa0DE56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnDeRose @cab_tj @TJGirlsBBall @TJColonials I’ll take it to the dry cleaners if necessary!! Let’s go TJ!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turkish human rights lawyer may have been killed by a cop, high-tech independent investigation shows: When Turkish… https://t.co/dOUdtVjBEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning!!  Weather sucks in Toronto, and its 28 degrees in Australia. thats not fair! Have a good day everyone!!  👍❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewParent1 Why does it matter so much? It’s the same school. Northeastern literally gets called the name of a… https://t.co/lIS4ifx9OW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that ANOTHER Snowstorm has come and gone - stop by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN TODAY for the HUGE BOGO… https://t.co/nRQo6uagVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apple https://t.co/0Q9oW4ioEC @aigkenham @AiG try https://t.co/0gGPtYOWxR and make the ark of the covenant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pourquoi toujours nous dire de PAS Oublier de changer l’heure? En 2019, tu peux pas! Le cell le fait à ta place, Vi… https://t.co/F72EU2DclT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side note: my autocorrect changed the song title to “I Wanna Dance With SOMEbody” and I think that emphasis would m… https://t.co/iKRQssNpLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave The world will not be destroyed by those who do evil, but by those who watch them and do nothing- Albert Einstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss my boy randy more than normal @GarciaRandall best squad leader, even better friend❤️ https://t.co/46rJCeU2eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Defend_Trump where is all the support for this national emergency.?  Why is this group so silent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon @Unpersuaded112 @politico I would say that we all need to go after McConnell in any way to get him to… https://t.co/oUT4fkqJK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I was really attracted to this guy's neck... IDK why it was beautiful though]]></document><document><![CDATA[The staple of all my outfits is a jacket,I'm literally nothing with out my jackets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got a notification that Jonas Brothers have released a new single. WHAT YEAR IS THIS!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquel que aprende debe sufrir. Y aún en nuestro sueño el dolor que no puede olvidar, cae gota a gota sobre el coraz… https://t.co/ILpO7CwmfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are very excited to be playing with @cahoneydrops ⭐️ this Saturday @thenewparish in Oakland! 💙 Great old friends… https://t.co/xSodLmwZ2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a guy walked in wanting a half sleeve done today. He also though it would take 4 hours. 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @jonjohnsonwip @SportsRadioWIP @AngeloCataldi @WIPMorningShow @nufced I thought it was hilarious the… https://t.co/gdd9NQt5Rc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen, this is the woman that I once admired and liked! She helped Obama win his first term with her popular show… https://t.co/Geh11Qmdts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelirvin88 @CanesFootball @CoachField All you need is oxygen, and water...and Michael Irvin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMedland @JSportsnet He’s not part of the old boy club, paid his dues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanDonovan @paulkrugman In this “information age” we get to know everyone’s “dirt”. It’s up to the voter to deter… https://t.co/ErZDxYE0pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm working on a little something inspired in part by my work and experiences with #autism.    #storytelling #comedy https://t.co/Rj09jrUxsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a long time, my large blue friend. Snorlax duo in Clear weather against boosted Earthquake. https://t.co/GUlAm3oI5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter! I need your help. Over the past season:  (1) what is the book you had the most fun reading recently?  (2)… https://t.co/WoajLe47Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is the kind of content @LeBatardShow was looking for last week from Brad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DZMMTeleRadyo @tunyings_kaindo Usec “na kung saan” TUGADE...🤭🤭🤭🤭🤭😬😬😬ha ha ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to I Love You by People! - Album Reviews, Credits, and Awards - AllMusic -  https://t.co/O5eBBA7Pvv The first listen today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cfbechara @YevgeniyBr @PERTConsortium @kush_r_desai @Angiologist @GBarnesMD @VladLakhter Been there, seen (and rem… https://t.co/VwBmhufvnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andweknow I know this is gonna seem strange to ask but I'm almost certain I seen a new video posted just yesterday… https://t.co/97TBUdVDoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strive4liberty @SilvrtonguedDvl @MyTimesProse @Brandon_Bahret @CathyYoung63 It was, and then they decided it wasn’… https://t.co/OynF6f7b5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally updated our miniatures scene for #Spring  #Totoro #nature #toronto @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/oMbgqxeZKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ajstotts Tijan is a strong favorite. Jordan Hulls would make my list too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachEricPogue @AtotheBewc @GoldenGrizzlies @lakeeriemsoc @ncaaLGBTAs @NCAA @NCAASoccer @HorizonLeague @OULGBTERG… https://t.co/w20UgZi7PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteButtigieg makes his case for 2020 - And it’s a good one. “2020: Pete Buttigieg on freedom and farting cows." https://t.co/pgubQLMeZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very proud of my little man. He competes at a very high level in some of the top ⚽ tournaments in the area as a… https://t.co/W1so4JHj03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maximaxoo I did explain to some students once that if we saw dinosaurs on a faraway planet, they would be gone by the time we saw them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frum seems to confuse correlation with causality. Is he implying that immigration is to blame for the state of toda… https://t.co/QSZoxeBkPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is -4C / 24 F in Dallas, TX, right now....This is outrageous and will not stand, man, It will not stand! #OOTT #natgas #thecatwantsin]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mindset digging...realized my mind was in chaos til I added links missing...Ignored, it was my Brinks prison...Sha… https://t.co/8XOAzCjm7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Mohegan Sun Arena to Dunmore HS for the back end of my doubleheader. Dist. 2-11 subregional final between Weat… https://t.co/KyyF9FmcjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERYONE THINKS THEY’RE A CRITIC🤪🎦📺🎥📽 Of course, I’d vote Bela JarVanka! 🤷‍♂️😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoga was delicious this morning! I woke up this morning sore, tired, achy and grumpy. Wasn’t very functional. Final… https://t.co/8PX1S10Vdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ New American Tattoo Company https://t.co/skktLF52Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyrion promising to marry Myrcella off to different kingdoms to Littlefinger, Varys, and Pycelle respectively in or… https://t.co/H4IYBP4iGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanLucMeisel @cauldroncomics Awesome dude. I'll watch and listen to it when I'm at the #drawingtable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyRacePass and @JamieBall5J  have been working really hard on this during the off season to make this happen this… https://t.co/E8KfJk2lDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tamango_ @TroyMI_Police The kitten has found an excellent home as the Troy MI police mascot. Kind hearted officer… https://t.co/g4xibARu8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@korinne_mn @AlejandroAttrct Love your new video, Korinne! Miss you too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic @maggie_fizz Zuckerberg as the owner of Microsoft and Facebook City of Salt Lake vs Ocean R. Trump’s… https://t.co/CKdHFiFNLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Collin_McHugh What makes you think fans believe players know what’s best, what’s best for the players sure... but… https://t.co/efqNU29OKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just nasty, all night long. Be careful driving this morning STL #TISL @ksdknews https://t.co/nqWTIss0Hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[WPM brought out the 🏹 this week. @BeMore27 would be proud. https://t.co/4oJano7APa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lazybones #remy #dogsofinstagram #dogs #boxer #comfy #sideeye @ Elmwood Village https://t.co/UBjiHyONlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hyl_ian I know a late reply (you could shame me) But I am proud of you getting this 😁!!!! Been rooting for you to… https://t.co/jIHRihz32Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[silence.tae house.of.drums The House is getting back to performances this year. I'm all for it. @ MUSE Center For T… https://t.co/C9qoHcuxQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was cold &amp; wet! But who cares! We love what we do! A great team effort! Thanks J-Town! @Fuerstenberg15… https://t.co/fGifi24q1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoctaHambone Start with a TB  in 16 oz coffee, also a TB ghee. Whip in blender for 25-30 sec.  You can double the… https://t.co/BhdMejqy1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NacoTheNautical 2nd from the left is 20 And the one all the way on the left is my brother in law I also have 2 sisters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipperviews @op4kids0context Nami stabs her own hand and makes it look like Usopp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know... A great #USTitle match at #WrestleMania I'd put in @MustafaAliWWE @reymysterio and @AndradeCienWWE #SDLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wise_dumb Not happy with the ending of @CrashingHBO not one bit, though I do have faith in @peteholmes and @JuddApatow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro tip! Today is @nicolettospasta 3 year anniversary. Swing by and getchu a bowl of pasta and a free cannoli! Yumm… https://t.co/FrcYLrCUWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BbmblondeGene They are like termites , that destroy everywhere they go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jockey Ryan Moore riding today at @ChelmsfordCRC  🏇Forbidden Planet, trainer Roger Charlton 🏇Albert Finney, trainer… https://t.co/H0phDGFe5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t believe the competitive scene is now 5v5. y’all playing a mf pub match fam😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahGragson Mine would be lots of side by side and passing with no cautions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left for work at 12:30 and @GiantWaffle was playing Tetris. I check in on my lunch at 5 and he’s still playing th… https://t.co/n8TkwmtJ9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[“(This bill) also points us back to the principal that by giving responsible citizens the ability to defend themsel… https://t.co/56l3RDNdFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesthaverEmily I am allergic they exacerbate my asthma but I refuse to be without them. When I was about 4 my asth… https://t.co/bixVanpxaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @lloydleefrancis The fact that so many states are legalized marijuana while so many languish in pris… https://t.co/5QH5GhNE4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a nation divided by racism, and the abuse of privilege and power. It used to be that those who had, still ap… https://t.co/dDLsgdk1i5]]></document></documents></author>