<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Me enoja mucho el hecho de que le digan cosas a @xdannniela si saben que lo buena persona va más lejos de un peso o… https://t.co/kl0r1yPxYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is fully in the next chapter of his life and I’ve eaten an entire gallon carton of goldfish today @Dani_Biggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fighting with @SickKids to combat childhood #Epilepsy. What’s your VS? #SickKidsVS https://t.co/5KPRhDS3wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day !!!!! @ Maria' Make Up Room https://t.co/cnh6hhdoXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate bill to find a study assessing extension of Northstar to St. Cloud is heard before the Transportation Financ… https://t.co/AmFmaD5nRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@870South @wonderfullone Amen!!!    Stephanie Flowers you are a hero!  Wish more people would rise up and stand up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScreenCaffeen @Mallorymillett1 @sabine_durden @Acosta Amen to that, Monique. As children, my parents in South Texa… https://t.co/qcJgSeYAOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessicatNY so much for the "flurries forecast. There was 5 inches of snow out there! How did you do in Long Island?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget about my baby girl😍 she’s also gotten SO BIG https://t.co/EVjWmCLSrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shot is from a couple years back but the message is still true today and everyday. 👊🏼💥Happy… https://t.co/ZiLyfTm5wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Better question: how do you get away with declaring a national emergency and then flying on Air Fo… https://t.co/SCbkVTkidu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another observation on my journey thru the 2000s - today seasons of SNL. @thesheertruth did not get a fair shake. T… https://t.co/2wwdH9sFkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great thread: These commenters take spoonerisms to “a whole nother” level. And, no. You cannot  split the word “a… https://t.co/s51Q0NKOxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re praying for you, Alex. May the Lord give you the strength to get you through this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can afford drugs you can afford to eat. If you care about your children you will feed them before feeding yo… https://t.co/M6L74ZQxgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatingBeagles @_drazzari @ForchiniWinery @PezziniFarms @jflorez @drycreekvalley @DemiCassiani @cuvee_corner… https://t.co/VKaSRb239Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @Acosta The fake news media etc., are blinded by their hatred of Pres., Trump they can't discern fact from fiction!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support  It says here I only have ABC on demand. If this is the case, how was I able to watch the red carpet… https://t.co/nWKYmNQhzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JW4Hillary @MichaelCohen212 @WSJ @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Keep dreaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever has that pic of @RileyGreenMusic signing my walking boot can you please send it to me?! 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the 🦆 was about to cross the road a Chicken said Don't do it you will never hear the end of it https://t.co/RNvVRXaekq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul under a fair and balanced congress I would agree with you. However, this congress is obstinate and obstru… https://t.co/gv71aurPnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKimSue 3 hots and a cot-sadly, some think it’s a better place especially in cold states.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshua6761 @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Giving most Americans access to vital health care...as opposed to build… https://t.co/lcSDw3UiL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this. ❤️🙏✨  #quotestoliveby #quote #sotrue https://t.co/HbauWVx2QU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bowers217 upcoming Teen Book Club reviews will follow AP procedures. 🍎🎓 https://t.co/HwwD5deGju]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear idk if Saturday was “national leave your partner day and stay single” because Saturday night todos mis hbs… https://t.co/Y95CMdUu8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDK, I just really feel like they should be charging cishet white men going into a queer centered space]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeesaTheBoss Girl them bxtches kill me. My husband this, my husband that smfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargaretJosephs Oh HELL NO @DanielleStAUbAU isn’t even with Marty anymore which is more proof she’s psychotic and… https://t.co/EifuKTcu62]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi if you were wanting to try on your swim suits from last summer to see how much weight you’ve gained I’d suggest… https://t.co/0G8DRdTQ2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NobilityInc @realDonaldTrump @Mikeste23528871 I know right ..not enough space..lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamKeithFL @DrCherylBrodie We need to do away with the DOJ policy that a sitting President can't be indicted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Quieres Ver Una Serie de Videos Sobre el Crédito?  https://t.co/PXi4lrbolE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24loves75 @DonnieWahlberg @NKOTB I keep asking who is running detention....you may want to get into trouble!!! Don… https://t.co/FXurznotn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyaSone7 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity 🤣🤣🤣 He’s controlled by, Russia and Saudi Arabia.  Two countries that have… https://t.co/0HskUsBNG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve heard a few keynote speakers that have left me with more questions than answers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at Biotest Pharmaceutical Corporation in #Hinesville, GA. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts… https://t.co/6NF62eXCYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soaper410 @HarryRHamlin I remember this too.. She was out n abt w/Bolton right away too..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing my ray of sunshine ☀️ good luck 🍀 today at @dancecelebrity ! #lyrical #musicaltheater #jazz @ Stephens Audi… https://t.co/34Ox3AHcRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having some fun in our awesome space!  My playground, feeling so fortunate to have this space to move, play, get st… https://t.co/w2VVLrIQHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the morning I have an extra 2 hours to eat a balanced breakfast is the time I have no breakfast food 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA['Remember Lauren': Father of slain University of Utah student Lauren McCluskey urges support of campus safety bill… https://t.co/wcSSYfp0qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Culture Committee for the ALC!! #GiveWhereWeLive #KWSocialAmbassador @kwri @ Houseman Team - Realtors https://t.co/lZ19WWC0Xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[There can only be one winner for season 4 of the #smallbusinessrevolution, but we're All winners now that… https://t.co/dxACtS7Ze1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there’s anything that I love more than chocolate, it’s tea. And then when that tea has added benefits to help me… https://t.co/OGaiHmskDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkAndreFurry @NHLFlames @GoldenKnights This was so sweet! #vegasborn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished week 8 day 2 of #C25K #Trainer on #Android with @zenlabsfitness! #everymomentcounts #run #running… https://t.co/6t3yVJkLT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the sales men come up and talk to me and I wonder if they own a toothbrush or know what toothpaste is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresenius Medical Care is hiring in Evans, GA! Read about our latest Clinical Management, RN job opening via the li… https://t.co/67jHkvkNOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I had a dream last night that Morgan Wallen told me he was majoring in pizza crust in college... like what the heck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLayton82 True but when it comes to Nightmare it’s just always so much fun even when it’s not a great film. That’s… https://t.co/48uKvyuOy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to our talented athletic trainers - Your tireless work in keeping our SA’s healthy and safe does not go u… https://t.co/esn419Jqhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rantsofagymnerd Do we have the same team?! I was also scrambling for people because of Stanford's bye, counted all… https://t.co/D271jEAVsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Missed our #Broadway Show here’s a Clip Of #itsaprilshowers Giving Us #wizardofoz #dorothy  Email Reservatio… https://t.co/lhKX7BDEvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puppies and coffee to make your Monday a little brighter!  Courtesy of @GroundsandHoun1  -  How to make a weekday… https://t.co/XIJaZjATik]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life knocks you down,  pick yourself up, start putting one foot in front of the other, and soon you will look… https://t.co/61lT7jsLrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Governor Polis !!https://t.co/YdPedJu9fn https://t.co/9wjGmt615z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAGouge @SydneyKing312 One day you will be rewarded for your sacrifice.  It wasn’t because you were less loved; ju… https://t.co/jKSZWxloFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had tacos in a little over a year since I left Vegas, I’m so excited rn 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend was all “ babe you know how my eye was all swollen so it looked stupid well in my mugshot i tried to m… https://t.co/od1PkHmfl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the hardest jobs is being a parent!  My husband always tells me to let my boys do the dishes...well here’s a… https://t.co/nnkLGzwBrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Readers want a sensory experience. Make your story come alive @WriterLindaO #SLWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao if I threw cheese at my dog she’d look at me and be like uhhh bitch I’ll eat this and shit on the floor for yo… https://t.co/cn8dbZerW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingsPlayszz @RuanAntunes7 @JeremyMartinCo3 @pizzalover4189 @Lynette_50 @mfourie64 @dm_stp @CJG_Pokemon… https://t.co/78FEKE3ofm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssholeToMany @richmurry21 @Big_Money_Robo @TopFlightTweets Lmaooo man why Vonte told him u was fighting that whit… https://t.co/Z88Gfk2ZbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's dinner time for someone....🐾💕😊 #dogsoftwitter #DogLife https://t.co/Xe30Q0KXzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoldenCasey @MarcusEdelstein Nobody is saying kids aren’t smart and CAN informed. Get educated, be involved. But vote at 16, no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Female CEO Doesn't Want Women Working For Her https://t.co/63UQIKuW0W via @YouTube to every FEMINIST OUT THERE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SplashyStackss Okay but who’s the artist bc this shit looks stupendous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin Hmnn a long, long, long history of #fakenoose hoaxes by African Americans.  SMH https://t.co/HDEXLyrISg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump We all have families yet don’t commit felonies or endanger our Nation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot my glasses in my car and I’m so blind so if you say hi to me and i don’t acknowledge I just really can’t see you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized I only have 3 episodes of Parks and Rec left and I don’t know how I’m going to handle it... https://t.co/gaTogdPXWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday George Harrison: Beyond The Beatles Spotify Playlist https://t.co/hjjTq7lpqc via @JamBase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen That's why I worried about President Obama ever frigging day. While no one is perfect, he was just w… https://t.co/0Td48oyeIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eleorabinovich @zanoni Ese gato desfila. Mi gata es una bola de pelos que se arrastra...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning, I had an insightful and engaging discussion with community advocates and organizations on the importa… https://t.co/sKUn4ip6L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We packed the place last time for the #merseysidederby so it’s time to do it again. Time to win this damn thing for… https://t.co/nWBX9Dj4PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genevieve Hart started the Princess Half Marathon! https://t.co/Na3J1TJPjA #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already can’t control my face expectations.. but it gets 1,000x worse when I’m drinking..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sulkyracer Let her stay and expose everything she says! Maybe her constituents will get rid of her then! Expose her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a day filled with more smiles, laughter, and insight than tears.  I post a lot but this is more perso… https://t.co/bv3ta2jLIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *puts self out there agaiiiiin* *gets stood up agaaaaaaaain* My &amp; my heart: https://t.co/0zZlgzUV0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicola_scherer @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves I have NEVER in my life seen someone perform with so much feelings an… https://t.co/XAos6vTE64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s time to redraw the Ohio congressional districts. Republicans are responsible for this gerryma… https://t.co/MWY0g32Vp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tall_6ft8_guy I’m from Seattle! Used to see Nirvana for 5$ at the Redmond Brick House. 😎 GenX music wholeother topic 🌟🌟🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dieser Wolf ist so aufgeregt, dass heute das Powerwolf-Shirt angekommen ist! 🐺🤘❤🔥😎 @ El Paso, Texas https://t.co/7R75PkGRDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think my cousin and his girlfriend broke up and if they did ima cry because they were my otp :,(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OznovaPam @number1slacker1 @kdubhitcountry It's so good to hear from you! Hugs!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT’S T-SHIRT TIME 🔥 First 350 students will get this Liberty Basketball t-shirt! #RiseWithUs https://t.co/cGNdtwSG0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just laying in bed with no interest in doing anything. But I feel like I need to do something or else I’m wasting my weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing is listening to my older co-workers talk about why all these strokes and heart attacks are killin… https://t.co/sd0VRQbKRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Accounts Payable Clerk - https://t.co/Oh8dZPIOKh #Accounting #Alexandria, VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen and Amen and Amen!   I believe this wholeheartedly!  The devil will fall on his face in despair!… https://t.co/RdL5PonFOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS @MelodyThomasSco Oh my goodness, I loved every minute of it 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to checkers and ordered 4 things.. I left that bitch with 2 bags full of food and 2 milkshakes for $5 thanks for being a new worker 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KreweCarrollton Here’s one more shot y’all might want... bc u can see a boot! ❤️ https://t.co/CERDoP35ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganVolpert Nope. A pastor who abuses he staff but grows the church. A teacher who roughs up the kids but gets gr… https://t.co/SniT8v5Wwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m really tempted to skip class for the first time and just sleep in 😭]]></document></documents></author>