<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hahaha! Now we know what those sex robots are thinking about while they are on recharge]]></document><document><![CDATA[El  Bobo Tanainas es el presentador de las noticias sobre el clima. Este fue su reporte para el día de hoy: “Lluvia… https://t.co/JKaaVfwXYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did Meadows break rules and bring that woman to sit behind him?  @RepCummings]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Thy gracious word, In meek humility, This will I do, my dying Lord, I will remember Thee.  Thy body, b… https://t.co/QmBAWFED2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I want a YSL bag .. then I’m good for the year. I like bags more than shoes. I think designer shoes hurt 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ate like @bflay tonight. Kale and Wild Mushroom Paella 🥘 and Pistachio Brown Butter Cake. @ Gato https://t.co/iFcG45mpX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTrump $MeganD1025 Hardworking single mom, out here struggling.. What is the group?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydhayd @Aerie Never agreed with a tweet more!!!!! @Aerie is where it’s at :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you @DonaldJTrumpJr #loserson and to all standing behind you and clapping #shameonYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjablake YouTube has thickened my skin!  It’s so fun to be poked at. I’m ok with it, but thank you for your kindness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought doctors take an oath to do no harm. They shouldn't in good conscience even provide an abortion, and if ba… https://t.co/g3P0kI3vxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a man who doesn't put me down all the time knowing I'm hard on myself as it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencerideas I loved this! “Quit wearing busy like a badge of honor” 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Non-Certified Aid-4" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of oppor… https://t.co/SgVe0jCMlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re the president of the US. Is it a dark day for the USA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellakalaw Just pick a day and let me know what time works best for you, and I'll be there. It would be a nice br… https://t.co/78FOGD1qIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend more time on Zillow and Petfinder than I do actually preparing for graduation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope that one day I’ll have a girl best friend who also considers me her best friend. Because at this poin… https://t.co/IGNCQXFwwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not supposed to line your own pockets!! This tweet right here is proof of you being unfit for President.… https://t.co/sxPJqIUP3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraAnnRI @kathyprojo @RIHouseofReps Come out, damned spot! Out, I command you! One, two. OK, it’s time to do i… https://t.co/9hDDVuhU2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarilynLavala @thedude77 @drhoyer1 @meaculpau27 @Big_crusher1000 @GracieLovesUSA @Macshivers @WagonKnoggin… https://t.co/aoZdS6Q5tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM IN SO MUCH PAIN AT NIGHT BUT I CHOOSE NOT TO TAKE PAIN MEDS CAUSE OF THIS STUPID EPIDEMIC THAT TOOK TOO MANY OF… https://t.co/unrdosigRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Kaja Bento Shimmer Eyeshadow is a new favorite of mine 😍🍑✨ I got Orange Blossom because I love peach, but I’d lo… https://t.co/GTHcwRnPRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReggieTap7 Yup. Been around forever. I prefer no sauce on mine though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bridget25358513 I think people would start rumors tbh.... so I would strongly advise against it 🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicOlague ... las mujeres gozan de los mismos privilegios que yo. Desafortunadamente estos temas luego provocan di… https://t.co/Cjy31xlJye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Husband feeling spoilt on his birthday by the @BevHillsHotel  thank you for making his 61st birthday special… https://t.co/DwJxtNAIfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[People think Americans just care about themselves but that hasn't been his experience out talking to people in communities #drvivekmurthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakeChristian8 @WorldofOutlaws @DavidGravel @JJR41Updates @DIRTcarNats One hand man👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The duranduran was so awesome last night ... thank you Simon for the tickets and passes ... it was a pleasure meeti… https://t.co/jLTMPvPXju]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been slacking off for a bit and I’m a weird place lately , i just wanna be around family and friends and focus… https://t.co/63GS9v1GPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m convinced y’all don’t understand how streets and avenues cause y’all been saying the same dumb shit since the b… https://t.co/5YAspRspDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is just another Trump &amp; definitely not good enough for our Democracy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg. This video is the bomb!! Love it!! Great job. It made my morning. Nothing but smiles!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renevelation @libby_poche if your god sends people to burn forever for the simplest infractions, then he is not a… https://t.co/6c4hoouPfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrubbsMg @CTE_BaltCoPS @Ryan_Imbriale @drobb An awesome event! Thank you to all that shared about the great things… https://t.co/taPS4ZV6QT]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% freaked a couple out today because they asked me to take a picture of them and I started giving them posing cues 😂 #photographerlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanhollinger I'm in America so I have no idea but if there's any chance in hell they have any Vincent Price movie… https://t.co/SfTd3l9SfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump takes every one OUT SIDE the UNITED STATES of AMERICA"AT THEIR WORD." But the FBI, CIA, NSA,  DOJ from… https://t.co/PSiCrRXu1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madsen414 @wolv54b1 @JungleJimsMrkt @bodyfit67 @cellmavin @excitedtofeast @afrobeerchick @OkiTimes @PeychoJoe… https://t.co/sjWeuBHkJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBlack Hi! Can you message me? I was hoping to message you about a film festival but it won’t allow me, I think until you follow me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww, man, it’s been like a year and a half since I’ve done this and it feels amazing to help someone else without… https://t.co/9jWRSPSTZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B3asTOfTheW3sT Fix took him! And he behaved! Tried to make a warning call but 13,000 people weren’t going to let him act a fool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatfanR Well, I mean technically had mom made dinner I wouldn’t have eaten them. I bought them for the hubs. So, yeh...her fault 😬🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriDixon8 @EarlSimpsonII @Barbaradye921 I noticed that. However, Civics is typically taught the semester before E… https://t.co/qX09JIBysE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot new in the market for lease. Catalina Grove Villas in Coconut Grove, already listed 2/2.5 Townhouse ready to mo… https://t.co/3se1jNdIh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The myth of me and you Is fiction turned to truth Most loves don't make it through But the great ones do.. 🎶💕  https://t.co/ahijope6GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost detallesdelavidamisma • • • • • • ❤️💗🙌 Síguenos en Facebook y Youtube 💗🌊😋 (enlace en la bio) detallesdelavi… https://t.co/9d1uM1DX8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four. Fking. Minutes. #Wow #DoubleorNothing is going to be amazing. Can’t wait !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whittneyyy08 I was going to say that my dad drinks Mike’s Hard all the time and no one says anything to him and th… https://t.co/ynWwBKhax4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t see people abbreviating LSU to LS or FSU to FS or WVU to WV. So why. Please someone tell me why. People… https://t.co/YPmBcZLojN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rise of #BrusselsSprouts https://t.co/vaVsLtBjM0 #nutrition #healthyliving @brownfield @BRNAgNews_Amie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sparkt4 @BballWarehous @scgirlshoops @nancyb0324 Thank you so much for working on my jump stop with me coach mark!! 💪🏼🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @999ktdy Polyester Power Hour Party!🕺🏽✨💃🏻 #ThursdayNightFever #StraightOuttaThe70s @ Rock 'n' Bowl de Lafayette https://t.co/zPVQ6gbwhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure I took a bath at 2 am and didn’t even use shampoo or conditioner because my hair is crustyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earthstrong_ras happy born day fiker. I hope you enjoyed your day, love you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rap was in a much better space when niggas used to beat up and rob niggas like Lil Xan and Lil Pump and that weirdo… https://t.co/itXqH7apPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjustdebb Yeah the body soap, I get the peppermint one usually but the lavender one is fire too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon My heart breaks for our planet with what @realDonaldTrump is allowing, nay, encouraging to happen. Wil… https://t.co/LeUAvpYbUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re truly living #RALife when you ignore your 8:30 class in the morning to have 5 residents in your roo… https://t.co/cb3MAtcsfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keridwyn55 @jparbones @ZPiet @EmrysCass @AOC Yes and all the wealthy people have private health insurance because… https://t.co/NZ6GkU8Aoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You are a nobody in the political world so you will be next to get investigated since daddy is pres… https://t.co/l99AQ2o8JL]]></document><document><![CDATA[t-3 days until @TinaKay511 whoops @CFullman30 ass in Coleman!!!! @MariiahGarzza &amp; i can’t wait y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[The body language between characters by Rumiko Takahashi is so great. It's like everyone is on a string. https://t.co/CXZ4zDxpF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Dear Mama Dane, praying for you the peace that passes all understanding.  I’m sorry that things are so… https://t.co/TRjxx12bxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redmsixsix @smooth_skippy You ppl are just so brainwashed. Y'all have BIG anger issues bc u don't know when ppl ar… https://t.co/JAwzEM7YUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC GOP doesn’t care, they will not go against him!  Just let Fox cover him and yoh all just watch the tape… https://t.co/Z9P7Oya6uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prayingmedic You have been on my mind for the past 2 days. God bless you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LKaurEdu @LetsTalkScience @NorsemanTweet What a great activity, Loveleen. Looks like your students really enjoyed it! Amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megawaveband I’m marrying a girl in the morning and then I’ll FaceTime ya. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he will lift up an ensign to the nations from far, and will hiss unto them from the end of the earth: and, beho… https://t.co/sUIOvHOgc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jazzzy132011 Come be a chronic drinker withhhhh me. Please and thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm surrounded! My babies; Sara, Scully &amp; Ben Solo. #Caturday #CatsOfTwitter https://t.co/KiJn2JuUje]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 #InternationalWomensDay #BalanceforBetter 😊🎶 https://t.co/S4do7YRp7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tidalwave7705 All gone. That’s what would work for me. Just make him go all gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Dr. Gu, you are one informed and empathetic doctor and human being. I wish you could be Surgeon General.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lust for bdsm and all that bondage fuckshit because I’ve never experienced that, I crave what’s new kinda like a… https://t.co/hxAkfJOoD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left chocolate and marshmallows in Payton’s truck a couple years ago, which he let melt, and I’m still planning my revenge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mill_cats @InukshukWolf I did.Thanks.I hope your #TuxieTuesday was wonderful.:-):-D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL Run for a political office. I cannot imagine what you go through,  my prayers are with you and you… https://t.co/NjUA76dxip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sistagrl1 Isn’t it a trip that the black community has refused to simply cover him and keep him out of the way. We… https://t.co/AW96Y9w7a3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MClaireEgan I miss you and Justin so much you two were a super couple😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cnic__ And our money could be spent else where. But not everyone will be happy. I never wanted him to go but felt… https://t.co/wSSEX31afR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't the salon owner the sam guy that played Maranda's uncle on marrying father Christmas? #hearties @hallmarkchannel @erinkrakow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson"@Ryland_Adams Beauty By Ryland Adams" #ShaneDawson&amp;Friends @Quidd https://t.co/vMMm4i2y9m https://t.co/VSRGgVVMSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaci150 @arkiegal411 @TwistedOne96 @currie14_kelly @Jasmine8137488 @GKeile @CynthiaRunnels1 @my3monkees… https://t.co/9D4rCjsGBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annastrassner @RimmerEdTech That was our first question. Where is Anna?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pvargas902 Yea but I would have gotten some flowers a teddy bear and went somewhere for dinner on some surprise shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz casi San Valentín 💟 en Vicente Guerrero, Baja California https://t.co/DSIzMz688D]]></document><document><![CDATA[GENESIS EIC 🌟 Offering: Mop, Vacuum, Swipe, Dusting, and More!  All Supplies Included🧹🧽 Prices Starting 2 Hours 2 M… https://t.co/caitWYsvdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @travelchannel 💀 spooky staircase 👿 creepy findings.... 🤗 Can't wait!!  👻👻👻👻👻 Adventures. Have I told y… https://t.co/yiw5zBen8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sjhernan3060 @paopao619 It's sparked a bigger curiosity for me, but unfortunately my family's records don't really… https://t.co/i49vX6Vhik]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a better note than vet school, I go home in a week and a half!!!!! https://t.co/PLyuVd45IL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two high school swimmers that became best friends years ago.  And oddly enough, still fit in their same high school… https://t.co/6z47Ar3WOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final day of the Summit #LSRSummit2019 and great speakers including Janet Silbernagel @JanetSilb, who shared her wo… https://t.co/fLxNqVV1wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I know how to do is take care of stuff... whether it's a masculine or a feminine task....do I enjoy taking care… https://t.co/JVyz47Ha6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#libertyline first #snow day @ Jacksonville, North Carolina https://t.co/L9kwiRJdVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turned in a job application. Very small place, low stress. Can I get some good luck and wishes? I need this! #BPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t seen my Valentine in nearly a month (he finally comes to Vancouver tomorrow!!) so here’s a #tbt to when w… https://t.co/wiCljUoTjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beilis_jay Lara Trump doesnt mind that the shutdown caused a few families a " little bit of pain. " she is a shall… https://t.co/3IyGb2uHn3]]></document></documents></author>