<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I wait tables at a restaurant and this is my paycheck for two weeks worth of work. I worked 28 hours and only made… https://t.co/3W5l5PKRHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way I’ll be accepting of #Sora in #SuperSmashBros is if he can alternate between #Donald and #Goofy like… https://t.co/s01zL5BIE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtyard construction begins at Glendale Lutheran! https://t.co/GTUA9Z4Wmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polite_Jerk @MSNBC Was still entirely deductible.  Before the tax “cut”  Bring back the marginal tax rate.  Tax the 1%!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instagram can we PLEASE for the love of all things in this world get a DARK mode?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfSub70 @chancethefarmer @acaseofthegolf1 U will love the wedges just played mine yesterday and o my goodness love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lasvegaslife #colderthanawitchestitty @ Casa De Sintay In the Rocks https://t.co/MMCVKipfW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bummed to be missing another #wlpc event, but someone has to keep the wifi working while the rest of you relax. 😁 A… https://t.co/mK7nnBxI1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tOSUFootball @brutusrocks36 @EricBow51047210 @BuckeyeNotes Just an old high school vid of you and Brutus. https://t.co/NWXmA2k3Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good guy that Bivol. Nice to see a respectful, analytical fighter.  May not be everyone's bloodthirsty cup of tea,… https://t.co/OmKKM4lNoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad always told me, “nothing good ever happens after 2am” and you know what, he was and is absolutely right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walk me home in the dead of night, I can’t be alone with all that’s on my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wore it best? Erik Gudbranson joins Rob Brown and Brooks Orpik as Penguins to wear No. 44. #dkps #penguins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrennaSimonSays @AmyKremer @RandPaul Nope. USA isn't #1, but it also isn't as bad as these subjective reports sugg… https://t.co/Cf2Xq68vNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicFlairNatrBoy God bless you @RicFlairNatrBoy #stillthebestthinggoingtoday #diamondsareforeverandsoisRicFlair #Whooooooooooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindalexyy Lol I’m moving literally like 100 feet from there this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a mentor used to say... all children are born through the eyes of Virginia Apgar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtySouthSoc Symptoms include: driving to KSU on a Thursday evening in high rush hour ATL traffic. #CCLFever]]></document><document><![CDATA[So #Humbled to see all the ❤ Ts put into supporting all Ss @Santiago_STEAM to have meaningful STEM and CS Learning… https://t.co/AmWLoN1NFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@habermetrics how do you manage Ross the Corsi Boss after these last few games? Rotate out 17 with 47 and move 15 t… https://t.co/iDlsSH5wL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our young writers are hard at work on writing their Myths, Monsters, and Legends! @ BookBar https://t.co/qvw9jSZCsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[NIMROD:   Nobody Is More Ridiculous Or Delusional   ... and i totally made this up 🤷🏻‍♂️ @KozNBCS &amp; @BigUrbSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattcasale_PIRG @WalkBoston Sidewalk’s are the responsibility of the abutters / owners not the city , can’t blame the city for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Like Ilhan Omar marrying her brother to get around immigration laws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all the @NapCatsGBK on their league honors!! #BeTheBest #GoCats]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Priyanka  aka Cougar hiding in the little arms of a boy named Jonas should be immediately stripped of the UNICEF’s… https://t.co/REGiwG7SnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PointsBetUSA Forgot to add that I also got a call from cus service asking me to put a review and then send them a… https://t.co/QXSb7R4JQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrumpyScot @carolecadwalla @Arron_banks I should wait on you to acknowledge Trump’s successes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read.”_Mark Twain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurelPfahler i understand the latter but in our soccer system how can we assume the difference in quality between… https://t.co/8mJ5PYy47D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitetailLegacy @LindsayThomasJr Like I said I can’t prove it no way but I consistently put those minerals there t… https://t.co/wXHuUXqbAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the difference between Professionalism and Code-Switching? #LetsTalkBlackIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduation to big sister!!! Baby McKell coming August 2019. We can't wait to meet the little one!! @ Utah Lake Stat… https://t.co/rUUsZNKypx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN NEWZEA-LAND privAte                           DNA-LAEZW(h)EN  THiSANoTE  i S L E 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to play both my Macdara Ó Faoláin mandolin and Lachenal concertina in the same concert.  Always enjoy playing i… https://t.co/ZIHwOs0uoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanHarvill @dixonbryce Only thing I can figure is they know college football fans here in SEC-country recognize… https://t.co/XGaqaKNYAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all, that’s what it’s all about right? 🙌🏼 I have a vlog coming for you guys this week of some behind the scen… https://t.co/yh9849QwkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Exotichikes Speaking of being under attack, perhaps none gives the appearance of that more than this one (though k… https://t.co/By4bZNjvGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Smith2214 @AJL_VII Conor never made it in the pen club in grade school]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big night for @InternatlShizz in Temple’s win over SMU. Our video report.   https://t.co/cQB8ml9ukt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovelyLikeLaura sis i read EVERY book you recommend and no i’ve only read the first one because i read the descrip… https://t.co/0WSKzWqsqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you finally move on and they hit you up with can we talk https://t.co/SjyZRqjxdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiTelevisaMx @FelipeCalderon @EPN @SCJN CORRANLOS  SON MERCANTILISTAS...ANTIMEXICO..ROBAN SE VENDEN--… https://t.co/2OMwXSIFst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can somebody please just treat me like an actual human being. For fucks sake man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieCarrel Would the guy you spoke with on the podcast have undenialable proof that it works?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapping up coverage of Lincoln Days with quick hits of @joniernst’s speech, @AnnLWagner criticizing city-county me… https://t.co/qbo1eGlFdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[More often than not my Saturday night vinyl sesh leads me to Black Sabbath. Tonight’s it’s their s/t. https://t.co/7xHCs594ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know some of you may not know Allan but some of you may.   Either way, he’s been posting about his depression a l… https://t.co/6ONy106b0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way for @britt_morrison_ to wrap her final regular season week with @UBwomenshoops!  Had a great final week i… https://t.co/vBkKS53twa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe @slayyyter is doing a Chicago show in June.... like wow....  that will be a moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night! Something the Seniors will remember for the rest of their lives! Great kids and great coaches! Class a… https://t.co/jyGeTdxsxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for P!nk Beautiful Trama World Tour! @ BB&amp;T Center https://t.co/L5evN2rSYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con la bendición de mi mamá y de mi abuela allá voy. De Rayados toda la vida #MonterreyEnConcacaf2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenKirkman They're scouting out a hip new restaurant on Melrose for me, Jen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/sBnzj94nkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley @PeteButtigieg Sounds great. Doesn’t have a chance of winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerJCox I can confirm from being in both places, the spectrum was as good of an atmosphere tonight as Vivint w… https://t.co/x5psgulCl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonHathaway3 where are you ... #modelling ??🤭 @ehrt3r @KubotaCanadaLtd @NASCARPintys https://t.co/twwkfiYwVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, there's a shade post from a supposedly-unauthorized intern.  Guilty angst from the last sane person left at… https://t.co/zF2hG7bCL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BowlingLive Can you play global deejays san francisco remix? McAllen Flamingo Bowl]]></document><document><![CDATA[A portion of E. Main St. here in #Carnegie is shut down after a tree is blown over and is resting on powerlines tre… https://t.co/aDWipXacRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsTaraDowdell Regardless, prison reform must be taken very seriously. Especially w/regards to how unbalanced sente… https://t.co/fvm9eV8TGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_USA_ @Debs2See @SikhProf Not with interference when he's doing his job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part b of my daughters math question has me really pissed off https://t.co/kd10UOjPaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judahperu1984 @Nzuki_101 Thats not what is bro. Everyone is saying twood wasnt focused or he was out of it or he d… https://t.co/0Nu9RV06SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly A fair press needs protections. A lying press needs corrections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a little post Valentine’s Day cookie love. Drop by https://t.co/J91mS3qTpF and we’ll send some your way.  Just… https://t.co/OX6EgNLYPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t say you been in a relationship several months or years if you break up during that and date other people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Sully__ If you start with YouTube approach I can help record and edit for you 😏 also rebound lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fort Drum Service Plaza in North Okeechobee, FL https://t.co/sQyrm8GFCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariahLeola They were trying to ride a fan boat in a field. https://t.co/RrTl06mHfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbeck @ToyotaCenter @HoustonRockets @JuliaMorales @ca_rockets @bull50 @CalvinMurphyHOF @RocketsPxP @dmorey Here’s to 37 more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I hear the train a comin' It's rollin' 'round the bend, And I ain't seen the sunshine Since, I don't know when I'm… https://t.co/ETO5sbpeIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kool Haus in Toronto, 2006 😎 @evanescence #fallensweet16 https://t.co/rBK0paCNV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moillorens Seguira diciendo @delvalle_ESPN que las cuentas se hacen en Mayo? Ojo que al Madrid se le puede acabar la temporada el Martes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WXII Just talking about the rise in adult suicides with my journalists buds in Philly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrookedIntriago Until you have a heart attack,  or get shot! Then OHHHH!, THEYRE COOL THEN!, HUH??? https://t.co/7LqHhwWnIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @Teleflora DO NOT ORDER FLOWERS FROM THIS COMPANY!!!  I ordered roses for Valentine’s Day and they sent a spri… https://t.co/VWiLuAUnN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNAiAnalyst If one were to take away the Genentech money I hardly doubt this one would have a 3-handle... Street n… https://t.co/hWXe4P0vGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman I remember when a first term legislator I know claimed that she "led the way" on education funding, on… https://t.co/B7fEK2FqoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[like I said not that hard to figure out since we have 60% of the diversity in our company all in our district 🤦🏾‍♂️ 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you dont understand that dogs play by biting,your dog needs to get out more.If you kick a dog for play biting yo… https://t.co/6SHzyy9I6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katieladyy_ @Karijo1011 Well when he cuts them off, guess who can take them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business Finance is the most poo cheese class if you like it I hate you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leozuckermann @MuySuFrida 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 habrá que limpiarte la sangre de las comisuras...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeciMustGo @JessHa6s There’s barely any fans up there, that’s why there’s no ushers...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Hey Sweetheart, think you could get that laundry finished for EOD.  Wife (in a mocking imitation): think you co… https://t.co/oyFS1CSmy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Tweet Got 568 impressions and I have 2 Active Followers You See Why I'm A Leader It's Time For The Necessary Changes To Come To Past]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruth64933323 @JJ66616 @raulmares72 @yogibythefly @OdinsMovieBlog Thank you Ruth. I did want this though 😂 https://t.co/SpRs6obIa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how we advance medicine. More eyeballs and open communication with privacy.  Imagine if you could cryptogra… https://t.co/8rkEhmTVSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drogyn1701 @Xr377 You may also need to setup a dedicated port for STO on the router.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpiwholesale @krassenstein This coming week, another Mueller indictment Friday you mean? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[*GROWN UP LANGUAGE*  (Swipe 👉🏼) Zit game strong, but overall a great night of education with @watmgnow at the… https://t.co/QUxVpL6Lxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yallaACADEMY @Pat_Malach Just don't mention it when they factor in a race. They'll try to kick you out of the race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewfNukem Same here ive tried a few times to get into it and for me it doesnt compare to @ElderScrolls games. I th… https://t.co/JfMvQP9NAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basic concepts of #RulesOfOrder seem to continuously elude the Chair and the vice chair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Epcot - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/EBA7WgJMAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenKTallmadge @tambid1 @TheLastRefuge2 @dlsenneyehc Nope. Only that there's never any evidence of actual wrongdoin… https://t.co/u87JeFJLOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god. A point guard threw a lob pass to a known dunk machine. They must plan on teaming up again. #Celtics #AllStarWeekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mosaic Session IPA by @BluePointBrewer @ Barfly — https://t.co/UBbmAKGYCy]]></document></documents></author>