<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Bella woke me up at 4am to let me know there were raccoons outside. Now she’s passed out and I’m up wondering if th… https://t.co/K9V99wMfS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd annual #BIGBEADBASH2k19 @ Gators Downtown!! Today, March 5th, from 6pm-12am! There will be lots of beads and pa… https://t.co/zdHNbwqmMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eden1985 Your not wrong. I tried to avoid but it was impossible. You either watch the night of or your going to be spoiled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three years ago i felt MC was not real. Then over the years I was sure. It is confirmed recently. Now, I have this… https://t.co/ntM90XooNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick12865787 @SunandSipCups @JadedDragonMMA @gunav8r64d @AOC Then just plain 1 ‘follower’ troll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙃I dead ass just grounded isaac now I'm hiding his xbox controllers and play station control. https://t.co/8UdeJVVpvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gru0407 I don’t know what Cameron has been saying to Liz he didn’t say much of anything except, she lost her mind… https://t.co/sGgbzk4yku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCSEMaryland @ADWCathSchools @NCEATALK @USCCBCatholicEd @CathStandard @Marielcua you are amazing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hear the acoustic version of “Rednecker” by country artist Hardy. Go to our website at https://t.co/lBOnTx9fnX for… https://t.co/g8xEPKB3mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case anyone ever questions why I think Times Square is kinda cool....The Hollywood Walk of Fame Has Been Named t… https://t.co/xgVP4StSFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigo americano, aunque se me note DEMASIADO que no soy gringa no me responda en español , sino no puedo practicar my english, okei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natalie Lash has arrived for the Oscars celebrity gifting suite today! natalienunncosmetics what time is it where y… https://t.co/kpc9SH1k4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @liinda_holder Hope he wins a judgement for it all! @CNN24HrFakeNews @CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love getting all the way to school to realize Callie chewed a hole in the crotch of my jeans!!!!! Love it thx Cal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @FoxNews We need less of you and your stupid racial remarks!  BTW, don’t talk about our GREAT POTU… https://t.co/A0UIQ55EXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so cold in the apartment I literally can’t get out of bed what is going on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceMeyer This morning I needed to see, read and believe. Feeling dread, frustration mostly emotionally, mentally… https://t.co/PWXtFvZh4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[MISSION PHOTOGRAPHIQUE - Le surfeur des glaces #lapresseplus. ⁦@AngelaRummans2⁩ ... next aventure... in French but… https://t.co/OfJocYzyNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolaMotz @whatstherukkus @j082298 @The_Acumen @ai_jared Not tackling the rigging, means it continues. In fact cand… https://t.co/Fgpy3xBT2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillBrinson what about #WillGrier? Where do you see him? #REDSKINS PLEASE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brothers are a year older! I'm grateful! Happy birthday my men dem!🎂❤ #EtukBoys #Twins https://t.co/2jJKQj3oOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arisoneedy @SELGALORE i’m not sure if francia is shady towards selena though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So why are people now digging up more of our past? I'm now hearing stuff about John Wayne. This is all just crazy n… https://t.co/cg2NdpdQb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[u ever have such a bad night that u already know the next day is gonna suck too? cause same]]></document><document><![CDATA[But first going to run with Ruf-A-Loop RufALooper  This dog has so many different nick names..he answers to all of… https://t.co/nRfyQr0nJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After reading the series of tweets by @SimGuruLyndsay, it seriously hurts me when the Guru's gets so much harassmen… https://t.co/VoiU23PZtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live, love, happy! #wordstoliveby #saturdayvibes #happythings @ Liza Byrd Boutique https://t.co/cgYNgjDHIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicholasperna1 No cliff tonight... but tomorrow i will be at the cliff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@takemomalong @Adventuringgal @miliman12photos @MattsRoadTrip @MyVirtualVaca @DanaHFreeman @KaraDiDomizio… https://t.co/WJwtXR5AHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepArmstrongND You seem to forget that there was a taint review done on the stuff seized from Cohen. Also, it was… https://t.co/3Yo5iMzXaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelenaNNBA @KATUNews No word on citations- but checking with @ORStatePolice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaunaSallai Absolutely way out of bounds,  no way people are going to sit still for this, I am beginning to think… https://t.co/XXUHuiM0Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟 SHINE BRIGHT 🌟 Life is too damn short to let anyone dim your light . My girl @polk_haley and I will get it poppin… https://t.co/tPEvKCiEkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[getting back on cam in 15 minutes 🥰♥️♥️ come see me and have some silly hangouts before bedtime!💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaseballPoodle @UMNRecWell I sure do, probably as much as you love baseball! I'm one lucky poodle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never felt more violated, disrespected, or triggered by something as much as i have by the snow/cold this winter 🥺😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need just a little bit of aluminum foil and don’t wanna go to the store. Where are my neighbors when i need them?… https://t.co/X0qGXWSRey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Falcon_105 @DanyCastiel @Akemi363636 @garciacg17 @andyspeirs1 @59Hamdeen @myroques @alisa04059519 @PiaNordic Beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC lets talk about idiot, idiot, idiot and moron,moron,moron.   Thanks for helping Pres. Trump get reelected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy, living in the great North is a lot of fun. This is my aunt and uncle’s house in Minnesota. #SnowMageddon2019 https://t.co/VoI5sxR5li]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommonGloom @Ticketmaster I just paid $102 for two $35 @adtr tickets last week 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AldeaPardo Para mi el cuello es casi punto G wn... Uno permite, acepta y goza la tocá de cuello con concentimiento… https://t.co/SAXapJ5zEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickJam54531190 @JesseKellyDC Looks like maybe Chalula?  But, could be Valentina]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiring a social media agency can be the difference between a good company and the best company.  Get our service 👉🔗… https://t.co/0QS6eqhg95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow @ACMawards How is @lukecombs This One’s For You not nominated for album of the year? This is a rip-off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning the #magiccircle #crochet #crochetersofinstagram 🌙🌬☁️💫 @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/TeZ0rLTHlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you #TraderJoes 👉🏽 a step in the right direction to reduce #plasticwaste ! It really is up to all of us to de… https://t.co/60M0T7juph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaMartinezB8 Lo q usted y su hijo no ve! Es q se sigue repitiendo! Los tales disidentes que siguen siendo las F… https://t.co/eF5PcWpsYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all better not tell me you’re headlining for @jonasbrothers when they go on tour 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillRiley @BrianOake - this alarm clock has changed my life. I have it set to @TheCurrent to wake me up!  https://t.co/lZ9lxfcDMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakeRi62685290 @michaeld0716 We have a few fickle fans..dont they realize we have some players playing with the flu?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please educate yourself more before you make the costly decision not to vaccinate your child.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Taubes tantalizes us with the re-launch of old blogs...  our local 🎓obesity researcher re-releases his respons… https://t.co/N2ck29GU6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful view of the Launch tower for @SpaceX! The historic DM-1 launch was RIGHT here early this morning! So co… https://t.co/zXyaRZclUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jyotibansalsf so encouraging that it took time to find someone to take a chance on you! Great story @jvrionis @Unusual_VC @StartupGrind]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:12p  Today was a great day — I am so blessed by my tribe. I can’t thank a few of you enough for being there for m… https://t.co/R3xvZqIPgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @HillaryClinton @SenSanders Private BIG plane along with campaign debts &amp; lake house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father Ted, you will be in our hearts and prayers forever. Thank you for being a friend, a teacher, and a mentor. https://t.co/CAZCPrBbyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time last night at @zinque_bar in Venice to say goodbye and give a warm send off to our friend @nicogourdon..… https://t.co/vl6VT2fBga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why wear it as a bib when you can wear it as an apron #momisilly #seafood #oceanicboil @ Oceanic Boil https://t.co/AuBEBNMH9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara I actually don't believe much of anything, said by anybody? We all #LIE,#LikeDogs, sometimes, Preet?… https://t.co/U4uBvp63Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzsix7 man if i knew you could use your hips and legs like that i would be doing so much more weight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class time: Who's Who among the Cheeto in Chief's " best people" THREAD  "]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know of a good place to get your eyebrows threaded &amp; tinted ?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I plan on turning Twitter up! Ppl to anal retentive,I love those who laugh w me https://t.co/Cs2Wd4yx1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LADYBUNNY77 @Statistar30 No you’re perfect in this post. However, just as in business, a “Leader” is only as good… https://t.co/zLGyMjq3HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stl7thward @alidreith Happy happy! Enjoy your day. https://t.co/Z7uvQcrOZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not ashamed to say that i need constant reassurance. feelings fade and people change. i need to know that you fuck w me how i fuck w you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd Geez, you guys tonight....so negative about @JoeBiden .  He’s going to be one hell of a candidate.  He,… https://t.co/sqR5kXc3gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly think the worst part of working at a daycare is the washing your hands hundreds of times. My hands are so dried and cut up 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sister just called me and asked me to get her toilet paper and i said "good luck" and hung up 💀LMAOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Miller calls George W. Bush's immigration record 'astonishing betrayal' of American people https://t.co/HJMM1QpExl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsabelleVallu Não era só comprar um bilhete do metro? Queria eu decidir quando eu vou trabalhar sjjdahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only reason his royal whiteness hasn’t cancelled is because cryotherapy is good for athletes]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to love him with all the heart, and with all the understanding, and with all the soul, and with all the strengt… https://t.co/1Urei7touG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lydia Bolin crossed 15K. Time 02:05:50, pace 12:24 min/mile, est. finish 8:37 am https://t.co/HCjMYM5T68 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pistachio Patty is still available! @ttaymillek #special #springbreak2019 #hitusup @ The Healthy Hippie Cafe https://t.co/HBLAsNB93l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get the REAL colluders &amp; CRIMINALS now.....  the ones Obama's FBI, DOJ &amp; buddies commited!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’ve been at work for almost half an hour and the only person to even acknowledge me is my fav coworker.  Eve… https://t.co/wi1MUozK6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you hit a freaking pot hole in KCMO!  Cost me time and money!  Hopefully my rim isn't jacked.  UGH!!  Finding… https://t.co/2yRzN0irVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ps. If you or anyone you know works at google, please be an ally and step up (if you are able to).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Take Your Favourite Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up     Click Here: https://t.co/y2UazxBM5p… https://t.co/5mLQlR17Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkaine @AnneHolton Hey in This is Us such a crockpot set the house on fire...surely you can afford to upgrade!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m bout to pop up with a kid next year so I can “ my kid is my valentine “ y’all to death 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fuelfest2019 was AWESOME! Freaking loved it!!! And the highlight of the day was finally meeting @codywalkerroww an… https://t.co/eG0GOnET70]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to be a better husband:  -keep a groomed beard -support your wife, not belittle her -cook dinner -Ditch your wo… https://t.co/MUTD6B4pGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jg_CincyChop I haven’t been able to hear enough to  agree or disagree.☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before church beverage (at @7Eleven in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/qneYuiFCK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[With everything going on with the Jonas Brothers, this video seems relevant! (This was when Jerry and I were first… https://t.co/HpOA4VeKfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-reading Harry Potter again (or rather, listening to the audiobooks!) and one thing that will NEVER sit with me i… https://t.co/ml0HzNCgxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO COOL seeing @lizadonnelly draw live at @20x2 at #SXSW2019! https://t.co/t32oS2pEm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad @ToddKTLA @MicahKTLA @chercalvin @veraktla @DerrinHorton @JohnFenoglio @mcdade_mb 🙏❤️😉🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has the most genuine heart ever. I love her❤️ https://t.co/nhhESjUuYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave660dave @ThePhotoHour @StormHour Ah!  Nice!  See the color difference? Experiment some more! 😃 The wind speed… https://t.co/zfrbxcdmXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Caught Up In The Country by Rodney Atkins Feat. Fisk Jubilee Singers. https://t.co/ZLt3kN86zU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @jbtherealtor for my Singles Awareness Day card!!! Haha!! YOU my friend, rock!!! 🤘🏻🎸❤️ @ Bishop Arts Dist… https://t.co/w4NXGWWr69]]></document><document><![CDATA[New team, building new relationships, enjoying new adventures. #TUProud of #TU_TLife STMs supporting Mesa CLG Plati… https://t.co/KjjF3ryEw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: arrives to my eye appointment 10 min. early as requested.  Every Eye Exam Place: even though you're here when w… https://t.co/aq2K2hlCvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is great rn.... just waiting to see what kinda curveball life is gonna throw at me next 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arkantart @DonnaLeeThomps8 @CoriSigma @RatesDaGoldfish @JentoInfinity @LolaKittySLC @tinkertoy5 @LordGraydon… https://t.co/Rf1lBJDmfV]]></document></documents></author>