<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It really doesn’t get much better than these two. #Chicago #Family #JohleyBetty #Corgi #Corginstagram #GodDaughter… https://t.co/MaZK9EhblD]]></document><document><![CDATA[6- what about a lover? C- I have met women who care.  I will find either this love in the mind scape or a love in p… https://t.co/rcX1Htupqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to wear my American flag speedo to Orange Beach for spring break ☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well. Can’t argue with the quotes. Lol @GlenEwing @WAxelFoley @donaldjr https://t.co/dNFaJn9KrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí casual viendo la Copa del Rey de Baloncesto. Semifinal Barcelona-Tenerife. https://t.co/EzMov2Gvn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day today, more racing to come tonight from @DISupdates, looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyeball @Chribonn58 @TamRuther @cathmckenna @liberal_party @JustinTrudeau " All your sheep are baying for you." condescension indeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missbreezyy @MrsMatt13 @MattJackson13 @NickJacksonYB @KennyOmegamanX @backstreetboys @BranCutler She knows all about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[My reward to myself for working through the weekend is @Nigella_Lawson’s caramel croissant pudding. It really is on… https://t.co/ic4IFFhK7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump The Dems have the opportunity to expose the (allegedly) most corrupt, deceitful, liar in… https://t.co/xNZn4wDgIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy seguro que alguien puede identificar a esa persona que parece descargar en la trabajadora toda su frustración… https://t.co/M2IXQR5kbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck tomorrow fellas! Let’s start things off right. @hunterrunion_15 @cdawg_07 @rileykramer_1 @cooperdelooper… https://t.co/QpURcfw7xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittyhawk311 @JakeMc945 @emtee2355 Now you did it. You're wet, aren't you? I did that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Masked_Astros @MLB @SFGiants @RaysBaseball @Orioles @astros @tigers What the fuck is WAR? Who cares. I’m talking about real stats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jackie_Redmond @GrittyNHL @NHLNetwork Did somebody say, Broken?! https://t.co/254flgGaPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSamperO @DELAESPRIELLAE La memrmelada que te dio santisb a ti danielito es pura pecueca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @VedanticFlaneur @Vito53904302 @gneely17 @SaltLife_614 @mikethomas585 @arc76676 @JeffHall30… https://t.co/ZSM400H8OJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t see @Braums_Inc fries on this graph @MikeSherman. #CrimesAgainstHumanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanlpainter @RobPaynterSD61 Thank you @ryanlpainter. This is a very important and overlooked issue. I'm proud to… https://t.co/qE53MBwS6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Be Hoppy by @WormtownBrewery at @legalseafoods — https://t.co/YouxSzunoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My other love!!!! #sonya7iii #lakeelsinorephotographyclub #lepcgroup #lovemycamera @ Lake Elsinore, California https://t.co/oQ8xNQOdFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like someone’s excited about the new @marenmorris album “Girl” that dropped today. Lorraine is showcasing som… https://t.co/DKdBRVerrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bachelet do us a favor don’t go to my country to support Maduro cdtm just don’t even show up..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @NASAEarth Is this on-going now? Just curious.  Robert Morton, author https://t.co/mnEB9rwfGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[KASB's Gilligan on HB 2330: Entire community needed to combat bullying #ksleg #ksed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zforgash24 @MichaelRapaport Whoa!!! U unfollowed sum1 who doesn't know u?? Wow!! What a loss!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BassTamer Im glad you saw these boss 😂 The 90's arrive tomorrow &amp; youre #1 with a purple tail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust the process - Chapter 3.  Excited to announce I’m taking the leap to Charlotte later this month to pursue the… https://t.co/aWAidPp2nT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love our Redemption kids dance team!! they are killing leading first service worship!  Today i am serving in kids… https://t.co/BHJk5iH7ZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Leave No Ass Behind - part 2” new at: https://t.co/1yJpviC2re https://t.co/X8n1JcUwG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't want to embarrass myself. Would be hell of a thing to tear my rotator cuff throwing 55 mph and go on vacat… https://t.co/a6iw9Zfy9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overnight @JetBlue flights from PSP to JFK. Pilot said were waiting for 15 mins (closer to 30 actually) for a plane… https://t.co/2uqR59LBaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some real free throw struggles going on right now for both teams. @cfcaeaglepride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outside__out You and your brother got some great video. What phones do you two use?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer Beating him in 2020 is all that matters.    The legal processs will be chasing him until he dies.  It’ll… https://t.co/GwNSf2vpbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Calgary. 3-1 over Isles👍 Caps tied for first in Metro .... (NYI has games in hand) #AllCaps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amouranth Whenever I hear the words "Bon Appetit" I think of the Disney move, "Lady and the Tramp," when the dogs… https://t.co/hGmSFfTCga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@accordingtomio This is as warm as it will be until probably Wednesday... ice and snow tonight, plunging into the s… https://t.co/sni4hKQbeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last Drop Lounge selfie. I have come to this room for 4 years for better or for worse because I love comedy. I… https://t.co/77s4hklvW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath All parody aside Trump was a Democrat. And good friends with JFK Jr. Who advocated for gay rights b… https://t.co/OdRPLdXB28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep fighting, @EqualityVA: “In #Virginia, it is still legal to discriminate against LGBTQ persons. Presently,… https://t.co/OTZoP4rDO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Alexa and Siri won’t do: the latest development in personal assistants https://t.co/kt1MFNT6Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[dreams that I wish I had every night. These are the realities I wish I had every day. I don't want to look at the s… https://t.co/zGLM3PTGoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Room shook me to a point of a freak out. I made it probably only 35? minutes in, if that (Shut off at the bel… https://t.co/XmbyChoFEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t stand Lebron. If he goes to the Lakers it’s another slap to the face for Cavs fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResethO Hmmm... you evidently have not seen the ladies that I am talking about. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeThePlan #QArmy Are We Having Fun Yet. Prayers to all of our Great Patriots taking Flack we will Overcome https://t.co/x5HQQ2rZoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why are you threatening to release 800 ISIS fighters? Do you think a wall will protect the US against an air attack?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @JoaquinCastrotx @realDonaldTrump Hey Pelosi is this the same wall that you voted for to spend $40 b… https://t.co/XcTXFc1iUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t thought there was anything degrading about saying “women’s history” before. Similar terms, “military hist… https://t.co/POoiHHHVH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a special grandma slice from @Joeyshousepizza today. Many thanks! It was wonderful. https://t.co/CDTASzVFGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of #GOESEast/#GOESWest Mesoscale Sector Coverage today 03/07 Real-Time #ABI TrueColor/IR with East Meso1 (red)… https://t.co/H96GTLZ9vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do i get up 1 1/2 hour before work an for 1 1/4 hour i lay around?  Why dont i just sleep for another hour an fifteen minutes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My barber dropped me as a client for a  nfl player, smh the cycle continues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningsMaria : @RepDebDingell represents Dearborn , MI. She reports that anti-Muslim crimes are on the rise there… https://t.co/repVtF1USH]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC Bound and Down. Kenny Fuckin Powers. (@ Gate 6 - @cakairport in North Canton, OH) https://t.co/Qsd4qB9vPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: what should I eat for breakfast?  4 yo son: maybe you should eat a taco?  😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a meme that said gay culture was standing with all your weight on one foot... but like, do straight peop… https://t.co/XBdhulbx3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the results of President TRAMP'S employment FAKE NEWS!  The kids first "job" out of High School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jEn_BaBy72 I wish it was here lucky u Jennifer check your DM I sent u a article. Let me know if u got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN your going to resign from congress Muslim Jew hating bitch you can’t serve your full of HATE.....!  Leave… https://t.co/RqEJwhm7V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to Sierra for always having the best advise and voice of reason. A true CMSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussiKiviniemi @PrimeImageVideo There is an HDMI connection that also contains your audio signal…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaberNotaloca @ELTIEMPO @petrogustavo Psssss las pasadas elecciones las perdió! 🤷🏻‍♂️. Q es para ti nunca? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the messiest @benandjerrys ice cream date with my girlfriend at Venice beach, it was delicious 😛🍦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4nalyst Lmao there’s so many things to learn bud. Like Kevin Nash also played shredder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie, I was kind of proud when my cat Russ hissed from inside his carrier at dogs bounding about like fool… https://t.co/oWiaUEnoJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Madison Heights, Virginia https://t.co/HGC5XPvAqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Comic Book Day is here! #NewComicBookDay #Comics #Comicbooks #Marvel #DC #Avengers #JusticeLeague… https://t.co/SXPtj5VMoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for tomorrow's Chaffey Trust Scholarship meeting as we enter scholarship season.  ...Proud member of this won… https://t.co/42GPMJRl9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Brannon! We are very proud to have one of our @MWHSWildcats students be an advocate for the arts at… https://t.co/ngbdlVl9TP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Sent my donation as soon as I heard Bernie was running. Go Bernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raducom @SealeyGerald @Razorsmack1 @pjbowles4 @KamyMAGA @GeanineC @RodHillis1 @tweets4poppy @DoingRight1… https://t.co/m8aKzTcjU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ava Sofia named her new unicorn Kitty 🦄 I think it’s love!  #daddyslittlegirl #avasofiacox @ Trump Plaza Residences… https://t.co/3T5PG7AJwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I like to stretch on my side.  • • #morningstretches #josiethefrenchie #frenchiefriday #frenchbulldog… https://t.co/bKz3JSoVgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite container logo: the hard-working Mitsui O.S.K. Lines alligator. https://t.co/uAjUVq4hDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulls game next week with my boy @BigPoppa_23 hopefully they don’t get smashed 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sonyapgh @steelers1288 @DunnJeffry @randycrossFB @charlesarbuckle @ForzaCorrado @WaymooMoody @joeybagovdonuts @cjg57 Nah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gallagher_JJ @GMA @ABC @RobinRoberts @JussieSmollett Faking a hate crime should be prosecuted as a hate crime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sucks.. I was too late and everyone left me.  No one answered their phones neither so I could tell them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you share a bottle of red with Villa Gallace’s favorite visitor, the great Mario Andretti?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic Alert: National Grid will be making a repair today beginning at 9am on Dedham Street at the intersection wi… https://t.co/YLY1oPvz7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate goodbyes .. I’m always the one that leaves a event without saying anything to anyone 🙈😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s all a game, that many of us have yet to learn how to play! Grab the “In Home Banking” board game or course now… https://t.co/i0pfw8QvKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byajperez @TheoTypes Media companies have lost a lot of untapped talent because of these practices. I'm a proud… https://t.co/giXkJgaacM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalVegas @JamesInLasVegas When all the resorts are gouging you and nickel and diming you with all the up charges… https://t.co/rIxBLVULLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[לשריין את @AviBuskila בעבודה Too much wishful thinking???  🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻🤞🏻 @HavodaParty @GabbayAvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The crazy thing is, ain’t nothin poppin in Jacksonville .. like why ppl even go there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun time working on my first #characature design. It just happen to be a plus that the theme involved the… https://t.co/OvXqb7RjIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final NC State 14 Bucknell 2. Final K count  was 6. Great overall game by the #Pack9 this afternoon. ncstate_baseba… https://t.co/nPLLHqf3UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakeriley It’s hear, hear, right? Not here, here? I need to go to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firewings doesn’t do the student five free boneless anymore this is an outrage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, JJ made a mistake. His sentence will be severe.  Chad Ruhwedel’s sentence will be commuted as he’s not Jack Jo… https://t.co/Y8MQAC5qkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cady has herself a new piggy-back buddy. @ Riverbank, California https://t.co/qweQrZWCPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Mulroney @fordnation @fordnation will now play the "new" Boss Hogg! https://t.co/uIrl7aXnck]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @OssiningSchools will be on a 2 hour delay today.  Be safe everyone. https://t.co/8sP5HjlXnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have fun being booed by your own fans @Bharper3407. Philly fans are the worst in sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitman604 @harjo111 They are scared of the sex trafficing investigations closing in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is that when I start watching @didyouknowgamin videos I can’t stop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are those masked men? Great day on the mountain with @jim_morafb and bwlocknane !  Let’s do it again😀. davidmko… https://t.co/d7h0RpQYIU]]></document></documents></author>