<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey @FedEx do NOT pull into my driveway again. Your big a$$ truck is too heavy and just ripped up my yard. I WILL b… https://t.co/SWEWdJSy2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ever so far deep into not following someone that you can’t start to follow them at this point because they’… https://t.co/gQpLCaSWaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorAyee_ this was just a random person online that started a petition to do this 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump WILL YOU PLEASE FRIEND ME so I can write you PRIVATELY Sir]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always think about this one time when a girl told me I wasn’t Mexican enough to use a brown emoji. I sent her a p… https://t.co/tdbOsDdGpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethenny Mama always said, tell a lie then you got to tell another to cover the first lie. He didn't have to do th… https://t.co/gv1sej9JcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewLiptak I’ve experienced the reverse too! Like, I’m allowed to have feelings other love for something without… https://t.co/U9sLrDDmIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARIA TALKS WAY TOO MUCH AND ASKS SO MANY QUESTIONS ABOUT EVERY LITTLE THING! BUT I’LL NEVER TELL HER THAT 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakeShowYo @anthonygolino Look at his teammates 😭 that could never be L... nvm man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even Tatsuro Yamashita sounds good when remixed into Future Funk ❤ ❤ ❤ ❤ #music #futurefunk #rlm #reallovemusic… https://t.co/fy50eXUKWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilElroyJets That shits gross lol you must be going through a lot if you chugging that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygriffin @AOC She’s my daughter’s age. What a wonderful young woman!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i asked this white guy where he worked and he said “nowhere where you shop.” helllllllllllaaaaaaaa offended.  i lit… https://t.co/JRkXqzmIMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinabop29 @ForumsMeghan @CoconutBoombox @RedSoleFan Happy birthday 🎉🎁🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PC_Angry Not even reading this because she is as dumb as a box of rocks ....she always looks like she is sucking a… https://t.co/TThniZovXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most surprising moment of #Oscars so far for me is @ladygaga’s ability to sing in that necklace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missbfitzg has a new youtube channel and a really spoopy found footage film that you should all see! | The Queen M… https://t.co/AgCprt5bG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally thinking of making a side business in making shirts, sweatshirts &amp; baby clothes, etc...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Yes sort of like you relationship with Luis Farachahn !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you believe that @jgonzodotcom and i were vomited on in the first bout? Would you believe by the same boxer t… https://t.co/h3QG9IViCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratitude party ! What 3 things are you most grateful for right now ? I am most grateful for being trustworthy, for… https://t.co/PfWfPSBG8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 371 of student teaching: Currently dying of exhaustion. https://t.co/UnnfuJkegk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was out cycling 8.84 km with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/8CG8QOeTdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy jugue con mi ahijada (camila) como por mas a de 4 horas y que me encanto... mi niña es unica🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you haven’t heard some black excellence whistle tone all black history month 🤩✨watch for your health]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Chris Christie says Southern District of New York should concern Trump more than Mueller probe https://t.co/cjZIUIkLim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the airport between three (3) bachelorette party groups is the most jarring wake-up routine I’ve ever experienced]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lydiavalle__ I'm SO jealous! I haven't had them in forever!! I hope you liked it 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chloe back at it again😭...MY OVARIES ARE SCREAMING AT ME. This is actually the cutest child don’t @ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last nights dessert samples 😻  I orchestrate events, play with food and make things pretty...and I get paid for it… https://t.co/0fbLeA4B9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nonmendacium @TheMeltlingMan1 @pattonoswalt People need to learn to reach in to their depressed and troubled friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliyyaSwaby @CollierForTexas @EmpowerTexans Cheshire doesn’t realize he shares the pew at worship service with Tex… https://t.co/aI5BRSgd9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antes de Trump ha hablado Bolton, Melania y hasta el propio Guaidó. Curiosidades de un discurso que, pese a centrar… https://t.co/Je7MSvIxRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigHomie2 I ask God for forgiveness for myself but thanks for the extra prayer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dream is to marry rich and live the easiest life imaginable im so tired this is a call for help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei If you own a copy of "The Art of The Deal" and you do not like DJT,  I Propose the #DestroyYourCopy Ch… https://t.co/44jBFsRfci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwspeers @ASCO @ConquerCancerFd @ASTRO_org @shanestecklein you better have applied!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my old admissions stomping grounds of NJ.  Driving in Jersey is like riding a bike. https://t.co/pujjJ82jes]]></document><document><![CDATA[New head shots for some really big news coming soon!! Thank you @collitonstudio for all your amazing work and that… https://t.co/KxaELGJPQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[He loves me ❤️#loveisintheair #hisQueen #valentinesday2019❤️ @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/fQKZdmdQuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Can Bernie Sanders survive the modern left? Hell, the modern left can’t even survive the modern left. The… https://t.co/CIeJWhf9aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Aricka I needed to go study and she said " what's that do they have music " 😂😂😂😂 bitch , someone claim her please]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Frankenmuth #PureMichigan (@ Frankenmuth, MI in MI) https://t.co/tAOM2Op4YV https://t.co/SZyFyWGSMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add your name: Congress needs to investigate Acting Chief of Staff Mick Mulvaney https://t.co/Sye5bX6Nr7 via @CREDOMobile #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2BRqYKVT2e @aliciakeys @beyoncre @serenawilliams @JanetJackson @SteveKerr @StephenCurry30 @philjackson… https://t.co/ZxHA2kMdHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Obispo_Manuel Me encanto todo lo que dijo hoy , como siempre y dejé la valija please !!! No se vaya nunca de… https://t.co/UUnfoKLax6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad that I made two huge orders last month and stocked up on jumpers and sweaters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet #audreyrestaurant at the @hammer_museum  #mydayinla #retro #vintage #mod #midcentury #restaurantdecor #ucla… https://t.co/Uye7XEY83E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theobaldkidd @dbongino Therefore it doesn’t matter what the “generals” do Because really nothing would change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorpheBrushes @jamescharles I love my palette—wouldn’t give it up and recommend EVERYONE get at least one!!!! With… https://t.co/0ajK83t5De]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @Nataliv6 for being the reason why I made it 🧗🏻‍♀️✨📣😆 https://t.co/c12RahrIyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 82 of #backgroundtobestfriend  It's hella windy today. I can't get back to sleep. Guess I'll try and be product… https://t.co/WVObKj6U4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome people and an even more awesome cause #brainiacball #familyandchildrensservices #tulsa https://t.co/9I9Ip08da0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elena_SF_CA In MMM canon, Fossil combatants battle as they did when they were extant. #2019MMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending 2019 AZCEC/AZCASE Conference at Black Canyon Conference Center. Keynote, Kristin Souers, outstanding!  #AZCEC19]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you understand you can’t get a bachelor’s degree at community college and that most employers won’t give you job… https://t.co/4RJerPnpSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should cry white privilege more often. It's the truth. Whether or not it is recognized. No other countries inca… https://t.co/D1p6kESXOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been waiting too long and with no answers. When can we expect the bike lane to extend from Yellowstone to Uni… https://t.co/tQu2nomBgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The LORD brings the counsel of the nations to nothing; he frustrates the plans of the peoples. https://t.co/1imf0o1iTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNiyago I can’t. 😂🤦🏻‍♀️😂🤦🏻‍♀️😂🤦🏻‍♀️  I am literally in between these emojis right now.   #CheerUpADN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @RepLeeZeldin @RepTedBudd @EliseStefanik First remove @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok so not that I don’t love my dog already but a wiener dog could really make a girls life better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Alexa, what’s the weather gonna be like today? Me: Alexa, what’s the weather gonna be like tomorrow? Me: Alexa,… https://t.co/8ss2PvxIxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[⠀         (\__/)     ⠀  (•ㅅ•)      　＿ノ ヽ ノ＼  __     /　`/ ⌒Ｙ⌒ Ｙ　ヽ  my cat when ( 　(三ヽ人　 /　　 |  the doorbell    |　ﾉ⌒＼… https://t.co/khWQnmYXb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sentencing for Sandler isn’t complete. He’ll return to court in about 2-3 weeks to be given his sentence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cart van on Berry Road in Norman. Flashers on. Loading a woman in a wheelchair into the van. So many trucks, cars d… https://t.co/6FqgfMtkyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[something must be in the air in 2019 cause everyones just been showing their true colors left and right 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shinedown fabulous show last night in Fayetteville, North Carolina !! https://t.co/bYDcx98UtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE the tag words at the end of the Ice Pick's Pies article!  Hahah!! https://t.co/t5ljIEzGPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingswift79 @OldManSwiftie @tarahlovestay @taysavedsonia @swiftside13 @noahlevy13 @Starlight_Manna @LucieJobson… https://t.co/CKWgXMFlF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back_daddys @LoriMichaelFl Kushner and Trump have a hand in Kashohhi's murder. They should be indicted for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goallll!!! #25 Maddie Harris scores the first Lady Tiger goal of the night, with an assist from #11 Rachel Ramm. ⚽️… https://t.co/nHhfiwSr3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bali Days and Bali Nights | Get a Trip for Two and a Pair of Watches https://t.co/68xfti97nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got to enjoy paradise these last few days to celebrate two close friends saying "I do!" It was absolutely gorgeo… https://t.co/nTKthWpnK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am:      ⚪️ single      ⚪️ taken      🔘 Just tryna have fun with my girls]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 #MakingAManager #ifunny #TheOffice #MakingAMurderer https://t.co/rE6ymRuQ0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my free chance to win $150 in points. Tons of wins here! https://t.co/6v5j7TpNsp #instantwingame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferbourn Haha, no I think it is scraping windshield wipers on ice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youcantdohockey I! Cannot! Handle this! I’m still thinking about this and Professor Kelly is tryna explain foreche… https://t.co/2etRjMSdmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchwartzApprovd Mom's on point again!!❤❤ #ArrowTextsFromMom #Arrow #Olicity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lashmeupzo on ig!🤩 check out my promo pricing, dm for availability!!🦋 https://t.co/fZvqF8WyDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hangout with Samantha it’s more clear why we’re friends 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alabama_amle Hi, I’m Harriette and I love middle school!  I’m a middle school administrator (K-8:  best of both wo… https://t.co/xyOHhd3TZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @LadyJustice1111 @freddysuperlano Praising Adam Schiff to keep up the good work?  We know who u work for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me lmao Y’all need health to even have any of the other things. Mensos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for this snowday to have made my one-woman Cohen Watch Party possible! 🥳 #CohenDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savagesare_ Ya do it!! That’s what I did with my midterm and final and I still got an A. I took him over a 6 week… https://t.co/9uBuuEfzBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saschipman @chrislhayes I thought the same thing.  He had to come by and get his hi-fives for last nights threat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Underrated_Dom @beels @ProudResister @kylegriffin1 @PalmerReport @travisakers @Alyssa_Milano @krassenstein… https://t.co/sU0mwExHf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening NOW! Amazing Materials for You by Amy Dickson on Teachers Pay Teachers  https://t.co/YawIatR5Bv https://t.co/o4tEN68PPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo just heard the news about Nacho @AndyTelleria . A little bummed out —&gt; Crying at the gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[hot take: rachel shoulda ended up with joey bc ross is a shitty person and shouldve ended up alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruthhill74backu @MKL712 @hallmarkmovie @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott Exactly, Ruth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You don’t have to raise your voice to communicate” “You don’t have to raise your voice to communicate” “You don’t… https://t.co/4R1gPAupjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Yes my question is why does is that person in the back of this totally “not photos… https://t.co/w6NKFj7GWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[⬅️ booty day!! 🍑🦵🏽💪🏽💋 . .  #week8 #bootydays #tiuloveyourbody #tiu #tiufa #mondaymotivation #mondaze #bootyfull… https://t.co/qcS0rRdM5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google Home's Assistant could one day know your mood. Take that, Alexa https://t.co/x2aSp24xY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_L_ecrit @glaad @ShadowhuntersTV 😫😫😫😫 he's ruthless https://t.co/yTZioVGwaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeggyCallahan  Gotcha Peggy! Thanks good woman. ✔ So sorry it took so long, spring cleaning LOL. 🌴😎🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @senatemajldr What? It was crickets out of the Republicans when you found out....]]></document></documents></author>