<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RockyTopSkiBum @beckyjlomax @publiclandlvr @MattsRoadTrip @RoadtripC @traveling1223 @brownpeoplecamp @publichands… https://t.co/ZRGtotH088]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW AVAILABLE FOR BOOKING!  We're really out here building an empire from nothing! Listen how the crowds singing al… https://t.co/iLNHqLcFad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 15 ESSEX DR #Milford #CT  #realestate https://t.co/x0lNlOBnhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ariesgirl401 @AngrierWHStaff What I should have said is that I'm having trouble understanding why Stone wasn't imm… https://t.co/G7GyqNL0lB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This diver had a dry erase board and answered questions with the audience #diving #aquarium #tampa @ Clearwater, Fl… https://t.co/Z8bat3vCSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATH_0522 @AOC I also buy all of my own classroom supplies. Sometimes I also buy my students classroom supplies if… https://t.co/Uwlms7bjzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My eight-year-old self picked one hell of a role model. Sending all my thanks to her tonight. And to god for creati… https://t.co/qs7yoK8KYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfchronicle @hknightsf @EvanSernoffsky Good on Gonzales for speaking up about the leaked reports. Some of that ini… https://t.co/xIerBgf5wx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJessLyfe It's happened to me alot. I think if we hear any given language enough, we understand it better than w… https://t.co/LsT97O2t3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treating me to a beer and a brownie! #daytonlovesbeer (@ The @BarrelHouseTap in Dayton, OH) https://t.co/dTD5SiJgbS https://t.co/uANL3SUlH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathryn_riman @htubbscooley_RN It is good to a point but then like most Cousteau courses goes from detailed and wa… https://t.co/YfQCABFddA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics What does he have to do actually shoot somebody on 5th Ave?  These so called Republicans are a twisted bunch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trey enjoys screaming over video games all night as if we don’t have neighbors. We are going to be the most hated p… https://t.co/671O1s7l2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReJeanneDSmith God is your strength right now..... Lean and depend on him and him alone!!!❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking coffee while driving and trying to avoid all the potholes should qualify as an extreme sport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truly striking graphics but as always it's the great storytelling that dominates]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Sharenado day!  Love seeing all those amazing projects! #geniushour #studentvoice   Brookies rock!@lifelegeros https://t.co/6OmF5xneMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thacoachmike I know you’re an avid reader. What’s your advice on the next book I should read?]]></document><document><![CDATA[psa: victoria is also a dirty toe sucker let this be known to the public i shall not be shamed https://t.co/roQ4nLULPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter Maybe so, but he still said otherwise in public. It doesn’t matter what he thinks in private.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davechannel come on Dave Channel, what are you doing to get your original shows aired in the US? I can’t take the… https://t.co/hd6w10UZBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misspunk63 @survrad @Josearoni10 @ScottSm06816011 @dunbdav @Sequencer16 @SealeyGerald @ImabitcSumtimes @CaliRN619… https://t.co/jbN2cXm6QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If one does not know to which port one is sailing, no wind is favorable.” -Seneca #WiththeWind #DueNorth… https://t.co/RvL7OdWIgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommagrizzly74 @Steelerschic85 @sara_hemminger @kamcam65 @Jen_C_ @DemTeaParty2020 @CajunBlueAZ1 @Mookyluv3… https://t.co/NVV5NuPEzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good turnout tonight at Spotter Class in Charleston MO.  @NWSPaducah @wxmanmeffert https://t.co/1lAiSXAjlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Way2gosassy @Monroesmydog It will be interesting to see what the average number of dogs at finish is this year.… https://t.co/Es1PhaUwdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TherapyChicken @Frank_Kitten We welcome all our new friends to PAWS and can’t wait to make you our Bunny Besties! https://t.co/HWSGxKuz3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenrottier @ParkerMolloy @DrSamiSchalk @slooterman @SFdirewolf @AspieHuman Past my bedtime now, but I’ll have a… https://t.co/2lQY8Wp671]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes These are not North Korean women. They’re Vietnamese even though they’re waving the N. Korean flag. Notice… https://t.co/JTfq5d1Adp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Koe is in 5 days and that means i need to find 5 hunnies at the concert 🤪😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprising,my complaints don't seem to get any responses as https://t.co/CZkalboY2r I actually got a call from… https://t.co/hQtqR7R4AV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect. @Jim_Jordan is a liar and he looked the other way when young men were being sexually assaulted.  Perfect f… https://t.co/tzZjxo4aW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caroline is balancing a mini rubber ducky on her head at after hours.... to save the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubCarson @CrankyClair @Senturion @REDBLACKS Lol You're such a fucking shit disturber]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i don’t marry someone who’s down to do painfully cute, corny stuff like this we’ll just have to compromise and d… https://t.co/b0eq7GSgYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahmariexx_ Update I used the target-brand crest strips because I’m boujie on a budget and must say just took t… https://t.co/xuzkNQMjZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just met Bruce Willis and Masa Takayama all in one day are you literally kidding me right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘High when I stroll//Not even leaving foot prints in the snow ‘ https://t.co/UDjjjzJ8oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar retweets post blasting Meghan McCain for 'faux outrage' in response to Omar's remarks on Israel https://t.co/tPZ91rj92e #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keepingupwgab Hell yeah lmao. Speak your mind sis. If you don’t it’s just gonna get more annoying &amp; you’re gonna snap one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulObrienUSA @coolhandjux @DineshDSouza Blame everybody else for your bad behavior too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anna_armao @c_bright28 @joanna_rebitski I mean that all sounds delicious so no judgement here 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although this week is FULL I am honored to be in the presence such outstanding students, doing outstanding things,… https://t.co/BNBnBT5Lzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cucuta, Colombia -- U.S. Sen. Marco Rubio visited a border staging point for U.S. aid to Venezuela on Sunday and wa… https://t.co/vJiGSvqVTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriciaglane @ameliabrowntale Yeah....@Queenofgeeks mentioned Tinyeye on this thread...I’d never heard of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder She is as mean as her husband. Don’t be fooled by the packaging]]></document><document><![CDATA[grocery shopping at Trader Joe’s on a Sunday evening is personal hell yet you can catch me here every week 6:30 on the dot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin Probably not, because it shows earned credit for a failed course. The grades seem hauntingly accurate, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal Wings  Make good today From your broken of yesterday Hug the universe And it will hug u back Fly with y… https://t.co/3uW5fbSwcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaseyChronisTV ! At the circus and joining the act!@fox6now https://t.co/XcKtZL8g7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 Jump Street Begins Production - Principal photography began September 28th, 2013 on Columbia Pictures’ and... https://t.co/d2bBFpRQq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louisville! I’m playing at @GoodwoodBrewing downtown tonight 8-10. No cover. #livemusic #louisvillemusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 52 of Stay in Touch is posted https://t.co/RNK6MwJWfm  Getting help The… https://t.co/GwKQ9SrQHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever is saying I left Ferris because I got a DUI.... IM LAUGHING MY ASS OFF. 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - @sfmoma in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/sXiNZVHNru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersCanes305 @WPLGLocal10 Thank you, it will be a warm one! No matter what have fun 👍😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TilnishaRosser huge thanks for capturing the beauty of parental engagement #DSEMissionPossible @hpchief @anneladd… https://t.co/PxsS0FmGBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so close w my Twitter friends that I don’t even really care when they come into town]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so you cute, but you are no where near me...keep trying though. It’s entertaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[I flipped and got a cramp on my right but cheek😂 currently can’t move 🤘🏻 #parkour #Muslim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerinxHall was well represented today at the @nhdmo Regional Competition. We had 7 students total compete. 4 stude… https://t.co/6Hevg4qUes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clever stuff in here! — 25 HACKS YOU'D WISH YOU'D KNOWN SOONER https://t.co/SLoYvwyiOi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OscarRunnerUp @msamandaspears @MalDaley @KarenMPeterson @AwardsDaily @TomiLaffly @joyceeng61 @KusReporter @jazzt… https://t.co/rhaz16C53M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for me!! COPPERTOP!! Let’s not forget I’M GETTING SHOELESS JOE JACKSON INTO THE HALL OF FAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you didn’t grow up quoting Austin Powers GoldMember and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really important report by @EdBuild This is especially concerning but not surprising 👉🏾 “For every student enrolled… https://t.co/1ybvbAhmHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Senate Candidate’s Natalie Rivera and Tricia Flanagan https://t.co/Ime8FsAjjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from vinestmarket  -  Swirling like memories or dreams yet to come  ___  https://t.co/Wbp1fr4sYb will be j… https://t.co/angcegF2J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkiwicks How funny, I’m reading it too. Signed up to about 1000 runs as a result. Dude is so cool but my God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineCOTW Exactly. Especially poor women who have limited opportunities. It's just a cruel policy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first night of my first True/False summed up in two images. https://t.co/5Ek99tXDHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only I had a dollar for every time I hit “remind me tomorrow” for my Mac updates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebizarch @essenviews I proofread repeatedly. I have th same problem. I'm convinced Autocorrupt just likes messing… https://t.co/I1AzUXD5Ff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both teams in the bonus and the free throws will begin with K.K. Bransford at the line for MND. The GGCL's leading… https://t.co/niPa0yEWwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lavo323 @steph93065 @SteveKEspinoza2 Yeah, its certainly a slap in the face for people who came legally. But I am… https://t.co/hNeLgr4lgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Krock1057 @GregBall75 @TheRealSideshow To clarify, the section is about some of the best new indie artists in 🇨🇦 .… https://t.co/zGEXrKE5c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[DON’T FORGET! If you are coming to tmr nights boys 🏀 playoff game (and you all should be!) it is a NHIAA event. So… https://t.co/RRO2ZssdAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheValuesVoter You would think.   But then I've been told that abstinence is the only moral choice for those of mo… https://t.co/jw9AHOnkdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showed Aaron my new phone background. He said it looked depressing and yet beautiful. And if that doesn’t sum up my… https://t.co/IFqJUKWtDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un futur membre de la French Mafia du Rouge et Noir : Nicolas Boulay a signé un contrat d’un an à Ottawa après 6 saisons à Montréal #LCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before we go out today we will critique. #phototour2019 #acelatosu @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/iE6OwImoYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dozens of headstones vandalized in historic South Fulton cemetery https://t.co/jC4AwPdZqr https://t.co/A4u4hhMS8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shulmanshines @FairviewES_NC @UCPS_MonroeNC @AGHoulihan @judydteach4 @Renee_McKinnon1 @KellySThomas 😂🤣😂 #IGotYourBack 💜💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A mature Christian sees Christ in everything and everyone else. “ - Richard Rohr. @RichardRohrOFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Caltrain commuter trains need to be longer, not shorter.  #secondstop #noseats #commute #safe? @CaltrainStatus https://t.co/12DV022Hf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re not educated politically, DO IT! Cause there’s currently old white men in Congress who are ruining the ch… https://t.co/SUG4BdCJsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoapDigest @YRInsider @MelodyThomasSco @YandR_CBS Kudos to the writer of this episode! I am a fan from day one and… https://t.co/Li2zWV5qwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening today! 1-3pm Horticultural Heroes  https://t.co/OejDgKQ7AJ https://t.co/VqkpwNylIU  #trompeloeil… https://t.co/yabvvZDoNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Durante Conferência Global sobre Crise Humanitária na #Venezuela, representantes de @jguaido anunciaram que doações… https://t.co/xCO9gGjkGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who didn’t sleep well and now has to go to go teach in a 3rd grade class where all but two students speak a d… https://t.co/m4K8mN3tT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @julianzelizer @CNNOpinion A lot of people think that especially after he went abroad and called thw #US an embarrassment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKlemens the amount of eyelashes and eyebrow hairs has me PEEING, CHRIS ARE YOU OKAY LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shayyy___ Happened to me once and I thought I could get with the shits and it happened and I was like https://t.co/pHgMklOKtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnLeenerts thank you for following me back! https://t.co/jFaSDwRBaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace Hands down the best.   Nichole gets better every day.  For me, The Eleventh Hour and Nichole are the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all #accountants a great first day at #QBconnect London!!  I suspect that accounting is more fancy in Londo… https://t.co/uTRXDP7dB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what had happened was: after that amazing win, we hung around to thank our players and just as I told… https://t.co/UfbKjNgb2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAX team welcomes the CSS Team! Partners in positive customer service solutions! Thanks to SOC @Maggie_Ronan and… https://t.co/d1D7hZI3no]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother played the piano for 40+ years @EbenezerUMC in TN. I have a copy of many UM Hymnals she used. 🎼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missusbrian Nah, people who spread peace don't attack others. Start on yourself.]]></document></documents></author>