<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Comey There will be so much healing when you are sentenced to prison. McCabe is throwing you and Rosenstein under… https://t.co/7jTppt13dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachie_smiley Shoot me an email if you don’t mind. Wife and I heading out of town for a few days. D.Saur@chatham.edu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun view for Friday morning! #TucsonSnow #TucsonWX #FridayFunday https://t.co/UI8uy8UM8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews The DNC had just cause. Fox News isn’t a news org. It’s your propaganda arm; like RT is f… https://t.co/byGrIiKDG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonHerFFB @bateking_ With his money and friends in high places he will not suffer any consequences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing I have 4 more months of college is definitely what gets me through it 🙌🏻🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: @UW_MBB defeats Utah 62-45. The #Huskies remain undefeated at home.   #GALLERY: https://t.co/d8CRB1heOB… https://t.co/k5ILPbAi7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santana - Put Your Lights On ft. Everlast (Official Video) https://t.co/hriJbPi7sx via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the backyard oasis: a new goal for 2019: 100 Incredible Projects By DIYers Like You https://t.co/zYGoGMrC5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNCLRCOMusic @dutchiedino @wearestorytime @ShadyParkTempe Haha ya its just adding grain onto the photo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @HallieJackson What's the "very sad thing?" Is trump "sad" that the coastguard was caught???]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a joy to have former @chbcdc pastor @TripLee back with us, preaching this AM on Romans 6, new life! Do you nee… https://t.co/ljEhmPcdnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shathiHoneymony @BWGovernment I know I'm worth at least 5 times that much..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L_Flores19 @TigresOficial @Rayados Él no jugó la Interliga. 🙊 y el 6-2 pues era la segunda fecha del torneo. Dolió… https://t.co/yxH8IQxvce]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Sacramento, CA, check out this job: https://t.co/9gxl4yVQoU #Engineering]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year where brunettes Iike to spice it up for the spring. Ombré highlights using uberliss glaze an… https://t.co/HpxhYYohco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate my entire 10oz Ribeye Side of Ribs. with green beans and a baked potato at @texasroadhouse this is the mos… https://t.co/2FsYsttnr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 Insanity. Current mayor of the town I grew up in just N of Austin. Looks like a cartoon character, but a republic… https://t.co/4G5g35HYjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherLarimer @Alyssa_Milano I'm not running for office. But if I was Venezuela would pay for the wall. We could s… https://t.co/5uttI5m8nP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tart sourness. - Drinking a Pineapple Sherbet by @whistlepunkbeer at @whistlepunkbeer  — https://t.co/654QkKKTXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulKinsman @975krock @NLFolkFestival @nlnoise_ @Indie_Country @americanaUK @americanaroots @JLaC975… https://t.co/2u2vACGzWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealroytovar @HuntsmanAbby Tell that to Mitch "Make Obama a one-term president" McConnell. Obama and Hillary Cl… https://t.co/f8S4CHy8NS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLoeSeattle There was a group during the big snow last month! Talk about trial by fire!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanPlayfair hey buddy, question for ya since I’m a hockey player from Arizona...in Senior A hockey in Canada lik… https://t.co/AtxfK3Kjyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si eres antiimperialista y anti Trump no puedes apoyar este titere.!! https://t.co/7X3QF9512N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye has NEVER changed yall been calling him crazy for years Taylor Swift George Bush Yeezus And then appreciate h… https://t.co/j7aglSbQ5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!!! anniezigman was PHENOMENAL at her senior showcase this afternoon! Annie, so proud of all your hard work! Hon… https://t.co/MPF3z6xRTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_hippiequeen @DoorDash Pretty much! We're in 77070 and they are fast and the food is hot! My work is 77024 and… https://t.co/qoyHsb5Bef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard Turn on notifications! Retweet! Donate even $1 to https://t.co/MzdPrLDJ65 #retweet #Tulsi2020 https://t.co/hpWYCiTvTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[OECD will follow Canadian proceedings addressing allegations of political interference in foreign bribery prosecuti… https://t.co/BwZxZs0S54]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amazing @CulverCityGov Vice Mayor @M_Sahli_Wells shared a fun fact: the movie “Singing in the Rain” was filmed… https://t.co/J9pqdfqoDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go Jacks!!!!! #AxeEm #SFA #TheRivalryIsReal https://t.co/DmP8CIURYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s been 10 years. Scary. I remember that day in ‘09 and how boring I thought Twitter was https://t.co/p4z60XlXSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPN_Action @WWE_MandyRose @WWEAsuka Hey my name is Curtis good morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot_Musket @mdrache @molratty @AOC They are going to primary the hell out of @AOC. And I think they’ll win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariastephanos Please be careful if driving in the snow tonight or tomorrow morning have a nice weekend Maria]]></document><document><![CDATA[$300 million guaranteed contract to play #mlb and you want to play football...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #WeWantNCAAFootball on @tyltsports. It’s the best video game! https://t.co/UiW3NrUo1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if you could start from scratch regulating ride-hail? Vancouver thinking creatively about dynamic fees based o… https://t.co/d807JvIUD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomi Lahren goes behind the scenes with the Border Patrol  https://t.co/OQ0zIZtYIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticiAmerica Este tipo Villanueva,esta peor que Maduro..Ahora Vizcarra y su gobierno calcula, las lluvias..!! Y V… https://t.co/T8AQ5tj423]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlassJoeJP Actually if what @CraigHoffman said on #CDVTW is true and they are still in on Rosen, it's a great move… https://t.co/pCjWTB0plb]]></document><document><![CDATA[لن تنضج إلا بعد أن تشعر أن لديك الكثير من الكلام, ولكنك لست بحاجة إلى أن تخبر بهِ أحداً. .  جبران خليل جبران]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dolphins host $1,000-a-head fundraiser for hometown mayor who is favored to be the Miami Gardens county commissione… https://t.co/k6XOcSnm1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God the father of Abraham Isaac and Jacob I come to you to say thank you for your Mercy and your Grace and you… https://t.co/ETUo7BRbXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[OSU coach Wayne Tinkle watches his guys warm up from the student section. https://t.co/bdf0JvEFaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the release of our 2019 Football Schedule pick your favorite option as wallpaper for your phone!… https://t.co/dGR468vBqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the hell gets off on this, this is fucking disgusting human behavior]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonewman2014 Hahaha haven't used black planet in years...I don't think my account still works...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost the 3rd month of the year. How y’all “New years resolutions” going??🤔😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil morning sweat before I get this Thursday goin. What are you gunna do today to #BeGreat ?! https://t.co/ntsjg7j0AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karic_Jones @GrizzTalkOU The idea that UDM doesn't have money is incredibly silly Karic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at McCarran International Airport - @lasairport in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/ewYIefzNWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen_B_Smlth @Cianaf But Cian did. And he literally just said, if he gets an accurate target hes gonna catch it… https://t.co/f0fYlYblcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love details.  I spend hours and hours looking for small accessories and extra touches that I can include in room… https://t.co/cgDLC1tFQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Motivation!!!   #simple #monday #motivation #🔑 #mindset #grateful #hardwork #realtor #realestate… https://t.co/e3AIvbt1As]]></document><document><![CDATA[Group projects second semester of senior year are a whole new level of painful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrodoyle @stormpics Yes. The tornado also did a loop right there at telephone and 4th. Nothing survived in that sp… https://t.co/Z4cxdaL0Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guide to the major megaprojects transforming New York City https://t.co/MZLORGGaI7 via @CurbedNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hans, I love that you lead by example and speak truth, love, and kindness to so many people around you!  This is ab… https://t.co/YCMFgNX31g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClimaPeruMundo Veremos como sale el Sondaje, minimo isotermal en capa de contacto estimo yo..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney This is why civilizations fall... https://t.co/ZfzWYvsxw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonHelp @amazon   This isn’t the first time that your delivery service has done this https://t.co/5a1JA6X4SG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two great awards and two great guys who helped make it happen! @ Nashville Music City Center https://t.co/0uYlyTuNo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day ❤️❤️ #valentines #happyvalentinesday #happyvalentines #happyvalentine @ Joe Cross "The King of… https://t.co/BPO3jA7ofs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you didn’t drink enough water out of the hose when you were a kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctorbuttons @IndianaOhmz @JBadass408 @forthemasses @badibulgator @LaikaAndYuri @GerbusJames @keigh_see… https://t.co/LDKCqPSTyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@el_gmac73 @Hat_Tweets @GMaclagan @SquatchoSpotti1 @mke59fifty @hatsgamestrains @Muzixndmd @FiddySicks @JJHoserHOTD… https://t.co/KFGSpR92kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_wawrow Keith Moon and John Entwistle aren’t  walking through that door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cougars win 61-40, advance to D2/4 Class 6A final against Scranton or Williamsport next Saturday night at Mohegan Sun Arena]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairwayFairholm People need to keep bringing this up like Kucher's caddie issue. Only then will the #PGATour start… https://t.co/sxh4SLVRhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna say a quick thanks to all of our police officer out there and people serving or have served. They are th… https://t.co/Ts8xkgqrPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Mr Paul,you sir work for those of us,in the beautiful state of Kentucky,You should be talking to us first… https://t.co/ITVelSQgaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danieltobin The unemployed were finished off by Net Neutrality repeal? That would 'splain the current jobs numbers, I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody:  me: im so broke, did a magician make my money disappear or sum?????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doll eyes 👀  . . . . .  #modellife #malemodels #modelling #mkexplore #shotzdelight #rsa_streetview #mychicagopix… https://t.co/Y7oCxr4Zua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinLyman @VansWarpedTour But can I gamble in Atlantic City with you if I fly in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, looks like there’s a lot of outgoing freight/boxes this afternoon! Sorry Karon lol. This was inside the loadin… https://t.co/o2EvHziMra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivyfikes @itstammytee Everyone check out https://t.co/kQrAaaaFRo for all your golden letter balloon needs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cutty_6 At least your teams tank properly. I guess the Bulls think their contenders now and the Blackhawks, well,… https://t.co/mnTe5vEGnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEChampions Great I been hoping he get a better move set just started working him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilverRainbow @iceland @WestIceland @lonelyplanet @ThePhotoHour @StormHourMark @StormHour @SnowHour… https://t.co/KjeLZNDdX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan once again shut up. No one has seen the Mueller report.  Mueller is the one looking into trump and Russia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcenters I’m exactly opposite. Have Netflix. Don’t have Prime or Hulu and don’t want them.   Tons of stuff on my N… https://t.co/JiGZX3SfWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone hmu first for once?😂 I feel like if I didn’t make plans with people then I’d never get outta the house.. smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[People recording themselves doing “acts of kindness” makes me cringe so hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSWALDORIOSM @DavidAl90 @NellyMaceda @Mx_Diputados @lopezobrador_ Sweet! https://t.co/WI8ZaU0yUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CabasalEmmanuel @iamdavidfearme @ChildRiceNice If you ever come to Bible Study... 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Urunderarrest I'm sorry Dane, it didn't come across as one. But I get that now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@studio326girl @RealJamesWoods @RepAOC Stunning look on this very attractive Marxist! Be kind with the subtitle, it… https://t.co/1jnpl09njg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanlawler Yup. I’ve tried pitching this valuable service after seeing just the worst notes possible. It’s not icing, it’s the cake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phDusher @CallMeMoprah We see the same in Special education services and concepts of “multicultural” literature. S… https://t.co/GY1VmZIxow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD @realDonaldTrump Please stop trying to play politics with an entire religion. You’re better than this… https://t.co/vlPdoy4bSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Chicago, New York, St Louis planned parenthood only in black prominent neighborhoods. They are des… https://t.co/6lmtLBN0wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis Would you care to make a wager on that?  We can have PayPal hold the money until Trump and I win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overtime. @IndyMetBball 47 @TpKnights 47. Met holds for last shot and misses. @indsportstalk @indyhsscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabe_TFB The dog was actually scratching up my back so my form was not on point. Sorry 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely last time telling this bitch happy birthday.......acknowledge me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc @ReporterPhoenix @LifeOnTheBeach7 @kennethfawalter @Catlady628 @nl_misstanden @GaiLuronNicky @ivanarijs… https://t.co/G3mfpHJxVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Werwolfram @AMNH Not sure it could doff a cap with those arms, though.]]></document></documents></author>