<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@requiaopmdb @guiodias Uma foto sentada sobre dinheiro séria melhor? 2.9milhoes pagos ao senhor,lembra conta pra nó… https://t.co/uzYKB1ylHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you going to scheme up. When you meet with Kim Kong Un. And when it comes out you will of course dey it. Y… https://t.co/Ih2EjVZtsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye West to invest $1M in Avalon Regal Theater, owner says https://t.co/DiQ9bqY5AW via @suntimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing my little bag of tricks. Love you, Honeybee! XoXo ♥️♥️♥️♥️ #bagboy #babysean #ififitsisits @ La Habra, Cali… https://t.co/hkn1Q0QxEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is wrong with the black race, all we see is black faces when crimes are committed.🧠]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son is a FAN, it has a dynamic young WOC host, and it’s evidence-based while being FUN. New Netflix… https://t.co/cmBPXfSp4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doug Byrne with a pin in the first round! @ The Schottenstein Center https://t.co/90CqgMrieq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been long enough-with no trial-even traitors get a trial.She could get time served from a judge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas Oh crap I missed it 🙄, did she talk about you??? #BeBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends If Pelosi, Omar, Harris &amp; AOC are the future of the Democratic party and America....God help us all🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fri Feb 22nd 7:30pm I’m on bass with Alpha Dog Blues At Tanger Kabob House Cafe  5735 Telegraph Rd Alexandria, VA… https://t.co/Fp3LdbIzyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been on my own shit. I’m growing and transcending every day and i’m worrying bout myself till someone comes around🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clydetombaugh @Hank_Venture @kevinandbean @thekevinryder @kroqkom @kroqbeermug @DJOmarKhan @KroqChip Wednesday was… https://t.co/bfwyqHWJ5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 11th #dool #days  NBC spoilers  Fri Mar 15th  @MrRobertScott @Tyler2929… https://t.co/s6jY7agAe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y   X    Q  No dejar  Q todos Los millones  se quedan  en Mexico  Y no al extranjero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennymofodavis @TopherBeard15 Well that took a turn. https://t.co/6SGOH32nqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Allow your pain to cleanse you and burn away what needs to die.”  ― Bryant McGill  . . . . . #retreatyourself… https://t.co/4BctgZ6k0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stage view from LAST year’s Sitzprobe. Always such a thrill.  #FaustDC #operalife #choristerlife #joyofsinging @ Th… https://t.co/fT3d3YpnOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We were trying to protest the war,” John Tinker said. “We weren’t really seeking to set a First Amendment preceden… https://t.co/LMtDKYBA65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman "we stand for treating people -- even the most vulnerable, a brand-new baby -- with the dignity… https://t.co/ltjsdD4jo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totalmente, yo no dormí pensando en mi familia allá, mis hijos que aun están allá!!! Mi impotencia es grande!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chouinardphoto Happy birthday! Hope you spend it doing things that bring you joy🎂🎉✌🏽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we fight to pass the #NYHealthAct in NYS for a single payer system, we must protect those who are uninsured.… https://t.co/EGrXIUQDw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/2lrjTt8den]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExposingLibsBS @fedagentmark She is an attention seeking has been, ignore her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss Glenda made new special sand for us 😍😍We love it https://t.co/7fkc2ihMJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton Wish I could get to your new Ole Red Wednesday, maybe Saturday, have surgery Friday #SoExcited… https://t.co/lcS4hU3nna]]></document><document><![CDATA[I probably still have this ancient shirt somewhere. I wonder if Taylor Nicole Dean has a PO Box I could send it to… https://t.co/gvxC0Qy2UZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I think it was only one time. But I feel so weak and my throat hurts and my stomach ache only disappeared when I was sleeping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aradinsc @Frankly_Emily @jessicaverdi @zaceubank @AlizaPearl @Hyper_RPG NO.  ONE. EXPECTED. THE. (sexy) CENTAUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redhotdealer Yeah the contestants were all kind of equal until he brought out the secret weapon. 😂😂😂😂😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duff admitting he has never seen an episode of Cake Boss is savage. Like, he knew he was gonna face off against Bud… https://t.co/aGlDmHOEZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be the hardest ball I’ve ever hit. Stayed back on a curve ball and got one.  Against the wind too. Fences 250… https://t.co/tXq6xT4ile]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some classic sh!t right here: Man angry his photo was used to prove all hipsters look alike — then learns it wasn't… https://t.co/22YciuoS8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jean_Marbella @gussent Same! HS counselor said local state university pretty much accepted everyone from our magne… https://t.co/ELxKCnhRar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WWEChamber #EliminationChamber prediction? @TrueKofi! https://t.co/dX3D5Nltf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SnowDay in Londonderry NH #Orchards #orarerhey? #urbansprawl #NHlandscape #NHwinter @ Londonderry, New Hampshire https://t.co/haA09m7TlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been sitting at the salon for over four hours ✂️ I remember now why I don't get my hair done often. I have too much… https://t.co/pxOBhd9USg]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Elon if those 3 tweets about @Tesla prepare carefully bc SEC will consider any public announcement you make abou… https://t.co/i1zbZPwse8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Think ya got enough material for a number 2???  **Exits stage left** https://t.co/byeSX5uzTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida es una chinga, si no chingas, te chingan y si te chingan, ya te chingaste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileighNelson just hung up the phone without saying I love you soooo Holly is big mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today you are you! That is truer than true! There is no one alive who is you-er than you! #DrSeussDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeltcalvert @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @GOP @SpeakerPelosi @HouseDems @SenateDems I forgot about your inab… https://t.co/zsODkMscu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BadVictorianist Oh. My. Gah. I can sing every word to every single Jim Croce song. Time in a Bottle? Best. Song. E… https://t.co/EWYCGMvVnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO You all do know you sound like a bunch of babies to President Trumps adult.  You should climb down out of… https://t.co/HCg0pHtsfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book displays are ready for Women’s History Month #WomensHistoryMonth #FCPS #weneeddiversebooks https://t.co/Rz1F5hB0DH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaydreamDrea my coworker had to leave work early the other cuz “his mom got fired and he needed to go help clean h… https://t.co/DI6L8Rd5wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticusSarah @politicususa At least they can probably sell them to help with the costs that FEMA and insurance won't cover.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the only one waiting outside of cvs so they can open so I can get my prescription]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerriweatherSun @sharon_elle @ElizabethPand11 @EkbMary @SonyaBaker2 @MustangRehab @CyntWhite @Blueequus775… https://t.co/9Vmqt2Rs5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruno le acaba de cantar unos tiros a un gato ajhshdjsjsjsja estoy orgullosa de mijo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Forget quirkiness and warmth and material commitment, boring shiny boxes are where it’s at!” #architecture]]></document><document><![CDATA[New model data suggests snow ❄️ after 9PM through about 12AM from Hale to Chilton to Chambers counties.  Something… https://t.co/rbEKiqTIIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate to see grown men afraid of their own shadow. Tell me friend...do u also sleep with the closet door closed? G… https://t.co/9m1BlKdbdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just scrolling through my tweets and dang I really need to proofread better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running for office not an excuse to be a racist.   Sad that @MarkMeadows thinks it does.   Also pathetic he thinks… https://t.co/dKhT4xOBd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[War is not the answer- ever. Blessed are the peacemakers!☮️ #PakistanStrikesBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ridingwithc @realDonaldTrump @MichaelCohen212 Oops your right.  I think we need to create a calendar on Twitter fo… https://t.co/quZJjxyA7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a little experiment. I scrolled through the pages of some prominent #CPC MPs. I discovered that the pictures… https://t.co/JhgL2dKeJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for day 2 at #TFDevSummit! @greenexecutive kicking off with the Lightning Talks. Sitting next to @inureyes… https://t.co/8RQSeiiqvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a pleasure to host @latriceroyale  join us for the season finale of All Stars 4 this Friday at 8pm… https://t.co/E23FGUVMtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rather be straight with someone I love and care about than passive, if you think I’m being passive aggressive with… https://t.co/yiMD2HbC0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only one more day till my Christmas present to my family... @Shinedown @MoheganSun is happening! Can’t wait to take… https://t.co/s3BTPuJN5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 mins til @NBCGoodGirls west coast season premiere!!! I can’t take the anticipation! #excited https://t.co/3w03vV4RLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just getting off work from a 12hr shift and my baby love gave me a rose for Valentine's Day thanks my love you know… https://t.co/Fv0n3Riyup]]></document><document><![CDATA[carm3n05 and I starting a Harry Potter marathon!!!  Getting ready  for Orlando!!! @ Oceanside, California https://t.co/fjmvvvrv4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put money on it shannon gonna throw up tonight or gts before everybody else😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatGirlSera @matunos @drdina1 @DonCheadle I don’t think I’ve ever heard a woman think that trans people were oppr… https://t.co/SCyZkG9Ndv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotorRacingLLC @MatthewTodd04 @NickBromberg I THINK IT STINK THAT BUSH IS RACEN IN THE TRUCK AND XFINITY  .ITS LIK… https://t.co/ikthN1wgOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brettbarker Or Peanut Butter Patties and a @dietpepsi #devilsadvocate 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homosexual  in the church is the root of this horrible  state the church is in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHOBHMeanGirls #RHOBH seriously I'm getting called a #bully because I'm standing up for @LisaVanderpump . Are you kidding me😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tiinaaa97 Nah I think you can do the first month free probs but then you pay. Do you have Spotify? Cause the ice project is on Spotify too]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m like — 3.3 million viewers turned down the trailer — #backfiretohbo @HBO — don’t let your channel fail..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocket alum in Happy Valley! welcome home to PA! @SGSchoolNews @KellyBrooks6 @EliJBrooks https://t.co/fFgUThoyGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy anniversary to the love of my life... xoxo #braddybunch @ The Diplomat Beach Resort https://t.co/gjJtuTW5KR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrgustafsonfhs Congrats!!!  p.s. Can I get a full picture of you on the Iron Throne???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPS pretty sad when you call three times because your package is to be delivered today 2/14 and the driver even co… https://t.co/Vdmt4Oznhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all about the $$$$$$$ Trump only cares about the $$$$$$ How much is Trump enriching himself with his policies?… https://t.co/I2HRtrzmQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Agents should be required to send out their RFPs by November 1st and decisions made no later than January 15th… https://t.co/6vkPyRgkav]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicoJR16 @chorizy @_AlohaMrHand @MrDelicious13 It's all so good.  . I have a frozen garlic turkey breast that you… https://t.co/7h3X7BmcBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toe431 We use the song Chicken Fat! Really old school but a great beat for kids to follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unsung_Gamer Yeah I mean it just pushes this up the priority list. We did want to work on extending the front yard… https://t.co/ZKo9E3bv5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @voxdotcom He looks untrustworthy to me - very suspect. https://t.co/sMVeEQdg7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we planned our weather reports and practiced with a friend. We selected the weather, a location, told the tem… https://t.co/un1qun44A5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let spring break commence with a friendly Ss vs. teachers basketball 🏀 game. We still undefeated. Sorry not sorry k… https://t.co/eoWfGbJb8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent more than 15 years catering for House and Senate leadership and got to see them at their best, worst, and m… https://t.co/1Ui4xIsWcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have such a bad headache and if these people laugh one more time i stg]]></document><document><![CDATA[See. I don’t take a long time to get ready. I can get dressed, do hair and make up in 20 minutes.....and then there… https://t.co/QmhRQecRxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve all known the infrastructures through out the country is horrible, yet building a wall is the nation emergenc… https://t.co/mgx1vRjpaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women's History Month! _  I am proud to invite you to "UNFILTERED: An Unapologetic Conversation On Masculinit… https://t.co/QLwGSH8aMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is why people who don’t turn off their brights while passing me are the trash of human existence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Kettu by @Rhinegeist at @brewdogusa — https://t.co/V3Ze84R9mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hcs_StudentRep @HamptonCSchools @byjanehammond @crabbernews She does do a great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a Twitter break. Look what arrived just in time! @WilGafney #AJLevine https://t.co/aP39UHYH4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I couldn’t stop cracking up when I saw this ... #BernieRally #BernieSanders2020 @justinlong #gottago #ghosting… https://t.co/FtWYvAbScL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how often I say I hate tumbling or I want to quit, every time I see how far I've come whether it was thro… https://t.co/F2uDUCz2mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlaangola @TeDigoqueWeb Eso es bueno le van a hacer como a allende... Lo van a matar y después dicen que se suic… https://t.co/809fdPDoOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to announce that #BerkshireHathaway was recently recognized in the top 3 of Fortune's World's Most Admired Co… https://t.co/CIB7YS2BMc]]></document></documents></author>