<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#dailyinspo #blessedbeyondmeasure🙏😇 @ Huntington Beach, California https://t.co/zuYDqwi0H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does a salary cap help ...? The NFL and NBA have been dominated by the same teams and there’s been repeat champions… https://t.co/4TBPf4ViFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[(I’m gonna be introducing you to plenty of my new Truman friends from now on, so get ready)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras el clima esta de puta afuera #covereandoavalentin #veteya en Edificio B IADA https://t.co/zsnmCZG7lH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn is the cool laid back respectful dude .. you don’t wanna meet Shawny .. that nigga a SAVAGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubSantos @GNL_Oficial En que canal van a pasar el juego en Estados Unidos???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Free Eddie Gallager Highly Decorated   Seal NOW   !!!!!!! #FreeEddie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lhlabb @PolitiBunny Oh great! Another libtard soyflake who wants to abolish the 2nd amendment, citizenship for ill… https://t.co/KLSbhhba9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone be posting about snow, imma ‘bout to skip school just cause I wanna fit in 😂😭 https://t.co/hjK7FcBXbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lil guy, you really should just focus on your raking and let the adults worry about adult things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mumonamission5 @local_sun @pufpufpafpaf I’m not the one being deceived, I worship Allah the God of Abraham,Jesus,… https://t.co/P7wVEIA4Pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outcome split in Morningside College home cheer and dance competition.  https://t.co/CvXOOBKzKZ https://t.co/QOdsneXsPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @brielarson and @SamuelLJackson’s credit, they are the best part of the movie. I’m very excited to see more of… https://t.co/S8hdMPRsGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 @Arriadna Thank you! Say it like it is: Kilimnik IS Russian intelligence. What have the Republicans do… https://t.co/EH33dRftRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_eel I don't care about her. What they actually did is a danger to all of us. If you don't see it because you… https://t.co/AqM3ssLuZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spreading the message and empowering others!!  #manupalreadybook #platform #changelives #author #speaker… https://t.co/483VysCZj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brothersosborne kicked Ass in Plant city Fl. Thanks for an awesome show. https://t.co/5eCf1rzEfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is up for hookers and blow, after a day of insider trading at Wall Street?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priscilla_MR21 Yeah i was actually baptised Catholic but we switched to being Lutheran when i was still very young… https://t.co/3tiEaH5t6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man has  I problem making us look like the next Venezuela! @TeaPainUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a completely normal brain and I, too, believe it’s a character flaw when a player doesn’t sign with the team… https://t.co/G3UOAp5JYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norvina really just followed me.. I’m literally celebrating this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighGreco @MisterCDavid @aelder027 @Li_vely Y'all niggas cheated any way on those 90s jawns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rigofuentes @PuebloMagicos @gpeoyervides Foto digna de una postal! Saludos Presidente!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote in our latest poll of who recieved the worse set of scars from humanity! https://t.co/wvU1irnuiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support All ways trust in the lord - https://t.co/QOZR69OyLb #fundly via @Fundly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckECheeses @thattricktaylor I worked on the cut table at Pizza Hut for years while growing up and I’ve cut thou… https://t.co/TXxCGi0o97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurting both of us and hurting everyone but it's all a big cover for Hitler doing exactly just that. @HillaryClinton  @BillClinton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how they jumpy to conclusions early; then deny facts when they become apparent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE @YouTube Excellent drummer and Alex is no slouch on guitar either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevieGeesus @RealMobTalk7 Craziness...they make it really attractive to snitch....I mean cooperate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbraStreisand @PassarelliAllan We now know that Trump has had six private meetings with Putin. No other American… https://t.co/rMSAf37Mkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankJForte @BarryARothman @NHL Makes me think maybe 💰💵  had something to do with it??...  🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Bernie Sanders Plans to Defeat Trump in a Debate | NowThis = Directly Confront HIS LIES!  https://t.co/bFl10MNqgm via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[They called it ski-joring in Colorado. Leadville had a weekend dedicated to it. (minus the buggy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janelle Monáe and Yalitza Aparicio are still here in case y’all forgot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3500 Overland Ave 3500 Overland Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90034 https://t.co/NLc40xcizD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next few day it is believed that records will be broken in my neck of the woods.  We have experienced a very snowy… https://t.co/BiSC27JlDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Whoso findeth a wife findeth a good thing, and obtaineth favour of the Lord.” Proverbs 18:22 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCAR_Trucks Well, this race is over already. Still think it's good to have cup guys come race? 😴👎🏼👎🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRounds says @realdonaldtrump paid the #hushmoney because he loves his family.  He cheated on all 3 of his w… https://t.co/db9ZxLklB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LACourtReport Loved the way he would look at Refs on a questionable call when coaching at Artesia! 😆How can you no… https://t.co/QVMEbgcJlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Jorge Garrido UMN Using udder wipes at weaning to detect PRRSV at the Research Topics session at AASV Annual Me… https://t.co/XwrfacqjRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travis Braun Braun started the Princess Fairy Tale Challenge! https://t.co/HgzlqjPyyR #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHo18678740 @x_gamma @timdthomas @NRCC @realDonaldTrump I compiled these articles from news sources to make up… https://t.co/CniOAkD2Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too but you make them so great to listen to and watch muted broadcast! Thank you Matt!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arnaudrichy @BenWalke I couldn’t agree more ..even quicker, putting bespin, Kessel, jabba’s palace in galactic ass… https://t.co/Wscuvf0OUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the,, right,eous two here,,,,,,,trump of ,,,,,god,,,,,in first picture,,,then who's the two Fishers,,in the… https://t.co/gzoHMdnor5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@framebridge I have not received my order despite being told I would receive it before Feb 14... you also have not… https://t.co/FLJdRyWkaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait for #Concachampions this week. Hope @MLS teams can do some damage. Still outside hope that @torontofc wil… https://t.co/AjKXBIjgqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best negotiator ever.   Leave it to Middle America to vote for this dumb fuck to be our President. Incredible judgment and choice there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else just start happy crying every time you watch nectar videos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nanny knew best: Mike Bloomberg's trans fat ban paid dividents https://t.co/dLaLkBARKf #Obesity #transfat… https://t.co/WvgjVqhpQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you find something comical about my appearance when I am driving my automobile? https://t.co/n8G3tfskn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dollysaysno @copter_dave47 @kdlang @nytimes Here's a longer article that describes the plot. https://t.co/3A6PB3Si8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreWoods5 @EricLessig Knew you'd reply.  Absolutely zero disrespect to you or your daughter. It was soley directed… https://t.co/OR2dDAAZ4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@streetruffian @zpurton @KemblaCoxy @TDNAusNZ Worth ever minute. Phenomenal work, Coxy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EASTER 2015. edwardjones chase jpmorgan #health #family #harriscounty #law @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/ymlVhPn46L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trees as tall as skyscrapers. Sunsets that lit up the whole sky. Big metal bridges. Everything about San Francisco… https://t.co/kPPffBA4Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity these freaks , bucker, polosi, shumar, Cortez, and Omar are headed to destroying this magnificent coun… https://t.co/dclAf5Jqu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Films opening Feb. 28-March 1, 2019 - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/PfN3oGEct7 @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇬🇧UK🇬🇧 now will teach sex-ed beginning at 5 YEARS OLD—Parents NOT ALLOWED to opt out‼️  Children’s books like “My P… https://t.co/LfF1rcEetg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKGenest I only watched for Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper to sing “Shallow”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[D-IV boys hoop quarters: Mules wear down Pittsfield to move on https://t.co/zzCDpoJD8b @seacoastonline… https://t.co/NC3o2i0mfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[LCQ transfers to wins for front runners. This will be interesting for Barcia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glenn_fogle @1Romans58 @Solmemes1 @gatewaypundit Wouldn't help much. The muscle composition and joint diameter wou… https://t.co/x2udEzjNbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjoeyfatone I called it since the Brooklyn clue and the 1st twitch! I stuck to my guns! Awesome job on the mask… https://t.co/esdufw38bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would agree because the stadium won’t open in time for the 2020 season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimelessNuggets @Theotropho You keep saying that. Just because you repeat it doesn't make it true. It may be true… https://t.co/rPvziyvPbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/wepeB1lKrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @JRubinBlogger Has anyone told #Bernie that NJ...14EV.... has enacted #MustShowTaxRt.  More States… https://t.co/0rdLXb0y2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalLoveYourPetsDay   •Wolverine •Sweet Mary https://t.co/wdZ7rN5amL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You see there you go again thinking you know the law, constitution and politics. Of course they ar… https://t.co/4GF0KWFngy]]></document><document><![CDATA[EN VIVOLA  LOS ROMPE TARIMA  🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 @papasecreto @donollie @miguelitoaguila @soydjjhonny @UProductions1 pap… https://t.co/DtVkzpnT9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@zingermans Applewood and Cherrywood smoked bacon...  Ohhhhh sweet mystery of life I’ve found you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOrcl I went directly from working with pre SSH Windows into the post-CAPS era of docker-everything, managed conta… https://t.co/4G6phWPux4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unen esfuerzos las Fundaciones Andrea Bocelli y Carlos Slim  https://t.co/9lUzo3w1dX @fundaciontelmex @RenatoFloresC @Telmex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazRdik69 @charlieINTEL I also wanna know when the game as a whole is going to stop lagging when someone jumps in or out of your party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with you. If you want to buy better pillows like I have done go to bed bath and beyond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the official seal of the @VAStateBar, which is an agency of the Supreme Court of Virginia. https://t.co/AhvKMIpeYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhm... mcdonalds seems you’ve got some explaining to do.... your NEW #McCafe TV Commercial is a lot like my video I… https://t.co/fx8L35q6OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FryJared @TrevorJudge Plus with a defensive HC he is going to take a CB or LB in my opinion. We could also use a RT tackle]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: Charges filed in what investigators describe as ongoing gang war in Houston, including murder of Lamar H… https://t.co/MZFudZ9VRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lthomasnews how to submit questions to ur show?  Here’s one. Everything we hear is Woodley is the better wrestler… https://t.co/6LRvOLAYAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[US arrests #cryptocurrency exec over 'multibillion-dollar' fraud! #OneCoin was an elaborate #Ponzi scheme. #crypto… https://t.co/1ySOBFh04E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoJoBo1 @MaskedSingerFOX Thanx. I have downloaded the app but I don’t know if I can stream. We will see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wittman7 @b27moore @MLBPipeline I like Smith a lot. I am just projecting a well regarded 17 y/o. Could grow into a… https://t.co/3pl1g12FBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris How about those that maybe manufacturing lynchings?  Which side do you stand in solidarity with? #JussieSmollet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PitzaSlice bitch 😂💀 lol you’re carrying the thing right with the blue boots]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this is why I don’t have Facebook anymore... They don’t even ask people to opt in...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStigall Government is forcing Tabora Farms in Hilltown out of business]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Starbucks in Columbia, MO w/ @tweetedbyscott https://t.co/RnHi004R9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido EL TIEMPO ES ORO!!! NO DESPERDICIEN MAS EL TIEMPO Y DERROQUEN A MADURO !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at 30th Street Station - @amtrak in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/PxhAOOpt73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems surreal @TampaBayRowdies and @Tormenta_FC had a friendly last night. These 2 sides opened the door for me and… https://t.co/w2TtQyldMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a tiny app that easily removes EXIF data from JPEGs. PRs welcome for removing other metadata from other imag… https://t.co/jbDuUSzKbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite the lack of diet, nutrition, and end-of-life care statistics, this graphs loosely shows Universal healthcar… https://t.co/34eNl20ypA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re my friend and it’s your birthday .. tough luck. I’m done going out . Don’t ask me to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabreena Wadhwani started the Ascension Seton Austin Marathon! https://t.co/KgJln7c5kZ #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gretzz_10 The best 7th grader to ever play! I swear he was in 7th grade for 5 years then showed up on UNC roster hahaha]]></document></documents></author>