<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[And John Cluverius, an assistant professor at University of Massachusetts Lowell, suggests a last minute ad campaig… https://t.co/1cvYMo56u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snipekerr I'll keep an open for the scores when I can. Should be easier in post season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankkly38 who knew John Weiss and Bob Kraft had things in common! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do Erika’s gaggle of glam do when she’s out and about on these trips? Does she keep them locked in the suite u… https://t.co/UgyhdtZZ6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_jacks12 Its the worst aint it. Like damn im just bein myself. Sorry you thought of me in a different light]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes, he wrote you beautiful letters &amp; you fell in love🥰! https://t.co/MLZfGPIcIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton had won the 2016 president Elections, On orders from PUTIN and Trump America's Media controlled by… https://t.co/i873gqz0WJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time I had the stomach flu I was in a recliner all day...@keselowski spends it in a race car...and wins.  He’s… https://t.co/bLWsgKvbDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourmumspants @mikenedie @zypisfy @debbiepalm44 @DB_Grimwalker @Duke1CA @AtheistsRead @Cern_lXXl @dadbaddy… https://t.co/s6a72df5Gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not ok. This is not ok. This is not ok. This is not ok. I am not anti-Muslim or racist or xenophobic or sex… https://t.co/gfFbcnKQID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunes que Guapo eres, espero seas un día Rápido y Genial, que les vaya bien a todos en su inicio de semana.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[TMW you show up 90 minutes too early to training... https://t.co/zvzmu1Ymlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with Riley at the @Ottawa67sHockey game @ TD Place Arena https://t.co/4KqSF8HWu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seen like 5 teenage boys last night at Wal-Mart buying vday gifts, it’s so cute! All this love in the air ❤️🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattlanta The moment I saw the car coming right at me at twilight at intersection of Jones Bridge/Abbots Bridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[A visual representation of what my goals look like https://t.co/zFaMhGyvhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started this book today and holy shit is it good. https://t.co/XrgppwUzdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios @TheRealStanLee @Marvel That was the best part.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the new sound and direction from @Emarosa. Solid work on the new record! #PeachClub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDGOP This is what Democrat ACORN (community organizer) Activist do once they get elected. They only know how to s… https://t.co/O0vxPob1CV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I   think   I   miss u most  of  all @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/Uw80Hx1J2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christina_gual It was closer to an AA meeting than a worship service. Might be ok for some folks, but not me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a bigger DS putz than I thought.   Holy crap, the treasonous evidence they have against you must be vast.… https://t.co/ALjfQlL4xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @RodStryker Millineals paradise...need to pay attention it is anything but.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow Seriously - would Trump still have a job if he was CEO, or Chairman, of ANY #Fortune500 company ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid: Autograph?   @timbhealey: Mind if I sign my Chipotle order instead of a number?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's take a moment today to remember that time that Arby's almost killed Genesis @gb_villalobos https://t.co/p1dYRqGH0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[History has proven that “Great Commission” Christianity reduces solutions to social issues to interpersonal transfo… https://t.co/9vAEFopJbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ik u aint callin me a hoe frfr first off im nt even the one textin people but ok keep on thinki n watever ya head t… https://t.co/l7cxvC1XOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could you maybe not use a picture of treated soybeans that aren’t allowed to enter the food system.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans @Cassee999 Until the scuba diver that has to clean the aquarium is in there cleaning it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always appreciate teams leaving it all on the floor against one another and after 32 minutes come together!… https://t.co/M1xpV8pdY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEEI @jtomase As of last night, Kyrie Irving's 2019 #Celtics do appear to be in a 2011 #RedSox esque free fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPaine10 @Morning_Joe @NicolleDWallace Not a good mix of panelists today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey...@LarryZielinski @tplafferty @PeckOnSports follow the instructions as we have a great chance to get… https://t.co/72jj3Gz6uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebDoob_ @Kunle_AK @toondaye @ebunxoxo @metrobomi I did brodie. Preciate ya 🙏🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyBreslauer @scarletradio @jonnew Damn Danny I forgot about that Cuse game!!!!!😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dazon goes out, Bama comes back. Dazon comes in, Bama falls behind again. It's not a coincidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer Don't make me laugh! Your former boss didn't for the Nigal Wright affair, why would Trudeau for this!… https://t.co/WezF9xU80v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampPup I love that she thinks she said something about cheating but all comments show no one got that from her l… https://t.co/pht65RZDse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoannaZeee @Crabgirl72 @dbongino Every congressman or women gets the same amount of money, if you have a problem w… https://t.co/y0Lwguukc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtBale1010 if AWE is hiring I would love to become a ref but once I take pro wrestling  classes then I would love to become a wrestler]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bag is secure I’m talking about Padre fans acting like they are about to compete with giants and dodgers that’s… https://t.co/mb82pBpPO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryMetsFan13 @MetsMerized @SNYtv @Mets Sorry but I think you need to be attacked for your ignorance and childish behavior]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenDayforNE @Patty4Nebraska @NebraskaMegan @senatormachaela @senatorblood @MattHansenNE @Adam_Morfeld… https://t.co/KN88PJTc6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdultDiddy @Gowser93 @DillionHarper @Mrsperverted @LustfulBeauty01 @bad_rock9 @xDannyBoy92 Beautiful picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madnuhrah @Russian_Starr #WeOutHere #WeBeenOutHere #PDXwhileBlack https://t.co/lzRo7hOZD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mix957GR when will we be hearing #BoysInTheBand From @NKOTB on radio? https://t.co/ZqMNPI4Pqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bosslogic @jimmyfallon @FallonTonight No surprise! You’re mad talented my guy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bizsnes @djWHEAT This is how you can get a global emote?!? The path is clear to me now. https://t.co/RhPUmxqyfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewVanDrese @YostBuilt @umichhockey Wow didn't realize that, ugly stat. Overachieved last year but have to say underachieved this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Redes Sociales Progresistas R.S.P 3,000 firmas para hacerlo realidad. Baja California Sur. https://t.co/LH0fYtMuXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharethecities @WedgeLIVE @UrbanistOrg @TheStranger @richsssmith @RealChangeNews @ericacbarnett @jfeit “There’s a… https://t.co/sdryHWPwMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending my Sunday night watching #WorldOfDance @NBCWorldofDance @NeYoCompound @JLo @derekhough @iamscottevans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get yourself an old school girl. They can be a stubborn pain in the ass and you will fight, but in the long run, th… https://t.co/8V43TCGWaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 🎯https://t.co/lK5tSTfZ1h; #PragerU......What it’s s all about.  🇺🇸👍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @KingRicochet @WWEAleister @RusevBUL @ShinsukeN @LanaWWE Should be a great match! #WWENXT #SDLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollinSherwin @USFWBB You should take one home now that you’re finally a grown up. #adopt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UFOL3TA @TatyanaPavlovi1 I'm a big fan of this new series, Project Blue Book]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am declaring/guaranteeing that if @IndyMayorJoe can come up with a way to ultimately minimize Indy’s pot-hole pro… https://t.co/c1CpO4e9ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Pittsburgh vs Edmonton. The penguins yellow jerseys are just awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandrasimmons @BrandiRedmond @RealOCEmily @DrJamesMercer @TheEmmys @nbc @GettyImages @shopbrandiland I love ❤️ eve… https://t.co/fAK7HzFGVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topdawg619 @CCHSDONS @DJRalph7 @Donsfootball Is it a package deal does dad come to 😂😂😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[you want some mirth. I know you do. If you are bearing in mind about the rental property for accommodation, it may… https://t.co/BvVjtLUvg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTwersky Think about it. We called someone GOD for scoring 63 points in a loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone in the Ohio GOP congressional delegation own a jacket? @Jim_Jordan @RepBobGibbs… https://t.co/H7sxmQ8fb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m suing Apple for every you’re your fuckup I’ve ever unintentionally perpetrated. Damn phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsbyCoachP @CoachHixonDimes @DavidBoydhoops @DaveNedbalekUTT @CoachRjayBarsh @chibbs_1 @LamarBigs… https://t.co/cmJpdaceYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ten years from now (2010!), every big company will have a Chief Culture Officer on staff and, if big enough, a tea… https://t.co/Q9eQFT4JrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaLHE the rumors are not true yo if I could fill in anybody in fw it would still be the mosher yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump AMERICANS can't afford Trump failure to recognize the real problem in America didn't Cross the BOR… https://t.co/tBdSgRJrMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kidnapped and surprised is about the only way to get me these days. #grateful #ichoosehappy #caughtintheact… https://t.co/sl90DD0SAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zacwoodward As long as you don’t have to look like... https://t.co/gwCrQ69AaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wrong and disgusting. While exercise and diets DEFINITELY help, some people actually need medication and fu… https://t.co/RgK8YEpcPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely if that next President wants to start the Next Revolution!  @USFreedomArmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some cookies. (@ Not Your Typical Deli - @nytdeli in Gilbert, AZ) https://t.co/cx1JzVpMHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tootsysmom Don’t go out unless you really have to... a hair dryer at the frozen area may help that garage door...]]></document><document><![CDATA[O @PSG_inside vai ter q decidir se fica com Neymar ou Mbappe. Se demorar vai ficar apenas com o Mico. Heheheeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She think it got some gotta do with my momma why I can’t love her like she need me” 🔊🔊😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being up 5-0 in snd and blue screen, and to make it worst it counted as a lost. @Treyarch please fix this stupid ass glitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddeherman @MckinleyDHughes Please. I know who he is, but I'm a historian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really impressive by the 16 year old! This kid is the real deal. The 🇺🇸 national team need to lock this kid up as s… https://t.co/bKBYI8xT7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terps invade Annapolis today @TerpsMLax let’s get it! #MarylandMade https://t.co/Fm3E80yMLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osfashland Caesar shall never die!!! Except the like 8 times a week...twice on Saturday’s and Sundays...  #CaesarTFANA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t get a picture with @BigDradio, did you even really go to the game? #VegasBorn https://t.co/kExdMn4IaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephiHill Unsolved Mysteries with the guy's voice made it seem like my death was imminent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Día de partido con mis bellezas Santos Vs Toluca @TSMoficial @priestra @SergioMoguelB @lirarragorri hoy ganamos https://t.co/Z7cRYp9IUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAStartingLine @ewarren Haha haha haha haha haha, Pocahontas, you are truly funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I appreciate that they care about sick birds. We need to get the ill eagles to the vet https://t.co/e7MMcUezq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougstafford Obama's move was to circumvent existing law and do what he pleased. Trump's move is to enforce existi… https://t.co/lYgZUioaoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone else: booker t lunch jams: 🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 DONT GO CRYING  TO YOUR MAMA  CAUSE YOURE ALL ALONE  IN THE REAL WORLD!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Seger concert in Austin @ Frank Erwin Center https://t.co/Y1dTgUj1dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunshineonmyface #zag1 #zag1📷 #ibikekern #healthylifestyle #health #activeliving #healthyliving #activelifestyle… https://t.co/NOgZpyZfvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Ashton Johnson for advancing in the 3 Point Shoot-Out! He'll shoot next in the Lewistown Sectional on F… https://t.co/qbvOW2zcsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so grateful for a horse named Jordan. My daughter Vero and Jordan filled our lives with love for many years! W… https://t.co/0OPr7QrDgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CodesMcGodes Good thing the Lions gave up on him so he could succeed elsewhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gotfocus Jack Donohue used to always say - you only have so much practice time - have to maximize it - always run… https://t.co/j1L37xDaI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna tell u all about my trip tbh but that’ll have to wait I guess lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the mayor had done something to stop Intelligentsia Blue Bottle and La Colombe from settling in New York we don’t need them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the players and coaches who were honored. To Charlie and Craig I say - CONGRATULATIONS...thi… https://t.co/u0BxLESNGR]]></document></documents></author>