<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlexontheMic The weather in the whole USA is SO extreme lately!! Look at Flagstaff Arizona and Maui Hawaii “Major… https://t.co/5oAXfYmfyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @seanmdav @JussieSmollett Luckily he’s not a farmer, lord knows what scam he would pull! #spoiledhollywoodelite #different]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS ME! I NEED A 3 PAGE ESSAY EXPLAING WHY YOU DID WHAT YOU DID AND WHY YOU ARE APOLOGIZING?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls stop asking me those questions idk ask someone else @ Feednoly https://t.co/SnejPHTFDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[another thing calendared this week, hoping to see you there https://t.co/8rF1BqrcjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flat earth plus MOMO equals = 👱🏿‍♂️  (Whoever allowed that emoji to be made)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emergency alert system: Shelter in place.   Me to my friends: Come over to shelter in place with me.  Friends: Ehhh… https://t.co/cEoPHWE3tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look guys: I KNOW I help Pitt and Philly. As well as Hershey 💕. But PA is not only about them. I repeat I am very u… https://t.co/qhBcfFnhCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 20, 2019 . branches reaching up/ roots reaching down as mirror/ symmetry of trees . #haikulevenhagen . Yet… https://t.co/akZbHaSMZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[That ‘rap’ scene in the end credits of the hometown episode of the Bachelor had me CRINGING! The rap and the damn b… https://t.co/W4rGCzmz2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin is a news reporter in Chicago and was at this McDonalds when R.Kelly walked in. Dude is really sick in th… https://t.co/aZIc6Y0ZDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews Cohen's lawyer knows. It's coming. All of it. Fox lies...too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Agreed. 28 USC 594 (h) gives the court the main role in the release of a Special Counsel report. The co… https://t.co/Y008eYHWTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how many miles a year I put on my car going back for stuff I forgot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rooshv You can’t help but display your prehistoric sexist views on women, even when it limits your range of gettin… https://t.co/0hZnH4qZD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is disgusting. My home state: disappointing me one crap idea at a time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sun finally came out today and It was an automatic energy boost. Thank you God 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I used to say there was a price to pay for all that sunshine -- natural disasters, skin cancer, eye damage (w… https://t.co/s0mwytGumG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexste12760351 @davidmweissman Agree. Their very open-mindedness and appreciation for differences makes it much h… https://t.co/n5npxpl99n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week &gt;&gt;&gt;   2/21 Thursday - @_UnderGround317 Open mic   2/22 Friday - @wticlothing Pop Up 👕 https://t.co/kq65dlVKXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legitimately cannot and will not return to Florida sorry! I live here now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@interface2learn @AcreAustralia @sea_australia @CiscoCSR So pleased to be partnering with your teams! Hey look… https://t.co/k6hlgGTIRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry work, you're gonna haveta wait... This is my life. Go ahead with your own life, leave me alone.🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinningtheBattl Ask Who Will Support this Fight by Sharing the News? We request your presence @FOX5Atlanta… https://t.co/pAvlj3JKKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @TheMominatrixx If you listen to Giuliani you're the fool. The man is demented saying the truth isn't… https://t.co/1JrF7EBX8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Drake said “You just need some dick with no complications” https://t.co/nReih0hHvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman @wally_polischuk I will campaign in every upcoming primary and caucus in any way I can to ensure th… https://t.co/9zWIMwhjou]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPRING FABFITFUN SNEAK PEAK BELOW🌸  You're going to LOVE what's inside your Spring Box! 😍💐  Each box is well worth… https://t.co/amUTniDncM]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my bed frame is wack and likes to drop from time to time. Tonight right as I’m leaning over to turn off my lamp… https://t.co/uP3HLDZ0mI]]></document><document><![CDATA[cute boy~🌻🌻🌻 Hope u like it~ ️@titlekplee  #กลจของตต  #titlekrt  thx 原始素材 from logo https://t.co/meEHxFfwCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had known how comfortable maternity jeans are, I would’ve been wearing them my whole life. 10/10 would recommend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gIitter_gIue Tbh he just creeps on everyone. He called me by my IG handle for the longest and probably knows yours too. Watch your back 👀😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AndTheVerdictIs If you jump over  a barrier to take a selfie with a Jaguar you’re going to get mauled. Let’s not blame the poor jaguar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 Why? Are they afraid of what Schiff may find? Too bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Fanart Repost from @anas.magg “My new drawing! My dress for tinaguo and pizza!!🌹🌹😄” Thank you, we love it! ❤️ https://t.co/gpP5yLwnLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you think about watching some good ole porn before going to bed but your phone on 2%. Sad sleep tonight folks 😂🥴✌🏾✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 @senatemajldr @SteveDaines @SenatorEnzi @SenatorRounds @JimInhofe @HouseGOP Just heartbreaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to my first dress fitting earlier and then had @porridge_puffs for lunch! 🍚🥖 #porridge #lunch #losangeles @ Po… https://t.co/4SYzJo0RyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for our own Karen Galena - it’s official, she’s #TeamKelly @kelly_clarkson #VoicePremiere @STAFFMARK… https://t.co/mh5bnIUyWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorqd25 @jenhlawrence @susieostinson @april_gators @Education_Poole @jimmysawtelle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck Lady Jackets Bowling today at Sectionals @PerrysburgBowl2 !!!! #NoPinLeftStanding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TONiANN_ROSE @jarpad @realGpad Everything that comes out of his mouth, and apparently camera roll, is a sexual inn… https://t.co/TCzynTvmRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted Bundy has a gf named Diane and anyhow those are my parents’ names aaaaaahhhhhh how did nobody who watched the d… https://t.co/QXROqy2XBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ithestud And I’ve never said one is greater than the other. Ever. You’re getting defensive and presumptuous...seem… https://t.co/VIxZy0FKRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to one of my closest friends @blakely_luis2 I hope your day was everything you wanted and more I lov… https://t.co/0vcibnDwxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys get first look 😉 It's been a while since I've posted a training clip! https://t.co/jOvfQJ4kZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. and Mrs. Chad just asked me, a person standing on my feet (as God herself intended) on St. Charles Ave., to mov… https://t.co/dRoUFZMAM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PaulDouglasHale #Independent wIth #CRPS-II #SMP #RDS  Mother #MaryGreer of #Atlanta - #Flovilla Is Murdered  Fu Sh… https://t.co/uVQWiVafHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @hollybsteele for helping us on our STEM excellence journey! #falconpride #fsdlearns https://t.co/0Jk95ZtloF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyTomTompkns @JoelleMonique I’d love to see  tall bigger chicks in more super hero roles, but she’s gonna do an… https://t.co/NKOm3aH5np]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting a @krispykreme and a @Starbucks close to Wilson Central High School would make life so wonderful for teachers...💙🍩☕️💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was definitely one of my favorite traditions @fssdPGMS! This is what school culture looks like folks. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread: “What masquerades as hope sometimes is the oppressed becoming the oppressor.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dick_pleaser69_ I raised my son well, knowing exactly how I like for him to lick my pussy, and like this clip from… https://t.co/Wkw2o0Ls0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samfarmerrrr I was sleeepingggg I’m too upset to respond to that message 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[this bitch blocked me on everything when all i’ve ever said to her was nice things😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2nd song “Let You Go” is Out The link is in my bio 💖 https://t.co/tWLAffLH00]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up feeling invincible because for the first time in a long time, I remembered who I am, what I’m capable but… https://t.co/L6ilkT5pAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinRThompson1 @shitfoodblogger This is the only way to have an Oreo! 😋🍪 https://t.co/fJDnwDdoxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two of the best people (and coaches) I know 😊🤗 @coachmull2 @CoachHG 💜  https://t.co/CSQvF4YcS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer @CPC_HQ Your kids are going to have the opportunity to live in a post-apocalyptic dystopia following… https://t.co/yfwhZRFJXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is practicing guitar in the room next to mine and they’re fantastic! Can’t wait to meet them tonight before… https://t.co/rUaClG53wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are really getting into character @Lamkin_Ele in drama club @CyFairISD @CFISD_FineArts @MissMallard15… https://t.co/frzGgbOPn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This child looks to be about 16/17 and Terrance beat this young boys ass back inside the vehicle. The cold grabs a… https://t.co/g7X7CT3YwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heart wrenching but outstanding article by @DrJenGunter a unique perspective as an Ob/Gyn Mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better. - Samuel Beckett]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good time tonight at Salt Bar! We missed Janice but we danced through it!!! ♥️♥️🎵🎵🎶🎶 Thanks to everyone for all the… https://t.co/KkxIYhYnYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[And The Winner is... Abbey OscarViewingParty Oscars https://t.co/IAxjaWQGjq https://t.co/yCbnqt9Oza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also on a work travel related note: Ohsee’s instagram/hashtag content is in @SeanDoesLights’ hands until Wednesday evening, as an FYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[get you a mans who lets you rant to him about the bachelor &amp; ACTUALLY listens]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the many many years that I’ve known you... you’ve been doing nothing 🙃 keep up the good work poodle face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spiced_ice OKAY THIS LITERALLY JUST HAPPENED TO ME like this girl was complaining about the shared rides taking to… https://t.co/HirJcpqtMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7 @AlaskaAir My fantasy seatmate would be Lady Gaga! She is amazing. #iFlyAlaska #OTRCSweepstakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is jolly. Victoria Secret Original Gift Card - https://t.co/hFAvjtW5ko Teenager Post # 5039 elle1340 https://t.co/bqIuIVHM0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildjhovall @badhopper @cellmavin @OkiTimes @JonMontag @DaveK72 @lhtetrick @JohanBBT @Just4BeerLovers @wolv54b1… https://t.co/ayLvCvIWJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I just now discovered a special email quarantine place where apparently many legit emails to my ULM address go t… https://t.co/2npM7KyFCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family isn’t big on apologizing. So when my mom apologized to me tonight about something that hurt me back in hi… https://t.co/Mc2k3NmBtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaviLadnier @WomensProject @Colt_Coeur I wish you would have had a show today..we would have come to see you again! #HateF**k so great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had it with the fear mongering. Pita chips are dangerous? They’re NAKED! Where would they hide a weapon? https://t.co/d17t0eNKuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utter rubbish , the two boys know what they are doing and respect each other . Let go your speculation .  american… https://t.co/sFg2ZZygXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me muero de ganas por estar en la playa con mi mejor amiga y que mi única preocupación sea no quemarme con el sol ☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #WakeUp #pray #hustle #riseandgrind https://t.co/mT1Jpcul40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, Trump is still president and everything is terrible but let's not forget about the time Kristen Wiig performe… https://t.co/SKd0DSJBWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krussell_17 Ugh but my tired of my toes getting cold even if im wearing them with fuzzy socks. U right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juant003 I think I jumped to false conclusions about you. I’m very sorry. I’m also very glad you stood your ground… https://t.co/Ioq4U6luDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great reminder when you’re having a discouraging day:  “A professional is simply an amateur who didn’t quit.”… https://t.co/C8hNJ5eUL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Save the eighth-grade jokes and schadenfreude for the next time the Patriots lose in the playoffs. This is not abo… https://t.co/JxgEg6De4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuciGabehart @jgabehart16 Happy birthday JP!  Cant believe you're 17!😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zack used to look at me like this when we first started dating and even now it MELTS ME🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian @fleissmeister We love you Khloe. We know you have too much class to go on that stupid show! Lmao. This guy is an idiot. ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KickGameRunGame @Scott_Stiller @LeVeonBell Don’t assume to know me... like you I’m entitled to my opinion and my o… https://t.co/hGJj8F2bCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake me. Everytime. A child needed us. A mother needed us. That's all the reason we need. Focus your energy on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi 😂😂😂😂😂😂 I don't think they're listening but nice heads up! Build the wall now @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild Hope and Coverage are great albums and if you disagree you’re just wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four salt trucks coming down Union Blvd., one after another. Street looks nice and clear. I like it 🤗  Great job as… https://t.co/vAcIOXj4uS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns @RobinRoberts @GMA @WWE Two. Brother Roman I made bracelets and put Punch Out. Leukemia for everybody even you]]></document><document><![CDATA[👑 BIRTHDAY QUEEN 👑  Happy 23rd Birthday to me!!!! Woooooo 🎂🎁🎊🎉🎈😆!! Check out this super cute birthday makeup look 😍… https://t.co/GAEPKEyqtL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentines 😍 @ Texas Roadhouse - Colonial Heights https://t.co/Y2K9qc7U30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Hallmark Channel, for making 8.7 miles on the treadmill tolerable on a rainy day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelHyatt  I am reading #freetofocusbook You are spot on. I literally hired someone who’s only job is to answer… https://t.co/tf4PR9sKEQ]]></document></documents></author>