<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Ironhorse76 I’ve already made my monthly $27 contribution. I’m thrilled and can’t wait to start volunteering and w… https://t.co/QDRIRB5xM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylee_moody2 thank you kaylee! i didn’t even know that one picture existed 😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shewrick @ShatterverseEnt Also, turning a streetwise and hard edged burglar with a troubled past into a mild manne… https://t.co/l73NwwVNnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWiseguy @BigIndianGyasi I don't believe you need to take a moral stand on MJs music. If you can condemn his aw… https://t.co/Bk6N1pEVWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @MoniqueWorthy After reading some of these tweets, You just don't get it. This woman is just doing her job… https://t.co/aYMoHI0eh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most lopsided title fight I’ve ever seen. 3 10/8 rounds possible. Woodley didn’t even show up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the best way to get a job  I was born to a week of love  My age is still going up for me  I like to thin… https://t.co/ega8KY6GVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asantosrubino IMHO, esta plática se podría haber usado mejor, si es por simbolismo, con seguridad con tanta creati… https://t.co/0jdOiMpJXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forest Hills NY Tue Feb 19th AM Forecast: TODAY Mostly Cloudy Hi 45 TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradford Lott crossed 15K. Time 01:37:54, pace 10:18 min/mile, est. finish 7:55 am https://t.co/GsK0HTG9PB #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@startrekcbs Emperor Georgiou from the future perhaps? She could be retrieving information from the past. https://t.co/JwSqPPRFpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport She needs senate rep support to get him out office! Waiting for facts that they cant turn a blind eye to! Its coming soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Be afraid, very. Afraid that a patsy isn’t in the future for you... (Think about it) Your enemies are getting desperate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tornadosis06 Completely accurate. The most verifiable fact on twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime ET shoots a shot outside of 8 feet. So good at everything else. https://t.co/rPsblF401P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canada 🇨🇦 is definitely the best place to live on earth.I’ve travelled to all the continents in the world except So… https://t.co/W4QPorN9je]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @KAG4All @robjh1 The Democrats are so full of crap. They can’t remember what they say from one minute to the next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was on my school’s undefeated soccer team in first grade. At the end-of-year party (at a Pizza Hut buffet) everyo… https://t.co/Z5XGX7lJC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up doesn’t mean getting older! - @benrector what a show!!! https://t.co/YXgXnbx6kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. The thin layers of paint veil but do not erase one another. Something of what formerly was still exists. Though… https://t.co/x9A192ayd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a super rad Game of Thrones fan theory. It really displays the depth of the mythology in the show and books… https://t.co/GyIbV46May]]></document><document><![CDATA[U can see as the weeks go bye aoc doesnt think before she says stuff, she is virtually a white with some tan skin, smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RacistIsAsRacistDoes Viral video shows police pulling guns on black man picking up trash on his property - ABC New… https://t.co/Z5OKKkJHyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyeFigueroa @BossKaylaE @30SecKnockouts Violence is everywhere. This was just repercussions that was violent upon repeated request]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Whitney Winter Witbier by Inventors Brew Pub @ Inventors Brewpub — https://t.co/KmyjMbYhSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm glad, I opened the door...Thank you Jesus... @ Murfreesboro, Tennessee https://t.co/4htIrsHjGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carnaval on the Mile 2019! #GOD #FamilyFirst #LMMM #MissingMA #CarnavalOnTheMile #2019 #SundayFunday #Winter… https://t.co/17NIAuNksb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my partner @KarlFrisch's 41st birthday! I'm asking everyone we know to contribute $41 (or whatever you can… https://t.co/HH9XIyYTnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for Saturday’s home game and🎇show at SDCCU🏟 !! Check out my latest video on what to expect when you go… https://t.co/YoVDL4RsqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tim_mcbreen @waynesadin @dhinchcliffe @QuestDX @ClintBoulton @MylesSuer @MaureenB2B @WSJ I agree.  But it takes a… https://t.co/b1ofS99342]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay Fleming | Professional Photographer | Artisan Portrait https://t.co/HEyqTN59z6 via @YouTube @JayFlemingPhoto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esteevius @Alyssa_Milano I wore a Trump shirt during the primaries. I was treated like a god. I could wear a Maga… https://t.co/9yurUfCfA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Round About Midnight by @WeatheredSouls_ at @WeatheredSouls_ — https://t.co/yBByHu4br3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsVAA @wolfteddybear26 @realDonaldTrump Well trolls, when not addressed attack good people without reserve... even… https://t.co/atGfZNyX74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airport fits are super important for immigrant families😂😂 statements are being made]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second City sounds fun, but have to been to Third City? Way more teeth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @politicususa Republicans could care less. Trump’s should have been gone 2 years ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScutRaisins As a middle school teacher, 8th Grade reaches directly into my soul. It entered my eternal top 5 this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sak_shoes You've caused hundreds of us to outgrow our clothes. It only seems fair. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPTIMIST CLUB OF VW ORATORICAL CONTEST Sunday, 3/3 at 2:00pm. Students are asked to prepare a 4-5 minute speech on… https://t.co/vvT2pUjBYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[LPF Convention 2019 – Light Up Liberty https://t.co/SxMZzKnlst @LP_Florida]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our forefathers knew the difference between LEGAL and ILLEGAL.  Our founding father's wouldn't have made middle cla… https://t.co/mZiw1PtMyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching SNL every week and my favorite part of every show is always Weekend Update. And as a life long wres… https://t.co/mQkir0ZLKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flyerspaul This just shows you the entire thing was made up. I thought the hold up was the opt out after 3 instead… https://t.co/KH9ot5cN9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHANERAVENSFAN Not when you have 0.0 Qbr in the first half ! https://t.co/JQOOIlFjs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ku Cinta Yesus-Qu S'panjang Hidup-Qu (I 💝 Jesus) . #jesuschrist #ilovejesus #happysunday #simnarek_photografy… https://t.co/6a3drHigSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trollkashi @IMPACTWRESTLING @ClevelandBrowns @WhereImFrom @RockwellMasks @PursuitChannel @Twitch @zachary_wentz… https://t.co/1f7eTt6Pig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won’t be able to go to any games in the Swamp this year because of my Landscape Architecture internship…😫 #SwampLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eyeongaryjohnso @Milehigh_Sam @AmericanIndian8 The savage is in your mentality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyokaArchetype Following you for a reason...thanks for the discussion. The slow drip of climate change is numbing… https://t.co/k4S1vBhreT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 Share this until they reprimand the racist that assault him.  This is considered a hate crime.  It’s t… https://t.co/V5XQfGRWQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot its_zay7 yesterday. Let me know what you think. @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/0bs3VYbM3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @DENTONCBC @badhopper @JonMontag @JohanBBT @zappafaye @OkiTimes @Paul_TheBeerGuy @wolv54b1… https://t.co/68WCHKNkXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStation is there anyway you guys can help me get dlc from my wife’s account transferred to mine? We shared… https://t.co/aQq2R8i4B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹are red Violets are blue When I peek inside a colon I don’t wanna see 💩#GIvalentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove No.    No reason other than spiritual entropy.  I'm made out of faulty stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1122jwhite @SenFeinstein Donald Trump would carry babies upside down by their feet and you fucking know it bro. Do… https://t.co/xQdbGL4RpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharia Law is a religious law that's protected to practice under the United States Constitution. It's very similar… https://t.co/0q70ktafa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soda_hunter @MJGIV79 @HOVAAA @FullyPoseable @feedme_tacobell They look cool though. Not really into gross cards bu… https://t.co/0nzHA7QGLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekMelange @GailSimone @screwjaw @chicagonerds @DarkAndNerdy @gordondym @zero1 Proud to be on this list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently wearing one wireless iPhone earpiece is the thing this year at #CPAC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttesenAo @BeckySmirks Mental flexibility requires different perspectives. Looks like you are limited to one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirk on NBA arenas saying goodbye. “It’s been humbling, even though I haven’t said this will be it . . . I’m going… https://t.co/A539OYcNqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want!   Nubia just announced a phone-smartwatch hybrid with a flexible screen and it looks insane https://t.co/WmF7E78xQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #random #landscape #landscapephotography #clouds #cloudy #longexposureshots #longexposure… https://t.co/0nEkZlq4tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA A MERI CAN IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE UNDER GOD. THE OTHER LAND OWNERS MAY NOT BE MUCH UP… https://t.co/iI4lMduSMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brain when I get 8 hours of sleep, clean my room, and read a book for an hour on a Sunday: https://t.co/aQBFlbTTwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like a comfortable win for @MSURacers 🏀 @OVCSports tournament is going to be such a great watch. #CollegeBasketball #Epilepsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready! #bxtarheelssoftball (at @AGameSports2 in New Rochelle, NY) https://t.co/iFytfeZ2dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @UVUmbb practice right now and I’m telling you right now that the 2019-20 version of the Wolverines is going to be crazy deep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to #win @sixflagsDK Tickets! @1039TheFish https://t.co/BXMbvWBk1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@king_david_ines I watched this game live in my unit’s day room on German TV. We had permission to go beyond the 01… https://t.co/yQtICwMVnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickydirtyjames @nhlbecca All I’m saying is that professional sports is a business and you can’t get upset if a pl… https://t.co/OxV9jH49Rq]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘No matter how long the winter, the spring is sure to follow’ • Today was the first day when it felt sort of like s… https://t.co/3nS9DJyxTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait wait wait forget that last tweet. Twitter is rushing me with lots of info right now. THERES A TETRIS BATTLE ROYAL!??!?!!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pivotal moment!!!!! I’m driving around LA without using maps. A bitch knows where she’s going. Does this make me a local now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Your bucket list for reimagined pancakes, from California to New York: Whether you like them tall… https://t.co/M9bKpNhT9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantalMachabee Virus ? D’après moi il fera peut-être être partie d un échange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timely session, complete with a discussion about the misuse of data by certain consumer genomics companies... #SXSW… https://t.co/T5Pj9bEOB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd @Los_CoachGruden had to defend @MichaelVick twice a year for a few years. He knows first hand the hea… https://t.co/UVaUcs9VEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerbDeanMMA Should be at this press conference! #UFC235 #UFC #HerbDean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tweets4MAGA @DaRealGrizzle Why am i not surprised.  wtf happened to my home state of MI??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarBombBoom13 @ArizonaCoyotes Grew up in Winnipeg saw him come in to the league a rookie...always was a class act]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MobilePunch If they use MILITARY this time around.People may face them. Leave election for people to decide for Go… https://t.co/YSyrtf3FAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overall losses reported by Airbus since 2016 are now well over $4 billion, including latest $494 million charge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattblashaw of #yardcrashers stopped by our booth to film us for https://t.co/qtvacyZQOH @MitsubishiHVAC https://t.co/Rek2xo7Jvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[24 February 2019  #GodofAbraham  "America the Free"  #SoundCloud  #NP  #NWO  "Border Security" Mind Control  Marchi… https://t.co/QgsJN3fNlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to adjust three times day and you need Tommy John underwear because you won't need to adjust it at all best… https://t.co/V5z0qGwLQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually think Haney beats the brakes off Teofimo at this stage in their careers. Lopez is electrifying, but styl… https://t.co/7Dvm0owLs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't you hate it when the soap gets hung up in your butt hair? I wonder if I can fart a bubble?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s me, ya fav Hawkeye-Bulldog hybrid, feeling a lot of stress about the Iowa women and the Drake men playing at the same time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast This female dog is wroth 70 million +  Why are you enlarging her  platform to spew her hate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Campbell County!!! Good luck to you- glad our paths crossed.  Hang in there .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like Alfred Blue, but it's time to make the smart business decision. He still has talent and value and we… https://t.co/QKM1Ki4Tly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior @Merri__Magic Kushner had to change his clearance document 40 times.that should be braking how many… https://t.co/jGgAwl1EZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyb911 @RamieIsTweeting Mostly the lack of cleaning up the mess.  Have your kids do it and report back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Joni Mitchell’s book of art and lyrics to be published in October: A rare book of handwritten lyri… https://t.co/tX8LCO4le3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorrainecink @captainmarvel @JDHeyman @AngeliqueRoche @tamarakrinsky Hey guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaiBid plus you are sexy and a hooper. could only be the best of the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noble_Recon Ahh ok, ya mine turned 1 in January. Joker looks like he'll be an awesome dog.]]></document></documents></author>