<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This goes to show when you have money you can pay a lot of people to do shit for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTinHills @israelwayne We shall agree to disagree. No worries. Love you as always sister.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got Emily’s nephew to say he wants to listen to punk music. Mission accomplished.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5ReasonsSports What th he hell made him think BBB(Lonzo) was worthy of th hay draft pick? Useless! De'Aaron Fox wo… https://t.co/cZt7QMpFpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothySoden @Saints @Kirkwood_Five WHODAT! I recognize Wawa! Renewed my season ticket today! Love making that Phi… https://t.co/AqKI5E6o6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Angeles Rain has stopped officially for the week!  Those that experienced roof leak can get a free quote on rep… https://t.co/0Zvm5Ghk3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we were setting up our tools in our #makerspace . Took some wood and made a clamp rack. Thanks @PortPerryHS… https://t.co/i7BwjURkzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColMorrisDavis @RepMarkMeadows Well Col. you know how the GOP is today. The GOP at large wouldn’t know a FACT even… https://t.co/1XiXhDxsdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it though? When people are rushing reviews out to meet embargo while not even bothering to properly learn how th… https://t.co/ztpIglqVOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dy-no-mite. Full house, energetic participants...thank you!! (Remember gratitude helps our mood and decreases our d… https://t.co/PaIscAFLLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunkyGayJesus @Renevelation Be fair, his mom needs her hair washed (a lot).  He's been busy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boru2308 @jkbjournalist @nytimes @thecrimson @jayrosen_nyu here's another "Sullivan and Mackey represented the act… https://t.co/ZCO58VGgF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamonSantore You’d have to go to the FasTrac desk to verify your ID and credit card, as this would be your first W… https://t.co/CwCyKHSsdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying out the new AR Feature on PoGo.  😜🤷‍♂️  @BigCMen doing some acting while editing.... https://t.co/0t5rvnKasZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mustangs_Bball Awesome team work, and a strong mental focus makes the Dream a reality!  Go Mustangs Go !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngrierWHStaff A cure for those that recently discovered Trump was lying. It's a shock I've got to cure it is dige… https://t.co/zVZm4w5KzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter game is pretty horrible, apparently. https://t.co/kum2bHR41v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats RM Varsity Girls Softball on their 2-0 win over Buena HS at home today! Spartans Elevate-Together We Rise!… https://t.co/XSvls9NBF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg @TheAtlantic It’s been “Mission Impossible” all along, at every level… Trump “conspired” w/Russia… https://t.co/gEeDDDJ0Rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have done the research and it is clear that hydrogen and probably carbon energy will both replace fossil fuels.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tour has moved up the coast - Drinking an IPA by @lagunitasbeer @ The Old Cayucos Tavern  — https://t.co/5ZrdAzRal0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BastardProphet @RSun82 @BrandonMSparks Some people are better than us Sarge, at dealing with pimples! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_VicenteSerrano  aquí casual viajando a la mañanera @ElMariachiNinja @Rafaherrera1983 @QuesaVerdades otra vez cómo… https://t.co/hKlP1fGZNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed catching up with @blaireinfeldt today. He was a student @SnowCollege and @SUUtbirds during our tenures at e… https://t.co/CNfhKURQc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UconnWins @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Yea check your facts but again see what you want to see.… https://t.co/Ewh5Dht9Br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two wrestling legends, the beginning of an end of an era. #Undertaker #TripleH #RAW #WrestleMania27 #2011 #TBT https://t.co/fbnd9I4Cex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanPurdy2 @Sassymomof6 Oh your dogs favorite treat isn’t peanut butter balls?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Good. Any arse who wears that silly hat or espouses Carlson or Huckabee Sanders-like propaganda, s… https://t.co/YR0ggwF2od]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating, testing, and implementing this system is going to be a game changer. #PPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today 8pmEST/5pmPST  https://t.co/4HR41BI4Yo and https://t.co/xtZrVo9YTb also available on the free TuneIn App at y… https://t.co/EO8HwYu1m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinSincere @DeborahRiddle16 @FoxNewsinSocks @watspn1013 Other than the fact the guy wasn’t a “conservative”, we ca… https://t.co/zGcj72jYd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see all the sus Valentines Day portraits and posts on the gram ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[After I turned off my alarm I went to get a drink of water and dumped it all in my face cause there was less in it than I thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Its_Me_Manoli Muy buenos días Manoli y feliz Lunes y inicio de semana saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anna_hosein @jessero24365783 @ekhardt_j @AllNightShow @GodsMercyaGrace @can2009 @ProfitableWord @Music4HimNow… https://t.co/mwqkTwQzc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferndawg810 Nah I take it personally bc my homeboy died that way. Shit pisses me off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allihend Well, she DID put her own shoes on this morning, so... There's that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duciswild Your chance on Valentines whoopee tonight! https://t.co/dAMfyHgGFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealBucs still waiting on you to announce that you going to battle in Chicago.  The 🦇🦇🦇 hive is strong in the city]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Me a Story Night ⁦@CowartDISD⁩ ⁦@lsalinas0612⁩ ⁦ ⁦@MolinaSunset⁩ #DallasISD #teamcowart https://t.co/9VSdDHbAyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Way to go @poncaschool  guys basketball team! Great game! Congrats to @CarterKingsbury, @14_evan (nice last… https://t.co/NHFYKQVZwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anger is an acid that can do more harm to the vessel in which it is stored than to anything on which it is poured. -Mark Twain #pcm335]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWjedimaster @FrankMCardillo @jenillo @DillosDiz #AlwaysMGM https://t.co/iT0afH5UVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who did you like most  Astro or Scooby Doo biggest question of our time ( forget real issues, we do anyway)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realize cardinal birds exist in Star Wars because that’s why Captain Cardinal is named that. After his red… https://t.co/8Lv898Wn7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at metro community provider network in Englewood, CO w/ @idragonluv https://t.co/veYUIOCF4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday 10am or 11:30am.  127 S M St Lake Worth ・・・ Happy SATURDAY! Slide to church for week 2 of “BACK 2 the BLOCKB… https://t.co/gvG3rVMVSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie is about to tell Colton one of his biggest fears. Certainly fence-jump material. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[where’s the Esquire profile of the first generation Asian American kid who knows what he can’t do, but also knows w… https://t.co/WDLEJ3uJRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to 1 crying daughter and one with #omg. Still is good to be Dave ? https://t.co/VTBOdYzqGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC almost Sade Baderinwa ❤️ just random come here You know who Sade Baderinwa is? Oh yeah. Aight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting day for slcemeraldbelles_ ! Ready for @agt Best of luck to @kathrynlark and all of the @varsitybelles. A h… https://t.co/CBfvrG8Nuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonGoalie31 @THNJaredClinton @TheHockeyNews 2 Lindberghs. Our Oscar, their Tobias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[and hopefull and don't dwell on negative things or things i can't control i cannot change anyone's opinion of me bu… https://t.co/86YT6x1cv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes You're a grown man eating dinner. Why do you want a straw? Are you a toddler?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuryTanya Live the photos of @NCHSCardinals having a great time at the Winter Formal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting stories, great laughter, deep passions...what a great way to end the weekend: sharing dinner and conversat… https://t.co/QVAgi2St7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Secret_Vent I'll watch it with you and hold your hand at the scary parts lol😯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmzcustomz @brandonbeckky3 @KY3MariaNeider Glasses Friday... it's trending!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revolutionary at the time, but I’ve never seen anyone jump any other way. Proof of how effective Fosbury flop is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[House been on fire for 20 mins and the fire department just showed up lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nor has it taken a position on the NCAA’s outrageous penalties against Missouri. Come on SEC, show some guts!  #MIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can not control my laughter, @rollcall just lost all credibility. @ScottPresler have you seen this article yet. “Am… https://t.co/LdQ7QTv5Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeasOfEmbers Oh goodness, that was for you at all. Frustrations with some work related people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/MYxiSvE1W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I just found out @CinnamonGhoul goes to UCF? So like when can we get a beer and crap on the Raimi films?]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Long Beach: broken clouds, 55°F 62% humidity, wind 6mph, pressure 1016mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ujullu Obang with the SLAM! This @CWOSSABball semis is heating up!! @NorthPoleHoops #GameSpeaks https://t.co/iv2BDjUyfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyFirstHockeyMemory was playing minor house league #hockey and wearing my uncle's old football pants and shoulder… https://t.co/GKcYxB776f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamateyko @taricoariel Un honor imitar a Mateyko y hacer este video junto al gran @taricoariel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AQueerPanda @KaelanRhy I follow for Validation.   Validation Morghulis. https://t.co/Kv0nPVh9y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[asi es fuera esas 🐀🐀 #LasHijasDeLaMx   tienen podrida la mente seguro estan despechadas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Typical Democrat/leftist/progressive narcissism on display for all to see. They don’t give a rat’s… https://t.co/UfQDMsfBKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should lock her up and throw away the key.  She's damaged goods and dangerous.  ‘All I want to do is come home… https://t.co/GhC2BwFY5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robertson again! This time BTB from Brad Smith. This offense is cooking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 minutes in and three opposition players have already slipped on the surface of the stadium formerly known as Avaya #Quakes74 #SJvMTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our final #BlackHistoryMonth story @abcWNN! Incredible job by our producers @BrianaKStewart and Gentrix Shanga for… https://t.co/JIpJLTwA5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbrogan Learn to grind your own. It is best that way or have a reliable butcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s probably marks the beginning of the end for MA. Only chance to save his job is winning the SEC Tournament, and I hate that. #wps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ian_Fraser Opinions as a political analyst would seem out of scope, but there must've been some quirming in the se… https://t.co/mbREqXYWpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate chip pancakes double fried in bacon fat topped with peanut butter and bananas! Oh also a top shelf lunch… https://t.co/WepmL9n7gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirtbagdom first pic is from elder scrolls online, second is pokemon anime lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice feel here to take it outside. Steps out around the 15 but was a hair away from the house call. https://t.co/A6kDXUvNSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who will help me in telling Congress that they need to reunite the US citizens with their loved ones who are found… https://t.co/hmjaxdMEbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gartmanreport @FoxBusiness @stewvarney I’ve said it for many years, we need to purge our education system of the s… https://t.co/LbAxekbgDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga Bradley Cooper + Lady Gaga = ❤ Together Performing Shallow 🎶 #Oscars #Oscars2019 #BradleyCooper #LadyGaga… https://t.co/fU37dAKSGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #Milwaukee #brewers team 1965-2016, position players.  https://t.co/4ps528uSTQ … … … https://t.co/ENNitPsUHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseMOrdonez1 What is mentA-L illness stAndards in different NATIONS WHAT is A-men, Amen, Amend...Amer i c A… https://t.co/A9xXUO1mty]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is definitely not an intersquad, but someone didn’t tell the clubs that. #SpringTrainingForEveryone https://t.co/hHLInis2Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, my phone is definitely listening. I talked with my mom and sister about how it’s been 20 years since graduatio… https://t.co/CWhNUphW2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign On: 5 Ideas for Reforming our Justice System https://t.co/VJxzrAaGYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleMorenoESPN please please please DO NOT pick my Spurs to win the NLD on Saturday. Thank you. #vamosvenezuela]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Monday, let’s get to work 😊#mondays #dance #minneapolis #gucci @ Saint Paul, Minnesota https://t.co/aZUEDSluGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawyer for Cohen raised pardon with Trump attorneys following FBI raid: report https://t.co/6LebXryZ4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LeavingNeverland even if you don't think he was a pedophile, ask yourself this question what grown man acts like a… https://t.co/U2hPJRFES2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Albania #follow #like4like #tagsforlikes #instalike #likeforlike #follow4follow #followforfollow #l4l #f4f… https://t.co/5uSYf4dU1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[90210 IS COMING BACK! 90210 IS COMING BACK! 90210 IS COMING BACK! 90210 IS COMING BACK! @90210onFOX https://t.co/z5kNUqpHyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone would’ve done that when I worked retail I woulda hit, “ shit, you wanna cover my shift tomorrow molly?” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside each of us, there is the seed of both good and evil. It's a constant struggle as to which one will win, and… https://t.co/Fve4cfJWyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen To Your Boy @raydanielsshow Right Now On Power 96.5 FM WUFO NEW YORK @power965wny go here outside of Buffalo… https://t.co/2rdbSNii1A]]></document></documents></author>