<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Guess what? I believe North Korean's Minister Ri Yong Ho's summary of the talks (number of lifted… https://t.co/b9XKx2xLEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been feeling like an unproductive slug for weeks, but then I looked at some of what I've painted so far this year https://t.co/jPFrrQUnOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Wayne is blasting on virtually every corner of New Orleans and I think this is the culture I’ve been missing my entire life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a few simple travel traditions that I try to stick to anytime I visit a new place as a reminder that work is… https://t.co/IHC9K6gz9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[question about the vignette data: was formatted to specify black female or male doctors because people assume white… https://t.co/kvC222B8aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utah students are amazing but especially students in #DECA. Great job Utah CTE! Thank you to amazing sponsors as we… https://t.co/sdbAyS40x5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flcnhvy @elonmusk @AstroAnnimal lol I ordered ”Moon” from Amazon bc Earth was sold out. Mars is also available... https://t.co/NAh3uOCfiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy right? #funniness #laugh #grin #hilarious https://t.co/gRfORmaftU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittyAmnezia Business has been that great! Or have you been on vacation or playing an awesome game?😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CajPaLa @Chernynkaya @TwitterSupport @FoundationWohl Temporarily suspended. Good work. Hopefully this will be permanent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debating on if I want to move this summer or the fall 🤔🤔 @Victoria_Valice]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Poshmarkapp began, @Tracy_Sun personally built the first community of 200 members and took it on digital plat… https://t.co/8IiWA8rIt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone! I am home from my family vacation!  Will be streaming later today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[our green shirts actually work tonight #fattuesday @ Brass Rail https://t.co/xbi9H6f2LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonBream Very much so. Especially the folks in Lynchburg.  Miss that “y’all come back now!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC SOCIALISM is an economic system where the value made belongs to everyone in that society, instead of a group o… https://t.co/M8PlyCVzRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Oglala Lakota. They only call us in when shit gets seriously fucked up. https://t.co/4qrnDuvA6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #positivevibes #positivequotes #positivethinking #youwillsucceed @ Connecticut https://t.co/DcC88J5dZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Occupational therapy. (@ North Shore Medical Group Professional Building in Evanston, IL) https://t.co/84r54VkBiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got wedding plans? We would love to photograph your day!  Shouldn't weddings be fun? Let us take the worry out of y… https://t.co/lILKHq9sMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Family Day from the DBars! 👩🏻🧔🏻👦🏻🐯 #blessedbeyondmeasure #FamilyDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seeing LP at the Fox tonight. There are some (very nice) young women in MY SPOT. I’m incensed! How dare anyone… https://t.co/yjCyq8M86a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniewilkins04 @CarissaR_NG That’s good I actually exercise through a program on YouTube called Fitness Blender.… https://t.co/CXYxwQhHst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help if you can. Your dollar will go even further to help my kids!!Donations to my classroom are currently b… https://t.co/uLb99HLCdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly don’t know if I should just buy a California King and stay with a 1bd because this co-sleeping thing is… https://t.co/djrJnGAKBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @TrumpOutNow He calls everything he doesn’t like collusion.  Do you think he understands what it means?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Build the wall, close the southern border.  There is a legal process to enter the U.S..  What abou… https://t.co/UVQBXmDkZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shareblue @NancySinatra I thought we were suppose to help every one not scam n lie to them n they wonder why peopl… https://t.co/NFjHFmYVR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decades after Roe, black women are still denied reproductive justice  https://t.co/OMaptcgfAG via @phillydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @karyoly53 Yolanda, good to hear from you! We thought the worst was over! It seems the fight with “d… https://t.co/ilZmVhRqe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't this mouse pad the cutest? I couldn't resist getting my precious poogle's picture on something else! mypetcan… https://t.co/z0eXV41bPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the smartest and some of the most educated people I know (not necessarily an overlap with those groups) hav… https://t.co/XTPi6MCmMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the plus side I can now say I was the first one up for doughnut Friday 🙌🏼🍩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ultrahottie2000 @MJ_JustSayin This is how boring Sarah/Rex/Eric are https://t.co/6d7HsJzL9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying goodbye properly to our fantastic holidays in Florida (USA) enjoying de Bayside Market Place 🤗🍺👨‍👩‍👧 (@ sega… https://t.co/Nw5IUqT5U3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InvisibleMiriam Claro si fuera de otra manera no sería Miriam contra viento y marea]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear @russdiemon music be having u str8 up in ur feelings... #PsychoPt2 https://t.co/uEByCd36GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to this tweet, which I am very much in love with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fairy_sherlock @astudyinsnoggy @almosttomorocco You’re welcome to fly to America &amp; join us Anna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHMattSimon @stratham_dems His opposition to legalization of cannabis was precisely why he was appointed Chair of… https://t.co/SALZnJJ8l4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moi qui regarde mon chum en lui disant que je l'sais qui vient de lâcher un pet. ⬇️ https://t.co/CFh6SDD731]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to dierks bentley saturday night and this is how I fully expect to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TH3R34LTRUTH @AlexWY18 @fellspeaks @basedinfidel8 @JayCory7 @Chriskl70208387 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy @johnw299… https://t.co/KRuXSYNMlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[From one Chihuahua owner to the next...🐶❤  This warmed my heart so much.😍 #BFF #HuMansBestFriend #judgejudy  #Dog… https://t.co/Hh2ofQdG3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DShadowgazer Now my mind went blank. I’ve met a lot of drs with weird last names in my life and now I can’t think of anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take time and visit resources around campus! Leave for a meeting a little earlier and stop into an office to say he… https://t.co/T35qMAZ84N]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's fine, Michigan is going to make it to the Final Four while State will get eliminated in the second round again ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked the Lord for a reason to get out of bed, and he send a ducking moth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 “Kidney Surgery” (Read: Plastic Surgery). Look at her pics. Before “kidney surgery” she had a lot of lines… https://t.co/9D0Vu1k701]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attacking someone because they are a Trump supporter doesn’t ever turn out well for the attacker! Especially if you… https://t.co/WyvJvZdASY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You have better lips than most white people” is one of my fav compliments]]></document><document><![CDATA[I having for breakfast scrambled eggs grits with cheese bacon and waffles with syrup @ Providence, Rhode Island https://t.co/F1RF4iq0Az]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would hurt my wrist right before my spring break trip. The life of Jazmin,  siempre algo man....😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wednesday #words of #wisdom — #thankyou Joseph Pilates! 🙏🏻💜 @ Pure Pilates https://t.co/VcC22ydK7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is no pasta kitchen. She’s gonna need some serious counter space #HGTVHomeTown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying out goggles (again) for swimming tonight | 6 March 19  #littlefish #hesgettingthere @lompocaquaticcenter… https://t.co/iqi9cPyoJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#farmers #conservation  #naturalresources #cleanair  #nuclearsafety  Farmer representation. Retweet. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWBunch It’s only been half an hour. So much pressure. https://t.co/QNcCwrRvra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the great group who joined @SESchorr and me this pm to talk personnel files and risk management at… https://t.co/tFshh6imix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYounker @findhorror @PromoteHorror @QueenHalloweenW @bringbackfear @isaacrthorne @crashpalace @GothGirlVonDark… https://t.co/IjWCAY0scu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just here to provide CO weather updates to all of my followers...in NC 😂 #newish #almostayear https://t.co/eU0HZoAE9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also forgot to point out that at dinner some dude tried to claim that Messi is underrated lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueSNRadvisor This is just the time to vet our candidates. Once they have run the gauntlet, they are tougher and… https://t.co/iDRCP7gqB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just received my DNA results from @Ancestry and I have more Native American DNA then @ewarren. You can call me Pocahontas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ima take my baby on a date Friday&amp; Saturday 😊 we going have fun 👩‍👧🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elistrawman02 @Charles_BSwans @Xnarakax @Stardust_1416 @sweettina2 Some people I don't give 1 second too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday night at the @MilwRep to see The Chinese Lady. #TheChineseLadyMKE  is the story of Afong Moy, America’s firs… https://t.co/UIvjIIGhdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stcrawford2 @KingaSurmaMPP Here’s my ??-how does the rest of the province feel about having to pay for Toronto’s t… https://t.co/iELuGIsjWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Move successfully completed! It was a cold weekend! Back to sunny Florida. @ Memphis, Tennessee https://t.co/XQHeQybyTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apetivist It is extremely hard for me to do that. Going through what I did and seeing my friends going thru hell b… https://t.co/Erkzrta4AB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timriggins28 @AOC @bungarsargon What's inappropriate? They don't fight for anti POC insults but questioning suppor… https://t.co/vOBVYYrWI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anyabeth Eff that. My (autistic) son took quite some time to use the toilet but he is a gift to the world. I feel… https://t.co/UNkv7PvBs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eb36675c19f5405 @realDonaldTrump Won’t happen and no not majorly, President Trump is doing God’s agenda for the wo… https://t.co/SwE6iigflN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evankirstel (Flat earthers run from this picture screaming "Photoshopped! Photoshopped!")]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SeaRocketChapter member Nancy Blissett-Clark is speaking at Fort Cooper State Park about "Bat Houses: Where the Ba… https://t.co/CwGSklmaED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLuVCS @Twitter @n_blanco22 @delandbulldogs @IB_Bulldogs @MrsNunezVCS @MrsCSGreen @dcasanova001 @LouAnnMoffatt Beautiful! 💚💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewKMedia Hi Drew, we have vast experience in mobile app development and would be happy to assist you in building… https://t.co/en6SfW1Bqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really pray for Eli’s family because this is just the most horrible accident I’ve heard of it breaks my heart 💔 #RIPELI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there Anything that this man Won’t lie about?  (Unbelievable that people believe him, trust him, support him)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_ridenour Drew is the one who’s been wanting to come to Liz to check to see how she and boys are doing; he and… https://t.co/LNcdZf1kIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can find me sitting court side at the @chicagobulls game tonight! 🔥❤️🖤👌🏼 #BullsNation #TeamArchi @RyArch15 #30thBirthday @gelorton]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t always dress up at work, but when I do it’s because I have nothing else to wear in my wardrobe. 🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/xeplXPOFWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorrlynnn18 girl thank you 😭 it’s taken a lot of change &amp; time to get where i’m at 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_ntd @DiscoveryCSC It took them 18 years to find enough people who were remotely affiliated with academia or s… https://t.co/nlh4y2qR8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to my daughter ⁦@mikesassmith⁩ running in her 7th marathon today in Austin in 5 minutes. I feel another B… https://t.co/mJCVIQTM1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a blast! #Oscars2019 #NeverLookAway #WerkOhneAutor #wiedemannundberg @filmedienrw https://t.co/JyPjSsMtLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #chestersprings #chestercounty @ Chester Springs, Pennsylvania https://t.co/MuFSmTY8Cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisonkestrel @calacademy @inaturalist @RebaFay @MicrobeExplorer @carrieseltzer @ArachnologyNerd @CASBirdman Yay s… https://t.co/cMlXBOerU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoSwagLihh @_reyeskimberly @Etelvinaa__ @enriquescooter Asuu, Tia mora gonna whoop my ass 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I don't understand how are people so DUMB!  Trump signs Bibles in Alabama🤮🤮🤮🤮🤮🤮🤮🤮🤮 https://t.co/yEstjMv2jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Red_Ehredt Outrageous? Yes. Out rage us? Never. 🚩 #RB4L #RedbirdTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both Mary-Beth Tomaselli and Linda Roberts have been charged with murder in the first degree. We will have the full… https://t.co/IGnfjCxNU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why I paid $1,063 for mocha’s tooth to be pulled to be told by the vet exactly a week later “i’m starting t… https://t.co/WIonSkTQVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg @MTV_NellyT in the confessional in the lobster costume 🤣🤣🤣 Jay caught him off guard. #dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did Gaetz get info on Cohen's affairs?  Tweet sounded like it was dictated by Trump before he left for Vietnam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @RedSaintPotion No sweetheart YOU are abhorrent and unacceptable..such a tool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delissio making 1/2 pepperoni and 1/2 cheese?? I fixed it though... https://t.co/JD5VquHpkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who You Say I Am - Hillsong Worship https://t.co/1fmifP131i via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t understand this and I won’t try to. It’s God’s timing and I just have to follow it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your clothes on, ya dirty hippie! Nobody wants to see what you're selling, yo. For real.]]></document></documents></author>