<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Annnnd, the @JoeyBats19 bat-flat has found its way into hockey! #Bluejays]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I have to see the original Frozen now so I don’t get too far behind in the Disney Cinematic Universe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swardley Interesting. I have, and irregularly use, several dozen of these for irregularly needed items that save m… https://t.co/JPwA29jF56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because too many of the Republicans are part of the swamp. They would all be stepping up to defend our president an… https://t.co/xnWWBZlqoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooof. I’m tired. Give me that hour of sleep back... #dst https://t.co/Zj0wZng8lP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach lily.... what’s the warmup : 1000 reps for time! GO! Well.... she is the boss.... #preyingmatus #mission22… https://t.co/YjpuvOD8Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh &amp; BTW . . .  veracity's stock is nudging up in Rome? It's been suffering a few crises Stateside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @jamietrexler We should be so lucky, but I am sure we’d rather see him rot in jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of GREAT stuff being sharing in hour 1 of @NJAHPERD! @CoachFoe, @foes4sports and @AdventureEdGuy all doing the… https://t.co/r7imvZ9You]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureneoneal @k_a_aitch I remember you commenting transcripts problems with your stat class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMikeH49 @LomaahhMore @adamcbest @CarlyPildis Of course. You are absolutely right about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No that’s weird asf why we dating if u would grind on another nigga or dance period conversation period anything th… https://t.co/h4Q4z5XSLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson You sound like Stalin. You keep trying to discredit our most respected journalistic… https://t.co/oxjtbbXWI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @anthemgame Yes he is. That was just one play. The season is 82 games...👊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealVladivostok A lack of safeguards doesn't make a system more secure. It only makes Fraud harder to detect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to get up sometimes when #tinyhumans unofficially assign you as their designated head rest. #ZenFrancisMacatol… https://t.co/5FfP0vGZTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back from Rosauers at about 7 with the Black Bag.  " Day I Die " The National on Spotify going in the Background wh… https://t.co/HafxZklMKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome experience covering the US Poker Open and meeting some great people this week. The game of poker is alive a… https://t.co/NKSzaDbBcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Per @JimRosvold, longtime college hockey referee C.J. Beaurline (currently in the Big 10) is retiring after this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoDatFishin @bigbearrods @Lews_Fishing @TUFLineOfficial @Line_Cutterz @bayoubugjigs @CajunLures excellent!! 👊👍🎣🤘☠️🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_man951 @FunnyGuyEv @eortega06 No Evan is just an idiot.  Acting like Flacco had legit threats to throw to after… https://t.co/vXb3f22BVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The main track at @santaanitapark sits empty on what was supposed to be a busy and historic race day. I’ll have the… https://t.co/nuMQRiEdd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Never Had One we are doing it in 2020 on our ten year. We were young with a newborn son.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDannyGoodwin @AlexTachalova @Casieg @navahf @JulieJoyce @wonderwall7 @jennyhalasz @SEOAware @JuliaEMcCoy… https://t.co/SNP8UWOuJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't be emotional when it comes to destiny decisions. @CherylSMoore @kairos_mke #crucibles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridget_joy_ Trump is the national emergency and domestic threat to America and we need to call and flood the Russ… https://t.co/w4E9NGXJyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Build the wall hurry. Do it before they come back and keep their butt’s out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbeeboyy Some people experience fender euphoria vs gender dysphoria  So they would rather prefer being perceived a… https://t.co/EyB8kToEJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supermarket Keeps Retraining Employee Living with Alzheimer’s so She Can Continue Working https://t.co/A9atteTa7n via @alywalansky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @CraigSBPA I think they should just stick to asking how to make a drink because she definitely doesn… https://t.co/NKr4r1QBvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got 55 hours in Anthem, have gotten my Storm up to Ilevel 488 Masterwork and am still finding fun and enjoyabl… https://t.co/Dzz6Z6eCpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been a couch potato ever before, but just a couple of times today lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on @SUBWAY it’s 2019, there should be baby changing tables in your bathrooms. Smh 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattThompson87 @sonnylax Sorry to jump in and reply. But I only follow the cool people...who are quality snarky basketball fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving 100mph to the Crib.... this Thunder ain’t gone catch me lackinn at a light Ya heErrr 🚗💨💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t sleep last night looking forward to today and ended up sleeping 2 hours. It’s going to be an early night😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the mood for a scary movie on RedBox..Anyone seen The Nun?? Is it scary??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus Yeah plus he’s doing a great job with Germany...Merkel’s speech in front of the first ladydaughter il… https://t.co/FrGgFsb8Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewF Wow that’s something... you really just be 100% now... you never know the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.J. Barrett went 1 for 7 shooting in the first half, missed all 5 3-point attempts and finished with 4 points. In… https://t.co/h44oNGjUrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskerMan4Life @rachelvigil24 @WACsports @CBUmbb @CSUB_MBB @ChicagoStateMBB @GCU_MBB @NMStateMBB @seattleumbb… https://t.co/TTcxqUvKvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these takes on the preferential ballot make me conclude that after 10 years, a lot of you still don’t know… https://t.co/DaP89PrXEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usually my days at work are boring or good, but today I’m about to hit someone 😒😒😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pushing an agenda under the guise of diversity has been driven into our Corporations, using HR to eliminate any emp… https://t.co/TIN0NF8qJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @CBS EMANCIPATE the INFANT. No soldier will say its not my war. https://t.co/273iYkUOc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @AEWrestling sold out in 4 minutes. I was wondering how long until it sold out. I am really looking forward to… https://t.co/RwfdFZKisE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apinkglitter Wedding rings stay on is hot! So is honesty and communication!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyron Woodley has a moment with the new UFC title yesterday at media day. I should have asked him what he said to t… https://t.co/OXDYMOXT6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LI0NHEAR7 @CarrieWilbur1 @ScottWalker The fact that you think a medium post from a Luke Thompson is what’s in the… https://t.co/ZMQkykTQyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Process_31 @_RPACollege @jdempsey_RPA @HelveyCorey Congratulations bro..welcome to the family]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I’ve ever screamed as loud as I did for @poppy Poppy when she came on stage! I was at the front!! Sti… https://t.co/moKg3MxwUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are always disappointing. Taking out a huge portion of the field, and we won’t get to see nearly as good of a… https://t.co/On2FtkPKrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @Happy19111 @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1 @billcrowley3rd @Flavio72162205… https://t.co/wcabCEE2gP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The feeling you get when you see the person you really like is crazy the way you feel when they text you never gets… https://t.co/2R3vcrs3ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just saw @Danb119 omg i just wanna kick it with him all the time 🧡 https://t.co/wRkuY12HPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey if you haven't had the chance to catch a live show in a while, I'm doing a free Facebook live concert tonight a… https://t.co/cQCji2uZMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @justicedems @PramilaJayapal @SenSanders The destruction of democracy is the agenda of The Justice Democra… https://t.co/WT4rJjH7XT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slissethhh_ @_Sierraaax My boy is making it, if he got shot by the black hood and survived. A little stroke ain’t gonna stop him]]></document><document><![CDATA[why would I want to be fashionable, that’s the easiest thing in the world to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[My perfect Gaming snack are Blueberry pop-tarts, big pick of skittles,  40 oz sprite soda, and Metro Exodus and Resident Evil 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar If you mean phone calls, in my case I probably answer about 10 % of the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xjay84x @ItsTeedz @JohnHillbery Nobody is forcing them to play sports. How about they do like most college kids an… https://t.co/e5Dvx6lqLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Better question.  Who's just tierd of hearing about the fu$$ing wall How about they do things to help… https://t.co/QgPd2R8zQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LosCampesinos If you come back to North Carolina I'd be eternally grateful! We traveled for DC and Boston. And it… https://t.co/9LK0gBPycp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlyntleedom Just a busy day and lack of help is all. I appreciate you for checking on me 😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LA_Swiftness @drivelinebases If only there was a way to toss a ball super slowly by hand!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy B-Day Mickey Housely and congrats on #mickelylodeonfest (@ Joke Joint Comedy Club in Houston, TX) https://t.co/RZtsADiQbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drvox This isn’t the east method. Fly into jfk or LaGuardia, take the subway or car to grand central, take a train… https://t.co/G8YkF8ubOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaveByKorenar It was a gamble but a good one... No one could have predicted him to be what he was in college football this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop reposting pictures u already posted type beat https://t.co/7LfZHWGfFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.#mnwild post.   @Stalock32 ...”when your’re not winning you get a little pissed off.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpMindQrime @paulsperry_ You call yourself an American while you scoff at everything it mea s to be an American. A… https://t.co/vW4RmZR4o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeeJoe_Allen @EriksensuaI @MaddisonNoah @PremLeaguePanel He actually said the exact opposite and had Hughes been a… https://t.co/pvk7Hevp0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting sports connection as Parks and Rec was co-created (among several other great TV shows) by former "Fire… https://t.co/hU92NuhxCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coco_montes @TBTimes_Bulls @SoFloBulls @USFBaseball @GatorsBB “Staff” day boy smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMEN and God bless WORLD have a great day don't forget to SMILE @DennisJBolt 🔱⚡BOLTIBOLTZ CAN'T STOP WON'T STOP Be… https://t.co/LzEQaO8nJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else’s phone glitching? Like shaking when you try to scroll? https://t.co/8S9O3uxdrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeStehn @thehill Ahahahahahaha.....it's just the new math...it only looks like it's more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of Math on the "Planes" here in Colorado with @steve_leinwand. About 80 of us from in and around the state ar… https://t.co/4WZuMxYAHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son influence dans le manque de redressement 😂😭😭 ! Les Lakers ont un bilan aussi catastrophique parce qu’il a été a… https://t.co/OXX3gZLpYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@discordquads oh no i ***LOVE*** the music. T Bone is The Man. just maybe some music is Too Interesting Stylistical… https://t.co/IyX1dYLsIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDo77900635 Thanks for Following! Like a good spy thriller novel or know someone who does? Please check my aut… https://t.co/HixxISIzaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the FDLA shows experience! Get your tickets today!  Go to https://t.co/VwHGMdCaQu  . NYFW is around the corner… https://t.co/5dOM9jPdtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing about this guy that can’t be argued is his level of consistency to stick to his narrative no matter how o… https://t.co/wLPAmKvuxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katnapersden Just, wow...  I simply do not get people so much of the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robotmonkypants I guess that’s the thing.  If I couldn’t go and couldn’t sell my seat  or even give it away, I def… https://t.co/R1nAv8Rmz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @CNN @ABC @LowranceAlice For 2 weeks all you hear is comments about Empire actor Jussie Smollett, yet not on… https://t.co/pRyP2XNZXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErrataRob You'd be dissatisfied if he got only the second best legal representation?  This is such an absurd statement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell How about #M4A, literally his legislation? Doesn't that help cut down on Black maternal death rates?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys played well today. Way to go Big G!  #hardworkpaysoff #Teamwork #HoopLife https://t.co/udpOFmllwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@decmckenna3 from the archives. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/OEs67UDwtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_siepman @RRidley11 @Cricrifi @miket136 @iamIqraKhalid The people objecting have 12 followers. Bot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris you, have a greater chance of intercepting at ports of entry, than along an open boarder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SERIOUSLY WHAT. 1: guns aren’t for piercings and 2, that’s an earring??¿ https://t.co/hiCbMGRKCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YardHouse @VancityReynolds  can I get one of those virtual high fives to go along with my favorite gin? https://t.co/hkbwEarhuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirty Boots: A Column of Critical Thinking, Border Crossing, and Noblesse Oblige https://t.co/yetUjqAxsS https://t.co/5hs3jClU8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MahirPropheT Seems to be. Long range is when u notice its not the same other than that seems fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[About a year ago, @iCarly_Rose took a baseball to the face (@SimmerJimmer7) within her first month at Furman. Since… https://t.co/Q8OfLZMWkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @Nicole_Cliffe At least your mom is insanely cool. Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumb holds Phillies down to 3rd place, or lower. (Includes Rice Barper)]]></document></documents></author>