<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@morganmpage My transition was relatively trauma free.  Yeah, I planned it out well, and I was lucky, too. But most… https://t.co/5lngtkcMgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest pill I had to swallow was learning that no matter how good you could be to somebody,no matter how much… https://t.co/S2iDOa7tSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Sales Coordinator Exterior - https://t.co/9J7TPVKncs #Sales #Alexandria, VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOLUNTEERS_TN Equivocation and false dilemma 🤣 but keep trying though one day you’ll make a good argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can tell a lot about a person’s character by whether or not they clear the snow off of their car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE MARC IS LIT, ESKETIT I MISS RAVING (too bad I’m not rolling, but I’m drunk?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank GOD I have an unusually high threshold for pain ... I don’t know how regular people or weak folks would feel… https://t.co/O8VozOCFXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[La campaña ÚNETE administrada por ONU Mujeres, ha proclamado el día 25 de cada mes como “Día Naranja”: un día para… https://t.co/brnIOf59O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can have an in tact manicure or you can peel crawfish but you can’t have both]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yhazony No one trust lawyers very much. Think about their public image: they go to @SCOTUS to argue that babies in… https://t.co/HZjBmfnaUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike got me 2- 2 dozen roses and when I asked him why he said “because I love you twice as much” I really have one… https://t.co/DCTJXf48oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Wehner @JohnJHarwood They act like frat boys. My son says to me, "In Trump World, Malkin is an anchor baby,… https://t.co/Q11NlO58oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't get what the hype for those bang energy drinks is ...not impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriargroveES #springbreak2019 visiting US Naval Academy. Impressive place! Grateful for those who serve our countr… https://t.co/trJYzctiul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trOJans_SUCk @TheBigDisco The way we are playing we are going to fck around and be in the lottery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @hjhollis93 @NGDAverk… https://t.co/x79O8OR3K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin is, no doubt, very beautiful &amp; intelligent. However, her thinking is always one sided… https://t.co/IJrdMGuoX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Prepping” I’ve failed😅 @ La Feria Wildlife And Nature Park https://t.co/0t503OIAEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @kstreet111 And the Director of Elections in Utah said when A Parent fills out their Missionary's voting… https://t.co/1KgF4aQluL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyH21 Good to know.. He did tell me to put my paws on you when I’m at the airport tomorrow... lol I told him I’d spare you 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[You r right David. If #DonaldJTrump signs this disastrous Bill, then is he the brave warrior we thought we elected.… https://t.co/pwEML0sglE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__kaewmanee @RandyDntShootEm Yea period you hood boujie ass nigga lmao https://t.co/uEo2pmPE1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know campaign season is fully underway when you see someone with  headphones in that’s not connected to anything 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My small baggage today is that it’s 10:40am and already have had a booger wiped on me. My large baggage would for s… https://t.co/STuX8rNeLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiffany Tygart Tygart crossed 5K. Time 00:59:17, pace 19:05 min/mile, est. finish 7:39 am https://t.co/f11SrlQDa3 #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson Sixth Grade:  It was the best of times, and it was the worst of times 🤓 https://t.co/dwuToSGrHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early voting in the special election runoff for Texas House District 125 starts TODAY. Tell folks you know who live… https://t.co/H5bqm8CUrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a snowy Friday night downtown. #Denver #Colorado https://t.co/lpl619O1O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbooH2O Real life, almost called the doc back for a pink eye note instead]]></document><document><![CDATA[So so proud of my favorite human and mentor @natimontelongo!! She represents the very best of Texas and Julián is l… https://t.co/Muie4aiU0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodiewill2 @SpaceX @NASAKennedy @elonmusk @NASAJPL @NASA Wish I could! Next one 😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are all these men from my past coming from. Time to go big time bitch mode. Leave me alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharpTusk @MeredithCD @the_foot_wedge @RazorHog66 @golfnhogs @lydialynne @lorismith73 @IowaHog @SpfldHog https://t.co/w1xtytXrJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsaddison2 @mrjdaher @BarrhavenJan @StBenedictOCSB @BenedictParents We are women, hear us ROAR!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣 Trump installed a room-sized golf simulator at the White House, Washington Post reports  https://t.co/UTTyLXdwdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recap of a conversation I just had w a random girl in the dorm elevator:  Her: you go to the gym here a lot, right?… https://t.co/JTxxEOm5Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STLinOK If you want to hit the gym, let me know! That’s my mental health release! Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PTM ya me quiero dormir 😩, pero hace rato: otro café sin azúcar y con crema 😪🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the City Wax Boutiques WE ❤️ A DEAL ! Book now!  24/7 ONLINE BOOKING  Marietta GA https://t.co/0gHkCblxbp… https://t.co/Go7e18jnG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjrr76 Que te puedo decir.... ahí seguirá el régimen 4ever con la gente restando en lugar de sumar. No entienden q… https://t.co/ssIZeIq9H5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @realDonaldTrump 20 hours to muck shit up for the American people.  Then he spends 4 hours dreaming… https://t.co/SIZF2u6Tca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeld31 The OKC Phil is performing the entire score while the movie plays in March! It should be wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DidlyDennie You should be asleep. Don’t want mommy and daddy to ground you for being up past your bedtime do ya? 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch all of the madness at @goldennuggetac’s Sportsbook March 19-April 8! What #finalfour teams are you betting on… https://t.co/hQ6ISk7DNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the road to @amsupdates can't wait to see @JimmieJohnson on the track in the @allyracing car! #CHASING8 #partyintheinfield]]></document><document><![CDATA[Urgent: Protect the North Arm Trails! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/xTIxHtdTqD via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfierce78 Antonio Brown and those who support his actions during the past year insult my intelligence. Without fan… https://t.co/FFTZaWWgJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annefrankhouse and the new cue is going in the wrong direction 😬😔 https://t.co/xMoU1pvvy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @uofmemphis women’s basketball team with a great road win against @Tulane; warming up for @UConnWBB this week.  🏀🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dating ish is annoying. Damn near asking me all these questions before we meet...tf we supposed to talk about… https://t.co/re9tny2zjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oml Jacob keeps asking what's so funny 😂 from the other room. My side hurts. 😑🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraedenCounts From what I’ve gathered from my research it’s probably just an ENORMOUS coincidence...... JL was a h… https://t.co/DKgwmh3Azb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciakeys Alicia you were amazing as the host of the Grammys. You beautiful heart ♥️ shows through!! God bless yo… https://t.co/jhVVPP4rVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicate Flower Donald Trump Whines on Twitter Over His SNL Portrayal https://t.co/A9IDD1tmQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Utility A" at HMSHost, then look for people you might know at the comp… https://t.co/bIxLMjgmb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LivingMyBestLife #OneDayAtATime #ILoveMyLife #BestFeelingEver #IAmSober #Truth #ODAAT @ Positive Vibes Only https://t.co/lZvnYPLXJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my math lovers: a Desmos Math-o-gram! https://t.co/o7xWhECgHs via @desmos Happy Valentine’s Day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect chart that just sprung from a conversation I was trying to describe about the Mango Mussolini 👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is doing what David Koresh did at Waco and what Jim Jones did at Jonestown: he's destroying his people by ref… https://t.co/alL6hAgcaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know they say there are no stupid questions... but this right here ?!?!? Are u fucking kidding me?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airplane ticket to Eugene ✅ Rental car to @OregonWBB house ✅ @UCLAWBB victory ✅ Still feeling #AMileHigh Way to rep… https://t.co/E8FcWE7DzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke to passengers in #Florida  who are frustrated. No way home. Ticket prices are sky rocketing by the second. Ev… https://t.co/lSoCDQE07p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/bBEW9xYnj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never cared for Prada or Gucci but if the dollar tree store ever do some racist shit I’m really going to be upset! Happy Wednesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you look up at night when the skies are clear, look up at the stars and say, wow, that is so beautiful? So...inf… https://t.co/K172lE8ZuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #MSUPLN! Whitney York here,  Digital Learning Coach (or TIS) at @murrayschools! Twitter is a phenomenal way to… https://t.co/U1Qo2UYT6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molly_knight @Jim_Jordan Every question or stmt. by GOP they were all like...AH HA...GOTCHA! But they SO didn’t do… https://t.co/xc9er7iLfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaRiaCat @Jim_Jordan I am overjoyed we have moved away from having troops lined up on the north and South Korean… https://t.co/fJT4DKHBlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLueCrew I do my laundry on the weekends and a load or two during the week we have about 15-20 towels. Summer ti… https://t.co/JRszrAjgO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Arts And Science Center in Independence, MO https://t.co/wf1sAm0VHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I talked to Missouri lawmakers about their plans to fix the state’s roads and bridges.  @KOMUnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I was on a call with NASA today about Lady Rocket possible venture which could qualify for Moon Mission ! Fly m… https://t.co/JcYFZglBr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcuban Not my ? to answer BUT the tax deductions for parents paying for college are archaic. Single mother has to… https://t.co/sLw8BgD8yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed dancing like a fool to music in my very own room AH spring break ily]]></document><document><![CDATA[if @realDonaldTrump is such a good “business” man then why does his administration have such a high turnover rate]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tatiana is in #Charleston #SouthCarolina Maritime Center on her #RoyalCaribbean 🚢. https://t.co/yMWBfUwCjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have to try their #local #beer. Pretzel bites coming. - Drinking an Anti-Hero by @revbrewchicago at @elephantcastle… https://t.co/OjKMoIToj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MengiKuldip @GenPanwar @chutorjan @Jungle_View @better_delhincr @devendratiwary3 @ajitsinghpundir @PNRATHOD1… https://t.co/eYPXmPVaCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopTrump2020 @MeMySylvanEye @realDonaldTrump YOU HAVE GOLFED 171 TIMES SINCE COMING INTO OFFICE AND SPENT MILLION… https://t.co/iW8rQVC31I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attorney Lee Rothman wraps up his closingg arguments in the sex assault case against his client, former Istanbul So… https://t.co/9WvfEcWkpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been so long since I've touched the wanting hand I'll put my love on the line Yes I hope you'll understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're at TOLO, Tigers. Where are you? 🐯 @Mrs_Etulain and I rocking the furs! @bghs_utc tigersasb . @ Battle Ground… https://t.co/JVhUtyar2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MargaretJosephs I laughed my ass off when Marty went into the pool,won't be the first time I'm sure and won't be t… https://t.co/VmTg39ciaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[RBA needs to light a fire under the #BunchofJerks during the intermission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yemitawikutsew @Ethiopia_Abebe @eskinder_nega If that is the case why you crying 😢?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother is judging me because I’m going to the store to buy a half gallon of ice cream. As if she doesn’t know me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plutema @FortheloveofPe9 I had a cat what would clean my basset’s ears...she never had ear problems until she didn’t have her cat anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of my abs. faves! Your esty graduation party. You were so happy and proud and so was I! Congrats again… https://t.co/HwnczMMrQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfcAZendejas @OfficialLivePD @9PMRoutine1 @LivePDNation @LadiesOfLivePD How sweet! He loves you!! 🐶🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with measles outbreaks across the US, at least 20 states have proposed anti-vaccination bills  https://t.co/empELkrozK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonia_mafs The preview for next week shows that AJ continues to struggle with anger and anxiety. 👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[My childhood home is going on the market soon in #OrangePark near #flemingisland it has been #upgraded… https://t.co/dhupQjGbm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell you how many times I’ve gone to @ChickfilA on a Sunday only to realize I subconsciously want what I ca… https://t.co/3fi7wSYjk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Korn @JC_SHAFFER @JDavisOfficial @brianheadwelch @RayLuzier1 @fever333 @fieldyofficial Can’t wait to see you all i… https://t.co/NckY3pQyxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[the power on that stage right now i have NO WORDS https://t.co/wpMLfMy1ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting and historic day today for @medaillemavs and @MedailleMTennis! Join us at the South Towns Tennis Center at… https://t.co/1cZGf9VbwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN, you're going down, you're nothing but democrat thugs with a camera, you do not represent real America and your… https://t.co/iWmlgQ00KR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @Joyful_33 @IlhanMN Usher in more Muslim police like #NYC .  ty @POTUS #SCOTUS 🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏⭐️⭐️⭐️ #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little pop-tart is my favorite. @brendonurie @ Pechanga Arena San Diego https://t.co/Jcv1xqVxii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseandlune I was just having the discussion about how I don’t want to know anything about the show but I’m weak a… https://t.co/rVwYrF0KQz]]></document></documents></author>