<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So I'm suddenly hungry and the rain outside sounds like someone is cooking meat https://t.co/dnc1zMEBW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liesandperfidy @McCoveyChron Although that’s like ... the opposite of the original joke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know who manages the @ATWOnline account these days, but it'd be great if they could finally fix their Twitt… https://t.co/2COQX99ITd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wayne’s featured on 4 songs on this new Drake album... I’ve seen enough don’t even gotta listen https://t.co/PdUXMFx69C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods There is no doubt that many Republicans are in league with Democrats in seeing that the Trump Ameri… https://t.co/DhAb2z1sIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re doing this. ❤️❤️❤️🔥🔥🔥 #feelthebern #bernie2020 #notmeus @ United States https://t.co/XyVZP3pUjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 400 Northlake Ct # 306 #NorthPalmBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/BzkOJk37wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMaxwellStory @jamiecsteel We train them that way.  Help keeps the Donald out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you call for Desmond Trufant’s head but you’re ready to riot about the Brian Poole news... https://t.co/aIilYxVzEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double feature #wednesday #36minutes #hitt #strength #goals #hittworkouts #denverfitness #trainforwhatyoulove… https://t.co/BJlPHxf8uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to David Hutchinson @CauseRecruiter for hosting sector conversations https://t.co/FJLoOicXVt  I'm proud to… https://t.co/ghF90Pwi4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EasilyyR6 I can put a box of these away. No idea why they even wrap them individually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all needed that @21savage tribute by @JColeNC. Beautiful. #NBAAllStar https://t.co/rSk5wijesn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAcademy what lifeless bloodless show are you going to be subjecting is to this year? #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top end racing at Evadale Raceway 2 16 2019  from the starting line looking down the track to the top end. @ Evadal… https://t.co/UkQV1ZwMCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We not only going to see the first NBA Finals without Lebron in 9 years....we about to see a Lebron-less playoffs 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that time 3 days ago when Sober Rizzo said he’d get me banned within 3 days? Good times man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatchingBirder @Everything_TN We met at a truck stop, Johnson City Tennessee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkelley21 Yeah, but how do you cut audio from a Cookie Monster presser? Especially when “EveryWordRunsTogetherOneR… https://t.co/2BaAC0JO13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenXpatriate @atlcouncil @amirrf @JenniferIde1 The number of locations and the hours they’re open depends on the c… https://t.co/wXnrX8g4A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adriaunawalkerr @SincerelySani__ Person raping someone* fixed that for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acary169 @ShaneClaiborne There are few, if any, good arguments against better gun regulations, and this old classi… https://t.co/e5i8kMjLF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paigowjanet Actually lower housing costs would significantly improve situations! Hmm...]]></document><document><![CDATA[**person in Toronto pulls fax off of machine**  “Says here Jack Johnson to LA for no one but Mario Lemieux will pla… https://t.co/SCQVKVuYGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls Bball tonight at 7 on WSYB MSJ -Poultney at 7 on NSN https://t.co/mOuzWvtWZA Rutland -Lyndon Girls hockey at… https://t.co/Wgc3zCXPCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would it be weird to have a kid and then make that kid only listen to people from a certain region and see if you g… https://t.co/ERNrB0CavI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InfobaeAmerica Ni que se cambien de grupo sanguineo, Dios lo sabe todo y es suficiente, el ama al ser humano y tam… https://t.co/Lk4uUeOxyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[SATURDAY NIGHT!!! #indiedanceparty #darkwavedisco #newwave #bloghouse #dancerock #homesweethome #fig19… https://t.co/ubEOQjeTE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lightning_Round @BB_Chargers What do you think the Chargers sincerely believe are their priorities going into free… https://t.co/4RXcuEaVbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fauuxrios STOPPPP I HAVE DRYING LOTION FOR PIMPLE! and only one bed for us, extra cuddles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, Detroit. I am going to miss you. Every time I start prepping to leave, I get uber emotional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RectorSun @maggieNYT @xtinatkacik Should I say it? It’s a sign of the times. Unless it has something to do with tr… https://t.co/HHXzC09UcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Playing. #upcomingshows #comicsofinstagram #comediansofinstagram #comedy #weedporn #riseandgrind… https://t.co/RJIoCXH2Kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used to have a piece of paper for games and that was it. The set up has since gotten much more complicated...… https://t.co/Lx6jjNpPpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President: What is the status of CLARIFICATION OF THE 14th AMMENDMENT? The original ammendment referred to slaves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are being painted clearly as a complete fraud Donny.    We all know you are a criminal, now the world knows it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Turnbull Canyon Hiking Trail https://t.co/GT1KZXmRZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team S&amp;Y meeting some great people at the BOMA Resource fair today! #BOMA #fullcourtpress https://t.co/4cmThhSqso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because you had a baby in the wrong time, doesn’t mean you have to give up on yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Emerson Electric Co? We're hiring in #Austin, TX! Click for details: https://t.co/eCa9b2XBNy #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardbond76 Thanks for following back...yesssss https://t.co/lPx1k341kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#you👀me ?? One thing I have to say for sure, and it’s that if you haven’t seen me in 2019, you don’t even know me.… https://t.co/LqFdjYRnHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter golfers are the worst....this shouldn't even have to be addressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[10shit.liljay 10.shit 10shit.liljay3   THE DANCE YOU DO WHEN YO LIL NIGGAS GETTIN OFF DEBBIE *10 A P* @ Okinawan Ka… https://t.co/KEH5nP7QsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited because my law review article, dropping any day now, tackles ways to address this issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_Schiff @WhitfordBradley  Cohen's testimony today seals it: Ziegler-Lyman 2020! Who says no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I’m not staying up this late to see a Joe Thornton Hat Trick. Cmon #NHLBruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didnt fill. $apop breaking out now. Good luck to those in. Watch out for this though these israeli stocks can be tricky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DixieMoonGirl Happy Birthday..!  March is also my birthday month.. I'll be turning a few years more than 44 though :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaymarie918 Stop complaining, kids are starving and cold, first world headass 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Peter And Miles. No One Really Important. #MilesMorales #PeterBParker @SpiderVerse https://t.co/ijRpypfYXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike Lee is a moron. Choose love vs. hate in 2020? I can’t think of a more hateful side than the left. @charliekirk11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vikings Taking the air out of the ball with long offensive possessions.. up 46-32. 4:42 to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantaFeNaturist @Jefff_Fa_Fa Flying nude would certainly cut back on TSA staff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philiphutcheson @RussellV_74 @CaseyAlexander_ @gmathews_24 @robmarberry0 @glosan_ @Elipep378 Internally, that team… https://t.co/XLj0v4wXcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohanBBT @TPBrewing @DRE_Go_Fish @ephoustonbill @zappafaye @cedarflats @JonMontag @Just4BeerLovers @wrayzors… https://t.co/OOldP6v7jH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillRulli @linorulli Honestly, isn’t there a clause in your lease that the apartment cannot be turned into a modified greenhouse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're all hypocrites at one level or another.     Our humility determines the extent to which others will tolerate… https://t.co/p7lIpIskyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all is said and done, I hope @TomFitton gets some kind of presidential commendation. One of the hardest workin… https://t.co/OefMLVQqI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, probably yelling about the Orlando Magic.  I'm amazed folks who I believe ate awesome and cool follow me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmbustamante @__ayduchis__ @LuchyB @Lizz_Bennet @vivibarreral @hermanntertsch  Era lo único que faltaba para Febre… https://t.co/QQ6xc4TlWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sgraves924 hey brother- can you help me with some Civil engineering work? Hit me up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatwouldDOOdo is that dude #NewEraHatsOff from union worker to another, keep up the good work bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferRobson8 There was a time - certainly up to the end of Mackenzie King's ministry - when officials were excl… https://t.co/Ttv99asnTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisweedies Nothing like a good tit, gumbo, gumby convo to put off doing to work to on a Friday. You da best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días ☀️ |  Colosenses 3:15  Ustedes fueron llamados a formar un solo cuerpo, el cuerpo de Cristo. Dejen que… https://t.co/n59hy57GSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what @OfficialRezz looks like when she comes to Arizona quarterly to take all the 16 year olds and @RYYYY19… https://t.co/pzkWyIJN3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinCOnTheAir Justin that fish is about to be good looks like a cat is about to eat it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kid_primetime @YS_2Gz LeBron’s played against harder teams in all of his Finals appearances (aside from the Mavs)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPaulGosar Thank you for not participating in this Democrat white wash job, you rock...Democrat party bigotry and… https://t.co/bEbXro5CMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go for a run, @neodude said. Yeah!, it’s only misting!, I said. https://t.co/EbFweljhS0 https://t.co/LhyOJay3zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lounafenty @rihanna HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS VERY GOOD, BUT SHE LOSE TO THESE #MUSICIANS, WHICH… https://t.co/yZ2ljbXXz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amrita_rout @OneNoteC @OneNoteEDU @msonenote Love being at a conference, and while taking notes in OneNote on my i… https://t.co/wIgbhrsg0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Honte à l’#Espagne. Faire ça à des citoyens qui ont commit le seul délit de vouloir voter pour l’#independance de… https://t.co/76p7AmzVh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a #TANGELO a cross between a #tangerine and a #grapefruit and I’ve tried 2 of these so far and I hate them… https://t.co/cH46rPgtMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[. #GREATJOB @CoreyLaJoie with the @GoFasRacing32 #32 your doing an awesome job keeping the #TeamKeen @KeenParts race car looking great 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[An ICE truck parked on a school’s sidewalk to have lunch? Too cute by half for me. These look like steel toe intimi… https://t.co/TrPd46dFwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucas_Wiseman @PBATour DUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IfSheBeWorthy Nice choices. Annihilation was robbed of a best picture nod.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk More careers have ended with a "right now" than a vote of confidence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@News8Daybreak waiting on Greg fields to tell me how to dress this morning I am up waiting on you guys to make my d… https://t.co/M6JuM98RvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Wild Goose Community Church https://t.co/bEcTsThSno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaroldBingo @bansky Playing lineups with no Ingram nor Lebron is nuts and a team that has absolutely no shooting s… https://t.co/TI2pJ91Hbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlecCurrier @USAFmom3 @Josiegirlz5 @StormIsUponUs @GenFlynn @bkerb953 @Ray37676747 Truth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PARISDENNARD 9000 LIES IN THE FIRST 2 YEARS IN THE WHITE HOUSE.   DONALD TRUMP IS THE BIGGEST LIAR!!! https://t.co/RudWJf5Fp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnNuevoDia @marcoregil @pattymanterola @AdamariLopez @SANDARTI @Telemundo51 via @facebook acaba de subir esta noti… https://t.co/vJdjIGF9AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[tomorrow is presidents’ day and we have school. wow that is messed up. how do you think Abraham lincoln feels😔 or george washington😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delavegalaw I get it. My daughter’s a Girl Scout, so we buy them from her, of course. But I still buy a couple of… https://t.co/bAtR6XK0lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samar3450 @HackerShane Definitely beautiful! The both of you defiantly are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CRT19 Six month data on alcohol-mediated renal denervation for hypertension looks good in CRT late breaker. Good p… https://t.co/V1HVHQPLQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianschatz @AyrieGirl The Republican plan for climate change is to let it kill brown people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maxie_UK @joswinson Perhaps, but surely our ideas on what is humane cannot to any great degree?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cohen May be a liar but you praised this liar for two years until he as you say it, turned RAT! So… https://t.co/0m4Y58Sdly]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just weird that you have this plan in your mind of when things will happen and how old you’ll be but then it never plays out like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Consciousness needs the mathematical Universe to create the details and content of our subjective states. The math… https://t.co/K37TgdDDwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyK @Twitter @dickc @bohan @TJay @stephanied @ju2thalee @mooreryan @evanr @semurph @LiatBycel @LK Congrats!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tru_Alpha @XThreeee Scumbag dogshit fucking piece of fucking living breathing fecal matter. He and fucking Elgin c… https://t.co/WV0UI8xEOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Feeling great? Ruptured Spleen? Ahhhhhh, it's a minor problem? https://t.co/wHVvbaj6JQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your external dialogue becomes your kids internal dialogue. Be carful what you say! (Jim Kwik)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you see the difference!  This is David Manning CEO of Xstream Travel and myself Joseph Mitchell MBA!  The first… https://t.co/jwJXyEwHo0]]></document></documents></author>