<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day everyone! 💋💋💋 I couldn’t pick a favorite so here are some pics of my #valentinesootd 🌹🌹🌹… https://t.co/BtCgSZ80aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that sounds nasty 😷 but your girl be lazy AF and I got too much hair to wash it all the time. Dry shampoo be saving my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Can anyone say PURE JEALOUSY? Rosey only likes ugly men bc she's insanely jealous of nice looking, younger women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Postmates order was cancelled after 20 minutes of being “prepared” because the restaurant was “closed” but when… https://t.co/gsHH9EUcNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will not allow myself to be with someone who doesn’t make me feel like i’m chosen everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this suppose to be a metaphor for how I treat men? If so....all my plants die, I kill them 🙃🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexicana por Fortuna y Jarocha de ❤️!! @ Hayward, California https://t.co/zILxxakwvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The airport is playing an awful, awful rendition of the Star Spangled Banner.   This is my own personal purgatory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman talking to her son while walking their dog: "Listen Neil, believe when I'm telling you that I'm not being jud… https://t.co/PNcu8ii8ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are at it again! 2 WEEKS FROM TONIGHT! Check out another epic lineup of artists to hit the Jete stage • •… https://t.co/CmOnDiqp0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitRedWings @LCArena_Detroit @MotorCityCasino I’m going to leave now😂  #LGRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/AIKYLGG0ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What’s your last name? Oh, like the market?”  “Yeah and like the island.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever fw somebody so hard you have a attitude when you’re not around them😩😕 https://t.co/lP1PKeCAFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at one of our reporters @AJWalkerNews killing it with her braids! @CBS12]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each year for Valentine’s Day, my daddy takes me to go eat crab legs. Been our tradition for years! I’m excited for tomorrow! ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredwilson @aweissman @whitneymcn Rufus! But I don't think I have given experimental country a fair chance yet :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePlantEmoji I don't do musicing in the instrument way but sometimes I do do (heh heh heh heh poop jokes) musici… https://t.co/bq0JvZSoDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPackett omg what a terrible day. i’m sorry you’re going through that. but you’re right, i am here for you. you ne… https://t.co/9HqYkqJV0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send a Twitter message!  .@people_sd .@seoulmania .@wonsoonpark @seoulcouncil Seoul Seongdong-gu, South Korea, Shut… https://t.co/fnGMYJwn2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new hero - and a little known, but awesome environmental rock star in Congress: @mcduff2009   https://t.co/y5mxYVkARw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hinanee I read it as "drive with your eyes dipshit" and honestly.. mood..]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u see me looking like shit this time around the year, mind your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armonandtrey @armonandtrey  Total Spontaneous Combustion🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 @armonandtrey https://t.co/CaQikv4Aht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gumplr @AmericaNewsroom @RepMarkMeadows @SandraSmithFox https://t.co/WzF6LQbSJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deven made me watch a scary movie before bed so if I don’t sleep tonight you know why]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katjetson @CloneNic Welcome back to the East Cally Girl. Lol.  Melting fast though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all are the PJ to my Nick. ❤️ Tomorrow and Saturday are fully booked, but I'll be back for a limited engagement o… https://t.co/2nbIAfhvJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM SHOOK TO MY CORE!!! @KaceyMusgraves REALLY DID THAT FOR US TONIGHT AND BROUGHT OUT @TrinityTheTuck AND… https://t.co/laUFr69Krh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamHillLVRJ @J15Emerson Get the man some Swiss Miss! https://t.co/UuWPyWpPcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bazelonbethany @The_Globe I LOVE seeing your AMAZING pictures of your family on a FANTASTIC trip! THANK YOU for sharing! 😎😀🤗🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[“hey siri, show me more episodes of siren.” 😭 my 2 fav things. 🍎🧜🏼‍♀️🧜🏼‍♂️ @SirenTV @FreeformTV @Apple]]></document><document><![CDATA[No u bad ass ur the lier for real. U are the worst human on this Earth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @taylorswift13 if you wanna release new music today or tomorrow while I'm on vacation I'm totally okay that ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pampisford @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM @vallouard @leonalombaerts @rayanf9416 @MelindaYoe @Indinlily @Eagleeye47… https://t.co/EOWHAcF6US]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duolingo is tired of me not taking 5 minutes of my day to complete a ring ..😂 ma bad https://t.co/xb8G76YYab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonWeigl It’s uh... there still isn’t any actual length of hair on the one side still... so... no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t this law, only American citizens can vote?  @TeamPelosi @AOC @KamalaHarris @RepMaxineWaters @SenFeinstein… https://t.co/sbWvWsJhuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss moments like this. @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/FvLdaUrhqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[..........so much for seeing him in action in Denver.   We jinxed it, @loveandhydrogen 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Correct!  Solipsism from Latin solus, meaning 'alone', and ipse, meaning 'self' is the philosophical idea that only… https://t.co/eDvP9OZwNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're craving some amazing Mexican food with live music, then stop on by at The Maya Mexican Restaurant! . . We… https://t.co/3zoCETK406]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw I do not favor the thoughts and actions of the Democratic party. Illegal aliens should not ever hav… https://t.co/tnYAXVzBFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[You rocked it!!! So proud knew you  would bring it home for Worthington! @wcsdistrict]]></document><document><![CDATA[ADOPT: There’s not denying that Nash is one cool cat... Head to @nashvillehumane if you’re interested in meeting hi… https://t.co/SbKEoJ3PoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Man, I hope you are out of pain and you have a speedy recovery!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fbf from April of last year. Doing my thang at the spanishmonastery 🤩 Are you looking for models for your next fas… https://t.co/lYQlltjNXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianocabj83 No tengo mas vino .🤷🏼‍♀️🍷 si ese es tu fin ......#LaTrilogiaParanormal https://t.co/QUl3U5I1zz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so tired but I can’t sleep. Living that post chemo no choice zombie life. #ayacancer #colorectalcancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingNewsCo @VinceMcMahon His own falt he takes away what people what to see like Becky vs Ronda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is here and Clubpapi is ready for toning, the best Latin night in weho #clubpapi #mickysweho #gatorosso… https://t.co/rDn7Ae8P6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cara Deus foi tão bom esses dias, colocar meus planos nas mãos dEle foi a melhor coisa que eu já fiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LunaAmatista Yes! Unless they're very small but that's rare. I usually break them into fourths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 1416 DESTINI Lane #Southport #FL  #realestate https://t.co/aYUkRBOp5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGodfatherMoody To be fair, it did suck. Seemed almost staged actually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll emotionally never get over the Lady Gaga/Bradley Cooper performance #theoscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USEmbassyAbuja @EUinNigeria THIS IS NOT AN ELECTION THIS IS RIGGING ROBBING OF BALLOTS AND BRIBERY NOT AN ELECTION… https://t.co/NhyK2wPgRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay gusto ko to. Pag ayaw tumigil ng mga BN at sasakay yung isa sa paiyak2 eh malamang. Remember”u see things, u kee… https://t.co/qsPAg3EqzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s to the point it’s not being a ride or die 🤷🏼‍♀️ it’s being a dummy for someone ‼️😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello brands! If you have been shouting your love for women from the rooftops today, then I assume you’ve also been… https://t.co/HEfrt7m5zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amara🐱♥️📦 #fridayboxpawty #catsinboxes #teamcoopcrate #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #blackcats… https://t.co/I1uhfmlQ1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of you guys con el nopal en la frente are afraid to show your mexican side and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[With this proposal Cupich takes up reform ideas that were discussed in the fall at the plenary meeting of the US Bi… https://t.co/913yt2D5um]]></document><document><![CDATA[not being able to fit my first name on a scantron is by far the most irritating thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sportsnutrition ⛸🤼‍♀️🤸🏾‍♀️🥊 #weightmanagement 🍽 #gettingreadyfor 🙏🏾 #nnm2019 🍎 #stopby 🛑 #theclinic 🚭 scandpg… https://t.co/vAjPRIG4un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Majec_3771 @robgreeneII @FlickReynolds Movies don’t usually make me feel like sh*t but st times very sad (eg, “Amo… https://t.co/nxfOOuaCMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resistance Management isn’t something that can be fixed in 1 year. It’s a lifelong investment for your operation. #FSAgConf19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s make @Clare_Crawley the next Bachelorette!!! We need some more mature women this year!!!! @fleissmeister @chrisbharrison]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been at the hospital for 4 hours waiting for my lil sister to be seen. 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[White House travelling press pool devours @Bolay while waiting for ⁦@realDonaldTrump⁩ to finish golfing.… https://t.co/Sr2gKq5NEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try me $39.00 first visit new client only Brazilian and Underarms thereafter $65.00 per visit expires March 10,19 call and pay now Zelle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy @BravoWWHL @BravoTV When will the US get ALL of these?!! #realhousewives #bravo https://t.co/g9JeFQAXCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[problems: exist me: just you fuckin wait until august 2020 when i have silver hair and my life together, then we’ll… https://t.co/0krjZOd7fH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneyridhs @EBB_RI It’s great to be part of such a great initiative!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took biochem the semester before taking physics so now all of my physics inexplicably looks like beta oxidation https://t.co/I2Ofa7Gtyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why all the other housewives hate her #rhobh #rhoa jealous of her success]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLammy @jennycohn1 This earned you a follow from a very sad and very frightened American.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pretty sissy and her little schnookums 😘💝  #smartlovemoves 💡❤︎ is power💥  #selflove  #selflovequotes… https://t.co/B2qyn9RUMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MillionLittleThings "The more you try to push away the past, the more it haunts you"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ser Godinez en el extranjero no fue fácil! Después de 9 meses de trabajo constante, solo puedo dar Gracias por la oportunidad Gee beauty 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZvilleGirlsGolf @twins4me2001 @ReidVonDie25 Happy birthday from the Skinner’s! @skinner0109]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne It's hard for a racist to stare racism in the face because deep down inside they know they are ful… https://t.co/GqfNm72amu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love working with kids bc I said “alright show me your backbend” and the little girl said “I was put to sleep onc… https://t.co/aZkeAhHQzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[February Shawl complete! Went way back to my very first missbabsyarns purchase in 2015 and used Yowza Beatiful Drea… https://t.co/O4sFlU5Wy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF I SAY I FWY JUS KNO I MEAN IT . I GOT YOU .EVERYTHING I SHOW IS PURE OML.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughfriknfraser @JimCarrey He never does talk about them....now we know why..he's got a closet full  of secrets..m… https://t.co/EiDHAMhxlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csalitros @yepitslancaster @indystar @downthebyline It’s definitely interesting. Only had a chance to glance at the story though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I constantly ogle nice horses in the most cartoonish construction worker way imaginable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson should have won fr but she ain’t need that petty competition nearly as much as this one lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my mom really bond over looking at wedding rings (bands for her and future rings for me)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy boy playing in the yard! I bet he did #zoomies  #alexanderthegreat 🐎🤴 #foreverhomeneeded #adoptalexander… https://t.co/yZ2QGsCsii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liatrueba El “Plan de Seguridad frente a la violencia contra las Mujeres" recomienda a las víctimas evitar lugares… https://t.co/w2EaVptUzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I choked on my pop-tart. 😂You can’t deny his game is strong. If you don’t  follow him ..#treatyoself Do it. 😈❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like we've made it big time?!! 🤷🏼‍♀️🎉If you're in the Waverly area make sure to check out our S T U N N I N G… https://t.co/PSqOZd1jtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamPeekeMD @bioedge Is there a stigma if you have hypertension? Hypercholesterolemia? Diabetes? Need I say more......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clutch Gene How many titles Scottie won w/o Mike blew lead against Lakers in fourth Kobe and Shaq won W/o each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlyssaMastro44 You and VJ were so great last night - your friendship is beautiful! I can’t wait to plow through your book tonight. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Efe__EA @_AdamaSesay This too is okay. Opinions are never enforced (lol).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because apparently it’s weird to work 7 days a week but like so goes life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @EllenPage @Ilhan Another thing, get mad!! But, if a church is of God it would be non-welcoming  to t… https://t.co/E4Rd8Zjz4R]]></document></documents></author>