<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@anntensity Tell them to get caught crossing the border and we will show them the wall at ADX in Florence, CO.  The… https://t.co/ODe8cPg5df]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all’s servers suck. Fix that shit before i go back to fortnite @PlayApex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nextcontext You mean something like "If we could make the Earth banana shaped, would the escape velocity be lower?… https://t.co/4wTcHVNm92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZuluCheech That's great then. Sure the women who find yall attractive are happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you think it is only Black Heterosexual males...  there is a war on all Black males. We're Black, we're Male… https://t.co/YuekTbFM6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYT's exposé on the lies about burning aid trucks in Venezuela shows how U.S. Government and Media spread pro-war p… https://t.co/Y3DWCunztV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelibrarywitch @karenblanchette @com3tp3nguin @jfrobailey Because once Civ has its hooks in you it never lets go. One more turn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestG0ATRussell If you were a Sonics fan and you are now a Thunder fan, then your opinion does not count. Seattle… https://t.co/FxhEaAwQKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What if the next New American Home was a condo? And what if there was a new American dream, not of auto-dependent… https://t.co/fFtITm17BP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello! Last day of the week.. Yay @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/7DWrqXguLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, this has absolutely nothing to do with chasing people out of restaurants.  This has everything to do with sensa… https://t.co/ZtzANWudhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeiboldG8r @UFpharmboy @shawndanderson @go_pharm_gator https://t.co/Ser47KV6YF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourOtherGun Exactly. Y'all know I ain't that type of person. He explained to me what the other dude did and I was… https://t.co/sajVSwn0uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite today's WINTER SNOWSTORM, GNC in the Winona Mall IS OPEN - So stop by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN T… https://t.co/7m2HCHl3X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream as if you'll live forever, live as if you'll die today. • • Top🧥: Luxe Leisure Pullover Bottoms👖: Luxe Leisur… https://t.co/nN7qG2Zhp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW, In N Out burgers are bland, and the fries are like cardboard. First time tonight having them sober. #Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should point out that I commend fda for this. It isn’t their job to overprescribe regulations. This is certainly… https://t.co/8uR5whRkC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rudy the wrecker and conspirator in a Mojito haze is back doing Trump’s dirty work, trying to sully Cohen. Rudy oug… https://t.co/iuY8RVpUYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Ric Flair hits the ring, 4 of my 5 All-Time favorites will be in the ring at one time. The only one missing is Stone Cold. #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pouissant1 @JustJVega @POTUS @GenFlynn @CropDusterAnon @intheMatrixxx @MonangeSauvi @MoonProfessor @Jordan_Sather_… https://t.co/1theKBoKdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittMcHenry Britt,  I respect all that you say but you want him to stop his life because of an accident.....what’… https://t.co/cQ4sgiP3Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pkentma @McFaul @OriginallyNoNo @realDonaldTrump And history will show how really stupid don the Con and Mike pence really were.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if the only Generation Z members who  Are influenced to do micro budget film Are the same ones from coastal elite e… https://t.co/2HkUlzyaBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sug_knight Got my dad a meat thermometer. Sounds dumb but he thanks me for it a LOT. https://t.co/llBo2Zk9UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it states in the USA Constitution and the Canadian Constitution there will be no Sharia Law aloud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/dBRsWoRuSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pilot Travel Center - @pilotflyingj in Avondale, AZ https://t.co/pZkXiVV2Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sister Cyan? 🤷🏻‍♂️  Using the New @jamescharles x @MorpheBrushes palette. I was able to play with some color and cr… https://t.co/1odOgEidvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @RobersonSpring Percussion!! @SpringISD #SISDPVA @Spring_Build]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, a right-wing Democrat like Joe Biden or Amy Klobuchar.   Eric Holder is corrupt Wall Street lawyer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brickwallblitz When the 49ers drafted Solomon Thomas over Malik Hooker 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FicasBeach I have followed this redhead for a long time! She is definitely one of my favorite redhead’s! She is de… https://t.co/rDnXvmOT4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add me on Instagram: phillipspearmantattoo to browse through my tattoo art. Message me there for all tattoo consult… https://t.co/lpUqAfpjOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we come face2face with @jimmyfallon w/ his kids at MSG. All my gf noticed were his banana shoes...lol fml. Didnt notice it was jimmy. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very good beer! - Drinking a Buzzworthy by @SmogCityBeer/@MoonlightMead @ Otay Ranch  — https://t.co/p059bHUBWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typed “thanks” today and it autocorrected to “Tonks” so that’s where I’m at in life and I really can’t complain. :) @Tonksnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday ill be kicking things off with a rare hip hoppy set at LOVERVILLE so pull up💕   tickets in… https://t.co/wPT7OMdvSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SNL. Co.eon through... #oscar2019 #redcarpet @ Academy Awards Red Carpet. Hollywood https://t.co/41axBm6Mif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to Gov. Baker: MBTA riders pay taxes, too. And, whether you ride the T or not, we all gain by keeping transit… https://t.co/dWnagoMuvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcuspopoff Why does he troll everyone he comes in contact with??? Did you teach him this?😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markjboucher @KamalaHarris Negates research from economists, factual data, and other countries that have proven th… https://t.co/bhyPriG0HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude was on it today. Excited for him. #LeftySwag #WeOutHereGrinding #DoubleDeuce @ AB Pitching, Hitting and Fitnes… https://t.co/S76n2A2fJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But in all these things we overwhelmingly conquer through Him who loved us.” Romans’ 8:37 —— That’s a promise from… https://t.co/eCb5NqwebA]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Zombie deer' disease found in 24 states, could spread to humans https://t.co/BTW6oTz3bW via @WPXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Adam SCHIFF is nothing more then a weasel! He perfectly willing to spend taxpayers money on nothing mo… https://t.co/g4zzTSCzQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some fun facts to kick off your morning y'all. #texasindependenceday #Texas #thestarsatnight https://t.co/kEkmeMrmUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Members of the @AHSLadyHoops team checking out the @hudwbb-@CFBlackTigers' game. I see @shaylasellers3 &amp;… https://t.co/lsmKtDTXZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quidditch World Cup 2011: # 15. Good Game! - - - @ErikJAWS - @ New York, New York https://t.co/Mjg9PQDcxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayuda pasar unos años en diversos países del mundo para concluir, como @RafaelNadal, que “los españoles no somos co… https://t.co/ranxnZptJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[704 Hilgard Ave 704 Hilgard Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90024 https://t.co/WwLHlUsu3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see them income taxes peekin at me in my account so we had to celebrate 🤷🏼‍♂️🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this side show All this deflection Puts me on the fight For starters We need to overhaul the FED college loan B… https://t.co/PwhnN9Vg4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Two points: 1)Hospice gives exceptional care; 2)something similar happened with my dad on Hospice (and afterward)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBsBigHouse1 @YahooForde They don’t know, do they?!😂 Michigan has the defense to shut down any team in the country… https://t.co/EgMMXtO7QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[18 miles apart and 4,280 ft difference in elevation.  Looking forward to the next adventure #allmountainambassador… https://t.co/Mk7uBFUp9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does my teacher have a upside down cross at the top of her forehead https://t.co/1Z08kYq61P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallsJeremy @Kikiontheriver @MiamiOpen @HardRockStadium The ad that showed on ESPN this morning was awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macleans @SenecaCollege Staple a $20 bill to the top left corner helps too 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Who knows? The way things are going this may not be that big a deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muzic Empire Mix Tape "Eternal Desire" vol 01 by Muzic Empire | Free Listening on SoundCloud… https://t.co/KRHhXRwsrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my brother @trex93 you have me for life love you slime]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Beilein says Cassius Winston’s performance was one of the best point guard performances he’s seen since he’s been at Michigan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And at the time I was trying so hard to complete all of this shit because I REALLY wanted to go. And they wouldn’t… https://t.co/3i7KiF9dIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning greetings 🌞#coffeecheersclub! I’m flying to #Texas this morning. I’m providing #autism training tomo… https://t.co/TlKIngWaTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's "Daily In Store Special"! A Free Hose Reel With the Purchase of a Pressure Washer! Like us on Facebook and… https://t.co/xm3u6HKYR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kool_bae @SecularScarlet Geologic time is almost incomprehensible. I try to imagine what it was like 100 years ago… https://t.co/BoV7FTCusU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRCATucson Jared Clark struggled early but came on strong to lead the Lions #AZPreps365 https://t.co/YilLKVDncn]]></document><document><![CDATA[He hates plastic bags caught in the bushes. @ Sussex County, Delaware https://t.co/road5OUImu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrtablaze And all this racist anger and fighting began with the first black president, and the #democrats are clin… https://t.co/Yks62EA9yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think the stoppage in @Benaskren @Ruthless_RL fight was early ? #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[A stunning thread. Be warned, this may trigger PTSD-type responses if you’ve been through an active shooting or an… https://t.co/dcavETCjY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias amigo! Una gran responsabilidad! La asumo con mucho entusiasmo @michelleriveraa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woogiewaugh Consenting is the key word there. If it’s not consenting that’s some nasty bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really need to apply for jobs in Cincinnati but also want to take a two week “vacation” after I move up there so I… https://t.co/E5ygNIw1A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Your threats against Mr Cohen sound like they come from a mob strongman instead of a US congressman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alxcristol @jessedriftwood1 I’ll change my answer to box 14, right near the middle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lama Tharchin Rinpoche’s Supplication Prayer  OM SWASTI May all be auspicious! KYÉ CHHI JIK DRAL NANG WA T’HA YAY P… https://t.co/FzmCplWc61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP Have you listen to the shite that comes out of your boss’s mouth dude?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Democrats making a big mistake. They need to unite behind a solid candidate. Republicans had too many candidat… https://t.co/ffLoWmbgmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Murray- we a dying but it’s one of those horror movie comedy spoofs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, good thing I make the trains on them after work... train that hit that car was the one after the train I board.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canonlaw You should go to TLMs. The only hymns I hear are Marian Antiphons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying goodbye to grandpa (@ Sandy Hook (Gateway National Recreation Area) in Highlands, NJ) https://t.co/ZovysfSZmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t decide if Cleve doesn’t wag his tale at me because  A) He isn’t excited to see me               OR  B) He’s… https://t.co/v1OM8Uk0I4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Jam Band by @Boulevard_Beer @ GuestHouse Bellingham — https://t.co/TEqgG0K4ND]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the argument that Netflix made when switching from ratings to thumbs up and thumbs down. It makes so much… https://t.co/IGFR1mOi0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaxFootballGuru @AustinDJordan @NFLVR @PfgVibe @JulieNoted_PFG @NFL No question...Mel Blount. Anyone who has a rul… https://t.co/VaitcNl7ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Karma, man, she's a bitch. I hope the rest of @GOP learns this, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first @BNBuzz book signing will include a 1-hour writing session for parents who want to learn about writing not… https://t.co/5lHnG2uTUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOBODY turned on this game to see half of the screen on Calipari @espn!!  NOBODY. STOP THE SPLIT SCREENS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine this coming out of any other presidents mouth. Even Nixon wouldn’t have said this. At least not in public.… https://t.co/t24yUiLyMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horseracingbest @JuddmonteFarms Con mucha oportunidad de conducir a este gran potro]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @LevLane Advertising in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/ZZAHNUyLc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a Light lyrics - Don Potter https://t.co/9LZLpJjz36 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: The EWC Women will open the 2019 @GCACInfo Championship on Friday as the #4 seed and will face #5… https://t.co/6I0Z2YQ2FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatterofKAT @Raptors @MastercardCA How much do I ❤️ this pic! #WreckingCrew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tax policy tweets are the best tweets.  (I may be the only one in #ldnont who thinks that.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What a waste of our tax money.   Since the potus don’t pay taxes he does not care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaniejoly consultation on modernization...details on forums now public here https://t.co/TeP9YqkA5X @QCGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@time4brady Let ‘me hate.  @JHarden13 has been amazing.  #Rockets https://t.co/uXdS1oGvkT]]></document></documents></author>