<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Taji_Johnson8 @HarvardFootball @Coach_Poppe @SouthernSwagg4 @Mansell247 @TEwracademy @ChadSimmons_ A huge honor, c… https://t.co/UkJxMcOtoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, I watched this one, and still felt she could’ve done better considering these are the kids who have to live wit… https://t.co/ZtlXebpgpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsGucciBro5 Yeah I’m hoping they somehow turn it around but I won’t be surprised if they just botch it again in the draft]]></document><document><![CDATA[#6at6: Humpday Headlines 1️⃣ ☔️ in 🌃 ❄️ in 🏔  2️⃣ 🏫 closed and delayed 3️⃣ 👩🏼 to 🏛 4️⃣ ⚾️ 💰 💰 💰  5️⃣ 🏀 battle of th… https://t.co/CccpFFNXVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like a private party for two every time they perform together. I'm just the creeper on the outside of the door… https://t.co/mlsey1Y9IC]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m starting a new usc themed thread called: substances i find on campus that look vaguely like cocaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSilve42 Fun little factoid for you: the metallic colored paint gives a more intense high and is more toxic 🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPells2 Do you claim your withholding a as single or married? I learned it would be more beneficial to have status… https://t.co/5asfFGYKrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 8PM on Friday.. Cody &amp; I are drinkin &amp; dancin around the house jammin to 2000s hip-hop 😂😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lost. What did Amara do to JoJo? She’s the one who let Bobby call her friend a shady bitch. #LHHMIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[olive garden turned our special education classes away because they can’t accommodate us and it’s 110% empty 🙂 i’m livid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts @GMA @ABC did @RobinRoberts collude with @JussieSmollett in her #Exclusive . She soft balled the whol… https://t.co/5MxH9NSTlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to this lovely lady!!! Thank you so so much abhimani2 for letting me be a part of your special weekend!!!… https://t.co/L5hic8rqIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Former Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper says he’s running for President]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Character Parade @OgdenElementary Celebrating #drseussweek ! Great day to be a Stingray! @Ogdenpal @OgdenAP… https://t.co/Wdnd2jT9CL]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué harías una semana en #NuevaYork? Yo todas estas cosas de película, literalmente 😜 https://t.co/4Un7oEvyST #LowCost #NewYork]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights and Magic ✨with ladytron @ The Fonda Theatre https://t.co/qyB1juciVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to be clear you never genuinely cared . You just love to play your games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malahat Summit Nikon d850, 155mm, 1/200s, f/11, ISO 200 • Ahhh, the Malahat. One of the jewels of Vancouver Island.… https://t.co/ueJ6rYCWBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t tend to surround myself with childish adults.  I have little patience for unneeded drama.  This includes en… https://t.co/V0ynifOuNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceySlade1 Grom Here to Eternity by Caitlin Doughty. (Death and funeral traditions from around the world) Really c… https://t.co/EIUKbHGVEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can u please make ur app compatible with chromecast so I can watch the freak show on my tv? @tiktok_us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Eyed Susan. 🌻 #photography #WildFlowers https://t.co/yifPmdDlmq https://t.co/zRcTXvJ2i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF! Got a love those Friday morning smile’s! Have a good one everyone! #Specialneeds #NewFaceOfDowns #sisters… https://t.co/vXCnEBbVxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsea_lately Nooooooo!  But I know what you mean about no basketball 🏀 ;-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Ocean Breeze @GinaStartupArt #contemporaryart #artists #showyourwork #abstractart #mixedmedia #artoftheday… https://t.co/ZUOJYM2dJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrashFilmGuru Worst thing is some of these sources have been or are funded now by Venezuelan state TV and you wond… https://t.co/3eXG9iZse1]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry @CaraBaldwin14 i’m going to be late for curfew i’m being held hostage by some robots https://t.co/5OGfiwSXZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great night celebrating my Dad mikebrown194710 at the @WHLsilvertips Navy Night 🇺🇸⚓️🏒 I am so blessed to hav… https://t.co/LrfNAjqG8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMooreLPM @lkoturner I don’t know, but I am pumped they caught on so hopefully 20 years from now I don’t have t… https://t.co/8VIpcQFTyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissavorbeck leave it to you to appreciate the fucked up things i say 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else rather impressed by the impersonations they do of their family members in therapy? I kind of feel like I kill it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[tvd gets taken off of netflix tomorrow what I am supposed to do with my life now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept @MrsDarlahZ challenge to post 7 covers of NONfiction books; no explanations-just 📚covers. Each time I post… https://t.co/A4Ek60CwwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally as soon as I get back on a decent routine/sleep schedule i fuck it up again 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@whoisalexjacob Hope you’re proud. You played brave and you’ll always be a #Jeopardy champ &amp; #JeopardyAllStars competitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending time last night just dancing.  My favorite part of this ? 👅  . * I do not own the rights to this song* . A… https://t.co/YIuqKUJ34a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump isn't bothered by Kim's human rights record. He probably admires it! Most mob bosses do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolishPatriotTM he is just introducing th other dude, honestly Russians have no reason not to like Obama. He works… https://t.co/koaoZOPa2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @DGPurser @realDonaldTrump Pelosi and Schumer are all talk. If President Trump is out of the country… https://t.co/p00AafUO1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobcesca_go No. He had his day and did a nice job moving the platform to the left. Now, bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 Bernwood in Pebble Valley Taylors is a golf course community. 4/2 With huge screened porch. 250,000. See it on… https://t.co/770PyLnHyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im the type to wear slip on vans with no show socks, I hate how they look with regular socks 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paramus_Schools #GLAM squad! Today we’re talking assessment, single point rubrics, standards based grading, and mo… https://t.co/USx93Qi0Lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashton_demouy Jeeze you got me beat there I just woke up but the past 3 nights have been pooooop and Netflix isn’t… https://t.co/hZj4NubFm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been looking for this for MONTHS and just when I don't need it BAM, why is life screwing with me so much rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my review of @SevenStillsofSF and @stanfordcourtsf Blog link in IG intro. We had such a great time! Your… https://t.co/vcYhBL3U8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[*how sweaty my shirt is when I take my jacket off after attending an outdoor wedding]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/udg851A8Ki @craignewmark Please help! This project is huge and I need help while I have a match offer—… https://t.co/wTri1unbGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GEYermo Is that why I passed out on the plane for an hour and woke up still tipsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMAZING JOB for some AMAZING lil people!!!! CONGRATS &amp; a sincere Thank You for all that you do to fight #ftk… https://t.co/cfi156Jzta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s dinner Cornish hens bake Mac and cheese and fresh collard greens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh I’m ready to go out on tour and play keys with these badd babies for the next 3 weeks 🎹💅🏼💅🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pettigrew_alex *Plays Maxwell's Silver Hammer*  "Oh crap is this song about a guy just murdering everyone?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[when uber drivers ask me if I am "ottoman," I don't even correct then anymore.   yes, I am Ottoman.   Autumn, Autum… https://t.co/kitzpHa4Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fliume @DarkSideGeek @gdurrett @NickWaltersTV @MatthewACherry Omg she would love the applause 👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meggrim349 @dr_board @sadgirlWRX I feel like a piece of kelp would have a higher IQ than some of these people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toryshulman @SamSchacher @EricaCobb @steffrjones @KellySchuberth @BrandonLondonTV @aljackson @dailyblastlive… https://t.co/wMz1WY9nrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big hair, even bigger lashes 😆. Something about adding lashes really completes my makeup look and I love 💗 it. Who’… https://t.co/noZPwCcRAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sean3airboater @WPLGLocal10 Thanks youuuu come join us Im working at Carnival on the Mile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump My feelings..... https://t.co/ibnDVPL6Bp]]></document><document><![CDATA[All those #TeamOneLeague people, please consider supporting a CBA for players. Travel concerns are reportedly at th… https://t.co/WDYCYSU6Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a sucker for the #torontoskyline in pics! Beautiful pic of bride @Joywink 📷 jessilynnwongphotography… https://t.co/CNvXSGwBAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[a real ass healthy relationship where y’all BOTH benefit from each other, learn new things from one another, grow t… https://t.co/g1YsB0A6TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiseFallNick I dont know, I was laughing too much and didnt have close captions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LailaMcQueen @monetxchange @ThorgyThor My sister you are amazing ! Every single interview I had I always say you w… https://t.co/o2wuRjZwFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you let a 5k girl race The Mile: lap 3 - 😴 lap 4 - 😧 lap 5 - 😫 @ Kent State Field House https://t.co/tOeCv2bxTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes So now @DNC glorifies anti semitism. @SpeakerPelosi @chuckschumer @HouseDemocrats @SenJohnKennedy… https://t.co/JxP4RdxDyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to need some complicated political shenanigans coupled with irrational love of crowds feeling again...  We… https://t.co/lewqR9fvuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommonGloom @KaileyCeleste deadass my yungblud ticket was $16, w fees it was $25 and some change so i thought "wha… https://t.co/WEqYdUWlOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverYOGgaL @mrshutch123 @GillDoc5 @kaggsclarke @a_g_m_f_63 @LilyYog83 @imnotsnooty @GMlovelyYOG625… https://t.co/eCoePZIHHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gorgeoussss_e Exactly, cleavage is nothing compared to what they probably did on their spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t mean to sound like a basic single girl, but I really do not like valentines day lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thankyou Mr. President. Make America great again. You’re loved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taraduggan @SFC_Style The menstrual equity frame was actually born out of the 2017 book #periodsgonepublic! It’s a… https://t.co/eavKbzcfzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paidinfull912 Lmaooo you way more active than me I can actually chill out if the show good enough. I thought I dro… https://t.co/0hvbmeNd0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[😟😪💔🙏 I so LOVED watching him!! #RIPJanMichaelVincent #GodSpeed "Actor Jan-Michael Vincent died in February, TMZ rep… https://t.co/XL0ambmWDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fourth0fficial The only bad thing about this is the bull had to be put down. On the bright side, I think it’s tort… https://t.co/OAEwKICeCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW you can’t get on the second F train that comes bc it’s too full and you forgot your book bc you’re brain dead f… https://t.co/wcBOrwBlSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄🌸" Despite the forecast, live like it's Spring."~Lilly Pulitzer https://t.co/qWf8nUPCVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper As a kid I hid from my sister by getting into our refrigerator.  Instead of looking for me she took a… https://t.co/KRKWrUv8SJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring forward 💐 @ Seascape Restaurant and Pier https://t.co/e3kLzhIKzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Verses have helped me through everyday🙏🏻 I Corinthians 13:4-7 Psalm 46:5 Philippians 4:6-7 Proverbs 3:5]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: can i have one nice day  my depression and anxiety: https://t.co/ZCn7ze2z1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The parents from Abducted In Plain Sight should have also been thrown in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you queencourt22 @ Rancho Cordova, California https://t.co/eWZ60rFb1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusaneWong @Patrickesque I will now. I was open to him, but this changes things. He obviously lied and is still ly… https://t.co/IAchIHJM4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders will not beat Trump in a presidential election. Love him all you want, but it will not happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just hope anyone trying to get pregnant, gets pregnant. One of my worst fears and nobody deserves to go through that]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you know what? Everything is okay. Im safe. I play a smaller role in people’s lives than I fear. Now it’s time… https://t.co/1RBup4h5BL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who eats tuna fish this early especially on a small regional jet so we all have to smell it.?!?! The heat on the pl… https://t.co/6tOFMCFwRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yummmmmm 😋 (@ wasabi hibachi in Miller Place, NY) https://t.co/3JzSdIBAQN https://t.co/MmZ3uesNm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nunya business...to know who I’m with...  But clearly...it ain’t mine, either...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano You and the other looney democrats are disgusting and sick with a mental illness #TDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you can learn about typography while playing poker with guys (or gals).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Now we know why they want it gone they do good to Dems bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle Censorship is just one of the steps down a slippery slope!  We can't let this happen!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Barbara, Oakland special ed teacher, should-be award winner. #oakland #teacher #oaklandteacherstrike… https://t.co/WiLekwJK0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm... Can I hope to score a NASA internship as a biology undergraduate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillShaikin He should change the name of the team back to Anaheim Angels then.]]></document></documents></author>