<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Here we go #RiverCityRumble @JAX_MBB @OspreyMBB https://t.co/aKuatiX4Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RL_Miller be used as a wedge to subsidize them after they've become uneconomic due to a declining base of ICE vehi… https://t.co/o5uosGTSCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraydenStarnes9 @cojack2323 you guys are th business majors with math and stuff... did she calculate this correctl… https://t.co/1fVA3M4OGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Knicks and Clippers lose, please do not try to contact me tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[What type of “man” threatens to lay hands on a woman? I wish you would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For what exactly Joe? You’re comfortable with the Obama/Hillary justice dept. plotting treason? I’m sure the people… https://t.co/dknqGYXDg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for the #writingcommunity if the term “clutching my pearls” is out dated. What would you call doing this? https://t.co/ktRolNJWJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story, composed of primarily man humor, and drama, touches on the mystical guidance force that governs all thin… https://t.co/xu4x2i1wCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adnazteca @Rayados @TigresOficial Qiero llevar a mi hijo y conocer el eatadio q no.lo.conocemos ....saludos y espe… https://t.co/tKZvqMOrml]]></document><document><![CDATA[This semester really doesn’t afford me time anyways. I feel guilty doing anything but study]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjamesgalan @alexiaguirreee @elizabethgalan_ @jordanchulo_ Y’all finna lose your money 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxShafer3 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Come on max she doesn’t understand half the words you just used. Trumps base is uneducated morons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise This story alone, should be the reason that anybody who Voted for this Bill must not be able to hold… https://t.co/5g6Ru9wTxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to spend the night with the piano man (well, as soon as I can get through the giant mob of people wai… https://t.co/HbDF6JdgB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedStripeRocco @sotcreggaeradio @wprb @Selectajerry #HockeyTaxi🚕 rides again! Another pregame warm-up with my baby… https://t.co/W2qFLE1IdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cane River Apa by Cane River Brewing Co @ 1911 Historic City Hall — https://t.co/YUBDqrY3DI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulomeo I didn’t like the fact that he wasn’t for Medicare for all. We need bold initiatives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Quan2491 @FloydNueveNine Ay I don’t let people forget about church league lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJ_NCS @ShannonSharpe That's definitely the only thing worth watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@munday_tatum @StateCoachD @BillyGlasscock4 @PackFootball Congratulations]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's like telling bees not to pollinate, I mean the fun,  just began..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdwood_wood @curly_lovitt @lisaponyexpress @Starrbryte67631 @Brandonmartine @markfuller86 @pausalaura… https://t.co/18HBdroGfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity No tRump it’s because you are a batsh!t crazy criminal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a @nilslofgren 12 months! Will now see Nils and his band in May @thebirchmere after seeing him with Greg Varlo… https://t.co/F8r2xxOl6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[A downtown congestion charge and parking cash out program would help end this insanity. @LitmanVTPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamChronicler Putting it another way:  Has the civil service become so politicized it is now incapable of independ… https://t.co/CFt3frd1v8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissFlint @SenFeinstein I followed you a year ago or so.  The best thing I have ever seen you tweet is when… https://t.co/jP2mVAXNmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I too would stand behind him if he were standing at the top of an empty stair case]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Intense Ass kissing is not going to get you that Nobel...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philly drivers crack me up. They really risk their lives by cutting off tractor trailers at 100mph on I-95 in order… https://t.co/OTMaLPh5eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgrmse @AOCpress Cat self propel because some of those propellers have a plastic piece Omni smaller portion of the… https://t.co/OBcIeBgizL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been on the grind tryin' find my way (Ayo, ayo ayy) People come and go but I'ma be the one to stay (Ayo, ayo a… https://t.co/lmHiEoGfTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Ann Coulter's days as a conservative are over. What's next for her? CNN analyst?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The House of Representatives just passed H.R.1, the Democrats' ethics- and election-reform bill. But there is no vo… https://t.co/st7kFFWYhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraArchulet10 Hun that means so much to me and to know thta it helps someone in some way. Mucho Love hun! 😊❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanLegion @netflix @AmLegionPost283 @MikeD0WLING It was a fantastic evening thanks to my wife @Rebadams7  and… https://t.co/rLRar3lxCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHigginsSD that was good been. Cracked me up. Gotta take a break from listening for a bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Im_Mike_Y Agree to disagree. Rubtsov (first rounder) plus a first rounder? And a fourth? Nobody outside of Minnesota knows who he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qikipedia Sometimes I receive information I don't know what to do with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zechariah 12:9  And on that day I will seek to destroy all the nations that come against Jerusalem  Just as the Bib… https://t.co/w7XAMRDSHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IowaDieselCrew I loose my mind when people don’t know the difference 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForThePeopleABC @Ben_Rappaport I claim fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. #Forthepeople Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/… https://t.co/taNCiIX7HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ideally building a football team with 4 safeties isn't the best way, but that's okie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Mr President or as I like to say Mr. I know everything about everything. You are very silent about the workpla… https://t.co/jj4gufMcWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @FreedomIsntfr14 Do socialist not know the difference between actual money and tax credits ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do everything with Love. You never know when your last breath will be. Allow everyone to remember you in the light… https://t.co/ayaYIdsJL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_deitchler The media attention is crazy! It’ll be interesting to see what he ends up doing. I though Pippen w… https://t.co/HsbTRWP6U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter I'm going to retweet everything that I do today over and over until you get it together and get rid of that… https://t.co/cBV4Qw1u4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unusual game day. Before I go to HC, I’m going to my daughter’s confirmation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Zamboni towing another Zamboni.   Women's hockey is wild, y'all. https://t.co/FSsIo9mMtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, and it’s Vladimir Putin’s fault we have @realDonaldTrump as @POTUS ...  the blame game doesn’t make the results… https://t.co/0igtW4rNIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawn_haggard @chuckwoolery U didn't see on the news 2days ago how USA began  I got fake news. Most valuable thing… https://t.co/gFKv99Ipj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some day maybe I’ll meet a girl who I can love half as much as this guy loves Kyler Murray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnsonburg holds a 16-13 lead over Cameron County at the half. Austin Green leads the Rams with 7 pts, Caden Beldi… https://t.co/mX5XiyFje5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly ladies I would wife u up if ur down for this I am not insecure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime from Lakeland. Riviera Prep hanging tough. Trailed Seffner by as much as 15, trails only 31-27 at the break.@J_McPherson1126]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix Hey @MrPeanut please pull your ads from Alt-Reich Hasse Netzwerk @FoxNews. If you advertise you mus… https://t.co/aQmG8EyZmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gods_Giff @CoreBTSLI @StarBoxing @TheParamountNY @CoreBTS @barracuda @PPFpretzels @whittneysmith_ @IntraLogic… https://t.co/wKaY94SWdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starrbryte67631 Good morning Stella. Have a beautiful Monday. ☕️☕️😉💕❣️ https://t.co/jCgl68mWGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets reflect on who we may be addicted to as opposed to in love with, don’t accept crumbs, your emotional stability… https://t.co/nGpD5e2fsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm glad I plugged the semi in last night.  7-Day Forecast for Latitude 44.06°N and Longitude 89.28°W (Elev. 889 ft) https://t.co/U7mIXiH3qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GodFirst✨ #BlessedDayFam! #PraiseTheLord✨ Do you need a new garment today? I’m not talking about a physical garmen… https://t.co/duZQ73WiAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeskii I feel you. As long as you keep your awareness and take heed to the signs, you aint gon fail Bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pic is from this check in location circa 1950's. Haskbrauhaus flashback - Drinking an 60 Minute IPA by @dogfishbeer… https://t.co/gzNYOHN5an]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate Recap: he misidentifies a local conservative Phoenix news anchor as a liberal who intends to use a T… https://t.co/tv4C29lsEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeebusTrump In a sense, yes. NATO countries are protected by our nukes. We are obligated to defend them with nukes if necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if it’s the cheerleaders or how Hwrd Rock usually smells but I think the atmosphere in here is 70% hair spray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #Cincinnati #Bengals from 1965 on.  https://t.co/EDxJKThI3O … … … … … https://t.co/7U4B89a6Wb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's currently 24° F and clear in Harrisburg with active alerts. Visit https://t.co/D0EYeDbBdR  From  1Weather… https://t.co/z6r8zLCcc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go!! Boarding for #FirstDayAtPAE flight to @LASairport begins now. (Agent just offered to check carry-ons t… https://t.co/1aVpqMzqDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not like Harper alone would mean a WS title but it would be a huge piece of being a juggernaut. God this hurts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaMarshall12 He had to overcome lots of fear...I had to exercise a lot of patience! We both won. Dudes one dedicated lap cat!!!😂😂😂🍸]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are myths, there are legends... and there’s @gregarious and @briansolis #SXSW @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/dpvXaMnxd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All gas no brakes straight to the neck kinda day I prefer it that way 🚛💨💨💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denhousewives @DenverChannel @AuroraGov @JoshWhitston Leah- that’s very generous of you. Send me your info at Tom.… https://t.co/NeEqdVZ6Tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Only a guilty person tries to defend himself this much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always wanted to go to a Haters Roast, but now I will never give a single dollar to @MPPresent. This is not ho… https://t.co/Uvd65zM5to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Str*ight artists trying to figure out how much queerbaiting they can get away with so they can get that g*y coin in… https://t.co/Znw3IaiiMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Facts #LeaveMeAlone flippdinero Voice  #Swervin #BitchYouDumbAssFuck @ Amber Pointe, Kissimmee, Florida https://t.co/bbtuetSzOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrenuzt @Vickynguita @NBCNews Venezuela es zona de catástrofe. Como si hubiéramos perdido una guerra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me performing at the local starbucks so i can get money to afford roxy tickets https://t.co/gJLBhraO62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justinarchies_ I want u to know I use the word gimmick all day because of u Delo fan boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to lose all that bulking I did last year and put it back on as lean muscle. To get so far and have to start o… https://t.co/GOglKbOLfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a music video tonight.  Follow my IG story for behind the scenes, if you're into that sorta thing... #VinceVicariEP  🕺🎥🎶📼📺👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best people! Love love love love love! @ Mission Church https://t.co/2mydb4JU4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[In s recent interview with Complex magazine about the history of the evolution of streetwear on Fairfax,… https://t.co/4tbv0bO9De]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion has already proved himself and really didn’t need to play 1 single game in college.. if I was him I’d fake this injury till the draft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WPXIGordon @WPXI If Detroit Police are correct and charges are filed then Allegheny County Controller Chelsa Wagne… https://t.co/KJBrGMrzKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrigPodcast @AAFFleet @SDFleetBeat @SDFleetPR @aafiron @aafhotshots @aafexpress @TheAAF @AJTarpley I'm totally… https://t.co/5lRGmKA7IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me getting ready to rock and roll at regionals we won our first game 32-22 @ Duncan Lake Middle School https://t.co/75wJsmthYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeumannDadEO I've entered so many of their giveaways haha someday I'll win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbrender Because Fred and Jeff “Coupon” Wilpons own the team. The same owners who didn’t want Piazza and only… https://t.co/zX2ROuyfLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm considering dropping everything to go buy pizza rolls because I haven't had a proper bag of pizza roles since I came to college]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moowood72 @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump No. This one has a Trump judge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be the first global apparel brand to incorporate more sustainable cottonized hemp into our products.  Less… https://t.co/Igre2kPXQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATX_PATRIOT @ROCKONOHIO @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Trump the Chump https://t.co/RXAXKfUYr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Jealous losers 👎👎👎 No one cares, I’ll be watching Republican debates on Fox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes #GymJordan ? Isn’t that the guy who covers up for pedophiles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When one door closes, another door opens. Even when the first door was slammed shut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneSchumache1 It's not about agreeing or disagreeing... it's about the constant negativity coming from people ju… https://t.co/17XZI9ZWZt]]></document></documents></author>