<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i’m making an etsy for the vintage store and i’m already annoyed. ughhhh i hate etsy but i think it’ll bring in more traffic :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pulled out my 34 year old flute today because my 10yo asked. I also established the fact that I don’t have the pa… https://t.co/psS1q3oCHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balance is hard. It's so easy to get sucked into consumerism, politics, hate, fear....etc. Follow your pain and pas… https://t.co/Oqu4qq7HX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The email was cold and distant, like Maine if you are someone from the West Coast. It started with “Dear Applicant”… https://t.co/3UIIfSbg1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq Agreed. That Trump blows smoke  may be the best we can hope for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary look at me! @meanders_ @sdowns https://t.co/M7LMyBgpmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And where does the Governor’s bill do worst? Poverty.  We don’t have to wait to see how things play out, Mr. Secret… https://t.co/YbuNMV7lze]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice little escape up north to work on thesis @ Kensington, Pennsylvania https://t.co/OOHYS4Bw7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i die don’t just yeet me in a ditch, yeet me in a ditch of spaghetti so you never forghetti k thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homemadeguitars @AOC She sure is and I love the fact that she has made many folks afraid. She is making a differen… https://t.co/p0ZF4Y4s33]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like going out with picky mfs, niggas gotta have the right liq, perfect spot, perfect music, and perfect ratio to have a good time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple tablespoons of vinegar in the water - boil 15 minutes, then in cold water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna You are one of my favorites. I think that your dress for the opening is fabulous. The best out of the bu… https://t.co/XnjYOyb9Jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateMansi @justinhartley Waiting for Victoria Konefal to weigh in about her name. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many passes were they making on possessions they scored? How many deflections were they getting in games they w… https://t.co/9l8qdkAagX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me, help you! #mariferdesign #GraphicDesigner #wsgraphicdesigner https://t.co/aWEWxc2kEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tocc4JackAdams Stars because they we are two points (and the Knights losing again) from being in that third place spot in the pacific]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmaMauler @joshuabaerwald It’s easier to look for a break in the conversation when you’re in it. So then you can… https://t.co/N91C0ZtYBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando estas comiendo tan deli que no quieres que se acabe la comida 🤤🐽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Ada at the Sunset BLVD. merchandise shop in Hollywood Studios was fantastic today and for the ENTIRE shop… https://t.co/PQC6Mssp7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone: #YGISGOINGTOJAILPARTY   Me: ok but Blackpink is still coming though right? https://t.co/YM3H8hFL0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberBrownWV Me too lol although I think I may make it my mission to make sure Fast gets booted from my district!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUENOS DÍAS!🌞  MIS CORAZONES BELLOS!❤️ BENDITO DIOS!🙏 FESTEJANDO NUESTRO ÉXITO ESTE FIN DE SEMANA  EN SEATTLE,WA GR… https://t.co/hNN3omxcQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoiseResists @CarrieDDahl @MSNBC @JaniceMcGeachin Swastika finger wear for republicans. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the doctor mentions heart failure and more issues about my grandma. https://t.co/8koa32vSD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve lost to way many people throughout my life due to natural reasons, you really think i’ll care if you choose to walk out? I don’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh the memories. gotta love a good hatch stand off https://t.co/7gtHW4JjCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MajorJensen33 I read this at it only took me .2 seconds to realize this is the opposite of what you would say. Great tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this nigga tryna be funny getting me a Gucci bag .I asked for Chanel]]></document><document><![CDATA[To add fuel to your fire @BillSpadea- we had 25” of snow fall in Baldwin, WI yesterday. No salt or plow trucks stan… https://t.co/bQ0BZ7u2DT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing you a day filled with love! 💞 ⁣⁣⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ ⁣⁣⁣⁣ #realestate #pnw #seattle #bellevue #tacoma #sammamish… https://t.co/JlOmT5Zy7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take some time to find yourself first and recoop, take an outside perspective and make it a learning experience, no… https://t.co/JE2sCQO7Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dchinn2005 @AlisonWarren6 @mimibeck617 @NO1GifQueen @BeckyBo37839654 @Errriee @KKay7777 @ksage10 @AnaHRuiz10… https://t.co/Vrqhf2vG59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPPDiddy2 @RepAdamSchiff @PPPDiddy2  Are you kidding? Trump doesn’t plan, he won’t take his briefings, and “knows… https://t.co/jSIm4rKWfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McguireScotty I think he’s had way toooo much wacky weed   Better stay in California]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s audition season!   #allthedialects #matilda #secretgarden #rollofthedice #actorslife #latheatre #kmw… https://t.co/LL5FLmyrqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay found some tweets from when I was 11 and I just wanted to say YIKES these are so bad like why tf did I say thi… https://t.co/fTskXvufN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gender bias in academia is for real! Be the agent of change! #InternationalWomensDay #WomanInScience #HumanScientist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect night❤️ in #nola @ FrenchQuarter NewOrleans https://t.co/YRjWcnf4Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChewOnThis31 @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Hello Russian bot  I know because you don't know how our government works.… https://t.co/XBbnZQ1yRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[life really be hitting me when im in the car so if u see me cryin..,,,..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall Your words are powerful and spread in all directions. The words can be returned in many types of reflection.]]></document><document><![CDATA[KC BH dog show airing on NBC Easter Sunday presented by Purina. My girls are home in NY w their dad and 6 inches of… https://t.co/nGLWcrJhIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KSjZ7pUTfj #onpoli #ResignLisaMacLeod  #cdnpoli https://t.co/VsZ097s9ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are committed to preventing homelessness and helping those who are struggling through job-training. Check out th… https://t.co/TAF7pEBR0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1dawg4life @mikehanback The hunter told me he recalls 24 inches, but it’s been 8 years. He was going to locate the… https://t.co/IIiSsVm1K8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wonderful thing (actually there’s many) about @mydrunkelephant is when my 4 yo wants to get ready w/ me I’m not… https://t.co/1wwMCsgfVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamjackiemc @SusanSmythSL Thank you darling and you rest well...1am with you over there...😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any recommendations on a florist for flowers for a funeral please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normayoungwhit1 @AOC @ltthompso 😂😂😂😂 That’s hysterical. Do you honestly think that the IRS doesn’t have a team of… https://t.co/eBO6TNs17I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMyro Popular Mechanics: "At big car companies' headquarters, does every employee drive that car?"  (Spoiler a… https://t.co/vUz4mZYPAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mavs17888 Same tayo girl haha. Kaya lang wala si maris now.   #POPSSSS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing at the top o my lungs tends to make everything better...#janisjoplin #mercedesbenz #music #acapella… https://t.co/feoVfOSEbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thousands strike in Spain to mark International Women's Day  https://t.co/kbsI8tkNAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nancybugx6 @craytusjones That is a loonggg time what is the reason you cannot finish?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's scary when you got someone in your neighborhood trying to get your kids up. Police are searching for a coupl… https://t.co/PmMD5GG1iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Streets To Homes,Reconnect To Homes,The Red Cross,and The Mayor's all Communicated a plan and support,this would… https://t.co/IGx3VNBgCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jensen2077 @CBR @michaelrosenbum Yea, that was kinda my point. And Birthright isn’t even considered cannon, so it… https://t.co/bfWQzs9qeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blessed#family#happymonday#ittakesavillage#love#grandchildren#thankyougod#hangingwithnana#6amisbetterthan5😳😜 @ Roc… https://t.co/lP6Ug0lLLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Don’t feel bad. It’s horrifying, but I watch Fox a little every day. Gotta know thine enemy, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Karpiak @k8bischHRLaw THANK YOU for always making me just bust out laughing Adam. You are the best!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton @ShefaniStan You’re supposed to share values with your partner - not lack of values. 😑🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pm3900 @Cricket6 @Fridaygirl1969 @davisis1 @hannadjh @madShana She was very lucky to find someone like you to live… https://t.co/55ue5ao51L]]></document><document><![CDATA[While these are great ideas to address the dignity of all people it is still unconscionable that we haven’t solved… https://t.co/afEEVgpqQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s all I’ve watched on my lunch break and it never fails to make me laugh the whole time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finkerton driving down the Henry Hudson on our way to the hotel pre @moeperiod and you announce the boys are comin… https://t.co/DpcBwwAcf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a break from social media for a bit, so... https://t.co/DPYMbvPzdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawkeyefirst @Ballzees @TooFaced @ShoeDazzle She has always appeared to have a mean streak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[love being able to cook a nice breakfast every sunday morning w/ brax 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gate. Less than a minute later, the sun was behind a cloud and the shadow was gone. #blackandwhitephoto #shadows https://t.co/xgYfOy767f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSchwarzenegger crying in Midnight Sun actually broke my heart. So brb gonna go cry in the shower because that shit was so sad 😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Documenting Manchesters rapidly evolving sky line the town hall and Bethan tower represents the old and new. The pa… https://t.co/6XpfOCMEPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[this dress is gorgeous but i genuinely can’t tell if this is any adams or isla fisher but regardless they slayed… https://t.co/wi0z99sxoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_akash i’m testing my theory that you have to have a PhD to pronounce it the second way hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TataCalde @FIA_F2 @ArdenMotorsport @hwaag_official @ClaroColombia @escuderiatelmex @Coldeportes @fiawim… https://t.co/b8L6feIuf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxtheatrestl - do you ever close due to weather? How do you announce?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boyfriends are cool &amp; all but have you met my roommates? 🤷🏻‍♀️ Happy love day from the 515! #valentinesday⁠ ⁠ https://t.co/ph7IzP4TgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost thehappymindclub • • • • • • @ Sacramento, California https://t.co/FyKEP9YkbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jordyn didn’t do anything. Stop saying you take responsibility and that you were drunk. #RedTableTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gjglenn @RobertFife I wouldn't worry about the money As Minister of Women's Affairs she spent very little to advan… https://t.co/Xew298raXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AcademyAwards #Oscar2019 #RedCarpet #Fashion #WhoWoreItBetter https://t.co/0DpPOsdb03]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second I would’ve heard that recording I’m walking in that building and beating those ugly, horrible BITCHES UP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing you &amp; yours lots of love on my (2nd) favorite holiday of the year 💜 Happy Valentine’s Day ✨ 📷:… https://t.co/yWIMn0Hc1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Jesus!!! 🙏🏽 @ Old Saybrook, Connecticut https://t.co/l3pSHzSOzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missin’ my cat Lilo aka LiLi aka Leland Palmer 🐱. Even though we are 1,000+ miles apart we’re still very connected.… https://t.co/TnagBBVOVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[he teeth whitening products behind these numbers include chewing gums, toothpaste, gels, and kits that promise to r… https://t.co/uvDzRKuLjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I decided I was going to fly to LA to attend the show, I told myself it was because 2018 had been awful for me… https://t.co/6acz2VDpu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuwqO1P1QuabXpa @WorldsBestCBS @dimash_official #TWBDimash , #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[brushed my teeth for 17 minutes just to piss off my roommate https://t.co/NXfs5gZt9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every word of this. Take all these songs out of rotation. https://t.co/dlsZxIyBmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s still really fucking weird to me that I live in Arizona after living in Missouri my whole life and idk if the feeling will ever change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laker622 @realDonaldTrump The very least we can ask from any of our governments is to not disintegrate us in a nuc… https://t.co/tXpyD7CsWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to update, it’s just Hiram Lodge, and I’ve never hated any fictional character more in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman! I sip from the chalice of your love, Sweet ambrosia churned by the Gods, In the vast ocean of mystery, Sad i… https://t.co/KLqZnHYpaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JmeJeannie is an absolutely amazing human being and honestly deserves the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love working with the team at @EminentSEO ! Happy Monday! #seo #socialmedia #marketing #marketingfirm]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is no amount of badness that I Wanna Get Better by Bleachers can’t fix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slactingco Cake is one of the funniest plays we've seen in a long time!  Betsy West is hilarious.  Go see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every morning he asks himself, how can I endanger this country, undo anything Obama accomplished, and/or piss off t… https://t.co/80wcngylv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should watch Tashi and the Monk. I love this documentary so much.  https://t.co/hLEGL7aJKm]]></document></documents></author>