<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lkbowles @JoshPower5 @cspan @McConnellPress @senatemajldr Sorry that’s a separate issue that Trump’s on the wrong side. So many.  My bad 🤗.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveled to India recently and had the pleasure of talking about @Accenture’s 2019 Technology Vision report – our p… https://t.co/wMuQ2DXSIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[People might think that a 5 minute talk would be easier than an hour long talk. They would be wrong. The lightning… https://t.co/0pDtfffFph]]></document><document><![CDATA[GORGEOUS NEW LISTING!! IN PRIME HARTSELLE LOCATION!!  415 McClanahan Street, Parker Real Estate Residential  EXTRA… https://t.co/lJQcW7zp7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to get home with @ofdarkarabella &amp; orders whatever she wants]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sunday... @KyleBusch wins and @MartinTruex_Jr comes in 2nd... #RowdyNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DecalT17 @CellBioProf @SenTedCruz @HoustonChron No I’m confusing anything. The average temps cited of the 1930s as… https://t.co/vTYwR9MMNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMFodera @CarStan1114 @UncorkedRemarks @lovefromitalia @ricasoli99 @ciarahinton @SarahHellerMW @alifeinwine… https://t.co/VLoewSwWRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A ferry on the Sound, its windows as bright as ingots of gold, seemed to be carting a load of light out of the cit… https://t.co/Wtj1u49Qy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like long nails and I don’t know why...shit just been growing on me lately 😩🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You alone I long to worship…. (@ Emmanuel Christian Center in Spring Lake Park, MN) https://t.co/ZKOMYVZP3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lincoln Financial Field - @lffstadium in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/A4p7pBDxPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champwebdotnet You do get that an entire @IndyCar team is owned by wealthy Argentines who have frequently sought a… https://t.co/E4c5hr9EB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock @ciarakellydoc Weather was actually decent here for once. Great outdoor walks today.  Closing in on… https://t.co/aGToluoxR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic, as always. - Drinking a Tea Weiss by @CraneBrewing @ KrogHaus  — https://t.co/5SPrJPoC2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaseyForge @PLDenis4 @__alex_h_ That’s not a specific TFC issue; it’s a MLS issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even have my own work Truck #Tmobile @ San Diego, California https://t.co/T5uia487kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who designed these ugly @NHLFlyers jerseys?  #LetsGoFlyers https://t.co/N8rI40EQXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp Hence Gov. Northam not understanding race relations. VA is a weird place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_RyanGuillory @TheTobster111 Syphon off 10% of $100M for the Trump family ? $10,000,000.00 ~ That's a nice chuck of pocket change...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvin_knapp @dirtvision Everytime I have watched a race this year so far.  I get kicked off the broadcast about 5 times.  #pleasefix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acaiprincess What I’d write with the rose petals https://t.co/dSXHdaVG7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graduate Tempe Biannual Award featuring Ulises Heredia https://t.co/KPQzFCbjPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home game 16: @GTMBB vs. No. 17/19 @FSUHoops with @elmore83. Another sold-out game! 🏀 #TogetherWeSwarm… https://t.co/qY2nJFSh79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackBPR Anything to insure the Lefts grip on power. Indoctrinate in the schools then get them to vote off that ind… https://t.co/XzWEgVWr5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preseason odds to win the West. I’m loving all the LAL- Lebron disaster talk. “Playoff mode”. Memes.  He’ll be 36 b… https://t.co/ldSgXWJPRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the @TheAAF the Columbus team could be called the Columbus Monsters or Columbus Bullies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uofmemphis to see Governor Bill Lee give the West Tennessee Regional State of the State address.  “This is a remar… https://t.co/O0XepVl4QT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveSheehey When am I going to get a hot take on Megan McCarthy's rabbit dress?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, it’s tough because we’re only dealing with four years, but... ehhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen O had 2 hamsters, Rachel and Phoebe. One (can't remember whom) killed the other one and literally ate its head. Fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarletA_447 I always tell people: I don't run. If you see me running don't even bother looking behind me because… https://t.co/Qmx5lSxXGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyIntHD @sadieastanley @taylor_ortega I’m like the biggest Taylor Ortega Fan you’ll ever see! I’ve seen the mo… https://t.co/45ua6kjyP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 19 - MSNBC Daily:      16 states sue Trump; Any ‘first-year law student could argue' case, says CA… https://t.co/1CIs35aptZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewWinston @jessicalongdev Ha! Unfortunately Trump sucks all the oxygen out of every thing.  And of course, bad… https://t.co/jyMT8UYMTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the canes don’t win tommorow we got problems but until then idk it’s life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting sleep w folded thin towels in instead of a pillow. It’s been great! https://t.co/BjxYIVFL2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 @Sportsnet Blue Jays radio is in great shape with Wagner and Wilner, a worthy duo in the tradition o… https://t.co/L8zxKbYjGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanSproul Minimum wage jobs were originally for unskilled teenagers working part time. Once a person builds ski… https://t.co/VxKMb88Ug0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 2AM, I need to start getting ready to sleep https://t.co/wnUUxMAKTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why in the hell would he go on @cnn?  Obama did Fox just a handful of times in 8 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get how people are embarrassed to hang out with their parents, I hang out with mine y me la paso a toda madre. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the teetering Blue Jackets and an upcoming week filled with opportunity and peril  https://t.co/Tcqfd5OHoO #CBJ #NHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see her tonight! #EllaMai #detroit #concert #nightlife #soldout @ Saint Andrew's Hall https://t.co/jhKn069dbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost made it to 10! But I’ll take 9 after my win last night! @hqtrivia #hqtrivia https://t.co/BRY0BFCZAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HikindDov @JessieJaneDuff @IlhanMN And American Jews still vote Democrat. SMH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/3 of presidents (down from 3/4 in 2018) say they are worried about Republicans' declining confidence in higher ed… https://t.co/QUOWfi68Ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen is pretty much owning Jim Jordan. It’s not a route but it seems like a bear down so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Porter tearing it the gender construct apart on the #Oscars red carpet. https://t.co/Q3kud58tbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justicedems @IlhanMN @AOC @RashidaTlaib @Ilhan You’re a racist antisemite and embarrass our Country!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the music portion right with @jennylewis and #LukeNelson #SXSW #netflix https://t.co/1MB7aVBSMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LlucyRobles @ferbelaunzaran A no existieron contrapesos? Tu crees que gobernaron con el congreso afin? Ilusa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCallGarrett Proper etiquette says you shouldn’t unleash that type of fury on someone the first time bro it was a courtesy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dntfolwme @anon16830911 @samisnothappy @aymanndotcom @AnthonyJ_48 @mshafiquk @MaajidNawaz https://t.co/3SPvthzFk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Johnny MFing Wrestling helped Velveteen Dream put on hands down his best match to date. He is a damn machine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawrence_ Harper will sign with the team that offers him the most money, it’s simple and easy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Kinda tough position to be in, when your own family is doing opposition research on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might take longer than you'd like, but God always gives you an answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Eddie @PROUD_USAER Funny @dmitriperov1 @moekamerow @ThomasPKennedy3 @JohnLeksander @godrockin Hi John Buddy… https://t.co/5KPCffdgWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[IU Media Guys. Stop comparing Archie to Bennett, Wright, and coach K in their “rebuilds.”  There add comps right no… https://t.co/1lKPxScVv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I'm more excited by the idea of a Joker trailer in April than my own birthday in April]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu carita bonita cuando duermes, esa la quiero besar siempre. @Kitziafm 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow — the turnout for @accathon capital’s initial event, Panel2Cross!  Founder, Michael Zhu is introing how we make… https://t.co/65PMbBCys1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDC_HIVAIDS Tell Dr. Mermin that the reviews for the Ryan White Care Act field of agencies that I am in direct kno… https://t.co/w6TLjbAQ7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Infinity War again then told my dog I would throw her off a cliff to get the Soul Stone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 88% Off Services at Kepler Family Chiropractic https://t.co/RRfob0I1uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never stop dating your spouse. Love my Wednesdays with my lady sarahparks82 @ Radnor Lake State Park https://t.co/dNqEWgwF9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPlatizky Wow so interesting maybe more actors should sign up to take the BraZen Giant Ensemble Casting Workshop w… https://t.co/ylI6ZlIEzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoria_29 @Victoriaokane @imsure @gailtalk @GulfDogs @Pudingtane @seanhannitysays In two years the Pres race now… https://t.co/iQmW7PbLtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know all of the bands that I see on the Mystic Theatre marquee, but the different scales of tour bus (or be… https://t.co/eD2snSUPLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meagan_McHugh @CraigSmylie There are some things that only god can do....]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need Key Glock tickets for this weekend I’m on campus now $20 get them while supplies last  #AAMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually Duthie I didn't watched a single second of your unnecessary coverage of a made up non-event. I consider it… https://t.co/bTxIriyt4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_McGowan6 @DougGorman1 @kyle_patton @ChrisFisher247 Guy was in the gym at 6:30 this morning the day after he won Mr. Basketbll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhollon @realDonaldTrump What good reason did you come up with and that was almost 2 years ago......... why did it… https://t.co/3NiYT0UkiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottCoker @valerielouredaa @BellatorMMA Scott, will u put in a good word for me???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLW @laparktapia @TheSamiCallihan @beINSPORTSUSA Never saw anything like that in long time and I’m so happy… https://t.co/rarUx93npp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How much information do you want to obstruct before you go to jail Mr. P. You are making an easy c… https://t.co/gTOptaDoMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the dorm above me is fucking rn cause all I hear is the bed moving hopefully they get some rounds in for me too 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motorola memories: Life was simpler then..pocket size was perfect and; one of its best features was that it could b… https://t.co/ZdWZivmJw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my birthday!!! 🎉🎊🎂🎁🎈  Day 16 of @MarvelStudios superhero of the day!  #ElizabethOlsen #ScarletWitch  I would h… https://t.co/M80kFu4UoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SticksMix @Yvonne195063 Wish I could be more specific. 2nd Dr. appointment Wednesday. Could be serious. Don't want… https://t.co/mNIN4YbCKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marybenti1 @thehill What’s with everyone trying to arrest everyone?  Nobody should be arrested in this situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexialex The thing said the meds are less intense and given for a much shorter time. Then they switch to strong Ad… https://t.co/qz93SSMDky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellie (first thing this morning): “Guess what? It’s Daddy Daughter dance day!” 😍 #elliebelle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3GrandStrand  @F3_VitD 2 pax handled buisness this morning. #whetstone https://t.co/k1jkHut56B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnMcLaneKuster @ChairmanBuckley @DartDems Will you please resign so NH has an actual smart person in Congress rep… https://t.co/7f6AslmTU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegingerbanks @gingerbanks1 What are those neck wrap things you always wear? They always look so cool on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VidiyeTshimanga @tuandense alternance de façade vous vous êtes jeté dans la gueule du loup il n y a point de porte… https://t.co/CbYTbw9296]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge shout out to my @LeakyCon/@bwaycon/@MischiefMgmt fam past and present for this. Thank you all so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust me they are impressed,it’s just that your ceiling is so much higher and they are gonna push you to the max!… https://t.co/vePY74n8xY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times and good eats! @ Fujiyama Steak House of Japan https://t.co/V3KfPqjrgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WK_Stylez Everyone knows they are delicious! Especially when they are stale]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan, you’re such a damn Libtard that even you believe your own lies!! Jesus man, can ya keep it just a little real?]]></document><document><![CDATA[From six years ago at an APSE convention in Detroit. Me, with one of my heroes in the business, Dan Jenkins. He die… https://t.co/PMhEbaK2Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjaimesb No evalúan que la brecha no es importante siempre y cuando los más pobres sean más ricos, o sea, que el e… https://t.co/OiO3LXXGtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[As part of my efforts to support #autismawareness leading up to and throughout April, I'm offering reduced rates on… https://t.co/2GwIXv5QYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowkey wanna go back to my HS to see my plaque from state and how the school progressed if any]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Unto me, who am less than the least of all saints, is this grace given, that I should preach among the Gentiles th… https://t.co/qh6IGtLsMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk Oh no, please say it’s not so. That his life is not in jeopardy. Alex Trebec is a bright beam of light in o… https://t.co/vHY5wovQfB]]></document></documents></author>