<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Are you f****g serious he is the one whom hates the NFL and that is 90% black shut up trump 😠😠😠😠and loves the KKK🖕🖕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Predicts or “hopes”? No way in hell we are letting them manipulate this scourge back into the White House again. No way. Nyet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atwell_kristen @Baseballprobz @Baseball I literally do dishes every day after lunch at the office 😂  Today I did t… https://t.co/eORBbXCIVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the things about love and life is that most end in tragedy because they cannot go on forever I feel for you… https://t.co/MkjXI5XSlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad sent me a message saying not to drink 7up because it had some acid in it or whateva.. I told him I don’t dri… https://t.co/BLbfcsCMjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyHighJason Awwww thank you my dear friend.  Love and miss your handsome face💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he got into an accident he was not driving they made him sit in the metal part of the truck with a lap belt ..… https://t.co/dfYT0sOK3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dyson: 1 Spider: 0 Not gonna get away from Nanno with the extendo vacuum wand.  PETA Folks, no comments, please.… https://t.co/jI3hv66eSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl, that judge told you to STFU. Go to jail, and do not collect $200.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/H331fIY4ax #WebRTC #webrtcdevelopment #Beth #jordyntristan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to still be alive after today, days like this is why I always thank the man upstairs before I lay myself to rest at night🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DentonReports @offallawson @gabrielmalor @Popehat I’ve never felt that “woe is me vibe”. I loved teaching. It cons… https://t.co/xV9XL3UD4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you used to think that “reptile” and “republican” were the same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holysnipxr Looks like I’m not sending him anymore homemade curry 😡 @RiotShockTTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithClaverie @JudithLight She’s CRAZY good on this show. Ughhhhhh heartbreaking. Wait till you get to the scene w… https://t.co/HHRhLiL2q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m drinking hot chocolate out of my chip cup, watching the vampire diaries, living life minus having the flu ofcourse]]></document><document><![CDATA[It isn’t even FA time yet and every NFL fandom is losing their damn minds!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenlp @markshiver @JayInslee Not answering my question, just throwing out lies. So tiresome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Shut up, Henry” is our new “Stay in the House, Carl!”  #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️🕶💕🗽🇺🇸💍✨ ************************************ ditaeyewear #ditaeyewear #ditasunglasses #magic #magicbychloe… https://t.co/Zu9NZB8BMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cCZN4pphr2 “Arts allow for elaboration, allow for repetition. Memory is certainly enhanced through rep… https://t.co/JWbG3HDtDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @janiyadowns ! You are one blessed, gifted, talented, intelligent and humble young lady! Love you!… https://t.co/WavWfx0Y3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRalphNorman @RepMarkMeadows @GOPoversight These jokers think that they can get away with what they've been gett… https://t.co/iP8EZALPh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Jonas brothers and @taylorswift13 have a tour around the same time period I’m screwed. Anyone have a goldmine I can dig into.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Speech? This was the ranting of an idiot hopped up on #adderall to a group of people to… https://t.co/hcLOXa6eJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was a little much, here are my #5happythings : Not crying when things got stressful - twice (yay, the med… https://t.co/Ub8wZaHzq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know?  One adventure on my bucket list is to compete in a fitness competition? I'm checking it off this yea… https://t.co/ZJ3dfI6ZUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Q1yeHLIng2 and donate if you’re able to. We are also on Facebook by searching Support Working Animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our science department has a reason to celebrate 🎉 and show our love ❤️  to @Mrs_Krukowski There’s a new dragon on… https://t.co/pLyactx6If]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tutorial for my previous eyeshadow look will be up on tuesday 👀 Sabar na]]></document><document><![CDATA[the internet is the easiest way to see a snapshot into someone's life, it's also one of the most deceiving ways to… https://t.co/oGLDtKizfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigredwavenow So heartbreaking. Jesus, be there &amp; help them. Thank You. Amen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTS of “The Struggle” by @dtroubledmind  #actorslife🎬 #modellife🌎 #thanksfortheluvnsupport @ Pine Bluff, Arkansas https://t.co/PiYpZMVt81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remember guys, that we have a one week break until the NEXT season of drag race... I need a whole year to breath honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Their funny helped build my house” says Ron Howard of writers Lowell Ganz (Happy Days) and Babaloo Mandel who firs… https://t.co/yuhf6CQVCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Soups and Stews to Warm Your Body and Soul  - https://t.co/Hb3SQ7YZmV #healthyrecipes #soup #winter #healthymom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kawawa to si mahal kung mag kasama kami ngayon HAHAHAHAHAHA mall pa lang gali pagod na eto pa kaya- panay na reklamo nyan ay apooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you thought “Mahershala Ali” was the trickiest name associated with Green Book, allow me to introduce you to: th… https://t.co/PEulN43CcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es que, lo que pasa en la política de mi isla, duele. https://t.co/hF7N7yJc8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @Pacers @keybank @IMS @Jbriggsy_14 @tattoo49ers @GAstarwarsfan @dega_boy_87 @DannyLeBlanc24… https://t.co/nNp0FcJjT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck #23 and the prodigy volleyball team today.. second day of tournament play! https://t.co/VuksRZQdla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino I'm guessing you enjoyed that happy ending? What a disgusting little man you are... https://t.co/rXQH7bACy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby girl 😭 she’s having a rough time, but if she can protect her friends she’ll make it through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trench_art_room @AspynOvard @shanedawson @beth_marie8 @Ryland_Adams Agree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlessupMoose @1thankfulgirl1 Hahaha - listen #fam - you tapped out on my goodwill at #PaczkiDay - bang out those l… https://t.co/jQcRwLBjxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenbbooth Hashtag how you know you’re parenting right!!!!! way to go, mom!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t ever remember my old demi fan club user name cuz it’s been so long lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[New delivery waits for our Group in April. #Theater is always a big hit for #incentiveprograms  #eventplanners… https://t.co/EOx63eovfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunterpence so enjoyed watching you play, my son chose you when he was drafted even though he’s a pitcher. Hope yo… https://t.co/uzdgUQ7kqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irunningdad That’s so wonderful! What a weekend! He’s so cute!  My team is the Canucks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need the witch doctor that made the weather great in NOLA yesterday to do something about the weather in SanFran. #delayed 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been BEGGING for a Michael Jackson doc and I can’t fucking watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never tell a child their dreams are unlikely or outlandish. Few things are more humiliating, and what a tragedy it… https://t.co/sYqNhxvPe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had this at 9 , just got a call back for another interview on saturday @ one. Wish me luck you guys. This could be… https://t.co/JOU5itUqlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was in the 2nd grade, I requested Goodbye Earl at the girl scout sock hop. Mothers were terrified.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took Scarlett out for a drive today ❤️🌹 @nickhogan4real #r34gtr #skyline #gtr #r34 #imfast #nicksaidimthe… https://t.co/WnO8TiZSE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickMcEnroe @DaniilMedwed No he’s playing very well and a threat to anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fantastic ‘Wax Museum’ held by the 4th graders at @WoodrowWilsonelementaryschool in Neptune City.  This is o… https://t.co/VJkgZGNbiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretChipmunk7 @Adult_Sex_ED Yeaaa hahah “ soy la pequeña maravilla” https://t.co/cM14Dxf5IK in Spanish 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smhcharu @alcheskaa and i’m pretty sure it was also a transphobia issue too 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting truth @GovCuomo #moneyshouldfollowstudents #EquityforOssining #HarmedSuburbanFive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TwitterSupport can you delete user @nicolefacee since it hasn’t been used in 10 years so I can have it? Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 It's alway "opposite day" in the #RussianAsset's tiny brain. #ImpeachTrumpNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is coming...soon? Right? Please? 🌱 #coldblooded #lonesomemushroom @ Walnut Creek, California https://t.co/DcKg1UX0e9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algunas personas necesitan perder todo acceso a ti. Permanentemente, sin ninguna explicación. @ The Safe House https://t.co/evPhNW2avq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Galentine’s Day, friends! 💕 #bestdayoftheyear https://t.co/hdTyw26Ccp]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 418 ANDERSON AVE #Milford #CT  #realestate https://t.co/9bbGsoQ4Sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makinguthinkcom @IlhanMN The parents are responsible for their situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cohen has zero related to Russia collusion, according to most recent news reports. Cohen is a liar thus not credible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whew. Y'all get on here everyday with theory and debates going in a complete circle, using campus wifi. You haven't… https://t.co/gPgAsyyUWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have had 4 bad things happen to me today but I had  3 GOOD things happen to me and that’s over half the amoun… https://t.co/ikeej90VpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally remembered the name NB RIDAZ! and I’m all about it on my playlist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im suppose to be to work at 6 and im sitting on the floor smoking a blunt and my phone on 13% 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minjiiminie This was SO gooood! I hope you write another hot and romantic taekook fic soon. First time was just so great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewB64 @BeaverBaseball Cheer loud for me, Drew!!! Can you believe baseball is back already 😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwgop History will show McCabe as Paul Revere; Trump as Benedict Arnold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_RossX @JimC267 London is probably like New York Mike. lol I would love to visit both but the US and England c… https://t.co/m7NGCHLyyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best advice I heard today was, “don’t feel bad for cutting out toxic friends who want you to give advice but ne… https://t.co/qoZYlWURN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol I think you we just found the next American Idol! Absolutely 💖 Alejandro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was such a success but I’m dead tired y al rato todavía a chingarle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ever let someone make you feel like you ain’t shit when you’ve done EEVRRYYYYTHING for them except wipe their ass 😂🤣 scary mfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m calling it now. The @ColoradoRapids home opened next week is going to be a snowy one. #SnowClassicoPt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night, friends. I’m beat. I’m gonna jam to some Bee Gees til I lose consciousness. https://t.co/FeUsCTTlHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are humbled and honored to be recognized as the 4th Best brewery in South Carolina by @freetimessc .  Lot's of g… https://t.co/AV9AcEUsdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re $1500 away from our goal! #metoo #churchtoo #BelieveSurvivors #endchildabuse]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog laid a nasty fart in my room looked at me and then left. I love her Sm tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickiirvin And with  her cheating lying husband while he signs Bibles WTH?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueLivePDFans quick question... Should I celebrate being DISEASE FREE (AML) or should I not? I mean, the last tim… https://t.co/TcwVFa54BW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be beside you on your big day, Congrats Chelsea !!! 💕 @chelshelton99 https://t.co/WHYBwwWQg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[God does some of His best work in the sky over @BigCedarLodge. Looking forward to spending time there again this ye… https://t.co/Nn2S2C8zPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bank Of Stockton - Carson Oaks - @bankofamerica in Stockton, CA https://t.co/DkMbR8EgZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliefisher @GaETConf @ncties Whenever I hear that Fisher virgin "gasp" I just giggle because I know another is hooked!! @carissashuman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_cothran @VarshPrakash They were not at all deceptive. They were just... SHORTER. Feinstein was just as rude… https://t.co/Tp8VEqcjL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannicassette @weareKING Same! I hope you’re enjoying the day too my love ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[With one look, indeed. Such wonderment and pure, approving joy. She’s glorious. Billy is glorious. GLORIOUS! https://t.co/3CUL7NTpSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who does the music on #TheExpanse ? It’s so good. https://t.co/P2bNBRzdog]]></document><document><![CDATA[I punched my bf yesterday and he got a black eye 🤭 like oops did I do that?¿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Nope nope nope. I call BS on @davidfrum . @SpeakerPelosi is right.  I lived in non English speaking coun… https://t.co/o6Cn85Xnlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk what y’all are talking about february took three whole years to pass. it’s spring semester. everything hurts. i… https://t.co/R9Blwd3ig0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dellojello @cj_isnotokay @Katrdlee - your brother was your anecdote/example.]]></document></documents></author>