<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Learn from your mistakes &amp; don’t use them as an excuse to put your partner down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bostonrex @ainafehst @BorisRuiz22 @DoraGodoy @elisapxchx @Farmarato @danngonz @DUALIPA @Edurodriguezmo… https://t.co/2FC9b0v3ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulHembo What's the net after federal and state taxes for those players? About half of that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerfthemeta @LAGladiators @SeoulDynasty We’ll see. 😂😂 https://t.co/0IaytI9sRz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@All_American_4U @OlgaPer65487606 @Jilliemary @tripletsfan19 @Tom__Coleman @heroldbarton @kittymayo7101… https://t.co/JyPnZCno0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel free https://t.co/fNSvrWlcpX  That doesn’t make progressive tax rates any more inefficient and immoral]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s not a democrat. His minions are mostly evil. His favorite saint is Petersburg. Loves the NRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PHOTOS: Federal Way pulls away late to beat Puyallup 73-64.  https://t.co/BgNJmjK2mD  @smithlm12 @thenewstribune… https://t.co/z4vI10tAAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OssoKXLY   @700espn       THOUGHT THIS SAID IT BEST !! https://t.co/OPqJSZntwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fortressfin @heyitsCarolyn @EinsteinMaga @leftovergravy @raducom @luluHru @MAGAgirly @ctanner3 @familyfirstcorp… https://t.co/sEtWGYKVpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is terrifying.  I hope child protective services -at the very least - is investigating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the annual VALENTINE’S DAY TRIPLE FEATURE!!! 💜💜💜🌈🌈🌈👨‍❤️‍👨👨‍❤️‍👨👨‍❤️‍👨🎬🎬🎬  First up, ISLE OF DOGS https://t.co/Tt4WJ8Zh1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGettys CONGRATS  BUT WHY DID I WATCH THIS AT THE GYM!? https://t.co/tqSZ7EdR90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 Gender...pull down your pants look in the mirror....you only have 2 choices]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstrosOptimism2 They all taste different. It depends on the water. Try them grilled or broiled if you're just putt… https://t.co/uSmcB1bcxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time setting up account, going into 3rd month of fail, faxed info to @BankofAmerica repeatedly, with confirma… https://t.co/Sz7pBb8Wfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my work is available on https://t.co/bo67fHYDel   #thedailysketch #drawing #sketch #painting #art #draw365… https://t.co/f5RsmNRVrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone who could.. or is willing to help..  please take a minute to check out my story.  https://t.co/y3XDAC9ILQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noooo #SNOW ❄️ Yes here in #LasVegas ... Maybe I’m just having some kind of TV 📺 #weatherman flashback? How can thi… https://t.co/DdUFqQ0s0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjeong But did you die??  I had too, sorry lol... I'm sure people quoting your own shit gets annoying lol...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amethyst_heels @justinbrummer @StoneBrewing Stone cheers!!!  Cannot go wrong!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Central Florida sunsets really are something! #Braves @680TheFan https://t.co/KGgn8Yg80g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nascar Live 2019 Chat with Hamm - Atlanta Race Recap https://t.co/Pp9Kmp7qKZ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillydog70 Tommy Lasorda: There are three types of baseball players: those who make it happen, those who watch it… https://t.co/a0i6W2Biov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly pretty selfish of my parents that they couldn’t make us taller than 5’8’’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte @steelers @Raiders https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 @937theFan https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/5HmAwxyIv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMalikaSiker @MarkKassMBJ @MKEBizJournal @PfisterHotel @SURGRestaurants @OmarMKE1 @CarnevorMKE @_kathyshouse… https://t.co/71u080kWFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @fbi How is this happening in the UNITED STATES of America? How long do we sit here and watch our… https://t.co/QZRIIGjiTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBoog68272815 @Griff3945 @Davis68Mo We were told 15 years ago while in the academy, "don't believe it till it show… https://t.co/9WCqBdwNjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thatsright6581 @CBPSanDiego @WhiteHouse It is a complex issue but discussing the ideas is far more productive than… https://t.co/DHN1ZeNXl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a look at attorney JARED RICH, candidate for Tues Feb 26th @NYCSpecial2019 NYC Public Advocate, who will hire… https://t.co/5FfZqZLpiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kap wanted 20 mil to play in the AAFL? 😂 dude go play let’s see what you got... 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[TV commercials give Documentary type titles to people being interviewed. My two favorites are ‘Retired Cereal Worke… https://t.co/JRrsHpXa5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[31 in the box. A prime number. How am I supposed to share these evenly amongst the four of us? https://t.co/YAZehyXcRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PubliusPost64 @michellemalkin Apparently it does, conservatives are all about patriotism, the rule of law, and def… https://t.co/wQU6qyKvQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym you are a loser and a liar ! Time for you to be removed and indicted for allowing children to be mo… https://t.co/TCgb5df8dP]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QXdsm2zJ88 Facebook Marketplace toll-free number is 1-855-479-3999 #facebookmarketplace… https://t.co/iK7ajETTJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @McMasterU study shows that #outcomes #measurement is seen by #nonprofit #workers as detracting from the quality… https://t.co/pelrN37LAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsmeraldaIP If they don’t have bee’s knees, then how great could their knees really be??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Oh Happy Day by Twin Leaf Brewery @ Twin Leaf Brewery — https://t.co/OwstplQoR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why people just don't can't respect each other really it makes 0 sense to me. we may not agree but I sure respect p… https://t.co/pgsMcT27GC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Robert Kraft was grabbing prostitutes, you know @stoolpresidente is as well. One prostitute, everyone knows the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Exception6666 @Uvargpa You have seen San Francisco and its daily shit and piss cleaning patrols?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Eastern Connecticut patrol officers had to fight for their lives in a gun battle with a suspect. Those off… https://t.co/Ese0Yzpm3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Let's be sure we understand this. Two #Muslim #Democrats somehow were allowed in the #Congress of… https://t.co/h91bZnAoQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertkraft0 F.Y.I " NEVADA " seems like the land of adults ! I mean they have a lot to offer ; like brothels and… https://t.co/OVAZuGQFq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanDennison1 @camsnapp30 I just looked on the KHSAA site...it says 6’0.  She’s gotta be taller than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday night podcast catchup, in bed post pneumonia recovery. (Dr ordered early bedtime).   Next @Adam_Stirling int… https://t.co/GdEbCdBacS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFrankShirley @phicago @MEM_IMAGES_LA @McCulloughTimes And even in that embarrassing nadir, the Dodgers were like… https://t.co/uhHyInfFgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in Manhattan has a Canada Goose jacket. Feels like they’re wearing uniforms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RolfSolber45 @DonaldJTrumpJr ?  Stats are ... Lies?  No wonder you support this administration, you like being lied to...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at American Airlines? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and… https://t.co/fMHpSKVE3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadians in Syria, mostly women who deserted their Canadian families, of questionable morals, with one or more chi… https://t.co/ZQzmoe75eD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jggg Soooooo true! He’s a monster and deserves to be treated like one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Da mucha pena lo de hoy mas que todo por la afición que va al estadio, los guatemaltecos que con mucho esfuerzo van… https://t.co/yPMqkSWo5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[A month before her historic women's title match Our queen faces @MariaLKanellis https://t.co/edhmmYVSQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I pee while looking over my shoulder through the crack of the door to make sure he wasn’t gonna attack me. I wal… https://t.co/kRE07ZmYAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerseyGirl2inPA @wxpnfm Have you heard the band Piper? Billy was a member.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flipgrid I am helping organize a teacher conference for over 200 and I am looking for some fun give aways. Would y… https://t.co/UsiD26D37u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Instacart shoppers denying insulting batches like:  #PayUp @apoorva_mehta https://t.co/03lmUICYta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taughteeona Blows my mind people are that addicted to a game they bring it on vacation with them 😂 wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nfrank326 @DamoneHardy @JeffRisdon @erikschlitt Could be.  Just didn't make sense to me.  He's literally never pla… https://t.co/eniOXqMpDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to say it... Bohemian Rhapsody wasn’t a good movie. Tell me I’m wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CEThomson Yea this is just incredible, I mean the media is all over this crap,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero se enredaron en los conflictos de interés... Terna para Corte: conflicto de interés https://t.co/StmtrZOC3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A relationship is just accepting the ugly morning part of a person I can’t do that. Like no. Ew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpompei @JayHilgenberg Jay and @olin_kreutz are both on my HOF list. #DaBears  https://t.co/kKZOl1krq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco Bay to New Orleans in 77 hrs 🚂 #californiazephyr #cityofneworleans @ Glenwood Springs, Colorado https://t.co/PgsEW1rOMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this homeless guy’s art in San Diego area. Really impressive! https://t.co/cVJjJoE3Uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myliemoore Hey @JaxSlayher gurl got skillz...oh and PHAT AZZ to die for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more and more you show me your colors, the more I’m getting used to the thought that you are just a statistic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[its sad how well my dogs know me. one follows when i get up from bed bc im usually going for food. the other gets i… https://t.co/XXyc4nhyiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricChumbler So McCracken has them doubled up in points and they’re pressing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstephens99 @churchplanting Thanks for your prayers. You will be missed @samstephens99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhiRatio1618 @drew12289 Manafort's lawyers own court documents cite that he gave 75 pages of campaign data to a Ru… https://t.co/Fh3pXUWfU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit some awesome milestones today. 200 followers on Twitch. Almost 2400 followers on Twitter. Setup the doggo cam,… https://t.co/iRnh2jttDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dieharddawg8 @karenehowell @DearOldState He’s just not a salt of the earth wholesome State guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog Ash got out just before I got off work.  By the time I got home from work, it took me 2 hours to find him dr… https://t.co/Lgl6La02hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend @SHalbhuber might make fun of me when I pack more than I need for a trip but it was nice having clean clo… https://t.co/xdFE8KHDGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dilenser @moscow_sity @KIRILL_aka_KID @motiv_14 @Deadinternet @GrJulianna @LenaWatermello @Satisfacti_ON @Kay_Nj2… https://t.co/jSJxzsaZ8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've got to love when someone who's made his entire fortune putting style ahead of substance goes out of his way… https://t.co/cfsiegW4lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou @ModelCarolAlt for #CrushingIt with us on #RadioPiscopo this morning!  #AvengerRadio ! https://t.co/RxG1uC80s5]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a presidential historian, you ought to know who the current president is..  ( but I totally feel your pain)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sidewalklabs gives us a tour of their vision for the waterfront. A harsh lesson of life on the streets. Students s… https://t.co/HuFHeusaN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @mercyculture with get_repost ・・・ SPEAK LORD! At Team Night, April 7 we will be receiving our first Heart f… https://t.co/4PbDS0LeZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 years ago today, in #InternationalWomensDay my beautiful #mother took her last breath. I miss her like the first… https://t.co/HgGzJKBF12]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Saginaw #MidMichigan #WestMichigan #SouthMichigan #CentralMichigan #ListenTo OFF THE LEDGE #Band #Youtube @… https://t.co/g5N4xmPYIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al lado de esto, la foto del #puma  arriba de un arbol en Lo Barnechea se queda chica ... Que le estamos haciendo a… https://t.co/XC68bIcFvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisJPeterson Bad things happen when you come down the middle with your head down...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone who lives near me to be my friend and get vegan food with me all the time cause whenever I ask my me… https://t.co/hY33w9C3C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from dlondon_fun_and_fitness  -  So true......ten years after you said that to me..... @ronniekinggroup _m… https://t.co/BDdPzN4NuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nprpolitics We have another #emergency in our country #VoterFraud!Please read my #nonfiction #book HUMAN ERROR… https://t.co/gLQsFMnxdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Saturday at TOM House #LeatherCocktails https://t.co/yHfesjpy7X #RegimentBlackandTans #BBcorpsla… https://t.co/LMowT6yhdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomHousenick @NazWrestling @KKidWrestling @becawrestling What about the Lions Classic?! Are you covering that event?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senior Jimmy Mulvaney added 13 points including MAJOR free throws in the fourth quarter. 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new @SailPoint office is, uhm, kind of neat. Innovation and cold-brew coffee...the intersection of next-gen IGA! https://t.co/lW7IObXqu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthleticsFan01 I’d still prefer rondo’s assists, even in a limited role, over zizic]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2XMvtktK0n .  Visit the website for rates, schedules and other info  https://t.co/r5NLCcyX4h (link in… https://t.co/t6EOsoJL8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/HRSo0FZ2UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que brujería es esta : No me escribe, me pongo down y digo cuando me vuelva a escribir , ignoro el mensaje 🙄 . Dent… https://t.co/9fd6RnARxX]]></document></documents></author>