<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When you’ve been gone from school for 2 days &amp; your team has held down the fort you take back blizzards!… https://t.co/PyA0zKqC2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[#melaninswagg #melaninmagic  #picoftheday #blackstyle #blackmodel #blackqueens #melaninbeauty #melaninqueen… https://t.co/Oozk0LyG48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders is doing as much to destroy American politics as tRump! Anarchy is not the answer, nor is the cult of perso… https://t.co/BlBbesdqD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s pay the federal contractors now. They should be made whole as well. Thank you for restoring our workers pay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs roses 🌹when you can get a #goldenglowfacial for #valentinesday with a blend of #wrinklerelaxers, #PRP, an… https://t.co/3Zz69vkK5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with Dad!  #dadisarockstar #weloveteachers🍎 @ Northwood Elementary School https://t.co/WbFrXqdK15]]></document><document><![CDATA[#crescentmoon#night#sky#photography#nature#lunar @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/Bj0WJSn3EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how many tries it takes you, sometimes you just have to smile, move on and try again! 🎬🎭#Orlandoheadshots… https://t.co/I7s4XtCRS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to get my grabbas back 😢 I’m getting them long long this time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sobegirl Thank you. Words matter. I'd also be more comfortable with "disclosure" in this context.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA It’s way past time that the liberal nut cases assaulting conservatives, who are just going about the… https://t.co/FQ0Fdc3547]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson I'm having issues with my pre show party ticket. I have emailed the address given several times with… https://t.co/1CmyZki009]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliceLfc4 And let’s not forget the whole “are the buttons pulling because of the buttons” that the more “well-endo… https://t.co/ovjx34QueH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMitchellMD @PinoyDances @joeferguson @Ann_Kirkpatrick @realDonaldTrump She’s dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMFanSupport when are BTS verified resale tickets going to be made available? We already know non legit fans got a… https://t.co/OSFEu3uZkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @Maggieb1B @TWITMO_INMATE @BRella315 @RealTT2020 @Rbigzs @karli_bonne @JETH0MASCUOUS @ZyroFoxtrot… https://t.co/g56EpQlgYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWA_Awareness @DigitalSages Why do people do such horrible stuff? I just don’t understand. :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you love yourself and have respect for others, people feel this energy and try to plug into it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never stop being amazed by @Mr_Max_Adler and his performance in #Glee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you please say a prayer our FOX10 coworker Will Curran who was killed in a motorcycle crash last night and hi… https://t.co/DUxH7CkkEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4uConservatives @missymoss4 Have you seen the bogus charges?  He čonspired to commit a hate crime to incite politi… https://t.co/nascOUNPEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_erica_nicole Now you know the bounce back isn't the same as it was years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most frustrating things in college is when you have a group assignment and no one shows up but you ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stone has filed a formal apology to the court:   “Undersigned counsel, with the attached authority of Roger J. Ston… https://t.co/GkXBc7STtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY #ValentinesDay I LOVE MYSELF I GUESS, since I just took me on a pretty good date yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Fells Point Historic District https://t.co/2B3uwDrXoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night learning on Enriching my 5th graders in coding by approaching it with wonder and discovery. We are alway… https://t.co/iONq6qNMVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother probably hates me bc I keep changing his Netflix profile on my acct lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbrownehr The movie and the song are amazing. I can’t get enough of those two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSiefken @pbwarrick @SolutionTree This is so exciting!!!! We have all worked so hard and the recognition is a bonus! #vcelem]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you believe that today i rewrote all my notes for a class into a new spiral and called it organization]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes me sad that the boys I want to text me back don’t fucking text me back! But then I’m like thank you, next! 😂☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Jonas brothers go on tour, you BETTER BELIEVE MY ASS IS GONNA BE THERE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @Michell44342742 I believe you as much as I believe your boss. NEVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @NASAHubble The Bible says that the stars sing to God! #biblicaltruth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanSekulow  Find someone that do something about this illegal activity---Talk about saving America these muslim… https://t.co/OZF9hRwsbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation gee gas prices going up 7 cents for the holiday. #ONpoli crooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cselley .she writes while dreamily staring at a photo of her darling Justin #heathermalice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Point Of No Return by Expose on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/NgBcurQmnM https://t.co/0PcaDGXoTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose your closest circles wisely. Make sure everyone in your boat is rowing in the same direction. Guard your hea… https://t.co/8K1VtrJc33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniekarni @maggieNYT Geez, you sound like you’d do anything to be one of the really popular kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Trip to Sandals Ochi Beach Resort in Jamaica! via @poweratl https://t.co/omxw8MiklI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talmadge18 @Ernieclem Lookin’ pretty legit in the uniform!  So proud of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachmadkins Happy Valentine’s Day to only as well @zachmadkins (and moose obvi) https://t.co/eeXDwci9ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Based_Jedi @archpng I'm thinking about a struggling mediocre opera singer who thinks s/he witnesses a murder but t… https://t.co/OOLiNVPdVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Tito pulling up with our black and white Rubik’s cubes tmmrw ✅✅✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banning2021 has now begun calling my cat, who hates literally everyone but me, Darth Floof. https://t.co/DCJiMGE3zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenbourgoyne @ladyotl And why does Beth have to put her life on hold??? #ThisIsUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotivationalMonday: It’s time to take the 🌡️temperature in your workplace. #PressPlay 📹to see why checking in with… https://t.co/C4C3G4Pym9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought the purpose of getting money was to be free ....  Steve Harvey is a multimillionaire... and still a Slave,]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted #bangs but didn’t know if they would work for me. Researched how do cut them on #YouTube but went to… https://t.co/IhkSC0kbWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly so glad to see that players are taking a stand against slow play.   It is getting out of hand, and had… https://t.co/LLLKfVJ1l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[just told @beeboobopbip he needs to shower me with even more love &amp; affection or else he'll be cancelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[An undocumented college student and her mother struggling for the American dream. Read the heartfelt tale of a Drea… https://t.co/Gdlwwi5NOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian_abettera Good morning Brian!!! Interesting stuff happening in Chicago I see.   What’s your thoughts on that.… https://t.co/g7Tc0BgQBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[s p l a s h  o n 🌊 Here's a throwback to last summer!  #summer #beachlife #BeachDay #ocean https://t.co/DoUJTKCULb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although I don’t really talk to my aunt anymore, her and my uncle are so strong for everything they have went through]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryfromFAMM I’m hoping that this example of a judge departure from guidelines is an example other Judges will follow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Station vibes ✌🏻😜 @Brittchedeville @ Tease Salon https://t.co/LMbcnS4BLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said••Just diagnosed with psoriasis on my face (well whole body 80% covered in a month!) ... you can still see… https://t.co/az2s1a22v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so the path to my Masters in Educational Leadership begins...  I’m in need of much luck and many prayers! https://t.co/nPdMHpAh8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th grade teacher asked me to pay for nine and I did it, then I talked to about five others. I'm bad at staying in… https://t.co/XVtEtTSWTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck this bitch and that ugly ass suit. how r u a century old and this smug to children]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who is super excited to emcee the Wed June 5th Graduation event!? @WMHTPubMedia @discoveralbany @HoxsieAlbany… https://t.co/pCO6C8VSd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh crap, that's the hardest one?   I'm only 34 mins into the show and I've already taken too many pills.… https://t.co/IIw9ZNoTlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@step4battle What are you talking about? This isn't about the police. The policemen I know here in Texas are very p… https://t.co/L1fXuqqbNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[When change happens, you have a choice for how you are going to respond. You can either lose your composure and rea… https://t.co/xTe7krg2E6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day Idjits #SPNFamiIy #akf @Mark_Sheppard @JensenAckles @jarpad @HiUncleJensen @realGpad… https://t.co/Ww165UThVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Amici’s In North Haven in North Haven, CT https://t.co/vneK3bMESV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We believe [Exxon etc] were lulled into complacency by a series of lucky near-misses.  Chilling story.  Read it n… https://t.co/LuLpvOaV47]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure I know three Aretha songs but I probably wouldn’t know she sang them bc I don’t listen to her independentl… https://t.co/Uu10vB047b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just handed sis at the drive thru window my ID instead of my credit card...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catheri17984166 @cathmckenna You are sad, pathetic, dumb ass  Say it with me one time?!  #BuhByeTroll]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the guy buying beef this afternoon- asking you if you prefer the flat or the deckle end of the brisket was not a… https://t.co/CbeNEw4no3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanChariton @BernieSanders Remember what kind of person employed her.  That. Says. EVERYTHING.  Protect your en… https://t.co/avT9JnljDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tallared @remko1 @jolteon @MMattKahn Can’t appropriate culture that has been historically forced onto you 🤷🏻‍♀️ ma… https://t.co/a4Q3nWilVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Missguided @sugarberrry Because I’m currently in NYC celebrating my 21st bday and will be sad to come home so a mi… https://t.co/j7RZlOyxvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police are still looking for the suspect in the carjacking at Schnucks in South County.   But I’ve already gotten s… https://t.co/R0CBj2kGki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff I don’t want you guys to leave for good! I will miss #ShepHappens action every weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @Julianna_glass @thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @cowineco @CaththeWineLady @Cbp8Cindy… https://t.co/O4Xn80bYHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday #snapchatfun #snapchatfilters @ Greene County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/jvRy3ck05Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Truthtease @J_Allen_CA @DrummondJeff @Aaronam69 @Larryputt @z_chrissie @RandallKraft @OutOfTheBlue201 @t2gunner… https://t.co/mggMl4EggI]]></document><document><![CDATA[what if I mess around over spring break and come back to Austin with a puppy named Boone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chic Leggings Style For Every Week of The Day https://t.co/RTycHKfrmE #Wholesale #Leggings #Manufacturers… https://t.co/WShAQ23XOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night activites included a Bolts win, one last pirate invasion, and good times ⚡⛵🍻  #saturdaynight… https://t.co/1x0uXs3i1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanWantsFreedom @RedBroward @DWStweets Oh okay. Thanks for clearing that up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ How much more crap/lies 🤥is the @GOP willing to ignore?😠😠☹️☹️😡😡 @POTUS’ has NO humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ion need no love I just want money and some drugs (and a real ass mf) 🤞🏼🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValentinoAndy77 @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @Southappie… https://t.co/doYYcJKvIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DoorsHiding  #ShotOniPhone8Plus @ Golden Gate Heights, San Francisco https://t.co/56DjuZ1eVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IreneOnorato I followed you as well.  I look forward to seeing what the Lord does through your writing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[are vital organs really are working nonstop, I respect that type of grind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss @tazarae20 If he survives to run again in 2020, we will also have to assume that the GOP is a majo… https://t.co/FUYiY5NjzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great teachers never stop learning! #ECET2Lou #WeAreJCPS #Zone1derful #WeAreJFK #BlastOffRandolph #SavageScholar @… https://t.co/GPQsI2pLMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Su mamá también critica a la gente que maneja rápido/feo y no sabe qué ustedes manejan peor? 🙊]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you run then your knees are already runner’s knees, why do they have to call it a syndrome. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @realJeffreyLord @KurtSchlichter              What a joke!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Been a long week so far, learning to breathe it all out at the end of the day. @ Scripps Ranch, San Diego https://t.co/HLN9orHaQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my new commute home I have to pass a pizza place, Thai, and 2 bars... torture daily]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd have NYE 🎆on this private rooftop terrace. I mean, it even has a full wet bar and a perfect view of the… https://t.co/CIHd0dN0Ku]]></document></documents></author>