<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Scary True Stories Told In The Rain | Thunderstorm Video | (Scary Stories) https://t.co/E2v4v33Sid via @YouTubel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terfle Right?! The ending is different but unique. The camera scene got to me tho 🙀 https://t.co/mhga08xoTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve spent the last 2 days with my mom before work and it’s been the best 2 days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinbarnes Oh geez! I wonder what they think after something like that happens. Are they like, “oh my bad, human, I… https://t.co/C3khxwWEuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[fellow Witches of Vin Scully Ave- 👑 @suejo825 sends her regards (thanks again for the 📸!)  @nerdyDodger @seawitched… https://t.co/i1nhHJge7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacyBenge @grandprairieisd @KEstesJones @CinLeeECE @aharveymitchell @steph_frosch Would love to see you! https://t.co/wVibcDUeHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BojorquezCBS @Enrique_Acevedo @jorgeramosnews The plight of the Venezuelan people is so sad.  The US needs to lead… https://t.co/FkR1JGa2ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momstrosityy I’ve never been a fan of roses 🤷🏻‍♀️ I like Lillie’s and sunflowers. And my moms obsessed with tulips]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah Brady crossed 3.1. Time 00:30:00, pace 09:40 min/mile, est. finish 11:16 am https://t.co/tHsx1Ud2Pi #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the worst thing Donald Trump said to Andrew McCabe - CNNPolitics https://t.co/eevifgutPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation I’m all for guns! But this trophy hunting I can’t get behind of. I respect the sanctity of life. Why kill the animals ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julianna_glass @AlanSemsar @BCLONA @Vegas2LAMag @CaththeWineLady @DemiCassiani @LoriMoreno @_drazzari @JMiquelWine… https://t.co/spK66gn9TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brentwood staff learning and growing together at the staff PD. https://t.co/fVzeKuyr89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madameaiello @sgojsic @FIEdConsulting Often times it’s families who feel they should be supporting their child’s n… https://t.co/lTJTBqp8SW]]></document><document><![CDATA[dinner time! grand canyon roll (mushrooms,  onions, and cheese), banana roll, hot cheeto roll, and chicken katsu ro… https://t.co/Fmq3TGp7lG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two selfies in one day. Unheard of 😂 . . . . . . #selfie #fitstagram #instafit #fitness #fitpro #fitmom #fitspo… https://t.co/N7JI4e38lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost time to go!! NYC!! #travel #vacation #newyorkcity @ Kansas City International Airport https://t.co/tVrdJxGJ8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly I’ve simply become ANOTHER Woman sexual harassed and put into my place of Unjust/swept Under the Rug sexual a… https://t.co/vdLguAY9G3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy pelosia just stood on National Tv and lied and said their not a National Emergency at our Border that tell yo… https://t.co/Sjz5ZmHAjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @DavidYankovich Now do you see where the problem lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Fitness Night with ACS School Nurses @ACSPHYSED https://t.co/CMhTfkkO3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnphilippines For your market, please read this is now confirmed, hand stamping will no longer happen with the NS… https://t.co/pgZEG4b32E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screen your Dreams Trinity International Film Festival proudly accepts entries via FilmFreeway, the world's #1 subm… https://t.co/jPRSZw98Ye]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could say we spent our Sunday here but we spent about 5 minutes after waking up before going our separate… https://t.co/DjzBsPeJXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never had so much on my plate &amp; think I’m actually loosing my mind 🆘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing (and tweeting) in solidarity with my sisters and brothers working at @CAMBAInc.  They deserve better, thei… https://t.co/5OZHJ2uLAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio Who Do You Love by @5SOS and @TheChainsmokers  #iHeartAwards #BestFanArmy #5SOSFam]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OliviaColman is just the greatest thing i’ve discovered in the last six months. (i know you brits have known for y… https://t.co/AaP2rVj66F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Here you go...because deleted tweets are never really gone... https://t.co/ya1mDQShat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current #MoodOfTheDay: No Students today? No Staff today? We will miss you ALL⭐️’s. Enjoy the long weekend. See you… https://t.co/J4j70k8LbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add to your TBR today: https://t.co/ZSl59YqxMe  #troubleatbrayshaw #comingspring2019 Edit courtesy of @MusingsoftheMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the final countdown! 13-story treehouse project reveal coming soon! @jswatersschool @chrisbowling01… https://t.co/e54Q1L8l6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOMEONE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE COME WITH ME TO SEE BETTY WHO IN JUNE!!! 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasmStardust 🌸🌸🌸 I’m the eldest of three. There’s me, my sister, then my brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunniHopper1 Always. I have always much preferred moonlight over sunlight. I literally do not like the sun, too much of it depresses me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandadeibert My sister...she's successfully worked on several FDA submissions for lifesaving drugs, while being a… https://t.co/RFfhkQCzcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[netflix needs to drop a new show. I want to be excited to watch something again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially been with Duncan for 5 years. He’s made me cry so many happy tears this weekend while talking about… https://t.co/VEPDis8hvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW two losses in a row for Oregon. @CharlieCreme now has them as the #2 seed in Portland]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtfffff I just put it together that X100PRE means Por siempre.. que pendejaaaa! 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress Trump put them in our WH SOLD THEM CONDOS IN TRUMP TOWER MADE $MILLIONS! Trump said so himself🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicaelaMia_ @RUWrestling Great pictures.. such a role model for Rob.. I hope Rob is as successful as Willie in college..]]></document><document><![CDATA[self-care books straight up act like we dont live in an extremely corrupt capitalist ass society in which many can… https://t.co/fTDdBIV1i5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing #AlitaBattleAngel. I’ve seen a lot of Twitter posts about this movie so let’s see if I join the party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever gone on or want to take a @DisneyCruise?  Here Are The Top 4 Things To Do While On A #DisneyCruise 👉🏼… https://t.co/9AtYRz4195]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisJackson No but my daughter tagged me in this.. 😂😂 https://t.co/1meSGiq6tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shemaiahng Happy to supply you with any liturgical photos you might need!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long Distance may get the best of us sometimes, but nothing is ever better when we’re together 🥰 @ Dixon, California https://t.co/uRGwn9i0ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came back to Japan🗻🇯🇵  I will do my best by switching٩(ˊᗜˋ*)و https://t.co/smMEj4yt6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psabrito 86 deve ser na linha de montagem!! Aquilo é um mundooooooo!! Uma coisa linda de se ver a linha de montage… https://t.co/ZepCEDYVUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigeria's Yoruba language is second most spoken foreign language in Baltimore schools - Face2Face Africa https://t.co/TbLnHADol8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems like @AmericanAir is boarding like 15 flights in this one area. #Charlotte How many lanes are there? https://t.co/Mm1dwDPEl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_almdztori If you ever need take home tests or hw done lmk $$ I do it for a decent price lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump loves children a hell of a lot more than @AOC, that’s for damn sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatherineDines @elle_dee_see Right?! That’s so amazing!!  @AlgonquinColleg really cranks them out💫 https://t.co/QtIHR0GcWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping @PLTWorg design their new national assessments today at the #PLTWSummit   It’s exciting that students will… https://t.co/urwRIfYgL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t read anything you just tv watch the news about yourself!  You’re just a  fake with a big mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mama_Liberal @IndivisibleNet It is better.  We voted for this too, it passed, but it's not law yet.  Every time th… https://t.co/Ylo9vDN3Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smileyxhunter @SeaveyDaniel @ImZachHerron @JonahMarais @jackaverymusic @corbynbesson @whydontwemusic I love all of… https://t.co/cbqOCkX2ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump You know you are lying yet you keep doing it. What has Trump got on you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seremos felizes pra sempre? Trabalharemos pra isso! Mas que sempre fomos felizes, ah, isso sim!… https://t.co/yH4kbXhFE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life will be complete if I could ever afford these merch from @HayleyKiyoko @LaurenJauregui and @AllyBrooke (jus… https://t.co/c64WoTzg6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zumba after bible study.  Church girls want Summertime Fine too.  3x a week for free 🙂.  Hit me. @ Mount Zion AME o… https://t.co/QNfFHPfJkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What on God’s green earth is this cursed artifact?  With that said @RainForest_Cafe how do I get one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSchulman What does she sell to Dems and Clinton’s? Trips to Epstein’s island? Kids under 13? That is THEIR V… https://t.co/09vHqIFT7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[down at the bottom is jeffrey and he is P I S S E D https://t.co/tjmYycF5Lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donwinslow Lil Donny is not a Deal Maker nor a Debater. He doesn’t know the Best People or Words. He’s a Failed Re… https://t.co/2Qh24rArmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier That's right. The only reason she wants to come back is that we're kicking Isis as**. She's bad news… https://t.co/BIcLmekPqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Diversifying the curriculum does not mean lessening the rigor of that curriculum; rather, it potentially enables m… https://t.co/andTm4nrdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa where is the money?  Start answering or go away. #ResignLisaMacLeod #ResignDougFord… https://t.co/Q3vuD3X3df]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway Bless you. You have the platform. Please keep your voice out there. Tired &amp; Angry at all these attacks against @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn. bella really said screw it and laid down in the middle of the forest when her bf broke up with her to just die lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[That?s some humor right there. if brains were gasoline, you wouldn't run a piss-ants go-cart 2 laps around cheerio https://t.co/NxXryNfadv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people I haven’t spoken to in years decide that they want to involve me in their pyramid scheme. 🙃🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we go back to Andy and his adorable baby and leave this Jussie bs to the police]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost @luzdehoponopono ・・・ Divino creador Padre , Madre , Hijo todos unidos como solo uno . Te entrego mis memori… https://t.co/K8drs9lwvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really hard for me to decide that I should stop listening to the #coldpodcast because it's on @WonderyMedia. T… https://t.co/VZJ6ske9ra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump There is a crisis. A BIG one in the Democrat House of Representatives. Running away… https://t.co/KTTIPJCokw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinkGinandCake Morning, Jo! How's the gusto going? I might take a shower 🚿and wash my hair 💁 today, making sure no… https://t.co/RpTOHsC2F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[swear 2 god I need to move somewhere w good public transportation bc I’m the WORSt car owner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonWalker_ @shaygrudolph @ChandlerLKinney @LethalWeaponFOX @KevinRahm @MMitchenor @maggielawson @keeshasharp… https://t.co/2Qwazw7whj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcAspinall For sure. He knew his stuff. Now I have a craving to watch some classic horror. Hmmmmm....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My valentine gave me the most wonderful gift - a trip to Atlanta to visit my most wonderful daughter!!  See you all… https://t.co/a84TsxOfO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrut40882043 @975Middays He is a dodger @Dodgers @Bharper3407 we want Harper we want Harper HarperWood https://t.co/6itzXfru1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching my 600 lb life and the guy died in the middle of the episode and Ive never cried so hard watching a tv show in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSimoneNY who the hell voted her into the government? I hold those freaktoids just as responsible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alayneswinter Great! Yeah, I don’t know anyone irl who likes asoiaf which is super sad and the only time I get to… https://t.co/6OA3MGiwcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Anti-Muslim Poster Of Ilhan Omar Led To Chaos In The West Virginia Capitol https://t.co/2LrrCOcU8e #GOPRacism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherry50waldie @CplUSMCRetired @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi So, you are trying to say who shoul… https://t.co/QLODz9xvvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we’re just gonna pretend cam reddish and RJ Barrett weren’t 2 of the top 5 recruits? AND Duke didn’t have the #1… https://t.co/aO51vCYWs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leslie just requested “where the bag at” at the bar...I like her mindset]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dallying  "Faith is an attitude of trust in an object that allows the object to work on your belief.  The more you… https://t.co/iLrgD8AwlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation @OfcAZendejas Happy Birthday OfcAZendejas!! Miss you on #LivePD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Some of us are not that crazy. We are trying our best to stay away from the crazy people. I'm a native… https://t.co/SAljE9N5fT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuánto tiempo se están en sus viajes ficticios,pregunta seria es que quiero ir a China imaginariamente.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manicsocratic Tired of old white people opinions? Sorry. You’re in Arizona. It’s all we have. No one else exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW your innocent tweet causes a barrage of 30 back and forths.  Alts is inflation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tautandlogical @ClwtrBkAtty @jonrosenberg @MeghanMcCain This person blocked me. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmoaknBooks @goodreads @tjenkinsreid Can’t wait to read this. On the hold list for it at the library.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hunter Mountain Ski Resort - @huntermtn in Hunter, NY https://t.co/geYds8P4hC]]></document></documents></author>