<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Spark_to_Write My sister does this for me. She finally, after idk how many years, got me to watch The Office and a… https://t.co/kYrspHe4Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any really pretty graffiti in Granada?  I my town there’s the scribbles like on the sides of the bldgs th… https://t.co/EMCdUrMIN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi must get a handle on her anti Semitic girl she hugged on Rolling Stone. It’s not a rock and roll con… https://t.co/OiV023YNQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib Never been stimulated by a music video.... till now thanks babygirl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my favorite holiday besides Christmas. Happy National Drink Wine Day 😍🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, while all this is happening in New Orleans Jensen Ackles is literally gonna be turning 41 tomorrow and i… https://t.co/u8Exu5X4Ug]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a year @BoilerBall. No matter what else happens in March, this season has been a blast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a “celestial being” tearing up my mentions for the right to say HOTLANTA https://t.co/7NVQdXubv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @TomLlamasABC They are... Bolton is a hawk and so is pompeo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpraguePlague @1manwolfpck @Moriah1423 @JayFAnderson @fakeleny @smithsara79 Shift the money people are already pay… https://t.co/jdreLhNBKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok if you all continue to say “unpopular opinion: I love twilight” yo it’s really not an unpopular opinion like,, I… https://t.co/cctV0WwczO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama DOJ drops charges against alleged broker of Libyan weapons https://t.co/zr3IKu2itd via @politico]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MarkMeadows - you and your old- White- whiny, entitled, self-serving buddies are a despicable disgrace. All of yo… https://t.co/JRGFGMktMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSCampbell Even Ingraham thinks Donnie trump is dangerous!   Maybe there is hope for Fox News yet.  But,.... I doubt it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nafsnep I agree. Their season is over they are only playing for contracts now. Hopefully we have a team next seaso… https://t.co/krsB8QnzH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time flies when you’re in love! Happy 4 months to my best friend!🥰💗🔒 @ACoopshaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco How about other things that need funding the country needs.... Hmmm, how is it you say h… https://t.co/DEp7gKAbs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MidwestEvolve  Chevy Bolt &amp; Mitsubishi PhEV Outlander with #ZEFenergy DC Fast Chargers https://t.co/9ybIzuYu57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cynthia74015493 Not catholic, but my daughter is.  She may be oblivious as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CillizzaCNN Boy, am I in shock that CNN would post this! https://t.co/wmpOi6YDXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Wang chose the Prodigy Peel for her patients because of its holistic approach to minimize carcinogens. Visit… https://t.co/jddsH9C8qL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like they’re looking to question her boyfriend. Too much of this these days. 😢 https://t.co/c1zDib8Iek]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW just had an extremely emotional conversation with my younger brother. I almost cried. He really needed to hear… https://t.co/UsV0nM47XS]]></document><document><![CDATA[How @mahnoorie and I felt after speaking to j-school students on diasporic media, ethnic news and why local news ma… https://t.co/87GbJIafhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy You can kick it. Change you body to Alkaline eat Organic and Clean. Cancer cannot survive in an Alkaline… https://t.co/OHSmeJqzCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#magic or something else. Thanks to @cazalis for pix thanks dharmayoganyc for 🙏🏼🙏🏼 @ Dharma Yoga https://t.co/W1kagpk3La]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a broken wing she carries her dreams. Man you ought to see her fly 🎶🎶 https://t.co/EMhEKTlycu]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @ReggieBannister and #GigiBannister booth for #Productionmagicinc the IS NO ALLOTTMENT for autographs!!! You can… https://t.co/hxcYGak1H1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest gift we can give to any American. Is a president that’s actually working for them also a Congress. Tha… https://t.co/n7zBnT8Eis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USPS this. ASAP - your facility doesn’t clarify service animals can’t enter your place if you. I was respectful to… https://t.co/oRgJISxRKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamavista You must be so proud of your son.  I love baseball.  The weather is so crazy all over this country.  I’v… https://t.co/knzwHymgox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @EmanuelMacaron We aren’t so powerful anymore. Or so respected. Let’s thank Trump and Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newphantasy Is it?! I’ve been wanting to watch it! The commercials look hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 25th Birthday to my wonderful nephew! I love you and I'm so proud of you. cmore_0305  #nephew #proudaunt @ Ri… https://t.co/dFP8fPychp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solangeknowles is to powerful thank you for delivering a masterpiece, QUEEN 🙏🏻😭💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judellenf @bigredwavenow Oh now that Tune Stuck in my head reminding  me how Old I am LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think by the end of this year I’ll have my actor’s mission statement together😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a gym partner! Who is willing to go to the gym at least 3 times a week 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1SteveBurton @BfordAnderson We were in the newspaper! https://t.co/6nIpaj9fo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet I won't be listening to the #KC @Royals radio game coverage this year because I can't stand or approve the "my pillow" ads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get more smiles per gallon. • • • • • #accioadventure #optoutside #foreverexploring #mountainlove #whyihike… https://t.co/s4i2159piM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 228 Tripel by @StormcloudBrew @ Horrocks Tavern — https://t.co/5Tz161aV9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @cocoaudie the world is watching the Trump Administration work for the American people and the best… https://t.co/QUuVUEySYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric is hands down the best part of #SexEducation don’t @ me @NcutiGatwa https://t.co/ukYIZqoD4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awh okay I’m only halfway through the episode but I really do hope Colton and Cassie are together today because they actually are quite cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PulpAndBear Mewtwo también me encantaaaaa :') jaja https://t.co/MgEb5sDxRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put a wall around Maralgo, in Florida. Keep the “illegals” from working for trump. If the wall keeps them out then… https://t.co/nTngfMoP3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need more #immigration judges, faster and more humane case management that doesn’t rely solely on #detention, an… https://t.co/rfHc8usuC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very cool story about our @HMSHawks @Firefly_Space this weekend! Thank you @Gloria4Lisd and @cedarparkmom  for fi… https://t.co/x5DUwWhpxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneBrazeau1 @Bowde94 @felixtennis L’avenir du tennis Canadien est prometteur ! La relève est solide !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Animals with Quotes - Gallery #funniness #chuckle #smile #comic https://t.co/H6u7Zn6qqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vinchenzzz @WillieAtFLO Agreed there but that’s the easy choice. Unc he’d have Ramos and Coleman for senior level stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vous souvenez-vous quand vous avez rejoint Twitter ? Moi, oui ! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/awRfCECdnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people copy me, idk how many times i got to say it. BE YOURSELF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colors of love ❤️ 👁🔮👁❤️ . . . #funtimes  #music #color #currentmood  #onlyloveisreal  #loveunitesusall  #openheart… https://t.co/BcqKG802Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Well I figured out they are floating somewhere in the universe with all my Tupperware lids]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing my mom said when she got to the hospital yesterday was “damn your lips are tore up” 🙄🤣🤣🤣🤣 I was str… https://t.co/HPBMDqgg2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol i’m so over expressing something that bothers me but nobody caring to not do it anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec your boss will do anything to get notice good bad or indifferent.  @POTUS loves the attention and hearing… https://t.co/Q8N8gH1zXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can still taste the alcohol in my mouth from last night. RIP my shift at work today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the best cuddle time with my mom since I’ve been in college and I’m just in awh ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the coldest temps we’ve seen since the end of January, but for the first time in a while you’ll need your… https://t.co/sWSDB6d5Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[-the day isn’t bad, the events that occurred in your day were bad, tomorrow you start over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO Awwww ❤️❤️❤️❤️ she’s got a bad tummy. If she won’t drink water, spits up bile, take her in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ☀️ was hitting a lil bit different today..  #selfie #SanFrancisco https://t.co/aub8wynMCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breakfast #waffles #waffle #food #foodphotography @ Waffle House https://t.co/PBfAAPsrgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rally4publiceducation oakland_ea today @ Oakland, California https://t.co/mt7ZGsUgAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost 5 am and I’m up. Seriously considering staying up all night to reset my body clock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attorney suicide: What every lawyer needs to know https://t.co/XRvOjm9luK via @ABAJournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright peeps of Twitter, I was off so it’s been a chill day. Quick 30 minute poll, so please answer 😂 gas station… https://t.co/xlgOoCIweF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Pack of lies.  #ImpeachTrump #FakePresident #UnfitForOffice #TrumpForPrison #MuellerTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoHWFanClub I'm the most happiest when my son and his wife come home for a visit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@nancygilesnyc interviews playwright @jeremyoharris historian #dwestonhaywood and Writer #antwaunsargent new play… https://t.co/YtODVgOPuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to figure out why I captioned a photo last night with “Welcome to the Jungle.” Because that is a hysterically lame thing to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gildawabbit ask @SheekTrey how his butt is doing since buying my program]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hallelujah Anyway has snuck on to a @thefader playlist!  https://t.co/coDj6n2k2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JxhnBinder @AnnCoulter I think he deserves to be moved to the gallows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shrinkage is real... loving my clients hair growth &amp; healthiness of her hair. #teamwork #healthyhair… https://t.co/pIlnrOJ9yH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankiemuniz Did Malcom garduate from Harvard in Malcom in the Middle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on this made me want to change majors. https://t.co/upvQCeA5dG via @utashorthorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys to say I love @amyphxn  is a freaking understatement... That’s my freaking homie in a half right there. I’d ta… https://t.co/OuxC7QIox1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked down to get a girl scout cookie and looked up to see the @WashWizards have the lead. #lifeisgood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh-Oh! Tyga Reportedly Got Dragged Out Of Floyd Mayweather’s Birthday Party For Fighting [VIDEO] https://t.co/49Joi5DFSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to bring the beast out of you. In fitness it’s either you get stronger or fold 🤷🏾‍♂️  #legday… https://t.co/HBMj9CgjSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually tell my classes/children they are my “favorite”, but that it’s a secret they can’t tell the others. The… https://t.co/nP2a6PDQLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun night with these amazing people!!!!!!!! Machado!!!!! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻😉 to those I just met it was so nice to meet you all… https://t.co/QnYx5T8FId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pudelzrock @JoanBen46634671 @Serremmy @jonz970 @gbspurs @Rjdishon @JoeMil34 @fortressfin @jphack519 @stevenfbuss… https://t.co/r8j3Jy0hPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“O Lord, make me know my end and what is the measure of my days; let me know how fleeting I am! Behold, you have ma… https://t.co/j67SAVCt97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je vous annonce d’ores et déjà que ça va durer plus d’une dizaine de jours. Anniversaire de la sœur, 11 mars. Carna… https://t.co/jwPnyhtuvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanLoizeaux @Zaqueem interviews about our story.  It became a very odd combination of the two. But now since Fr… https://t.co/mddDwikcED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Senator Brown in OH is looking into running.  He would be a moderate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to have to keep a tally of the number of times Kevin makes "whale's vagina" references. 🙄Current count: 1 #Kurkas2SanDiego]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's "By".... NOT Bye"... And we're looking at your finances and tax returns to uncover the crimin… https://t.co/spVjoGcZ6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That’s hard right there mern”... no it ain’t.. we both know it ain’t 🥺😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamLehman @alliepal @TheWonderJam That sounds very similar to my first experience! I attended a yoga class and th… https://t.co/ZfELxEWASs]]></document><document><![CDATA[up against deadlines for my new packaging to be ready by spring and I haven’t slept in 2 days ........😩😑😷☠️☠️☠️☠️☠️… https://t.co/vwHdXTfcoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Awww poor little Paul. Breaking the law for years, gets caught, blames Mueller. What a baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadLindberg https://t.co/EAkprcPi2q Please consider helping me out by retweeting!!! ♡ :) #payitforward #anxiety… https://t.co/uxjwTTXfdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My love bug graduated Level 1 and we will soon to be onto level 2 🎓🐾 https://t.co/pW9N30v7YI]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment you realize you have a wedding the day avengers endgame comes out https://t.co/pR9OXN2mUy]]></document></documents></author>