<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Coaching day at @mtolivemiddle today #digilead #njed (@ Mount Olive Middle School in Budd Lake, NJ) https://t.co/PvPtfYThph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pledger's School for Hockey Referees  Lesson 1: Get of the way of the dang puck.  Lesson 2: Get out of the way of t… https://t.co/mCqytsPFFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KupoNews @UPS @UPSHelp I had an interesting experience today with packages too. @Amazon sent us a package with the… https://t.co/7wxu00hw1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got an 790 in sats on the dick math section  Which only existed in one test given to me by myself and graded by m… https://t.co/v9mNVy23KJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexKendig @NashvilleComedy Dude. Don’t toy with me. #FriendlyGhostApp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P_Funk36 I don’t see that at all. Goerge definitely has more moments then anyone if we being honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockydm92 @ByMHarrington Yes Eichel is why theyre still this bad. Not the fact they can’t build around him https://t.co/V2zi0YlJeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will set you back about $1,800, but you save money in dog food and poop cleanings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[how was the preaching?   "Bro he didn't even use the Bible." https://t.co/nynKqhc6ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ingrained in my brain that after people found out that CFA donated to anti-gay organizations in 2012, Republic… https://t.co/Wt71Fji7bN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelatedboat @NotPatReilly I was missing NYC last night. This was a helpful reminder of what I'm missing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMURPH88 @Swamp_Fever2020 She is a puppet for sorrels and other big money power mongers waiting in the closet to come out and rule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy valentines team! Enjoy your treats from your leaders @MoOniica_14  and myself! #teamloma @j1111c @pdelao255… https://t.co/9hI6wqrIug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@risa_cool46 僕もわけわからん状態です。  追加公演って事なんですかね？  それだったら規模が明らかに小さい大阪フェスティバルホールをあえて入れた理由がわからない。。。  最初から武道館でやればいいのにって。。。  ま… https://t.co/QidQPyVvLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OMW #Home (@ United Polaris Lounge in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/Pcc6OWsYVy https://t.co/7aKuWLEorC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scooter conditioning today at track practice!!! https://t.co/8v5Pcsy0nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachRHaywood @JacobCar3 This by far is tweet of the day!  Very happy for you and the Tigers...keep it rolling!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye tomorrow I need all the pretty ladies in #MiAmi to slide thru the shoot!! 🎥 @kardiakfilms all ladies welcome al… https://t.co/FfadkD7DLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how some people manage to look pretty much the same as they did in high school. How do they go to college, disc… https://t.co/9BkBM1X67g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finallynce company recieved payment now have to wait until it processes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalVegas That’s crazy. My wife just got hired with 9 others for same position and they plan to open more shifts… https://t.co/wS1G8LuKPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it wasn’t already apparent, Toronto vs. Montreal Round 1 would be intense]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Monroe, LA, check out this #Cosmetology job via the link in our bio: Beauty Advisor at Ulta Beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[DVI gala! #dtjax #havananightsneonlights #jacksonville #facepainter andressantandreu @hashchi thejimajamma @ Downto… https://t.co/y0nZXJsKY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAaryanKartik @kritisanon  bew best film is actually an fazul fazuk budget film . Film suppose to be on budget 1… https://t.co/hk8Ow509Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sotoleandro_ @alejandrovg32 Señores ayer @RicardoEMontes Llevo a su Sra a un Rest. Donde venden Preparan Comida Ve… https://t.co/5DasxgtE2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDazzMann @NICKMERCS @TheScaryNature It would be a crazy fight haha a gorilla usually is 500-600 pounds of solid muscle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/NtIympejyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[☝️👂💯 (live) Radiohead in Rainbows - From the Basement https://t.co/SHgwa7H1wy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prisonculture related, and as entertaining as it is interesting: 'The History of the Codpiece' (and a bit more, as… https://t.co/u74I86In2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very wet, very heavy snow - and it’s very slippery beneath the snow on the roads. -SK #WPRO https://t.co/dv4MJSrsHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Sales job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Contractor Sales Rep at… https://t.co/O3zTzkO1Db]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I wake up in the morning thinking about food.” #NBAAllStar   CC: @BigDaddyDemps]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never expected Him to arrive by @VW  And I never knew I could call on Him via @Uber https://t.co/C44nHOto9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis @WhitlockJason Agree there. I would say it’s a lock that the Dolphins don’t even consider him]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re Italian AF, you make your own beet gnocchi for valentines dinner 🖤🖤🖤 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/dgu0x8puFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starisbornmovie @ladygaga #SteelBookCase #AStarIsBorn https://t.co/B1B52EjdQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWiseguy @TalkNats2 @Bharper3407 Took you this long?  😉  Since he started with the Nats and all the Yankee loud… https://t.co/t8R5jsYBq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devrodriguez3 @Clemmens_PBR @ryozella @PBR_California The three NorCal Baseball 2022 from California high school d… https://t.co/bTYbrlAeT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out g eazys name is gerald earl and I don’t know what to do with that information but lmao what a name😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MostDopeMurphyy You’re just gonna steal my tweet on twitter on twitter day to my twitter in my twitter https://t.co/qM8RpTDp4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t win, but we also didn’t come in last! 2020 is the year, I feel it. @RedRaidersBHS https://t.co/DaQz9HTWat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eriel Santagado Orlando Metro Gymnastics Grad and Rutgers team member !! ORLANDOSTRONG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCALidahh Found this footage of you trying to park. https://t.co/eJRoSkqX10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClimateAdam @MaryHeglar You didn't grow up in the 60s listening to it being used by the worst sort of racists. Tha… https://t.co/vr1QwTUAr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Crew96 moving to Fox Sports Ohio?  Ugh.   That means conflicts with #Reds games here in CBus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaaada__ Dawg I’m just telling you the truth . Believe it or not it’s your choice whether or not you let that shit happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redskinstoday_ Except when he comes here and forgets how to play football like so many free agents before him. The… https://t.co/OnnD45QlTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding it difficult to put it into words how the last couple days have gone into such a short form...And there is… https://t.co/iBQRR3Hgjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ldogls @TaggartRehnn @kaysintBB @HondoResists @illegitamatepr1 @GonzoBaggins @ToBeSafeNSound @KITTYBAYOUTSFAN… https://t.co/Fj4dRjbHV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP on by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN TODAY for the HUGE BOGO 50% OFF SALE!!!! BUY 3 GET 1 FREE on GNC Ear… https://t.co/PVrii4ZOYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCF_Knightline We’ve got to get back to the same formula that dominated #USF in the first game. Active hands and g… https://t.co/wOqPnNu0nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claudiashein @lopezobrador_ @GobiernoMX Albado sea el pejeova!! https://t.co/XBRjkD4nMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaxReformExpert Yes one a “traditional” Dem, one  a socialist lefty and one a demagogue mandating and dictating ... Party is split.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren Caught Off Guard When Opponent Brings Up Ethics Complaint on Her ... https://t.co/Ler9JyqUcO via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come President Trump can’t get what all other presidents get ... just that simple]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't believe this is my first smoke of the year. Cheers to my first of many rotations on IR. #workhardplayharder… https://t.co/yoQgOg49r1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinLaBar @WWEBrayWyatt @MATTHARDYBRAND @DaveBautista @undertaker #5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Montel_Williams @dbongino @MollyJongFast @dbongino @Montel_Williams Guys, I love you both, but getting into a piss… https://t.co/sI0T1qcv8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TMobile for the $4 @AlitaMovie @atomtickets movie tickets. My battle angel @BeiMommy striking a pose lik… https://t.co/xx087QbM4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not far behind you bro... Been holding on for the last 25+ years but it might be time for me to let go as well.… https://t.co/mFcunsKZ1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly. Y'all act like she did nothing. If most of y'all were given the life she had then you would just be compla… https://t.co/U2HjxCIqfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Really Gone by CHVRCHES. https://t.co/nRscEINnxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The scores 32-10 but with the drama between the refs and SMU’s coach you’d think the game was more intense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End 1st: Bear Lake 18, Manistee CC 12 (Girls District 109 Semifinal) @HarrisonBeeby @MISportsNow @freeppreps… https://t.co/ArhJQo9PfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkohlrogge @TheRealSwanee @charliekirk11 @POTUS @FoxNews It’s not “my opinion.”  It’s objective fact.  Border cros… https://t.co/1FoRuc3PEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thuban_Isesi @Nebesu_ @JJPriegoTV @OverwatchES Hay una "La batalla por Sebastopol",la historia de Lyudmila Pavlich… https://t.co/IVAM2xwkht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OstranderM620 Sweet girl looks so big!  What happened to this little Pre-k girl?]]></document><document><![CDATA[ECC Results at NJCAA Nationals: Candy Wilson loses 2-0 to Kendal Biddle of Cowley at 149]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolsinelloV @ThomasPKennedy3 @FBI @TheJusticeDept Almost a Billion?? WTH. New Yorkers better wake up]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best little buddy watching his tv debut on klgandhoda -   cozying up with his favorite little Elly… https://t.co/ba2TcbniNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AOC if you were not such a raging Twit then possibly you would be treated differently. But you keep being you… https://t.co/YP3jeUSvn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to commend @SeanDCleary for his excellent taste in headwear, featuring the limited edition JB Snapback… https://t.co/uLoL8Qobhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Sales Specialist Flooring" at Lowe's? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. You m… https://t.co/kIOJOiNb4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK: Congrats to our Northeast Inland All-District AP selections @kelseyw212, @shadrahamsher and Nikki Weber #TDR https://t.co/OvbAp0VTmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also heard he's had problems with the law in the past, pretending to be his brother when pulled over several year… https://t.co/zQC2WmJgOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing the #WomensTagTitles the @WWE needs to most definitely change the #menstagtitles. They are absolutely hideous... 🤮🤢🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallieField @TMobile Congratulations @TMobile @TMobileHelp @TMobileBusiness Ranked one of the… https://t.co/AXRp7GLlya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early Mardis Gras jazz concert! @ Sherman Jazz Museum https://t.co/YQAOdyDvJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolannjaneee I also want to talk about disability and mental illnesses as someone disabled with aspergers syndro… https://t.co/o6sxo1gHr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to now have LinnDtum samples loaded onto my @Roland_US SPD-S.  Now I can play @prnlegacy covers prope… https://t.co/n9gR6ZIq33]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Muslim born in Kenya speaks!!  Why wasn't Michael Lavaugh Robinson with him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanFlanagan24 Hate to say it as a Yale guy but that finalizer that tangled Fake up was Mikey Powell-level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiscoveryID @TruReflections That's good to hear partner! Because it's going to take A LOT of hard work and patienc… https://t.co/QIOJt1sUfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the PPTC Cherry Tree 10 Mile Race in Prospect Park. @ Windsor Terrace, Brooklyn https://t.co/2QFP72vTOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wheezin' the Juice by @GrandArmoryBrew @ Tony Sacco's Coal Oven Pizza — https://t.co/mxiew32Gki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Daydream Layers (Galaxy, Idaho 7, Mosaic) by @OtherHalfNYC @ Pamkakes — https://t.co/XCdxuD8NZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBC10 Philadelphia is live on route 130 near Haakon rd for a water main break. Traffic is down to one lane as crews… https://t.co/EUjVoOjV0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedImmigrant @charliekirk11 The bill allows him to use the 1.37 billion to build while they sort out the rest.  We will see.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just getting started on this interactive doc, really love how this format allows inclusion of data points and info… https://t.co/NOli57IbKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnahealthnut @Helenhs @5M23129 @thomaskaine5 No, she’s not. You underestimate the absolute hatred people have for… https://t.co/NZCpfJzgeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Flyers win today and they pull to within 5pts of the #Habs (one gm in hand) - add another team to the group of tea… https://t.co/SMXt2oAyNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have NEVER had problems out of my car. And now it’s having a mind of its own]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emi_da_viNci @JackieHillPerry Yes, this verifiable just a little Church History and Tradition https://t.co/2QyMPghYkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t tell if I’ve been up for 30 hours and still feel fine or if I actually did get sleep last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s always good vibes coming from this guy @avancinimtb 🇧🇷🌈🥇.   #GlobalMountainBikeNetwork #GMBN… https://t.co/EO1P1hoSyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[SMH and that is one of the reasons why I don't fuck around @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/YslTGYB8fG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadian_cousin @EvilBobJ My wife and I were just discussing the lack KAC sightings and not missing them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long Beach CA Sun Feb 24th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Mostly Cloudy Lo 43 MONDAY Mostly Cloudy Hi 67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers @DellaMills17 Payed of by Trump and Russian republicans party.]]></document></documents></author>