<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Kamalah_Daniels @Bala8105 @ScottGerard1 @SWSx72 @mkraju @CNN What about when trump was hitting on Ivanka?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboveTheBurgh @PrimeCreator2 @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2 @glammalg11… https://t.co/uOL8IN41Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably freak out but then realize GOD knows the reason and even if I don’t that’s the path that man wants to take… https://t.co/IWpW153FI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcbball16 @Jeanna_33_Cunn Joanne look at your baby!! Congrats Jeanna 💪🏾💓😘 So proud of these girls!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind @Heather_LPUK This is a huge fucking lie. Trump is disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo why this nigga Drake looking cute? 🧐 I ain’t neva eva view him like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unit 5 &amp; 6 test tomorrow! Review went home today, study!! #hhheroes #RCISDJoy #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/z7vfEvgblC]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s it I’m going back to my old self. Cold hearted bitch here I come 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn reminds me of when uncle eustace threw me off the jetty at pigeon point. I almost drowned tlking bout learn to… https://t.co/LqJrrVrA5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO SO SO SOOOOO great seeing so many friends today!! So ready to do all the dancing tomorrow 💃🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real quick: why is it suddenly super cute to record yourself chomping the fuck away on some food? Lmk because I don’t understand 😳🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not drunk. You're drunk. 👑🐻😻👽💨🍩🍆🍗 #HeidiBanks #HeidiBear #beardedqueen #beardedlady #beardeddrag #beardeddragon… https://t.co/zjpwYBtqYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieJayde @Ohmwrecker Whoa. Sorry that happened dear. Did you even Gift Sub anyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@texaslawg The thing I most dislike about myself as a boss is that I put up with consistently poor performance by s… https://t.co/QqF4VAFm0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love candles just bought like 8 🙃 mind you my pony tail short cause of me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all know that. Why didn't Congress, FBI know that? Oh wait, protected by deep state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dzunner @bigsexy_tote Good grief..... Fine for you....I'm not that much into cruel and unusual punishment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump It's over a year and 13 convicted! Many more under indictment.  Did you really believe t… https://t.co/OpWQwt2lDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, one of my friends said “you can tell you’re a women in your 30s because every time I come over, you have… https://t.co/T6kt5j6XA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisakers It's called take out.  Makes you wonder why Bob Kraft went to her place of business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/riTmWEF1eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s up with your online gift card ordering @ChipotleTweets?? I have 100+ gift cards to buy (your bulk purchase p… https://t.co/7fRIdiiTjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenkelley85 No doubt!  Our gift to them is to be that example 👊💥 #WeTeachuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am officially putting my sister up for adoption. https://t.co/VewyxlkWiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teenage self is crushed. RIP Dylan.  Condolences to his family. Actor Luke Perry has died at age 52  https://t.co/oV4vB0w6wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Home Design your own dream house in My Home! https://t.co/qTxjMheRTq https://t.co/RhRri6OV5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The film MOON made by @ManMadeMoon yes I read the instructions to this game, Mikel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricSharp_Real @Gusbuckets I don’t think so, there were no cameras aloud during the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je suis très couleur neutre pour mes ongles ces temps-ci. J’ai donc arrêté mon choix sur cette parfaite nuance « Ri… https://t.co/GMThpQwPGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyimbee @bordie_ Hey bee what about a buzz craft reboot for two mil😂😂😂❤️❤️ congrats I’m so proud of you🐝🐝🍯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamMrGittner Parts Purposes Connections... interesting idea for math games you create in class]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JussieSmollett @EmpireWriters @EmpireFOX this needs to be fixed ASAP prayers prayers prayers praying 🙏🏻🙏🏻 facts b… https://t.co/rqlbPNFtJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure why people think 19 is boring, it’s pretty great, stayed up till 1 with friends playing many sports and ga… https://t.co/FOI1BTiaM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHESTER IS HERE. My cat son is home 🥰🥰🥰🥰. He’s such a good sport and sandy_p_parks is the best mom for driving my c… https://t.co/pNLzUMNO12]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simon and I are having two different conversations on messenger and imessage 🥵🥵🥵🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @RealJamesWoods Please help this go viral. No child should feel shamed to support his choice of Pre… https://t.co/b0D5IRqIh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't attend a global health conference, talk ad nauseam about #NCDs, and then not take an exercise break in betw… https://t.co/MTurdxh6u2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A peek at @mumfordandsons last night @FirstNiagaraCtr @ KeyBank Center https://t.co/4z6eWTrVKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great time at the kids dance!  Thanks stucco! @canyonhscougars @CanyonStuCo https://t.co/jFrYbr32o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Senior Games Technician - https://t.co/hAZIhY5UUO #Tulsa, OK #FacilitiesMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 You waited until today to bring up a study that was done in Sept. of 2018? Then you only quoted the… https://t.co/TTh6MZtL68]]></document><document><![CDATA[all_dolled_up_llc is glamming up today's Vixen!  Makeup is done and now doing hair.  jent31 is getting a new headsh… https://t.co/NAGeyURdMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ First Church of The Nazarene https://t.co/E2G5slZk14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Lake by Collusion Tap Works @ Collusion Tap Works — https://t.co/gXW4j7teU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Construya su casa con el @infonavit  Su plan es entregar en todo el sexenio unos 150 mil créditos para autoconstruc… https://t.co/1MKDO6dMbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who finds Solange’s music kinda...boring? I’ve just never been a fan🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_Jones @WWNortonLibrary SJ Rozan works out at my gym!! Can’t wait to read her next book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eminem @netflix My heart just broke.. I didn't yet hear the news and it's by far one of my favorite shows. Hey… https://t.co/WaAFcn8x61]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are an endless number of reasons for grudges. For today, I am just going to stick with the most common.  1. M… https://t.co/G3WvgiQ3Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates Cavalier is an apt description. Maybe we can still be shocked, perish the thought of what more outragr… https://t.co/09gAi19Zkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people decide what to do with their lives please help me I’m tired and stressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be dramatic, but if the Jonas Brothers are reuniting, I will spend my entire life savings to see them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashermaj It's truly shocking what selling your soul to the devil does to your body.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHOtheCALL @realDonaldTrump Absolutely they are spineless - these are the issues of the people who voted for Dona… https://t.co/5QLvdUhSBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarkinDavid Soy lecithin Soy oil Soy flour Soy starch Soy sugar Soy sauce Soy infused beauty aids Corn infused bea… https://t.co/tLYotOUzRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein These children have been brainwashed by their teacher! The 16 year old tells her “I vote… https://t.co/ZauPirpTgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a guy throw his drink on a girl at Austin’s last week. Idk him but I told him he was being a d***. He said, “sh… https://t.co/XpqjKL0orf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyKitching I'm not taking your words as a prove of what will happen, or as, but I'm seeing them as a confirmat… https://t.co/bIJ5nprLuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoosterTeeth @sorola @GavinFree @bdunkelman @burnie Peanut butter and syrup!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing my favorite for good luck! Because I can’t hear this song w/o thinking of my time with @BTS_twt in Fort Wor… https://t.co/DWY27MRCqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoNonsenseMofo @ThePunisher @AliceInChains @benbarnes I did too! When he is bringing flowers home to his girl ( I… https://t.co/Ycitxh4RDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help me win this Japanese candy giveaway from Japan Candy Box! 😍 https://t.co/zC8DbRg6Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn @Whataburger screwing up my cheat meal 😡😡 like how do you forget the cheese??? That’s the best part of the bur… https://t.co/IVsBQygANB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Try meeting somewhere we’re not paying your property for you to be there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Mack56 @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert YAY!!!! Everybody loves @brennan_elliott and @IamLaceyChabert 😍😍😍😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHampton270 @kyrstensinema Wow, and I haven't seen any snow here this year :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationsgiantburgers looks and tastes like #mcdonalfs can only dream of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨ if ya need me today I’ll be over here dreaming about the sushi imma eat tonight 💭🍣😜 . 👉🏻 if you know me you know… https://t.co/mi0Imp90WZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Starbs will you accept these foam roses as commemoration of a Catholic saint’s beheading? Thxsomuch 😘 xoxo @ L… https://t.co/WmYxl3hFvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidanielr Dice esto. Pasa que FrauPelusa puso candado en su cuenta esta noche: https://t.co/Cf06yYrC3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edylynch @AnnCoulter No one needs to hold him to his promises. He will hold himself to everything, if congress let… https://t.co/cjHaM3FIlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#misunderstanding #chain #reaction #chainreaction #try #h2o #water #hcl #end #favorite #flowers #lilies @haikujam… https://t.co/rKgD3gvRnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @Seajay603 @LouieGohmertTX1 I could see him paying only $59.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJDENSE @STAPLESCenter Celebrating @ChuckTheCondor  birthday Staples Center with DJ Dense https://t.co/56SPbT9eDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least it's better than spicy/greasy food burning my insides and tearing me apart (literally)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk Please take your time and do whatever you need to do for yourself. We're all just so relieved to hear you'… https://t.co/TT34f7LxHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly He is Responsible for exposing it. "Journalists" have had a left wing activist agenda for years, no on… https://t.co/ZjcduC3tJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is @barbaraballan Barbra... My New Biz Partner in the Famous MIAMI Salon @barbaraballan ... She is leaving tod… https://t.co/QxpzaWqHZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[National margarita day and nowhere makes nonalcoholic margs bc everywhere premixes:(((]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @JeffreeStar for distracting me from the pain of cardio.. it goes by faster watching your videos 🙌🤩… https://t.co/crpdfZ46V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me ONCE AGAIN say that you BITCHES are NOT gonna catch me in the FUCKING MIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 27 years old and Im not sure I can get out of bed this morning because my feet and ankles hurt so bad...  I pla… https://t.co/ukHAAwTliF]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY! Here is the music video for our new single “Serotonin” premiering through @dream_bound ❤️❤️❤️ Preorder our… https://t.co/ckyrCzf1sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is my heart so torn up over a ROBOT on MARS https://t.co/6S1t2d8KFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darstin1957 @DeploraBot108 @anonglxy @geegeebythesea I think you mean you "thank Satan every night". As evidenced by...the Orange one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precip is lightening up but roads are still hazardous and will be for hours.  More showers to come.  Latest on… https://t.co/Xm8JboPlwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m down 15 pounds this week 🙌🏽 also a bitch has PCOS, so that’s basically a miracle. I, Lillian, am a miracle worker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lydialynne @RazorHog66 @MeredithCD @SharpTusk @the_foot_wedge @lorismith73 @IowaHog @golfnhogs @SpfldHog Morning! I love a lazy Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting back up to speed on the #superdupersaiyanchallenge after my weird sickness yesterday. Need to focus on gett… https://t.co/isou08zHit]]></document><document><![CDATA[My happy place.   I'm smart, sexy, salacious, and I sew.  #Seamstress #MyOtherStressRelief #Brother #Serger… https://t.co/QYpUqmopXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[True Detective (S3; 2019): Although missing the compelling angling towards cosmic horror of S1, a huge rebound afte… https://t.co/WQucQpq9nH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not stay asleep for the life of me, I even took extra melatonin, I had my stupid impending sense of doom feel… https://t.co/HCoy8RgVSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see LVP being a major hypocrite about these recuse dogs. Here it is she has this center, takes in dogs all the ti… https://t.co/jRJtCVK0kU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonahwexler @DanCrenshawTX He can't handle the truth...believe I've heard that a time or two]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pyplate @jennycohn1 @Phire2Fire @J_amesp The more I watch of this documentary - the more I believe it has to offer… https://t.co/PZkyHDUfVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feaco @realDonaldTrump So you are saying that politicians exaggerate?  Kind of like Obama telling us the ACA would… https://t.co/TUf218Cvav]]></document><document><![CDATA[these ppl at the car shop know i know nothing about cars and they’re trying to get me to do literally everything to… https://t.co/51YiQ5iaX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I messed up trying the lemonades @Starbucks /: now I’m going to go broke from going there &amp; chipotle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff @PascoSheriff thank you 😊 I appreciate y’all @Kimberl38218406]]></document><document><![CDATA[woke up and decided to cut off 7 inches of my hair so here we are https://t.co/gYztOOarmJ]]></document></documents></author>