<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Happy v day to my beautiful wife. raeraehills love ya girl. #milfalert 🤫 @ Hillsborough County, Florida https://t.co/rMZXYFDKGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr Swindel’s Traveling Perculiariam circus @ Punta Gorda, Florida https://t.co/qRxjCDUUYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LazyMasquerade Well deserved! I can only hope one day my channel is as good as yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing being grabbed around here are pensions by you dirty pervs...keep tour damn hands off...please and th… https://t.co/CkBrebeQqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 5am. I just had the weirdest dream lol.  @RyanPhillippe was a power ranger.  Wtf. He was kicking ass thou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it AB won and the Steelers lost? I think both parties won today. We will see who ultimately wins some time later. #Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mollydog and #snicks enjoying thier #snowday 🐕🐕❤🌨 #sunday @ Olathe, Kansas https://t.co/3RQkucfMeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMPD investigating a double homicide on Glenn Abbey Way in South Charlotte https://t.co/uYu435Ka66]]></document><document><![CDATA[HERE Is list of previously issued Emergency Declarations: https://t.co/Bf0CNpoD0h @CNN @nytimes @ABC @MSNBC #SCOTUS… https://t.co/Cq9bwMz0aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @Kaepernick7 @TheAtlantic Kap should never play again in nfl stand for flag he is bum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digging thru some boxes at Rat’s Nest yesterday and found this absolutely adorable photo of Danny’s baptism https://t.co/9IPspwzoPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SingaporeAir Very poor of SQ with a bate and switch. In the payment process of booking a business class reservatio… https://t.co/bn2FR0p83S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even in an election yr where pols want to look good, NONE has objected to Doc's boy remaining 2nd in command at council.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You Big Orange Turd, there is no reason for the Wall of Shame.  (Only if were built around you.) Y… https://t.co/ALue4ttwmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting no records or PB’s but getting it done it 30 degree temps, wind and freezing rain. Congrats to everyone tha… https://t.co/ozbt4iWSSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This idiot was so proud of himself. Now get him back to the home, he needs his anti delusional meds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElliotRapp @BMoonB73 @billadler @realDonaldTrump Not saying you’re wrong about Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarsynCruz I bought Lillard but sold him. He doesn't poster enough. He does acrobatic layups though. I bought the… https://t.co/dgQ6zejyNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antes de firmar con @Phillies, Bryce Harper ya era el favorito para ser MVP en la NL (6 a 1).  Otros candidatos: N.… https://t.co/aQM5vRyqX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BartYasso @dwarfparatri I want to meet him someday... btw 13.1 In 2:32.05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeytar68 @pham1717 Exactly! He leads by example. The rest of the team needs to take note of how u need to play: with an edge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josh24601 I'm saying it's crazy he had the level of hatred that he did and transitioning to the NFL. No one just l… https://t.co/a3GdzP0WKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camping out at Disneyland to be at Disney’s California Adventure for opening day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[✊🏽we need more elders like this. Matter of fact I’ll taker more people passionate about black and brown lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesthatbc 😂😂😂 my rule is if it comes across my TL, it’s my business. Sometimes not either, I make the rules on this here phone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym, you are one dumb sycophant and the damage you and your fellow republicans are doing to this countr… https://t.co/bUEb07AEnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great music video by New Kids On The Block. https://t.co/GOybBVLxgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My once-decent handwriting has been butchered by years of typing and Bic pens, so I now use this fancy fountain pen… https://t.co/lKi4BzOjry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing sunrise in surprise this morning. I’m out reporting at #RangersST with @kelly_doyle_.   Tune in to… https://t.co/DX9x4TEHI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#flwx #iphonephotography #stjohnsriver #floridawildlife #getoutside #morningwalk #promoteclay @ Orange Park, Florida https://t.co/ltuG7kepa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out 👇 I uploaded a beat I am fucking around with lol 🤘😎 trying to better my craft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleeHughes89 Whenever I think of Kelly Clarkson they start turning Hazel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ajani_iAm Me! 😂 I need to get back to my sex toy business I’m building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattatouille Its perfect and Season 2 is coming.  https://t.co/LJa42Dyj37]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teacher says If you don’t sweat in the crack you’re not doing it right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoured to have you share your insights with us today Your Worship. #OER2019 #ptbo in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NexJuice Amazon my favorite is being able to buy things from another persons amazon gift 🎁 list supporting them. P… https://t.co/wkGl3lTOD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids: Get ready for a fun experience!!! @ Faith &amp; Grind, LLC https://t.co/5sxjRgrA4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessmead Are you printing a raft underneath? I do this for 99% of my prints, otherwise I get the same results]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillAdvo Fair point. Actually, the coverage has been about financial abuses. There are many charters doing good wo… https://t.co/bqMBwbnK7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_nig_osias @ronaldpen_a @Kiyyaaoptima @men_den_hall @McCdonaldsx Nigga they’d have ME ooked spammint my phone a… https://t.co/cxBtlc0eth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay I feel 80% better this morning and still have a runny nose but it’s not that bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else at eat their whole entire Dunkin’ Donuts order on the drive back home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias a .@CarlosPavon9 por la visita a nuestra cabina para hablar de la @CopaOro, que se viene este verano. Graci… https://t.co/vHhaaqRAl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...man does not live by bread alone, but man lives by every word that comes from the mouth of the Lord.” ~ Deuteronomy 8:3 #ESV #Lent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Good friends with Cuomo. America was never that great anyway. The democrats new motto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you watch Alex Jones ironically, you’ll never need to watch stand up again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Training volume is the most critical variable to monitor in long-term athletic development.” - #TheSystem #Ch4 📝 https://t.co/IW61FOmCUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TranceAddict my opinion. No one has to like my opinion at all. It’s just what I’ve chosen to go with. The player… https://t.co/JZcWZwpzkI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a breath of fresh air in the stodgy old man halls of Congress!! From a 64 year old Retired Navy Chief who n… https://t.co/v2CGcCveKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spicynormie For real...especially canceling individuals...like we got bigger problems. Say your piece and move on… https://t.co/8qCWSfyiUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/b5o7Hw5cQF Its not NRA its south dakota george Johnson eklund popchop LLC theeler wheeler Morgan LLC F… https://t.co/b4k5fx42bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skmorgane @srsupp Yes, it’s matter of degree. But, say a seminar invite, a panel invite, an invite to join a proje… https://t.co/IxlsgzSZas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueVavoom First of all he’s on a date with you. So you’re the focus of the nigga single and seeing other people is… https://t.co/IS7xOe0YeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here wondering if I’m headed in the right direction #LifeChoices #Choices #Thrive #ImHungry #Starving… https://t.co/Qe53A17UDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathmckenna @ShawnMenard1 Spoiler alert, the trans mountain pipeline will not be shipping any pollution to China a… https://t.co/sETFguTQuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please go to sleep .... you are exhausted by your terror. Drink your warm milk, lay your head down… https://t.co/iwqu8S3pow]]></document><document><![CDATA[As South Africa is overrun by murderous revengeful criminals, everyone is praising the government... shameful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy valentines 12.00 @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/GKivoh0xDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cowboys have players to resign.  Texans didn't pay honey badger so seems odd they would pay Thomas.  Chargers are i… https://t.co/uORKid2Nxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be aware your #GoogleNest has a secret build-in mic that was not disclosed by #Google]]></document><document><![CDATA[These bitches out here havin more money then these lame ass niggas -DOLPH 🐬]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the victims of the Aurora Illinois workplace shooter was an intern on his first day at work in the human res… https://t.co/CWfS8rOP0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Butta1231 @michellemalkin Just wonderful...a tweet from a Trumpkin  containing a sentence so poorly constructed it… https://t.co/oroGqNJnoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velast_k @TMKSESPN @RealMichaelKay @DonLagreca Don’t hesitate about that waxing either !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEXT GAME! It's #Spurs Vs #Raptors (Friday 2/22/19) from the @ScotiabankArena in Toronto! Tip-off at 6:00 PM on @ESPNNBA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[« Slim to none » I hope he’ll come Stateside with that arrogant Hidalgo smirk.  Trust me, he’ll be facing more than… https://t.co/WBSjiiYHd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UBSSW A4. This is a place where micro and macro practice intersect: Listen to your clients, learn from your commun… https://t.co/Zlk4N1WwxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Chicago metropolitan area https://t.co/3oeig84fDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump declares an emergency declaration he is going to open a can of worms whose lid will not be retrievable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yorimashigatari When I was walking in Memphis I was walking with my feet ten feet off of Beale I love Memphis so m… https://t.co/nSvOvCaHLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smudge and snow and frost. #windowtree #snowtree #frosttree @ Montana https://t.co/uFgT2WJuea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis Hey every media person in the world says duke is the best ever .... bullcrap.... but there the media darlings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dixon_drake @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/Y14aLPLOB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not a huge meghan trainor stan but this bitch got her bff and a husband. im-🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger So let the declassification begin and a real investigation start into the ones who truly committed crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammy_Roth Well do I recall those events. We shouldn't forget that the rationale for the Steve Peace Death March t… https://t.co/5G5KowuQfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Uncle Richard's Monday!!! #LetsGO #UncleRichardatWork @ Harlem https://t.co/e91GZ14wHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomHolmoe @DKaulana Let’s get @themikesmithway back in the Marriott Center! Such great memories of his flat top ha… https://t.co/lKAyi5qPwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraJean2017 Well I am professional trucker and I am passing through Wyoming. Unfortunately the interstate is c… https://t.co/Bh7lQxQ6qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyAStewart @jodes0405 @sbclsn @BenAndWoods @shelihiggins Bummed I missed it but I’m really sick and went home early from work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s our companion article on the migration to the north. https://t.co/f1w92cTeiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarkCloudVA @VoiceOverDom @joshhodgeson @IVANVZA_ @JayJitsuVA @BreckinMathias I liked it never seen the show but it makes want to start it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminiscing. Still the best and proudest day of my life no matter all the terrible things that have happened with t… https://t.co/uXIZamSm8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would have been an epic start to a new series! Thanks for the memories @dave_filoni looking forward to the… https://t.co/YcBD9lFIa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX Didn’t watch, I shut the TV off when Brad lifted to let Jiet in on the slide job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMArcher @UvKLvr47 @RussiaMaddow It was a damn good tweet. Too close to the truth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamTomHolland on @TyltEnt—Tom Holland is the best Spider-Man https://t.co/571Nt1mq6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BackToLife proud to be part of this great event!  What a great way to stand for the innocents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dean_Moriarty36 @MSNBC @NBCNews You didn’t fix squat. He’s a criminal, a traitor, a liar, a grifter, a racist, and… https://t.co/0BPTcEULhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKaylaKnapp I think there's a hierarchy of what's important here  Dogs ⬇️ Everything else]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to understand his subliminal tweets. Critics? Where are there a ton of critics? Hollywood! Movie criti… https://t.co/HkUP2QoBij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive 3-minute thesis #3MT talk by UAMS MS2 student Barnes Bloom on the outcomes of general anesthesia in tota… https://t.co/2K6A7b097Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with Royalty was KAE. Nigga we’re on your side REGARDLESS, but you know good and damn well you was the reason...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone that defends Drunpf iand think he is intelligent or a good leader defend this exchange #UnStableGenius… https://t.co/p46RhJAV8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Barreto I been saying they need a salary cap but Bryce Harper deal isn’t that much. It’s the years that make i… https://t.co/CeKvDZ06nm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adremafe @ABCTVpy @SaraMorenoPy @jguaido @robertososapy Nadie discute lo excelente que es, sino para q lo tengamos… https://t.co/2tMsma9vp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shame is that a racist like you is the number-two Republican in the House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[His speaking with a forked tongue is fodder for the spirit of many being affected. Indulge! https://t.co/T7iRjBEdz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanozIchimonji They toned down the fanservice though. https://t.co/rNIOTJs042]]></document></documents></author>