<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DRFInsidePost - is there something wrong with the https://t.co/NQS9lUyN85 site - cannot log in to print Gulfstream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad you’re not a GM! Give me 25 guys that love being around each other in the clubhouse who have grit, determinati… https://t.co/yF5TL0ABMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if anyone ever sees my whiteboard notes and thinks “ooh honey no that’s wrong”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dog walkers job is never done! . #petsittingsince2007 #insured #boarding #petsitting #petsitter #dogwalking… https://t.co/reP48079K9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @signorvinomtl ・・・ Prepping for the week! // #pasta #seafood #steak #experience #foodiesMTL… https://t.co/GloyvuWHe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maloonds You’re like an urban gay Indiana Jones getting into a forbidden temple before the gates come crashing down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @GhostOfTick @GreekVikingX @Lo_Gannicus @Hybrid1979 @r0xie_f0x @BertJ4411 @dgvreiman @CoachforPOTUS… https://t.co/sSsVuJchgk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye San Antonio, Hello South Padre Island!  #spi #southpadreisland #gay #springbreak @ Greyhound Bus https://t.co/rSf7GXUtFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivicSAM @WabashCollege @WabashDPD Can’t wait to hear about it when you all get back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jj_mason You're the first person O thought of when I saw this. It's like someone made it for you. :P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Technically we aren’t allowed to wear hats inside the buildings on school campus just saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si lo de Arias fuera cierto, merecería cárcel por corrupto. Pero jamás comparable con la violación de mujeres y men… https://t.co/NddtErkNIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[T🤪G💃🏻I🕺🏼F😫 tix onsale NOW (bio) for May shows with the kind, gentle yet firm, hairy but the right amount of hairy,… https://t.co/2j1RE7EeYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to chair this important discussion on #urbanism #resilience #SeaLevelRise #transportation… https://t.co/AhtoEJTmsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UConn_iQ @UCONNInCHIP @UConnTIP @UConnResearch @UConnHonors @UConnResLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[SXSW Community Meet Up tonight (Wed, Feb 20) at WeWork Barton Springs in Austin. Stop by for light refreshments, gr… https://t.co/KZvpFdX49x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfmaterial1 Well done. My reference was more to you "keeping me in mind" as being funny. Cause it is.  Here's one… https://t.co/9c08XxFIir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selenaa_nicolle I just find it hilarious but it’s cool at the same time lmao😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juandmedinaa @ethanchangchong @Marcossanntonio Cada vez que digo que no tengo mood, termina en bomba😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basssgeniee yessss it’s hot 😝 i love mine. i thought abt getting my tongue pierced but nah]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just really can’t relate to these young kids bruh lol. Like who raised them!!!!!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lehigh Valley International Airport - @flylvia in Allentown, PA https://t.co/5h6VgFxqbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @KyleLacyAH to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations, no reviews. Each day… https://t.co/DLzjxLKY17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sr. Presidente, lo mismo se intentó hace 60 años y Cuba sigue igual. No es posible hacer razonar a un burro, con el… https://t.co/4D8jfXAovM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Got a replacement phone and @HistoryExtra shows with no art. Other devices still show it. Other podcast… https://t.co/rJI7U2hci6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally listening to @Whoscoops and holy cow it’s awesome to finally hear @FroyogSoftserve’s voice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I reposted a video about Ilhan Omar on Facebook and a teacher from hs had the audacity to comment this... https://t.co/YWc6MGzl4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s often a disconnect between what I want to do and what employers want to pay me for. Finding the right job i… https://t.co/hYoJOHU6cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would any lovely female like to go with my handsome friend to the movies, he is single]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided is time to step up my Instagram content/edits. I hardly ever post anything now a days. Need to step up my game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to give a shout out to @Jess_hannigan and @JohnHannigan75  who wrote Don't Suspend Me:An Alternative Disci… https://t.co/mMNC4QXgJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine O Ya bullshit.... Give me some more  CRAP . YOU DEMS .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Mark have you seen the Grand Canyon from space?”  “Of course. I took a pretty great picture of it too.” *starts se… https://t.co/gLxUPTAkfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Lafond @MikeDesorbo1 @Ken_Rosenthal KC played him a first for a few games before they traded him. Can still be a solid infielder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now... Dems say building a wall's immoral. (Every admin since Reagan has said build a wall,fence,barrier)  Here's t… https://t.co/xxLnLOWZXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsizeless07 @datsderrick I’m gonna need a bucket for the tears if one of my teams wins a natty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechrisives @_mtaylor @BarrhavenBIA @barrhavenindy @BarrhavenJan Possibly...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never felt old until I referenced the movie Thank you for Smoking to a bunch of high schoolers tonight. No one… https://t.co/q8HqxZ4GYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeanineC @CPdevo @teli707 @rdrhwke @missyt79 @AsiaTater @casati112 @legend929 @jitterbug01 @DaB1rdM4n @WongsinGirl… https://t.co/VKIqMxpNbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoreleiEllen I love this one! Looking at my disarray this evening ( morning 4 me as I slept 4 once) I usually can… https://t.co/Lf5oCseuF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You really never realize how great you had it, until something bad happens. Like damn, shit was pretty easy 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancynursez637 @JulieSilverMD @statnews LOL IM STILL DOING THE THING'S THAT WERE HOLDING ME BACK THEN . IM DOING T… https://t.co/3UeO3CKLz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timbray Did they stop cleaning up the shit on the sidewalks constantly? Fear of that was part of my impetus for le… https://t.co/m9p0uAjl8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KandissM1 @Turki_AlOwerde @Yasir_KSA2030 @ceasere @with_dun @305local @KateStewart22 @SpiceOfOurLife… https://t.co/jgVXL7uiNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best types of cardio workouts for weight loss https://t.co/239wXpsMQ3 via @MensJournal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FtblSickness @Giants As a Jaguars fan whose team is picking after the Giants in this draft and need a quarterback,… https://t.co/HinM9WHzSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much appreciate, brother. I’m grateful to you all for the opportunity to do what I love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZito9 @antwiggily @sherry25793049 @xwordmark @mdx3232 @JoanneTirado09 @cindy_nurse @Crunk5454 @Anna012666… https://t.co/P33NCfzvGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Netflix has the Andy Griffith show now all I need is Gilligans island and the Goonies, then my child hood is complete]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QbtkFwqar3  https://t.co/3YVNU4h8SX  THE NORTH STAR........... THE NORTH TEXAS STAR... HOLE IN THE ROO… https://t.co/gFIOXr5Fw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two transactions for @Wichita_Thunder:  1️⃣ Beaudry trade voided and he has been re-added to the roster 2️⃣ Dillon… https://t.co/XifYYzT9pN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Polackio @SlyFlourish Maybe? But here’s the head scratcher - I would expect that free or next to free online game… https://t.co/oCNW1wzgQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to meet deepakchopra today at WEDU local PBS station where @davidponraj helped with the pledge drive #help… https://t.co/vXRuSYGqU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRMoffitt @BrianBrachiopod @AngharadBond @anartdecodiva @RJDownard @Drstevenhobbs @derosajoe51 What is your con… https://t.co/Lrild31QqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuteaggressixn Ppl aren't robots ya know. Synthesize your logic and emotions (they're valid).]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are very good and obedient dogs with so much energy to burn! 🐕💨❤️ @austinpetsalive https://t.co/DhQDVXGGoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StinkinGenius1 @Aaron_Torres  Possible Arnie band names: "Traveling Wowburys" "Arnie Spanier and the Hot Takers" "Stinkin' 182"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rite one Eucharist last night with the Merbecke Holy Communion setting. Makes my heart sing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still have not received an explanation or apology, so Mom is boycotting Brian Williams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter is a strange place. Someone can sit behind the protection of a screen and spout hatred and vitriol. We don’… https://t.co/TwGpoXFQhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, bored in the hospital. Better start shopping for new vinyl records. What should be next?   Meat Loaf - Bat Ou… https://t.co/OHc9zEXSp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fkhanage I agree but I think it’s not a bad thing having a manager that wants to chop and change and play different ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeFede @CBSMiami Kraft is Trumptrash but private consensual sex shouldn’t be a crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyKnows1 @karen_erotoo1 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @seahippy29 @crimsonfate88 @jfradioshow @HernandoDeSot11… https://t.co/ppolF6iMWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seaiiruh remember when I took a hit off the bong... hahaha never again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rev_Claire @cagesideseats That's actually kind of funny if they ran with that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Stout De Monde by @basculebrewery @ Bascule Brewing — https://t.co/seeDTY2W2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you laugh at the way I dance When you smile when you hold my hand I look at you and I understand Sure feels go… https://t.co/z5OJhWchSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Squad record release show is this Friday, February 22 in #memphis #tennessee at @901Growlers  #redsquad #rock… https://t.co/RKnKwrhBS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeStrawMedia You bastards! You should be more like baby boomers with fat pensions who "retire" to collect those… https://t.co/M3mBJWUQwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Oldham 2 airballs. Luckily Sahatjian has 8 with two 3’s and a deuce to give south a 12-8 lead. 1:31 1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I said to myself “Grant. You have to get up by 3:30am for work. You have to.” And then I got up at 3:29am. I’m so proud of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaVelleNeal I dont get why people think paying 25 million on Harper would be better than getting Cruz, Schoop, and… https://t.co/mebhf7um2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt de hoje é uma lembrança da Nascar. Sem palavras.  #nascar #texas #texasmotorspeedway em Texas Motor Speedway https://t.co/STHxv2JEVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishaposner @JTAnews The @JTAnews story makes no effort to explain who the group sponsoring this and similar floa… https://t.co/oJ3PwWUsRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We get an extra hour of daylight starting tomorrow!! https://t.co/eN74wVOq05]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuve o tengo una excelente semana, me fue bien con la asamblea, hice deporte, me junté con mis compás de la escuela… https://t.co/aC5gcjj7js]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Because you are drunk with the lefts hate.   Please just be aware that you are a tool being used to propaga… https://t.co/cP0F5GSU3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylerdoying @instagram @OpTic_Scumper 's account got all messed up forever ago, and never fixed it. Idk if they w… https://t.co/BMz7gc4Sxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump unravels further, blames father, Fred, for his birth. “It’s his fault. None of this would have happened if it wasn’t for him”]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is everyone obsessed with Billie Eilish i do not understand the hype]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apgocrazy_ When you tryna block the sun from hitting your eyes https://t.co/0IeQqMQbt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @npfandos Cohen Cheated On His Wife With Multiple Girlfriends, Cheated With His Businesses, Lied Under O… https://t.co/fisTjpKOlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[John McCain and Steve Forbes hosted the show and other Republicans showed up as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Floyd I had him winning.  The key was the 4th round.  Daley was on top.  Landed strikes.  Mvp was on top.  Didnt land much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinAndrade I gotta be up for work in 4 hours and I could care less what a fuckin game]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BernieSanders: “I know where I came from!” (This was off script not part of his prepared remarks)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu ainda acho que o vizinho de cima se joga da cama de cabeça no chão toda vez que vai levantar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormResist Overall my model leads towards preventing the apocalyptic riot. Time dictates time off from oh war by… https://t.co/nHT3WltOXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian5191 @RedBull_Rocks @FUTsFriend Yeah I can finish it right about now just need to buy Pique and Isco and I ha… https://t.co/NCfF7vqSkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy B-Day to my #CalTakeOver Bro Andrew Burkhardt https://t.co/xRb5lZpu0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great first step. Georgia, like Minnesota, should outlaw civil asset forfeiture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime in the CIF State Division III Southern California Regional final:  La Jolla 36, Crescenta Valley 15  Every… https://t.co/cOpB3NLyJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren You're going to accept contributions from labor unions though.  That's a giant progressive slush fund.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤫🤫 Just let everyone talk. He'll put em all in hush mode soon just like Baker did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kruperti @BCWEIS @Crewfan011 KC will do our renewals in July/August.   So .... a lot? ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTGRMatt *joke about how I would have guessed Chillicothe invented chili*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was totally tired until I heard the raccoon fight going on in front of my house... Quite a bit of blood on my curb.… https://t.co/pR42TNgKEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelhoub @ronawsumb U dont. U keep bringing him back till he proves he’s good enough for a smaller extension. N… https://t.co/yeLYGQDXia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it bad that I’m only a junior and college fever has realllyyyy set in😫]]></document></documents></author>