<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @realDonaldTrump Maybe he could go there and part the Gulf of Mexico and lead the people to Florida!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimBlair7 @ArtscenteratVT @virginia_tech You look like their older SISTER, Kim!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oussnoo What’s up! What about sales funnels and information capture pages?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiPiero7 @TribeHotDogs This bad boy would be here in plenty of time for Opening Day...I don’t think you hav… https://t.co/A9D2WYAN3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am only awake right now to hear Best Picture and be disappointed when it ain't Black Panther.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachabetic @JennieWTHR @SeanWTHR @Team_Penske With 60 wins, Brad Keselowski passed Mark Donahue today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty, 2019, acrylic/paper, #markperryart @ East Hampton, New York https://t.co/gZ3GGLDVwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukestar14 @GamerCommunity @FortniteGame @nxtpyne That would be the best skin in the game tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Ronald Reagan was a racist but he did  evolve. How man blacks were costars in his movies or in his cab… https://t.co/LiWNZ2BccH]]></document><document><![CDATA[he surprised me with tickets to the aquarium, he knows me so well🥰🐙 best valentine’s ever! 💓 https://t.co/8rrHffwAkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to the good old days when bad employees just stole office supplies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_5th_Turtle It's the same line lol, kicker says it. It used to be on TV so much as I was growing up, and it's o… https://t.co/wGNhGw49GZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has already begun to snow. 🌨️⛄❄️ Ya comenzó a nevar. 🌨️☃️❄️ #Nieve #Snow #StateIsland #NewYork en Grasmere, New… https://t.co/IdlxM7LrzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethCantBeKilld I used to like him when he did stand-up years ago now I can’t watch him for fear of vomiting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter: Help needed. I’m running for chair of the Democratic Party of Wisconsin on a ticket dedicated to superchar… https://t.co/mGDsAUQkth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your thoughts on mental illness are bullshit.   They’re invalidating, harmful and fucking stupid.  I guess that’s c… https://t.co/PwCBubyroG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandropacheco71 @KateFresePhoto I miss stoli the goalie and his ravioli saves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bangladesh Fire Tears Through Crowded Neighborhood, Killing 70  https://t.co/NjWbuqGBtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sweet little blast from our past.  #fungilover #homegrowngoodness #fungi #fungiporn @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/DOPdx4lDIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bus got pulled off the highway for over 8 hours today since the roads got too bad. Weirdly enough we were parked 2… https://t.co/tgd32BIDts]]></document><document><![CDATA[How the track coaches feel when they see the forecast and temperatures for next week: https://t.co/AYqZ4leBGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love knowingly staying up too late &amp; then in the morning being like: ¿¡ I dOnT uNdErStAnD, wHy aM i So TiReD ?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that are that dumb did vote and that's the reason we are in this mess in the first place...]]></document><document><![CDATA[trading the blackout life for the book smart life (only bc i’m living the broke life)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, help us to find ourselves in serving those who are vulnerable, sick, and homeless. https://t.co/re7ipKrV3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLPatriot @markrobinsonNC Sorry that he had to meet you, but he seems great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andres_quintero @LuchyB Eres patético y no sabes de USA.  Toda la vida New York ha sido un getho comunista o sindi… https://t.co/GC8wHKqbok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brpetertotleben Behavior of any type is much easier to understand than something as intangible as transformation.… https://t.co/m30NWHcQub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting Mickey is still magical 🌟 (Photobomb courtesy of Donald Duck😂) https://t.co/VYdRGSKVuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day be like... 🤔🛹🎥 #Wednesday #BehindTheScenes https://t.co/V50XyN8r10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobKarpDR @WMCBoysBB @JimBreuer @espn I was actually thinking that you and your camera were the only thing missing… https://t.co/da5vVL5QOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say this because I care. #CBJ can we crash the net like we give a shit? CRASH THE NET AND CAUSE CHAOS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sixers @tobias31 @BobanMarjanovic #Definitely  #forty  #definitely a man]]></document><document><![CDATA[What brightens up the day is a lovely teach day breakfast!! Can’t wait for the breakfast tomorrow!!😜 https://t.co/QLs4dzOF9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[a popular trend, especially in styles of dress and ornament or manners of behavior. "his hair is cut in the latest… https://t.co/KDLkLlavil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the day with my beautiful cuz and her kids. #SexyPrimis #TheRealJoeCab @ Lake Eola https://t.co/dUg5yXxIwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimFlannery2 I think we were lucky to be able to grow up when we did. Our son coaches Little League and has to dea… https://t.co/EMl4tmrc4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[OOOOOH, okay, Joe’s mother is in Hospice. Okay, that explains it. Best wishes to @JoeNBC and his family…]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird. I kind of thought recall meant @apple was taking responsibility and making things right. Which they are. So… https://t.co/j202DQcvCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kattaque @BixelExchange @indiedesk @SBDCLosAngeles @LAAreaChamber @Lindzlou031 @eliannevenice This is fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot think of one other “functioning well” person that does not use either text message or email other than… https://t.co/dSU240Y682]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Phlebotomist (PST) - Castle Rock, CO -… https://t.co/Wwcx5Q2p31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Wait, she recreated the NASA Challenger mission? Isn't that the one that tragically crashed with al… https://t.co/ph0bw5ZR3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @tribelaw @RepAdamSchiff @AdamSchiff @tribelaw is the epitome of a d*ck head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyrann Mathieu 👀 cmon @steelers  My favorite player on my favorite team seriously would make my life 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here the latest WZ Daily BAY BAY that ya just gotta PLAY PLAY @WRESTLEZONEcom w/ @jjansen34   https://t.co/ItqGlV7WbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewProfilePic #slp #slpeeps #update #itwastime #headshot https://t.co/jP7l8zLtO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[ole miss needs to stop spray painting all the grass green and just give us free parking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashtonteriece Ugh I forgot to tag you!!! But know you’re tagged in my heart 4ever!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisScoon From the beginning, I have been reluctant to comment on Smollett not drawing any conclusion until the… https://t.co/9X0SxDqAyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[9/25  #touringmusictech #stageleftcrew #thistourlife #stageleftview  #guitartech #basstech #zoé #zoétheband… https://t.co/Yfj6rhWKN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTestyTarheel @Timrslater2 @KenMatthews #msm is a puppet for the left. They wouldn’t want to disturb their appea… https://t.co/qXCeF1F1C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like not enough people in Boston are watching this bruins team. Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalearbuckle @Jack_Perdue @bbabyxkate @maddiejeske16 @Evan_Terzian @sorryimrileyy Impersonating via Twitter. Think… https://t.co/DIonWj6jmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21_smileyriley @kailah_casillas there are tons of reports that , he always cheated on Khloe with many other women but hey]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all born sinners desperately in need of a Savior. God has provided that one true living Savior- His name is… https://t.co/y69b0RvFxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtarm Steve Greenberg only got the case because Sam Adams wouldn’t take it. So Sam referred him to Greenberg becau… https://t.co/NFsXI2mKDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roblesangelito Muy bueno... creo le va a ir todavía mejor a @Rommel_Pacheco ya que lo hace muy bien, además tiene… https://t.co/0siaA6PNuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHoopCentral You mean a washed up star is rumored to go to a lebron team? Didn’t see that coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I want is to be a Transformer. Is that seriously too much to ask? https://t.co/IsXHQ6KajW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clean coal is coming West Virginia! #TrumpBase  https://t.co/8AQu1YJgjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallNotEvilGood @GOP @realDonaldTrump I am fair minded and my heart goes out to those that have lost loved ones re… https://t.co/MVtnQTlbqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this Snapchat, which spices up herb puns even more. | 24 Snapchats That Are Way... https://t.co/ciotVSsTIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paint Party: Day 2!!! 🎨 #teacher #teachersofinstagram #teachersfollowteachers #iteachart #artteachersofinstagram… https://t.co/pxFQqRzAsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adaniels33 @UpTheThunder You don't call that anytime, against anyone, it wasn't a foul!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliEhsassi @Tomhamish25 @AndrewScheer How about Trudeau resigns first for a) repeatedly violating ethics rules, b)… https://t.co/YW33lP5Ktz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanEFrye Haha. Didn't happen to me. I'm so immature I would do it again out of spite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MANX38 By on means am I dismissing the racism and homophobia angles, but I do believe that this individualism move… https://t.co/fSkpabf8Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find out how we can fix the Fakebook of lies with 'Correct the Record'. Sign &amp; RT: https://t.co/sCQmjd86hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Star Wars: The Last Jelly Donut #BuyAMovieBreakfast https://t.co/0OZJ8scwLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Thumb wrestled” a fellow bald guy last night. That means we rubbed our bald heads together out of respect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amityf @WCCO That's just what the priest says when he puts the ashes on your forehead [apologies if you already kn… https://t.co/ukI3rCTMS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_i I’m still holding out for physical games, so that Edith Finch hard copy would be a great addition to my library!]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚽ BOYS: Madison County and Cedar Shoals are still tied 1-1 after the 70' minute. Remember, the Red Raiders and Jagu… https://t.co/lG0dGxPSH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to wish my baby girl a happy birthday 😍👑 @rihanna https://t.co/SJBUT26EOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched a few people talk it and now I understand it. Michael Jordan was good. But he is the most overrated pl… https://t.co/BYPXXIfKB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redsfantexas @BigPopa1971 @Brandonmartine @Starrbryte67631 @DollyDwyer10 @GarDolphin733 @markfuller86 @PamelaM5050… https://t.co/ToXDbIwfb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a few things I’ll admit Americans do better than us Brits at football and that’s pyros. The @FA hate it whi… https://t.co/ImUK4LrDxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mihotep @BRAVEmediaMO @realDonaldTrump The good news is that it will be very difficult to move this forward.  The… https://t.co/NiclCqt09a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m cackling in the car thinking about @raymondchalme talking about mixed dancing and I can’t explain it well enoug… https://t.co/ycNKJDRMky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EGO206 @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett I’m what respect Ron? The judging of  who?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One To Three Inches Of Snow Expected By Wednesday Morning https://t.co/36OuJ8J1J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is the first time I’ve ever posted me on here 💆🏼‍♂️🤷🏼‍♂️ https://t.co/hKUJtSk4RO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_pickert @NaughtyAughty Yes in every situation there is a cop definitely no cap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shiny Diamonds by @indybrewing at @BruCity1 — https://t.co/PXPd5vg9la]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinDeurloo All good questions, man. On a typ job I'd never model them, for those reasons. It's a special project… https://t.co/FKkImc5FcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening 1010xl aka (Gator radio) cry over Carson Beck is music to my ears]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chak moun deside kwè nan sa yo vle. Gen moun tou ki deside ENVANTE istwa yo vle pou yo konvenk tèt yo jwenn yon rez… https://t.co/OIKApLADTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arinfishkin I thought we’d need a stretcher. I was so relieved when he immediately shouted “that was awesome!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an example of why the @MLB_PLAYERS and owners are having troubles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typical_chicago Sports movies? Each bracket with a different sport. Baseball, basketball, football, and a collecti… https://t.co/nyG8cFOKcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glxssyness @IGGYAZALEA I hadn't even noticed the checkerboard pattern!! WOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@eveewing on the Chicago mayoral election: This city has organized so hard. And educated ourselves so well. And Ra… https://t.co/Ggfer3shfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi   Hay Nancy u need to put a harness on your little BOSS AOC she will Ruin your shitful DEM party which is GOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight we celebrate the Life and Legacy of one of The Greatest Rappers of All Time The Notorious B.I.G. aka… https://t.co/HsJP6Yy5aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @HLAurora63 @Alyssa_Milano @southernwayjim @TrumpOrBust2020 @DanCovfefe1 @Dawn_DeMore1 @FuctupMike… https://t.co/5RbMkAZ7ZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh with football season over I just wish there something to keep me entertained for the next 4-5 mo... Oh yeah are… https://t.co/ksm4jQT1UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best examples of "the real world isn't the same as our hockey twitter social circle", and it still invol… https://t.co/sjPQDsdlmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @Navy_Lady_45 @OutOfRegister @Maggieb1B @SickOfTheSwamp @PauWitkowski @midwestright @gsteck74… https://t.co/pin2E9J97m]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT &amp; POST A pic that was taken RECENTLY.... like this one for @theknot (this is my serious look) https://t.co/OtquYBuvt5]]></document></documents></author>