<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thoughts after watching Oklahoma’s Offense vs. Army film:  - Cody Ford is a mauler who constantly wants to play thr… https://t.co/BN1aHjpdZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierrabydefault Apparently there’s another article where they just dismissed this tip too. 😐 It’s just too much ba… https://t.co/ioS4VhoyyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel awful for those individuals who actually do experience these heinous attacks. While we stand up for a liar,… https://t.co/GRnFxRfrwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[To have your sewer bill automatically deducted from your checking account each month, you first must go online, pri… https://t.co/CYWJAtmsOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year on this day I changed my entire life. I don’t know why I can’t stop thinking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emeraldireland1 Southern Comfort gets tweeting stuff I probably shouldn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlysonDecker10 But I also couldn't deal with living somewhere when the Earth will inevitably start shaking and all… https://t.co/OrGL46ZAmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 1:00am and I'm seriously considering playing through Mario Odyssey again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lollujo @Golden_FM I love that the regen rovers and Holme saves are pretty much in sync. There must be a fm guru o… https://t.co/0gYbj6dkUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#humboldtcounty  #coast #naturalbeauty  #naturephotography  #landscape #blackandwhite #photography  #photographer… https://t.co/wrWdMaYnLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Tom Izzo’s right and toughness triumphs, you’re due for a long winning streak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AutodeskHelp I’m interested in getting the Entire package Autodesk Architecture, Engineering, Construction Collect… https://t.co/qXjNVaKZdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomas777161 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Note to Tom and his 195 followers: entrenched establishment… https://t.co/UGpOIx9Q1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little just added the cutest grandlittle to the family line 💕 #excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @JessicaRyanXoXo @katrinamorenoof @MissAprilSnow @NoahBensi @Moriahmillsss @SadieHolmesxxx @texas_patti… https://t.co/yiaoztsISa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BofferdingUSA Trifecta! Bofferding, @NomadMilwaukee and the shuffle?! 💥 that’s gonna be fun #cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMEEvangelist Thanks.  My role is to create an environment to make great things happen by great people in our orga… https://t.co/jhy4eLWuGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michigan_Dawg @Robopz @ianmdallas @KipHenley They agreed to break the rules as they understood them. Neither reall… https://t.co/axS1sMn9FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano It must be that Tucker Carlson is tortured by his own looks. Not a heartthrob.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarIemagne @sahvagemodes don’t underappreciate First Off before i slap both of y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy es #MAR10DAY. Es el dia perfecto para terminar Super Mario 3D World]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordGram @Sanjiflow @JinbeGoat Zoro is the first mate. Jinbe is the helmsman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_hentai_hero_ This gotta be a different Lead Mead bc this is not the one I live by]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several floors of university building collapse in St. Petersburg  https://t.co/6XuNRo6LVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un placer compartir experiencias en el #AAD2019. Ha sido un gran congreso con novedades para aplicar en consulta de… https://t.co/qibHpApZEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful video from @sandyhook shared at @CoalitionSafe #notinmyschool Summit https://t.co/tp24l58X5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfister This is great.  For some time I’ve been convinced this is a primary potential of collections as data, digi… https://t.co/KDNnZUDa6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mat13Barzal @IslesBlog Secondly, so bc MDC scored 2 goals in 21 games he sucks not an improvement. Not far off fro… https://t.co/FrBYQODcKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Senack Musicals, ballets, movies, comedy clubs... that's my scene! Oh and wrestling!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently @SouthwestAir is making people pay fare differences to change flights when they don’t want to fly aboard… https://t.co/faDRJTxnat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denton Texas. Right on university drive and razor ranch. You got Texas woman’s university, and University of North… https://t.co/FuqTkbrfEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lord knows what we need ❤️🙏 #needs #love #choosekindness💕 @ Indialantic, Florida https://t.co/k9Z0xDypRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaneSelvans My original strategy was to watch Netflix things that I had already watched in English (Master of None… https://t.co/7DrbLCjpAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivyyRod Ven con cuentos de echarle la culpa a NYC! Esas mujeres que trabajan en corporate America andan en tacos y… https://t.co/AUCDEwOtOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike @NikeUnleash tonight’s shoe blowout is a tremendous opportunity for you! Release a pro line of shoes made EXC… https://t.co/2ge7iSXhrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you guess at how to align text, use probability as your guide. It’s most likely...  1) Left 2) Center 3) Right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the new Bunker Strings Vol. 1 from @Thesteelydane https://t.co/9edpczlQm2 @tremusic13 @M4rcoDS - super in… https://t.co/wicB4ZoaDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobalTV why must I see the exact same commercial during every break when I watch anything on your Apple TV app. S… https://t.co/Qg5WUX0xjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iowahawkblog Just avoid their monthly red-tag sale. All the employees are in a bad mood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorCattDelaware @GirlOnFireSally They cost 40% more now, because they're imported from China.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6, 1973: Doug Marrett scores 2 goals against RPI in a 9-3 #ECACHockey QF victory. Marrett's 8-goal performanc… https://t.co/YbcJmoGn3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three failed SD cards later and I think I’ve found one that _might_ actually work for a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the middle ground.  Of who I am.  And who I will be ohayo_brandon  #photography @ Newport Clothing and Gear https://t.co/LCsIlw60br]]></document><document><![CDATA[this medicine’s claim to make my family’s coughs “more productive” is so fantastic that it might as well promise to… https://t.co/LbXyWlPZu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EHMM_GEE That just means you have more time to give us a tweet of wisdom before you go in 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNightengale That doesn’t make sense, Bob since Harper is not as good as Arenado. But skill doesn’t have anything… https://t.co/4TjZkgjzIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawDogStrikes GDQ- about as good as it got tho the A series were pretty epic too]]></document><document><![CDATA[With just 2:25 left to play, Eastlake leads LC 48-38 in the 4A girls state championship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyper @FriedgeHNIC So Austin Mathews is a sparkling -2 his best pass last night was to Connor McDavid has not… https://t.co/8ga9hr5GpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[That SV12 was the secret weapon @Gknowles7 @TKennedy_11NL @Bwesolowski3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakersfanatic37 @ClutchPointsApp Last yrs roster that won the East, yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennDonaldson Will pay Skygreen Leopards in CBD-infused ten-Dollar bills?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saint Clare 8th Grade Boys volleyball game on Thursday at 7pm at SPPS Collinsville.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Right_NJ @realDonaldTrump @DanRaviv @i24NEWS_EN That wasn’t on our channel.  We did live fact based reporting/cove… https://t.co/EhJ6UwIwg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work really takes out a big chunk of your day especially if you got a million things to do. 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Londoner: Julian Assange closer to a journey home https://t.co/NpCaav2U0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now - #HeLiedAboutEverything Horror Story  Sad Terrifying R I V E T I N G! It just keeps getting worse. @BenitaANYC @DiscoveryID]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the strangest Twitter days of the year is tomorrow with #PitMad. Someday I’d like to be the guy that helps a… https://t.co/cuX4Abv9g8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime my brother and I drink, I just make him catch up on all the @TheoVon podcasts 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost No one likes Socialists. Silly democrats how stupid can they be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummmmm where was the security for this? @jackdwagner https://t.co/UnJvdSIuNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[TheGreatest ofAll(+or-)Apostles quotes J[i]ES'US -John 14:28-31 'Ye have heard I said,I Go aWay+Come Again unto you… https://t.co/vkpphJIhYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I guess all of the house repubs that voted against #Potus and his National Emergency Declaration all went to the… https://t.co/h4tdOuDXPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to stop watching videos about food in Austin. I just gained five pounds waiting for a video to buffer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brock_parker @meddlingmage @Top8Games Rome wasn’t cancelled. Caesar died. What else did you want?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myrrlyn Problematically, when faced with an insoluble state, functional programmers advocate for an immutable one,… https://t.co/sx9bhn7zQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress got the best reply. They deserve to be called impotant.  We need many more brave and intelligent people li… https://t.co/sJHADJwAhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Klay Thompson criticizes Warriors fans for lack of enthusiasm during loss to Suns: Golden State Wa… https://t.co/PsGEDxxGKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii All the ppl in Hollywood must now be shaking in their boots in fear they'll be heading to prison for a… https://t.co/zhrMXpz8Rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[VictorDavisHanson 2018 : Drought and Decline in California https://t.co/WBCN8FelEg via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Promo gang shit💪💪💪 mileenahoney1 lilbitof_karis... u dont need me 2 plug in all u need is it #followfinger @ North… https://t.co/MqbmzwmO1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cornf1akesCrib @sunwolves Tahs are only doing two things: 1. Pass to first receiver who runs at two defenders. 2.… https://t.co/43w1Ziix8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mbta just a FYI about north Quincy station.... the 100 spots you left us is full by 630am. These condos do not hav… https://t.co/TYHjwLbNb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Politics_PR Oh, how cute some are still third grade and not improving just caught in low IQ habits!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wess413 @campbellitstrue @trudygonzales @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump True! And that’s a horrible choice to make but… https://t.co/UleUxv2AdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bp256r1 @NickInfoSec @hacks4pancakes I put square pegs in round holes electronically....wait nm that may not go over well either]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milenio @diputados votaron por la guardia nacional militar y el senado no... Cuales diputados fueron a favor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When his Uber is arriving in 10 min and you’re still cleaning the bathroom https://t.co/JDufF4aMaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only time I remember to go to @creativemorning is when it happens to be in my own building 🤪 #creativemornings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Girl_Lafleur Which is why missing playoffs doesn’t benefit them. They don’t get the playoff experience that furthe… https://t.co/XqXvF6IaBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @ImabitcSumtimes After she catches the flies does she eat them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being ignored is so much worse than being hated at least if people hate you then they remember you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring training allows you to do that. Pitchers will probably takes some swings in their last two outings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Gun “aficionados” are always angry when a group like the British Medical Journal crunches the numbers on g… https://t.co/ek3whHqtY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we are talking about thousands of empty seats at WB.  You aren't fitting thousands in ramps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually your dead ass wrong. It’s not a victimless crime! I’m a citizen of Chicago and this little hoax has cost t… https://t.co/UhynGrDkne]]></document><document><![CDATA[It takes about 2 days to poop out a #Lego- and as a father of a 1 year old, this is a tweetable statistic.  https://t.co/7IwuK35ANR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo se que aún estás a tiempo.. no soy quien en verdad parezco y perdón..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Venezuela is a bad example of Socialism just as Nazism was a bad example of free enterprise. You mi… https://t.co/TIz9OZYg93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1999Vegie @FisherJillian @littlesnitchboy @NuttMichael And I tried uploading dog pics. @comcastcares is awful but it’s a monopoly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duffy_ma @Choosy_Female Chris Boake told me as a new prof you have to learn to juggle bricks or they fall on your… https://t.co/29SU2SY4fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnP1752 @Millie__Weaver They legitimately need to get off that dick once in a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a waste of time and taxpayers money, you have been played trump, I can understand why you filed bankruptcy six… https://t.co/LTeJdgvgdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdmcphee As I’ve seen not infrequently on twitter:  THEATRE STYLE GUIDE: Mamma Mia! If Momma was Married Mama Rose… https://t.co/qWCLU26HWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this isn’t even for a pint. It’s a bottle. Do I at least get a kiss first? #WashingtonDC https://t.co/vXDwM1qmhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was escorted by #Military police.  Her husband is in Japan.   #AmericanTrapStory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is a struggle, just remember... Never Give Up! #life #realtorlife  #justbelieve #helpingothers @ Long Beach, C… https://t.co/7NZeOVtOj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @Trumponly @southernwayjim @Tweets4MAGA @DanCovfefe1 @TrumpOrBust2020 @VFL2013 @DaRealGrizzle… https://t.co/Nuy3yxDECS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bam_MrBedrock @steelers Lol. Youre gonna be disappointed again. Doubtful they move up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TroyMI Please be sure to shovel your sidewalk. If your neighbor has a disability or has difficulty shoveling, be a… https://t.co/ShvKtGXDxy]]></document></documents></author>