<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@choctawnationOK 00000-.02 or I2.5O matthew ' na yIf ne JnsT ne JaTh na yIf ne scaT  09-.I o'r I.I9 GallaTIons ' James Th lords roTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Et s'ils réduisent à nouveau le prix des billets, ils font le même constat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday Mornings at all_city_riders  Get your day started right ...  #sacramento #Poweredbythepeople #Kstreet… https://t.co/Czh032ZFJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at these dirty piles of persistent snow the same way as all these Weather Twitter accounts I was super excited to follow a week ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[The look you give your clock ⏰ making sure it sprang forward for the early morning Sunday news on @cbs46.  We start… https://t.co/1Yzs1yHcUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Congress approves #border deal; Trump will sign but also declare #emergency https://t.co/FO8t6QYc0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most I've seen it snow since I been here for 9 years. No snow plow in my area where I live.2-25-2019 @ Sweet Ho… https://t.co/OovsPgKG5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg Alec Baldwin is not a perfect person either.  Nobody is. #FoodforThought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennieWrennnn @piersmorgan @MailOnline @DuchessofSuss It’s you and others like who are obsessed with her color. Th… https://t.co/hVr5ZScbmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @ibew481 was recognized by the  @EducateIN for our Partnerships with local high schools. It was awesome to ha… https://t.co/msA2NnAI3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[people really are just stupid with their assumptions and thinking they know everything and their insecurities]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently saw advertisements on LinkedIn for jobs at @shakeshack here in the Indy metro area. Please, please, plea… https://t.co/BKiSQqMPri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 - The River, Tybee Island, dinner/dessert downtown, and it's seems like SCAD is everywhere! @ Savannah, Georg… https://t.co/MIN3W2f9yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @POTUS @senatemajldr Mitch is terrible and not the right man for this job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧨🧨🧨 You Can’t Win The Presidency Without OH-IO  !Surrender Already? Top Dem PAC Says It’s Giving Up On OHIO For 202… https://t.co/uyclVECJjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's chickenshit any way he suckered punched that other kid. That other kid's at fault for not learning how to defe… https://t.co/xY2K7wZvT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electrovirus It’s nice but also outdated so if i got it I’d be switching some things up 🤷🏻‍♂️ but they said when i… https://t.co/tT31tJ5BW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonCrabbMusic You deserve it @JasonCrabbMusic  Ive seen you so many times i cant even count it on my hand !!… https://t.co/Fm1aaDXmsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm about to ball out tomorrow when they put the vday chocolates on sale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ethan_Mills_42 I find that Buddhist philosophy is all fun and games until somebody loses an I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ese Aldo mariategui es un jijuna hay que decir la verdad eso es poco a lo que todo en muchos años a despotricado co… https://t.co/ixVOxPMAbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennis_Jon Just read his comments about Anna and the other female tennis players. I didn't know! Thanks for the info.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cathedral Basilica of St. Francis of Assisi glows golden as a ray of sunlight slips past storm clouds and strik… https://t.co/N5o3zfL8k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwarren Ya know what would be great? If our digital assistants could help us unplug! #unplug… https://t.co/CsYYwpBElx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too Funny! But who gave Donald Trump the most air time in 2016 with there Morning Joe Show. And the host were regul… https://t.co/FPeDJr1zz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9sak2 I'm of the idea 2 edges is the optimal haul in the draft but we need 1 for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DezA_laThotty The 4 boys who beat up the man downtown and recorded it on FB Live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[E o @LADENTROMADEIRA salvando a emoção!!!! Acompanhando o jogo com vocês, Direto de VEGAS!!!! Só o repórter de camp… https://t.co/bWBBMLFy4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can someone tell me to pull up talking reckless then not show up 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMZeidman WOW again, I hope they gave you a time frame on the repairs. Good Luck. Frank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChasingAphrodit @ArtFraudInsight Reasonable question to ask why is the archaeological lobby so interested in seeki… https://t.co/KxpgqTGLHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old man at the car wash paid for a $50 premium wash on his 5 Series BMW. Then tipped ONE FREAKING DOLLAR!  Tip: Don… https://t.co/O0YYKsM2z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhanCollins Oh ... quoted definition aside from STRANGE WORLD  these days in So Many Ways! which it is :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StellaDubois8  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte’s too little for jogging, so we walked instead. At first she was so upset with how much trash littered ou… https://t.co/Z71GTmTaAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @GMA Is that kinda lile your dads National Emergancy at the border?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Netflix disables your account because of too many shared logins https://t.co/2dGwJblnl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Telling the truth isn't racist. Disagreeing with a liberal, that's racist!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELL YES, P4 BABY! LET'S GO AUSTIN! WE CAN DO THIS! @Whitney_Dillon3 @Mariel_Lane @mamawatchu @ShawneeWard… https://t.co/Bn6fHfqLDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ New Brunswick, New Jersey https://t.co/2NwFZErGcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushJohnNabors how bout his scenario fire @MikeAndersonUA and then we pull Billy Donavan out of the NBA and make h… https://t.co/EkpR4hsnhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump Trump paid over 7 billion dollars to farmers hurt by his stupid trade war. That sure sou… https://t.co/Yc22rK0fnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to follow back. but twitter won't allow me to do it.  Why @TwitterSupport]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donaldrosner @OysterBayBrewin @NYIslanders Awesome. Congrats! Can’t wait to grab a frosty Rocker at The Barn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NITIAayog @amitabhk87 @rashtrapatibhvn @RailwaySeva @RailMinIndia मेरे प्रिय मंत्री जी !यह आपकी जानकारी के लिए “बह… https://t.co/oFdRryRmHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actually this is the army corps of engineers replacing preexisting wall.  Run your bull shit somewhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[For me this qualifies as an ideal death row meal: red Burgundy 🍷 (fresh, red-fruited 2013 Domaine Drouhin-Laroze Ge… https://t.co/rJ0u3lJcbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfaber It’s a victory for the left ... something CNBC should consider when it lets its reporting focus on the… https://t.co/ecgeKqA0P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanacanalskwgn @chrisparente @christinerappwx @KenClarkTV @KirkYuhnke @DutraWeather @DrewEngelbart @SamBoik… https://t.co/Bfx31xiOlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not saying it was Jonathan Safran Foer, but he was Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSDStrong Remember the victims of that horrific high school tragedy one year later!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wuttangie @Braveswyn @ToriTeal1 @GetBenThompson @maggieNYT I have no idea what the hell Brokaw is talking about th… https://t.co/EskkngIYdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@will_boling @benmckee14 That’s two words, Mr. Boling. Two words I agree with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I got to drive a hellcat tonight and that made my whole week #2018hellcat🤩 #iWillownONE https://t.co/W0G6AtUv29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_staal @ShannyBee2 @egyptiansteven What? You think the Keebler elves just threw some eggs a flour together a… https://t.co/jCReP3iezO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mblemons @speedtrap31 @TeamHendrick @allyracing Yes the team thought they were ahead of 2 for free pass so they to… https://t.co/xTaDhOnp4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN Your and her beliefs do not represent those of the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Funhouse_F3 @F3theFort @F3RockHill @F3LakeWylie @dkgray92 @FishSticks_F3 @F3_Jekyll @Homebrew_F3 @toddbrodie2… https://t.co/prcxirmDDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Glad I’ve upgraded to 500 mbps with @metronetsystems. https://t.co/sl3mhyd5np]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the last 25 years I’ve fallen in love with English football this is still the stuff that drives me nuts. Just… https://t.co/cfgcc0L63v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heinrichdsjr I understand the physics, but it's still magical. From the top of the lane? I mean, that's not possible…]]></document><document><![CDATA[More morals than you if you support killing babies. Sex for money isn't murder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ight, I’m gonna cut the NHL inside crap out now #NewProfilePic https://t.co/zDbaYRCnJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the bots on @PlentyOfFish for asking if I’m single.   Yes I am, you don’t need to keep reminding me.   #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY!! New wheels!! Finally got a new manual wheelchair with back support for his scoliosis and pain. Perfectly… https://t.co/DCZ8DpbTp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorenzClimate Also useful because of all the consulates and embassy types in #Basel, also home to #Einstein for a… https://t.co/aoke3VI7N4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevemckinion U could have just ended that sentence “at 5:30 in the morning” &amp; it would be just as, perhaps even more, true 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewParent1 I respect the hell out of the team. I know UMass fans and respect them andnim happy for them. But t… https://t.co/7VRJDpABDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ More snow on the way in #NYC today but these hydrangeas on Martha's Vineyard  have me  thinking of summer. Phot… https://t.co/yroi8pH7ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the opening interception, Mekale McKay finally found the end zone.   On a night where the Commanders struggle… https://t.co/LF6Jfp9KrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[5x3 @365lbs 2ct Pause Squats  No matter how long or short the pause is... These don't get easier. @ Anytime Fitness… https://t.co/NFlwwhW0eW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your favorite place in the PNW? Is it the mountains, beach or the dense forests? Cold winter snow, warm summ… https://t.co/dwh9FUGTJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's hella people here. Jesus Christ. @ Gold Dust Lounge https://t.co/qb9UegnQln]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissainJax South Orange Park Publix parking lot is interesting as well! Cars in line back up into Blanding Blvd.!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When the adults around young people work together to support student learning, students earn higher grades, score… https://t.co/O3IzGpVasU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing more American than apples and @JamieWalton this is what your cult leader replies with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t be overstated how valuable our next generation of GOES geostationary satellites are to our weather analyses.… https://t.co/UjO4scmcXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes #Hearties #WCTH #HeavenWouldBeSeasonSeven @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seacrest to Mike Myers: “have you ever signed on to something without reading the script first?”  Myers: “No” https://t.co/ZO4eRSNZQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basilebilo Qui c’est ce troupeau de chèvres ? (Et ce n’est pas gentil pour ces sympathiques bêtes à cornes) rememb… https://t.co/dHX4V7KtZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbramel Lol.   So what your telling me is he spent 21% of his take home pay on two big Nigerian bodybuilders to wh… https://t.co/t0tFWvnpt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theleaderjustin @Richardalmazan1 #TheSurvivors comic pages first look https://t.co/05jdPfNuKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fesluv @SUBWAY I love me a Subway meatball sandwich with lettuce and extra pickles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamTheManCS @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @NBCPalmSprings @WxMikeEverett @AngelaisMonroe @KateMantychWX… https://t.co/bAHVcC0oYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must be pretty happy if I am starting my mornings with Journey's Don't Stop Believin' @ South Whittier, California https://t.co/qYyAJ3tpzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The elders did absolutely everything wrong, based on their own words, and still don't seem to get it. #Exvangelical… https://t.co/nvFpYvQy20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eda_edie @ShaTrigga @SonyaDevilleWWE So was Steph sleeping with Savage and we found out that wasn't true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyImageTV @Matmenpodcast @BTCRich @AndrewZarian Well yours was way better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Road to WrestleMania goes through #WWEMinneapolis tonight, let’s go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez Yea and obama said i could keep my dr and my bill would go down and now i have no insurance and pa… https://t.co/ZOauMkkK21]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to get this workout in Have a great day 👋🏽. Add me on #snapchat👻 Theq8boss 👈🏽. #itrainloco 👈🏽my hashtag check… https://t.co/zsbq9evm6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a rockin’ good time with one of my all time besties, amygafftape !! 🤟🏻🤟🏻🤟🏻 @ Rock 'n' Roller Coaster Starring… https://t.co/ERVchtKcs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@step_basketball defeats a tremendous @CardinalHayes squad by a final of 77-65 here in the @CHSAA_NYC Semi-final a… https://t.co/3SaYtaB6Pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsStillIsrael I’m so jazzed about this I’m crossing a continent for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @ClassActPod How many marijuanas do I have to inject into my ass to OD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support our emerging Reformed/OPC writer — and an important topic! @mika_edmondson @ThabitiAnyabwil @AlsoACarpenter… https://t.co/5WSi185WNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[An the category is... #OscarSlayage @theebillyporter shuts down the #Oscar2019 #RedCarpet #NativeSon https://t.co/mSEgxwXPnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMALifeOfficial Dana could go with what I call the  “Ronda Rousey Route”-after having your golden goose’s confiden… https://t.co/BXr56Vh3U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Drones have been effective in AFG, Iraq, Syria - they had Hellfires on them to kill insurgents. Dron… https://t.co/k9BCB4ZEYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the Devils should buy it and use it as a "hockey house" for their younger players?]]></document></documents></author>