<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lorimcneeartist @muz4now @paulatooths @JohnLusher @CarlRamallo @scedmonds @ShiCooks @socialbuzzlab @terrinakamura… https://t.co/GKYX7Mndiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xo_mirra I have no idea what to believe or think about this case. It’s driving me nuts lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me creating this meme account knowing it’ll get me fired: https://t.co/q7Ji1CReNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColHogan @AmyPeikoff @nytimes Subjugation becomes inevitable in an authoritarian regime. They don’t have to go alo… https://t.co/4fRN0Q8v4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdnekwomn80 @JasamMagic @AutumnH64376507 @peia_stacey I’m with you.  The only thing I want Sonny having is a gun w… https://t.co/9u9NGaGBZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[•▪•▪• from babies to babes... forever my little   seester, my lovah!  •▪•▪•  #californialove #besties #oneoak… https://t.co/I3RdTu8joi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpsareNazis @BillKristol I got kicked off for 12 hrs and I didn't threaten anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katie wants to shade Lala soooo bad but she’s in too deep with the friendship #WWHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it this far without orion playing fortnite and now he’s super into it and I’m doomed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swaps4 How could someone go about looking for sponsorships, as a small streamer who is also interested in writing as well?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pitsagainst american rescue dog show.  Best in snoring, pitties ROCK 😨😨😨😨😨😨😨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the women over 40s love that alcohol-BO-Flower perfume that lingers for 20 minutes after they walk by?? Its… https://t.co/DEk1Ttj7KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FINALLY UNLOCKED MY FIRST REACTIVE CAMO LETS GOOOOOO https://t.co/YRaglEMWhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brickandbutton saw this and thought of you. Here’s hoping your break is the easy one! Good luck. 🧡🧡🧡   https://t.co/gqBeDpBnX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarrettude so did you come out holding a book by Kant, Nietzsche or Rawls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayharrington3 Now its Monday and getting down on D Day!! Yikes!!😉😄😁🤗💕💘👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways  Curry Chicken  &amp; Cabbage  For dinner Tomorrow  Night When I Get off]]></document><document><![CDATA[On our way to airport @SouthwestAir  flight. Disney here we come... https://t.co/9RAKBw7ojG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltUSPressSec @eirerate Sounds like yet another real "standup" guy. Any wonder he's one of Trump's buddies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you happen to be close, come listen to my husband &amp; the band! https://t.co/6vRWb8kTzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mathnasium of Atascocita Humble in Humble, TX https://t.co/y1oSSAn6QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @luksicc i love you miss you so much pretty. i hope you enjoyed your day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deckard_deckard  I follow back all #MAGA #TeamMAGA #MAGAveteran #BuildTheWall #SaveTheBabies  👼👼👼👼  #TRUMPVILLE #BackTheBlue #KAG2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a barista, I hate the new cloud macchiato in case y’all were curious. As much as I love ari, the drink is trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackMitchel29 @jill_magnussen @AnnaCAAlves17 Good evening Jack and good wishes to you 💫✨💐🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @TGBrews @DaveK72 @badhopper @JohanBBT @wolv54b1 @OkiTimes @JonMontag @Just4BeerLovers @Stef_Pellerin… https://t.co/nblWsbZqN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doodlyroses Rude. I'll have you know that MY neglected website is from 2016, was made in one frantic week, and has… https://t.co/lrW3c01C19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbaldy89 Hi Courtney — I’m a reporter with Channel 8. I’m working on a story on this today. Do you hear the sirens… https://t.co/shIVRFaY80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairborsonaro Tive uma palpitação, antes de ler o final, pensava é a Dilma por favor diz que é, kkk até meu filho… https://t.co/48n3GqwTif]]></document><document><![CDATA[The men won yesterday, it’s the ladies turn today! Go big blue!💙#WeAreUk #poWEr @KentuckyWBB https://t.co/JSm5WEQP07]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teenager Caroline Dillon Wrote a Bill to End Period Poverty in Schools https://t.co/UOkH28fAxO #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is international women's day in my book the future is female as fuck #InternationWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikexingchen  McDonald's VS. Burger King in Spain BEST BEEF in The World??? https://t.co/H1TIntHxJi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Power of Love cover by @newfoundglory is all I need today and for the rest of the week probably.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheer mom life!!!! #cheerextremeallstars #cheerextremesalem #cheerextremesizzle🔥#cheermomlife💄💋🎀 #ceabria👗 @ Virgin… https://t.co/M3viNMvZNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you're somewhere prayin', prayin' I hope your soul is changin'! I hope you find your peace Falling on your k… https://t.co/USPqDJME6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the divergence in the GOP demonstrated? ALL Dems voted YES on the resolution against hate.   It’s the GOP… https://t.co/fsmYPYOsbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new post on #TheDailyProfiler in response to comments on the White Women Yoga Meetup blog. #WhiteWomenYoga… https://t.co/YS46tyP58Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love. Love. Love.  Thanks barriopdx for your love, hospitality, and this photo. #pdx #seportland #mercado @ Portlan… https://t.co/JRR5JWgOp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[ima go back to osaka to that one shop tha claims to b chicano and see wassup]]></document><document><![CDATA[❗️GAME ALERT ❗️Imma Send you Someone’s @ and you have to quote this with either smash or pass. why OR why not. IF y… https://t.co/5JDD2lZJ1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi the fucking Foo Fighters are sitting like two tables away from me at this award show right now and I’m gonna PUKE I’M FREAKING OUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were a day late for Mardi Gras, but enjoyed Henry’s Louisiana deliciousness just the same! Always good to catch… https://t.co/dVQsmJ6M1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just THOT it might be good for a super throw back moment.   She was living her playboy fantasy for sure.   Rinse… https://t.co/6tJecOZRCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly tired of getting the fucking run around with guys. If you don’t wanna talk to me, just tell me instead of leaving me on read🖕🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day! ❄️ Have an adventurous weekend. Clocks forward tonight. Best #mypnwlife #skibum #pctclassof2018… https://t.co/dV579yRB5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[UofSC School of Medicine White Coat, Black Tie Gala #isthereadoctorinthehouse @ South Carolina State Museum https://t.co/3syhWWYghR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jobs is looking quite majestic amongst the clouds today :) @ Kingsbury, Nevada https://t.co/uS8Lx74hm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i the only one that misses Ned Declassified School Survival Guide???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickWilsonWFNZ This is a tough one. Would buy. Would not wait in long line for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry some people.are jealous devious dividers stay focused dont let anyone distract you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not much to see here...just some gorgeous palm trees against a beautiful blue California winter sky ! Stop to enjoy… https://t.co/R5xDaJc4Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NKOTBCT @joeymcintyre @NKOTB @DonnieWahlberg @WaitressMusical Such a beautiful picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did he just say Cassie is the one ???? Is he allowed to say that #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to cheer savyy_13 &amp; AUM Softball on. Go Warhawks🥎 @ Auburn University at Montgomery https://t.co/BQ4bkUa9aJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans bitched about Cohen testifying while Trump was out of the country. Saying the President could not defen… https://t.co/xXOIwye6Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Brandon, your therapy is meant to be private. Don't tell your Mom about it. Just say, it went fine n you're proc… https://t.co/AqJWTQq3nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday morning games call for white!! Bring on bracket play!! #22 @ Champions Park of Newberry, Fl https://t.co/G7S2SNdHkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Equity, costs, lots to think about here. Particularly trends in online in public &amp; selective]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should be referred for a mental health evaluation... #SeeSomethingSaySomething]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Legally_Fated Idk why but I’m so disappointed lol. These some of the most humble Dook fans I’ve ever seen after last night 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a solid @FPTAStudents leadership team! I can’t wait to work with you all this year🔥 Thank you to everyone w… https://t.co/J2IyPmxspN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the guy you like hasn’t looked at your latest Snapchat story https://t.co/syG0BzOGPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @IvankaTrump Ivanka doesn’t have the ability to know that most people work really hard and would not b… https://t.co/2HVdhclrdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do some people insist on making everything more difficult than it needs to be???]]></document><document><![CDATA[The paper carried an add for a gold Trump coin! It's called a commemorative coin. Made me want to barf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLoveBel0w Thank you for finding and sharing this. It's how we learn, when we educate ourselves. John Wayne may… https://t.co/sskrZnf6EN]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU for trusting me to give you a new shape and freshen up your haircolor!!! So fun!!!   #redken… https://t.co/eqrATJxbd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @americanair ! 1/2 your flights to #CLT are delayed and looking at board - more than 1/2 leaving are delayed.… https://t.co/OWivkRe8YU]]></document><document><![CDATA[MI LISTA DE MEJORES VIDEOJUEGOS HASTA AHORA: 11 - Forza 10 - Need For Speed 09 - Assassin’s Creed 08 - Grand Theft… https://t.co/hz0hbP7LKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trees are budding everywhere!  #springinaustin #buds #budding #trees #flora #green #onawander #austin #atx… https://t.co/0qF9SynvoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only one who is honest with me about how much I suck and how to be a better person is Credit Karma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overnight shift texts to ppl bc I know they’re sleeping ; a series https://t.co/eAMVZndHXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are not already, please consider becoming one ❤️💜❤️ #NationalDonorDay https://t.co/DWiufy42tV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_monzon322 @Ginger_Lyn_66 @L_ei8ht @readnallthetime @strom_annette @brandon7nettles @tpcowgurl @Cha51brolll19… https://t.co/I2BDDWbSyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños mi luisangelfrancoelflaco  que hoy pases un día increíble un abrazo desde Guaymas Sonora en Puerto… https://t.co/Qu99LDcdS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed speaking about the legacy of Dr. Lucy Oxley at the 3rd Annual Black Feminist Symposium at UC. We h… https://t.co/ENLnPzGUDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @jayrandel to post 7 books that have tremendously impacted my life. Here’s day 1  - I nominate… https://t.co/th7QNWi1oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph_aknee_ Ah I needed it to be a miniseries so they wouldn't leave out any details! I'll still watch it though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenDawnFox29 welcome back to weekends. I hope your feeling better. Now if only we could get @MikeMasco to join… https://t.co/RaGFTuYNWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoneyGold_Chell Girl, the intentional ignorance in my posts between '05 and '08 is certainly cringeworthy. Lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodneyDavis Let’s not pretend you’re a man of the people all of a sudden. C’mon now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump has the authority reprogram border security funding: Karl Rove https://t.co/WkgKQbeOnN via @YahooFinance  “Tr… https://t.co/ZCY5IX0VTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsaTeresa @CathJSweeney Also disinfect common touched items - remote, door handles, faucet (princess phone)💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg I have a thing that plays vinyl, cassette and CDs! Use it all the time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Richard Branson's Secret to Productivity and Success Is Simple: Work Out #FitnessGoals #fitspiration #HealthyLiving… https://t.co/A5sHwAZLRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[the way i just casually talk about how excited i am for this release as if i haven't heard it a million times over by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYT: Trump asked Whitaker if he could put prosecutor in charge of Cohen probe - CNNPolitics https://t.co/IPeIZk6Wt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GagasSonn @ladygaga @bobby_campbell She needs a tony and an Emmy and then she is GOAT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tailgating tailgate Taiwan  @mainedcm  / Stacy  #DADDYSGURLFirstCrush  #MaineMendozaBarbie60]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 9th, being gently awaken by the sound of these d e s t r u c t i o n b o i s https://t.co/Vt85yFcSgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you looking at my Axe ? #Axethrowers #bullseye #sexyaxemanofmine @ Class Axe Throwing https://t.co/l4oPNEIuBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's my girl!  So proud of you!  #YouGotThis   You'll do great things!  💙💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl was such a condescending little b to me at bar close tonight... like excuse you but no bitch it’s 1:55, y… https://t.co/chROPhikNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[On March 8th we’re setting our tables a little earlier for our Women Empowering Women Luncheon. Join us in celebrat… https://t.co/grnONYGPtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Sleepy. And it’s not my fault, boss! I had to get up an hour early to avoid...the I-10 San Jacinto River bridge… https://t.co/xRFHDkOXB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanna_shi JUST NOTICED ON TOP OF THE ORIGINAL TYPO THIS IS A HE NOT SIPPY I USED THE WRONG PIKACHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nvhgmmd @SmilesbyPayet @destinyleigh221 Just my first hand experience and many other mothers of vaccine injured kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is 29 with three kids, and the oldest is 11? The fiance is only 22? Pump your brakes sis! #FamilyorFiance]]></document><document><![CDATA[me attempting to cover up the dark circles under my eyes this morning #artist https://t.co/1ZAMlvY77Z]]></document></documents></author>