<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@aunder Thanks, April. Definitely thrilled  about the time off. And I love seeing all the energy around #Angels - congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: immigration vs. emigration; immigration policy; reasons ppl migrate; sequent occupancy; forced migration; histo… https://t.co/XhEw2rvJrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[❗️Open House❗️ Saturday 3/2 1-3pm | 8109 Castlebridge, The Colony| 3 Bed | 3 1/2 Bath | 3,200 sqft. | 3-car garage… https://t.co/YGUN8fJRhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyPunchPI @thetonyisabella These morons and their constant stream of inane carny bullshit with comic pros/con a… https://t.co/R0VJQCKmQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@godstoychest That’s not what I said. #Jesus was clear that we are to not judge others’ sins. Even if you believe h… https://t.co/UJnyPUDPxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaShaunChambers @ArmauneeSmith1 @Carolynjean12 @Rickee_Smith3rd @ShaynaRae_ @Salaya_27 @RickJrSmith 🤣🤣✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_Kavanagh Went in Red Hot, Precision cracks the Sweet Spot on the Dot, Lights Out KO 1 Shot, Fast asleep Awake… https://t.co/FI4xtZ5lzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeDuncan14 @TraegerGrills Oh man, bacon at 350 for 20 mins... you will be addicted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u cant have a pina colada in the carabean where can u? 🍹#pinacolada #bahamas🌴 #atlantisbahamas @ Paradise Island… https://t.co/TA3xpqN0xY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eBikeThoughts: Very nice update to the @ternbicycles GSD cargo bike for 2019. Now with Enviolo continuous-variable… https://t.co/z6tvdu1McU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Unconfirmed.. '@SenSanders  Has not been asked if he would add a 'if u dont kill unarmed citizens by accident… https://t.co/dHFku6pBu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fighting with @SickKids to combat childhood #GeneticDisorders. What’s your VS? #SickKidsVS https://t.co/fuf8kgw65J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mills Gregory Davey - 3/1/2019  What an unreal feeling! #NewDad https://t.co/rd1Uo58Hlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one pic I allowed to show I was there! @HarrisonChad @will_roland bemorechillmusical billrolandantiques @ Gotha… https://t.co/Q3Oo28Otqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottforFlorida @BernieSanders Fuck you #RedTideRick you lying bastard]]></document><document><![CDATA[McConnell spurns bill that strengthens protections for voting rights. HR-1 now while you have some control, or late… https://t.co/OlJyMn1Omk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scheer tried to be cute when he demands Trudeau answer for himself when he’s not here. #QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WRDemonBB ready to hit the floor tonight v @LithoniaHoops . Winner gets a ticket to the @OfficialGHSA Final Four i… https://t.co/s5InE4JA92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STV1993 And...playing at that level coming from Florida ..huge bro...congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilppmd @nationwidekids @NCHUrology @salpert93 Just passed you guys on I-71 heading to a college tour at Otterbein!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman Here come the Omar Minaya boys! Jose Reyes next. https://t.co/h0qbJVxCUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the socialist #FeelTheBern blaming the USA for Russia’s aggression.  He is not good for America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News: my wife is stuck in our bathroom. Doorknob broke and you can only access from inside. My friend Terr… https://t.co/OYQIE9UnUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot out to Colton for knowing what he really wanted and being a class act]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob_m_curry Chelst and Edwards "Does This Line Ever Move?" has some nice activities appropriate for HSers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WatchChad Ok Chad you didn’t have to be creepy about it, we all know your a big fan🤢😂 you should have just asked f… https://t.co/Q40QuDXq1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Fine View of Pleasures with Sarah @ Caesars Palace https://t.co/aRbkcrOh7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s a bit contradictory to promote “girl power” when they went out of their way on social media to say “#teamnicki… https://t.co/Q6feDpIlz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBasedMAGA @RodStryker ,,, Stupid Ppl have to follow him otherwise they would have nowhere to go ,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocCityRep @WillCleveland13 Hitch was good, Bad Boys movies were hysterical, I enjoyed Independence Day and I, Rob… https://t.co/P3YJfiNvUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsamaddar @Palaeoboy Sounds like discs that some soft focus lenses used to come with. Talking first half of 20th century.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the fuck are you to insult someone’s intelligence, when your ass isn’t smart enough to know pedophilia is wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thee_AC3 @LittleNamms @jaydasneak Bruh if you think the kings can beat the Playoff version of the warriors, you trippin fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I got behind and missed this pod. As always @DanPorterfield is so on point. Take a listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do so many people put pictures of other people, especially celebrities on their profile?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up and my first thought was Lakers lost last night. Heartbreak after Mafk Heartbreak]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey Lucas remember when we were going to hog tie you and throw you out to sea”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little late night Mixed Modal Anaerobic work fine tuning some things  with one of my young hittas before they hea… https://t.co/gta3KnLKhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[-The Sabres have scored six of their seven goals against the Flyers in the 1st Period. -Claude Giroux leads all pla… https://t.co/YrEzUb1lhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker @DavidNakamura Mueller has produced charges against 34 individuals, including six former Trump aides, and three companies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No soy ningún improvisado, sé lo que quiero lograr y hacía donde camino, si me quieren seguir; sabed, ya hay un des… https://t.co/PneHgApmRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whaaaaaat??? This is getting real!!! Original DangerKatt logo by @artofant!!! #guitars #comics #DangerKatt #Moriarty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now after damaging so many with his words he is now sitting pretty with a new evangelical church in Arizona while o… https://t.co/s8oU1zvz5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinByrd3 @NBCNews Gays and homosexuality is completely different than confused transgenders. Confused people sho… https://t.co/dMC8zuCIJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[C.J. Jackson going through his typical warmups with the rest of the team. He missed Ohio State’s game against Maryl… https://t.co/bMqlg2bhNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/alC85cM3Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianjpapineau What the fuck???  The blue album is still a masterpiece!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyGolfBucky4 That’s what bad NBA teams do, win games they shouldn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solanco will play District 1 runner-up Mount St. Joe's in a PIAA-5A first-round game. #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops @golden_mules]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys I know only to WELL! Things are Much easier said than DONE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate White Folks Like Y'all Making It A Big Story.Destroying A Dead Man's Reputation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POLIV411 @MyTimesProse @ucladude101 @gbgary54 @charlesarbuckle @JohnMackeyAward @randycrossFB @uclamike11… https://t.co/8Dcfks1Vw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my favorite musicians. Kurt Cobain. Still listening to your music. Sad that I'll never get… https://t.co/4ooSnYmyb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAmandaJayne @SailorMoonsault @GCWrestling_ @FiteTV @JANELABABY @boy_myth_legend @MarkusCrane @MarkoStunt… https://t.co/qtw8JLB1ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been too many incidents I really wanna look in the garage on some disturbia shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching drum lessons tomorrow and would love to fill at least one more slot. Interested? Email me Tony@tonythaxton.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMFB_Stephaine Any american in that age group who donates their hard earned money to cancer research to me is an american hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite a serious bone spur flare up, @realDonaldTrump has apparently arrived in Vietnam safely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jasonkessler16 @GatorsMBK Scottie’s knees hold up and we know what happens Sr year!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchooledABC needs to throw a homage to 1990s fictional college Stansbury. https://t.co/xW6tnhejFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple Rainbow Unicorn Highway Star #purplerainbowunicorn #iangillan #deeppurple #neilturbin #deathriders… https://t.co/xggD70NBfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the revisions in place we still have not broken below 6.5 months for new home supply, this matters… https://t.co/oOWnRQoTlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now do the story of a president who sent thousands of troops to the border for a manufactured crisis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love it when you call me big pappy 🎼  Throw your hands in the air, if you'se a true player 🎼 "I love it when yo… https://t.co/zq7ZttYowJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I guess 4am is my new best friend huh?? 🤦🏻‍♂️ I just wanna sleep the whole night it’s once.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WWEAtlanticCity love u forever Dean Ambrose. 🖤 @ Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino Atlantic City https://t.co/XBi13sem5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkfphoto98 @CBellRacing @KevinSwindell @SwindellSpdLab That is a badass machine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nightly meditation - #acid #tb303 #mutableinstruments #modular #eurorack #dawlessjam @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/3dU5asDHig]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter how many yards are needed for the conversion, 3rd down is the Renfrow down #NFLDraft https://t.co/Lv6cANgfkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaadYousuf126 @seanshapiro “I am comfortable with foreseeable unemployment”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Text book example of the core values wanted and instilled by the United States Marine Corps. Simply Outstanding!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH I LOVE YOU IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE UNDER TRUTH GOD AND TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST. MY LEGAL HO… https://t.co/LZJErOl5T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @telemal @CoryBooker Did @CoryBooker help Jussie with his story? Maybe the FBI should examine Booke… https://t.co/yrxfvUN7ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *studies hard and learns the material* My brain 3 seconds into the test:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoniLynn817 Awesome beautiful sexy lady it's makes me feel like dancing 😝 https://t.co/5oE4asbijn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lole_simon My Grannie used to make pancakes with lemon and sugar. Delicious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exfkaty he lives in New Jersey, is not registered to vote here, and is going to get spiked on residency as soon as he tries it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. This one is so close yet so far away. Wish I could get over there ASAP. How far away are you @jwrentalqueen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For whatever was written previously was written for our instruction, that by endurance and by th…… https://t.co/VkQcQsL0Mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryce2STL @NHL I haven’t had this much fun watching the Blues in a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 59.1°F Wind:3.1mph Pressure: 29.983hpa Rising Rapidly Rain Today 0.00in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it stays a three-way tie for first place in the SEC. Kentucky, Tennessee and LSU. Wildcats at Vols on Saturday i… https://t.co/OZEbj8xHlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol I voted to keep Donald. Not because he was my candidate (he was not) but because this is my country an… https://t.co/46FIW510TM]]></document><document><![CDATA[But These are the best seats for Viewing the beautiful flat earth #FE yes it's true Satan has been lying to you !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM THE LAW.  #DREDD #SOUTHOFTHEBORDER #SC @ South of the Border South Carolina https://t.co/i7oJdmZ5gD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctitusbrown Somehow I knew you would be attracted to torment. The 2-page proposal is due March 4th and then folks… https://t.co/yorh1dx8hU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t often agree with NYT articles, but this one is right on!  Omar is an insidious hate monger of the west kind… https://t.co/D38ifMaeFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LadiesTakeNote - There may be plenty of fish in the sea but wait for your Nemo. Until then take Dori's advice &amp; just keep swimming :)🐠❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@___Swen_ These dudes better leave us alone we have important things to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto It is sad when Republicans miss the point. This vote is about the country not a petty power squabble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @SaveALot! Just #published #fitness #book "Ageless Athletic Assassin" on how #martialarts saved me from… https://t.co/8hr5V7jjW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[people get on twitter and act like a brand new person. they must be hannah montana and miley cyrus? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocoaSwann @fawfulfan The 25 thousand jobs the economic genius just drove out of her city 2 weeks into her term wo… https://t.co/5eX8cylvk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrestling State Perham vs Waconia 3rd Place Team Live on The Lakes 99.5 now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyaOldsSom @BosBizJournal Another wonderful article with great insight in the differences between… https://t.co/JZoMzqdzzg]]></document><document><![CDATA['It’s not who I was:' New Town woman sentenced in embezzlement case https://t.co/DgztKhsy8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the W column for @SalisburyBB with a 7-2 win over Neumann. Amisano (6IP) and Rosso (3IP) get things done on… https://t.co/sfVvhuLSHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama is always the excuse for trump’s shortcomings. Of course trump has done noth… https://t.co/1l1XkIJeOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still haven’t seen “The Greatest Showman,” and it’s legit driving one of my co-workers crazy 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba Ahora los inversores se las van a ver difícil y ustedes los perros la dieta de moringa congelada qu… https://t.co/6lWMaP9enY]]></document></documents></author>