<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I smartened up. Opened the market up. 📈📈📈 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/elOiToXPnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There's about a million people searching through your old tweets as we speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems appropriate for #sunshine week to listen to #SmallTownPodcast on #SmallTownSunshine! https://t.co/ObsihTW92e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lithohedron @diana_grimshire @redfacts That almost tempts me to search "falcon sex hat" so that the ads start floo… https://t.co/wEEjb7Fgy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WordsmithWorden @Jacopo_della_Q "I PRAY TO THE GODS FOR A GREEN TIGER!" oo... thanks.. that was fast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJohnsonLaw What really makes me SMH is how anyone running for president wouldn't have their taxes assembled and r… https://t.co/aOx8aVRuKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a time for a wave but that passed We need a revolution #YouSayYouWantARevolution]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lambstiel I just found out my friend’s baby is gonna be a Libra and I was like..... yikes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[...when you finally heat yourself up some leftovers.....and next thing you know your dad is eating it.....who needs… https://t.co/3qzz7eHobM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joegagne Probably the reason.  Nitro only lasted a couple months, but it got kind of okay at the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woodcider @HoarseWisperer @MtnMD @kylegriffin1 As a Seattle resident I can confirm that is exactly what would happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fun night enjoying the ephemeral voice of #auroramusic  🌍 #observatorynorthpark @ The Observatory North Park https://t.co/ZgkWqiScfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw my reflection in the doors at church &amp; realized these boots were not the right choice with this dress #failedfashionstatements]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's #CALL 202-224-3121 to get even #MORE  Cosponsors for #HR1298!!  👇👇👇📱📱📱👍👍 https://t.co/CPQthpzy3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsuncionZhane @TNTBoysOnline @WorldsBestCBS @TheTNTBoys Yes.  All of the highlights of their version of this song… https://t.co/cCXW76vvtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi I can’t sleep and I can’t decide if it’s because I’m alone on Valentine’s Day or because I’m extremely ill prepa… https://t.co/pwNdDxkSVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[theatre kids, it is with a heavy heart that I must announce our parents were right https://t.co/kr61bLXZVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried downloading the lyft app and I accidentally downloaded the driver app and didn’t realize what I was signing… https://t.co/XEBQ7HOhVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bedtime is anywhere between eight thirty and midnight...tonight it’s 9:53]]></document><document><![CDATA[i look damn good in a ball cap and it hides ur face and greasy hair and prevents sun burns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture of VP Pence and Jared Trump.  Who is Pence sitting with?  Who is Jared talking to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mward33 @TonyParks7 @kckhenry @DeanaRaymer @mmiller146 @MSXPrinEldridge @DaylLynn @BMGranger @lmb329 @MrsBenderCV… https://t.co/sfY5IlD2xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing big things ladies!! Keep it rolling!💪🏼💙🐗🥎 #LSCsoft #streak #playhard #greatstart #javelinafamily #GoJavelinas… https://t.co/J1lM6OmBQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elise_Jordan @MalcolmNance From what I’ve heard, there weren’t too many bars that he passed...🍺🥃🍷🍹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samantha is busy investigating part of last nights parades haul. #mardigras2019 #beads #shiney #noseycat… https://t.co/YOy5lllWHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanaryMugume @SoftPowerNews @OfwonoOpondo @lindahNabusayi @AbuMwesigwa Hehehe don’t forget your ethics behind as y… https://t.co/vKKR57czex]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do really bad my daughter has has pneumonia she's in the hospital $squishywet is my cashapp 🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🙏🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah!!! #SmoakShow #SmoakLadies  #Arrow #Olicity #DontMindMeImJustSwooningOverBabySmoakQueenAndShippingOlicity🚢❤🎯👓🍼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t but my ass fat so imma still skream it! 🗣 And the stretch marks on my sides DEFINITELY touch my booty a tad… https://t.co/vc9s2B9mnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roto08 @bobert1979 Why? He had a good time. He was way done before I even got there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say these things about it “not being for the kids” but won’t research anything to even see if it is or not.… https://t.co/ecASZN8e5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be dramatic or anything but tbh my lips look nice af in this pic 🥴 https://t.co/kMT2UbYhry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MF_Greatest @TonyaGJPrince 😂Good point and coincidentally Spike Lee’s movies was up against them both for best pic… https://t.co/cgUhTJ9l3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManyHatsMilles @PSmbasketball Sounds like some of my men’s league 4v4 stats in my early 30’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexAndHerSon @LindaCarmical @brendaslynn @BourneNatural @LearnIt2EarnIt @lindamclay @Brownielocks01… https://t.co/mYUXJPDpk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you "DEMAND"  and "COMMAND" your lower half to remain "TIGHT" and " TONE" hips, glutes, quads and let's NOT fo… https://t.co/OzIuowr6NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos @NicolasMaduro síguela cagando así Magistralmente, el rastro de mierda y el olor putrefacto los llevara hasta ti y será tu fin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the furthest thing from a draft expert so I’m just going to tweet the extremely obvious things about each play… https://t.co/WGoKlBOUfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerobaldo Esteem yo también caduqué en el sueño 😂. Me desperté triste. O sea, mínimo pensé te salvaba nadando pero… https://t.co/A5CBEg3EaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally, everyone: Have any valentines plans?  Me: https://t.co/HfWvD7BoS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hope_Carter @HTownRush @LisaKHOU @JanelKHOU @MichelleKHOU @chitakhou @StephKHOU Only in the shower. https://t.co/BtJoenfDUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya girls losing weight, clearing up her skin and has a new man in her life 😛🎉🥂  2019 is MINE.  2018 WAS GARBAGE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love children, too bad they grow to be adults and lose that sweetness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc Hey SMARTY BRITCHES...maybe you should’ve funded the border wall.  It’s just as much for your security as mine🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[remind me to never again wait until the day before it’s due to write a 6 page essay 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[One is key to a happier relationship...@KezhalDashti breaks down the research on @News8Daybreak. #iamup @wfaa https://t.co/bMnz8IWeT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily Who cares; his name calling and lies will add nothing to the debate. He assumes a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scalzi I’ve done it . I’m fat and I have no muscle tone but so worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Pastels hot off the press...one took two days and the other 30 minutes. I like them equally as well. It's rando… https://t.co/1hhgR3rPAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@studiocyen Ahhh yess that kind of stuff is so insane and cool! I had forgotten about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marizedeandrade @rafaelprimo @jairbolsonaro Empenho no que? E de que defesa falas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the MOST amazing time in  Cali with my bestie 🌞👭 she is one of the most amazing woman I know! She is full of… https://t.co/ZBNuKuhvdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone on my TL: Lemme get 10 on pummmmmpppp ..... Hol on...... pummmmmmmmmp 3 pump 3 lemme get 10 on 3 .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @The_Coach_Hart to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanation, no review… https://t.co/9GVyeslLAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @TrumpsareNazis @PressSec Sorry Andy #donthecon lies to the American people again because he’s a CON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPEmilyG majority of the biggest problems on planes...not babies acting like babies...ADULTS acting like babies...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈 . . . . . . . . . . . . . #makeup #Color #eyeshadow #juviasplacezulupalette #juviasplace #zulupalette #zulu… https://t.co/7NMkOzBhpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @MrsNovak2 to post #7BooksILove - no explanation, no reviews - just cover(s… https://t.co/MUQQrIMkIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4dagoal @love_ydw she tweaking. lol but let’s chill. I don’t think she’s having a good day though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been able to sleep at all tonight. Fucking sucks. Too much outside noise from surroundings in this hotel. A… https://t.co/A21JQUh7QA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomkuegler7 You are one of the least selfish people I know. I’m glad you made those goals, but know that you help… https://t.co/s9rI5geOPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 @alaskawater Let's try that on men (especially those who feel entitled)...outlaw Viagra or any drug that… https://t.co/uMkCoN27sY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland ‘We can flip Texas,’ Democrats insist, as they look to 2020.  https://t.co/fNxC2DG6EQ via @WSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that the extreme selfie phase is -for the most part- over. Either you’re Instagram famous by now or you’re n… https://t.co/okWTyz9nMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy Crystal made me do it. I was, like, this is stupid.   A whole decade later. Still stuck on stupid… https://t.co/5MSQ3GomeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from my office today. #sfscene #baybridge #sanfrancisco @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/4n0dSqSh43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey girl, you really rocked that new seating arrangement - way to separate the talkers. #comedy #tee-hee #grin… https://t.co/6Dmgn4KTmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma used to have a tienditia and sell these that she’d make from scratch 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball is Life!! Let’s go Burnham Boys!  Get a win at the frontier conference tournament...we’d b there but a l… https://t.co/xRjs7DCnAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's snowing again. This might be getting old... #SaturdayMorning https://t.co/ccMp5Zlnco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wawa is the only place that has my popcorn rn . I love them Mfs so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrColinfan @SeasideScribe @KasoKim @KatFitzpatrick @AmmerTime @mchastain81 The musical scale uses latin spelling a… https://t.co/tjsj2kF1yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I’m actually saying this but, I’m tryna move away. Like AWAY away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching America’s next top model makes me want one of those make overs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonbbyjojo @juliahopeart @moonbbyjojo  thanks 🙏 probably right According to ya&amp; my daughter Hannah Humphrey… https://t.co/o0zgkOj15l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRapperKlaus_ Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight.  https://t.co/dV1bRqmseN]]></document><document><![CDATA[-- it is NOT hyperbole to suggest our children may be the last generation of what you and i know as "western civili… https://t.co/HeRE2Xz9NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonesometoast @ThreeColumnsArt I LOVE the green suit @idriselba is wearing ❤️😍❤️😍❤️ Hopefully there is a beach ski… https://t.co/3ksqI7kBWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone want my @halljohnsonTX ticket for tonight?? i can send it ur way. getting some wisdom teeth work done today so 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very honored to be one of 50 talented and unique dealers to be included at the new @1stdibs gallery at the termi… https://t.co/5f6dgX6Tqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all okay I’m procrastinating so like this and I’ll reply w/ a word that reminds me of u]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 pages @imkylecooke 😂😂 giving me ross &amp; rachel vibes #DoesIt? #SummerHouse https://t.co/VUMa81fJEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philipnolan1 @facebook Wow never heard of such a thing......only in Ireland....🤔 bloody cheek.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rasmansa The evidence strongly suggests that a is true and we should work on that assumption. But no final decisio… https://t.co/HMvSdPqTjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter US Customs and Border patrol and ICE have, sadly to say, taken on Trump's prejudices. They're tainted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In action racing in the For Love of Chocolate 5K race the past Saturday. Took 2nd out of 10 in age group, and was i… https://t.co/yCCdI9zcCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Think_BlueLA He is one of the few ex-Dodgers I still root for. #Dodgers ⚾💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhoniDu Happy birthday to your beautiful Mom💖💖 What a blessing 💖💖 https://t.co/OGHI8JN6z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sidebar: I see posts on social media by people who think docs are getting $ from big pharma to administer meds, hav… https://t.co/Sa5U1axyn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family’s restaurant in Texas made Yelp’s tip places to eat!! 🙌🏻❤️https://t.co/7ysxbhOf2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got a new shirt from a friend!! it has fun stripessss https://t.co/iV5fJ8eiEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think god has put the right temporary people in my life because It has shown me who will always care and who won’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For fun $25,000.00 Share the Riches Gift Pack!  Play Free Scratch Cards!  We Could Both Win Big! #ShareTheRiches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway Thank you. The vast majority of #7train riders live in #Queens. Subjecting our line to a Manhattan-cent… https://t.co/0MJh40eSjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 4:14 Am real time Photo and so it is here #snowstorm #snowday #WeatherAlert #NY1PIC #NY1Snow https://t.co/7S0rk8IqB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few photos a gentlemen by the name of Peter Disbury from the Grand Canyon Hiking Group took yesterday at the Gran… https://t.co/QJXRkiODYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stellabelle @thatdappguy @hodlbrands @BlockchainZack @eosnewyork @Ashe_Oro @rushingdallas @JPederson96… https://t.co/s2YxIhkUMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather Or Not In Michigan https://t.co/A1ZhXGS4GN https://t.co/JO4MKIcJVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CNOY19 with @atkleiman, @madifuller13 &amp; @YWCA_Niagara! #5K #SharetheWarmth https://t.co/XVJPpJymCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton knows the exact moment he fell in love with Taysia!!! #TheBachelor @BachelorABC]]></document></documents></author>