<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at Carl Sandburg Middle School in Mundelein, IL https://t.co/mODKcYAfHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gem_Stoned @WomenOfMFC @chubby_cuties @_GlobalBeauty @SWRTxxx @pro_sluts @robertgiguere59 @CammyExpo… https://t.co/EIg0ZCecWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aiden_75 YOU have earned every opportunity..  hard work, strong character,  and perseverance..  keep grinding... o… https://t.co/J3n65JKePA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Cameron Pench (11) for his win in the Varsity Boys Pole Vault vs. Hart HS. @AthleticsRoyal… https://t.co/0Vl0BAWdzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Smoglifter by @brashbeer @ Brash Brewing — https://t.co/wnU0nvQuJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[dintaifungusa #soupdumplings #sweetlife allysteb @ Din Tai Fung  鼎泰豐 https://t.co/rJ8iqHFFL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[need to clear your meeting rooms from meetings that frequently run over or from outright room squatters? try this!… https://t.co/xq0UtDPLCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHP1972 @bmstokes @FRCdc @SenatorLankford They don't CARE. We already know this. Religious Fascists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmvaugha @amvetsupport @Anthony76606359 Did you read what I said or are you just reacting to the word lead?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I remember @Jakobcrowell1 doing this to a kid during a meet at ockerman way back when]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers Was Presidential and respected worldwide...seems like two years ago or so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet @FastCompany's Most Innovative Companies 2019 #FCMostInnovative https://t.co/cPqWUvCrZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OH_Playmaker11 @SeanyBennett @ESPNStatsInfo @BoilerBall Clean sweep baby....deal with it numb-nuts! https://t.co/yCGSr0DP7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacMallyMMA Every time it looks like he might be getting close to a finish striking he changes levels and goes to… https://t.co/dwY1IcXI1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching Bible Study (@ Riceville Mt. Olive Baptist Church - @rmobc in Houston, TX) https://t.co/GCUecdb3Vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Del 6 al 9 de Abril Levantando casa a Jehova en canoga Park California Ministerio Jehova es mi pastor https://t.co/2cWcYW6hBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saunachronicles #strongboxgym #strongboxgymkilleen @ Strong Box Gym https://t.co/BnaBK1md15]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the taplist isn't exactly floating your boat, but still find a diamond in the rough... - Drinking a Helles Lag… https://t.co/h5Xl1spmE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remarkable1979 I bet he tipped them real good tho lol. Or maybe he really just got a massage 😂😂🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You were so clumsy and goofy man, everyone loved how you ran😂😂 ur pants falling and you always pulling them up runn… https://t.co/lj8s3Ypur0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretending like I’m @reneritchie! @ Southwest Airlines Lambert St. Louis Airport https://t.co/FMR8cvg3Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at JOANN Fabrics and Crafts - @joann_stores in Milford, CT https://t.co/v6jAUzeEcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lise Ravary: What if SNC-Lavalin were based in Toronto? https://t.co/L5ynkt5CyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenmosher @milkchaser @pcampbell001 @priscian @JamesRider3 @RushhourP @ray_langella @AltUS_ARC @SteveSGoddard… https://t.co/srEkYqT5Ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you do.. Please, resist the urge to #TalkDownTo people or you will come across as A. #Mean or B.… https://t.co/6z1ak51IuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWinters412 @craigcalcaterra Always liked him. Gave him every opportunity to review the source. He has me muted no… https://t.co/6K1G46xJPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for the halestorm Five Finger Death Punch shinedown amaranthe halestorm hinder zack brown band Ghost band]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Grayhawk 10 Tranny’s deep.  2014 was a good year for the goat. https://t.co/m12OHM7E58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Purduebball55 @_jasonwright59 @JTBossHogg @jeffborzello That very well may be but the Big12 has the edge this year… https://t.co/FxsO5aKXyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngleRick Maybe you should have read the whole thread. A Raiders fan criticizing a player for signing with the Chi… https://t.co/YEXCbRPAXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shamusroan13 @MomO5Tiff @DadFiction @MrsTyler78 @sweatsntopknots @gentlemanvet67 @jdstalnaked @Mark_Neitzel23… https://t.co/6hghvUwMwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrooperTodKHP Snow=moisture. Moisture=bountiful crops. Bountiful crops=happy farmers. Happy farmer's=good economy.… https://t.co/wsd0mSzQTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_tamez ...y continuando con la gustada saga de las hociconeadas gay-adas 🐧 @SancadillaNorte @DonChannok… https://t.co/caG4Vb50yG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engaging the media for policy research: Four critical questions to consider https://t.co/R21Z56u5XE via @Research2Action]]></document><document><![CDATA[@universalhub why do you disable your site navigation on mobile? I want to get to neighborhood specific news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun at @rampup presenting @dataxu's @liveramp IDL integration-for-RTB results to a super packed room: -… https://t.co/XinfgGzkVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!!!!! RT @TrentonPK23: Inconsiderate people absolutely drive me insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was DEFINITELY setup!  Absolutely no way this guy isn’t either a loony liberal or on one’s payroll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHEVYWOODS keep my daughter chucked up and ganged out 💪🏽 https://t.co/fw2ZaxM1tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[... I am BillyMieder on https://t.co/oV9kX6Yj6z @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/csyzT7xim4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And IIIIIIII, don’t know whyyyyy I’m going round in circles for ya. All i get is your cold shoulder”  I got this Fever for ya, Love 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[85% of all the players in the NFL today are from single parent homes... Within 1 year of retiring from football, 76… https://t.co/v6bjWY1CVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY QUEEN  ❤️🖤❤️🖤❤️🖤 @fatbellybella 👸🏽 🖤❤️🖤❤️🖤❤️ I’m bumping nothing but Erykah Badu all day in tribute… https://t.co/0Lkcu4QkEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FedExHelp is it normal to receive zero updates on shipping location after inital departure? Package due at my door… https://t.co/voG8VLeLKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pompouspablo And I think I like him better with the fitted cap on He ain't even gotta try to put the mac on He jus… https://t.co/taNBia12dK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein This foolish woman w/supposedly 263k followers, couldn’t handle the truth. She blocked me. Everyone f… https://t.co/GLixcYBlcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Radio Zombie Phone-In by @BrewDog @ BrewDog Franklinton on Untappd https://t.co/fEwAjdIyUG https://t.co/dcrnZFYFcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jihadi Hoda- The Face of Treason in 2019 https://t.co/jt6lrQu7qE via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaliyahNevaeh7 @mjvenesco Hi Lauren happy Saturday https://t.co/CCaFv50I18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMCTheatres Boston Common AMC #TimeCheck you are 14 minutes ahead of the rest of #Boston . #CaptainMarvel  ? No,… https://t.co/MY7BDGi4y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t expect too many tweets from me tonight #ToonamiFaithful, Uncle Alessi is havin’ some fun in #Vegas this week!… https://t.co/cA0cEE0qtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[God of compassion, help us to give you our cares and anxieties so we can find peace and rest for our souls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo. I think you meant to send this in a DM. No way you wanted it public, right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 9 - Today's Headlines from The Boston Globe:            Scuffles erupt at Jerusalem holy site over w… https://t.co/zEWI1vHYIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DigitalVerticallyIntegratedLiquid  #gawx #Rainy #Friday morning https://t.co/wNMWtHyscN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anna_Filipic As you should. I used to remember how many guys who used to be creepy to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damnably @accorinrin @otobokebeaver @SaySueMe @BandDBGC @electric_muse Just booked my flights a couple hours ago. Third year in a row! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAPSonline Yeah. That’ll work. Let the “plan” determine the reimbursement. Anyone else think that’s why we’re in the 💩hole we’re in now?😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad first day of hunting! 🇺🇸🇺🇸 @ Higginsville, Missouri https://t.co/14bkY6eH1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been drinking for 4 days, about to start the 5th day in New Orleans... I think I’m nearly Mardi Gras out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike that shoe exploding during the NC /Duke game wasn’t a good look...got to go back to making better shoes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall Every time I see a picture of her, she has her mouth wide open, Stonewall Jackson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmelodifazio La ayuda humanitaria no la necesitan los 25 millones de habitantes]]></document><document><![CDATA[guys who delete and create a new Grindr account every 3 days need their service shut off 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Face Swap - Automatic and Funny by Microsoft Corporation https://t.co/0R1DUsCmaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElaineMomNC @CardinalDolan The Archbishop final wish was to be buried under the main altar at St. Patrick’s Cathed… https://t.co/sCZGYhuCrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USARenaissance @Don39779746Don @Serremmy @adwrn @T_FLgal @jonz970 @deed133 @Aug1405 @Walkdc77 @GeanineC @Rushelle8… https://t.co/XjoxW2KKzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i text Rayone.  Me: I Love You   Rayone: We love you too  The WE!!!!! 🤰🏽 #DayMade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaRTubbs @dodgerdudel @tedlieu It’s not factually correct to label people you disagree with as white supremici… https://t.co/GfzKhTZ0rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should know this... HISTORY OF RELIGION (Part 50): GENTILES ARE NOT UNDER THE LAW? https://t.co/d5CTbZ4MDj via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appalling, @JoePiscopoShow,  you are hosting the most ignorant, right-wing pundit you could possibly find. His lies… https://t.co/106j4rTBRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Queen is at it again! #BlackKittiesRule #13 @ The Cliffs of Insanity https://t.co/MSnxKVdfrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_little_old_me College , both of us were drinking.  Music cranked, speaker over my bed - she’s on top, it’s dark.… https://t.co/IpQIdzx8Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired by Momo 🐈  . . . #parkour #freerunning #offaxisacrobatics #gardenoflife #thankstomyhealth #sponsored… https://t.co/ETfUmwmdMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahHandy85 @MainelyRob @AshleyCote74 @BrittanyCote94 Gunna say it Starts with an A and it rhymes with Mylanta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLeiper So you are, at least temporarily off the polished, ice free, bike lanes and on the dangerous sidewalks, li… https://t.co/CfkbC4MrB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an unlikely task, being such a light heavyweight with a record that doesn’t compare to most at the state tourn… https://t.co/80m7wlKh7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Birthday Spotlight Celebrating The Birthday of Germind 20 Day Birthday Party: March 11 - Ma… https://t.co/S5YMtnnhkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AlabamaBSB OF T.J. Reeves dives safely back to 1st beating @WeAreSouth_BSB catcher Carter Perkins’s pick-off thro… https://t.co/iar0qWqbDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mj_lee I've been convinced for some time that schools close and are delayed often because the reduced traffic duri… https://t.co/OTexi5nq16]]></document><document><![CDATA[every morning I wake up and get about five seconds to wonder which hop along song is going to get stuck in my head… https://t.co/4n9a7iT4SD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d see myself become a morning person but I think I’m starting to come around]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimGavrich @Back9Ben @RichardZokol @LinksGems @AnthonyPioppi @TPCSawgrass @PGATOUR What’s this puzzle crap? I get… https://t.co/w8iFmS7fnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilHamsterEnt He’s a very successful journalist I think you mean Dave Portnoy but either way keep spending your t… https://t.co/ahhTaZs5hN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing brings us more joy than seeing you Mariano!! Excited for this weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather have Tatum if starting a franchise, but right now.. this year? Can anyone argue Tatum has been better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RossDixonEllis And I’m a guy who somehow made it to the other side of the country, so it’s not so bad. Either way… https://t.co/JkEjEfaRxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to formulate a tweet to really encapsulate the feeling it was to see Liger for the 1st time. Got the sense h… https://t.co/YYeUVkylon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always good to see my man Jorge at Gallagher’s and have his support and vote! He serves me and I’m here to serve hi… https://t.co/zYl0as8uFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond Perception is back!!  Food, Open Bar and unlimited Virtual Reality  Join us in TriBeCa Sat March 9th, 7-10pm… https://t.co/CByfdw3khO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micahhhh @benfrey12 @vols80419 @ldyvolsftbalfan @MMercer21 Struggling keeping the ball in the park still]]></document><document><![CDATA[til 6! (@ The Water Tower in Brooklyn, NY) https://t.co/sqZWbzuxYS https://t.co/fF5p92cG9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @MELOD1P @SPIRE_Institute @thegrindsession @ZO2_ @LonzoWire @LiAngeloBall @Lavarbigballer EVER!!????? https://t.co/hvTkTdoXKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princess_snide 😂😂😂😂 thanks. This has been fun (for me anyway). https://t.co/xDTjNxEdo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcLachlan60 @Victory_shriek Pretty sure it been done.  Without calling each other names.  #AgTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty pumped to be watching the @TheAcademy Nominated Short Subject Documentaries for the first time! With these,… https://t.co/MHg6sN5Vqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tim_Pnin Definitely a gamble. Especially for DET b/c those first couple 1sts could be good ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgiveness is always 100% a great answer for a type of situation that happens, relationships in particular.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalochRzaa @Coryphaeus11 At least one of his followers is a wonderful ex-Muslim with young children who desperatel… https://t.co/TdgvR96rh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex O' Connell is on 🔥🔥 🔥!!! #DukevsCuse #Duke #DukeNation #ACCMBB #ESPN #ncaabasketball @espn @si_ncaabb… https://t.co/YvUvKgDE7n]]></document></documents></author>