<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Come support you favorite ag professors in their last regular season intramural soccer game tonight at 9:25 at the… https://t.co/02sLgxT95E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #High5Conf Day 1! If you see any of our volunteers, please say hi + thank them. They’re the ❤️ of this event… https://t.co/sQRx7vLo98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodtomicha @__yonce I know I read Reddit and Reality Steve 😂😢 but they still made her look horrible at the beginn… https://t.co/CUoPCGVN8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vinyasa yoga gives a great sweat in &amp; I can be vulnerable on my mat with no judgment &amp; no one hounding me… https://t.co/DC0GbRxjPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to The Bank the last couple of years just hasn’t seemed right... empty seats and a lack of interest is not Ph… https://t.co/7EBoHl8KWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeannieruesch @JoelLacayo @stefredmond @advisorfi https://t.co/OxmlWapduM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDePace So your homework Scottie. 80% of Americans got a negligible tax break but are encumbered at tax time becau… https://t.co/5j37v3waBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[bradley cooper, lady gaga, sam elliot, and a star is born deserved every award they were nominated for. and that’s tea]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s Lovett or Leave it is reminding me of the only thing I miss reading in Runner’s World. That is @petersagal column.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digit, the baby sperm whale, is finally saved after being entangled in trash for 3 long years https://t.co/NREFMPy2HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just reliving the best day of my life. 🙂 @richbrian https://t.co/GdYHlAEreq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ever go to @tacobell in La Habra on imperial. You will wait 30 minutes in the drive through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camden Yards is a great ballpark with rich history but all i have to say is if the sox or the yanks were as bad as… https://t.co/35chpgYI1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these tweets about #FatTuesday and #MardiGras (did you see @OmarJimenezCNN looking super festive??) has me crav… https://t.co/LmbPJWL9fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero conocer personas nuevas, personas que les guste la fiesta, pasar buenos momentos y tener muchos recuerdos 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[my motivation to do schoolwork really went downhill once we stopped taking AR reading tests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my happy place tonight. Thank you altitudesbarandgrill  for satiating my craving for walleye fish fry... pe… https://t.co/YjmqWJCX70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PotatoWolfy 🆘️🆘️🆘️Emaciated senior in desperate need of a hero, stat vet care; vomits after eating! Only 1 pledge!… https://t.co/PiEWpU7EmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5: I was tagged by @CaitlynSaxton to post one of my favorite books for the next 7 days, adding a friend each da… https://t.co/LgYzo3QMt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[this time in two weeks i will be done competing and that’s hard to believe but i’m so thankful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigthink The Existence of Almighty God Jehovah is not an assumption concocted by our brain. God is a Spirit. If yo… https://t.co/v2pwcx0fUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was truly a beautiful movie. I’m not going to try to put it to words but I am deeply moved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am editing 4 paragraphs about tornadoes with my 9 year old. You would SWEAR it’s the end of the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYinLA2121 @MiaMiaCuIpa @TheRickWilson @tonyposnanski @ManInTheHoody @MollyJongFast @Kris_Sacrebleu News @ramcnn B… https://t.co/8nnFxLDue6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second interview from the new @TotalAccessPass segment “YouTube’s next big things” is coming tomorrow!!  🎤🦋💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rohangrey @aldatweets @ThomasMHanna Re-iterating also @aldatweets’s point that we also want more than just 1 centr… https://t.co/QgciSffcM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman Oh amen sister.. they can suck the life right out of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody: junior high me: 𝔰𝔬𝔪𝔢𝔱𝔦𝔪𝔢𝔰 𝔱𝔥𝔢 𝔭𝔢𝔯𝔰𝔬𝔫 𝔱𝔥𝔞𝔱 𝔶𝔬𝔲’𝔡 𝔱𝔞𝔨𝔢 𝔞 𝔟𝔲𝔩𝔩𝔢𝔱 𝔣𝔬𝔯 𝔦𝔰 𝔱𝔥𝔢 𝔬𝔫𝔢 𝔟𝔢𝔥𝔦𝔫𝔡 𝔱𝔥𝔢 𝔱𝔯𝔦𝔤𝔤𝔢𝔯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentullery @CentervilleCF To new to compete with you all, but I was there at 5am this morning putting in work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We really do not have anyone that we need to impress besides God (and He already knows everything about us)! Be you… https://t.co/PX69rcdhbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink isn’t just a color, it’s an attitude...👑🎀 #thursdayswewearpink #LAlife #pink #workhustle #trafficselfie… https://t.co/SvDhL2AoTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senzasabere2 @NutricionTotal @VPITV @jguaido @carlosvecchio @AsambleaVE @dsmolansky @MariaCorinaYA @marcorubio… https://t.co/y22XY7U5qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee, garlic powder, potato stix. (@ Ollie's Bargain Outlet in Horsham, PA) https://t.co/1IyevOus4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@costareports Don't a large portion of his base have an accent similar to Jeff Sessions?! (Asked by someone from South Carolina)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey husband it's weird to call you that #married #CanizalYES @ Oasis Texas Brewing Company https://t.co/oGqgi7rdp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom Jeans hinting that LP3 is going to be like Foo Fighters literally made me nut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alert! @bradschmity voluntarily ate a fruit today &amp; is about to read the second book I've ever known him to read. #sendhelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivoniaDistrict promotes the belief that everyone deserves a literacy coach, driving their work as coaches using t… https://t.co/YZfQ78trNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[let me give y’all an overload of cuteness real quick - meet woodrow💕 https://t.co/49XjVfVIAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what I found!  People on the web are searching frantically for Orujo de hierbas, and it’s frightfully hard to… https://t.co/sLc6PeDUsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing I truly want for myself (besides a continued successful career in dance)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple pleasures. #friyay #dessert #simplepleasures #yummy #michelelauforqvc @ West Goshen, Pennsylvania https://t.co/02Wxmb07q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do u mixup an order between 2 people w/the same 1st name, but drastically different last names when 1 person wr… https://t.co/tBLyyYyqDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I slept 12 hours last night &amp; got to start my day @ 7am fully rested. Why’d it take me 23 years to learn this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john30139910 Your as full of it as a Christmas turkey!!! If you can't distinguish this in her statement then you n… https://t.co/Nyj0VrxKkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE @Diamond_Ashes I hate waking up getting on twitter crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flyersgrl28 @BeardedJawn  I'll be at the game against Edmonton tonight...IDK, if Simmons will be playing. I'll kee… https://t.co/bgYItTLj6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@durnkposts @_diana_7 @JoannaOrtiz22 @VereEspinoza @plancartejenn @jmndt00]]></document><document><![CDATA[“All you need is love. But a little chocolate now and then doesn’t hurt.” -Charles M. Schulz Happy Valentine’s Day.… https://t.co/qm0aXjusaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does PhilipineGovt hold a MISCREANT-JUVENILE 4 act WTH NO HARM RESULTNG; REVOKE BAIL! she's held wthout RECOURS… https://t.co/GYdHgJbCZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home of the Mustangs Studios proudly presents @SocorroISD @HDHilley_ES @bbalde_HDHES @tlopez_HDHES @AOropeza_HDHES https://t.co/OkPrnn3f8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pshore73 @SQLGene @sqllocks Thanks! If you look closely at the necklace, the heart is on my home in Columbus. Gott… https://t.co/nH3uEfbLff]]></document><document><![CDATA[AI is like medicine. It can be life changing for those that need it, but everyone else should know better -… https://t.co/x7C8qaKda5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my eos chapstick at work and I hope no one finds it and throws away 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliant week heading home soon. ✈️🍎🇺🇸⛷🗽🎿😊💯👌🏼 #skiing #Vermont #NewYork #Manhattan @ Mt. Killington K1 Peak https://t.co/LD3ezLvuND]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little vampire taught me not to judge people by appearance or what someone says about them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrellnkheatac Ex mother-in-law and no, nothing is colder than that horrible woman’s heart 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neverturntupris i mean yeah, i've got an inflated ego rn but i literally can't fall asleep bc my brain is racing w… https://t.co/WV4NxbQ9GJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreamed about political science. My lest favorite science, but it is now the most popular science known to man. To… https://t.co/xwqrAbuSWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go to school full time and work three jobs and still don’t make 20K shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Justin!!!!! Pot, Kettle, Black, Liar, thief.   https://t.co/1qIPl5BTiI  @MarkFriesen08 @Politics__Right… https://t.co/mYFmFbY69W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @TomColeOK04 Had no time as he was to busy kissing DT’s ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this while out walking the dogs right now and I’m reminded today’s the second anniversary of the newspapers clo… https://t.co/CPtWLa08KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my phone for being the only bitch around here who knows what time it is. God bless 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Super70sSports I had an Afro like the guy on the left. When I was in high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting with members of the Government Street Collaborative to discuss plans for the Broad Street improvement proje… https://t.co/4r4IkFSHdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande I love you @ArianaGrande ... this one’s for you! https://t.co/yejmzyIcGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So like when will the trend of people taking pics of their legs in the tub with bath bombs die]]></document><document><![CDATA[People of #LosAngeles - big question here: do I go to the @LACMA or @MOCAlosangeles?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me still trying to find out what happened two nights ago https://t.co/6oZSIre1ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arapaho415 @loonyberg @Veriphide @Stephaniefishm4 @dwinfrey72 @RighteousBabe4 @MountainsStars @MingGao26 @Ex67T20… https://t.co/N13ncdjB7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sitting here waiting for Spring...pretending there isn’t 3ft of snow under me...and pretending I’m not freezin… https://t.co/Jfa2bM3hpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @iTunesTV I am now the proudest owner of my favorite movie EVER, #fromjustintokelly.  - @kelly_clarkson… https://t.co/3ZpWLR1cjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[my childhood dreams just came true  @aaroncarter https://t.co/NaZLzyf0ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barely Lethal Even though there were some serious cringe moments, my god it was adorable and I loved seeing Samuel… https://t.co/f1fmxejDRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a new face wash pls give me suggestions!! I have a combination of oily and dry skin. Really just depends on… https://t.co/PUYDYvhArq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday March 3rd The moon is 9% waning in the sign of Aquarius. Today is a day to cleanse away the past especially… https://t.co/DiLCKw3FeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need Khloe to never step foot into a NBA arena again and to go find herself a nice, faithful accountant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What sunshine is to flowers, smiles are to humanity.” ~Joseph Addison A smile only takes a second to change the li… https://t.co/hPkaQGuoWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanBelote No in my opinion any job is a real job if you work hard at what you do. Even like a self made busines… https://t.co/jkx3uQZNRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[miguelfloresphotography  #Peace #mua #photoshoot #love #believe #photooftheday #fashion #happy #instagood #followme… https://t.co/1wOsJ0bK6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHeatherEm @TheRyanSupreme Thanks for the info!!!!  I did not know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virgin Atlantic's flight crews always strive to be professional and presentable, but,  it's good to know their job… https://t.co/PDNO8fAZ23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilove4paws @ajsweetsoap Orange are my favorite, too!!! Thanks for reminding me to go look for my favorite cartoon… https://t.co/SvVac6rXuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalasAndie Because he doesn’t really love you. He loves the idea of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoRautins boy is 4 weeks old today!  #leonbergerpuppy #newpuppy #cooper https://t.co/KcCgcrjrqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long Game: Inside the Carnegie Corporation’s Quest to Improve Science Education. Good read! @SchwabNichole… https://t.co/2m5ai4dk5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah @IDF by  the way she is still a threat @tv7israelnews @CherokeeNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maurice’s is my fav store . Got a card for it and yeah ... badddd bad habits]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all pull up to this dope event tomorrow  It’s only $5 through this link 😱😱😱😱  https://t.co/UPAQkBLd0Z https://t.co/SQqeNMNkwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are finally beginning to watch Season 2 of @startrekcbs YAAASSS!!!11 https://t.co/gdLeNdUwpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving can be sooo stressful, but something about new beginnings makes me feel so good! 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[please show me the trend lines of goodwill donations before and after marie kondo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in love with you💫 @ Snoqualmie Pass, Washington https://t.co/kcl0YaR4ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews @JackPosobiec @PerdieXAmerica Her answer would have to be “NO”. Islam is anti Jew. Period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nofilter #photobytgb @ Pikes Place Market, Seattle, Wa https://t.co/8LcSJqjxjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you find yourself beguiled By the dangerous and wild? Do you feed on the need For the beauty underneath? Have yo… https://t.co/Z4rR4HRifd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowrysnow @utahsenate @annmillner @ywcautah Saw that - yay!! Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh if u ever see me with red spots on my chest or hands it means im mad dont get around me i will ATTACC FUCKVJFI… https://t.co/u2gSbveyX9]]></document></documents></author>