<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Buenos días. en ISAIAS (43:10)&gt;SOMOS TESTIGOS DE JEHOVA. https://t.co/tXwLVACoOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime..  @GreenBoysBball 47. @revereminutemen 25. https://t.co/4cHmLm12dU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chantoeknee Hmmm but what about the concept of a woman accepting a drink from another man knowing she’s taken? Mos… https://t.co/oBtrCfKF9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linxlunx Ada timbangannya nggak? Kalau di sini lumayan, ada timbangannya juga. Jd kalau terlalu berat bisa diakali… https://t.co/lMYRCGbT6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Kevin Kratz for taking a few minutes to chat with ATLs younger fans today. @ Metro North Soccer Park https://t.co/1yQx05v8AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be the only way I will go to Disneyland. Goofy Movie is underrated af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyKXXV hi pretty lady.  Looking good this morning.  Nice change to see you this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...the type of March day that tests your resolve and reminds you, as Michiganders, you’re made of tougher stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[after 2 weeks of balling at the gym i feel like im getting back to my best form]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoBS #Facts but never had a black eye... anyone want to hit me lol #KingJoeCross wants to be punched lol @ Joe Cro… https://t.co/S2ETZVnzCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabois What if it’s the equivalents of FB, Google or Amazon in a narrower, more particular domain?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramsey2234 40% of their games are against joke teams. Dolphins bills jets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very disappointed im at @SenWarren town hall and they hid the question cards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digby56 They’ll be the second (right after  Crybaby in Chief) to howl if it’s embarrassing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say something super cool.  Like late 80s early 90s Action Hollywood films.   If you kill me,  I swear to Christ I w… https://t.co/mDN7Vj8GLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamesFranko @ChampionUSA Dads have single handedly supported their business for years and now they're just neglect… https://t.co/IwcmW8VpMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leones Negros. Presenta su programa ante autoridades de la Universidad de Guadalajara. #BlackPower… https://t.co/TFagc1Tvw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jon the bone Jones @jonnybones you’re a hell of a fighter ... Such a pleasure watching you fight. What a mind blowi… https://t.co/QCBB84ex90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @Elaine_Greek @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/l6e7F5x0lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could not be more impressed with the product my wife @maddy_karolian built! You can pick the exact colors and sizes… https://t.co/Bd3DWTOdvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TannerFranklin Please direct your disappointment to your tastebuds. ✌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It was a grind, but I kept the course in front of me.   “It’s always gonna be stressful, man. What we do is stress… https://t.co/uIMcDjs5Ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masnSteve Happy Bday Steve!  You Did a great job for 7 innings today!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottGrimes I’d say @jasonsegel for me! I’m pretty Marshall Eriksen - esc. hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Categorizing Building Certification Systems According to the Definition of Sustainable Building https://t.co/YAFPemjvto via @IOPscience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC nope...they need to eliminate the motion to recommit...and why does your article not mention that most of th… https://t.co/EoNi3BakJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember niggas told me Jordan wasn’t getting blocked after Bron got blocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@umbernhard @crinpa @jennycohn1 @ElectionBabe @philipbstark And this nonsense: https://t.co/xu0i5x1FC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know not everyone will be satisfied: either it shouldn’t be a breach or if it was she should be penalized. I thin… https://t.co/HdkYJh7PeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barsinthewomb @CaitGates2Hell I agree. I don't like the new look of tobs. To mainstream and weak. https://t.co/e6BQqqZCYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DaleJr I know you like these abandoned race track videos......enjoy!!  https://t.co/O1m5eGdwHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not sign bill POTUS!!!! These congressmen do not have the right to stop American people from being protected! Th… https://t.co/glw7ql4Djq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnMalleyBooks @vernsanders @sabinmarketing @lennar_my @RedworldToys @thewriterme @EdwardCalame @joseph_akinbo… https://t.co/AmNLKUvpsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life asked The Warrior “who has more heart than you?” The Warrior replied “No One”.  “Prove it” said Life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prak @wykingjones @CalMBBall @CalAthletics Nothing changed but the weather. What’s up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to inclement weather, Cathedral High School will be on a 2-hour weather delay Wednesday, February 20, 2019.  Cl… https://t.co/x5U1frt8In]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook Live too. See you then!  #countrymusic #country #countryband #singersongwriter #indie #indiemusic… https://t.co/JYnvqoXD7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coolhtowngirl1 @SethAndrewsTTA My ex named the dog Charlie. I gave him his full name: Charles Nelson Faber https://t.co/KbU3Su83ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am i the only one who gets REALLY bad anxiety when the only response you get is “I’m praying for you” or “pray abou… https://t.co/cXiJ9G5EJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 20 - The Point:   The Mueller report has been cast as the panacea for what ails the country. It… https://t.co/NTf4SxkCwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...#MotherNture is so awesome. I love this gathering of #deer at the lake...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thankful for every situation that God has put me in the situations I’ve been in to show me that I’m worth more than I thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wtf? Register any way she wants. And report the teacher to your local voting commissioners and the school district.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortunately for us, we have an abundance of she-roes in the #healthcare profession. Thank you for leading the way!… https://t.co/G1JVUXwy3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way to soften this potential loss is if Drake goes to the sweet 16 in the dance... https://t.co/7xeUetiLlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeamusGirbaud @MutCallahan Do as I and many other, ole time @WEEI listeners do all the time,,, don't listen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely support these players. No room for this hatred in our society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul , you are a traitor to this nation and the Constitution.  You have always been a space cadet but now it is beyond the pale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiffanyWatsonX @TheSapphireLV I wish I was there Tiffany stuck work again 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArkayEvans @TheRyanAdams Especially once the FBI investigation gets underway...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Through all of life’s storms, you keep me grounded. Can’t wait until our next adventure 🌎 @ Nassau Bahamas https://t.co/A8wBAVzX27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @GovIvey That's because corrupt liberal politicians in Puerto Rico have hijacked the aid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CongMikeSimpson Stand Up for the Rule of Law. You’re loyal to a criminal. Be loyal to Idaho and America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of 4 in the books! Big bats for the Texans. 6 run 4th inning, Nice 2 run Home Run @drew_woodcox  Lamar Texans 9… https://t.co/kUmLDzSswX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaireBLang Thanks for having me on the show tonight, it was my first time calling in, excited to call again in the future!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si dio.. genero más cantidad de volumen en el campo rival.. quien dominó? Ahora tú quieres ganar siempre? Eso no ex… https://t.co/3yIGzL2C7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[KION: ICE accused of using DMV data to target undocumented immigrants: Supervisor Luis Alejo taking action @KION546  https://t.co/YT4a6pGMRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GezBuckley We do a monthly fly meetup here in Atlanta mate.  This was yesterday.  Come join us next month! https://t.co/9lveUOou0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[They won't respond to any of my multiple private messages!! What does that say??? https://t.co/vzkKGVHDoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders You mean voter ID which would prevent illegals and dead people from voting?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlliniWGym @meeks_kasey @maryjaneotto15 @shaylahscott Congratulations Illini Ladies !!❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's all said and done, they gon' wanna come. One of those days where I had to put my phone down and let my… https://t.co/hpzGsygiZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris One of the wealthiest countries in which the richest 1% have more money than everyone else. The trick… https://t.co/DaXDrSbX7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz Sign me up for a “Talos and his science guy” spinoff movie YESTERDAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValeriePrimros4 You're very very welcome and we'll be praying for your ministry as well👍😀🙏🙇🎶📖⏫☝]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Men play the Biggest Game of The Regular Season Saturday evening as it’s for The Regular Season Championship. W… https://t.co/AGIu8nkV2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay @CNN @staceyabrams Bernie's socalism will never be accepted,   Americans are still too independent to accept a bridle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK Google, where are you keeping the dogs and why can't I get them to come out of my phone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Florida Aquarium in Channelside! @ Florida Aquarium Caricature Stand https://t.co/USiFobDqHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have confirmed the honorees for upcoming Sixth Annual Gala get your tickets and join us on March 14th as we cele… https://t.co/mZS1p5k2K4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders comes with more baggage than Thurston and Lovey Howell took on the S.S. Minnow. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo How can a judge play this game ? This is worse than the Geman court rooms in the 30s .]]></document><document><![CDATA[PG-13 last 4 games played   5-16 FG  7-23 FG  8-25 FG  7-24 FG  Twitter new favorite. But we only speak on , Durant… https://t.co/MfYknUBz0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demi is going to replace Sarah Huckabee Sanders and our nation will be better off for it. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cityoftoronto Please update @waze as I depend upon it to get me around!  Thanks so much cc @311Toronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiltonHotels @HiltonHonors How much water is wasted daily when you tell all rooms to “let the water run for 20 min… https://t.co/GG3i15c4Kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sigue con tus movidas Reyna, pero no me pidas que me pase la vida pagándote fianzas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally makes me feel like a valued job candidate. #sarcasm   “If you have not been contacted within 28 working day… https://t.co/pw6JOe2i81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: Has the ‘good guy’ ever needed a ‘fixer’?  I don’t have a fixer! Do you have a fixer? I have a guy who fi… https://t.co/njCBVifMz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must watch this video &amp; agree totally with Democrat spokeswoman She knows better than you  !https://t.co/5efM5lGch6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom called me crying.... Zs tumor shrunk 52% in her stomach but unfortunately tumors popped up on her spine and pel… https://t.co/uedGB5PJ2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dlstoke I am beside myself about this on a daily basis. What about 15 years from now? What will we tell them when… https://t.co/bdlXm1ifFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MediaNarodoweMN I nic jej nie zrobia. Ona juz sie smieje z tego pozwu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlHeastie Apparently, you've been told by your real estate contributors that reform must die. You are the obstac… https://t.co/0qnFIAtjYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Skonie Skoop   Lion Killed Intern at Zoo When Gate Was Blocked: Witness https://t.co/u5zIowLo0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to my beautiful friend Jessica Errett for inviting me up to sing a few and molest her trusty Martin guitar!… https://t.co/v8oeINBNZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear, if you need a little mental lift, you’d benefit from following this fine humanbean! (You’ll also get expos… https://t.co/v6sMwgMpN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS Serranos military communications at Tinker Air Force Base on duty eat all military radio broadcast transcrip… https://t.co/kEwCMCRB3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t agree more he is one of the biggest reasons I stopped watching fox besides their as bad as cnn anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @alex_howes you’re prolly asleep. Big race I hear. Have fun tomorrow. Will be going nuts for Sep and the whole… https://t.co/N75RPXCFT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Egad_Games @thegamecrafter Happy to chat with you on my show when you're closer to launch!  https://t.co/ie1hfn4kBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did my mom aunt lil cousin and lady's eyebrows this week ya boy mastering his craft . Blessed Hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump signing bibles in Ala. because he’s a role model for all criminals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch Can’t be her, this person is actually standing up straight. RBG hasn’t seen anything but her feet wh… https://t.co/uzJIkRTZEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Top 10 Moment: Having my God Kids come and see me Preach/Perform for their first time! I was asked by a Pastor… https://t.co/XdRDXbfF4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Test not Guess Homer Glen man thankful for heart screening at Silver Cross https://t.co/LumLyTBPi3 via @Joliet_HN @FatEmperor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember exactly where i was when this happened .. this shit was epic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwlucas @MountSinaiCoLab Yes, coming to east coast soon! Will keep you in the loop for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a person wants you, they show you and shouldn’t downgrade you in front of others. If love is genuine, it’s gen… https://t.co/Jme8IPZd5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[at this exact time in a week, i will be living my best life w one of my best friends in new orleans and i am litera… https://t.co/v6NHOLQge7]]></document></documents></author>