<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hebrews 11:6  020/365 Wow I’m behind, guess today’s gonna be catch up day. https://t.co/GWsrqUklFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[me &amp; my nonexistent boyfriend running out of school be like: https://t.co/04DjvCJcpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiscountTire @Team_Penske @joeylogano @shellracingus @Pennzoil @NASCARONFOX @NASCAR @DISupdates @FordPerformance 💜🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worry about people who receive mental health disability payments. Most of the time people want to show the world… https://t.co/YWMChndJri]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at life from a different point of view⠀ 🌬🌊⠀ *l I n k I n b I o* 🔊⠀ .⠀ .⠀ .⠀ #sf4l #anxietymusic… https://t.co/fNUmNDoEa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hersheda @tressiemcphd I didn’t actually do it on purpose. It just happens. It’s kinda weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[yeeeep so in 2k19 we’re boppin to @VHSNYC it’s decided. thanks for stopping by hogtown :) https://t.co/fnnJVRqZNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I have to say is @khloekardashian got dumb b*tch written on her forehead. God bless honey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@africamiranda Can’t remember the last time I had my mama’s croquettes. And what a blessing to still be able to sit with your grandmother!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews This should never be allowed.  Men (trans) still have larger lung capacity and heart. Meds don't take that away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We begin #SundayBunday, as always, with a photo of the sexy @TeganZayne 💜💜 https://t.co/jCE3vcKlAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one: Student who owns 172 colored gel pens to write their class notes: https://t.co/PYDUQgD4fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @VP @FoxNews @JohnCornyn @SenTedCruz @senatemajldr @GOPLeader Trump: "I don't care. I believe Puti… https://t.co/XmoYkXY1Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve traveled internationally as an adult only 2 times and I fully agree with packing carry on ONLY. I did it visit… https://t.co/idDboY2xTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And at Shae’s for Sunday night karaoke and a dude legit sings Tequila 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Al_jazeeravt @JovemPanNews @veramagalhaes Cara, eu já não sei se essa Vera é só canalha ou é burra também.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these pretty, dainty earrings. They come in three colors and are so perfect for spring!… https://t.co/DJVEQBuUCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Statistar30 @Noodoggy I love how all they’ve got in terms of a response is shit like “grow up”. You can’t argue wi… https://t.co/dMnN9UwHTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final day of radiation treatments today! Praise God he is still feeling strong and positive. #tothemoon #ilovemydad… https://t.co/CeJYEGs7sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinkerKS @TonyStewart @VHeilbrunner Is this his next girlfriend after he got rid of Penny?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Nocturnal Black Lager by Wallenpaupack Brewing Company @ Wallenpaupack Brewing Company — https://t.co/wuXFSpzklJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way they are planning to visit where oh yeah Palestine @tv7israelnews @CherokeeNation make the connection… https://t.co/cnHo9B3V8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Individual1 #BenedictDonald @realdonaldtrump #caved to sign border deal averting shutdown, declare emergency in pu… https://t.co/VHjQItH1YD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xXSips_OfHerXx Lmaoooo accurate. Like who does this 🤣🤣 but we’d be no where without Mama Jamie 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how I USE to Love the Oscars!  When it was all about the talent, the dresses, the hair, the couples, the winners… https://t.co/PYePIxNz0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly i hate valentine’s day. i spoil my fiancé all the time. i don’t need a day to define how much i love her.… https://t.co/4PsqjZgS85]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all Nathan Fillion fans happy Wednesday I wish you all a beautiful start to your day stay safe https://t.co/EW3LStK9pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing the happiest birthday to the bar I call home: @rhinehausotr, congratulations on six great years! Looking fo… https://t.co/C5GYaPlNMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are my professors trying it today? it’s too early and i just want to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up to find a rose, a chocolate bar, and a freshly shoveled driveway. I am truly pampered 😍😍 @DonJewxote]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO ACCURATE 😂 my first concussion was getting body slammed into the water by both my brothers when my dad would fli… https://t.co/SFeCOW1cp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @JoeNBC They helped launch his run. He called in almost daily and they acted like, two 13 year olds with a 'boy band' crush 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildest_rose_ @the_ben_woolley let's saddle up https://t.co/pQzuPQVEgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[At an EMPTY Bistro Bistro on a Saturday night. An infomercial is on the two TVs at the bar. Me: oh hey, can you put… https://t.co/63v3c9JbMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton really messed up sending two great girls home who wanted to get married at the end of this #TheBatchelor #BachelorFinale]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is an interesting read. I had forgotten about it.  Wonder if our Provincial Government has read it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Accountemps? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and inform… https://t.co/VrCMlAEaw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCEsq I’d love to come to New Haven!! Can you tag a few venues that you think would be a good fit?! 💜🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh stop it U lie because the fact you want awar in space or the heavens the fact climatechange isn't in ero hands i… https://t.co/gxzqA5NHYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Scorches Mueller: ‘They’re Trying To Take You Out With Bulls***!” https://t.co/3C4gDH83fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this  on @FLPD411 twitter, #K9Dobies is                      “Paw-some”🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my airpods in my car and I’m bored af waiting for my oil change 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How in the world do y’all eat Cadbury Creme Eggs? Just the thoughts of them make me wanna puke. 🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOCK 🔒MCCABE🔒 UP‼️ #maga #WinningintheWH @POTUS @realDonaldTrump ❤️🇺🇸❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanGerhart @katya_zamo Oooh...podcast. Must learn to navigate them 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout lytle bishop took the lead 46-39 let’s go Pirates @lytleisd @The_Leader_News]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sapw @ElenneMigo @yellowbelle @DestiniLozano @Lanasanette @marykk196051 @LucyGee4 @AngelsCumber @Benedict_Fan_… https://t.co/rvajXGMYdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still THOUSANDS of #ChildrenInCages. @realDonaldTrump @VP @SecNielsen @DHSgov responsible. #AmericasShame]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ladies celebrating ladies.” Happy Galentines Day to my fave gal pals!💞thanks Leslie Knope for creating this iconic… https://t.co/H7yDkOrphR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hulu needs to better tailor their ads to their users. I don’t need to watch a commercial about heart failure medici… https://t.co/0ujKqZ4zTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pouring through #LdnEnt trivia with the help of @HeritageCouncil and @LondonFuse #PourOverLdn https://t.co/70jZ8SFwJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnoutPAC He might have to unseal all his records for review if he was ever nominated. Don’t see that happening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never working 5 12’s in a row again while pregnant. Bc after all this I just want to go home and chug beers and that’s frowned upon 😩😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm participating in the #GoHabsGo Challenge. Are you? https://t.co/GqFV4wmaZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarrahRochon People need to close their eyes,  scroll past, and shut up if they dislike something. Especially on s… https://t.co/Ctv24AE3vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sloop Forever Rotating IPA on tap now. https://t.co/yRcZ9Bh5b7 @sloopbrewing #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you feel like garbage and your kid wont stop hitting you and screeching :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 During the Civil rights movement of the early 60's &amp; during the War in Vietnam:(☮🌸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for showing us around your home! We had so much fun!! Love you @allyhaar20 ❤️❤️ @ Niagara Falls, Ontario https://t.co/VaSA0UGSwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like hearing the rain and watching clouds rolling in when I’m warm and cozy indoors on the weekend... . . .… https://t.co/psX8tdMMLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[He shot at Pasco police 7 times. A jury will decide if it's attempted murder #ReadLocal https://t.co/dVkJEDUhpY https://t.co/uLv8VDUAG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Finishing that 5k, was the hardest thing I have ever had to do. I ate more fettuccine alfredo and drank less water… https://t.co/O3BjoIi4aG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEvers13 @thebukuproject @RepublicNOLA I have to work in Baton Rouge all weekend! Wish i was though, have fun for me ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost tayloredtrichomes  ・・・ 1 acre of Hemp grown over 4 months can produce as much paper as 4-10 acres of trees… https://t.co/Y61FgRTV0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you’re in the party and start to get in your feelings but suddenly remember who you are: https://t.co/MmfWHFXXBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shoes #shoequotes #louboutin #christianlouboutin @ Boca Raton, Florida https://t.co/DAPgo6rRUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brycetache I am ready!!! This is the national emergency.#ImpeachTrump #FakePresident #FAKENationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been on the phone for over 30 min which should have only taken a few seconds. Seriously?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On sale for your special Valentine.. hurry, only 2 left! @ Studio PMR https://t.co/JzVHDym3oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweatsntopknots You must live in Texas - bipolar weather = 70+ degrees and ☀️ today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeandersonsr I do feel the rich could do more. But I’d not take it from them. I also feel everyone could do more… https://t.co/XbeO01wJ20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EPBAuthor Eric.....Eric.......Eric. This is easy to fix. You can be the boy One. And I will be the girl One. (...a… https://t.co/DrtdsgxNTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANYWAY currently headed into an interview for a job i reallyyyyyy want so send me some good vibes pleaseeee!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a lot of strange things last weekend, but the weirdest was probably agreeing to sign up for a dance class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How come his wife gets off Scott free for bank fraud!!!!  No consequences that’s why they keep on doing what they do!!!!’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life hack: if you get pregnant and break USA law you don’t pay the consequences 🤯  At least that’s according to dem… https://t.co/ZLStCRoWdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am super excited i got my tickets in the mail yesterday sept 6th just can not come fast enough so excited about g… https://t.co/yeFXz1Zlz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattwilhelm22 Lolol yess. Now that it’s recreational there’s usually a line and of course it’s taxed. Also kinda f… https://t.co/zzkNzUPKPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sparked idea on how 2nd grade works on Community projects -  #wakelet collections to showcase their target com… https://t.co/akgTfzM0F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved her on Who’s the Boss and extend my condolences to the family, friends and cast during this time in your li… https://t.co/Nu8N3W4IF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not how I want the world to see us!! But they do now.  In 2 short years he has made us the laughingstock]]></document><document><![CDATA[6-week challenge is over. i know this is not the point, but bacon egg and cheese and bbq sandwich on a brioche and… https://t.co/ZQZuxdGrmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will 2019 be the year you stop throwing social content spaghetti at the virtual wall!?   Get your content zoomin mo… https://t.co/fnhkOs0htY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exclusive @HomeDepot Lifeproof carpet with PetProof technology at Westminster Dog Show! Let’s go D23!! @LAPortelli… https://t.co/iDldJPxszh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is being an orchestral percussionist like being an outfielder? Boredom ---- and suddenly you're on run run run run catch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennisbasso #nyfw2019 @dennisbasso taking his triumphant walk with beautiful @modelcarolalt 💋💥👏💋💖 @ Cipriani 42 St https://t.co/8B5GZyHXnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoKhanna Thank you for your questions today, you laid it out with plain language. This non nonsense approach and c… https://t.co/R6eBgDYguW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fedupcitizen16 @HLAurora63 @maziehirono Not for Hawaii anyway so shut your trap woman!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milling about before the judges’ meeting, MD/DC NATS @ Carl J. Murphy Fine Arts Center https://t.co/8Izr7Oice2]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s no denying they are all stars in their own right.  “We become the character of heads of state and other est… https://t.co/YltDQVRqYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilentKW1 @MoSalah @LFC @LFCUSA @LivEchoLFC @JamesPearceEcho @_lfcleanne @MelissaReddy_ @BBCSport So realistic  You are so talented  ⚽️♥️⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld It’s wrong no matter how you look at it, Pope Francis‼️😡😡🖤🖤 You best do something about this sick mess wi… https://t.co/5FFLQYnx34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watching Killing Eve and, while it’s watchable, I’m not understanding why everyone is raving about it. I wa… https://t.co/bbR6crofao]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York tech/tech policy folks— I’ll be in town next week. Want to meet? Email/dm me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackLubner My new response when irritated: Mazeltov and a hearty shkoyach. ✌🏻👍🏼🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey people it has recently become my goal to tarnish voltron completely. And I’ll degrade any point of it possible.… https://t.co/2gdYZochxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Please haven’t you and father learned you keep peddling this BS and they just find more illegal act… https://t.co/hh8fdGMsAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCarterAuthor @GrandJersey @BritishVogue Oooh, I love those #spadays Have a recommendation in #Melbourne #australia ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosieperezbklyn will you be joining us this year in Canasota for the International Boxing Hall of Fame Inductions?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Valentine’s Day I got half a blunt and 3 pieces of chocolate cause the dude ate the rest... 💀 this valentines… https://t.co/PCj8YfrFIW]]></document></documents></author>