<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cdixon25 Keuchel lol. In all seriousness, I have to give it to German. Would be going into a season where he has h… https://t.co/h4npN1FPMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdriscoll03 @PeterCooper Small detail re: CFL. If the league doesn’t fold first, he wouldn’t be eligible for the C… https://t.co/HWHfLaiwvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hit best friends with @yama1989DD one of top Japanese players and a truest humble guy. Can’t wait till next Japan e… https://t.co/GRrlrpnKnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know, and firearm manufacturers/retailers are successfully helping the real America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How long are you going to milk the “but Hillary...” deflection defense? Nixon abused his power and resigned in disg… https://t.co/hjNPSoJtGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost ig_nycity with get_repost ・・・ presents  I G  O F  T H E  D A Y  P H O T O | @smbnyc  T H E M E | Night shot… https://t.co/ELdsx1ndWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deviled crab?? #deviledcrab #yborcity #florida #advertising #typography #street @ Ybor City Historic District https://t.co/L4gI5UUJfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyOlsonGolf You have a new fan in me.  I hope meet you someday, and thank you for being a role model to all the y… https://t.co/ygTaguwcu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this! #LGM Yahoo Sports announces premium offering for New York Mets fans https://t.co/a7VHc6wMpC via @verizon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agonified @sedaunal Yeah given that my twitterversary is in June I'm not hopeful for a ski trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @AfterHoursCBS Cheer for your team and respect everyone around you. Kids go to games. Something to think about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump how👏the👏 FUCK.. are you taking a cictory lap right now instead of apologizing for being a fat dusty asshole?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Monday !!  .. .. .. #travel #photography #nature #love #instagood #photooftheday #sky #beautiful #art… https://t.co/mcpUVeIau6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memetwalker UNCLE @memetwalker  ISHIT MY PANTS HELP ME AND BEETLEJUICE HE IS THE KING OF ALL WACK PACKERS AND HIGH… https://t.co/OKW6Pue6oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaDrongowski @TheMandyMoore @MaloneJena @HeatherMatarazz So you know Mack's twitter handle is IncredibleCulk]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck i caught up on run with the wind now i have to wait for episodes https://t.co/tPCzuRPUxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly the problem with those defending Ilhan Omar @IlhanMN   https://t.co/akoPRDZxws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savebymiller Carlyle played him with Lindholm for most of the season even though they didn't connect at all. Peopl… https://t.co/bU9B3vdYkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RP_Football_RP You just make a Twitter and suddenly think you’re hot stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Purposeful in Sports Ministry ⁦@S4HMinistry⁩ ⁦@team_jam⁩ ⁦@ShowChristNow⁩ #sportsministry  https://t.co/URXYrjPRL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerbusJames @hugh_bothwell @cxpage @doctorbuttons @LogicalReterg @badibulgator @GodKingNobody @alastairjallen1… https://t.co/6mXekyQeK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I appreciate the new Democrats in Congress because they remind me like the Dems of old that came up With Great… https://t.co/5ugdZZyJFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zeddary Tagging yourself "Author Jack Posobiec" is like tagging yourself "Totally Not Short Jack Psosbiec."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davetheactivist Until he gets revived with the dragon balls and comes back me a new transformation called super sayian demon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankLuntz @gregghenson Jemele, I know you are a lefty and were run off ESPN because you were too political but do… https://t.co/9ko3immAfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYU is opening ANOTHER free med school. How are they doing this who keeps giving us money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another new Boeing 737 max crashes - Ethiopian Airlines plane crash: Live updates https://t.co/tJ7pqrxcDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartEyes4Brady Fine...I’m taking my stuff and leaving... https://t.co/x7VgAslooG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 47.7°F Wind:3.7mph Pressure: 30.121hpa Rising Rapidly Rain Today 0.00in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie  Can be one of the major characters on newer version of dumb and dumber  #realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo much deception going on in The Favourite and all I can think is whoooo fucking cares]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck you @khloekardashian  for still being up tristens ass but being mad at Jordan , fuck you your not about girl p… https://t.co/qKbjQpNaCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephspencer00 @bnw852 @summershamrock @Kieran_IsAGod @BeckyLynchWWE Your exactly right]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @blackmirror episodes are supposed to be cautionary tales about a possible future, but how worried can I be… https://t.co/Bo5RidywHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@porkfriedcoffee I had another pic ready to go without him but decided to do the right thing. 🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyLeilaniJ @_friedchivken @Molly_Gittens Hahahaha yesss the fruit salad rapppppp]]></document><document><![CDATA[paying your girls and her parents pills without having to check your balance &gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quedan tan sólo dos horas para llegar, pero aún así decidí parar por última vez a descansar.  Hoy fueron 1,231 km.… https://t.co/45VO0BwyQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a dollar every time the Mexico Hardee’s caught on fire.  I would have $2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #CardingtonOhio Family Dollar is closed. Not sure if it has anything to do with the news today that… https://t.co/hZQJFX4ONF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSDesMoines @madridiowawx Good morning from the great white North, also now known as Iowa. https://t.co/2yzh5xKkb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m giving up alcohol for lent so I need to make the most out of my last days lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell Nooooooooooooooooooooooooo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of another picture. 🤔😈 #gay #mancrotch #crotch #shortshorts #meninshortshorts #gayinstagram… https://t.co/iHRoc34Fkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Is this the arguement you plan to give at your trial? I’d grab a couple of law books from the library and read… https://t.co/RvTVywVVe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite Oscar-nominated animated shorts (in order):  Late Afternoon One Small Step Weekends Bao  Animal Behaviour  #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabeth_malm This is proof that leftover pizza now serves an important purpose in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo decía mi abuelo, somos más los buenos 🙏 . . . #songwriter #songwriters #singersongwriter #musiccity… https://t.co/TtbvF1LpqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Sophomores Cole Stephenson and Brayden Mikesell on making the Honorable Mention List! @ColeStephenso19 https://t.co/NeEWQwa5Ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realizing all this that I didn’t see in front of me got me answering all my questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKidFromKent @710ESPNSeattle This is freaking AWESOME C-rog! Nice work Dee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_Y_Emerson @myarnell @lukestamps So in some way, via the Chalcedon, the eternal Son is experiencing something the… https://t.co/TnxYtbyvpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsdadohio If she says Chris Collinsworth... https://t.co/dK9mPcHEaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the DOJ allows this to happen where would most of the we the ppl be  I would say jail in equal justice seems to… https://t.co/wISQKzj41V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelbc @drbuendia @melbuendia UF! Dices esa palabra y me pones genuinamente a temblar!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[finished the 1st season of High School DxD ... 4 things I’ve taken away from this #anime  01.  Issei's stupidity is… https://t.co/x2MP3WyCKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Marko grabbed me up and dubbed me in the same thread https://t.co/lcC24GqKmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RectorSun (1) While not a lawmaker, I do purport to back govt transparency. Whether a local City/county council an… https://t.co/zGWsP3VZSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go!!! 🏆🏆  State Champs (x3) ✅ Region 23 Champs (x3) ✅  Next stop: Lubbock, Texas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoDakhil_NBA I'm guessing he thought Jokic would sink for the same reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louisiana weather is bipolar man. I was freezing my tail off in a misty Alex Box Stadium tonight and now it feels like a warm summer night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesgibbon Dear old England of the 12th century, on the banks of the Severn in Shropshire. The adventures of Brot… https://t.co/1bHQIgvBbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ResidentEvilRevelations2 Episodio 3: Juicio (Live) https://t.co/nhSOF3BduH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianbuchanan @dianemgoldstein ...because we all know no one who smokes marijuana to treat depression.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Forbes_Mexico Muy mal... Pésimo de hecho... Decisión dictatorial @nuevoleon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans are literally changing the meaning of words to defend Trump taking sides with America's enemies.… https://t.co/2YLq3OlqOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO if yo homeboy can’t respect your SO, then he is not your homeboy. Simple as that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimonFishbaum And when he holds those rallies or they get on social media, they essentially abdicate their respons… https://t.co/cdstBsyHJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, I feel like, for my own sake I need to look some people in the eye and tell’em “Fuck you” if for no other… https://t.co/DuVbehVx3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanSteinJr Sure, but I still feel like every situation is different. Of course you try always to discourage attacking refs, it’s useless]]></document><document><![CDATA[The are characteristics that we should be striving to instill in our culture that will lead to a community of mindf… https://t.co/JaxXrbDsl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureanomar Claro, García C...no lo ves porque no frecuenta los bares donde te metes....y aún así dudo que lo pudi… https://t.co/Bzpl4NEOmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta love these Kidz and this is a calm day #VOCarsonkidz #youbelonghere #godisuptosomthingbig #room4onemore… https://t.co/scvFU3teJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eploelnia Juasjuasjuas 😝😝.....pues fíjate, me llamo Antonio y me apellido CASTILLO....😍😍😍😍😍😘😘😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[O sea en pocas palabras si se hunde la economía en USA se hunde todo el mundo, pero si cae solo México, los que cae… https://t.co/yyPZFwIbTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahgschwend I have never felt more personally victimized in my entire LIFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyamos22 Google maps/earth street view. I do that often since I get anxiety about parking at places I haven't b… https://t.co/j7Yb7nsFs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy that days are getting longer . . #daylightsavingtimeiscoming #queens #jacksonheights #newyork #newyorkcity… https://t.co/etE5PGdclT]]></document><document><![CDATA[petesprattmuaythai kids with coach ninja.gabe 6-7pm Mon and Wed! @ Rodrigo Pinheiro Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu (RPBJJ) https://t.co/ov3mU2JmW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makemiracles94 @FoxSportsRadio @Chris_Broussard He’s not crying racism.  As usual most of you just don’t get it and never will🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethOnHoops If LSU wins the SEC  regular season Championship and SEC Tournament and be seeded where in NCAA Tourna… https://t.co/gJ1Wd4wzgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[QUE BIEN DEJARON LA IGLESIA DEL PADRE CUCO. en Iglesia del "Padre Cuco" (Las Quintas) https://t.co/hXdNT5VW1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #FacilitiesMgmt jobs like "Custodial Shift Supervisor (HCMS) - SNE"… https://t.co/a6y4ZzSKQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieGray @ChrisCarlin But I do respect that you brought the bigger issue up, I'm thankful my local church has ma… https://t.co/yC3mbeRAcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏🏿 @ Florida's 15th Congressional District https://t.co/Ji1SD3X42H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creep factor at 11 with this house...... never a dull moment when showing empty homes at night.👻😱👻  #walkingdead… https://t.co/QSwIpyqI1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Rigged and corrupt White House is the enemy of the people ! https://t.co/i0XOYpxGV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle 👇🏻 Under Armour CEO Kevin Plank 'was allegedly having an affair with MSNBC host Stephanie Ruhle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elleo20 @alonsomaestre7 @PadreJosePalmar @Carola_Union @JuanPGuanipa ¿Y por ese prurito le entregaron el poder al asesino de Prieto?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win an iPad mini from @RightThisMinute and you can too! Details here: https://t.co/u3Z3g7edfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday To the Homie. Come Home soon My G! 🎉💯 @Kay_Monton https://t.co/11BRrAm2Uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[TY to my friends who are working on these individual bills! Sugary drinks are bad for us, got to nip in the bud at… https://t.co/PxevniJ7eW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffdantzlertv @djohnstonuga I hear you saying that their mascot is the blackbird, but are we sure it isn't her? https://t.co/uponnzrLKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penstillers @ROHPittFan @madchad412 @sikuaka Looks WORSE than half asleep. Especially costing them games that were… https://t.co/yle2UJ0Qa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck that motherfucker. An anti-inflammatory that causes...inflammation over regular use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grown men think their opinion on what another grown man looks like will stop them from getting bitches. Very suspect behavior if you ask me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the @gwNURSING team presenting today at #SigmaCHWE19! https://t.co/pgQHUWuEtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I’ve ever laughed and cried so much watching a tv show. Afterlife is fucking genius. @rickygervais #AfterLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Your faith in yourself should overcome your insecurities” @ SQL Miami https://t.co/Wj1MNS2DQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t “saving the world” start at home? Shouldn’t we all be doing our part? Or nah]]></document></documents></author>