<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I left work with a small chalk handprint on the side of my face and none of my damn co-workers said anything..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Modric is the reigning Ballon d’Or winner   https://t.co/hbLePKUPS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump Tell her to rip Ivanka's children from her, not tell Ivanka where they are, only that they are sep… https://t.co/Ukg9n6sblG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending President’s Day with our beloved national treasure, President Jimmy Carter.   We spent Saturday visiting h… https://t.co/9dTm9Wxe7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe #GreysAnatomy15 is about to break my all time favorite show #ER @JuliannaMargs @JohnStamos… https://t.co/M1yAlPN0XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what tf is happening this week but like, wow I never felt more wanted in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever heard the saying Faith can move Mountains?  God tells us to Be Still. Be Patient. In today's crazy he… https://t.co/WgbWeWuHtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theoriginalbeev @RadioFreeTom @TxHillCountry6 I saw on Twitter yesterday that they're smaller editions for militar… https://t.co/51hViwKLBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[excited I can stay up and watch it since no school tomorrow. How nerdy is that???? #ultimatenerd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me back to this day. • • • • • • I, Kusama, am the modern Alice in Wonderland • • • • • • #ahh #always #art… https://t.co/WjUCj0aPeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OL_America @SkeltonSophie @Outlander_STARZ @RikRankin @caitrionambalfe @SamHeughan @SophieSkeltonUK Happy Birthday @SkeltonSophie 🎂🎉❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BillKristol Note to file: Don't get on Charlie's bad side]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are live this morning at @TiptonHurst with the perfect last minute #ValentineDay gift ideas! https://t.co/aCOMYNf3aS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaSamms1 They don’t come any more beautiful than you in this photograph!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalnutcr1 Seniors are "taken care of" under Socialized Medicine. They already thought of that one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillsMafiaHouse He said “he wouldn’t show up” pretty much sounds like he didn’t want to come]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTSOJ13 @UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump Trust me we WILL make America great again!!  First step:  getting the WORST p… https://t.co/uHsvIEoQUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have to ask people to block your significant other so they aren’t able to mess around with them... you need… https://t.co/uOVJYZiy76]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched the Red Table Talk with @Wale and it was amazing. His transparency is such a breath of fresh air 🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcpsforward @tkonz @SHSOurHouse @JCPSScience @LaceyEckels @CoachTatman @JCPSKY This is DEFINITELY going in their  #JCPSBackpack !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyReferee MJ por de LeBron. El señor Marco un antes y después en la NBA https://t.co/NVqL74ONfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget the time my boy got a text from someone called baby and I flipped shit saying who tf is baby and… https://t.co/Sq13gQJi53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t the fake president be censored for the hours of hate speech and propaganda he spewed this weekend?  He is… https://t.co/K5g5SVBfIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartofAlderaan @Carie80ESB @irishgeekgirl @darth_swlove03 @DomKivall @Viamgu @ddoctorsong @skylmae… https://t.co/9nzhb9EzsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel What’s there to consider! I wanna know what the shitler, as one of our friends calls him promised his boyfriend Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homelessness is my number one priority. It's about getting San Francisco cleaned up again, Marc @Benioff tells… https://t.co/RX09J8vafV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning everyone drive safely out there going to drink my coffee ☕ and watch the news https://t.co/8KmmIgu80J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading list for the plane ride to #19NTC:  1⃣ The Hidden Brain: How Our Unconscious Minds Elect Presidents, Contro… https://t.co/KISmqxW7rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it is a bit trite, however, do not do the crime if you can’t do the time. I have no sympathy for him. Partic… https://t.co/PLD5JFHcFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! NASA names facility after 'Hidden Figures' inspiration Katherine Johnson - ABC News -  via @ABC https://t.co/ak4aOExRMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissRubyReviews I love seeing Ruby when I stroll through my feed. Still, I have the startled response, “what, huh?… https://t.co/8ZUgMafbNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@effortfuleduktr I think what also speaks volumes here is that, despite beliefs you have that have gotten you criti… https://t.co/2S0H0cA9qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maranda_q2075 At least I’m working on myself, instead of still making excuses. I admit I have done bitch things in… https://t.co/ljoBa365qC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWimmerrr so they’re mad bc you have an exquisite taste in music...sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Protect &amp; expand #BearsEars National Monument! https://t.co/StjU8e9Iza via @CREDOMobile #StandWithBearsEars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WIG_BeckyAnn Beautiful. I lived on Whidbey Island many many years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets I’m going to say bad. The Democrats are the party that’s declared being for everyone, to finding a w… https://t.co/NnCM3fPqdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher Have a wonderful time and please relax!!!! You so deserve it!!!!😁❤☝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I would have tried to hold on to John Brown out of all these guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart broken but my money gettin longer and my ass gettin fatter so 2019 aight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenas y rockeras tardes a la #RockShow band ! 🎸🎧🤟🏻 ~Such awesome podcast Greta, Nacha,30 seconds,Oasis 👹😘💥… https://t.co/unEUJ24qHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando vi estas imágenes de pronto sentí que los daños que sufrió mi carro la semana pasada fueron irrelevantes 😅 https://t.co/fBLYpu8FOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heidiinicolee3 "hold on dont move I gotta get it from over here" - me in laudy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleroberson4 HAHAHAHAHA!!!! I didn’t even see that!!! I’m fucking weakkkkk 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postandcourier @JoeCunninghamSC Thanks Joe and the whales thank you 🙏🏼  🐳]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m high watching a Haneke movie and I really felt like there was a joke there but I can’t find it]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it’s finally @krbell21 birthday and you get to CELEBRATE! https://t.co/tHH6VMlyHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sad day to be oblivious: we were right next to lady Gaga and I didn’t even notice. Disappointed and upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only opportunity left for @VAratifyERA is to approach the @AlexandriaVAGov and make a final deal. #ERAFloorVote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renevelation @TheAtheistPig But this is why I hate when theists say we can’t disprove god. Don’t you have to prove… https://t.co/5bdAd6iaRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fun_eddie @MoisesLopez47 @Lisa130f13 @JamieRaee14 @katefamoconnor @Nykkynut @ElisaLopez7771 @Stephan66424700… https://t.co/yrNnD9vpc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing five different outfits that are western inspired and perfect for the rodeo this year! Are you guys attendin… https://t.co/dYmvWZucPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How wicked to be in love with someone but feel so alone at the same time ... shits crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing this week’s cuties!  Both such handsome boys. 🥰 Check out the blog for more favorites from this session… https://t.co/f8pMqbUNZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want 1 thing clear about #Oscars2019 ! @ChrisEvans is responsible for all the December 2019 babies coming to you… https://t.co/M3j217tcMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta say, 'The Thing' is my #1 and 'Psycho' and 'Alien' are right up there for me, too. Not that we need more list… https://t.co/fpCr7XrdxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misguidedgent Happy dinnering/parenting. I look forward to your booze choice later 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA Rest In Peace u beautiful soul. May your family find comfort that u are not suffering anymore. #RIPLukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew she was dead fox WOULDN'T have flashed that death notice if she was still alive !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[with this procedure or sniping the spinal cord guaranteed death. I don't think this bill is enough to save aborted… https://t.co/9JyUEHxGJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@destinysalinas4 @OhhMarii @Maritzaa_Mariee @kaila_torres @ibarraly BITCH ME TOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My crazy, beautiful girl is one year old today! 🥳 #siberianhusky #huskyphotography #huskybirthday @ Uptown, New Orl… https://t.co/nNdtQBY6mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EffugioSounds @Midnightasaurus Hahah well the wallpaper on the computer has something to do with that ☺️ but we wo… https://t.co/6U4X2Yl4af]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @EricHolder Correct.  But Eric,  we r NOT A REAL DEMOCRACY.  We r a democratic republic, thus representat… https://t.co/tKyev4KJ4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was so incredibly awesome to be behind the scenes of my first PBS Pledge Drive at WSRE! Y’all should know that I… https://t.co/Pzm5QrReDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MichaelCohen an embarrassment but honestly what was done today by this committee is a total disgrace to OUR countr… https://t.co/56N9TcCxKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ava @lpolgreen I lived in Manhattan when this Central Park crime took place. If memory serves DJT was a spear head… https://t.co/PkWwAXLFH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this great night in Philly with wonderful people. #MindingTheGapPBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tower6 @Morniesan @Jamierodr14 My tweet reply was deleted don't know why. Yes, you're right we should support you.… https://t.co/mz4U0a3kAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s better than beating one group of 🐅🐅  in a week? Beating two groups, of course! 😼🏀😼 #bbn #weareUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savana!! Happy birthday I hope you have the best day ever! Love you♥️♥️ @BurrowSavana]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PantsuitPolitic I love how you guys addressed the issue of respecting the person on @Morning_Joe but not their dec… https://t.co/v5AykQObuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFourmane Exactamente, estimado. Intentan , llevar a cabo, en todos los “frentes”: “El odio como factor de lucha “… https://t.co/pFbz0pz88w]]></document><document><![CDATA[New friends told me that I was really fun to be around, an old friend told me, “Stay Tina, Tina😂,” my scholarship d… https://t.co/zl4JmixeX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is most exciting to happen in like........ FOREVER!🤦‍♀️❣️#8yearoldself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwwww my ktla5news brother/ cameraman bchoo1971 shared his #ValentinesDay chocolate balls with me 🤣🤣🤣🤣 #justsayin… https://t.co/1eIygdot8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[why am i getting push notifications on this they'd better be sending me a free copy if they have the AUDACITY to th… https://t.co/tPaw6kjHFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllAboutDaTea I still don't understand how they think any of this could have happened if Dorit didn't give the dog… https://t.co/dhVLWs5YTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Yard Team… https://t.co/NFkT3nCGNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ox is loving his snuggie blanket on this snowy Las Vegas night. @ Henderson, Nevada https://t.co/d6ArPAkROu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎂Con Sue Photography and Design🍰   🍦Like our photos...Follow our IG 🎂  🍰This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 💖… https://t.co/qhpKXiTkyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[He sounds like Comey and I dont believe Trump threatened his family......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reimagine city life ... w/ BBQ #sxsw @urbanxaccel https://t.co/pMpvjacQ14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun night at the live taping of @PantsuitPolitic in Paducah! Great discussion about tech policy, perpetual growth,… https://t.co/QeWHj2Smyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Stopped watching all award shows. Not entertaining any longer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chillichilli98 @MusikMan01 @FlourishGoddess @fierymistress @thehill Again..  Call backup, Clear scene of bystander… https://t.co/QCovqfJEv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see now the only ones that are targeting are the Democrats and illegal Democrats in office under oathe lying to A… https://t.co/i27eqgwtyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to hear what the Spectacular 6 learned today and what they can teach their peers! #leopardpride… https://t.co/NYb4Gl8Sub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew Let's see how long they remain silent when the next issue happens that calls for throwing Trump under the bus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Spend money on our vets.  Honor and respect our vets.  Instead all we hear about are t… https://t.co/HV1XWBd8A7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheGoodDoctor will Shaun return to being a surgical resident? Will I be able to wait till next Monday to find out?… https://t.co/jZbzmJhu1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlfromhever One of the great what ifs of History,how things would have changed had that little boy lived !!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pause it at 0:04-0:05 seconds...i thought the bald dude had a pony tail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanParnellUSA @JudgeMoroz @realDonaldTrump They lack credibility on knowing what good deal looks like, the follow… https://t.co/Mjg9GOw8Zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gene Smith Says Urban Meyer is “Bringing Unbelievable Value” to Ohio State in New Role As Assistant Athletic Direct… https://t.co/jDn6HK4mHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #InternationalWomensDay let's remember Eugenia Duke,  entrepreneur and creator of Duke Mayonnaise. #southernthing https://t.co/uMMdTwSIGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the dress I like to wear for the Marisol Deluna Foundation Youth Fashion Show. It’s one of her signature desig… https://t.co/VmohDTAfDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BLACKout . #BHM #BlackHistoryMonth #BlackHistoryMonth2019 #SaidiyaHartman #WaywardLivesBeautifulExperiments . “Way… https://t.co/Zi1ibSA0gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm rocking a gnarly goose egg on my forehead today. I was surprised on how hard @SullivanTylor can punch.  Good th… https://t.co/eunzNdwAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson's Simpsons episode pulled after Leaving Neverland  https://t.co/JWcqlSz00q]]></document></documents></author>