<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Meghan_Trainor you were amazing last night! ❤️ https://t.co/RBSE2lIvHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveBreasia45 @Melaniiiin @BowDownTooMe @vesindica @niquenique_16 @tijhana1 LMAOOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boylers73 @ontarioisproud If nothing else. I am sure Gerry will be happy to take any calls from Ju$tin day or nigh… https://t.co/DN4unHJvyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[so sore from hiking yesterday that I’m actually limping today.... I get it I need to go outside more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of these girls, Top Ten awards for both groups and 3rd Overall for duo.… https://t.co/vkIvycIAwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU WANTED MCcabe FIRED! WE WERE ALL ALIVE when you had someone else do your dirty work for you. And so it was done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the new math that moronic, @BetsyDeVosED has the children doing now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Melania, GOSAR has a Message for you.  On a sign.  It’s about your pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alefolgarait @jens2go @rogueclassicist @archaeologyEAA @In2thepast @mgknight24 @ArchsEngage Unfortunately I think… https://t.co/h0Z57NjpBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶If you’ve never shouted to be heard, you ain’t lived in a woman’s world🎶 #InternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 @TheDemocrats @IlhanMN I don't even want someone who LOOKS like her in our Government!!  She can go… https://t.co/4hbDdbvKUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elskemccain Well that’s crazy. I believe in a lot of that pedo stuff but I’m a regular person and don’t condone ha… https://t.co/dR6rn2uOqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BacheloretteABC let the guys choose either Hannah B or Caelynn for Bachelorette. Just like what Kaitlyn and Britt had to do 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The countdown to @sxsw is on 📆  Gearing up for one helluva week with @Common_Genius #ImAGenius https://t.co/59JJWypKL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[“~8% of @Google searches are #health related. That translates to about 70k searches per minute, or 1 billion per da… https://t.co/liWVIsE1Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were taken by a Russian coup although Brian Williams reports it like a new concept... Yes Ida...  With the help… https://t.co/v0JQ4ing4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebStrickland65 @Fernie635 @RealAlexD @RealAmyD @czemeres Like... I have family in Hamilton and I am reluctant as… https://t.co/5WrPb8H1vo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rikipedia_DC @neosoulgirl49 @LorenzoANC7C04 So when there's condom litter do you call HIPS to dispatch a clean up… https://t.co/DrSejsmucy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s critical that we build #AI that’s  trustworthy.” @WHOSTP #DellExperience #politicoai #sxsw https://t.co/uUqUZRzTy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_jones5 @krassenstein A nd how many times did he file for bankruptcy , some business man- wake up trump voters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Jr's IQ is lower then pond scum. I wouldn't listening to a thing he has to say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the Day, Where Cyber Friends come to play, And I’ll even Pay 💰 🙌🏼  -hope to see you at Pistol Pete’s for… https://t.co/SGtKv1OIDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pour some sugar on meeeee  In the name of loooove 🎤😫 https://t.co/v6fRwFndg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickStump if you didn't know you and everyone you collaborate with are amazing singers and songwriters whomever… https://t.co/Bs9PLeRvvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conjuring spirits as I get the ball rolling.  Won't forget that I come from strong women.  Won't forget they walk b… https://t.co/25dNqox0YF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truckzo Obvio, un Mc Carthys con Leo está de cajón. En cuanto me llegue mi itinerario te lo envío 🛩]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Dog #DogOwners #Risk #Electrocution. Please don’t let your dog touch cables on the ground but also watch them touc… https://t.co/bF7iab2Ewj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Stratten, President of UnMarketing Inc, gave an impressive view of generational differences at LABI 2019 Annu… https://t.co/0XUlmDup3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight from winter to summer!  #lilbabyg #liltoddlerg #lilgiswildandthree #whathappenedtospring #waterbaby @ Hunt… https://t.co/J0NeN2HIb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad steamriceroll opened in @canalstreetmkt now I don’t have to go to Flushing to get their delicious rice roll… https://t.co/MZQEICsvcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to smirk a bit. #funniness #chuckle #smirk #amusing https://t.co/6dffEVRsxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck I can’t stop laughing . Y’all go look at my story on insta 😭😭😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felipelaso10 Y ojo de loca no se equivoca 🙄 tenemos plática pendiente 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck to coach Riley and the Tappan Zee Girls Basketball Team playing in their sectional semifinals game today!… https://t.co/SFfWzYKkLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stop reading it.. it’s amazing. so realistic. it’s like i saw her. what her life would have been like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CosmicKxtty Lmao I’m like 3 months away it’s not that serious. Just let people enjoy things 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theJagmeetSingh Ce sont les gens ordinaires qui perdent leur emploi quand ces compagnies sont punies. Ce sont les… https://t.co/cYf8YtJPDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My phone now automatically suggests “therapist” after I type “my,” so here if your friendly reminder that mental health is IMPORTANT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚫 737 Max — Boeing postpone new aircraft launch as airlines respond to fears over the company’s 737 MAX 8 planes  https://t.co/haNmjyDeYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maravillas medievales en The Met Cloisters 🦄⚜️#cloisters #themetcloisters #medievalart #unicorn en The Met Cloisters https://t.co/STSYUgwu3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!! Can we all just talk about how sexy Ms. @ReginaKing looked last night !! Absolutely stunning 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, let me get this straight: if I apply to a bank for a loan for a mortgage or even for a small loan, say $5,000 f… https://t.co/V4iq7HOgGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[never thought I’d say this... but I’m so glad Mardi Gras is over my liver is thankful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJohnson31 @codyjohnson @ChrisMClark1989 surprised you knew “hold you down”]]></document><document><![CDATA[호비 오빠, 생일 축하해요!!! 사랑해애애애~~ #SunshineHobiDay #MY_HOPE_JHOPE #OurPieceOfPeace #제이홉_널_만난건_행운이자_행복 #HappyBirthdayJHope https://t.co/msMR8lQeM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then I asked if they knew if Dead and Co. was coming to any near by venues... And they all look at me and said… https://t.co/gIwYyMVXVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The culture of your business should be fiercely protected with an unwavering commitment!  Culture is the reason you… https://t.co/hFvijfy8Pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I walked in my cozy home fixed dinner for my daughter and had a glass of wine, I stopped. I sat back an absorbed… https://t.co/KRMA2SyM64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ @HolmanJenkins @realDonaldTrump only gets re-elected if he releases The Perfect Back. If he doesn’t, bye bye Mr. President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @ACatholicKnight @JerryNadler @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Nadlers hate for Trump is years old. Na… https://t.co/0tJoGTbCO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy with ONE tooth at Walmart just said “you so fucking sexy you know that” so confidence is restored!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fist time #skiing in #california 🙌🏾🏔⛷🤗 what a great weather 🤩💃🏽  . . . #mammothmountain #sundayfunday #mammothlakes… https://t.co/KwND2KAQMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I immediately picked up The Secret to Southern Charm right after reading Kristy Woodson Harvey's fabulous 1st book… https://t.co/3ZDjss1K5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaughtySassyHez @KellirjA @Mamabear0772 @mad_moran @JanetCannady @Viola3219 @0SleeptilDawn @assassinswife… https://t.co/mzndnfOTxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight my very first green picture with @BGsMusic last night show was great! See you guys again tonight Sa… https://t.co/qI4p6iCMUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UberEats is offering Buy One, Get One meals thru Mon. Who wants to get in on this and #BOGOtogether?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days I would really like to not to have to be the one to have to do everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofzz2020 @VapidVulpine that's what's really important 😎   *notches another internet point on my bed post*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Trump_Train Yes we do , And I don't know what anyone can do , I can't understand how people could put her there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Necklace and matching earrings  1 available $5  #karissparkleroom  #karis5sparkle  #5dollarsparkle  #5dollarbling… https://t.co/2ECGmXgbD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamanthaHeller great show today - regarding B12 it also depends on your genetic make-up some more at risk of defic… https://t.co/qezktRgvkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[it occupies the pinnacles of power...it bubbles up from the abyss [of hell]. Love has just one form—your Son.” Afte… https://t.co/fy3132C8GS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Co-teaching with Ms. Webster at @ChapmanSchools. @kitrisetorain @twoods52 https://t.co/m0z75Xb8fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Choice of Champions! Always enjoy our time learning in @LakeCountyFL with @LeadershipORL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I'm having more than one beer tonight because fuck my life right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexTachalova @aleyda @KayleighToyra @hannahjthorpe @lauracrimmons @staceycav @SusanCMoeller @JuliaEMcCoy… https://t.co/tXvizoqQnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krs_one3 @Pink 😢nope tickets were to expensive. When they were good prices everybody said wait. She is in Florida… https://t.co/LqbRVMPtog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarefootIsLegal @_EMMA_KOEHLER_ cause it’s college and the bathroom floor is real nasty😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tall men on dating apps are incapable of listing their height in their bio without putting “because apparently that’s important” after.]]></document><document><![CDATA['The Masked Singer' Spoilers: Who's Behind Season 1 Masks? https://t.co/X4d7vlIOEz via @goldderby]]></document><document><![CDATA[D'Souza UNLEASHES on Democrats over endorsement of post-birth abortions https://t.co/vgaRCgv7Hf via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[for around 6 years, I’ve been with jakelyn on her birthday and now is the first time I won’t bc of college https://t.co/jSA0A2arm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainSmithEDU I miss teaching with you and your joyful "Good morning, Mrs. Konecny!" that I used get everyday! 💜… https://t.co/JTMuKYQzjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gazing out on snowy #winterfest weather🌫🌬and thinking of my #brunch goals! ❄☃️#HappyWeekend!🥓🥞 #WeekendVibes ☕🍰… https://t.co/AklN6YQTIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias por tu amor ¿Cómo pagarte lo que haces conmigo Me das la fuerza cuando estoy vencido Eres el centro de mi c… https://t.co/Oui2ErcAxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full foil with @Kenra_Haircare simply blonde and trionicshaircare toned with guytang_mydentity sand storm… https://t.co/SZx9ioNA1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindness is Free!!!❤️ #passitaround #dogood #KindnessMatters #easyacts #makessomeonesday #LifeisGood #greatreminder… https://t.co/yaSRFKb5BC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf @AOC I honestly think this argument is a little silly on your side kat. You’re changing things to be fant… https://t.co/CoHhRrzgLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point I’m convinced that the girl next door doesn’t have a disability because she’s always getting her back… https://t.co/NlG6MzUztF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsmhebert @Eduscape Hey, my friend!  We need an updated flyer with the new dates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter how many presentations I give I will forever stress to the point where I make myself sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok what caelynn was so gracious and kind the whole experience she did not deserve that I’m ashkkffeddbjsks #bachelor 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump slams Andrew McCabe's account as 'so many lies'  https://t.co/JtLdFqv9F4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RochVoisineRVI Tu te souviens d'avoir chanté ça? Oui, c'est sur mes vieilles cassettes...  https://t.co/OiUyMEed4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsTHINK No. She's second tier. Not a credible candidate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyslist Problem is McConnell has cheated to win elections in Kentucky a long time ! The RNC changes absentee votes for him !]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favourite #Oscars2019 photo as well!! @MarceBautistaB @untrabajodigno @domesticworkers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveJax @vyodaiken @VoteHealth @MelissaHBuckner @ThePlumLineGS Thanks. I can take it from here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pourmeanotherr Thank you babe I really needed to hear this. I started beating myself up because I’ve been at sac f… https://t.co/lBGx3GQLGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends that chat and don’t include you are literally the worst also friends who plan trips without including you a… https://t.co/Mzew0jL5gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martyb864 @duckduckloose @SandruSom @JoyAnnReid @amazon Shit. I live in LA too. Now I’m scared to file.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatJoser Oh dear José, my heart is with you. Hugs and hugs and hugs 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabulouslytabs In my Parma Senior High Movie Club sweatshirt on my couch. It’s fabulous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donrigsby It’s the Thompson/Rigsby genes coming out in me!! Lol. My dad LOVED Gunsmoke and Bonanza. So do I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Love Your Pet Day🐶!! There is no doubt that my pair love this little fur baby🐾🐶...not just today but… https://t.co/JdAWxCWrMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join @StephBauer17 and I as we talk using photography to boost creativity in the classroom. Tuesday 2/19 at 9… https://t.co/Iq1B2kh0Ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickL14020534 @SenKamalaHarris You didn't. Lol!  Have a gentle evening, Nick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JussieSmollett is quickly learning that acting out scripts is only meant for the stage and screen.... Spread… https://t.co/wIB7ULPWHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously celebrating the release of the @Weezer #blackalbum in the most fitting fashion with my first tat. 😁😁😁 https://t.co/0wEaBmhEhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom No one is deceived by Trump distractions! I think the press needs to preface all incoming tweets and… https://t.co/CYXp7JpJGE]]></document></documents></author>