<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Somewhere I’m sure there’s a tweet of him thanking the #NYTimes for exposing something the Obama administration did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished @OneDayAtATime on Netflix. What an amazing show! Every episode is so well done, i have never seen a c… https://t.co/AM8o35hvcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJesseMorse @TheFantasyDRS @RotoGut @BaseballGuys @Jeff_Mans Cool look forward to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennyLang1775 @RailYardDawgs I just saw that. Happy for him, saddened for us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basic question for life: What is your desired outcome? Applies to all aspects of life; work, faith, relationships e… https://t.co/qiymXgvocl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a WINNER!!! ⠀ THANK YOU to everyone who participated! ⠀  ⠀ Continue to FOLLOW / LIKE for MORE GIVEAWAYS to… https://t.co/YD5nvoR4xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hand out with celebrity chef Chris Valdes from the Food Network Wednesday night at my biz event with Spectru… https://t.co/JUWswSqWxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @chucklourieT This will be in Minnesota before long if Americans don’t wake up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyDoesStuff @i_womb 100 percent Living Mind, Body and Soul from conception, the Soul (EVERY SOUL) belongs to G… https://t.co/HE3qd43Hna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yea david keep it up. If u mcu fans is gettin pressed over soneone promotin u got a problem. Yall tend to forget… https://t.co/6M4vZGLnB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a caaaaasual drive up the road for a story I’m working on! Any podcast/music recommendations for the drive?… https://t.co/3H9ZvIlPpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DeVos wealth came from pyramid schemes. That's how they see #highereducation too. It's predatory behavior. https://t.co/spP2LVOHbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. Damien Williams...unload him and get 10x what you paid. Hopefully people sold high right after playoffs  Hey… https://t.co/sAKGbugSWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b_rockg @binchtits @CharlieDaniels Cortez the Killer is a classic. Cortes the congresswoman is an abject disaster.… https://t.co/g6vkizl2te]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScalzoandBrust You may want to check out who's officiating to understand which team to bet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierrealee @navarrowolff Después de us actos terroristas después de asesinar a personas inocentes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I miss about Atlanta. Dekalb Farmers Market. #theyhavethemeats #sharkstoo #atl @ Your Dekalb County… https://t.co/6WwqhJvJCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never noticed how many fans in the stands when I played. Didn’t matter to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These step-ups kicked my butt after the 200’ lunges w/50 lb dumbbell. #rvcstrong #rivervalleycrossfit #blueteam @ R… https://t.co/rsL7m5VNy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wins over @Vol_Hoops and @KentuckyMBB...haters gonna hate @LSUBasketball. #GeauxTigers #bootup #1stinSEC #Sec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAindex I think California has been doing the same thing for years.  I think it's time for those being persecute… https://t.co/c3pYpMSLmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-Season Softball: DeSoto dominates East Lee 15-3 in “mercy rule” fashion. Regular season starts next week...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Athletic City Update:  These Morris-Sussex Wresters are heading to the Quarterfinals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @WandaKA66182301 He should’ve thought of all that before he became campaign manager.  TRAITOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELL TF YES! And you better hope they even have parking spots available]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆 Congratulations to @sbabball! Etobicoke Thunder's 6th Annual Ballin' for Breast Cancer U15 Boy's Midgets (Champio… https://t.co/cbqgbVIHfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VladBooch We have lots to do on finding a better balance. But yes, the answer if that a lot of things are things t… https://t.co/Q0oG8mxGYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner Pathetic. You are really feeling the pressure. #ResignNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Slugg Literary Program is a tool to help address trauma and make communities safer . I am so excited to be part… https://t.co/lRQJWnsIfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Annapurna’s World Vegetarian Café - @annapurnaswvc in Santa Fe, NM https://t.co/pfmVTT8IuJ https://t.co/bxvAPfWDmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only positive of this game is that there is a Nova Scotian on the pitch.   Jacob Shaffelburg. ⛵⚓⚽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man.. congrats JT🤘🏻 this is everything we’ve ever dreamed of as kids. Make the ville proud brother 〽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idag invigs Kvinnokommissionen - årets viktigaste globala möte om kvinnors och flickors rättigheter. @rfsu är på pl… https://t.co/yNmydAhhTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tongodeon @TakeThatDarwin @jhwk316 @Alyssa_Milano Genesis 1:27   So God created man in his own image, in the image… https://t.co/6AjeeSmMwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like Lord Farquaad's cheeseburger buffet didn't settle very well. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newcountrysbest @timkellyonair @KUHSDenver Thanks Tim and Indie Country Radio🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Windsor at Hancock Park 445 N Rossmore Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90004 (844) 343-9413 https://t.co/eSWxEPIOXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeGinoB @BklynBckstretch I don’t go that far but I do believe the industry doesn’t dedicate the necessary resou… https://t.co/7IBgph5fKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Three Must-See Acts This Week: House Catz ’n Dogz 1 p.m., Sunday, March 3, at The Midway. $15;… https://t.co/iawozWocuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CapsKings come on Ovie why go to the box there - you have a two goal lead and the Caps need both points tonight  C… https://t.co/SzGERO1Z96]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningJoe I hope #IlhanOmar is defeated in 2020. #Minnesota should hang it’s head for electing this dangerous person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSchmalz congratulations on number 200. Very proud of the team and your leadership. Glad to call You my friend. Go Trojans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting take, given that Trump skipped a 2016 Republican primary debate because it was sponsored by Fox News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BaD Radio is an acronym not a contraction of Bob and Dan and I can’t take it anymore @SportsSturm @bracketdan @dfwticket]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjsrugbydad @phillymack07 @Mr_Berger15 @ThunderRugbyCA Big congrats @Mr_Berger15 Well deserved! Love to see more h… https://t.co/mtUEw6fkTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeahJustice @crys_sosic @Kenyadunn12 @Dana_Edwards24 @joseph_sester Welcome @crys_sosic to the #trucklife can't wa… https://t.co/rxcqRhB3Ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the 3rd YouTube video I’ve watched in the past 30(?) minutes of a @Tesla slapping all those who try and ste… https://t.co/Cl3B3geqMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the drama of sectionals begin on the boys side. Great shot @iamtahjaehill !!! Amazing comeback capped by this!!… https://t.co/GGENohE9O1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am grateful for a new #hope I’ve felt for the last couple of weeks. I am grateful for an #amazing roommate.… https://t.co/EOUolCGZdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geofurb I consider it a thing of value. That's why I'd never use it inappropriately]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry but ya’ll can’t jump on the kacey bandwagon now lol wbk she’s amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Brave #iG #Decentralize #Merkle #Tree #PPP #Tokenization #5G @ Diamond Club Orlando https://t.co/HrmRT26BSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @Jenn198523 Make your list sweetheart and don’t forget to put on the $20,000 you funneled through your cam… https://t.co/03RYOSDKBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched #freesolo. Damn! This has to be one of the most amazing athletic feats I have ever watched. I mean dam… https://t.co/1z8X3Sf9M2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyOstroy @realDonaldTrump You stupid people will continue to nitpick every little small thing Trump says you are… https://t.co/96vTW8yzYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckydayapp Hi @luckydayapp we have big Problems with your guys Apps Friday night would not work for me at all” so… https://t.co/wn5GDYcvzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU ARE THE ENEMY OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA AND IT'S ALLIES. YOU! Not Media. You Are a Narci… https://t.co/WSSkMFqqpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to thank @Austin_Reed14 for being my 500th follower!  I have now reached my goal of ".5K by Opening Da… https://t.co/2PEVsuEtRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LwyrUp406 @NickKendellMHH Don’t forget Heisman Candidate Jalen Hurts!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rksimonlaw @PascoSheriff @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @TempePolice #livepd https://t.co/sQw682raig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DatDudePB @AlexiLalas @BryanWeigel @MattDoyle76 @MLS @fccincinnati OK, I can tell I’m talking to a newbie.  So, t… https://t.co/XitJ9Mukzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richbenavides Yes. You can see the common denominator when they play hard and play well: defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @YouTube Boy @Talkmaster , you are up earlier than me today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeigoPaartalu @Nippertown @FFCSBraves @FigVilleUSA @NASCHartInc @cgriffywrites @mayaloumyrdahl @LibertyBottles… https://t.co/CQ9027x4Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Durant slowly destroying Golden State by fucking up at the end of games?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focused on a goal and not worrying about outcomes can lead to great success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇨🇦👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN! Sweetheart!💝Miss Nataly! The White RACE Canadian BLONDES👑Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The… https://t.co/t4kYAX1iJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson my stress level is high for a reason I do not know if you would believe.  I believe in coexistence.… https://t.co/NFii1fDt8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeHatem_ @sam0ns It’s a solid question and they probably won’t be honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long day at work, it was nice to come home to see that my new @Cubs gear came in early. https://t.co/F07FM2mt7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be 🔥! Can’t wait to celebrate another milestone for @OhioSurfer! 🎉 ⏰ 🕺 #swaggstyle #va2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LockedOnSixers podcast: Dissecting Philly’s series skid-snapping win over #OKCThunder https://t.co/luH5ac10UC via @phillydotcom #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrowder The latter but that can be accomplished by pointing out more that share her views, not just by focusing solely on her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome display of one of @ENCAthletics Core Values: Service #FaithAcademicsCompetitionService]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the point in my life we’re I’m too busy, I forget to eat until the end of the day...wtf is wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a certain someone don’t pick up their headset then I’ll keep em @ Willowbrook, California https://t.co/9M0XlfEq0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dropped my phone on Ripley. In return he put all of his claws in me. I’m in pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little #BTS of our cmuniversity capstone shoot. 🔥👆🏻🤓... #lifeatcentral #michigrammers #universityphotographer… https://t.co/e8XEWuUPzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you in a couple days queen @ParisHilton 👸🏼🎉🇲🇽🤗🏖🏝#PartywithParis #Cancun #Mexico]]></document><document><![CDATA[They lucky AB ain’t on his marshawn cuz then the whole Steelers organization would of got exposed Lml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bodan1 @Lexialex No. But I am intrigued by the Jordanian-American stuntman graphic novel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COLBYJANSENXXX @avnawards @AUBREYKATEXXX @EvilAngelVideo @AidenStarr Congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t understand people who have their phone’s flashlight strobe when then receive notifications. ESPECIAL… https://t.co/usNS5AWRQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeninistTweet @Rafa_Soccer14 @abcperez5_ literally how it feels when we play with raf lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adambrandi27 @GrindingTheTape I unfortunately won’t be making it this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rita22943329 @AYELEANDCO @ArantesStephen I think your baby got your phone again 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gayle King got bitched slapped by R. Kelly’s two girlfriends. I feel like he’s winning in the public eye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once a person realizes that the only fear they should have is having not tried something, this obstacle can be remo… https://t.co/KRJRTqAm2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Client cancellation left me with an opportunity to squeeze a workout for me.... #muchneeded #Beautifulviolence… https://t.co/aTinGgIQZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashholesimmons @gr8tvaluebiggie @Sir_Fahrenheit @Ange_lala_La @ribeyeszn @josephruscitti @BrandonC1323… https://t.co/LzY22QaVlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helmion_ I don’t think I’m buying much else this year haha. I did KH3 and Jump Force, but I’m done until my birthd… https://t.co/rvmf9QwMY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handal_dave @TomballHSBBall @TISD_athletics @TomballHS You better hurry. You’re top is dropping by the minute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They died over 100 years ago - today’s black have every opportunity plus than anyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sortacooliguess Exactly. At this point the words don't scare us anymore. Not Socialist, Atheist, Liberal, Abortion… https://t.co/zznDvlLA7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaOtten1 @NicoleAgosti Noooooooooooo!!!!! Ahahahahahahahahhhhh! You can’t say that, because I drive you everywhere! Lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsmaley Thanks so much for that! Have them connect with me on Twitter if they have any questions! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eschraderMB Good question for the blogger, @mikeneill - Hey Mike, great article! Can you share more about the cool… https://t.co/eilYU0xLSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @SebGorka Twitter, I'd like to report a murder. Seb has burns over 90% of his ill-fitting tactical… https://t.co/OC8sb6qSBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASA Shuts Down ISS Feed After Massive UFO Appears 👽🛸 https://t.co/lKiGQykFn3 good day from space.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darrell Brown sinks a huge jumper with 3:07 remaining to give #Bradley a 54-49 lead. Elijah Childs pulls on the "Br… https://t.co/vrBmMalVpu]]></document></documents></author>