<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Waiting to board the plane to ATL heading to SAN for #MivaCon19. This should be interesting, I pulled a klutz move… https://t.co/zOmL2mOwgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙏🙏🙏 (@ Calvary Chapel Chino Valley in Chino, CA) https://t.co/QV4sKa4g0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker Is there a more vial person on this planet?  Personally I do not think so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Online classes are all fun and games because you can do them in your own time until you have a big project that fri… https://t.co/SZDioTo34r]]></document><document><![CDATA[vibing to throwback r&amp;b and depressing songs for a few hours is a part of my daily routine]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Team Lead (Part-time and Full-time)" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about thes… https://t.co/WtTjk9Jl1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[when ur in a relationship and just wanna be weird &amp; cute https://t.co/VtJhtqTfhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's #DoomPatrol nails in the music department-- the song choices AND the score. We talk about music from Eps… https://t.co/8ser1TBAAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanktranks @allreadythen1 Oh I prefer that as well. In my state, we now have ranked choice voting. It's the best o… https://t.co/z8lM2ZCB7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says Lionel Richie is a musical influence..... can’t name a Lionel Richie song🤣🤣🤣 #americanidol @LionelRichie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where Do Mountains Get Their Names? https://t.co/2xteLdoZzR via @curiositydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieDornan_Inc Thank you. Freed coming on in a few minutes. Then to bed. My Friday chore is the grocery. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent my morning doing one of the things I love to do, photography!!! What an awesome day. I hope you are enjoyin… https://t.co/ztYxQhDpei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKunalKohli @TheLittleRoch @SPECNewsROC @savmayco @rachelbord I spot a squad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this.... and i can’t stress this enough.... the trancenDANCE showcase]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Washington County woman was rescued after she fell through the ice on the Pleasant River in Addison while chasing… https://t.co/Jf63El9bkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sage_lake7 @deedee_regan @dancintn @mcmurphyOUfan @LivePdBlueLine @scorpiorising14 @whitwhit78 @Kennedy888B… https://t.co/eDCCxQJS2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a go-getter on the job? Do you dream big and go the extra mile to uncover the next groundbreaking idea? Lea… https://t.co/1pJfueau2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rondog15970424 Hard to remember most of it. Traveled. Lived in hotels or couch surfed. Concerts. Clubs. Camping. And a lot of cocaine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Yes I might love them but there’s not really cliffhangers or as much character development so I’m not as invested.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats again @js19651983 @DavidManchee #goodteam #goodfriends #goodmemories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lundon: You pregnant    Me: Lundon stop fucking cussing all the time damn 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thread on Bernie- please read!  Not a Bernie fan and he’s still not even a Democrat  - but   Above all we ALL… https://t.co/T0W5EpPf7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lasvegas #eiffeltower #streetphotography #photography #color #video #photooftheday #porelplacerdecompartir… https://t.co/Oll4bEusbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the choice for breakfast is a circular decision. Simple and wonderful.  eatnpark_ #burbank #burbankfoodie… https://t.co/3ubUih6iVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had no boobs in middle school (also for having a big head).... look at me now b*tches big tiddies and still big a… https://t.co/TtWDgWjWgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I wish you were as fierce of an advocate for #BlackLivesMatter @TheView]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yesohyas #yesohyasbox #yesohyasambassador #fashion #getinsta #style  #beauty  #ootd #pretty #hair  #model  #design… https://t.co/PXyX2gaydX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @virgincheese plate at @eatthealthy thooo ✨💚🌱 @ Eatt Gourmet Bistro https://t.co/t22bBO0JqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t put my purse on the floor because it’s unsanitary. Sometimes feng shui and common sense align!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rica_Bee So very sorry for the loss of your sister. What a great picture and memory of a happy time together!❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love fantasying about a man before we have sex 😈💭 ..... my interest has been sparked. #gameon]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is someone who actually changed/influence pop music, it's this woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeraca @4YrsToday @RodStryker @CNN I don’t know but reading about it did not sound like a scandal. Trump is a scan… https://t.co/Lmmyspl7dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fharris39 @riteaid It sure isn't! (and it's starting to make my cough come back) :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexRoy144 @thedrive Film was a great reminder of  how much better our industry has to be at communicating with re… https://t.co/LnWrUxqgJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz: Ousting Trump via 25th Amendment is ‘clearly an attempt at a coup d’etat’  https://t.co/grxyLBc6J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg a lot of people...well some people...well very few people are just so nice and sweet it makes me so happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @SpeakerPelosi ! You have won a nothing 🍔!  The Dems are so proud of you. Try passing something tha… https://t.co/iwwsAsNf8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nets up! Protection at spring training. https://t.co/POdmVJgCOe @DailyNewsSun #AZNEWSMEDIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonhart123 @IHOP They took that hunk of plastic away from me but one of the employees retrieved it and gave it to… https://t.co/AxNJBUiioj]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏 felicidades por el gran melodrama que nos dio al publico @AmarAMuerteOf esperemos que tengamos segunda temporada… https://t.co/38O3FW6HS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacMizrahi @CBSThisMorning I was fascinated by you the first time I heard you interviewed when we were both much… https://t.co/CLqI9h8ejL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Norie57 @HuffPost I think the same about @JoyAnnReid  and @TheRevAl.  Ain't balance great?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hopwas2010 @FrazaKing Hello Ian. Do you hear wedding bells? Or the wedding bell blues? https://t.co/CjeoUj2a4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you see the way i look today, mind your business... i’m just trying to keep warm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SatSleepovers @ScoredtoDeath Looking forward to this. 2020 already full of interesting films.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tens14 It took me many moons to perfect my clothes organization skills. My ex used just put my clothes on the han… https://t.co/SrsDC9LQuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Virtue Cider Michigan Apple cans now available. https://t.co/qc6zyXxmlD @virtuecider #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why there's people complaining about the galaxy fold costing about 2k. It has like 6 cameras, 500 GB of storage… https://t.co/EZSPlbPG1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @ccatmpt @simplysallyh @jay_eatz @joneill55 @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @CaththeWineLady… https://t.co/GyYL2NkML3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashleyaddison12 I know several people that use it religiously and swear by it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se que por un mal dia no es mala vida pero ¿que se hace cuando va un mal año?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Linda91255450 Your right I must have superimposed your name: I’m getting tired. I apologize for my error.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Crazy irresponsible not tragic! Unreasonable ...why the students didn’t work or better yet decided on a comm… https://t.co/H8Xpx3KaVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN She has a good point; because we want it doesn’t mean it will magically happen. Steps, steps,steps. Make it a… https://t.co/2hKkjzFsxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked out this rad oasis in @aninsidersguide preserve! Listen to the fish! It was so freaky! And the wind in the… https://t.co/zOlvBhIEI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliee_alexiss @AmandaPietrzak tell me this isn’t the sweetest thing you’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met @JeanieBuss today aka someone I consider to be my idol wow my spring break could be over right now and I would be happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please place Dustin Crackhead Matters into Asylum in the dispostion of his loving limelight and Accountablity to Ki… https://t.co/3TskJI8ZId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riddle of the Sphincter! Mind you there are many including the one in your eye 👁 #BodyPartFilms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders This has to be a ploy just to get votes, otherwise you would tell the masses all about government’s pat… https://t.co/fnvGccOZZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm. Woke up wanting to let you know I'm sending prayers and warm, positive energy to your dad🧡 @theikawong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megankatenelson @CaroleEmberton My dad’s favorite is “slicker than deer guts on a doorknob”. (Tennessee)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s kids will never know about them tigers jumping through fire rings! 🐯🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join a great group of hard working educators changing the world one student at a time. Dedicated to Continuous Impr… https://t.co/Qie1gSFV63]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW your coworker is narrating everything she does. https://t.co/mj3VOCiUY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter Break 2019 with these jokers!  #toccoariver #blueridge @ Blue Ridge Mountains https://t.co/bxxF08Q2bJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Wow! No wonder you are being sued. You just refuse to tell the truth in any story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacklyn just came in my room, woke me up from a nap to ask if I would like to get in my swimsuit, take a bubble bat… https://t.co/27fJDDlE2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard on Fox Business that he paid the two brothers with a check! What an idiot! This has to be the easiest case… https://t.co/Spf2EYDjuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo tengo mi date de San Valentin’s este sábado con: https://t.co/i9pKs3hxhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabahzero I do volunteer bilingual child care at the local rape crisis center. It was honestly the only thing that… https://t.co/CHR3vACHAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers Good fucking question. So far they're pretty quiet abt the whole thing. That's prob a very bad sig… https://t.co/y8jiZPKou8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I die before @JonReynoldsESQ and St. Peter asks me to be a character reference, I’m definitely saying he changed… https://t.co/moozdUIXwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always appreciate what god has given you,  You really don't have a clue,  Look at people who don't have anything in… https://t.co/7vLE1RaUQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerrjoseph a perfect meme of how you feel about your fans when they bring balloons to the shows https://t.co/djKIu8KVAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yytitsahc I doubt it. I dat location. It ain’t too far for me to knock you out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad you enjoy being right more than you do about the feelings of those that love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicomx @FUERZA_MORENA @LuisaAlcalde @MeyerFalcon @yeidckol @tatclouthier @jenarovillamil Uf!! Por fin dijo algo R A Z O N A B L E!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our S. S. Conner Elementary Dr. Seuss Read-In was awesome! Thank you community volunteers, parents, and student rea… https://t.co/10puYUtcyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smirk for you. #humor #tee-hee #smile #laughable https://t.co/QG8aw9IMTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Done Sir!  VERY WELL DONE ! GOD Speed to You &amp; The marvelously Blessed People of your Country ! 🌐@POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Davon, one of the best Aqua Trainers @myaquaproject #nofilter #workout #water #cycling #hiit #spinning #boxing… https://t.co/OOks37SG3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[if he doesn’t care now, he never will and I’m sorry for that girl. I wish I could tell u 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monkees Singer and Bassist Peter Tork Dead at 77 #fridaymorning #oneofmyfavoritemusicians https://t.co/csjbGNxM66 via @RollingStone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SincerelyStayc @HEELZiggler @sarahtiana Aww how did you make that ? I need to make one for my dog but a bandana one :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m laying in bed this morning and my boyfriend got up and was in the kitchen for awhile till he comes in the ro… https://t.co/JgXcYDMqQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[and per usual I can’t be the savage I want to be cause my hearts in love smdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stepping into 7 like what!!! And yeah I’m your Valentine Birthday 🎂🎉🎊🎈🎁 2019 Avram 7 on Valentines Day!! My Valenti… https://t.co/UuSMeQYcWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HamOnt pals looking for some Saturday activities, this looks real fun (and reasonably priced). I can’t go, but you… https://t.co/29iYgriz3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IYAAYASammo62 @repcleaver @KMBZradio Gordy - I couldn't agree more.  The dems have become deaf and dumb to common sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not love a single soul on this planet as much as I love my niece 😩🎀✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the thoughtful woman who handed this gorgeous bouquet to Ginger for me last night @comedyworks for our #girlsinc… https://t.co/nJpWtPO2Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What???!!! I went up for a nap because we have a concert tonight (I work early) and it was 6-2 #Jays wtf ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird that every house in America doesn't have solar yet. Why? Leading with solar in California.… https://t.co/pISoySHeqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ma plus grande bénédiction ce sont mes parents. Je ne leur serais jamais assez reconnaissant 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexfitch540 @MillersvilleMBB YES BABYYYY😍😍😍Words cannot describe how proud I am of you. Can’t wait to watch your games:))]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta wonder  why so many are willing to lie for an international Criminal, what's he got on them or are they a… https://t.co/NMKcQ3fxu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful night for a soccer game! #tampabayrowdies @ Tampa Bay Rowdies https://t.co/0weYg2kfgo]]></document></documents></author>