<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Caitlyn Warakomski layers her #AnnaSuiSpring19 look for the winter season. https://t.co/EybZuhxe9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pappasito's Cantina - @pappasitostxmex in Houston, TX https://t.co/ISZLJgx9Ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that lie on social media to make their life (or something about their life) seem better than it is confuse m… https://t.co/iZZRJZmVhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st time seeing the #aguacalienteclippers... They won against the #southbaylakers .... Go #clippersnation !!! W/… https://t.co/Si8lGVKB20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherroCher @ShineSalty I say Lyndsey will be renamed in the penitentiary to Sweet Lindsey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Oversight Committee investigating 2018 Georgia election    https://t.co/lXplveBA43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can't imagine enjoying hearing you speak any time, any where!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello #metstwitter friends who has a fantasy baseball league i can join please and thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concrete Jungle. #LoveMyJob #NYC #SPECCronicles @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/PdCkBRX7L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signed up to volunteer @ all the special Olympics happening this year 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@measi @MBTA_CR Couldn’t have said it better myself. These system failures have significant impacts on people’s liv… https://t.co/AfqEwleHs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birbirini seven her şey güzel görünür. Bir karıncaya sevgiyle bakan çocuk da, yavrusunu hortumuyla itip yürüten fil… https://t.co/dn3oGjfXvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[we still love a woke bilingual king!! #throwbacktuesdaynightslashwednesdaymorning https://t.co/aAHPJlx4lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnnytaylor95 Like ok undoubtedly chickfila, in-n-out probs, altho FIVE guys is a dark horse, taco bell for SURE,… https://t.co/vXOp6MT8u7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom doing her best to support my hobby even though she doesn’t understand why I like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, let’s try this again, Mother Nature. First pitches coming at 11am! Be sure to check out our revised schedule… https://t.co/hMbjTvTKva]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joel is my rock star. Happy Sunday everyone. @ Wildflower Bread Company - Tempe Square https://t.co/fu0upBG2CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[While we celebrate #InternationalWomensDay, women in Saudi Arabia—a close United States ally—are being imprisoned,… https://t.co/xJYL9Nvf3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfkeeler @MonumentsForUSA @UtahDineBikeyah @ConservationLF @savebearsears @ROCKYOURMOCS https://t.co/4MZQ01kEnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angie_easley @OHS_CenterStage Congratulations on your People’s Choice and 3rd Place Award today!! @mymcpsva… https://t.co/nrwOfn3FYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it won’t be as good as @MichelleCreber or @rachelzegler or @ladygaga but tonight, I am doing a live cover of… https://t.co/PKmZy28sI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TOMS is an excellent example of a purpose driven company that truly walks the walk. I love following thier work an… https://t.co/l5SXZmMDV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streets are clear and Jaina finally feels better post op. Means we finally had a chance to enjoy the #snow . . .… https://t.co/vB1WQ8aFje]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do u have a mf 🌱 on the side pocket of ur bag? pokpok ka na talaga @Fynestchina]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Whoop whoooooop....More indictment ahhhhhhh hopefully jr’s name is on one of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you have to get up get dressed and go shovel, https://t.co/6Wh4SYXTDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an annual reminder to all men who don’t like buying flowers because they’re pretty but have no purpose and don… https://t.co/tZDQirDtaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotburrito9 @sarahshook @women_want_more I literally was about to say this exact same thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPapaPalpatine first woman i’ll watch get an egot asshole leave me alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remy heard a dog bark on our walk today and cried until i picked him up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who gets more pissed when I wear their clothes, @AlanaArmeni or @_dustin3v . I think it’s dustin lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for my bestie &amp; love seeing how far she has come since her surgery🤗🤗💪🏻 #proudbestiemoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’d to be out the cold and into the ocean back home 😩 I miss my girls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us know if you are joining in! Tweet out about it and Retweet to help get the word out! 📣   #TALEBookClub… https://t.co/9d6i6C4Rwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #nytimes I hold you responsible for the breakdown in families!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @NoLongerADem You were absolutely right.  I watched them go from the Right all the way to the #Left.  Sad. It’s all about them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The South End by @RedClayCider at @HouseofHops1 — https://t.co/QtMbDIVfET]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in supporting @KHS_BoysSoccer with a monetary donation, please contact @elllebsack  For $20 you w… https://t.co/Ms77kA3GoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Antony_Clements @TacoTimeNW @letitiawright @chadwickboseman They’re both cute though! Sorry to be shallow. 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine choices but please try something new. @CYDPdance CYDP: Celebrating 15 years (https://t.co/lHRweHB5lu)with chor… https://t.co/lGr3N1ziqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finna get cucked because my Loudcloud wants to STOP WORKING ON A SUNDAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showed my mom the new addition to my tattoo and she’s all “that’s nice sweetie” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A true measure of health is in your ability to recover. How fast can you move back into stillness. ✌🏼… https://t.co/uEJU1rspvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BodhisattvaKat @ellievan65 @Jim17930663 @RepBrendanBoyle @keithellison @BernieSanders how stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blueface cute I just need him to come up wit sum new dance moves and another song @bluefacebleedem]]></document><document><![CDATA[After-hike mocha and orgasmic carrot cupcakes from @creekside_az #Sedona #coffee https://t.co/iswFtYYYLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @SenatorTomUdall What a traitor to the American ppl.. thought better of you...sure was wrong..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNolanNation Baconscape...TM. 🤣 you outta consider trademarking this]]></document><document><![CDATA[😔im not haveing a good day today   my  bad  day  come  son bad news    my humben  call  me up  tell  me  he going b… https://t.co/SSzju4rE4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, likeX ll, I think I really NEEDED to read Electric Arches and know that this caliber of writing exisits and p… https://t.co/wmheAA0BG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@LCottler @UFHealthStreet talking about history of community engagement in research throughout the lifetime of… https://t.co/FuLWS9j25N]]></document><document><![CDATA[what is it about men with long hair that causes me to overlook any and all of their many faults]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeidiHallTN My husband has to get scanned every 6 months to make sure his kidney cancer has not recurred. It is a… https://t.co/qGGFnVvJnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You should come see me” a stranger ass nigga. Y’all don’t see how creepy that is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting in my quiet ass office and she starts roasting this dude and I LOSE my shit. Someone came over and aske… https://t.co/cdhEKAdS15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cryslatta Yeah...🙋🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️ I’m still waiting to get out of my awkward stage...🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abbott_Anne_ @SethAbramson @CNN @PeteButtigieg Again...how they propose to govern is the important part for me, no… https://t.co/hqN30d70Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PurdueRdSchool public safety UAS workshop is getting ready to kickoff. https://t.co/uzGX5TNrXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulldogBen @jhgurf @jilevin @jillwow @JoaquinCastrotx @JoeBarri @JohnnyBlkshrt @john_amor @johnconnisdead… https://t.co/uePZDY6pii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elgrizld If so this is the only legacy of Obama’s that Trump is keen to continue and amplify...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS Not a good actress but no not as long as they have her acting like an idiot! Get the old Hope back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter Boom! Totally gave it away. A #FakeTrumpEmergency  The American people should not have to pay for a campaign promise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a trip on #12south yesterday to the #bodieislandlighthouse in #nagshead #northcarolina &amp; the… https://t.co/7oAkrNWELi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard at employee Topshop meeting, “As Coachella nears we’re going to be seeing a lot more feathers. Keep your… https://t.co/Qr3HbJyJFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could care less about the headline!! But the pic represents the real spirit of WC and its basketball team!! So pr… https://t.co/lnWHv5kGkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfies after the show! #JoKoy #breakthemoldtour @ Peoria Civic Center https://t.co/PNOcWxODfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zlftcav2 @LindbergJulene @realDonaldTrump Psycho assholes! Anyone that claim these racist hat don’t stand for raci… https://t.co/2msEN0DgSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. We remember. We remember! We read ALL entries aloud. By the time we get to to CBNC, it’s been read multiple tim… https://t.co/QU1WqjGiMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janet just called me to ask about clásico regio .. her ass better bring me some ☹️🥺🙄💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the year of our lord 2019, please god no one keep listening to Kanye West.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turn up the music and stay on our phones the whole time. Is what me and @TheRealTobiWall do 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey, there runmeb  So nice to have you in the Ham!!!!  • • • #oisellevolée #bamabirds #venticoached… https://t.co/Ta9GkSLOgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goatsncrows You must be working tonight 😱  What sights have you seen so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarkPrinceLucy @realDonaldTrump .@realDonaldTrump @GOP @Franklin_Graham and Compsny, you agreed on Earth as it was… https://t.co/tP2l8TrHBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I could eat like 1000 pizzas right now. I want more pizza!” 🍕 #kindergartenquotes #relatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these amazing women getting leading roles on campaigns in advance is the best thing that could possibly happen! https://t.co/53Rqv2wNIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies I’m sorry for tagging you I just wanna keep up with you so I can remember who you are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating Professional Learning Networks are key as an educator!!! I’m so excited to see the connections these two m… https://t.co/MuicqJp32h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @JohnDingell you &amp; @TheDemocrats ANTI-SEMITIC, RACIST, KKK , SOCIALIST. PARTY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. Dirk knew Shai by name.   1000% sure he’s the smoothest dude on the Mavs. Don’t @ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @MikeChav32  Dom just woke up from a dead ass sleep and said “yo mikey!” 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yasminyrc @marthabtz @yelitza67 @esbores @Aiedayl @Jfhcr @mamuchis48 @claorellano @pgnora @geminchi… https://t.co/K1D4brsfyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s a man on the side of the road with a sign that says, “too ugly to strip, too dum to steal” and i felt that on a whole other level]]></document><document><![CDATA[After completing my morning Sudoku puzzle, this @PaycorInc add popped up! I’m so grateful that I work for such a fa… https://t.co/cjsbZiXaSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeannie_Moon 😲 Wonder if it had been reversed, young heroine older hero, if she would have thought it GROSS? 🤔  Wi… https://t.co/IwaUnNop0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[(with apologies to the, like, four? IU composers on here I still care about)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exciting to be able to see @e_mouchian and Grace Pulo from SJA in Sister Act! https://t.co/7m5t54TTtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constitutional Republic and I am President gold and money back due to the earnest Deposal of Donald Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can only hope you found a cure. It’s too late for my brothers, but better late than Never!😇😇😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been feeling baby kick but so far, not on the outside...until last night. Micheal raced over to feel it and pr… https://t.co/FkxwoQIX9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC what is  "beyond stunning" is your about-face regarding Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryLarmeu @jpretus Omg he just made me take photos! He’s going to apply! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rodeo Run 5K with @SuttonES_HISD Running Club! I love coaching these students and staff! So glad they have caught r… https://t.co/dvZW8h4AXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard_littler I'm...actually surprised that I didn't think this was a natural evolution of Vaporwave. Where Vapo… https://t.co/MEyREJegOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great reminder from @dsamuelsohn and @desiderioDC that Mueller will hand Barr not just the infamous special counsel… https://t.co/AAkUhoC1gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm back Sumbreo posse Lincoln's luck nups!😂 @ Solomon G. Brown Corps Community Center https://t.co/VUz3WjMwTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamieorians @SydneyOrians There is just something special about this team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love running into this one ☝🏼 @ George R. Brown Convention Center https://t.co/KQJlpTukmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to Sgt David Passmore and the US National Guard for their recent presentation on RESILIENCY to @ClarkeCSD… https://t.co/E8hQYoSO40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsRachelHooker I cheated and found out who won. Now I’m pretending to be surprised when the new episodes play eac… https://t.co/Ud1GF7g8A0]]></document></documents></author>