<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[They have the same music loop on repeat in the jury selection room. Our row has voted, it’s the opposite of relaxing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout ready to watch #Mizzou and Kentucky with @jakedesselle and @BlakeDesselle   Let’s go Tigers. Make it 2 in a ro… https://t.co/PKgRUXdqvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinVinny8 @tomsegura Looks nothing like him ... @tomsegura you going to stand for this imposter claiming to be… https://t.co/vUqbCKEFqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus wept, and so did I, preparing what felt like our last supper. How could I make her understand and be comforte… https://t.co/bkb6ui2y2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, what do we have to do to make MONDAY as good as Friday?? Don’t dread starting your week.  Wake up, think about… https://t.co/BTDXn5BRPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A question, the answer to which tells a lot to oneself about one's own character is this one:  "What would I have d… https://t.co/3AWDxJxNLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris @ewarren Her campaign is as lame as Hillarys She should quit now.  She has an EMAIL like issue.  Waste of time and money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanozIchimonji I’m a simple kind caring funny person so that’s what I put 😂 who is really shy sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌴TONIGHT🌴 If you havent witnessed the carter9882 band live you are missing a hell of a show! 🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶 Be in the B… https://t.co/rHIJ9BIThR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrTonyLeachon @jvejercito @bawasbisyoPH @raphbosano @joannarvaez @JoDiosana @DOHgovph Hard work and due diligence… https://t.co/TjHHjgLiSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a really good profile of a great reporter. https://t.co/sPOBuhliB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like most days I am not sure how to make sense of everything that just happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaVelleNeal Interesting @LaVelleNeal, I think Lecom (McKechnie) is one of the best...old school. Of course, I think they’re all great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS WEEK ONLY!! MARCH 4TH - 8TH THE DEBUT NOVEL "THE RED BRICKS OF KRUSCK VOL 1 TALE OF THE GUARDIANS" BY… https://t.co/m9PKvFvAhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorensamaro Concentração pro jogo do Galo! Professor @LevirCulpi não te liberou !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @BreitbartNews It’s pretty obvious, at least to me, the President has Carte Blanche when it comes to… https://t.co/MmrqXa9F1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[manafort under a new judge will get the full ten years to be added on his present sentence even though its wrong th… https://t.co/gUdL4ojWMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Event announcement from growatncf SAVE THE DATE! Join us on Sunday, February 24th for our Black History Celebration… https://t.co/NDkrLccVCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillsJM @JefeCochese Foster could be special but AB already is undeniably great. Give me the sure thing, not the dart throw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_A_McSquiffy @nhanh_hon @rgpoulussen That's actually a sad comment about the Crusaders and Matildas; slow, unreliable and undergunned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland at @bwwings — https://t.co/jsNSY7Kbjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missouri pitcher Madi Norman was once a Louisville pitcher. On Friday, she’ll get a chance to go against her former… https://t.co/RgVhp3wcKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonwalls @patricklee6669 @NaphiSoc @ReporterPhoenix @njterrie @felipem_santo @Catlady628 @JustWhatNowWhy… https://t.co/SPraLMu9sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning that as much as people actions may provoke me to respond I shouldn’t entertain negativity, I should focus… https://t.co/QaCpdtewH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyddsinna @__Wiegand He just became good like 2012 when he signed to good music .. he’s top 10 today tho .. but al… https://t.co/R6DLB1wjua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being up late is super wild to me. I’m so used to going to bed before 8pm every night so this is wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamAppleMusic on @TheTylt—I stream music from Apple Music https://t.co/zwWPLGvsaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you look at that! They’re actually praising fan art!!! Who would’ve thought?!?! Y’all leave my queen… https://t.co/IxwKAKw7bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJuiceJr Coming from someone praising a character saved by the Lord of Light😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys the opportunity to participate in.... (even include Jason In the question).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllemanIISS @RLHeinrichs @MichaelBerrySho @KurtSchlichter Scientific "consensus" has been overturned throughout hi… https://t.co/wJj83TEe1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to see if Brie can take her foot out of her mouth. #captainmarvel #marvel #sjwcringe #shareamc @ Century City… https://t.co/RLT0CLdt1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aún cualquier ruido por la madrugada me despierta con la esperanza de que seas tú.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton Well we no our government cannt make a decision unless they make money off the deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Titusville’s Hunter Thompson was defeated by Reynolds’ Beau Bayless in a 10-1 major decision in the 120 finals of t… https://t.co/WAk3238w1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amelia, Gary and Marty were there when I was and they are all fantastic! Made me smile to again see them on! https://t.co/bfUX5KXU5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorge Ramos said that he has criticized President Trump in a severe way and will continue to do so, but after meeti… https://t.co/09f4ijDaH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weekend is almost here! Time to par-tay 🕺🏾.. Question: who’s crazier, me or the cat? 😼 https://t.co/iZFGjWOgUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude my homee uod my ffijjfn im njottf finna be gordddabbed TJ be in the ihgddtsrdbhdgf a.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I go to enjoy a nice bowl of @NaturesPath Flax Plus Raisin Bran and discover that there are exactly three raisins in the entire box. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ednabug saw your embarkation video on your YouTube channel for your carnival sensation cruise. Really cool I’m sai… https://t.co/tY0pLPeG5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a White Shark Wheat by @hogislandbeercc @ Redface Jacks — https://t.co/qGAjX8rTqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the bond we had, i miss the laughs we shared, i miss your smile and voice. I miss the craziness we would cau… https://t.co/Aho9TJcqtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look y'all could've kept Venom out of this and no one would have cared #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJayLee22 @dirtlife0 @SMaxwellStory @DadSays4 @Shamusroan13 @sweatsntopknots @lilredtejas @DanielAshley13… https://t.co/ZYWLNXuXgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[50? Fuck that. This is the only time I'll ever agree with both Reggie and cwebb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STV1993 And you played for....please tell us about ur your hockey career]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was John Stennis not James Eastland who was the deaf senator Nixon asked to vet the Watergate tapes @RepAdamSchiff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis I enjoy these tweets, truly. But at what point do we stop laughing at this buffoon and ask him to sim… https://t.co/0yg4KroX2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[A goal by Jordan Morris and the crowd went nuts, a pretty emotional moment for Morris and the Sounders squad.   2-1 Seattle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like ole Aegon Targaryen gunna be riding Rhaegar in season 8 @rShather7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatShannon_ Yeah.. I’m a south sider lol only 3 miles. Pretty moderate incline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @Clear y'all got to figure out your bottleneck issues at @ATLairport 20 minute queue when TSA/Precheck is moving… https://t.co/NpJ4aO6cqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think of all shows “that 70’s show” was probably the funnest to film. Like it has to be such a blast to be a part of that cast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVE YOUR ARTISTS THEIR CREDIT BITCH... YOUR ASS WOULDN’T BE ON THAT STAGE TRYING TO CATCH THAT FUCKING NOTE IF IT… https://t.co/1J3XCQtUzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PsychicTerrain I hope your intestines can digest the iron bars of the law, buddy, cause it’s the clink for those r… https://t.co/CFA1oYPxNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's all about respect ! True Americans have respect for our President. Those who don't aren't Americans. They are… https://t.co/tiinH51itG]]></document><document><![CDATA[So #sad for our country, so many real issues to address and our Congress is defunct, because of hatred against the… https://t.co/iN2AdLzznI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody wanna draw me up a stencil for a tattoo that would incorporate the city of Austin and the state of Texas to… https://t.co/vJXYSB2QFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[TMZ Is One Robert Kraft Video Away From Helping To Vindicate Colin Kaepernick  https://t.co/jORgluqCeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been to a Utah-AZ game that was so poorly attended.  How much is due to VD and how much is apathy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayLogueTV @Uber Thank God you have a sense of humor. 😊👍 #supermom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefanvonimhof Brick and mortar is truly dead with apparel and people want some brick and mortar if only to provid… https://t.co/lZXJVNYBwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting that people who advocate for free market capitalism contend with Twitter’s right to implement any rule it sees fit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rhymes_with_Bat @EvanonHB That's cool. I'll try and talk them into running the triple option. That way we can get… https://t.co/bGN1OLbcoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a party that has demonized  China. The rivalry is real: China is a serious global competitor. But the langu… https://t.co/d26Wa7Y1nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Politicon @TomiLahren You should talk about echo chambers @TomiLahren. I'll be over there watching you embarrass y… https://t.co/GX6N2wlVr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarxBarl @olivepippi2 @tommyxtopher @MattMurph24 LOL Bernie is in favor of drone usage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it home after a good run, now time to get wet (and yes it's a bit cold, brrr) #miamibeach #miamilife… https://t.co/4fPlHiS4gX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfPainters @mitchellvii @RandPaul @LamarAlexander Check my bio. Bachelors in Economics. You're making ridiculous c… https://t.co/nLbjhVV0VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 so how long is this loading screen man... when are we gonna find out???? #dyingtoknow #philly]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Truly, truly a dream come true.”   @stevestricker choked up talking about being the 2020 Ryder Cup captain. Specia… https://t.co/L4JRPPccM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#quotesdaily #life #quotestoliveby #quotes #instagram #instagood #wedding #events @ Annapolis, Maryland https://t.co/l6j2ZNFEUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ArizonaSuperShow #FunkMachine @ State Farm Stadium https://t.co/6sNji0NghQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lotusfishicoot Nope, just wanted to add a weird moment that’d finally break Marvin, and a double duck Wet Willy se… https://t.co/4pDMJq2KYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will forever love this moment from with Dean and @ReneeYoungWWE ZERO hesitation on his part to confront them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always, excellent info from @photoshelter as 2019 plunges ahead....https://t.co/3dzYhMcG4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodmanJord What is your response to Miami New Times article ? https://t.co/UYelrqpnr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[China Panic – Today US Navy destroyer USS McCampbell sailed through the Taiwan Strait https://t.co/rIhJDUjbJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicken Bombs. Added pork loin down the middle for the win. #atbbq #tksundaychef #biggreenegg #shun @ Castlewood St… https://t.co/2jurI6MOhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[03/09/19. In 1974, Hiroo Onodo (pictured), Second Lieutenant, Japanese Imperial Army Intelligence, operating in the… https://t.co/GQWgnmsN3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mdowlingaz @NCSUgetinvolved He does look quite happy! I’m saving my favorite for Valentine’s Day 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough to do sometimes but we have to #beatthesnoozebutton 5,4,3,2,1 @melrobbins 5 Second Rule is amazing if you hav… https://t.co/dLiMnW9GJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes setbacks are just preparing you to be launched forward. https://t.co/a6pZgsZOsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again trusting @Kenzer704Parker with my life, heart and hair. Hasn’t let me down yet🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe My prayers are with your mom and that she is comforted by His everlasting love. I pray for you @JoeNBC… https://t.co/wSpnyjKjcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast of champions @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/9bKEoD7Hsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CruiseCountdown: 54 days until I'm #shipfaced on #NorwegianEscape https://t.co/gNYjen6UHE via @ShipMateApp https://t.co/i4IkLZxxdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShigBit @BAKKOOONN If the Boomers all wanna die, I wish they’d hurry the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bossanovas @eugenewei @patrick_oshag @benthompson @modestproposal1 Naturally, I made GIFs of when I created his im… https://t.co/mjo3OxDQuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NnikiTheBard @everquest I need that Fippy plushy, the watch and the books. I also need to get the discs for my EQ… https://t.co/WWrlbaUQ63]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auburn going cold and not making a shot? I feel like I’ve seen this before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @senatemajldr @SenateGOP Break from your mold of the educated idiots Republicans, the vessel of Trump a… https://t.co/bYt7zKQcp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi! Certified 2016 #BernieBro here.   If you believe in the causes @BernieSanders advocates and you love this count… https://t.co/X3C1QDVU1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaidersBeat Sign bell, trade 2nd rd for Brown, trade #4 for pick between 10-15 and a 2nd rounder. Draft Metcalf th… https://t.co/A086yTh8hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump just another example- I’ve heard stories of your visits to IN were you stopped and talked with pol… https://t.co/OEVyEXiF5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC Can you square these statements with your assertions that the investigation is nearly done? Were yo… https://t.co/qaN1Eob0qG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buttigieg’s answer is good. But these moments always remind me that most politicians struggle to seem calm and sinc… https://t.co/y0W4QJMUJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE BITING FROST (oil painting detail) - Maj. Frost, C Coy. 2nd Parachute Btn. Bruneval Raid, France 1942… https://t.co/CKfdeXfUC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNews He never was accused of being a racist in fact quite the opposite has tons of awards from minority organiz… https://t.co/eVN98yvAOk]]></document></documents></author>