<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you @CoachGSoccer for a great practice with @ChallengeSoccer tonight.  So happy the weather cleared up just i… https://t.co/fTfuesepeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[One is better than none. One view is better is better than none. It means at least one person cares. #SMBCME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you heard of Yamazaki? Just kidding, of course you have. Yamazaki is Japan’s oldest distillery and one of the… https://t.co/0pggFzI2Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m concerned that people will think I’m a narcissist because my mom blew up a picture of me and Des told her to put it in our LIVING ROOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Gas Stati… https://t.co/aq9suUR6ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited for this next step in my life! I will not break the news yet to anyone until it is official! 🥰😁    Lets… https://t.co/WnCe5Upltk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just really liked  this filter...😘😘 @ East Harlem https://t.co/3GmHz5IvGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marie02434580 She sure would have!! Forever love Mother Clair Olivia Hanks Huxtable!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to think we’re actually getting complacent to historic water rises on local lakes and rivers. If 2011… https://t.co/E7I1Pnzypm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Universal Tribe Energiser of the day  "I can look at you through my eyes. But I will only ever see you through… https://t.co/7rmtgqYR37]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to unleash my inner Bob Ross tomorrow @bouncyashley28 https://t.co/uWo2Eg8RTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess it’s a thing these days to hang out at Wawa late night if you’re in high school? So crazy to me..a wawa??🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally crying at the fact that I just left my parents this morning to move to utah to start my own life with my… https://t.co/2ZPzOESgYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is interesting to note that prior to Trump’s nomination for the GOP presidential nomination, many to most though… https://t.co/msNtmFwDy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of advertising... I literally decided to lease a new Subaru for my son rather than buy an older model use… https://t.co/Ss09Y5IF8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[For whatsoever things were written aforetime were written for our learning, that we through patience…… https://t.co/vZayLUXwWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ye of little FAITH ... TOLD YOU.. HE'S GOT THIS ! HASN'T LET US DOWN YET.... PUTTING GOV. EMPLOYEES Through another… https://t.co/auRE10aNgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sccsd #SCCSDCTE #SiouxCityCareerAcademy #21stCenturySkills #CareerTechEd #CTEworksforIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Audit Project Manager - Fixed Income Capital Markets" at U.S. Bank, th… https://t.co/zM59kjOpmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollycrabapple @TheTurbantor 20% of Israeli citizens are Arab Israelis including a supreme court justice that indi… https://t.co/TlLcD2JLeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @funder Fox News is a joke! O’Reilly fired for sexual harrassment.  Tucker Carlson defending child… https://t.co/Z2MlkIDlFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAby4thepeople @DawsonSField @woodseysmith Last I heard he is teaching at NYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AIRBORNEJAG01 @Lisanicole08 @BrianKarem That’s heartbreaking because it’s true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Monday friends!!! I’m going to tackle that to do list now! Details of what’s new in #March are coming as wel… https://t.co/kGM8kB40wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FriealityShow: for #InternationalWomensDay I spent several hours at the *California Institution for Women* in Chin… https://t.co/lziX6xsx6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My faith is strong in a Higher Power and I'm a Christian. But why are some Christians so judgemental? I believe in… https://t.co/TUElIUlDWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amara &amp; the General🐱❤️ #waitingfortreats #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #blackcats #gingercats… https://t.co/q7i6ae91ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you guys haven’t watched The Umbrella Academy on Netflix yet then you are missing out,  I ONE HUNNID% loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KONTENTLY @StableGeniusRN @KevinMKruse I think you just changed my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time softball season rolls around I get #fomo so bad. I miss it 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really want to get a “happy thoughts” hoodie but like they are sold out 🤧💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary I love twitter 💜💜😩 https://t.co/nEJkdCFG7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATBCMovie @guyguido @m_scrapbook @madrevo1 @madonnas_fault @MadonnaBible @MadonnaNowMedia @MadonnaNation… https://t.co/2Evk6kruW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanneSkyttar @cultureddairy @tgminish The plan is that the calf will stay on the cow but I am prepared if somethin… https://t.co/Ca6gilgklP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Booker told Colbert: “One of my friends says we have a criminal justice system that treats you better… https://t.co/0xK1kdXQ0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamShatner If you lick off the icing, you have a sweet muffin, right??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlmarino1 Ok, obviously you don’t know the answer either.  So, therefore that means you are a fake.  That’s a sh… https://t.co/cqGSOUbeL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting article on Oppositional Defiance Disorder. https://t.co/9dSpM8PGqC #CEtribe #edchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCastleSM biiihhhh wind was so disrespectful it blew it here! I picked it up &amp; knew it was yours right away!]]></document><document><![CDATA[drove 4 hrs to see the @raptors get nerfed by the refs and had no @littlecaesars pizza 😢 @ Little Caesars Arena https://t.co/fndTXDQZhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[those nights in black leather... 6yrs ago to the day before moving to Hawai'i ✌🏽.   #tbt  #tenderloin… https://t.co/4dLAakS0tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach__Hensley @madisonhhensley Awesome job to the whole team great defense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaushib1 @zapier @MendocinoFarms @klipfolio You’ve built so many incredible tools for me, it’s about time I return the favor! LOL! 🤣❤️🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo corriendo de acervos a nocturna cuando nos corren a las 6:30 antes de que se llene la sala https://t.co/WwnF2L00GK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not afraid of flying but if these Boeing 737 MAX planes don’t get recalled for an investigation I’m not flying on them]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s raining, I’m watching tv in bed with my dogs...and a whole sleeve of Thin Mints  DOES IT GET ANY BETTER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Manhattan Beach, California https://t.co/P5REtIggVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostgirl11 @NGDAverk @AlliCamAllison @VillainPeterPan @darker_dearie @hjhollis93 @Danielle21A @tweetNorvena… https://t.co/Am9o8iAwae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iggy gets a snack #iggy #white #egret #hungry #lookingforfood #birdsofinstagram #celebratewhatsright #iphonexs… https://t.co/H6V7uMI51Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you hear @WSMVHollyT say there’s cookies in the newsroom — but you’re out in the field 😐 https://t.co/q6LBf5QMdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I'm so excited to get my borderlands vault symbol tattoo in the next few months.  I love that game series]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK I live above our coffee shop, so I always vote coffee.  I’ll have you a pour over in no time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @bosstetter_edu to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, just covers.  Eac… https://t.co/TFGklSDsUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spenad06 LMAOOOO thanks for treating my friend and our weritoss so nicely 🥳🥰🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got us some new swag from @mvmtwatches 😍😍 blackkkk 😍😍  Also! 4 more months til Iceland! 🤯 @ Detroit, Michigan https://t.co/rCx9A0v5GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @HBO decides to show that slanderous fake news film starring a proven liar Wade Robson I will never watch anythi… https://t.co/3xtyPlWvhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpac2006 OPRIMIDO ACHA NORMAL UM CARALO. ISTO E A DESCULPA DO OPRESSOR. ELE NAO SOMENTE OPRIME MAIS CULPA AS SUA… https://t.co/TjGtw3w9KU]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let’s review - you are a young person standing in your grandma’s back yard, with your cell phone in hand, and ar… https://t.co/AgAxoquFra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meneses_J10 @Eunice_Flahh @jaayferr08 Hahahaha what does this remind you of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Testifies: Repupublican Reps: It’s all your fault Trump is innocent!!! Dem Reps: You still suck but give us ALL THE TEA!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @Dracaenawines @ccatmpt @Cbp8Cindy @thatsVeryKari @AkronWineGuru @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz… https://t.co/w9WDlE25If]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyjones_03 @jacketsfan73 I’m jealous that Janice gets to meet you! ❤️❤️❤️ your tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is actually so sick rn. Paid all my parking tickets from when Iived in LA. Big girl things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering a time on this #216Day when many of us used to be in the 216, then changed to the #330.  Circa 1996. https://t.co/DWjUUan3NV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue All people deserve choices Instead of only the wealthy few #eduvalentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever thought about being a Clinical Scientist? An opportunity to join GE has arisen in MA. Check it out!… https://t.co/v25qKMflO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dyams @ConservativePTZ @RyanAFournier Haha. Hilarious. You are very clever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPodolec @WestJet @AirCanada @SunwingVacay @flightradar24 Tom, is it the BM38 that show us it is the 737 Max? IF… https://t.co/IeXdd1qSAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Sadly the dims will look for something else to discredit you and your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #COP  MURDERED a #CHILD...And For NO REASO!!   He does #NOT deserve a badge!    Demand the #MURDERER  of Tamir… https://t.co/zD7gTCFgP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[👇🏽What he said.   The public is tired of hearing that investing in a safety net will slow growth.   Growth without… https://t.co/dYgPR2awPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoughlinTara a year ago today, i’m not crying you are 😭 https://t.co/XX0pNfEK9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Chantilly and Culinary students for the great Fat Tuesday meal!! @tcwchef @TCWCTE https://t.co/NMJEi7hl58]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je pars dans deux jours pour le Yukon ! Je retourne à la maison pour 10 petits jours ! Pendant que tous le monde pa… https://t.co/oTxtI9V0dD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Thursday thoughts my dear family friends from all over the world 🌎 Enjoy your Thursday with people you lo… https://t.co/Q6UGAaN1qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demar19671969 @WolfVivienne007 @MoishesMom @isabenfica51 @VeganRam @patla_rina @JAHIR_RINKU @soldier_777… https://t.co/FkaCEWS65q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFPDTenderloin The TL is the best community! The room was full of some awesome community members who are doing ama… https://t.co/XHny4vi4sK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeronim81322756 @ahope71 Pobre Peje, ahora, muchos no lo quieren, por no ser productivo.  #100DiasDeMentiras]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweepla @WilliamdeVry1 @TheWaterFairy @RosieClaire10 @GeneralHospital I LOVE Alexis! #bekind my ass!! More like #cyberbully!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone ever calls you a whale, take it as a compliment, because whales are the most delicious of all the cracke… https://t.co/2muljP7NSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachermrw @MrKitMath I find it interesting that it’s difficult for them to address race.  I actually was told tod… https://t.co/C1GdJ16XmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not much information at this time. Working to gather more. This is still an active crash scene under investigation.… https://t.co/ODXr7TyoSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinceMountain There is no better way to make an anthropologist immediately break into a cold sweat than to sugges… https://t.co/YcTvgt4Kxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter lost a good four legged member. RIP Zoey. Never turned me down for my random adventures, afternoon naps, or… https://t.co/V8W2cRis3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all of you ....much love , today and always ❤️❤️❤️😘 #happyvalentinesday @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/Y4Q8DiUQf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I managed to save that failed crystal from a while ago! #resin #resinmolds #resinart #resincasting #diy #witchy… https://t.co/OGACLAs1al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter nights are shades of grey. #snowing #nofilter @ Arlington, New York https://t.co/UvTBHAtcvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR @TheMandyMoore I’m just wondering what Parker Posey’s take is on all of this. Like Weinstein, why are we just… https://t.co/pRPXiynEBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to Drybar to get a blowout. It’s International Women’s Day. Wear purple ladies. #internationalwomensday… https://t.co/m2hrRTfu69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_liizzz Oh no 😭😭😭 I have my nose pierced and have survived through two tattoos but I’m scaredddddd 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Antioch #CA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/ZgUAW2NLmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pyIi1VKCp6: Heart attack signs and symptoms are different for women: Heart Health 2019.… https://t.co/6WwynkxUJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i took the over on how long jack would talk about dougie hamilton wearing a retired whalers number and i’m severely… https://t.co/NMvCd0K9SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@midnightamerica @KarenMonsour12 @MichaelMancare1 @LionelMedia @Scotus Absolutely, Lester. She should be replaced! 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆 "The Favourite" and ''Roma" win big at British Academy Awards - https://t.co/v3hGBGHNW4 #OscarsOn2 #AcademyAwards… https://t.co/hI7osNOngI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_jvxiiii @CoachRCooper @coachmarksmith @coachchadmorris @_kbolden @samspiegs @Ship28 @Gbrooks5_ @Dev_Bush1… https://t.co/YhSR346rAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelborger I realize the AHL is the stepping stone of young players but, there is also the older players who wi… https://t.co/jgvvQCYddi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex’s sister video called me and got so excited to see my baby bump 😭💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[This flowering abundance, in FEBRUARY! @ First Presbyterian Church (W-S) https://t.co/4YoLySpwna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coloradio_Eng Is it??!?! I was gonna say no, but then... I mean. Cold soups exist. My potatoe soup uses milk. Awww]]></document></documents></author>