<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So signing big names brings ticket sales? Shocker.  And the rangers expect to sell out a that new stadium next seas… https://t.co/WBAupJ7OCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OllyAitch @MooseAllain @andyibbs @ellenwordperson Ha! I had to read that 3 times before I got that she was saying she was “hāve”!! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished cycling 0.73 miles in 8m:05s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/DcFDDTQucm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out they’re cancelling The Punisher on Netflix https://t.co/8goLcWrXVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Base_Knocks @HelmetAddict had the same lunch box. that is all  so wonderful. being a footbll coaches son. i had an… https://t.co/VgSqGKNdz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muhammad198819 @ASavageNation Yes, she is an intelligent woman- filled with hate and bias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[gofundme for jassy correia’s daughter &amp; family https://t.co/jbCxFxUnQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[stuck in the maze, everything’s okay but it’s not really okay, my life’s a death race @ Cleveland, Ohio https://t.co/Q9ATiwGQgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IHboog @BootscootinGMaw @birdfarmerswife @dbatie @DozaEric @FarmChicJodi @GardnerKatyg8 @AtlantaAgCurt… https://t.co/yvqKac1zdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venmo I followed the link, went to the app and was not given the option for the rainbow  one. Can it be changed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PureMichGirl I am ALL #TRUMPREELECTION and I live in Volusia county, we are a #TrumpRed county #MAGA #KAG2020  #TrumpPence2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeesaRaaum @MBOKSR_MAGA I would wear a maga hat if it wasn't for morons like this Clown po💩 #LiberalismIsAMentalDisorder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching all these ranked teams eeking out wins over unranked teams or losing to them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greeted by this as I was getting coffee this morning. You never know what you’re gonna see. #adventureswithcharlie… https://t.co/YHjasKmgSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! #valentine #love #heyyou @ Koreatown, Los Angeles https://t.co/4Grj8DOEEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@true_pundit Given her recent anti Semitic remarks; her incestuous marriage to her brother and her defense of Isis… https://t.co/KUL5bn9bds]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DON’T like mustard but I love whiskey and this right here is EVERYTHING!! If you love me, send me bottles of this… https://t.co/4s0HzXtKQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Bipartisanship usually involves Republicans caving on whatever the Democrat party wants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBermanFox26 @astrosCTH How high on the list is their payroll now? So we can dream with a number and a FA attached to it.  🤗😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q4 Also the dichotomy of Black leaders. King vs X and Booker T Washington vs Dubois... teaching children that their… https://t.co/6rmmU13sZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarinColville @CunningSq16 @elizabethspinn @donaldhatesyou @unbrokeMs1 @runPattirun @Miduswell @JCoker13… https://t.co/FcYkRZmjtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pirates with a 7-0 run to open the 3rd, lead 35-22 with 6:25 left in 3rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZimmersEars @JimmyTraina Toby Flenderson. His character was too pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlickmanMr I can't ever go clean shaved and expect to be comfortable through a long shift at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfroJediii *speaks from side of mouth* and the multifaceted art of Toni Morrison by Steven Underwood https://t.co/KeuJyKDylW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is hypocritical for teachers to demand respect from students  when they themselves will not respect a presentati… https://t.co/DCcx6zisBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoarinOverWDW @missjoannamarie Deal. I actually enjoy working out, it's reeling in the diet that's hard for the 1st 2 weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tammyanddavid1 @OnlyHearSeeHate @Busydee_ @AndrewWeeraratn @alley167 It's time for us to regulate our government a… https://t.co/huhc33faV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guatemala Intel Head Says Caravans 'Well-Planned,' Not Spontaneous https://t.co/WdwGVoAwAj via @BreitbartNews The D… https://t.co/HTWLsY8tEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to spreading the good word about avoiding peri-intubation hypoxia and safer intubation with the… https://t.co/pvK09JGbxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFLDestroyers when do tickets go on sale? I want to take in a couple games. I was a fan of the original destroyers… https://t.co/MgJWq7lpjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no other. Whataburger has the #2 and #5 meals that drive me insane. Their fries are wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desckknowsbest @RealCandaceO Lmmfao dude stop you're nothing but a DEPLORABLE racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to be honest, that Roy Williams vertigo deal is bullshit! I'm sorry he has health issues but a delay of g… https://t.co/wpgAnd6qf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee Conspiracy: Cup 13 - EG Claunch Illustration https://t.co/pYQmbL9YWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezshabot @NoticiasMVS ...la 4T. Una voz más que se intenta silenciar; como otras voces y otras plumas. Ni el medio… https://t.co/XoTW2Rf4vY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hopadillo IPA by @karbachbrewing at @themuckyduckbar — https://t.co/KXgSxQSSI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N565UA Because universal child care will of the same"high quality" calibre as universal healthcare.... 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broadly, the law requires @BmoreCityDOT to promote biking, walking, and transit and pursue eliminating health, econ… https://t.co/PLsXElG7Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Spanish radio broadcast for #NYCFC with @RobAbramowitz so ... is your time to shine @GlennCrooks .. watching gam… https://t.co/TWWtORx2mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great blog post from my good friend @philip_ciwf https://t.co/DeESScHw8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgreatmom @realDonaldTrump #CreepyOldFatOrangeLyingTRAITOR #RacistGrifterSexAddict]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeFriender @rachaelpacella I take seriously those who engage seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strawburry17 @SheriCamarena Oh no! I'm so sorry to hear that! Seriously wishing her and you the best, and that everything turns out fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGGYAZALEA when is this single coming out. Im bouta be put on life support for it bein so long gurl😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheilaPierce51 @Jimi_Jammin @cedarflats @Tridon1955 @JamesHo03148924 @hqt__ @ZalewskiLaw @RonaJawetz… https://t.co/VOzUU2Kguv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahadevsharma So the same team that won 95 games that had no KB for 60 games, basically no Darvish, and the whole… https://t.co/0DjOITejyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kop205Row37 @samdownes4 Mate to be fair, 9/10 if I have a coffee after 3, I feel at my most productive at like 2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Backing up is not the same as backing down’ @levine_alison  #BerkshireHathawayHomeServices #AllIn2018 #GoodToKnow… https://t.co/2lrkYmVQp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Caramelized Chocolate Churro Baltic Porter by @moodytongue @ Flying Saucer Draught Emporium — https://t.co/jfCTDBGJYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeWept I disagree.  Democrats are constantly classifying people by different ethnic groups.  I do not see Conservatives doing that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIP: Miami has offered QB Evan Prater, who has already set a date to visit Coral Gables. https://t.co/BzPPp2hOCc https://t.co/MJdRs01NCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[CASSEROLE??? WHY IS THAT EVEN AN OPTION? ITS A PIZZA! NOW DELETE THIS AND STOP DISRESPECTING MY PPL MOTHERFUCKER! 😡… https://t.co/hXedW4mEEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP to the Norman Foster Building that used to be here. Fortunately it’s Vegas so something will inevitably come up… https://t.co/FfIvM555Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breakthechains #godheals #yourpastisyourpast #movetowardsabrighterfuture #godisgood #FallForwardandgetbackup… https://t.co/dtcffmcQeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then we go out for “drinks” @ Dragon's Ultra Lounge https://t.co/5TFXqjyQZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some art I was working on that I saw from Reddit , art and music keep me calm and maintains my sanity https://t.co/ugJEIRNYy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[After falling behind 24-8, Memphis has outscored Wichita State 50-25. At Koch Arena. The #Tigers responded to getti… https://t.co/Dupukn3R2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlights from tonight’s loss at Northwestern State 💙🧡🐺 #DawgsUp https://t.co/ss42Y4Xofx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenlooper @KimMaida Degree in Pottery Making. I also use everyday. No one can spin up a container like me 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melreynoldsU If he was with the Coast Guard and amassed this arsenal and was this filled with hate, imagine the nu… https://t.co/8ugtCJ05UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillsFGSN Not a fan of this move. I think this will come back to bite them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does “Jersey Assurance” mean @AmericanExpress ? Like, if I stain my jersey with buffalo wings you’re gonna pay for the dry cleaning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know where it went wrong for Smollett? He never thought the Chicago PD would catch the 2 guys he hired. He coul… https://t.co/5vTT6NCM8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinThomasNY The NYS Senate and Assembly are useless partisan bodies. You do nothing for the citizens of the Stat… https://t.co/0HPGID1d2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Mexicali, Baja California https://t.co/9boxgOfOSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very blessed 🙏 and happy Friday campers! Thank you God for another day 🌞 and for herbal tea  with honey 🐝  Listen… https://t.co/5z4ebDphXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 Born in the dark, nourished on shit (as the saying goes), a toxic amanita variation, but utterly tasteless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted a challenge from @CoachTonyPec to post the covers of 7 of my favorite books, no explanations. I will the… https://t.co/MrTgX8XjEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usmcsoonerfan I am pleading the 5th but it very well may be related to OU/Tex weekend. Hey. It happens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever get so drunk that your head starts to spin, yeah same. That was me tonight after I downed a pitcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this FAT WHITE man asked me if I was Salvadoran, Mexican, Honduran, Puerto Rican, Colombian ugh no season will always be flavorless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HallmarkHubby @HallmarkiesPod @HunksOfHallmark @anunderdogxo I'm experiencing existential crisis.  What am I suppo… https://t.co/7aMishCyEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay away from people seeking attention by pretending to be happy,  And  People pretending to be miserable just to get attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and start your day with Morning Brew, the email covering the latest news from Wall St. to Silicon Valley.… https://t.co/y9Hl6SZxFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing Business with Broward County!!🏖🌎 _________________________________________ Great Learning opportunity about t… https://t.co/GK4TC3yGwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseCanseco By the way you used your head when you tried to catch that ball and it bounced into the stands for a h… https://t.co/ZzF5Rsxe2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPN_Beisbol @marwingonzalez9 Va a acabar aceptando las condiciones de Houston]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saudiboiz @_AntStacks_ As a guy who loves puns. This is my favorite today thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather celebrate both teams players and success this season rather than live in the past and dwell on a call.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iiRetroZ @_SJPeace_ Educate yourself about the history of US Immigration laws and how US govt has destabilized Lat… https://t.co/6Tm9mMLtcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALF: Shady Spring 17, Bluefield 16. The Tigers’ Stephen Williams leads all scorers with 8. Braeden Crews with 5 for the Beavers. #wvprepbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @PopChassid “Disproportionate treatment”? I suppose that would depend upon what angle you’re viewing from. You… https://t.co/8WzWGS8CZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boeing stocks down 5% since 2nd crash of its new 737 Max. Several airlines ground planes since crash. Uncertainty s… https://t.co/La56xbGiXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richmintz I think they were great for quick long distances that would be too far for a walk. Washington DC blocks… https://t.co/JNZHXzKJWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DumfriesMorton @Politicalpete55 @SweChris97 Not true is the sense of being true. Is that what you mean? The SNP kn… https://t.co/TWKBjXkmSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starting_five5 You get paid for this dribble??? Contreras sucks! Grandal can't catch the ball, watch last year's p… https://t.co/3RSvJp4DTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#107: Housing (Part 1)  Along w/ the creation of shotgun houses, AA would popularize porch sitting. As simple of a… https://t.co/Lzz5ZiqyqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheesebox195 @HeyHeyItsConrad @PrichardShow All I want to know is does Bruce call it WrestleMania X8 or 18]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dailydrewism #drewism #BeTheChange #btc #stopandsmelltheroses https://t.co/PJTHB24bZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we need to do isn't complicated... Stop the human traffickers. Stop the drug traffickers. And #BuildTheWall!… https://t.co/IXgGRGGqLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best leg drop in the business! @HulkHogan would be proud. @WWNFIP @WWNACW @WWNEVOLVE @WWNLive @AJSlambino… https://t.co/d8zrZ0FudR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy has a conspiracy theory: Meryl Streep,  Glenn Close and Alan Alda are the same person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delaneyacarter Bitch go on somewhere looking like a turtle with no neck. @IGGYAZALEA is way more successful than you will ever be. 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crazysal5 @chuyjuarez @realDonaldTrump Lol. I see no reason to go bearish yet technically speaking. Wouldn’t be su… https://t.co/yUnUe6oZWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The CFD folk in the WTI trading chatroom are discussing this #OOTT https://t.co/TGHecW0kRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time the heat quits,  Ricky: I'm going to Britt's Brett: I'm going to Claire's Me: We meet again, 6 blankets and a space heater]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheelhouse. Thanks for the taste Dave. - Drinking a Barrel Aged Imperial Stout (Mothership Series) by… https://t.co/ZcE1A9xTVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Carolina week! Best birthday present I can get is a @DukeMBB W on Wednesday! #GTHC #ourblueisbest]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think you like that red berry wine,,,,,, what about that BlackBerry https://t.co/8r3elJGPBK]]></document></documents></author>