<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila What part involves the Trumps...surely there is a money trail there ...move the capitol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand. Good boy! Stand. Goooood!  . That’s all. It’s not a perfect free stack and it’s not a hand stack, it’s just… https://t.co/FhnKn0LLWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you work with wildlife in a bilingual context, please DO NOT translate wild = salvaje. It has very negative conn… https://t.co/i1SCGk7Fe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dem Bucks and Eagles have a nice arena. I hope they enjoyed my yells of “KARMA” thru their arena after… https://t.co/er5V8hRqry]]></document><document><![CDATA[uh ya’ll know ima be at cardi b singing  my lungs out 🗣🗣🤪🤪  oh and men are trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially given our #orthodontist my first born child! Both boys are officially a part of the #braceface club… https://t.co/wCCI1TJPy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grifter @TMobile grafting with @realDonaldTrump   Disgusting   #TMobileTuesdays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eekazn @edeneranon @awkwafina @gemma_chan @jonmchu @jennyhan @lanacondor @ConstanceWu @CAPEUSA I agree. AsAm as a… https://t.co/wogO2mQnp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My drive today made me forget I’m sick. It was simply stunning. @ Borrego Springs, California https://t.co/XmvQ2dHHJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol and as if me being a liar means anything since I was stating an opinion. People disagreed with me,  FRIENDS dis… https://t.co/PqQ8PnLrSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetsGetStoned00 @ajonsiegirl420 @Krktbrousseau1 @Artizzahn @rustman_the @JonnyRotten1714 @Carreenv1 @laurajax1… https://t.co/G1zZb1z474]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad we have a system in place that interrupts all we are doing, to find a lost child. There isn’t a tv show… https://t.co/wV0w66qArO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day the shop is open I will be showcasing an artisan. Every one is unique in their creativity and I am honore… https://t.co/IeWIKQWxt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @rowen316 Delusional. Just listen to one recap of pelosie or AOC. Absolute morons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad to hear about Luke Perry... He was one of my favorite actors growing up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read the book Friday, meet the author Monday! See you soon @danielmiyares! https://t.co/8acgwu8KXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have made great progress de-stigmatizing #gastropsych treatments but have more work to do to make these approach… https://t.co/3mpS98Nnl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m too in my head tonight and it’s keeping my physically and mentally exhausted self from sleeping. Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rvG9vbU5pL ahhhhhh!  I am INLOVE with this song!!!!!!!!!🤩😍🤩💙💛🔥🔥🔥🔥🎶🎶🎶 @sentimentfalls #iRememberYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOOOOOOOOSE @BazTastic77 @isabelle3474 @Diverboy44 @Crushinat0r @HeyDesiree @EPCATDork]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Weather Approved!🌻  🛍Playa Shift Dress  📍11 South J Street,  Lake Worth,  Florida   💻https://t.co/tGei6YP2N6… https://t.co/PI2fAz3oIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richdavisphd Man, tetanus isn't something anyone wants and if you go outside ever you're at risk. I can't believe… https://t.co/1OUtDTkacr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikey_huertas_ I would but you know I already have someone throwing shade at me for not doing it myself so I’d rat… https://t.co/mPjOYqob57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump We need a REAL President! https://t.co/KQTZXFLSX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[3) B- practical and symbolic value. “I would like to be able to take out my pocket Constitution and say that the eq… https://t.co/UiDXlE3wJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guided Reading with a little 💜❤️! Standards, text sets, and table matches are so much more fun in Valentine attire!… https://t.co/qTRcD5ITq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom watches Spanish Novelas on Netflix once and now this is how she speaks lmaoo bless her heart 😂💕 https://t.co/Cp4AyclIrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAY I hit 804! I can't believe I'm so close to 1K followers! https://t.co/rubWOZl5wr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roleplayers_TV I want your boobs in my life. To be fair.... I'm a transwoman and my closest girl friends all have nice boobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuggets have been suggested and SWIFTLY shot down with no explanation. This is a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I fell asleep at 1030 and today I can't sleep , my sleep schedule is a joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff Repubs Say God Made DT Pres.I'd Agree God Allowd Him To B Pres So His Corrupt, Dishonest,Immoral Bhvrs… https://t.co/mEYIpTiEc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OFemmeFataleZ It makes me crazy. The Democrats better start blow back on this soon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a seat, but bring a blanket. #ice #winter #collingwoodharbour @ Collingwood Harbour https://t.co/3LQNXpRljj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GwenLigaya When u reacted on my tweet and based on your effort to research, should i say u are okay with it? Hurt… https://t.co/JYvNF7LAhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This photo perfectly captures my mood after seeing meangirlsbway.   It was full of pure joy and I was beaming the w… https://t.co/1dZPNb010D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @debratankersle1 @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM @MyEngland2016… https://t.co/nC8yl85a7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @RussianDoll was amazing. (and not just because of my attachment to time loop stories!) We watched it all in on… https://t.co/ppVTRX0ro4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronxcore @madisonleigh_94 Ur right. My best friend’s wedding too. Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoisesLopez47 @Lisa130f13 @katefamoconnor @JamieRaee14 @simon_jrees @Stephan66424700 @AdventuresinOR @aprilgc777… https://t.co/SRskcLs5bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the wait. Great presentation @movie_pundit - thanks for confirming my preconceptions on the usefulness of und… https://t.co/z0IIVoa6As]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Look at this!    It looks like Charlie has forgiven Lily for eating his banana.  He is actually sharing his lu… https://t.co/1rrM1f6gNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingNLive America and Congress:  Take notice....this is what the Democrat Socialists aspire our country to be!!!!!!  Horrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webster Two nuts desperate for relevance. I guess their Instagram accounts just aren’t doing it for them anymore.🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[A real lady would never disclose her “digestive blowout” situation to a gentleman.... come on now. #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[So impressed by our emerging leaders this week! This group is committed to quality service and fulfilling our commi… https://t.co/TkWhPD3RuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Share your snow day with us. We're seeing snow in Fredericksburg, VA right now. Send pics… https://t.co/eWhlFCKicA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Media that has inquired. This is the 18th officer involved shooting investigation that the #GBI has been requested to investigate in 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cognizant is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #BusinessMgmt job openings, including "Customer Service… https://t.co/9dmvKTmymo]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh my god we’re trying to set up venmo for my dad (age 65, bad at technology) and we’re trying to answer security q… https://t.co/0K1zPOseae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helx101 @thehill @DonaldJTrumpJr Also, my 22 years in education say otherwise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure anymore on how I am feeling about the House Speaker.... #pick a side]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMalorzo @moinanderson @A_Badassunicorn @medpepper @witchofgric @AlwaysChica @stevie76 @gany760 @ewannaC… https://t.co/ZeGcwZLLZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom told me get out her face , but when i leave i get in trouble ? make up ur damn mind FUCK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nini_cherrybomb @AltNatSecAgency Right.. he's making himself, and his kids, billionaires.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I’ve been told to carry a knife. On top of that, I have pepper spray attached to my keys as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do your thing &amp; never apologize for being you. 💯 #yougococo @ New Jersey https://t.co/h4Mus7DPc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taasssh_ lmaoooo crazy because this is what i was referring to when i originally tweeted this. shorty posted her E… https://t.co/xFR7HEc1mB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The littles give out Valentines at Wednesday night church dinner every year. I take extras. #NewProfilePic https://t.co/jxUIop6EV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CovingtonAHS If you get any complaints send copies of the studies and note that narrative feedback was provided, w… https://t.co/ptmXODZ8TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s worse that my Starbucks coffee addiction? My Starbucks cup addiction 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAY! Our #POTUS has our #BuildTheWallNow going up! Greatest President in our history. Thank you @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vmore47 VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @catskilltracks for the beautiful sunlit photo - which needs no filter - of last night’s… https://t.co/11ogkpWAKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SeniorNight I’m there! So proud of U son! Love U #goGauchos! ThankU all for showing my baby some real Cali Love, e… https://t.co/LirGlI1654]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt #MY_HOPE_JHOPE I love you💚 #Jhope   #Ipurpleyou 💜 https://t.co/AC8uigtfwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every setback is a major comeback for success... (these were the most perfect words to hear today after something didn’t turn out right)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @TheRickWilson So Dan, why are *you* buddies with the owner of a human trafficking prostitution ring?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRedhouse9 I live for your divided house nights 😂 I’m rooting for ya moms team 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers It's not a new thing He has been dealing in trafficked girls since the 80s Te younger the better G… https://t.co/4WcP9HLN9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@civiljustice2 @CNN @smerconish AIPAC is an American non profit. It's not Isreali]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning photos capture the cosmos in all its glory https://t.co/Gx15xEbEmx via @NatGeoScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of an incredible holiday watching Cirque du Soleil with the parents 🎪 👫 #lastday #cirquedusoleil #holiday… https://t.co/KBwq62LTPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen Wish you cared about the millions of babies aborted (murdered) in their mothers’ wombs and soon outs… https://t.co/U7JPDfW32T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande I got clam chowder and I’m from Rhode Island so I think that’s fitting. It’s also probably my favorite soup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Figment is an augmented reality app where students can use portals to explore and they can upload pictures and reco… https://t.co/XPUcjUn2EK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 He at least should have had the same treatment Paul Manafort was doled out... 9 months of solitary c… https://t.co/Xef2MdNSZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_iBIGGULP That's when you stop saying anything.. unless he a coworker.. then you gotta deal with it to an extent. 🙇🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[KABOOM! Here comes another beautiful brush to add to your collection. The new YOUNIQUE kabuki brush has densely-pac… https://t.co/i7XsF7baQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think Laz should use these as bookmarks while runners🏃🏽‍♀️are grabbing their pages 📖 for the… https://t.co/LY7UkO0eKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe a hundred bad days made a hundred good stories. A hundred good stories make me interesting at parties. -AJR /… https://t.co/nJZZaayayj]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing my tax refunds are v close to four digits 🤑💃🏻 https://t.co/rt5zi3EaTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:15am @gozwift #trainerride through NYC!  I’m working my way through @tinamuir’s podcast — this episode was entert… https://t.co/HF2JXXu1h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kids being derps #derp #pups #dogsofinstagram #dogs #pupsofinstagram @ Spring Valley, Nevada https://t.co/gLsj3FNzxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly right...... #Repost @bishopjakes with get_repost ・・・ Anything you don't feed will decline! If you don't con… https://t.co/1JzfzEgNAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrGriffinsNest Howard isn't helping but yet Holland wants to sign him 2 more years but in the middle of a rebuild.… https://t.co/epIbdlMy6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RozeOliva @johneo09 @aliiibeary @LivePdFans Maybe he’ll let you sit up front next time ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@showupforthis So we might be ok with Jerry Springer, Randy Moss, Stockard Channing, Aqib Talib, Henry Rollins and… https://t.co/Bh5qlUMSN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stats_Stu @TheCCHL @CCHL_PR @centraljunior @Kemptville73s @CornwallColts @MyHockeyTV @HockeyTech Like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Bug-in-Ear Coaching, Teachers Get Feedback on the Fly https://t.co/Ut2c1i4fo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick selfie as I wait for my car in the parking lot after a sweaty but incredible shoot with @shootcouplepics ♥️🍒… https://t.co/BsQSTRDuo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahajoness Nahhh everyone is different and you have to really try to overdo it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for this, Jen!  @nathancullen, @MurrayRankin and others like them are the best MPs precisely because they ar… https://t.co/FdmPaDFWzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't had time to do a #60secondtutorial this week because we've been busy prepping and painting our living roo… https://t.co/XiamLrSL2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/B2cUzy9xfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Trump when he was young in his women haters club all alone.🤣😅 https://t.co/Fg1bobmgVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatonRifles1 @krassenstein I had a cocker spaniel that had such a bad anxiety disorder, I went to counseling with… https://t.co/iu7XOhU81d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that your significant other’s job is NOT to fix you. Professional therapists and uhhh YOURSELF ar… https://t.co/5cQBE4Hp40]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for KJ to come out of her room crying and not wanting me to leave. LORD gimme the strength 😭💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh... because he didn’t get the deal he wanted for the safety of the American people? He didn’t fail, you twatwaffl… https://t.co/kYaIh6IrUJ]]></document></documents></author>