<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Check out my website. I am excited about this hair and I get so many complements on it. It is high quality hair for… https://t.co/oqLPIbpani]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnEmerickEdD @PHinnovates 🤷🏽‍♀️ i just figure @BrianCCastrucci can make everything better. He’s kinda like the p… https://t.co/MJwxaxZBux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ballot-burlesque lady at your service! 💃🏻 Great night at @murray_hill ‘s Oscar Viewing party at @clubcumming tonigh… https://t.co/srxt6Wjs1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to do something that’s low management, but I know going blonde or going back to red is a lot of management]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfranken @NormOrnstein Dang it Al...I miss your radio show EVERY DAY! Please come back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The aftermath of @cade_beloso’s homerun that gave the Tigers their victory over Army.   Up next, #LSU takes on Air… https://t.co/CIOQOyPsdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing in this world i wouldn’t do for you boy 💙 https://t.co/IVMPD7ftxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @doris_goddard I will not be excited until he is out of office. Every time I hear he is going to be a… https://t.co/L6nbVWG5lV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelJesterKY Maybe the algorithm will somehow let them pop up again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weird_Dana just watched your Gacey painting Estes session. So creepy! I loved you and Greg or Greg and Gary maybe,… https://t.co/1XVfJpS3DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaPorter1 @BeatriceLacy @TShinkarenko @PatGrant7777 @Jilliemary @Tom__Coleman @jaimemiserachi @PattiBrookd… https://t.co/bGiz8MceB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto X #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para 1° lugar en el #TopNorEste @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did watch and  @60Minutes segment on coding and the gender gap was...interesting. Indeed especially since it left… https://t.co/6JdDWyTBjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yesJTYOUaretheBest 🤷🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️💜🙏 @jtimberlake  #thankyouforcomingtoPortland 🤘🏽 https://t.co/yBp0PxOf23]]></document><document><![CDATA[And ya know what, I know this makes me a disgusting individual, okay?! But I don’t care. Mama needed those last cou… https://t.co/WYR90uA871]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little post-kiln unloading brunch! Turkey and pesto croissant with avocado spinach salad! @ Greenville, South Car… https://t.co/Ve9TJhtbi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealfoodKev #DitchDairy #MilkTruth #milk #dairy #AgChat #Februdairy https://t.co/caVcM1kgCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hryhorczuk_r It looks like Spring wants to show off its glorious enlightenment but Winter is getting territorial a… https://t.co/2QtIIUDBBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Picklenose1 It does! I keep touching my thumb to my finger and having mini-panics, haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the Priestess of Soul and icon Nina Simone #NinaSimone #blackhistorymonth365 https://t.co/dsR1HMognJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've spent the last few days re-organizing and purging the office. Decided to order a new cabinet on Tuesday and it… https://t.co/fK0VhMDUWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love animals so much , I can’t wait to reach this major goal I have to help out animals 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[fk me and annie were about to just spontaneously buy jmblya tickets but we missed presale by 6 minutes fk :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieStelter @brianstelter Leo’s are quite fabulous 😉🦁👍🏻 Congratulations 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonChigurh81 @Alex_Sheasley @AdamSchefter Easy dude. We might win 6, Or 4. Probably 4.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi. Here to tell you that I’m watching Moana for the 3rd time today and I am Motunui’d out 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s cold, y’all. I just pulled out the snow pants to put on over the two pairs of pants I’m already wearing. 🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited that The Shield is back #theshield @ Chelsea, Alabama https://t.co/9U3d5GQCP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricIdle @Lawrence @andelman @TheRickWilson @JoyceWhiteVance @NicolleDWallace @tedlieu @Kriseman And the GOP becau… https://t.co/9WFpFcKasp]]></document><document><![CDATA[💞🎶💞🎶💞🎶💞🎶💞🎶💞🎶💞 jaycobbmusic miminaja @drodriguezmuse arthurleeland fiddlinbridget @charlierosemus @darrenmusic gone_… https://t.co/xgiB3E1Sfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amber_R_Born anyone who thinks he’s too cool to be rodent on main doesn’t deserve our time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomthunkitsMind Damn thieves need to have their hands amputated. They steal your money, time and patience.   #EnoughIsEnough #traitortrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re closed! Thank you to everyone who supported me over the years 🙏🏻😘 now... what should I do on this instagram a… https://t.co/QLfWLPtCcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE IT!!!! Woohoo!!               Train rides from LA to Coachella and Stagecoach could be a thing by 2020… https://t.co/zALiYeDpfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the weather like in Bellevue right now?   I'm heading back there after the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you who so kindly followed me please know I will follow back when I can Twitter is only letting me follow a couple at a time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward to this one every year. Not only is it great weather  but I suck every bit of data, info, knowledge… https://t.co/CbhWt04vYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even know if I’m happy with my job and it sucks so much.. I feel like I’ll never be happy with what I do. I… https://t.co/mPluoHjcWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCSTC_SchoolBus   Your website is down.  I guess all is parents figured the buses would be cancelled today.  Can y… https://t.co/dTyuxtD9rI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’M GOING TO DO SOME RESEARCH TO SEE IF MY DOG IS CONNECTED TO THE MOON! https://t.co/8HFwFMpZyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need someone to take candid photos of me so I can update my profile picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s great? #Idaho weather. Sunshine in February is delightful.  *15 minutes later I can’t find my car in all this snow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday!! We have in shop today:  Whole Cake: Snickers Cake 8" Chocolate Raspberry 6" Holy Canoli 6"  Chocol… https://t.co/mJLtwCBNMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lies, lies, lies by an unqualified, unvetted member of the #TrumpCrimeFamily #Traitors]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barney’s first day going to work with his dad!   Looks just about as exciting as I imagine a day as a biologist is 🙃 https://t.co/UpTzMUCXXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo aquí en Atlanta compro la pulpa de tamarindo por galón a una empresa colombiana. Y me lo traen a casa… https://t.co/9TPVdLuaV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the wonderful @HaileyKilgore ‘s birthday, and I am so glad she’s alive. Happy birthday queen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennyFitz32 @ChrisMarlowe Oh, Kenny. You are so, so wrong about so many things. https://t.co/jA4K3QfJhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I actually hiked voluntarily, hell has officially frozen over 🌞🌵 📸: @JrodChristians1 #arizonahiking… https://t.co/iNzUBmHUXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[But they shall swoop down on the shoulder of the Philistines in the west, and together they shall plunder the peopl… https://t.co/bmiBT9BhvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited a #coffeehouse today. ❤️these. 😊😊😊 @ Cedar Hill, Texas https://t.co/GyMV1NJauj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want some chocolates, tacos &amp; flowers ... oh and some loooooove 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[So um if I drunk text or call you just know I’m asking for money lmao 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up at 4:44 &amp; this song is in my head 🤦🏽‍♀️ inayah_lamis is a whole #MOOD #444  🤷🏽‍♀️🤣🤣🤣🤣 #niggasaintshit… https://t.co/kr10zwThNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cacheerlove @CA_Ladycats These girls had back to back 9 practices and have really come together! Super proud mamakat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash All political! Democrats promote killing of unborn babies, but it's not moral to take children after 2… https://t.co/axajPMAQGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the utterly magnificent @ReginaKing on her first @TheAcademy at #TheOscars ✨💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister-in-law, Rachel, made me this for my birthday. Isn’t it gorgeous? @ Gainesville, Florida https://t.co/tVfiBZZ1zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[January was like a whole year long &amp; then February was gone in a day.... hello March (my fave month) 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Speedway coffee is better than any Starbucks coffee.  The price is right too👌🏻💕☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g3rrity @GardenInColor @PegPisani I took the critique to be of those who see elite school grads as inherently bett… https://t.co/VBEIVPxy94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terri_P_Goddard @NatCookResists I have a theme going here.  Draco, Diggory, Severus and now Dobby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chamacos, en una semana andaré ya en San Luis Potosí y estoy muy emocionado; como niño chiquito un día antes de la… https://t.co/umX57FvTd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alonhern16 You are the greatest and always come through and this is why I love you! 😂🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry about what the President THINKS. We can SEE what the Dems believes !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I constantly have to battle for defending play in the Early Childhood classrooms, it’s insane and very… https://t.co/8KLNOZoibL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll give you everything you ask for, and you ain't even gotta ask for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo excited.....hanging with my Herba-Soul Sisters!!   #blackgirlmagic #blackgirlsrock #BGRfest #KenCenHipHop… https://t.co/9j3skbHTrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BittrScrptReadr That’s one of the things that make The Office so good. Their characters are real, w flaws, subtlet… https://t.co/FqLIihXq1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juli vos para que tenes las orejas? Escucha pues, las orejas 👂 no son adornos ni para ponerte las sunglasses son pa… https://t.co/za2dRwx0Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I hate to say this, because I was an adamant follower of the show, but “Dexter” probably could have f… https://t.co/eDvZSyVrpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo fuck ANYBODY who thinks I won't be loyal for that one. Some deserve it more then others. Fuck music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Hope he doesn't sign it.  We the people, your employer, want 5.7 billion! #BuildTheWall #SecureOurBorder]]></document><document><![CDATA[I save to the school bus everyday.  4 out of 5 times, the bus driver is the only one who wants back.   1 out of 5 t… https://t.co/gHfz2jdQO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got new socks and I got these cute ones that have sushi on them but the right sock for those pair was made wrong… https://t.co/vTSXQCw2WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPDSanTanCMDR @GilbertPolice So awesome Commander.. raising strong independent children is a treasure.. It was a p… https://t.co/W0TwOQPNQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be a recipient with my partner @Chris_S_Hancock of an award from The 200 Club of Jacksonville tonight. T… https://t.co/xzBojU6iZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell this girl to STOP going to my job to talk about me to my coworkers as if they’re not going to tell me]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ SWWET SENIOR FOXY needs OUR HELP to get her OUTTA this SHELTER and into a FOR… https://t.co/xoqKBPk8Dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloofSpikey You’re funny 😊.... good night ..... https://t.co/vIXxt5HlKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackdeth1969 Same. 😉 Glad you made it back ok. Wanna hear all about your death scene!! ☺️🖤🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyde2121 thank you for ALWAYS believing in me, supporting me and pushing me to be my best!!!! I love you]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was her college friends. Mind your business, stop clout chasing and please keep Teni’s name out your mouth thank… https://t.co/o6G1I0Mvzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS @CliftonsNotes @JacquelineMWood It’s also getting really old!!! Bring on a new guy for Steffy please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así comenzamos el viernes 🏊‍♀️ ¡Encendiendo luces y Nada! https://t.co/Hd64RqLML8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forkmespoonme @DivaVinophile @suziday123 @GailBenzler @jillianne_gray @shaunmyrick @winetraveleats @jflorez… https://t.co/omiuS0fXWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is not going to go far in her life if she continues to be high ob weed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mornings in the Rogers household:   Him: Good morninggg Me: Ooo you sound like Louis Armstrong  Him: 🎤🎼I see skies… https://t.co/0dWnIA7nmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is any of this legal? I think about all the things we know about Trump now that we didn’t before the election,… https://t.co/5LtAUkLRRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, the TRUE true meaning. | 30 Holiday Cards People Will Actually Want To Receive https://t.co/5vPH1NHTSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jah_Schwa @brooklynvegan Finally someone mentions a song he actually wrote!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beers (@ Mar Vista Liquor in Cardiff by the Sea, CA w/ @thegreatwax) https://t.co/7vVdYPH8He]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brockwilbur @cpatrickdood Okay, now I need virtual😆 Where are all my artists?  Someone please sketch this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boundless Athletic Minorities Movement begins in March! Your child will learn personal development, community servi… https://t.co/ESSFLwpYDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Ralph no one is paying  attention to you.  You are irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha the hotel manager (I think, I forgot my glasses in the room) said that the architect did it on purpose and tha… https://t.co/4i6NMmKu1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Longo says he wore a body worn camera the entire time he responded to 10 Jones Place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elections matter. The most flawed Democrat in the race is not going to do this to our courts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LacyClayMO1 What a one sided game y’all are playing. Such a shame 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>