<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Two different justice one for the rich and one for the poor, black and just a reminder of our justice system]]></document><document><![CDATA[Professional wrestler Booker T is suing video game giant Activision Blizzard Inc. for copyright infringement for al… https://t.co/WIeXTwwi2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong Women! #stetsonuniversity #Repost stetsonwrowing (get_repost) ・・・ The Hatters will be officially starting of… https://t.co/gywx89qP4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MysteryLuminous I seen a small girl in a white dress running through my house before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason804 @djtay1906 warming up! @ Clayton State University https://t.co/rlL2r9b7Vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deuce4922 If both UW and Arizona St. lose on Thursday, I’m in favor of this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fun design project that I created for "The Royalty Collection" - A company with an amazing mission of showi… https://t.co/oHD1cvcpGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[def fooled @MercedesInTheAM @jctheproducer @MercedesLV w/ the #TheCoveredCrooner easy to say lol!!! Gracias for hav… https://t.co/GMvdvW3C9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:56 3rd  West 26  Portsmouth 21  Dad's alma mater builds its lead over Mom's. Dylan Bradford getting to the rack at will. He has 12!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkenyon866 great meeting u on Twitter Lee-Ann, enjoy my latest horror film review ALIEN DOMICILE… https://t.co/cBoskkfVfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@player442ron @brianstelter @JamieStelter Kills Kings. I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth… https://t.co/le94CBDpTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, you’re getting older when you’re happy asf you bought a new bed room set for your bed.. 🙌🏼🛏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fogocinti @BrianMonzon @nbr9596062 @RhonieSays @DallasClaude @cjay_greene @ledrew @GarlandGloria Amen Elder Run!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeConchaTV Allow me to translate: "@CNN is in last place because we tirelessly drum for the Totalitarian Elitists… https://t.co/CxEDJ3andA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaseparis Wow that’s impressive. And very kind. You the man. And together y’all are the people! 🤘🏽😎 @tarafbennett 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomhfh @ShabanaMahmood You didn’t listen, go figure, he said if it wasn’t aggressively being pushed in schools the… https://t.co/OaCLmBn3PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Second half has begun!!! #Mpire19 #MbraceTheDream #F1NISH #BeatNorth https://t.co/yJDWSea1E6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m down. Who’s with me? @FAU_Owls_Nest @JackWhidden3 @KLV1063 @insidetheburrow @ItsOwlTime @OwlFamilyFAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition The only thing Trump will be president of in 2020 is the president of the circle jerk club in prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrumpyCatterman @HalfTangible Don’t forget. When Gal Gadot was first cast in the role, she was attacked for being… https://t.co/qNwgSaL8FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dveBillCrawford #dvemorningshow Bill! How have you not seen the Bill Cosby BBQ sauce clip. Yinz were just talking… https://t.co/QxspDgW18R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein Did God get him to pay that gynormous fine for false advertising yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwilsongolf @StaysureTour @ShackersGolf @Princesgolfclub Bad luck , and galling to think it was around 20 degrees… https://t.co/wGGh81IEWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBarrettPR @livingkatstone @ConestogaBiz @Kcarte02 @lkoster @MKT2090 @MichGrimes @n_dagloria @Atempleman2… https://t.co/UM82EfJddO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Jaeger trying out hockey #FirstDayOnSkates @usahockey @nbcsports sportsengine @ Parade Stadium https://t.co/eXgFqhhLi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenLL11 Wait you are saying it’s been proven but it is being hidden.  So it is like a David Copperfield  show?… https://t.co/MjmTRnD5kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @BAMAPERRY Is there any difference between what Jussie did (trying to frame some innocent caucasian… https://t.co/6GBDuNXwtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A world without women is a world not worth living in. A world without women in power is a world that will continual… https://t.co/Mq0QS1NB8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased to see the President is still working for a peace https://t.co/E6eLQuLPvG I see it the problem is NK does n… https://t.co/ClwlAE0kpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treestand_tweet Even out of sight on the “throne”...as I was reading ur tweet....🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein She made the right move. She will feel much better in helping the next Democratic nominee becomes the… https://t.co/7vR5T1E9LY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonchibnall @DonaldJTrumpJr I truly do not understand your point. Accusing by the use of generalities is useless a… https://t.co/uIjM6bw9O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday random car musing: I think the Triumph Stag is one of the prettiest and most underrated British cars ever.… https://t.co/ATheNhi1qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazzyintheusa That little girl gonna be captain marvel now? Or is that lady the captain marvel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date night #daddysgirl #daddyslittlegirl #movietheater #popcorn #howtotrainyourdragon #howell #newjersey @ Xscape T… https://t.co/yTz162JEcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got questions about language, accessibility, or related? Let us know, so we can them answered for you on today's sh… https://t.co/qn0DXgGmQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron (2018) by @jasondussault. 👑🏀🎨 - Miami Beach - 12.6.2018 @KingJames @LEGO_Group @SCOPEArtShow #JasonDussault… https://t.co/relz8hEotc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re ordering something, absolutely never say “I want...” you rude, unmannered swine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can see the difference with no Zion in the game. Carolina looks so much better than duke in every aspect]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever have to defend themselves over something they messed up on. This isn’t high school anymore people. You either… https://t.co/uMJGXkICSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hami a STAR ⭐️   #SlamDunkChamp #Diallo #Kentucky https://t.co/bHiHI6al0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your value and it feels good to be satisfied with how far you’ve come.  🔹 You no longer have to prove your… https://t.co/04Kd2QoyEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megkelly92 Just seems...I dunno, not really a celebration....feels awkward. Probably cause I don't have a link to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityNews @Ginella_M I did a bit of math on this yesterday in another thread but a critical flaw with the “research… https://t.co/TwnnqvuyoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kalamazoo_Track @SXMCollege @GopherFootball @ESPN_Schick @OfficialAJHawk @Coach_Fleck The on and off the field ant… https://t.co/mb5qEbQcDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder and correction: LHS_athletic trip to @OQMSMRB Wednesday this week at 7:20am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammyfoghorn @SFGiants @BuzzFeed @ussoccer @espn @TheEconomist Ha that’s a first! Getting a response to a tweet fr… https://t.co/htJKgyOUPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottpanozzo @dougammeraal @MrNumms @billobrienMI @JakeManning12 @WhitakerLowell @mills1em @RalstonShari Thanks Scott!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatrstanford @StanfordDiane @KowalchukFarms @Brentcollins5 @gwclayton Thank goodness Dianne has the “MediAlert”… https://t.co/AuysNdRrCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a face like that once. I met a girl at Zuma Beach in Orlando in 1998. That place was basically just a hook up… https://t.co/DlTFNNXOIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Than you @swankonsports for representing The Minutemen! #Logo #GoLex @PurpleHazeLHS @OldDadof3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody told me “you must be a hoe if you enjoy being single”....I don’t enjoy being single but I’m so busy I can’… https://t.co/7NgcOOrUPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zack, you did a brilliant job on this. "Thorough" would be a spectacular understatement. The links, the dismantling… https://t.co/yZXEcirV8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech Boston 22, Newton North 14. Tigers call another timeout. Bears defense forcing turnovers. Led by Lyron Bennett and Shamar Browder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Makiko_Ohmoto That writing looks similar like Bayonetta. And speaking of that, the food in Japan looks succulent!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallassooner Dear @netflix, I recommend my good buddy @dallassooner for this job. He is highly qualified in the ar… https://t.co/vecRTuDZuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather Everything is "negotiable" with this administration (including ethics,  morals and the truth).]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope CPD flies a lawsuit against Jussie Smollett. He should have to pay for all the resources used to investigate… https://t.co/VCL7MZaLzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @AOC and @RepMaxineWaters, since you are on (and the chair) of the financial services committee, can we make su… https://t.co/KqG6kJtGaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Berk(: i hope this tweet works better for you. love and miss you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hipismo #ChampionshipMeet #1SisterKitten con sensacional atropellada y galopando captura la 9na de #Gulfstreampark… https://t.co/QkkhW0qC1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamfelber I HAVE SOLVED YOUR PROBLEM!!!  You need to take a week off. Fake tonsillitis. Get @AlonzoBodden or… https://t.co/qeYr4ODO5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not an emergency you moron!! And I’m sure the stats you are quoting are incorrect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖕That is the dumbest false comparison a mind could connect. So an fbi that wants to carry out an objective in defen… https://t.co/M6tu2ZjGVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the driver of the number 34 @GOtransit bus heading to the airport this morning, you are awesome! #thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthony___24 I'm not sure if there are any advance tickets beyond that app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer The Democrats wanted no one to remove Muller but now wants the investigation to end and put out the ent… https://t.co/XXbOugSXSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color Reef by Ed Matzko edmatzkoart@gmail.com  #art #abstract #abstraction #abstractart #modernart #contemporaryart… https://t.co/oIOsJevsVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Friends! Happy Sunday! Just do it! @ John Prince Park https://t.co/Z1GD22Dsjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Vince shows up on a show, after 'months or years' between appearances -- he's been back stage the entire time! https://t.co/zwOJ75qE1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro A Florida Massage Parlor Owner Has Been Selling Chinese Execs Access to Trump at Mar-a-Lago – Mother Jo… https://t.co/8wH0nOVH5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “The New Yorker explores the degree of influence Fox News has on the Trump White House”  https://t.co/GwvKt7AKCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tresvantstreet @DuckerJevyon @zavierbetts1 @_keaganj @Ault70 @CJ_Johnson15 @cade_johnson @arothermund10… https://t.co/JzpOgP7TPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be so damn confused. Why did they do that? #HTGAWM https://t.co/wqlnXejS7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a double standard?  GOP uproar over @MichaelCohen212's lies vs the lack of uproar over @realDonaldTrump's… https://t.co/1oDYZouwJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBaileyWFNZ , they should use the college baseball model. Either turn pro out of high school or you have to sta… https://t.co/x6NoWyl7JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning World Wheels up to Atlanta for a out and back overnight doubleheader with Xfinity and Trucks on Saturd… https://t.co/O88AqTvwFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XavierRibalta1 @AlbanoDante76 @PPopular @vox_es Como sudas y el ambiente apesta a tu alrededor. https://t.co/f9pFeDA7A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willglasper03 who plays right wing because he can’t catch passes on his backhand]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my #CRACKINWAXMAILDAY from @CrackinWax &amp; @LiteralQuirk. Thank you! https://t.co/FASVC04iEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@semil Clinging to heuristics is one way to feel you are capably converting uncertainty into risk.  But uncertainty… https://t.co/VHUn5gz2SE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corruption in Caldwell County from the District Attorney’s Office. Former D.A. Trey Hicks has good reviews but our… https://t.co/fqVfeGf20j]]></document><document><![CDATA[First pack out of the way. It’s been tooooooo long since I got to #sendit #fpv #lumineerfpv #spektrum #fatsharks… https://t.co/qF8kTIJC17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burner2047 @PrimeVideo @neilhimself Well let's see... Prime Video seems to be doing okay... Neil Gaiman probably n… https://t.co/EIP5gtEYnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinballmind We can chat more later, but dm me and I'll check out your writing in the next few days and maybe ask y… https://t.co/Hq8zeBNbh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Browns lack a lot of guys that get open on route running alone. I expect Kitchens to continue to use Landry in… https://t.co/fIB2SF7UFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, last ever pic of current sim-racing rig before I start the upgrade. Something tells me I'll be unmounting that… https://t.co/yPA8rfU0Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a great day of wrestling yesterday! Today at noon is the Semi Finals! Whitehall will take on Dundee! #goVikes @… https://t.co/qKTGWgD5sQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanceCollection @TDTWinch @menakathakkar Thrilled to be hosting the Encore Dance Hall of Fame awards show this yea… https://t.co/mKISTHIh5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alison has been babysitting mine and Johnathan's Bearded Dragon for the past two days and the separation anxiety is getting me :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReasonsRExcuses @FOX26Houston Agreed and just enjoy life. Stop trying to be right all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Javi_Hoops @Alfred_AE86 Investing in property / shares / stocks is the way to go 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCamachoVzla Vieron a Maduro escondido por ahí.... https://t.co/pBqNW65Njo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flubbsfgc I kill myself so much it doesn't even bother me. Tbh I don't even remember the sds lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arindube @kimmaicutler Everyone competing would just get crappy participation trophies, but the people running it might get a nice prize...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinleeryan i like how the int’l market in tucson puts that stuff in the africa aisle where it belongs 🇿🇦🇿🇦🇿🇦 @NandosSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post 15 min 1:1 interval morning cardio... #alliethegymdog makes it a little tough to stretch (apparently she likes… https://t.co/i6KXyg4k1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was about to drink my V8 Splash Strawberry Kiwi and noticing odd language. Freda-Kiwi isn’t French.#Campbell… https://t.co/bxoKTh31eH]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Train Your Dragon 3 was a fitting and satisfying conclusion to the trilogy. Captures more of what I loved ab… https://t.co/MKPRqR8HA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DyllonJames16 Congratulations Dyllon! Really have enjoyed watching you play! Very well deserved]]></document></documents></author>