<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Cuddle up and get your zombie on!!  Nothing like a romantic zombie vampire comedy movie to share with the one you l… https://t.co/Njm42O4IVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar Game | Oscar 2019 Ballots and Trivia  Play Oscar Game live during the show with ball https://t.co/CY2oALN79x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamlevine @blakeshelton I wish blake wasn't even on The Voice!!!!! Get Keith or Tim someone GOOD!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#100DaysOfCode day  17  #WomenWhoCode  #javascript30  Javascript  flex tutorial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vou me inscrever pro próximo bbb (isso se não cancelarem pois tá sendo flop) mandando um vídeo pro boninho dizendo… https://t.co/KZkDe1aDDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think the Jonas Brothers reuniting is a valid excuse for me to skip out on my info exam]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is ALWAYS time to talk about sensible gun legislation. #StopGunViolence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miren este es mi novioo! no me lo miren tanto gracias. https://t.co/rgtNUDHpby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodiePrevostUK @sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @ValentinoAndy77… https://t.co/Veg1qwLN37]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shout out to all the strong and powerful women I am blessed to know!  We are half-the-sky ladies...never forget y… https://t.co/bbg5XkkDhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claudya_N @gisselleivzla31 Arribaa NO ABREN LAS VENTANAAASD DE DONDE CORRE AIREEE DIMEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emdiane87 @DmGFusion @Insane29472 @nct_yeet @missyouulots YALL SKIP TO 1 MINUTE IN I FOUND IT BTW IT SLAYED ME https://t.co/JgGuxsg1ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #functionalmedicine mentor told me years ago, " your body cannot tell the difference between French perfume and c… https://t.co/7aeVfyVcie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t explain how excited I am to be in Athens with Morgan and Ciarra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living at home has conditioned me to watch the entirety of the 6pm Kingston news 📺 @CKWS_TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_T_S @RoKeT_gal Havent been to any of these, but have been to Edinburgh,  Jedburgh,  and toured some of the South… https://t.co/QCQGUELOyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go kill some hillbillies. Judging by the graphic novel and @DeadlyClassSYFY previews, storming Chester's hide… https://t.co/R4i3c5E1mL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The adhesive on my popsocket does not hold well. I bought it like maybe a month ago. Bout ready to superglue this shit on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s stop wasting money on mars reasearch and invest it into “get skinny but stay in bed” reasearch. Thoughts on my way to the gym...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are state and federal officials not challenging trumps dangerous mental illness? Addressing trumps Narcissistic… https://t.co/Yf9kVpQoxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Like I say every time someone brings this up: If an AMERICAN CITIZEN commits a CRIME, they are sepa… https://t.co/pGYqdXsyIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eagleyez317 Thank you! We actually do like to be around each other. We were friends first!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VesperLynd86753 I LOOOOOVED A Star Is Born. ⭐️ Can’t wait to see Gaga and Bradley Cooper perform it! #HTownRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went out this morning to get the paper 📰❄️  Decided to take a few pics before I shoveled the driveway ❄️🥶 It’s stil… https://t.co/FH4uTmp4kC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eso no me simpatiza, Nick Así no funciona esto, ok?  Igual ame el vídeo 💖   #Sucker #SUCKERVIDEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost We need you in your Senate seat more than ever right now. You are the example of a man who cares mo… https://t.co/doMhLvJhl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Even if I don’t show up, it’s going to be very good,” he says of Jaleo at Disney Springs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By having faith, praying real hard and make sure DJT remains our President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#whitneymuseum @ Whitney Museum of American Art https://t.co/4W0ImIWxvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[God's beauty at work in mountains of California https://t.co/drXW4eoWdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyallantdf @AmyWhedonite Wow that must be so hard on your system.  I hope the people you helped are truly gratefu… https://t.co/ER7rt3Hbtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly Accuser Jerhonda Pace on Talk Show for Being a Prostitute! (Air... https://t.co/98KaLmvx8F via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[So disgusting seeing someone on sc kissing everyone while she’s drunk 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SjCattledog Your weather is still probably better than here.. Some people just don't understand how to drive in a… https://t.co/9P5nsxjyQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soft matte gold adorned silk thread bangles. Just love the contrast with the topaz gold karras. 🖤 @ Banglez Jewelry https://t.co/m3hQHBHSaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon Bill Would Allow Starving Mentally Ill Patients to Death https://t.co/xG6wdYTQIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones. Has it been shut down? Is Florida pressing charges? Where are the underaged ? They okay?  Enough with… https://t.co/rsmqn4mdRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly what i been saying all i need is @BlueChairBayRum @kennychesney  ,@noshoesradio  listeningto music and enjo… https://t.co/C0y1gFAqtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi @JahanaHayesCT @AOC @IlhanMN @RollingStone Ms Hayes i am so proud of you. I was so happy when you won t… https://t.co/zPttZYmdDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Il n’a pas l’intelligence pour gérer un dossier si https://t.co/GPJbP9zQ4K manque de sensibilité et d’humanisme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deanogormano If you could get it to LA, I’d take whatever you want to part with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo the adventures of billy and mandy was that dhow https://t.co/HWKPqh6Wnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[you made all 4 hours of waiting worth it queen, we’ve been buzzing with electric energy of your blue eyeliner since… https://t.co/l3VK3qEWLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cherrysss #pods #ejuices #juul #sourubg #smok #Myblu @ Long Beach, California https://t.co/fNuJuA1WQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i use my phone as a way to cope with my social anxiety and it something i need to work on wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[No se que hice para merecer a alguien que no pueda dormir por pensar en mi😻😻😻😻 https://t.co/u3XXBGA17C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexisD_2017 I disagree though. Especially if you work for a small organization and there’s nobody else with your j… https://t.co/IcPNJdoHJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to a @chiperiodprjct fundraiser and got my period. What kind of witchcraft/solidarity is that?? 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump Hahaha Russia help him win again didn’t even have to vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omwhitmireTV @wvua23 @whnt Talent &amp; hard work payin off. Great job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life should not be a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a pretty and well preserved body… https://t.co/mSOzMWo7WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[健康のために１週間プチ断食 (16/8メソッド) に挑戦してみます🙏 😌Challenging the16/8 intermittent fasting diet for this week to lose weight and get healthy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So bummed to hear this. @AndyKOASports is truly one of the best. I know he will be back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuttMe22 Yea, pretty sure this is an epic failure on behalf of the 'experts.'   They should have called this sham of a marriage long ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday honey🍯love and Miss you so much!!!!Come visit me❤️😘 @matthew_bayer94 https://t.co/sNZ6t6fgkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @Ms_Trista1524 at The Elks with the old heads. Akexa...play TEAR DA CLUB UP!! 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/wwUEggktLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn @kate_grahn Love Disneyland we are going in June after the Gh convention!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyHiltonPT @fyzio4u @LauraOpstedal If being a pain coach involves doing anything within the scope of any licens… https://t.co/siDPByUmxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonedeafvoice I was just thinking about that today. Especially with my history. The system sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeliliaOMalley @realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas Girl you had me at... hell, you just have me c… https://t.co/0Gol4QZv9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Duchene commercial for NHL tonight with him in a Sens jersey just didn’t not age well]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/689JIwegJt 2:37 you communicate I'm thrilled it will never happen again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I  ate a box of Girl Scout cookies in my sleep, so mad ‘because I didn’t get to enjoy them .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see Alec and Madize play together 😀 #Shadowhunters #ShadowhuntersChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happygojackie, @TheCurvyCritic Please help me out. Was Jordan hit by the car that Drew was driving before or after… https://t.co/SFhBvMWB8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippeReines The Coen Brothers will use this scene as inspiration for their next movie. Or @StephenKing ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's almost #valentinesday and here's another picture edit of my favorite little #munchkin @ San Marcos, Texas https://t.co/g9ifOGZuI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are looking at the original " Bag Lady. " Will we ever be rid of this creature that hasn't been foisted upon us?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breatheheavycom @justtranter Queen has always been a musical genius! https://t.co/nLp0NyltsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's why I love @TheWalkingDead. Twitter! So clever and on point all the time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greyallison Cute/weird slice of life: Azumanga Daioh Action: Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood SciFi: Full Metal Panic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full steam ahead🚂 #saturday #Poway #SanDiego @ Old Poway Train Park https://t.co/HTwK1Whg3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it on @bttoronto with the best of the best @DinaPugliese and @rogerfpetersen @ Breakfast Television Toronto https://t.co/f7y1WIt1Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t waste time, we only have a certain amount of time in this life. We all deserve happiness, find what makes you… https://t.co/kNas4E0uiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following the PD Day on Diversity and Inclusion, here are wonderful picture books to continue the conversation… https://t.co/llpzVY4ajI]]></document><document><![CDATA[More cuteness from Kinder!! Happy birthday Dr. Seuss!! @HicksTigers #WeAreHicksElem https://t.co/Zd8ltFMBhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather models are increasing the chance for rain showers this afternoon around the metro area. Chance is no higher… https://t.co/4anmuK3gFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[this set would be around $125 at my job, she is something else lmao especially if them stones swarovski]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinSlick @soledadobrien It’s as if @nytimes are trying to fluff the word count on a essay. Just get to the damn… https://t.co/8zOksFeFjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattiMurin My son is on Spring Break this week but apparently can't come home until tomorrow because of a… https://t.co/9DYSzdtcuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeting again because I forgot to tag them. Well deserved and well done @GordonRussell1, @johnsimerman and… https://t.co/3CMW9800he]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeopardy: “This is the first rule of Fight Club.” Me: Don’t talk about Fight Club?! Ken Jennings: “What is You don’… https://t.co/FO2PjV5qAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr He told us he wanted to see the wall built in our lifetime so that we would live o see that the death… https://t.co/bacg4C9Ouw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#latergram of me and the classy Beth Stelling! #comedygoals #femaleandfunny @ Helium Comedy Club - Saint Louis https://t.co/VURQE2wRiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish that’s the problem- many of these women may be there against their will- living in that shop. How else… https://t.co/25OtQ3Q9ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[S: Hwy. 87 is shut down both directions just south of the Yellow River. Please take alternate routes and avoid the… https://t.co/7sJfs3jrs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allygatorbeans I hope u get something @ your show!! I literally asked for a drumstick last time I saw them and he just gave it to me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday Things! susieheganremax  #acceptedoffer #remax #ayr #realestate #listing #conditionallysold @ Ayr, On… https://t.co/q5MQHb34q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peppertrumper @404Lawman @ExecGQ @Melissa1opinion @Rlp1660Rick @CaddieMobutu @BobPage43582244 @RealWolf72… https://t.co/nU5exVODbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beertheist Yeah, planning ahead seems like a basic adult skill. I get why some people don’t want to take the time… https://t.co/muSy1zz170]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my friends and family close and far and around the world...your in my thoughts and heart this Valentine’s Da… https://t.co/LekNoDYrkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAFearless @IsraeliPM @LindseyGrahamSC @USAmbIsrael Well...if Senator Graham was on official business, my guess is… https://t.co/ysP1QH3KA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀🏀🏀HUGE game Sat.night The University of Michigan vs michigan state.. 8pm. Could determine Big Ten title. 🏀🏀🏀GO BLUE 💛💙💛💙💛💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaRitschke @Dick_n_Donuts @its_willyu @queteimporta713 the “hating on white ppl” u speak of comes from something… https://t.co/ytHpgZcTwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shelene_Larsen @damonbever327 @LKnappD327 @MCortezTHD327 @MattEberhardHD @al_sirwet @Alfredo90591446… https://t.co/3w8zpTTsD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny @On_Blocks @chadfelixg @molratty @lordthx1139 @ArcDigi @BulwarkOnline @varadmehta LOL, I like how Mo c… https://t.co/q8S1fVgX5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need to retweet the quoted tweet below to receive a message. I like to keep it consistent and the tweet below w… https://t.co/Vbp537NOhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @debbie1202 How much campaign funds were filtered into the Clinton Foundation before/after election day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt for Joe!  I wish he'd flown across the desk and laid into that...that..._______! 🌊🌊🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sears UPDATE: THE SEARS MANAGEMENT TEAM (SMT) said it's scheduled for 3-2 and can't be changed. WOW THEY WERE HELP… https://t.co/TUAW84Me0M]]></document></documents></author>