<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Queen it’s because of race and only race, just proves you’re a racist too. Yes, Black people can be racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great speaking to Mrs. Connor’s 4th grade class at Gaston Day today about their bill making Ice Cream the States Of… https://t.co/a61VAiRYAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What infuriated King George VI about Buckingham Palace ⁦@queenelizabeth⁩ You know what I think? I think someone is… https://t.co/H759ZG5Fjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[can i have a hand to hold  a band aid for my damaged soul  i swear i paint the planet gold, swear i’m michelangelo]]></document><document><![CDATA[burst out laughing for some stress relief. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!  so creepy... I am literally laughing out loud… https://t.co/GfeLIHUbt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingwalty Soon to be cardinal we be trading rosen to Washington for 1st rounder]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be able to look back upon ones life in satisfaction, is to live twice.  - Kahill Gibran]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is America being control by communism? All things are possible. Open your eyes and take a good look all around you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Silver Lake Student Council for a successful Kids Day at the Lake. https://t.co/TBnGp1SjAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019 and i’m a millenial, if idk what you look like — we not linkin #periodt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano @GOP Their "Strategy" Has Been To Lie Under Testimony, To Commit Treason And Collusion With Our Most… https://t.co/w5tpmHVO53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just what was LAVROV doing in Hanoi? Can a investigative reporter out there pick up on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too Dope!!!  #RoyalRiz #RapsRoyaltyTheMixtape ClickTheLinkBelow   https://t.co/TEza1HUpRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEEPING IT SIMPLE super happy to finally have me time and work in my jeep perfect night to wrench and listen to som… https://t.co/yXHkboxfGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at Jacks, there was a huge group of magicians eating dinner next to me. At least 12 of them. No joke. Life is wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseEs22585133 @BaronKimble @JamesAJanisse @tcrabtree8414 @elonmusk @senatemajldr 2. ask critical questions about… https://t.co/tHwioI33Od]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalebrashad @MargaretWEgler @ShareYourLearn @hthgse @HQPBL Ooh! 💗 idea of a group theme song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taino315 @Darkskintigga If you are that passionate about civilization you would be able to present the facts with… https://t.co/DIjk4UXcYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierrejvallee @PierrePoilievre @CPC_HQ @AndrewScheer Its not about who met who.  Its about the alleged influencing of the AG.   Focus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanilaSingh @masonis_marilyn The link GOES NOWHERE. First, It was do to the #GovernmentShutdown, now it's just an… https://t.co/qBKZyYLX4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all these reactions to the Sonic movie, I'm not feeling to good that the Monster Hunter movie will be much better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjlathrop @tchambers31 @ultrarunmike TOSU coach said “2 bullshit calls in a row” on TV, yet no one is upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr @Jim_Jordan  Loved your appearance @MeetThePress .  And I want the truth about FISA, 302s, EVERYTHING! But y’all… https://t.co/BQac4ijY7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dolphinville this year we are reading the book Energy Bus. Each week staff is doing a wonderful job presenting the… https://t.co/hKLDqN9Wwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red And good for the plucking It’s Valentines  And good for bad poems]]></document><document><![CDATA[xsadboysclubx #reppin at the detroitpistons #game @ Little Caesars Arena https://t.co/fiMz2Pa1b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJ3_TB Not to mention the 26th ranked OL. Just a terrible spot for him. Willing to give him some time to see what he's made of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing a fantastic ⏰ 48 plus hours of Prep to @vinceea7777 @CoachMcMasters and Jesse as @SaintLeoMBB heads into… https://t.co/XtFGY1G7gP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came across this photo.. lookin good Charles #RIPChuck https://t.co/adY0oBeqrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalDisasters I'm beginning to think all the experts are simply guessing what's gonna happen next...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PassarelliAllan   We now know that Trump has had five private meetings with Putin. No other American officials pre… https://t.co/uCoWMrNYui]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know if the camera likes me, but I do like the camera. 🤷🏼‍♂️ @ Best Buy https://t.co/rPjjVuA25S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bella! I can overafford you 80x Lemme give u the life u want. I just neeed company Bella. Balla just please come back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @PapenShannon I can't eat cooked greens of any sort; become violently ill.  So I don't use hot sauce… https://t.co/iT2PbLNpAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was like "haven't been to Bryn Mawr in ages" so I walked 🤷‍♂️  #Minneapolis #BrynMawr #Coffee #Walking #GoogleFit… https://t.co/3YNa2816YC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BookFinksBookClub @luxcentral means #cocktails for everyone! @ Lux Central https://t.co/8swQUZx3sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Initially, the #Spurs viewed their 130-127 preseason loss in Atlanta as a bizarre anomaly. But it didn't take them… https://t.co/N3bnTihc0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socksocksocks @cowboys8219 Not sure exactly what comment or interview you’re specifically talking about but the la… https://t.co/DpwasElDCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people beast to get on the train before people are getting off you gotta give them the death eyes. I will end you, Relax!]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all watched cartoon network instead of nickelodeon and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[As someone who works in food service in the US I’ve been guilty of “Americans won’t do the jobs”. This is actually… https://t.co/ToWLA5ys34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are probably the biggest liar in US history. Keep on lying, it's being tracked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badam4ser @itsJeffTiedrich @marcorubio I say to you, go buy a brain, or, maybe rent one. The proper procedure is t… https://t.co/E564Xp6Bwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhanes92 @michengelhardt @Communitech @MaRSDD Awe, so glad to read it! 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[The article mostly sounded like candidates offering policy ideas they backed anyway as means to address racial inju… https://t.co/2CcRq504F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[KOFI JUST KICKED OUT AFTER BEING HIT WITH THE RUNNING KNEE 😱😱😱😱  #WWEChamber 👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 My teenage friends did all the teenage antics that black kids did. The biggest difference was we could… https://t.co/iKcF3zJiUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Circuitouslife I would never! I am a good boy just like you! Pls FAV and RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Coors Light by @MolsonCoors at @claim_jumper — https://t.co/KBiaigwSFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @JennyBlighe @sarahjessiexxx @AshleyFires @RahyndeeJames @whitneywrightx @ClubCarmenXXX @sarahsexyred10… https://t.co/X2CUvH2Epv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Keep me a check I ain’t got no regrets if I said it I MF meant it 💯@lilbaby4PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZephyrTeachout Google has FCC licenses for broadcast technology. Maybe complain to FCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I thought David Kaplan the arbiter of all things Cubs said the Cubs never talked to Harper at any point?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿What Mr. President? "Nobody knew too much about #HumanTrafficking until recently." [(#BullShit)] Then Mr. #Trump s… https://t.co/gKQ0Hetj5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like #SanAntonioCommanders Defense are getting lit, they becoming the next Defense Doomsday. #TAKECOMMAND]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article is meant as a challenge to @BoilerFootball @Rondale_Moore03 in a couple of years #BoilerUp… https://t.co/hwYPbnKu0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheronbrylski Thank you, @cheronbrylski . That is definitely the idea: Awareness and information can spur improvement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliomuniz Lo mismo digo, Julio. Muchas gracias por la oportunidad. Un abrazo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is @MeghanMcCain so ignorant? Does she have a clue that if we don’t embrace the #greennewdeal, China will pass… https://t.co/iDjomqJTZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauleyP Interestingly enough, fully one third of scripture tells of the dreams people had, then tells the actions… https://t.co/IoHinK6FfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dacowboys2222 That’s a great trade, good to see there’s reasonable dynasty players out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosBolsonaro A Raquel é da esquerda, a Ruth é boazinha! #tonhodalua #Bolsomijo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish some of y’all cared about animals and this planet like Steve did. RIP the original goat🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mainstream media have become totally irrelevant in my life other than I hate them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The New King In Town by Lucky's Brewpub @ Lucky's brew pub — https://t.co/8Ko2tjY8Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nayibbukele @us_chico @BCIE_Org Ya cumpliendo una de tus propuestas... La construcción de nuevas escuelas y el arte.... ✌🧔🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd Place All-Around at the #CloverClassic Gymnastics Meet in Brighton, MI. #GTBayGymnastics #TeamAva # @ Brighton… https://t.co/4Dqa93UXI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Warminster Municipal Services in Warminster, PA https://t.co/zEmjGpR4WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mets Nice but hard throwers mean rotator cuffs and sore arms.Its irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racquets Up!  For the second straight week Hailey &amp; Devin win the Varsity Girls Doubles at a SAISD tournament.… https://t.co/wycu0iPakN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it when people talk to me about my job with Cirque, the first thing they bring up is the accidents that happ… https://t.co/nzSReZpY0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westripp3 The other large rooms are packed with the large numbers of people who received subpoenas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT May The Rest… https://t.co/yiadg9O97r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gksteinhauser @RonakGopaldas You’ll be grimly pleased to know @WSJafrica has written up the #ESKOM electricity… https://t.co/7pvc5eTfXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @CoryBooker @BeefUSA That looks so good Congresswomen Cheney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter please go home. @ Plymouth, Massachusetts https://t.co/mIQq5lnfJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today me will live in the moment, unless it's unpleasant, in which case me will eat a cookie!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have incredible face pain right now. Yee Haw 🤠 https://t.co/rK2vTOLZ2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #Denver #Broncos from 1965 on.  https://t.co/EtqDr9f3wV … https://t.co/xHuU3Dc8aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find a few women you can settle down with and be about your business https://t.co/lYYfwmfQkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordiesherk11 Is the joke in the "here" or the "long"? If both - WELL DONE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searching for a beat maker, music producer that can make me an intro song for my future youtube channel. I should hit up @p_lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drexmgirlz @lcaligula @tera_sex @JoeySnatch @biencalmex @Assrulez @JuggsNL @TwistysExile @AbondSamer @herby2121New… https://t.co/vvvlW0BHHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I ask Oiler fans to stay with me when I say 29 has to play 2C. #LetsGoOilers https://t.co/fHcAlwqfeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Song Spotlight  Featured Songs for February 19, 2019  21 Savage - a lot  https://t.co/EADMm9aUuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Turns out, like a bad novel, a horrible nightmare at the very least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Montreal! :) #Sunrise 06:41, noon 12:07, sunset 17:34 EST (UTC-5), February 24. Day length: 10h 53m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Details, i.e. his absurdly bloated contract, his worth as an NFL starter, etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @GavinNewsom Newsome, wants to dilute American traditional values; by letting border jumpers break in line and… https://t.co/rP3RilqnUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of my single friends: I will be consuming large amounts of alcohol this evening if you would like to join]]></document><document><![CDATA[UL giveaway on my twitch @ 200 followers! Follow my Twitter, Retweet and follow my twitch! Will announce winner on… https://t.co/3bPyCZg894]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW what did we do to deserve new local natives, LEISURE, and the fucking black keys all in one night???]]></document><document><![CDATA[YET ANOTHER SKETCH!!! SEE IT WITH YOUR EYES!!! HEAR IT WITH YOUR EARS!!!  https://t.co/4rQSE79wlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chinese New Year celebration with Ambassador Li of CHINESE Consulate General in Houston, Mitchell, Qi Family Sharon… https://t.co/IUVZAoLAU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4evrmalone You can imagine all kinds of things. That is what our imagination is for, but to use your imagination a… https://t.co/gRLp2BFQUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pweiser So tired of this #rhetoric from our elected officials. We’re not a democracy, we’re a constitutional repub… https://t.co/eFIKyzfO8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes If he's committed crimes, then impeachment is their responsibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to get shots up with me later today? “Can a Middle-Aged Dad Still Perfect His Jump Shot?” https://t.co/DrOCw6J60P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @EinsteinBros Bagels in Grosse Pointe Woods, MI https://t.co/A7JNLX9R0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many of those 1,100 reside within the Occoquan District. We have to build on the work of #MedicaidExpansion by brin… https://t.co/9CurfzkMxk]]></document></documents></author>