<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@david_borts fabulous @wes_chiasson maybe Borts should publish. Cato ? @BrianCato]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Someone should ask this imbecile when she was a bartender did she claim all her tips why don’t we look into that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROAD2LPGA @SiGChamp Reachable in 2. Make for a real exciting finish maybe!! #GoTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Yeah. I keep seeing people talking about HS missiles. But never any actual evidence, let alone proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBFazz1213 @Phillies That won’t do it. They now have to beat Arenado $32.5 AAV and possibly Greinke’s $34.5 AAV. I… https://t.co/nLsVh3q4Fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Google is calling today Washington’s Birthday... well I guess @realDonaldTrump already owns enough real estate in your thoughts 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett I never weigh in another person's private issues. And I reserve any judgement. That being said Afri… https://t.co/gv1yzAachg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robin61mcr @musicand_tennis @TheJonesPR @okelmann @BuryBoy53 Sending love x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teliotross @the_fried_egg @BandonDunesGolf  Bandon Trails #13 green  to #14 tee..its a must and a tradition...skip the shuttle]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB to the Bills? I bet that’s not what he envisioned when he asked for a trade 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold @tweetmommybop @MotherJones @realDonaldTrump There's Yang everywhere!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only America can fire your dumb fucking lying ass . I’m from Brooklyn NY and were and still are a disgrace to be… https://t.co/dr7QxtC4d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @gsburmaster and @Keetan_Munsell on making 2nd team all state!  @swimdusty @CurtisLStevens @We_Are_SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Even Better Than The Real Thing (Fish Out Of Water Remix) by @U2 on @PandoraMusic… https://t.co/X45PwrOhXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Omar was put on the “all important” Foreign Relations Committee by DEM leadership. She has some interesting vie… https://t.co/1MczJUrXUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Squid_Ewart @youngcodling @AOC @washingtonpost @guardian She chimed in but she didn’t do anything as a politician… https://t.co/ahzM5uvOLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lloydbanks If you my Biggs you my nigga till the end! One of my favorites brother! Come out with a v6 part 2 man. V6 was so fire 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get out of your comfort zone  #BeYourOwnHero #Entrepreneurishment #beyourownboss #entrepreneur #businessman @ Texas https://t.co/3M1HXWn2p6]]></document><document><![CDATA[People hype up the wrong foods. Yeah bacon and ranch are good, but have you ever had straight shredded cheese outta… https://t.co/iEvLTKL7UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarratedWatson If Eli El Chantiry was still Chair tgat budget would be balanced.  Deans Chair?  $2.4 million hole!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyasportschick It’s incredible! Usually first 10 to 15 minutes is dedicated to negative bullshit about our president!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tradition at all UCLA events is our school cheer, the 8-Clap. The Bruin tradition at a Dinner For 12 Strangers… https://t.co/xb7bCUxG31]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best pal used to hang his head out the back of the truck and watch the traffic behind us. Should I just cut a ho… https://t.co/QeOsr10ib0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew these would be good snow shoes? #unexpectedbenefits @ Avalon Clinton https://t.co/NocMVzty2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey twitter what are we watching tonight? My functioning is so low that I’ve managed to start up Netflix but now ki… https://t.co/iFUzIIQiP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old Mainer on the lift: let the snow land only on the mountain so that when folks look at their dooryards, they’ll… https://t.co/mZyArhb1ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyCraig you really want to advertise on the Tucker Carlson show now? Hasn't he done and said enough about women… https://t.co/9tCoAsKoZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiscoSports4 @AjaxxEsports @bbuddhas @cocosmithy10 @tyschrupp05 @RyanHer88338280 @ProFootballTalk Noooo.... I dont want AIDS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running to win some goodies thanks to @looneytuneswom #gleam #giveaways https://t.co/R60mLqkDBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to catch @prairiepublic's Prairie Pulse tonight as #SanfordHeart's Dr. Thomas Haldis and Sanford Center for… https://t.co/TCDMGGfVFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that I just clam up when I'm frustrated because people think I'm hurt ... but really,  I'm just trying not to kill you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@North2North @Ken_Rosenthal Boras wanted more than the Stanton $326M and got it, no matter how many years. Ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[forgot the most important part. i was thinking a line drive up the middle    hmmmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro the pool ain’t the only thing that can make your girlfriend wet bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he’s just getting started!  Way to go Director Farmer and thanks for your leadership! @naic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dish guess I’ll have it switch providers so I can watch @GameOfThrones on demand leading up to the new season. Let’s go already]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Wheaton_Thunder men’s hoops on the Final Four. Here are some 2018 highlights with @AndrewPitkinRJ on t… https://t.co/EAJXHChlay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @NancyKoda I have date that true American s regardless of race are waking up to the staged racism a… https://t.co/F1U0JPvRlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[eXp Realty has exactly zero franchises.  Are you with a franchisee or actually with the company brokerage? Here in… https://t.co/Kdnemv4QN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevorjackson5 and @Tinashe are two great artists that is underrated and don’t get the respect they deserve... it’… https://t.co/bzz0xCaYKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to tune in to @KUSoftball pregame at 7:50am CT as we preview the matchup with Louisville and go one on on… https://t.co/WsiTkPEASY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@everywriter great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my write-up of PSYCHO SHARK https://t.co/KQQWhoAmGr https://t.co/XyucyrMbKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 52: Provide value! Use your passion to create slipstreams for others. I always said when I was young and coming… https://t.co/VUCx12mi9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:26.9°F WchillLow:19.9°F Wind:0 mph Dir:--- Baro:Falling slowly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:81% UV:0.0 @ 08:30 03/09/19 #weathe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrence Howard just made me love him as a brother. He stood up for his friend and co worker. At a time when we kno… https://t.co/OoPlWmxHcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VictoryMonday Big SHOUT OUT and Big CONGRATULATIONS  @HailStateSB 3 Wins @HailStateBB 2 Wins @HailStateWBK Win… https://t.co/96wIMRxKql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s been a bad day. And now it’s 4:08am and I just had wine delivered so .... here we are. #adulting]]></document><document><![CDATA[It wasn’t always pretty, but we found a way to get the job done.  The Apollos win a thriller in San Antonio 37-29.… https://t.co/U56NDJBKWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Good afternoon mr. President thank you for being Miami you are the greatest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthFaceHiker Of course! It was new to me too 😀 will also ping you on ms mail in case u wanna grab logs direct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlyonne I found Oatmeal on my way to Dallas this morning and it appears he was prepping someone for another round… https://t.co/ugJXhmF2b1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveLeveridge David! That means the world to me. Can’t thank you enough for your kind words. Can’t wait to get bac… https://t.co/sWe6tGfLYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslesBlog did I miss the part where devils attendance has stayed strong as the team has hit bottom this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheapgreengo Don't know how effective that would be. I almost wonder if a petition to get the bars to voluntarily… https://t.co/pZ2w6yfPy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro just told it was a dog in the byke and I thought he said a dog was on a bike I’m like rrrr? Turns out he just m… https://t.co/UvnE1rZ8Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Adventure is out there”! Plaid shirt from #SurplusPH! @ Tom Sawyer Scavage Fort https://t.co/8et42A4hJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we did an interview with @stonepizzagvl to find out more about their fire inspired pizza and their business.… https://t.co/Q9wjGYXj10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! Welcome to the future. Our Samsung Galaxy S10 Hands-On is live! https://t.co/llRRQp8yI4 #Unpacked]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has blessed @madflavor with another year! Happy Birthday Uncle Joey! They don't know who they dealing with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much fun last month with my beautiful boys 😍  #StartedAsChuckECheeseNowWeHere @ Chuck E. Cheese’s https://t.co/HvUS3FHlOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaherToumi @parthaskar @Jacquelin_Joyce @NeilFlochMD @Mpmok @cynthiamich @emilykate2803 @AbdTahrani @BrownAdey You… https://t.co/13aoU29ia0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Nonsense! You should follow @charliekirk11 to see how wrong you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so, so good. And Eastbay was so good. I still remember how the pages smelled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its No I just think it’s mind blowing that this woman cared enough about people to post it. The fact she appe… https://t.co/R5NaMI2STG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianCoz @mortreport Why would ‘that guy’ want to be reunited with Gase? I would understand if that’s his only opt… https://t.co/cbvDxfFPAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie removing every product involving Jordyn from her website. https://t.co/sJU40VJV1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 Yeah, like the Russians are doing it. From what I understand, the Russians owns her, Kat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carrabis already going after the Yankees, loser is scared already. See you in October!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NB_Tie @Jordanwclark @IanRowss Ian and I will be on soon https://t.co/2HW9mHCZq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any apartments in Chicago with air conditioning, or does everyone just sweat May-September?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jo_elparady I don’t think the giants want AB and OBJ and a quarterback that can’t throw the ball. Not to mention t… https://t.co/WNNEiSpnFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hankgreen @timoreilly @Moonalice What are you try to say hear?  Bias in natural intelligence?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr I already saw someone blame the Chicago PD. I guess that's a start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunny and snowy good times with friends old and new on day one of Tom, Haiko and Mikes' trip to the Pacific Northwe… https://t.co/kx488bPGXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might have put more wine in me than the recipe. https://t.co/qg1iUFDCfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one more episode to go of #EscapeAtDannemora and will hopefully get to catch it tomorrow... Hot fire series… https://t.co/NBujsA0qQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelStudios @brielarson @brielarson please tell me where I can get that outfit. I need to feel powerful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee Democrats need to be dissolved and put out of business. All they do is hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 If they do it, it will be undone.  Great to see them scrambling though. Delicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalieStandridge i've made mistakes in this relationship. i messed up, i wish i could go back and change it but i c… https://t.co/6l1fjFk6wT]]></document><document><![CDATA[if forgetting to take my medicine was an Olympic sport i’d have more medals than Michael Phelps]]></document><document><![CDATA[A white kid with a "high motor"???   His weakness? Being white 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/Clhe6nQyvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Kilimanjaro Club (Concierge Lounge) in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/1E75tm93tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debut album comes out next month! Your life will never be the same! @Supercelnyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @nytimes Story supports the continued pressure to secure the border and the motives of… https://t.co/GyZEqLkkNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wenzelj64 @DakSt8Football @thehill @DSUFootball @DSUAthletics @SenJohnThune @RepDustyJohnson It was reported on a… https://t.co/yDVOckTreU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly believe that the whole “don’t fuck with thots” narrative is an excuse used to justify why men generally… https://t.co/UrH3toc0Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwainEvent Huge TN fan, and I know we just beat them, but they are a better team]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won't need it until football. Twenty cent lines in baseball won't work for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just adds to a great season thus far. But all focus goes to that final goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWIPE RIGHT‼️ SWIPE RIGHT‼️ The first picture was taken on November 6, 2017. The second picture was taken March 8,… https://t.co/VxRrztQcd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MapleLeafs tonight is @91Tavares night! Let it be known that we are pumped to have him home! #GETLOUD #LeafsNation… https://t.co/JCDE4iEzq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinCl66124339 @ThanChesher @NBCNews @NBCOUT It is straight forward- you either believe in God and Church he crea… https://t.co/emySJZefFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@este_juanito @sunflowernaay Damn Juan. Tryna steal yo girls debit card]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cc Play Ball ⚾️🎟@Rockies can I bring the team? @BonJovi just a few friends...🏴‍☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great panel with the CAP team, the most intense problem solvers at Cisco #WOI2019 #WeAreCisco #companyculture… https://t.co/v3xCyl4iVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Holtman's Donut Shop in West Chester, OH https://t.co/eRLqDH6m0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing morning. I am a Uber Platinum man.   I want to thank...Sabeing Thai...Mighty Quinn’s Barbaque...and most im… https://t.co/w23xy5Zlz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestonTGabriel @Frick_Nanklin @jruhland21 @liz013199 @kyraorwickk Unless you personally suffer from either one of… https://t.co/NQC0Naoh8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only gonna watch captain. Marvel cause it’s linked to end game but after that I’m done except for spider man]]></document></documents></author>