<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Que lindo celebrar el amor, en todas sus formas. Aquí abajo el amor en su máximo expresión, presente en mi vida💙 https://t.co/G5RcVsQOjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymeganlove I would sign up in a heartbeat! I finally have space to potentially take nice photos at home but I’m t… https://t.co/j5eUgsfFfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dreamweasel @realDonaldTrump Mr president dude is making a pathetic effort to cover for his gaff. He doesn't have… https://t.co/HTRk0RdazZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst thing is when you put a pair of tight jeans on but they begin to stretch out the more you wear them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t seem to ever fall asleep at night anymore so here I am just online shopping 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i saw a few of my mutuals talking about vidcon and i was gonna try and see if i can afford to go but i remembered t… https://t.co/QhToqIFlFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Jean jacket makes me absolutely unhinged like I'm a Rockstar I'm untouchable you all wish you had me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still life with skull and moon watercolor @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/VRxiabwSiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police say the man was pointing handguns at passing cars and people walking by. 2 officers shot and killed him. No… https://t.co/rYGvGqe4AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you didn’t get me a valentine’s day gift either come throw money or donate any amount to:… https://t.co/Q9y8cto4i2]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT @JJDiGeronimo Do you have a #Professional #brand? Check out this advice. #branding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrvingDavis @Devitaits @alpha_dweeb @steph93065 @Bootz_Adams @Si_fazoooo @Mr_MileHi @bodydouble @auridgold @AOC… https://t.co/bCo5h6Bo2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another country concert....Rib Round Up ashpa_c @jlpet328 #countrygirls #countrymusic #besties… https://t.co/MXJq4FJk0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes, like at around 6UTC near -99long. in the loop above, one of these heterogeneities can change the wind sp… https://t.co/DbitaYdex5]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: I really need to go to the gym and get in shape me *3 hours later*:]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinLessler @Caroline_OF_B The same bias that leads to these issues means that we often need white male allies t… https://t.co/Dm3XVfWeqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino The commys have meuller! What do americans have for strength to get rid of these deliquents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Trump is a good man, and is trying to Americans free from Socialism.  If you don’t like… https://t.co/hhjYS1qAZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bells0_0 @propilot123 @JoeyFakaBean @kathygriffin @JussieSmollett Evidence must be coming in on Jussie’s attack, i… https://t.co/RWpn1tsvu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[i take it to heart when people i care about deliberately ignore me or give me the cold shoulder. so if you don’t he… https://t.co/KA594VGQKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I have to work tomorrow  Can someone buy a ticket for me for the 15th and I will pay you back on paypal I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents from Grissom Elementary on far South Side are here to speak about overcrowding]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't work yourself to death folks! Rest and Retreat are very important #selflove #selfcare  . .. ... .... .....… https://t.co/IncSt492r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you reach this level in a relationship.... Congratulations💞💞There is no breakup🙄🙄 @ Baybridge At Sugar Lakes,… https://t.co/tztVTfXi3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have no interest or like  idk motivation??? i needa be on my own we cool  u my friend  jus not toooo much]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s the same thing with bathroom stalls. why do y’all wanna be close to people so bad in public?????? bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yumabooma That could have been forensic evidence, and you washed it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh cool. Family that owns the Cubs is tangentially (at best) linked to a white nationalist. Cool cool cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyEasterBunnyWillBe bought by me because after all these years, he still doesn't know all I want is a FUCKIN Choco… https://t.co/VTpNGfkcvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I wasn’t the only one getting notes of Walugi last night... https://t.co/x3A3CUEejy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AcademyAwards #Queen The great Freddy Mercury #AdamLambert 👏🏻 👏🏻 👏🏻 👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisCarlos El lazo que les van a poner en el cuello es el único que debemos fortalecer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deleznable y perversa ACTITUD de esta mujer ante un problema que amenaza a las mujeres. ¿En verdad tú insensibilida… https://t.co/wLXSlYp2Sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun adventure yesterday watch the parade, got my favorite food at pier side grill, crab cakes and watermelon… https://t.co/St2VMLATSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[it just taste like cheap white ppl food to me lmaoo, the only thing i’ll get is the buffalo blasts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoondriftMusing Sadly not many do teach respect. A lot slack in that department.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLizLincoln @PiperJDrake @BreedingCynthia AMEN! Thank you, Liz. 💗 https://t.co/Kc12EWiV0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever written a sentence, re-read it, and then thought to yourself "that is the worst sentence anyone has e… https://t.co/hloZT281Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett What about Christopher Hasson who had a hit list of all your favorite enemies--Dem… https://t.co/p2txcS9tg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IPEEON_NAZIS I don't have one. I have a 80 years old cottage. We can have tea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you really love somebody it’s so hard to match their energy man, that’s the shit that fuckin’ sucks ✍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen. i’ve been trying to tweet this hilarious tweet for so long but my tweets are not going through. this will h… https://t.co/QINHi7878B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustaSlob @BlogChurchWork @Headerop1 @openpodbaydoor_ @pricklyeater @amvetsupport @BlueGhost40_ @SpeakerPelosi… https://t.co/wx70bskbIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching men’s vault: that other dude did that without a half twist and fell on his butt. This dude had the twis… https://t.co/76lnbm4v6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gatorland makes zip line handicap accessible #Fox35 https://t.co/b5ujFCRWIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really wishing my Saturday night looked a little more like this! Hope you’re all having a 10/10 weekend 🖤 @ Miami,… https://t.co/rW8ncu9Zxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennychesney @noshoesradio  hey  #kennychesney where are you spending your day in sun ☀️ or 🥶 cold ?!?! Because we… https://t.co/tyE9TGTZlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rarely take days off and this one was so refreshing(even tho I snapped a hundred pics but out of pleasure only).… https://t.co/0Ax40h8Q2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow those MagCam images really gave me chills. 😬 @Zak_Bagans @BillyTolley @AaronGoodwin #GhostAdventures]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jazzurday night!! #FFL #jazz #spaghettini @ Spaghettini https://t.co/tGRiZPz1zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklaureano989 I am so very sorry. Being a boxer mom myself, I understand the heartbreak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My job is literally going to be the death of me. They called me to come in and work on my day OFF after I’ve been w… https://t.co/XTrc2tO8ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did everyone on twitter just get the same notification? https://t.co/tYUPbhMunC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Necesito soltar lo que ya me solto hace mucho y nunca trato de alcanzarme de nuevo 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MindReels @MindReelsBTS @LizWhitmere is doing a thing!  Let's help get it done and share, share, share away! 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BayerUS Boycotting you until you pull ads from @FOXTV and @TuckerCarlson show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kellee_Marie1 What Jacob got me since I had a bad day lol https://t.co/tcPFidk4WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pathways &amp; Connections spending the afternoon with @JBakerArtEd @MPSPanthers. Thank you. https://t.co/jMxTPel95l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSavedow @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Do you really think you’re getting the real news? https://t.co/GTayl4jq5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ev’s Easter dress came in the mail today and I’m so sad because there’s no way it’s going to fit 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh why do I feel like I have to redevelop my personality and redefine who I am as person EVERY time I have an existential crisis]]></document><document><![CDATA[so now republican operatives (on Katy Turs show) are not sure Kilimnk is a spy. Really?  You know better because wh… https://t.co/cEAqhrnoo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dontshutusupp She speaks good English.  Scary thought is that she and others like her will end up here in the US e… https://t.co/av2r8CzbEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 Don’t you know it doesn’t matter. Nothing matters anymore. There’s no rule of law in the WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grimsley_ashley @kaylee_dyer I knew you was gonna say something Ashley 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will have #72 @RyanSmithRacing @HeffnerRacing @RedRobinRacing apparel for sale at the Icebreaker… https://t.co/aPtEpyHzfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[5. I do believe she has lied about her dad. MANY who knew her growing up said they were very close, not to mention… https://t.co/HZ1t9XEeKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words of advice .. when a woman asks you a question and starts it with “be honest” we already know the truth so don’t play stupid lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with martharedbone @JeanineLiburd @BRICartsmedia for #BRICHouseSessions with @TalibKweli  @ BRIC https://t.co/I8p68Cpag4]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨New Product Alert! @ “Best BCAA w/energy” use discount code “PAE” for 20% off your entire purchase. Message! ⬇️ ⠀⠀… https://t.co/ZDXPuBle9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[good afternoon just checking in to remind you that every single brockhampton song ever produced is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OCSB @OCSBSpecEd @deb_lawlor @RCopOCSB @manon_seguin @JoanBarry2 @pamela2of5 @debbiefrendo @OCSB_MentalHlth]]></document><document><![CDATA[C’mon Shay Sharp! Kobe willed that bumass team in 2012 to the playoffs but got tore his achilles against GS AND STI… https://t.co/8AAVTPFkzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebrickman @MarcDrummond I’d like to pay for highway maintenance through progressive income tax—especially those… https://t.co/DGF3hc4BSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need a really good conservative group of attorneys to sue Congress members that are CLEARLY not adhering to thei… https://t.co/i5rgv5ebGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little Louis the Ferret is ready for a forever home! At the @ontariospca Thank you @kalliemilleman for bringing thi… https://t.co/o1OfjYIdCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n_riddell And I definitely don’t think any era gets a pass. That’s not what I said]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay 12 years ago, Brad Delp, late lead singer of rock band Boston, passed away at age 55. #RIPBradDelp… https://t.co/MGKy2C5H0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on a MUCH NEEDED spontaneous beach weekend trip with Chase thank god]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fuji302 I practice Catholicism, I appreciate the interpretations of the Spirit and the Word by other faiths. And I… https://t.co/cFW60l0gpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjayiRiquePod HAPPY BLACK HISTORY. I HONOR THE ANCESTORS WHOM HONOR ME..GOOD MORNING AND HAVE A GREAT DAY! https://t.co/4YazsPhudT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pocket poems were a success! 📝 #ReadAcrossAmerica #WeAreVincentFarm https://t.co/QM5nZ6th5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Painting Large day in Exploring Abstract class was a success! Just one more week until the Winter session ends. L… https://t.co/lHwyjelRMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normanrockwhale @jayjayybaddie I’ve been listening to this clip on repeat, do we have a name??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Textured LOB🖤 •• sooo in love with this new look for my babe rana_kreiger how perfect is she🤩 @ Red Bank, New Jersey https://t.co/m7syrX2hs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB ravers don’t know how to rave lol sad to say I missed the Fresno crowd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma need for some of yall mommas to figure out why they are so angry. Its hella sad that too many of yall xan rela… https://t.co/aSQgsdhbKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an amazing time seeing @coheed last night with @jguardalabene. Super excited to get to meet them tonight! @ The… https://t.co/oXiSM9ZSBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Apparently, hence just the last name initial!😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna start getting my nails done but then I’m like I rather buy something else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerdyNovelty @RalphsGrocery I was told that I’d have to talk to the manager. Bunch of BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the Repubs call themselves Patriots as they disrespect John McCain a real war hero and Patriot. Megan McCain wh… https://t.co/9heYb4ULFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss New York powers — press, legal, political — gave him a pass for years, right through 2016. He was… https://t.co/XBwoblTGyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImWatchingToo @rsmerrymerry @PascoSheriff I hope so. Even our puppy(she’s big) is looking for her bc they play. Frustrating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McMccaffs67 @PhDForum @PhDStudents @WriteThatPhD @firstphdchat It’s been a while for me, but back in 2011 I surviv… https://t.co/WTYVXffc5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @LindseyGrahamSC I'm going w sell his soul for 500 , Alex...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexis is driving and my mom put her hand in the way to honk at a car and now my mom and Alexis are arguing and I can’t stop laughing 💀😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPCNikki1 @coachmandicf 🤣  I think that might win the “torture” prize. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong &amp; Delicate. Diego Cortez. Shown at #plitzsnewyorkcityfashionweek. . . .  . #fashionweek #fashion… https://t.co/rd1OOOSHZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[la persona mas especial de mi vida un año mas de vida Feliz cumple años mi amor!♥️🎉15 de febrero pero de 1968 nacía… https://t.co/mB4fkHiqAp]]></document></documents></author>