<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/FBaFzbeKHx Tony Kemp Went to Heaven to Learn About the Father's Blessing | Sid Roth's It's Supernatural!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This novel is so good. I can’t wait to read the final 30 pages today. Thank you Lisa Senz @StMartinsPress . You alw… https://t.co/3wnxpdrKKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t trust this damn Technology yo.. you really testing me today Apple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[great way to swim my last ever 500 free : breaking 6 mins and going a 5:58 !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed room for today's @UWMadisonCALS  Equity and Diversity Committee Lunch and Learn talk! We will discuss "When… https://t.co/SOKkIZjJ2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[fab fam lil nug is finally official!! @ The Westin Poinsett https://t.co/cidHTNHkF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Larry’s Latest Flamingo Fruit Fight by @BellsBrewery @ Metro North - Darien Train Station — https://t.co/dZNtn9yR2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @BreitbartNews There’s looking on the bright side! Keep that attitude in prison it’ll help time fly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMischief76 @notcapnamerica @Bsanchez1213 @emrazz @CsDaddy7777 Douchebro Brian hit the racist and sexist bingo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauriceBenard @lldubs Yeah let @MauriceBenard give you tips I have 3 boys I know all kids of moves you have to acc… https://t.co/cY658tVGjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie: *Tells Colton she can't get there with him. Also Cassie: "Are you mad at me?"  LMAOOOO. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Besta é aquele que acredita que quem causa rombos na previdência é o trabalhador da área privada. Nunca foi e jamai… https://t.co/yMMsaIWEPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[congratulations @TheNate156!!!  Great game. @OConnellHS @DJOAlumni @OConnellBBall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost baby shower time!  Who said I’m not crafty?! #phoenixrealestate @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/mipGQkAqgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta or you can unblock @walruswhisperer and get the animals out of marine land]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda got carried away but the vocal booth is so very near being done that it’s hard to set aside and try to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only I would buy a phone screen protector and instantly break it while trying to put it on my phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t line up my job interview with my hair washing schedule. Just another reason to hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my newest #listing 9 Bluebird Road #SouthGlensFallsVlg #NY  https://t.co/g6XgaZnpRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qKHB1YOAzx 0:26 the air feels weird in alot of places recently]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Qualtrics did anyone get a pic of my #lilbostonboy with his headphones on the big screen? I would love to see one… https://t.co/w9jxq1R8ut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely outrageous. I wonder if the judge was aware of the really nasty work he did for repressive people over i… https://t.co/mbEsyu6TYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetMeLiveFFS1 @UnkleSilk Everybody in the house be looking at me like a deer in headlights. 😆. I do the same thing… https://t.co/aI2XDMCCAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I understand. It’s almost 31 years since I lost my adored &amp; perfect Dad and I miss and love him every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKELLY; HEBREWS 4:12; FOR THE WORD OF GOD IS QUICK, AND POWERFUL, AND SHARPER THAN ANY TWOEDGED SWORD, PIERCING EV… https://t.co/VhAZqDolr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisaJardine @RansomSeries You know when that bubble bursts? It’s hard to put the pieces back together..Eric has a… https://t.co/FFuf3aQbxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[In bed...windows shaking from massive thunderstorm...guessing its going to be a rough night of sleep. Somehow bebe… https://t.co/xuW6JfpEBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[fieldingwinery X @benchbrewing 🥂🍻 . #goodtimes #goodpeeps #weekendvibes @ Fielding Estate Winery https://t.co/1sfINsrZcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe on this day last year I was pregnant and had no clue I would be going into labor the next day or ha… https://t.co/RkzRWQYGl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bridget, 6th grade ELA @DeSanaMiddle. Rainy day...hmmm.  Watching Dr Who reruns or reading #forsythpln https://t.co/YW3hDvX76o]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, yeah, @AirCanada... a *3-hour* delay due to a “soiled seat cushion” should be the premise for an SNL sketch, no… https://t.co/LCQliNXm0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course @Money23Green @andre are questionable for tonight... y’all afraid of @rudygobert27 tbfh!!! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animals do have feelings! So touching and precious!! #adoptapet #agedlikefinewine #nopuppymills]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AshWednesday #Lent2019 it’s not about giving up candy and donuts.. let’s get our minds focused on God. FAST on thi… https://t.co/IchhCl94h3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliviaNorwood Brett Young was at Red Rocks the other night, and I cried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @DonaldJTrumpJr Wait. Weren't you all bitching about using kids as (props) just last week? Stop it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalmargaritaday !! 🥑🌮🍹🥃 &lt;—- #tequila (@ La Santisima in Phoenix, AZ) https://t.co/IvgzHunXSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreenbanksy @PPansBusShelter Jake and I love being friends with bus stops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️ Happy Valentine's Day! ♥️ Xxoo love,  Claudette * Miss Fluff . . #valentines #burlesque #cherries #showgirls… https://t.co/puIHP0fEYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t perfect but I try my best to be as mature as I can be. Yes I slip up at time but I always make sure to be true to myself and mature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this is why you don’t let just anyone run your social media accounts just because they have one of their own!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@X2Mjc @S_E_Phillips @Aileenbsmith @EdKrassen @Reuters My father was a legal immigrant from Communist Yugoslavia. T… https://t.co/MGczz8CpGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am extremely sad right now but I still have a lot of extremely useful pieces of ‘60s-‘70s folk-rock trivia at my disposal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time I get in an argument I’m just gonna yell “I’m baby!” and storm off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Suzie_Taka @jennavanklav Binge listened to AMAMABAS on Friday. Happy with my life choices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sifill_LDF Good morning. This photo moved me. And it makes me think of the breakdown of our communities, of the po… https://t.co/3ADFOh5COv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffping @suziday123 @charmed_twice @AnxietyPath @dally_russell @SoDivineBunny @LaurenCurtisArt @angiesmith5… https://t.co/iqb8c4cBZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the sweetest baby boy, Travis Konecny https://t.co/GlRjk78Wvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends I love me some Nickelback, I have loved their music since they came out, my husband not so much! Whe… https://t.co/PDynMEkKPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing i miss about eating meat is @Jollibee Chicken Joy. If someone can figure out a way to make this with… https://t.co/SaJFY2JhGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albunnz Taylor Swift...j/k. Whitney Houston, Tina Turner and my favorite of all time, The Beatles “Here, There &amp; Everywhere.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lieutenantflan @KurtSchlichter Bitter backward??? Hmm 🤔 rettib ??? 😂😂😂🤣 Moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggjourneys @outofofficeblnd @lduboistravel @RootsWingsBlog @Deefordiane1 @Thetinkerbug @WithTheDeVaulls… https://t.co/Ejg2yNiSeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySkinnerCA @takebackousd Free Oakland’s budget, prioritize excellence in public comprehensive school]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at First Ward Place in Charlotte, NC w/ @wiljames https://t.co/gBHyuPRdXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC follow up to my last tweet.  You keep doing what you're doing and send me updates.  Totally impressed by you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason to hate Chuck Todd. I thought I ran out of reasons but I guess I didn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicksonright My husband was in the Navy. Every so often when we’re out to eat, if he sees fellow military or even… https://t.co/0OV4q2fI6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loud_Mrs It’s ok because regardless of their shady refs Bison still got that win💯🏀👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucking a niggas dick &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; ALWAYS giving a nigga lip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma made an IG &amp; Facebook so now she’s showing everyone my posts lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@28delayslater @BLKMDL3 @dogsoftesla @frunkpuppy Thanks Earl. Channeling his inner yoda!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @fsuwbb comes to town (or close enough). Much needed time with my #NoleFam @ Clemson University https://t.co/n1FVKcg41G]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your dude's a producer, this is the best seat in the house! https://t.co/Qe8qcFT0Ez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold 🥶 isn’t going anywhere in the Upper Midwest at least thru mid-March!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby. I AM and WILL be a great mom! I will see to it my child has everything it needs without depending on others t… https://t.co/XgDxDDVYZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meh. This reminds me of somebody else I know...who doesn't take responsibility for his actions, either.  Jussie Smo… https://t.co/iIKB5MxvIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter has been kicking my butt. Thank you jjthornhill and @aaptiv for this great workout! #sub305ktraining… https://t.co/caqAgN2HKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LePoint @mariametig @LouisChahuneau Mariame Tighanimine « l’hystérie collective » sur le port du voile : «Je pense… https://t.co/hpwKtzK4X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re losing far too many alternative trailblazers too soon.... 🔥 #TheProdigy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvbrian @smerconish @realDonaldTrump Did you notice that the question didn't allow for any description of his and… https://t.co/OE8FlkRKI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arts alert: go see The Crucible at Noblesville HS tonight and their stellar performance. Then spend Sunday afternoo… https://t.co/4pd7fhkrZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pharrell here talking about being a man while he wears camo shorts on stage at the #Oscars2019. Mmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out the @LouisvilleMBB with @bjweig01 #GoCards #BeatClemson https://t.co/xzr9lIIlow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crews are on scene of a small commercial fire at 1214 Celebrity Cir.  The fire is out at this time, but please avoid the area at this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HPluckrose I'm learning Dutch on Duolingo. I can talk all about who is eating a sandwich, drinking milk or reading a newspaper. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy at the bar was like “this is a make or break question: when you buy chicken nuggets, do you dip in bbq or… https://t.co/t0qoXY8mJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke needs a punch in the face....#MarriedAtFirstSight #MAFS https://t.co/FGenkgGwRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarbochov Sounds like something a person passionate about security should take up. Might be cool if someone local… https://t.co/HuJ7XJk6p4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry Nicolle - President Trump is about illegal immigrants - the left is RACE baiting!! 😡 President Trump is helpi… https://t.co/WbfOta16MY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't even think about it...he will hand out autographs at the crash site!  Leave the "wicckked one" BE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleryTV Thank you for driving to Owatonna. I have to drive from Owatonna to Faribault and I really appreciate you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics That guy is nuts.  Is he off his meds?  This is the result of Reagan's attack on mental healthcare… https://t.co/6YemOcsjRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @mattgaetz When you get in JAIL WITH TRUMF WILL BRING BOTH OF YOU KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN SINCE YOU HAVE HORRID… https://t.co/HvRvEibpjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardTHardy Well, if it was after firing him, we might just hear more interesting stories from this WH insider.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want my life to feel like I’m always on vacation but I’m here and miserable]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it still snowed after such a beautiful day yesterday. I’m done with you winter!! https://t.co/QthPg5e9my]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waitress: “what did you think it was going to be like?”  Melissa returning her cobbler: “I did not think it was goi… https://t.co/KASkr7SSdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HKAlyssa Just curious! I always ask — I just want to know the author will be in good hands. If they said someone s… https://t.co/EmnNyvpoZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was AWFUL. But I made it up with some good news, and a day of running around town. Today was good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport can we get a Straw emoji? Doesn’t need to be a plethora of straws just one or two would suffice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisOhEx Lmao my bad Chris 😩  Happy birthday tho! Or do you celebrate it tomorrow? Or should I just tell you happ… https://t.co/6oiAu0BMcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Previous coverage here: Man arrested in bomb threat at North Buncombe Elementary https://t.co/ETYiETbkTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[HR reppin’ for Spirit Day! 🦁🤗💚🎉 #SaintLeoUniversity https://t.co/LyMaJOS0ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanboyne @JoyceWhiteVance He seems to do the latter on a regular basis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Classichassis @MystryeDragon @MargNation @KaterinaKestem1 @Hailee_RN @songbird_ali @TiffanyRWiggins @Birdy_Willeke… https://t.co/FHWY9PnJQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I pick up my refund check tomorrow which means I can finally move to Norfolk and everything will be perfect 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump @GOP @FBI @HillaryClinton https://t.co/yTKIk1YG7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily @Martie719 No, the crime of *kneeling* is greater than punching a women so you know its greater than soliciting sex]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they say they want to hire me but can’t afford me. #next #girlboss  #entrepreneur @ Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/qrifx9FNGS]]></document></documents></author>