<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You can’t even complement a girl without them thinking your flirting smhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pres Wintersteen talks about a innovative and entrepreneurial environment at ISU #StrongIowa https://t.co/Xsu5Ju3Qsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmeinke if that is the case if the edge guys are gone I hope they trade back and address another need there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elena_WTAE Shouldn’t you recognize your anchors, when they introduce you on a live shot? It’s more professional, a… https://t.co/5CliXGdLxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LedyardNFLDraft Three ole miss players loooooool. Think that says a lot about the offense they played in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dawg @ScuddaButta said “I know you couldn’t join us tonight cause you had maya so I brought y’all a pizza.” That… https://t.co/dFbHohanZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I was tired... I really slept in But Tibbers kept me company https://t.co/CzgEDfWk99]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamXMen on @TyltEnt—can't wait for the X-Men to join the MCU https://t.co/8M7Zg60Wfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio @THEChrisMack I mean we had to watch him kiss Tom Brady so.... https://t.co/YRC9BjRHPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started running 10 days ago so I could take part in Tuesday morning fun run with @Skidrowrunclub @isri2019 and toda… https://t.co/cbRBWoVCX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemphisMafiaTCB The Department of Justice announced Wednesday that it has opened an investigation into convicted s… https://t.co/7eJz3qzXAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 50th Little Feat! From @drcraigwax The Rock ‘n Roll Doctor Can’t wait to catch up with Paul Barrere, guitaris… https://t.co/7TR8dKpxxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the suggestions so far! Any more? Trying to do a serious level up on API care and feeding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff is not happy with the way Mueller's report is being handled, so he's having a hissy fit. This politicia… https://t.co/DEO4BGDK8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[JOIN @djturbulence FOR ANOTHER #flawlessmondays @jewellasvegas 📲 440.487.5000 4 FREE ENTRY ON MY GUESTLIST OR TABLE… https://t.co/wWKVuduvsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Registered Nurse, OBGYN RN for Pioneer Womens Health -… https://t.co/LewyStHI22]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be the only person who doesn’t eat fries from McDonald’s with ketchup. They are so good on there own they don’t need condiments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Certain brands are not made for everybody and that’s okay. I know this quote is from a movie but still... “You don’… https://t.co/f2OCMHUxZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @mrdavehollis for letting me know how to watch this today! And for “If you’re not growing, you’re dying.” A… https://t.co/eOjNTqkFNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what if they put Ultron and Deadpool in to the maybe timeloop of this #Endgame?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MIJPVenezuela @NestorReverol @NicolasMaduro Viejo cagalitroso Ponte las pilas y ponle vigilancia a la mujer tuya p… https://t.co/rX0vy239ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting data from Kevin N Bass in Twitter. We are fatter due to excess calories from oils and fats. Not sugar.… https://t.co/YbntQ4zDfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either the wealthy have no taste, or this thing really is the ultimate truck...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t want to go on a rant about ASA college I but it’s looking like I’m going to have to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my co-author Daniel. I’m constantly blown away by his talent, creativity, and dedication. Honored to be wor… https://t.co/Y8SFJiUJ2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can read this, you’ve helped me reach 10 followers. Thank you! #hearties @hallmarkchannel #WCTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kings drop their fifth straight. One week till the deadline. Wonder who has played their last home game in a Kings uni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone that has a chance to contend in the NL East has done something to improve their team this offseason.  And… https://t.co/KkzIFCNYY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmartBeta1 @patrick_oshag @modestproposal1 We're not fans of buybacks done at rich valuations.   As you probably k… https://t.co/UGOM1KrWIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@booksNrulers @NBCNewYork he run the  local gas station, so,  till  the day he died  he carried a gun... we  never… https://t.co/JZRtKDzSFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren is so opposed to Big Tech she...  🤔Paid twitter 🤔🤔To use my data 🤔🤔🤔To target me with this ad 🤔🤔🤔🤔… https://t.co/c9bSh2l7qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiserableSDFan No, what’s going to happen is that obviously he’s going to pinch hit for Machado using our clutch player .. pirela .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una cosa es tenerse autoestima y otra muy distinta es echarse mentiras con el mismo fin!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notsgueda gracias por desenmascarar a @aran_tirado . Vaya que se ha quedado corto. En aras de la objetividad pedim… https://t.co/ng2K6gI7Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tuesday morning drive to the Chicago south suburbs. The stream is fixed and in focus today after a ruff Monday.… https://t.co/xUH8UO3wo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the near future for MAGA conservatives. Time for us to stand up as one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $2,881.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/e0kEvLJWRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please let me know! I will be attending District Boys Basketball Games at Ohio Northern, BUT we will welcome you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entonces la cancelación y el quebranto a las finanzas del Estado fue un error, hay responsabilidad penal en esto??… https://t.co/BCqQERR2Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put nuclear/radioactive waste in the f’n desert. That is where it belongs. Whether Yucca Mountain or another site i… https://t.co/TL0zvbeW0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bapartofmylife @patriot_loves @gatewaypundit The destruction of democracy is the agenda of The Justice Democrats.… https://t.co/8JZS42sr1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat ProTip for #TheTwitterPOTUS ...Wrong Answer. #bluffcity https://t.co/On56sUnJeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[First onto the line is #Spence...Connecting Spence onto the call now....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump Many of us don’t just think he committed crimes - to us, it’s clear that he did so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kipinitreal88 @Jeff_Ermann @Josh_Stirn Yep, so trye, thanks for the reminder.  Still, a neutral court game and I'm… https://t.co/TQJuSvOwoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Tequila Talkin' by Lonestar https://t.co/27QiALP2WZ #lonestar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiltfongjr @ZimmermanSXM He never had the opportunity to learn a route tree and I believe that is what hindered hi… https://t.co/8zr0SbHhVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_fanatic_sports @JCaporoso You’ve missed the point, respectfully. Signing RBs to big deals is proven to be bad bus… https://t.co/OiTLAjcx6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acrphoto I like them! They’re playing in the Wimter classic and I’m going. #gostars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeanutSC The series / movies are so bonkers that I didn’t even notice how little sense that makes.  Star trek does… https://t.co/nBxy9argxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at State route 58 (leavitt road Amherst) in Amherst, OH https://t.co/SS3Teqg2Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz after stumbling across who you are, I now check back on your profile occasionally to see if you’ve chang… https://t.co/xtbnqOHsBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times believemusichall while waiting for the main event @ Believe Music Hall https://t.co/x2obKzoGAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[THAT GOT YOU SUSPENDED?!? But asshole liberals can throw anti-gay slurs at me? Hey @jack, WTF?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobFinnertyWTSP @10NewsWTSP @BrightsideOn10 @GrantWTSP https://t.co/czvY664xCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krisalderson @britt_underwood @JasonWTam @kelleyrmissal @Eddie_Alderson @BrandonRBuddy Oh my lord how I miss @onelifetolive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeted #wifey “29 times my Valentine” My frd Elaine @Jleesmom humorously replied “Did you guys marry at age 2 ? lo… https://t.co/WvxI23Ftjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s intuition never tells her that you don’t care about the subject matter she’s been talking to you about for 20 minutes straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexintheA @FSKPart3 Imagine being a person who says that out loud where people can hear you 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilSadOso Carolina would be undefeated if they played San Francisco U twice a year 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pyrion I dare say the Americans are more infamous as bad tourists than the Chinese. Although the Russians are the runaway champs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got 5th tonight beating Jade and Soccermom(finally) Wally and Jameps were easily my bracket demons for a long time.… https://t.co/5lebAc4Asc]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I ask for @BeyondWland is for a dj to mix in All Star by Smash Mouth into their set 😩 plsssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fascinating glimpse into the fickle minded twerp that Carlson is. @vttrotter]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Pontiac for a pair of super-sectional girls’ basketball games. @SchlarmanHoops and Amboy start at 6 p.m. in the… https://t.co/1qfYwjEPTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidKieninger @wspd2pio Naturally it's a Ford.....I'll leave the rest unsaid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMFlint What did he do to make him a hero ? Bring you a big Subway sandwich?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonz970 @ImabitcSumtimes @luluHru @Briteeye777 @misspunk63 @AnnThacker2 @AW95NJ @galacticaactual @Lexa_Merica… https://t.co/iu0V52yUdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clira65 @StanleyRoberts @PavlovicNBCS @smoothie18 @Dodgers @SFGiants I mean he was well compensated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyokotown You being anxious about being anxious is making me anxious about being anxious.  But seriously, yes, I… https://t.co/XN2WdkGQqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frontrowpreps @juliansdayoff22 @jburns1980 @loud_eddie @MSSsports Hines rbi makes it 3-1 El Capitan. Turlock still batting B3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggie_emaw @CoachRooney16 @dent_hope @MindyWagner68 @CatchItKansas @KSHSAA I’ve noticed many schools no longer po… https://t.co/TrnecW6eK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GNSensay Yeah, but production is lagged 2 months so the flatter rig count should already have resulted in flatter production, but no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 28 - Fox News First Morning Headlines:     Trump-Kim summit ends abruptly with no deal: 'I'd rath… https://t.co/pKZyssKYm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epochchanger Very good analogy. That is exactly what happens. I'll have to use this one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see Shaq I think about how his wife is my size and I just feel.... scared]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for helping bring Super bowl 50 to our great state and being an exceptional leader on the field! You'll be m… https://t.co/lkDTvZZ9Wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Electric Lederhosen by @thebrewtorium at @thebrewtorium — https://t.co/DcaNkn5pTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHarvick We are too Kevin!! @NASCARONFOX is bringing it in 2019!! @NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love big Rhonda but i need one of them cars that warm up in like two seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierra_rebecca @atticsonline @AOC Im not trying to scare you hon.  Just telling you the truth.  You asked me to se… https://t.co/Nww6HRrQIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrattLP @CBR Ugh Turbo 💩💩. What a stinker! This was the good one with Ivan Ooze! Also the end credits opened my… https://t.co/BE2MwaiEB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointed I didn't take down the qualifier as I had a case of the "AVERAGE" last night with 7 of my lineups betw… https://t.co/zVVBgpJAfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARHSwrestling Congrats Michael and Bigler family!!! Great tournament so far and Keep winning!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make that 6️⃣ strikeouts in three innings of relief for @JackPerkins06!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The legend of Pilot Rob continues in the latest #Iditapod. The bulletproof #Iditarod bush pilot. Big game scout.… https://t.co/2CDuTUX1zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle Gun Laws are about saving Lives- Allowing Guns 2B out of control added to dividing our Nation by growing Re… https://t.co/gchzG8STpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draco_Rider Are you that fucking stupid that you don't understand that asking someone why is asking for justification?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts on the new @DetPikachuMovie trailer??  - Still mega hyped - Ludicolo is a legend - Pikachu says "hell" - B… https://t.co/SkQm6JE5QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendaFlournoy1 @MikePoynton @kfoxhouse @SafetyGirl100 @Jr7Jimi @kleigh062 @BeacheyGirl @79uptowngirl… https://t.co/EghniSQdDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of this, tonight's show will be a bit shortened! 7-7:45pm!  If you have any pressing #Preds questions, or… https://t.co/NgjXd86frl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baddgalmal You ain’t never seen something like that pop up on the computer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for standing up to the authoritarian con man occupying the White House, @repblumenauer!… https://t.co/x9zG2Ymy1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon would have generate over $20b in tax revenue at the cost of $3b. Every incentive package given to a corp in… https://t.co/9GR351kPe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les encanta joder al Chicharito con lo de “hacer y no imaginar cosas chingonas”.... como si anotar 200 goles de los… https://t.co/p8ObaqeURu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, our government is introducing legislation that would make the police oversight process fair and transparent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t trust other bottoms that I don’t know to hang around me at the club because they think we’re going t… https://t.co/puUEvMZoIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC  did you punish @realDonaldTrump  for making murder ok????!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyJaffeenergy My film Thirst for Power will be there! Try to watch it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The true best picture Farrely bros winner. #Oscars https://t.co/Yc7JPHZ9SG]]></document></documents></author>