<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[YUM and THANK YOU to my staff and @Manhattan_WBB team! Best staff ever @Coach_Sahar @ABassetti  @caltaylor20… https://t.co/LWl0OZ2JYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swatymyers Never leave home without ‘em. Car stash... Ditto for Cholula too. Keeps the fam happy😎 https://t.co/iN6S2DOgpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@postpolitics Trump is not a thorn in the side of the Republic...He is the Russian knife (Nozh) at its throat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deafheaven Hmm? Tom Dahling, you know my Emotionally Vibrant Self rather the film be more stimulating than what yo… https://t.co/K7OMMqzBiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylafacedd @Lane8music Can’t wait to get weird and have a bathroom adventure again. 😏😏😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[How adorable are my parents?! @Kiwanis #PancakeDay #Kiwanis #Parents #SaturdayMorning https://t.co/pUItm8tKyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[grp=soliciting,aiding, organizing+proffering legal instruct(incorrect),by which migrant wave caravans(intermixed wi… https://t.co/DADqlrhIPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianossaurus A tática malandra de um amigo meu que não se pode fazer um pouco de tudo bem 🙂 de uma pessoa deve estar na minha timeline]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Justice is BLIND @shaunking @ToneXComedy @SybilWilkes @RickeySmiley @MSNBC @TJMShow @IAmSteveHarvey @Diddy… https://t.co/WHD4D7fByx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living that #skymileslife #tamaroundtown #pwcability (at @Delta Sky Club in Tampa, FL) https://t.co/QgignDSFoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boo just gave me the just gave me the cutest valentines speech on the phone since I won’t be able to see him tod… https://t.co/GVZJVvzVON]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gave up coffee for lent and now I’m having dreams about it... when will it end 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoolieWoolz  Hey Woolie, if you could please review this Reddit thread and help us understand your haunted dreads,… https://t.co/JZWruOUq5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I love @ThomasRhett’s music, and because I say his name once and I’m constantly listening to his music, Facebook… https://t.co/HXk9O9MMYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels great to take action.  Join us! @MomsDemand Topeka Kansas #ksleg https://t.co/4VWydn0rYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Refs doing everything to make sure Portland wins tonight and sending the game into OT puts tomorrow’s game in jeopardy too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women’s Day holds a lot of meaning for me. I grew up in an evangelical, patriarchal world where women… https://t.co/96zCzfFR4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDreamer18 @AngrierWHStaff @foxandfriends Oh they’re out there! They just arrested one in Maryland.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne He has the same chance to win as the 99 Dems who are running. Frustrated Americans are 100% unpredictable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFStout @Utebuntu I have 8 only 2 were used tonight it makes me sad as this team is really coming together and the… https://t.co/ocqTbeWR7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 12 when women hood come on I got scared because men grewn men had there way  I've been raped so many times sold… https://t.co/eI8DlgtEnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Have you ever read a political science book? Or even a Wikipedia article on the shift in southern po… https://t.co/7QN3KE5AXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got summoned to jury duty hell yea pour up convicts! bouta fuckin rage 😋🤭😤❤️✈️😛👈🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victoriavolk7 It wasn’t you! You were two under what I saw so I knew better not to keep going!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindafader When I first joined Twitter I ONLY followed drag queens and comedians. Then I added those with politica… https://t.co/oAbuEtGgbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[El tema del aborto es tan controversial porque por una parte a mi parecer es valido cuando el embarazo es por viola… https://t.co/sNR9pAhcdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Igniteucsd check out the last #entrepreneurs #PitchPerfect #igniteucsd https://t.co/C8iO2xw1fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roncorning @KaraSewellTV I've been rocking yellow "computer glasses" for over a year.  They are a life saver.  Eye… https://t.co/SmUEDpm0Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carriecordero @Susan_Hennessey @realDonaldTrump What makes you think Trump would care?  All that work was not abou… https://t.co/5qHxyXeT3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMandyMoore @NBCThisisUs @skelechiwatson Was an extraordinary episode!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[a year ago today I found out that you were gone, not a day goes by that I don’t think about how hard you pushed me… https://t.co/DR6qwoewgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamfish728 Damn. That one messed up my streak. 🤣😂😅 I was sure that was Nick Lachey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ava @kikibaker Dr. Martin Luther King speaking at this link is AWESOME!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xtrixcyclex @PrincessBravato He is allowed to run but we don’t need to give air space]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rev. James Cleveland - I Appreciate All You've Done For Me https://t.co/u4uGwL8s1c via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper. Siberian Husky. Beautiful. #husky #siberianhusky #siberian @ San-Villa Boarding Kennels &amp; Suites LLC https://t.co/GqYQvsffrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[As They Are featuring the lovely @madivalentine publishes tonight on my $7 tier on Patreon! Link in my bio! . 😻… https://t.co/KEOUy2s0Ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rednekk_farmer Yea that too!!  How's the pretty daughter and the wifey thingy?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You too! And, your cards always seem to say the perfect thing (and make me cry!) I love you and I couldn’t imagine… https://t.co/GAe4WMFJ4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbharrison Yes you can! Don’t sell yourself short. You always bring the drama, the faces, the hands clasped. You got this 👍🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump The Constitution grants Congress exclusively the power to appropriate funds. This powe… https://t.co/xnQKrAGiRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FALLON1974 @awlasky @BeatFassbender I love Jimmy Fallon and can't wait to go to the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment we relinquish reproductive rights from the individual to the government, it’s only a matter of time befo… https://t.co/45cxyEmQWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @AdamSchiff @JussieSmollett That’s what happens when you think with your Dick at the “gay pride party “!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The Liar is on NATIONAL TV !! Trying to Convince US that Our President is a Crook n A Liar !! DON'T… https://t.co/Cl2uXLiPS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the cost of moving a manufactured home? https://t.co/yriIhuSSxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clerk_GC oh so now you remember what you said to the AG when you just finished saying you can’t recall the specifi… https://t.co/xfOUBQENal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are these ppl advertising their sexual preferences.. I COULD CARE LESS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[nation rejects his "model of governance."  Maduro revealed to the AP that his government has had secret meetings wi… https://t.co/7f5FOJ2gdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShirleenAllicot @heatherorourke7 @AmyFreeze7 @KenRosatoABC7 Good Morning Happy Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA And we all know that Mueller has it all....I believe Cohen 200%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, very interesting read. I thought we had more transparency and fairness on the Senate side with Burr. I guess n… https://t.co/4kKqWUUtW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rare cameo.   #lenahorne #lennie #lena #babygirl #cat #cats #catsofinstagram #rescue #tortoiseshellcat #misspriss… https://t.co/bsGdMUW6rb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan and Meadows were awesome and I was pleasantly surprised by Cummings closing remarks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue Box Cafe at Tiffany’s!! They gave me dessert on the house for my birthday!! A candle and everything!! So much… https://t.co/N7AQOm2HL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is #Friendship day in world.  - - #fun #vegas #california #dubai #love : #c4c #love #mixedgirl #morrocan… https://t.co/2UIlnTdBwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Barry have you read the Constitution or Bill of Rights? Check it out you will def… https://t.co/786MsqIHLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hang with some niggas who be killing , i just gotta give em a reason 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new girl literally switched her entire schedule around with the assumption I would switch two of shifts with he… https://t.co/zpAhkJ6qId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a text from my Nanna saying “call my phone I can’t find it” from her laptop, I call and she answers and says “i… https://t.co/7Wr8GJErY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmeraldEclipses @BravoTV I was really just poking fun at LuAnn who was so disrespectful to Carole two seasons ago… https://t.co/a3JftoT8Vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[why pay to go to a theme park &amp; not ride every ride to get your moneys worth????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family matters @movementmtg  Gear for all!   Hiring across Dallas / Fort Worth. @ Movement Mortgage Dallas https://t.co/6c6UiF36MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallardo2_pat @TaxReformExpert @Camsr2000 Right on,Pat!Reasons for trying to depopulate our planet is unimaginable… https://t.co/P2z3CwVVna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldManCraig @SXSWEDU @techsavvygirl Yes! Please! Help! (and thank you, John!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @SenThomTillis @lisamurkowski @SenatorCollins Backstabbing at its finest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you thought you couldn’t love @NKOTB more than you already do.. they drop  #BoysInTheBand. 😂  Greatest mu… https://t.co/8rzZNFXLFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tahnifishhh @KristinLea89 @Thornasty Ohh that would be hella fun. One dayyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 I Heard It Through The Grapevine (Part 1) (Single Version) by Roger on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/L63e2M0zcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not like these companies have labor issues and adverse effects on local public transit. Oh wait. Both of those are true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... I guess I don’t have to drop-out if I just fail everything 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit, I would die if I got to see my inspiration and the woman who makes me wanna fight anyone who crosses my… https://t.co/M4pJnisBX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze Reality is fluid for this one.  Jussie, not enough attention - send letter threatening myself,  unsatisfa… https://t.co/dSaKsGU1fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbball_wv @brooke__perryy  you are having one heck of an amazing Senior Year!! Congratulations Brooke!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBardugo doesn’t get enough love y’all and nEITHER DOES NIKOLAI LANTSOV #KingOfScars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so entertained tonight!  I ooooohed😯 and ahhhhed😍 and had major perma-grin😁 goin’ on! I am so proud of all ou… https://t.co/c92LureJrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garywhitta My kid is too! (I have no children but will 100% pretend I do so I can play this. The same way I preten… https://t.co/yZcynUtjZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derrickfromtx1 @yesmam47 @biggnm73 @CNN Ask swedish scientist Nils Ekholm. He coined the term *greenhouse effect*… https://t.co/SfL9W4KUNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know.. #tuesdaytravels 😄  • • • #birthday #adventures #travel #happy #fun #smile #wanderlust #life… https://t.co/qpneRbrwtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY! #DefiningAudacity show with Drew Myers at @NewGranburyLive 2-4 pm! Come on out! #Granbury… https://t.co/UzF7tBq1w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurie_olive @SashawnJohnson @LuhrmanMr @Mrs_Haldenwang @MalloryDiehl @elizondoreading @nisdelemelar Love the big circles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plan to grind out a pretty long night stream tomorrow, stay tuned  Bless 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning more about #3Dprinting   From @CrealiveD at @UOIT @durhamcollege  . #Oshawa #DurhamRegion #STEM @MaRSDD https://t.co/hywUINE2iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can get a much better hurricane in Nola. Pat O’s is for finessing tourists]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone stop me from giving into Saturday of crssd. I have FOMO on Channel Tres and Mason Maynard’s sets omg 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#POTUS is giving such a great speech at #CPAC2019  "We will never be a socialist country" https://t.co/BAvXh5chzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could snap chat me once and be one my top friends list if that tells you anything about my social life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajibzade بد از ورشو خیلی کم اوردین که دارین عکس های ساشا را تو تویتر می گذاری. معلومه شعور سیاسی نداری . کلاس تو و… https://t.co/ppH8ujHpON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiddeternity @glass_poetry @Blklyfmattering @samforbreakfast @chenchenwrites @cassandraintroy @BaileyC213 So excit… https://t.co/PpOoVMAk3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlaireKateLyn Dude I literally showed someone this saying that exact same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can’t let this happen guys.  90’s kids have the opportunity to live in 3 different centuries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or just emotionally, mentally, and fiscally conscious of what having a child entails at a young age....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jecoggins There is more Gold In Babylon My Friends Abundance for all! Go forth practice "Truth" and You Shall Find. https://t.co/myac8Cif4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we making an impact on #PainManagement in relationship to the #biopsychosocialModel and care? It’s too dictated… https://t.co/Bj7aTIRgQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Best Song From Every Fleetwood Mac Album https://t.co/GvmPq5cg7Y @UltClassicRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jerri_Gill @brennan_elliott @IamLaceyChabert @BonSomerville @maggielawson @danicamckellar @BrookeShields Thank you… https://t.co/Hj6yjJqku4]]></document><document><![CDATA[too funny #funniness #chuckle #smile #ludicrous https://t.co/jmdKTismkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which one of these pictures is worse??? !!! POLL BELOW !!! https://t.co/BGl5r4AGwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiepence I agree with you - cherry pie is gross (and all other pie too)]]></document><document><![CDATA[i look forward to the day i’m not afraid to post why #IAmNotOk, but i’m afraid the people i’m most scared of will find them.]]></document></documents></author>