<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Brutalemabella I think once you accept that statistics aren't the same as facts, you start to become skeptical of… https://t.co/oBDfLg7dnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green Book is another film that will be examined in the future as an example of Oscar getting it wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS https://t.co/0x0BaQibxU Malania idk what can be done these muslims@need to out of our congress and any high… https://t.co/eQtSoftmE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gettinviggy No disrespect to the logo, but you could always go with this. Everyone loves the Wu! https://t.co/JxljsryBj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelshermer on Why is there Something Rather than Nothing? Interesting insistence on an infinite regress of a N… https://t.co/biAwfb5VFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigletish ??? I don’t think you are a deviant at all.  If I did, I wouldn’t try to poke fun at it at all.  And I w… https://t.co/Iie8CONF5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@middleageriot @buffaloon As Larry The Cable Guy Might Say: “Now, That Thar, That’s Funny!” 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂… https://t.co/ARneosLMe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[That house is completely disgusting! #LivePd #LivePDNation #LivePdMass #LivePDWatchParty #ShepHappens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoingRight1 @OMARRSHABAZZ @OHIW14 @Aug1405 @kvmidd85 @mymynags @John_R_Berna @RevKeithBritt @kingconvictions… https://t.co/Qo7CWJM5jC]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMAGI-[NATION]: “an artist is supposed to  expand your Imagi-[NATION] like a breath of fresh air,not suffocate it”… https://t.co/3MNH7FYpIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deyshaaaa_ Ahh ok. That also depends too. 2 train should be like 40 from certain parts to Barclays. A all the express joints.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning 🌅 Have a great day 🙏🏼 @ Hudson, Massachusetts https://t.co/6nVkMfgN7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Flatter Flatter Flatter Flatter Flatter Flatter Flatter 2x DH IPA by @SingleCutBeer at @podguy — https://t.co/eg47gO6PGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaceyBirch Is this a U of F quiz or a real nature question?  Given the size in this case the Gator!  If baby gator… https://t.co/v1Me8aWqQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BarbaraBB_ @BiaRosenburg @JordanFariaLima @Andre_L_K Cursei economia na PUC-Rio, até o último período de surf sho… https://t.co/ZBSHfaHKof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyruleHavenHero I believe I wrote one like that. I’ll need to check at work to be sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bipolar Me is available on Payhip at https://t.co/GUs2It62S5 for $2.00 less in paperback at $13.00 and $1.00 less a… https://t.co/d8QQZ25rkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least someone got dolled up for me tonight #sanfrancisco #cityhall #valentine @ City Hall https://t.co/RysNOTjljz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having the tough conversation on what it will take to take our children and our community back!! Leading from the b… https://t.co/A1w7p3jiv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg Is it weird for me to say I loved how you handled this? I look up to that ability to confront this… https://t.co/biaY1fITbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgonzalezIII Honestly, anyone signing Kimbrel on a short deal if he's willing to take one is a good idea right now… https://t.co/lO3ttwzDad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red The ocean is blue #Megalodon is extinct. https://t.co/1z4AQQGoc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Obama border chief says @POTUS is right on @foxandfriends, just now. There is an emergency on the border. Wh… https://t.co/BdhzQKFwK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meami_Ami I WILL NOT REST UNTIL YOU REACT TO "Hell or High Water" BY CITY MORGUE (aka @zillakami and sosmula, aka 69's dad)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matador ambientándole la salida del closet a Petro?? Y la cantidad de admiradores en serio creen q los drag queens… https://t.co/wdjDZPz0b5]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the bus. Next stop #Oxnard see you soon #805. @ Bakersfield, California https://t.co/dxEEmCFqpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calltostand @Megan4MAGA @JussieSmollett  That’s what little boy’s get when the lie! https://t.co/htYdQDbWzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BealeStMusicFes since we all know Bloc Boy probably won’t be out of jail can we get @KeyGLOCK instead?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new story: Sakio Bika vs Lionel Thompson in the works for 3/24 #boxing #boxeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wurlybird27 @MsJayLee22 @15and9smom @JorieJukebox @VacationTaking @beckresc @indomituslifts @LuAnn_1970… https://t.co/7mMQAu6JOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkNel1026 @ben_fritz_ @the_meat_lady @corbittwall Makes a difference who’s money you’re spending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goliveros Jajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[River to reach 13 feet above flood stage Sunday https://t.co/lXfZojUKZP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marygayscanlon  You’re my contemporary.U learned about Holocaust.I am firmly, unequivocally telling U what’s happe… https://t.co/MLCgKG7r8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to Mark Farina Live at GLA Party June 11 2016 by GLA Recordings #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/LcDr7hwreY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStuedler This terrorist isn't an anomaly. We're just lucky enough that he's been exposed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minimus Ambus comic cover commission. He is enjoying his tea ;) #transformers #mtmte #lostlight #IDW #copicmarkers https://t.co/Kf0xfpKjFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[....... green....fucking.....book..... instead of Roma??? 🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaywardWinifred @RashidaTlaib @MaxineWaters You bitches can pay for it with your full pay checks and every Congres… https://t.co/rWBuD0mLcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Gazette Parade #Disneyland 1985 “Salute to the American Hero” https://t.co/2sThWVffY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jreineron7 Hi Jeremy..4.5" North Weymouth! Next! Ugh! Ready for Spring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @WWERoadDogg I just want to say that I have really enjoyed Becky’s story this year and Kofi’s story from Tuesda… https://t.co/IMinPaF4ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RenovaciónPRI es escuchar y sumar todas las voces. https://t.co/IZoelkHJcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rginvalpo @AloftHotels @Home2Suites @HamptonByHilton Left Hilton years ago.  #bedbugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can promise one thing. Idc how close you are to me, you fuck me over when I’ve never done you wrong, it’s gonna be your ass 🤷🏻‍♂️🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! 👍👏🎉 I lose all bodily functions if I run a sub 6 min mile. Just FYI...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjamindcrosby On personal examples much can be said: I think it follows the same rule for writing, if you talk a… https://t.co/0erHMBTsrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CStamper_ The party of tolerance what a joke it’s more like the party of hypocrites]]></document><document><![CDATA[breakfast at the office,  and now for dessert!  @Tasara22 @cgrenier609 @Dimetropteryx https://t.co/ubgMDo6jJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caminando por el #muro de la frontera #mexico #usa en #mexicali #bajaCalifornia nada ni nadie nos detendrá #actor… https://t.co/fAmDNYplTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been to one of these in a while! So hype! LET’S GO AMERKS! @AmerksHockey !!!!!!! https://t.co/WJNL9kwult]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fortunefunny @traviswall @Allisonholker @JessieJ Yass! You got the moves gurl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CutlerRidgeLAZ “You people” there you go again. Just can’t help yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joemcelderry91 Joe...  As I've already said, I'd love to hear your little something!  ...  RobtheElder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally! @AndrewYangVFA is on JRE!!! Been waiting for this since I heard him on @SamHarrisOrg @wakingup podcast https://t.co/e1go89Iu7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tulips getting a little 🌞. #dallasorganic. #dallasgardens  #garden @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/Jn4ZqU0KAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulafaris May he rest eternally, and may God comfort all those grieving his passing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stafturd @AndreMartel Hawaiians got cousins on cousins. I got cousins that ain’t even my blood cousins. And got he… https://t.co/3yX7xaMttS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrputinwork100 @sigui23 @kellinkelz Ur a bum. Worst player we got. 1-6 in tourneys. Biggest bum I kno]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things Teachers Say vs. Things Teachers Think | More LOLs &amp; Funny Stuff for Moms |... #humor #tee-hee #smirk… https://t.co/Ba5nG1lQpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme x Clark's for sell https://t.co/jeYhQ8XTjx https://t.co/SdogoFf3Fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played @Emarosa, @peachpitmusic, and @SummerSaltATX so far today. Good vibes only]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel I’m guessing most of these people didn’t come to Ottawa from the oil fields, so did they hire local… https://t.co/QlO0HtogBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @MeghanMcCain That is such a dumb comment.  They have enjoyed not socialism but dictatorships by narc… https://t.co/u21aSrgb5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and grind,  Happy Sunday errbody! @ Gene Green Beltway 8 Park https://t.co/afKC7JUO4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gerrymandering conversation quieted down after 2018 because Democrats won the House but there’s a scenario wher… https://t.co/tsyn0HCMec]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've spent the last two years of the Trump administration looking at everyone in the United States and asking mysel… https://t.co/azQla6uyN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at an adorable picture of my daughter: are you fucking kidding me with this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having life(spiritually) in this cruel world is something most don't have..I found it in recovery. I live for this… https://t.co/KFFrrzm1iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos, vamos América que esta noche tenemos que ganar Águilas a ganar! Pónganle huevos vamos con todo a chingar a… https://t.co/keRJhyb02c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días! amanecí por indagar un poco sobre los fenómenos que hoy se proclaman defensores del pueblo dominicano.… https://t.co/4BhqJQ0Gas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey coming out looking like Sonya blade is pretty awesome! #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUNDAY LOCATION CHANGE:   Friday: Vs Big Bend 6pm at Everett Memorial Stadium  Saturday: Vs. Big Bend 6pm at Everet… https://t.co/wkCMwwW78R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Ever  hear this comment?  I sure as heck have. Stay in your place. Republicans stay in power with that comment.  .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big win yesterday for the Tigers but this time of the year the next game is the biggest. Massive game against Templ… https://t.co/7SydG6Wtxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sboyd7 @turtlegloves If you’re nice, I’ll let you visit them. Hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the TP in a persons restroom tells you more about their financial well-being than the car in their garage… https://t.co/Tc8O8MKJTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had Canadiens +165 and Flyers +125 - so on bad, then good side of two EPIC melts! Still hockey is wonderful...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barnes_Law @KurtSchlichter I think Massivmmm  I think Massie is the kind of guy who really thinks you go to jail f… https://t.co/8ZntnsJETW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don’t even understand what it is. God forbid we get anything that allows you to tweet like a t… https://t.co/ViSChwUoru]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t just get my respect because we share the same blood unless your name is mom or grandma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiamRiecks16 Best of luck to you @LiamRiecks16 a true 3 sport athlete!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have taken Marine Corp recruits to Parris Island for basic..and..have taken groups on tours of Parris Island. Wha… https://t.co/ddnB1hAtaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's get 1 thing straight. Lil homie should of bounced.   Buttttttt....  Don't ever speak on behalf of the black c… https://t.co/wRL9U3PYya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THNMattLarkin Good enough, I enjoy THN and the writers there as a whole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MichaelHornsby, the almost 30 year old Riverside resident wearing a backpack and pretending to be a student while a… https://t.co/29R8yVcr6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAPTAIN MARVEL STRONGEST AVENGER CAPTAIN MARVEL STRONGEST AVENGER CAPTAIN MARVEL STRONGEST AVENGER CAPTAIN MARVEL S… https://t.co/moxSqJrziF]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mzYaRaNZgd  "There are different modes of transportation and what’s going to be important is the conne… https://t.co/bJJ8U66odS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world of macrophotography is weird. Didn’t think I’d see a metal waterfall🤨  #upclose #macrophotography… https://t.co/dq6tEHLXuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the University of Charlotte really made a deal with Joe Harris of “you can practice here but we get the trophy”… https://t.co/aFV2QmeUVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadMilan @Jennifer_Jayde @mitchellvii @SpeakerPelosi According to the Refugee Convention, those people are not cr… https://t.co/a9wpruPDJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throw in the towel NOW or white bag Doo Rag Just as long as it's WHITE RIGHT And don't try and change this into som… https://t.co/P27gTtoUBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt42301767 @UIPD @Champaign_Room This photo was taken by me, an MTD passenger standing near the front of the veh… https://t.co/xGZfrJDONt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My review of PSYCHO SHARK https://t.co/KQQWhoAmGr @RonGizmo @Talk2Cleo @sccart1 @palkodesigns @EmilieFlory @NylaVox… https://t.co/8LdVnZNE2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[This can be you:  JUST SOLD! We can help make that happen. Contact us at 201.450.0015.  Whether you are in NJ, have… https://t.co/nJnoKk6r6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Futademaru @itanimeirl If you somehow manage to catch up to it, select latest episodes will be available at a time… https://t.co/o8uwxaz5ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't go one day without thinking about you Lisa I want you in my life more than anything.. I honestly love you L… https://t.co/esE0bB33K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[UHV @UHVBaseball opens Red River Athletic Conference @RRACsports play with win over Wiley College https://t.co/GuBnBsKSl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson  a pervert child molester . Anyone who doesn’t believe this is a Total idiot . Those kids parents s… https://t.co/Jpd5zWRdwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_medinapaula @Chencho822 @LaGuerradelBSN @VaquerosBayamon Jaja! Es que es la cancha mas cerca me queda.  Tengo bajos de cancha...]]></document></documents></author>