<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I can't remember the Lions EVER getting this many important players that fill huge needs in the same day. Yes maybe… https://t.co/GPXNTFxB99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canotechris @BillyHallowell It must feel nice to be superior to so many other ppl. But, just for arguments sake, y… https://t.co/KhKTMgobhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @TresaBridges @SSG_Davis_Ret @Birdseye1 @CarolGarofolo @intelligent50 @Whichsideareuon @Muttonchap… https://t.co/aqCXWGG0nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wofford is headed back to the Big Dance for the for the first time since 2015 and for the fifth time in program his… https://t.co/9D8a8N8AJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @lenovo bought my daughter an #ideapad for Christmas and it has a defective mother board.  Not even two months… https://t.co/RrzvveLrKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you say a command and Alexa flashes red instead of blue 😳 always makes me freeze for a second]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met @emonggtv he’s just as nice as he is on stream. Thanks for the picture!! https://t.co/8fnnsIVBYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK Chuckle chuckle laugh my ass off fall off my chair spit out my coffee 😀😀😀😀😀😀😀😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VIUniversity @DocSaucier @NanaimoBulletin Congratulations Deb @DocSaucier .Great news all round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterericthor The most hysterical thing is that ALL the fears held by residents and assemblies on those islands ha… https://t.co/YvDMcNBVzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew21910826 @OOIDA @northjersey @Lewie_Pugh @5 As I point out they contradict themselves so bad it's Silly yet… https://t.co/ircDFiaOmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting, and I thought as individuals we had the largest carbon footprint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksbull @ArthurSchwartz @TheFive Jesus, you're a real person. I thought people like you only existed as points of r… https://t.co/wHpErrcY4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stand with @stephanielily . Our people (&amp; me included) are being poisoned by big industry. #swdetroit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Sunday @Hilltop_UMC we remind ourselves Jesus is Risen and today is a day of divine creation.   Today the big… https://t.co/H0veRCwvfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEMEHOLAT_TWEET If u say so, what happens when u see them dudes in public when u with her , https://t.co/fwl1IAU65P]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #snow is expected to begin after midnight Tuesday night impact most of Wednesday. #forecast models disagree on… https://t.co/EVL2boGzt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliePMcduff @ssophcia @MsMollyRachael That’s what I thought at first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They told me I couldn’t be a rapper... but fortunately, we don’t give a fuck what “they” have to say. “They” will a… https://t.co/1jGVSSrLoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This real Unc. And the worst part be when they try to overcompensate and then look silly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanShipnuck @MattGinellaGC Is Mr. Trump on the left or right in this photo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man that Roscoe Dash 2.0 mixtape was his best work before he disappeared]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle You said #Smollett gets paid $125,000 per year. WRONG! As the graphic that was displayed on the scre… https://t.co/r4X1LCl5If]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RandomThought I just told @CoriNicolee that my account is now an #Olicity fan account going forward. #Arrow https://t.co/GLZXEwRYok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clivewonderdog @blackfridayjake @DanaPerino @GrandCanyonNPS What a great spot! I don’t know it. Nicely done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpheliaPG @theappeal @BarbaraLNewsome "someplace less racist....where that is, idk" -- just look at any country we… https://t.co/WaH8RUvRr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[charlenekaye @KnitFactoryBK 2/11/19 Can't wait for this bad ass musician to put out her next album!! #kaye… https://t.co/Qtxd0TB5im]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flacco71 @ABC About what I would expect from someone like you.  Thanks for not disappointing me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore, there is now no condemnation for those who are in Christ Jesus, because through Christ Jesus the law of… https://t.co/jptzSizz9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murdo_mcghie @BTC_Experts @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump https://t.co/ST0LaOE9uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off and heading to the house, gotta load tonight and head back up! (@ Continental Mills in Kent, WA) https://t.co/lijeJj47V4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole65149076 @RealSaavedra @TomFitton She’s just drunk that’s all!! https://t.co/zmLxNuWIo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home sweet home! @ Washington Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/qHbZvFpZiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[El favor de Dios en tu vida te hará lograr más con menos talento. Su bendición traerá conexiones divinas: personas… https://t.co/VlDVURJ2wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many good memories at this place, hard to believe it's all just a memory now.  For 6 years it wasn't just a job.  M… https://t.co/Nvpk2mWIpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's now meowing, extremely upset. Like, you did this to yourself, dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @PortezLortez Ignore the haters. You’re beautiful and don’t look like a rat. Losers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Megan Kelly can address this topic on her show on Mond- oh, right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Face-to-face with a Skeksis! @ the Jim Henson exhibit #skeksis #darkcrystal #jimhenson #astoria #queens #nyc @ Muse… https://t.co/ULp8xZwIiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMatthewsfarms @travisfaske Uno road hwy 37 off of 18 has been closed longer than that. Gotta take the long way to… https://t.co/9LSCtT7rX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poll worker at PS 249 in Ditmas Park estimated 16 people have voted so far today. “Going to be one of those,” she s… https://t.co/USuRJEUmCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw @realDonaldTrump No one paid any attention what so ever to what Obama was saying in 07 when he said… https://t.co/AFuJVnmZLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new #minidj setup! Cute! Great portability and sounds great! All it needs is #fxbuttons #djlife #djteacher… https://t.co/epA11lt4T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe I placed 2nd out of 55 in my first poker tournament yesterday. #TableMountainCasino https://t.co/JBi9egsJD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything feels weird off acid😂😂😂😂 I feel like I cannot stop smiling bruh wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean The “FEAR” @JaniceDean is FAR FAR FAR more worse than THE ACTUAL REALITY- you gonna be just fine weather girl - 👌🇺🇸👌🇺🇸👌🇺🇸👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll give credit where credit is due, if Avenatti got his hands on actual evidence of R. Kelly abusing a kid and ha… https://t.co/tC0nJzheq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerryNBCBoston @GerryCallahan @NBC10Boston This will somehow be linked to Cheating and this is why the Pats won the Super Bowl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting her cleaded up #kryptonite #fladbedlife #diesellife #dsv #truckinglifestyle #goprohero5 #gopro #maxxmount… https://t.co/n0SDsC1w4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@victorconestilo But I got you mailob!! Tu si sabes! Pick your chorus!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curious to what constitutes "pushing liberal agendas" in podunk little White County,  Illinois. https://t.co/XHLdM8gvHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Papapishu i feel dumb for not assuming tom savini was in this thing I must watch asap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poglankford Its in no way “bad”. The players agreed to that in a labor agreement. When you sign an agreement, its… https://t.co/ymlKE0h9uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Got a Job at Chuck E. Cheese and They Recycle Their Pizza! (WITH PROOF) https://t.co/SLAO1FvoFL via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FemmeEnFeu @QueenBbecT The *idea* of sucking your own dick is not the same as being able to suck your own dick, so no...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MStrooo6 @BlueJays @HDMHApparel Marcus..I am one of Gibbys radio pals..sorry guys are making an issue over this...… https://t.co/NYhuFLOYZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“RECEIVE WITHOUT TAKING.” — #FromLiesToRiches #comingsoon #peteroestévez  #peterestevez1 #peteroestevez #author… https://t.co/7q3cmcHYhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I see a trump I'm reminded that some village is missing its idiots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveyBoy97 @Crigmaster @crzyprettychick @wrestlecon @GLAMOURSHOWSTAR @skyroomnyc @Phoenixnjpw @BrittniSacco… https://t.co/ZI6GGMB2LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewCobb8 I don’t even think he should be first pick in my opinion, but that’s what I think will happen lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/gzX112kyNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like buying an apple and peanut butter dipper from wawa and having the perfect amount of peanut butter for the last piece of apple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agoddamnedangel “Life is what you do while you’re waiting to die/ Life is how the time goes by,”]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys so ready to exorcise milk drinkers but what about the people who like cherry flavored anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beloved business in #Berlin closes after 140 years @FOX61News  https://t.co/qEVn3uu79h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bear literally jumped on Kristy's back as she was filling up the cats' food bowls!! 🤣 @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/vz3OcpYGjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gobank Hi I want to know how long my money from refund taxes is available to my account after they sent]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rockclimber# 3rdborn#babygirl# @ Jacksonville Beach, Florida https://t.co/75AduZFMcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never underestimate what couple of small dogs can do to a police dog, when it enters their doman. Just bit the fuk… https://t.co/9WuVwXhrIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMH360 @WatchMixer Partners get more viewership, they have incentives in place to become partner for this basis. I… https://t.co/Tx5OSFHKw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was wanting more Bourbon character.  Good but I have tasted better in this style. - Drinking a Barrel Aged Old Mad… https://t.co/F7E7z0h8xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PaleoFest @cullen_thomas @SUEtheTrex: New silhouette is a little more... robust/chonky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s time for @carlivatiron to bring back these characters back on Days. Theresa,Tate,Sami,Belle, Shawn,Chl… https://t.co/f16xuEu4EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denise_actress @JackPosobiec Yeah the hustory of white Christian conservative men is awful. I how they rise up one… https://t.co/GGKFkWJKsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GEBUSCA @CaraveoBertha Ya será un tema personal y moral, pero porque tendría que ser delito?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patottas Mi estimado Rafa, ya deberías estar curtido, jaja Y el te lo dije... bueno, que tengas un excelente jueve… https://t.co/BYICizWv9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[After game 1 it’s so hard for me to say “oh if KT just fixes this they’ll win” I didn’t hate the draft by KT. I don… https://t.co/Y6QUKELgll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycondocon This sort of thing only works where all the parties are rational actors and the landlord is not as overtly sleazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Dangerous territory you will NEVER Understand. Just Shut up and Deal with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well she’s officially dying; figures it would happen now. When it rains it pours I suppose. #WeekFromHell #FML… https://t.co/4GWe5HxDK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get @maddow to give us a recap of all the Game of Thrones sub-plots too?  She is doing a great job recapping… https://t.co/X832VWg5RK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estuary check in @ Smithsonian Environmental Research Center https://t.co/0wFuTnXKHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Northwest (@NWBearcatMBB) defeats Western 70-68. The Griffons did their best to pull off a miracle, but they… https://t.co/LYpZTQLsKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was the 1st guy that ever recorded me at a 5sec hangtime! He also served as my Freshmen basketball coach! Guy is… https://t.co/OgjFsjeo9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asalsman The showings in Dolby at @AMCTheatres #AssemblyRow this week are quite tempting...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightinFourteen @JoyceWhiteVance I wouldn't object to seeing him leave the WH this way, soon. . . https://t.co/YLUW5YXLT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The commandments, “You shall not commit adultery,” “You shall not murder,” “You shall not steal,” “You shall not co… https://t.co/Faa0H7SYVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ScottWeinerMD for well-deserved feature in Harvard Magazine https://t.co/IpItI6zO2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[로마서 8:5-8   Korean      5 육신을 따라 사는 사람은 육신의 일을 생각하지만 성령님을 따라 사는 사람은 성령님의 일을 생각합니다.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffalo_Phill @ShootwAuthority @BrandNewTweetr Incorrect. Loud mouthed out of touch with the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think it’s too much (fan service) to ask for the “Snake? Snaaaaaaaaaaake?!” line in the #MetalGearMovie? 🤷🏽‍♂️🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night at practice I had the pleasure to meet and introduce Bilqis Abdul-Qaadir to our U16 boys TEAM.  Bilqis n… https://t.co/KPrDdk8C5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleighbroucher Trust Haleigh we saw it for 3 mouths in the mirrors lol it was so funny at times others nit so much https://t.co/fWUkV2llhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellas son las porristasfiregirls, presentes en el primer juego de fundidoreslfa   #Fundidores #Monterrey #LFA… https://t.co/VCQ3rEBJ6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NannyCampOf6 are you proud of me I'm a police officer no matter what my limitations are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely proud of my brothas and I... huge win tonight but our run aint over yet 😈🤧❄️CIF Quarterfinals here we come #fightinglancers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Unger, D-Berkeley, is asking for the evening to review the amendment and discuss with constituents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A MAN SHOULD ADD VALUE TO YOUR LIFE, NOT BE THE THE VALUE OF YOUR LIFE!!! I WANNA BUILD WITH SOMEONE NOT BUILD SOME… https://t.co/09oSCN60KH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath I've been reading "Becoming" very slowly because it's physically painful to read her brilliant prose,… https://t.co/nlHo90KC4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ West Highlands, Naperville https://t.co/hbChgDQm9C]]></document></documents></author>