<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders holds campaign rally in Brooklyn  https://t.co/ctQoPofvMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[News flash: other fan bases are just as wild, we’re just out with the shits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTimHorton @CoachDerekMason @VandyFootball @AuburnFootball Congrats!🎉🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kitty Hawk Counselors registering students for high school. https://t.co/qemOI7Ae58]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Seasons Tx Center Chris Lopez - "If you have a heart condition, you take medication. If you have diabetes, you… https://t.co/4IddDcCMLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk What a whack job she is! All she does is spew venom and hate daily! @JesseBWatters https://t.co/4TeYDm7kue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMdeucey Aww good! Glad your day started with a bright Good Morning!🌞🌝☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews People don’t hear the siren now can you imagine if they make it less noisy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before and after ❤️❤️❤️❤️😍😍😍😍 @ Menifee, California https://t.co/eMrmEjbynk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colleenemcneil So glad you enjoyed @PerezCissy presentation. She’s amazing and truly wants you to reach out if you… https://t.co/eXzVGpjNfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattoak @allonsyrachel @tombiro @itsdoctorem @mattpentz @vena_dot_com GO AWAY OAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely disgusting that the club members of airline programs board before the troops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hot bath I’m bout to take is about to be fye(in my @Conceited205 voice)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abowman_24 @liz_ashley13 @peanuttor That show SUCKED. Literally every show we had between San Antonio and Georgia… https://t.co/k8kbU5NDHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to be the strings on your guitar Touch me and play what you feel. 🥵  #Alcorn_RYS19 https://t.co/b7E2ifOaqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being happy with the one who brings out the best in me everyday 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember getting called a low life by most of my teachers and co-workers. If I'm so much of a low life. Then why… https://t.co/dmqo4CucQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonlamacraft "As for the OGM90 + study, despite the implementation of techniques called "omics", it was limited… https://t.co/K4I6gj044q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our roundtable has begun, #BrockU Karen Fricker is beginning with the myth that surrounds King Ubu #UbuRoundtable]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go get a snack but I don't wanna wake up the puppy sleeping in my bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[on this day in history, my amazing godmother and i were appointed to the US Supreme Court in an unprecedented move.… https://t.co/bkUeCPrBxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d be dressing like a secretary and shooting corporate events, but here I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this model at Heritage at Vizcaya. Dazzling! What makes this place different? Gorgeous homes for the over… https://t.co/Es8oZJ1uQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the last day of our Sample Sale! We are open until 2pm and have even deeper markdowns today -- come and ge… https://t.co/4kgptTuPFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpearson @4AnimalLife @Fahrenthold @PressHerald @realDonaldTrump @fordnation Excellent point!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LasHerederas  La historia de una pareja que, al verse obligada a desprenderse de sus objetos materiales, alcanza l… https://t.co/XxchMRzQDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[New photog education blog up on my website as promised (link in bio)!  • Today I cover the importance of a welcome… https://t.co/z76d2COtZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A scoundrel from the future intent on making a name for himself in the past. @wizardworld #wizardworldcleveland @ H… https://t.co/Of2GoYB3nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU ARE WORTHY. YOU ARE CAPABLE  YOU ARE BEAUTIFUL. BOOK THE TICKET. WRITE THE BOOK. CREATE THE DREAM  CELEBRATE YO… https://t.co/qkrFB7gHXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[At intermission of @HPPlayNYC, @TaekiaB turned to me and said “we must protect Harry Potter” and I have never heard… https://t.co/3aRWfwh01e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Lovers, 10 words to chew on https://t.co/aIA38gmyX2 via @sunshinysa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaclynhill If that’s what happy looks like than I wanna look just like you girl🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was sent this today @ThoroldJRBhawks 2005 captain JJ Martin receiving the #suthy in #hawksgoals #hawkeytown https://t.co/BxHkYGuA2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be the first foreign lil bitch in Chicago for the k****z. I used the * so the pigs can't crack that one. Hint:… https://t.co/9tG4R4mO0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_K11 ... I still am doing this in work meetings 🤦🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/kF2Jo7IdvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddyBBCAN6 just wanted to say, thank you for your cast assessment with @RealityRecaps. It was a great two hour show! Love you both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/v6dbQBfreS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m obsessed with @lukecombs music!!! I would do anything to see him in concert!]]></document><document><![CDATA[flipping burgers will soon earn you more than caring for the sick and the elderly. soon, a manager at Mcdonald’s co… https://t.co/N45vuXLfAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Topsy_Tori @juliaioffe @IlhanMN Everyone has every reason to feel afraid of lsIam. They kiII non believers, jewish people dont. Sit down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onlyangelmylove @Harry_Styles #StillTheOne #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Hannan_Ismail @Irkalla_Caudron @TheLoveBel0w Someone keeps telling,dems, higher minimum wages, but why? If we ra… https://t.co/MDYt9TLd7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to our February Board of Directors meeting tonight for the @knoxvilletrack]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy. #teenheartthrob #dylanmckay #lukeperry 💔😩 https://t.co/YCOisimEX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karrin21262 @SatiristPod @jaketapper We have to fight for the right to play?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6abc 😡😡😡😡😡😡 there aren’t enough angry emojis in the world for this!!!  That’s horrible 😡😡😡😡😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership squad at #LIAC19. I may have FALLEN for them. (Peep the last pic) @ Texas State University - LBJ Student… https://t.co/ohi2DpnwLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimefountaine @barrelhouse This is great and reminds me that we should make a magazine together and I’m saying it… https://t.co/SlNQp2xLaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDealCorbeil If you think you have it bad....this puts it all in perspective]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexis_sedano Wait whaaaa? I drink water all the time and if it’s not ice cold I will not drink it!! 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMeadows We are watching me a. You don't even know what the heck you are doing. You're in your own little racis… https://t.co/NOuPfsiPts]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Heaven there is no beer That's why we drink it here And when we're gone from here All our friends will be drinki… https://t.co/FSfzxDLk0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially lost all my lashes ...  BRB a hoe needa splurge right quick !]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a troll; cause no one with a brain can watch FoxNews &amp; not know they spew trump’s lies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you guys see this? #GoGreen #RunGreensRun @miserablelib @jimmy_dore @RonPlacone @grahamelwood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pour être tout à fait exacte, cette phrase aurait dû s’arrêter à « sommet »]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was my first question to a former senior city staffer years ago before construction started. There are reports… https://t.co/rQX9h6IqAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImMatthew_Davis They’re having Hannah B as the next Bachelorette.. 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doritkemsley1 Oh my God...wasnt that the 2nd dog from Lisa's dog rescue?? You and your husband both knew the rules… https://t.co/UUpk14hFUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRASH standing up! Trash on the ground!Red shirts mocking a young man down!Civilization!Gone in a flash. All is fir… https://t.co/GfeP9pxYvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 This piece of garbage is the stupidest most vile disgusting President ever in the USA history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks mobile went down...was late for the @ATMSAStars book fair. Buuuuuuuut, then there was a fire drill. LOL https://t.co/yM0CIvpqHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i was little and we went out to eat, my parents always made me order on my own. imagine lil 2 year old pearl o… https://t.co/owQhUhge0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onos_147 @Tpindell So sure they are not teaching these solutions at my old  HS Located in the fashion District of… https://t.co/8jEZxUgyQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motivational quotes welcomed! @Rivs_Fans #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/KXbc3ykYeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVN_03 Sometimes it takes over 30 years to admit it happened. I never told anyone for 18 years.  There’s brainwash… https://t.co/8JZ65uWZzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You went willingly to the Mojo Freedom Dojo, @RantsOfIzzo. Worry when we ignore you. #WhatILearnedToday @realBradStaggs @RealRonPhillips]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bienvenido a #Miami! #vacation #SundayFunday ☀️🏝 https://t.co/3QffbTAhiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[HMW build a learning plan to integrate tolerance and literature? @Tolerance_org https://t.co/XJ77fc7W99]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact our agents show up to learn and grow makes me the happiest person ever! ♥️💃🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya'll ever used to get the #Sanrio grab bags when u were a kid hoping to get the cool surprise inside?  That's what… https://t.co/QBVfkfeeKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re live at Bon Secours Wellness Arena this morning with everything you need to know before you come out to cheer… https://t.co/y3gFnThRIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clancysjournal Wet wipes, portable charger(s), makeup wipes, hand warmers, ticket, snacks, money, change of clothe… https://t.co/CdmYq0SvCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh dear God. Canadian man, at town hall, says Prime Minister Trudeau was involved with Clinton Pizzagate child traf… https://t.co/pwnCv93qJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pros of being a girl: men want to do everything for you  Cons of being a girl: men want to do everything for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this published shoot with the beautiful motobeauty159 Magazine:  obscuraemagazine  Photography: nzieglerart  D… https://t.co/Gizn1LN4Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Hope you got some sleep last night and are feeling better today.  Your twitter gang is with you and… https://t.co/SQXBe7bwBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby fever is soo bad but I know that if I got pregnant right now I would die 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVanessaW @PascoSheriff It’s funny. I would never drink it. As a kid, I drank cola. As an adult tea. When I was st… https://t.co/FreZIkBFJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam’s first collegiate home run! #baseball #baseballmom #montevallobaseball #homerun #proudmom @ University of Mont… https://t.co/Q41TdDWzRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannykanell @CallawayGolf @TaylorMadeGolf @Titleist @MizunoGolfNA Rogue pros.  Callaway.  Game changer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mmklinger @ncaawbb @ncsa So proud as well!! Keep it up Sophia... you’ve worked so hard on the off season!!!🏀❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skeltonprincess How is having a gender reveal showing a dislike for trans people ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSmuttz Get me one if you can!! I’ll pick it up when I go to Orlando ! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carina &amp; DeLuca are arguing in Italian. Meredith walks up to them. #GreysAnatomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like there is absolutely no reason in the whole damn world to be smackin like that.   CLOSE YA DAMN MOUTH HONEY🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Bend mayor @PeteButtigieg , who is seeking the Democratic nomination for president, is up next on @Morning_Joe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's why it looks like she tried to wipe it off. She's conflicted &amp; know she looks like the hypocrite she is.… https://t.co/xVt35OCfxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out sick today.... but getting an email from the sub that the classes are awesome makes me smile.....Just like all… https://t.co/0CODK7KTVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antonydb @realDonaldTrump They admitted they gave it to him for a Speech. They should have asked for it back after the Arab Spring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SURRENDER OUT NOW ON ALL PLATFORMS 💓 https://t.co/fbSqvo9ve8  #Spotify #AppleMusic #Tidal #SoundCloud… https://t.co/HQt7xnwrOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and Ash were once apart of a rat group but the people on there are grown adults bullying us because we “don’t kn… https://t.co/ZKgHwMcbtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTH is #TheBatchelor trending? Y’all need to learn how to spell. 🙄🙄 #TheBachelor @BachelorABC #Bachelor… https://t.co/CBlXiBIqAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBROINTHEAM @oldmanebro @LAURASTYLEZ yeeeeaahh #LauraNeverLoses !!!! 🙆🏼‍♀️🙅🏼‍♀️💁🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️😆😆🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽🙌🏽 https://t.co/XG7iqfKewi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to get my friend to care about hockey for WEEKS and it hasn’t worked until tonight... when I showe… https://t.co/KxEUHIQgDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentAmeneyro I would love to do a Friday evening stream a couple times a month called Heidi’s Homebound Happy Hou… https://t.co/rfhCyiiANZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really hard wearing leggings when your dogs have light colored fur]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and your boo act like it’s your first time hanging out like fucking weirdos &gt;&gt;&gt;   “What’s your name ?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AricFOX5 Do you know if they are allowing chains on #Highway79 coming north into #julian  ?? #traffic #sandiego #sosandiego #highway78]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚧" UPDATE: Ocasio-Cortez responds to ‘wack’ Times Square billboard https://t.co/eoGZEXDSzC]]></document></documents></author>