<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of my neighbors in the hive FLEW to LA last night cause he didn’t feel like driving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dphs_ecantu  look where his heel is in relation to his hip and shoulder ... he stays behind the ball and controls… https://t.co/532JRCyz1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGGER PEOPLE . . . . .  #andyfrostart #contemporaryart #figurativeart #landscapeart #artcollectors #artgallery… https://t.co/WpW4cfdeWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[biggest pet peeve is probably people who unnecessarily wear their military uniform to the airport https://t.co/zq8bfg3ma6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ella_filipina @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Key words — “right mind”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember how he bitched about Dems going home over Christmas while the govt was shut down instead of staying in DC… https://t.co/m9htzySRJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Goodfriend Beer Garden and Burger House - @goodfriendbg in Dallas, TX https://t.co/gv96GhEoxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma miss it💗🤧 Thank you for all the great memories and people ive met along the way that have impacted me in a pos… https://t.co/PYevJNt8AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaders uplift their followers to become the best version of themselves. #PeopleSkillsChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARCHDrNguyen And yet tuition and endowments continues to rise. Where is the money going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to, but I’ve been cheering for @aafiron since the jump🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaBashCNN Lousy interview with Sen Brown. You asked him trick questions rather than ask questions which would in… https://t.co/VePllPCsar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamm Gala tonight still the prettiest of them all - thanks to alwaysflowersevents byconstellationpamm @cream_it an… https://t.co/f4BOnvwST9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarizardPlays @Chef_Lu_Bu Yeah, but it doesn’t look to me like these are viable replacements if you want to do HB… https://t.co/yGT14zLGT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the Wrestling Championships have concluded - watch and see how it began.  Thanks to Jeremy Lanthorn -https://t.co/ycxKcThNP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadmMonstrosity What do you mean I can’t return this video tape to Blockbusters?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump What a stupid thing to say, you disrespect him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolBa87190539 @UROCKlive1 @tonyschwartz @frankdugan The SOB is a f*cking worthless hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Tesla, the UMC you made in 2012 is apparently indestructible. Bravo LOL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it appears #HorizontalHarris is fine with legal prostitution😳 so people can smoke a joint and get laid all the… https://t.co/mr7HmTlQOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KleinschmidtJD How can the battered know what pitch the picture is throwing up? Follow up so that is how does a tr… https://t.co/UKMwHlnMhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night reinforced the fact that I am a perfect being https://t.co/XDeG4TVGlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moshekasher That's a ❤️ for vocabulary, immolate is simply not used enough in the current landscape. #influencerMoshe #foodstampjewsFTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breathes there an American with soul so dead they don't know the hypocrisy of everything Liberals said?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheoFleury14 No...respectfully, Theo...neither could the Conservatives.  That question seems a little troll-ish in… https://t.co/Q2uKyBNH3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I ain’t been the same since I loved that hoe, I ain’t been the same since I lost my bro.” So damn true. @LilSkies… https://t.co/EfPeYuKsQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SharCarter @FantaciiJaze @LangstonU @The1CoachSex @Coach_Griffin32 It was great meeting you too, hope to meet you again soon😁‼️🦁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenitezVEN @la_iguanatv Imagínate a Nicolás que no sabe de nada y habla mas que el carajo ... me imagino que las t… https://t.co/pthkEJRwLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @tammywalt61 @AOC The best example of fake it till you make it I have ever seen. Would love to hire her as a Sales Rep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoefelice @liamfunk_ @altheaedang @ashleywonng fun fact i stole that joke from someone else 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You won’t do that you LIAR, you love and crave TV ratings, no way you would pass up an op… https://t.co/zYuioloEez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdScottLondon Many thanks, Ed! He obviously had a secret announcement which he chose not to disclose...! 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm 122:6-7   Complete Jewish Bible    6 Pray for shalom in Yerushalayim; may those who love you prosper. 7 May s… https://t.co/fhAuNAjRCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra , Cortez is so stupid it’s even beyond belief. She will finish destroying the Democratic Party. The D… https://t.co/rew8p4EpAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany @mattgaetz How about your ORANGE CLOWN'S LYING https://t.co/Kyp3UmmsS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen @allahpundit Come on! We all need to spread it!we all Love! We will always have those who Hate! 😢😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Necrot was pretty sick too! @ The Showbox At the Market https://t.co/agXlTB135v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #VoteBlackPanther on @TyltEnt—’Black Panther’ Should win #Oscars Best Picture https://t.co/6jutGej1Qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOCIALIST AOC's ... Mom Flees to FLORIDA   TO ESCAPE N.Y. Taxes!  SOCIALIST 👹  BRAHAHAHA!!!  https://t.co/l4hfp0At5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill We need to find out who is supplying the opioids to the republicans in Washington!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pierre Poilievre: Trudeau either 'ignorant of the facts' or is 'lying' https://t.co/8tSKNcTBpN via @YouTube I say he is lying]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING INSTAFACEBOOGERS @ Farmington, New Mexico https://t.co/jw0OS7JbCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Compop7 @BartAllenImpuls I resent you all attacking women, lgbt, and people of color. I guess the world will never… https://t.co/Pn1ruPjDs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We cant retire the "disruptive" buzzword until everyone starts making better ads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saints Fans help us with Dawson Zebarth from Boise, ID a Happy Birthday today! Hope you have a great day Dawson!… https://t.co/AL8gmz1Uss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews @DavidMuir SO OVERPAID AND WE ALL PAY IN DIRECTLY  REAL BS NO ON IS WORTH THAT MUCH FOR SUCH A WORTHLESS GAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heisenberg08 @quickerthenfast @ChrisSteuber @Buster_ESPN https://t.co/mSVf30PlIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day!Heres an interesting painting of Cupid and Venus. Venus is lying on the ground and leaning on… https://t.co/ibulERqVZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Princess1Cassie @VirtuAss @amwalker38 @9Perverse9__ @saleputed @Natuky85 @TheHardDepot @pornmexmty… https://t.co/Yd9tg9mmRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Buffy’ Fans are Celebrating the Iconic Series on its 22nd Anniversary https://t.co/Sn3MH2ohbO via @ComicBook HAPPY… https://t.co/pNKbzFr4oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amgilstrap1964 @MotherJones Media trying to make Trump look bad?  No, he does a great job of that all by himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrensaFANB USTEDES NO SIRVEN PARA NADA!! ESPERO QUE LOS MATEN A TODOS EN LOS PRÓXIMOS DÍAS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft @AskLyft I had my insurance pay for a ride from the rental car to collision shop. Your driver I had was the a… https://t.co/wDTxZQNIxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michigan State had their 💩v. Illinois game and it looks like Michigan is now having that game v. Penn State.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉🏻 “Los Pequeños y Continuos Esfuerzos Realizados dan Resultados Sorprendentes “ 👈🏻 #CesarContigo 🥰😏😎 en Monterrey,… https://t.co/roVvZcyfKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok someone just told me I could have got off at Airport and taken Silver Line to South Station. Would have been slightly better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @USMC USMC...follow orders... A lot of this shit is cases of remourse for going over personal lines soldi… https://t.co/78DQUDajdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCK, just those few notes music notes on that ff9 trailer caused me to tear up as it unlocked like 10 teenaged memories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apóstol Y Padre De Multitudes, HOY QUIERO FELICITARLE EN ESTE DÍA MUY ESPECIAL.....!! Agradezco al Eterno al haberm… https://t.co/EriAdnaM8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a socialist hears about someone giving out free stuff. Lol https://t.co/UbI9vIxrjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawkpapersizors $59 for a half hour inside the parlour and $79 for an hour. Probably the best money he’s ever spent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiDolphins If you can be better than Randy Mcmichael.  It's a great start.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was pretty special to race a Mustang at Daytona sporting this iconic livery. #Roush #RoushMustang #IMSA https://t.co/9kicF1EoM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday! #Beckett #WickerPark @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/NKKxudMnhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the 5 most impactful jobs in #AI, @KPMG research https://t.co/cd6nZ8XcOS https://t.co/D5smfKg05i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tschwing32 Very true. The scary part about Shenandoah is 4 of their 5 double digit scorers are non-seniors. 3/5 ar… https://t.co/aYxgZjbbTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TobyB42996236 @RhondaTheCat I danced and bounce and even threw my hands in the air, when asked. 🤣 I actually really had fun. Holy haze....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @JohnMusz and Sarah Baehr for their work supporting #YANY youth arts programs. Great event and great ca… https://t.co/9aGAWkdWB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have black hair... tell my why I’m getting blonde streaks in my hair. What does this mean?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son keep whinnig about bacon fries I told him chill one day you will be modeling for them get all the fries 🙌🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with @jbfworldwide last weekend in Paterson, NJ 🎥❤️ Blessed to be part of an amazing team that fights to ch… https://t.co/qq76ry7VKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timburchett where does money seized at the border currently go? https://t.co/9H9h8I7PFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally misread this and thought is said “This is REALLY fuckin me with men.. 💀”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews " All Flesh Can Be saved...Its The worst of us That are In Trouble ".....*************** " Don't Hurt Real… https://t.co/qAWmUppM1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamieted23 @LaurenScala4NY @gatonyc1 @bflay @newyorklivetv Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Ar… https://t.co/26LtUCSoXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_propain I just listened to this this is fucking Kick-Ass!! I'm going to pick up a copy right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most i have seen Murray play the puck. Really helps out the D. Good things to come?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aloha Kitchen &amp; Bar - @alohakitchenlv in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/JYO1Adom0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the rain can't stop a fresh coats shine.   #TheHandyLion #SmallBusinessSaturday #SanAntonioBusiness… https://t.co/XSMabjIXqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciate opportunity to lay out my first bill of the 86th Session, HB1402. It would provide a mechanism to spur e… https://t.co/MEsuvvjCwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @CrackerBarrel Old Country Store in Longview, TX https://t.co/7B5NsvkOME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hovehater835 @BeckySmirks @krassenstein @EdKrassen 2scam artists..hard to believe anyone listens to them. I unders… https://t.co/HhIuOZ63iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically, Flanagan has more than earned the benefit of a doubt. https://t.co/nK4yQdxCYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquezGreen @haydentupman @tristan5800 @alanmo80 @Ryansjoyner @dkmetcalf14 @Brown1arthur Did a poor 3-cone time s… https://t.co/XrPj0BuEDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omeniesoftware I don’t even want to talk about what I had to do today. It’s too soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisHayesTV I say hand her over to the parents of that little girl for about 5 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ALLCAPS #CapsSens now 4-2 #Caps after they score four answers without response or any real pushback from #Sens of… https://t.co/mlEyadLuhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also try to focus on the positives. We all know, as current students, how grad school can crush your soul. It’s a… https://t.co/M4QKR1S4AV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little taller Brother mikepro_laf ‘s new music video “Special Made” just dropped and it’s straight🔥 #MikePro… https://t.co/Ux3u0y1NuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[How i stumbled across @ElleOnWords  -Read article and laughed at Harry Potter Tweets. -Started reading other tweets… https://t.co/Q79YU7Gfe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wef “... Public debt has risen – notably in the US in the wake of tax cuts and spending increases. Indeed, in many… https://t.co/IUZ2oxAwsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we know that all things work together for good to them that love  God, to them who are the called according to his purpose. Romans 8:28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristijrn @SenSanders @Women4JusticeUS Uh, retirement isn't that comfortable for most people on those programs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Big Mouthio in da house !!! @ Goldsboro, North Carolina https://t.co/aY9iadEqeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Can you post a photo of the spot where your parents dropped you on your head?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrafficAdvisory Hwy 98 WB in Fort Walton Beach remains closed while #FWBPD investigates a fatal accident from this… https://t.co/A5pvfuJFVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Paris Gibson Square Museum of Art https://t.co/vFJItqQxCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BristolDolt @UKLabour @CarolineLucas @theresa_may I'm back to being reasonably confident there will be another vot… https://t.co/NdJYSoPw0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Damnn_Harrall That’s cause thunderstorms usually in the summer and it hasn’t been summer in 7 months mf 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to be happy in whatever situation you’re placed in because those situations are what develop you into the person you’re meant to be]]></document></documents></author>