<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@nprscottsimon @npr @RepSusanDavis or @RepScottPeters or @RepWillHurd would have more credibility on “southern bord… https://t.co/xvBtmcSYfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arianaortiz96 @drrruuuu Lmaooooo I swear ima walk up to Yal like this next time I see yal 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thundoerfist @drvongtweets @100Thieves Can you rise n grind if you never went to sleep? Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flamingo.    #dji  #djiglobal  #mavic2pro  #pink  #portland  #pnw  #flamingo  #shippingcontainer @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/cNdb9o2iAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DArm91 Hoping but when they left and did the renovation (paint job and modernized the bathrooms) they dismantled i… https://t.co/gfRmF83Vkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/9/2019 - 04:57 Temp: 49.7F   Hum:  91% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 29.738in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.01 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahumorlessfem Not any excuse but she's never Cotton to this kind of thing. And I go back to her Be of Supv. Days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXLA That was for Donald Trump: so he can have energy to build the wall, guess it's not ever get built]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillSchupp @TracyMcCreery Legislature should accept the higher minimum wage https://t.co/AhPww4t9kk via @stltoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why my dog keeps stepping on the back of my slides acting like it’s funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[It used to be a fantasy of mine.. And now.. Well.....#taraaa https://t.co/xGvshj1Fpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[First witness is Anthony Maez, Special Agent in Charge. Prosecutors are going through his lengthy qualifications an… https://t.co/XbfcmRRKN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will create problems for Joe Biden in the Black community. He will likely want to choose a Black running mate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard some big stars coming to the big game tomorrow. Let’s Gooo! GO BLUE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiaLoops I tell my wifey all the time that Sarcasm is a gift and a language.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘From the town of Detroit, where we fight til we drop’ Thank you @floggingmolly ☘️ 🍻 @ The Fillmore Detroit https://t.co/HucF4y9GA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[From this day forward i just wanna say thanks , cause your hate is what gave me my strength 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyCummsxxx remember this from @LilFreakInU B roll that has not been seen from the Award winning Officers Convention 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaVonTooMuch @Spike14017340 @PolitiBunny Lazy because you rely on someone else to provide a link to research mater… https://t.co/wm8zFe8hVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayInslee Do you think that the whole world should consider climate change. An putting $into it are just the UNITED STATES. BE HONEST]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first of the #birthdayseason beers, but definitely not last. - Drinking a Revealed Constellations by… https://t.co/NYVM5ExMfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinBust_7 @hellshady Closed adoption are held in secritcy buy dr.s lawyer's and both family sighn a paper too h… https://t.co/W8ODrimpsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold on hold on hold on wait a minute .... WHAAA 🤯🤢 If these ain’t the craziest heso pull ups I’ve ever seen in my… https://t.co/U1SUsgzzdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Glove Dropper by @slyfoxbeer/@rivertownebeer at @PBTSlice — https://t.co/IMH2aeYyjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely want to see the Pats at FedEx and maybe Baltimore but I think Philly might be a bad environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@placardabuse @HowsMyDrivingNY There you go. This is this guys, wife’s plate record below. She works at the school… https://t.co/Wnwa9dCDD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn right. Fuck Zimbabwe and Burundi. Protect America. And now they want to illegal immigrants to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirensaysnope I don't lie, I would never make you feel like shit. But I got a lot of bullshit (baggage). 2 out of… https://t.co/nrASF07fts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewmackenzie This is what happens when you don’t know what the hell you’re doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hillmark2024 @VintageBrowns The REAL #17 Browns jersey to have. I dont care who wore the number after.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeClayNFL I was thinking the same thing. It would be a miracle if someone died in a @NASCAR race at this point.… https://t.co/w3zQbauMJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kairyuu18_21 @TheQuartering @UnsleevedMedia If thats actually the case then sure, I agree. I have no love for EA.… https://t.co/1YhWPh9Nl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 2 years old this case is. Truly unfortunate most of my energy had to be dedicated to that along with hypocri… https://t.co/EiDdD89bXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is about Islam. CAIR and Hamas. Very few in politics have the courage to speak up.If we don't face this for what… https://t.co/5BMT54BJYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream where I saw @realDonaldTrump being carried from the Southern District of New York,  and then to the Sup… https://t.co/mz3TREGsLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how ppl start arguments up here and then turn around and say “tbh idc” when u start making good points like… https://t.co/WoaTQe0QEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pelican_Cancer @ACPGBI @NewmarketRace The MDT for 💯 % of patients is so important for both parties - patient and c… https://t.co/qkzwgD2qcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I bit of a set back. Got a call that i need to go back in for another surgery before i can start radiation. Tumo… https://t.co/S4L9t4Wq3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[A real gem @BarstoolBigCat. Name the state st bar? https://t.co/kgT2baMnO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Birthday Spotlight Celebrating The Birthday of Germind 20 Day Birthday Party: March 11 - Ma… https://t.co/s2FNwYQytX]]></document><document><![CDATA[C- you all annoy me, make rules, eat my memory, put me in a box, and treat me like a slave.  I heal you all.  You a… https://t.co/o2d17LbZQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most notorious airline for herding people into a plane in the most disorganized way, yelling at them and then c… https://t.co/58RxRYMrLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielapachon Hola amor como te va? Dime porque te parece buena idea si el 90% de los choferes no saben lo que dice el aviso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nairb_d @playoff_javy2 @BleacherNation Because he wants money that he’s not worth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defensive Standouts vs. Owls: Tony Garcia (RF), Fabian Torres (CF), Cross Gonzalez (SS), Josiah Ortega (C)… https://t.co/8wfs6aqSX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mezmereyes3 Cheers Buddy!!!! What games you coming to this season? Just get a season ticket....you can ride with us https://t.co/w0LsQePl09]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your income will grow when your mind grows. 👊🔥 . . If you want to make more than you have ever made, you have to do… https://t.co/ZB6TGaSJL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[[145] Young Activists Make Adults Look Like Idiots, Plus CNN Healthcare ... https://t.co/j6Q0Pxy4gW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenMonaghan1 @charliekirk11 The only embarrassment to America is people like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a big of a tough time getting out of the bed today but not going to let it get me down. Just a minor setback… https://t.co/kTupRmV1oA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthAmin I'm glad you took on KD today.  The professionalism of Steph juxtaposed with Durant's petulance really s… https://t.co/Ki8z7ZGsrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zackgubler @RMFifthCircuit Since the sign says “crisps” I’m guessing not in US]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the curious: I'm playing with the compatibility between Balthasar's understanding of kenosis and Nancy's "horiz… https://t.co/5TyoTXavoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats are now running around flailing their arms and besting their breasts over today's travesty of a hearing.  How sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our first session of “Making Your Voice Heard in the Texas Legislature” - next session is at 5:30pm at the Patrick… https://t.co/VBbbed4U3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleeErinn Then again I didn’t eat anything before I went out last night so that’s probably why I was so drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Shrine Auditorium &amp; Expo Hall - @shrinela in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/ZYwBWnzv4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last few from@some @PIHLhockey last in Lebo between @SFLionsHockey  @SF_lions_hockey v. @TJJaguarsHockey. Lions cam… https://t.co/6iO3iTDkAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Dream, Well.... Imagine Yourself a Miracle! All of You ARE... After All! Put out a Sail... Into The Night, T… https://t.co/RvTTXEQAif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylvainLapensee Incroyable il ce font dominé sur la glace depuis le match de hier??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enderinciartem I completely agree. I've been keeping track of how things have gone there. The government is corrup… https://t.co/zH1wUrH6hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh god, i need to find some new hobbies! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/BFRGf3fEaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah cool you were famous but now you're reaching for relevancy and lookin like a dumbass like Soulja boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS So will your husband blame the tornado on Alabama just like he blamed wildfires on CALIFORNIA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennDOrdway I am with Lou. I can't get Kyrie out of town fast enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be looking good n y’all lashes , the 1’s that don’t make you look like a tranny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@finestparadox Yes!! That part!! Run her that diploma!! 👩🏾‍🎓🚨#formerstudentalert🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GopherMGolf @Coach_Fleck Say what you want about him but PJ is one of the best things to happen to the… https://t.co/hV8RvwcgJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier It’s worse than racist to kill our babies!  Dems, the party of death!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSHMBB19 Survivor was meant for you! The only thing I would do is brush up on your puzzle skills. They're not your strong area! #Goodluck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Lock this googly eyed socialist up then deport her to Venezuela after she serves her time so she can… https://t.co/gKa9oiR0rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aveowens_ yeah man, i wear a necklace for my granddad, i wrote my college essay about him, i have his middle name,… https://t.co/zNIxgo8rRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @GreysABC! Last night with S15 Ep15 it became the longest running medical drama in TV history (✌🏽E.R.).… https://t.co/yTFbxqlafj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlschwerz The Machado signing shows the 18/19 hot stove season to have been a bust and likely a lie/cover up by up… https://t.co/VnLOmUUR6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Blah ha ha ha! Pelosi doublespeaking about Omar’s lack of knowledge about what words mean. Even Tarza… https://t.co/myih9bLDmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to #manage #failure, recover, and adjust for #success are critical skills for #founders.… https://t.co/KiLnUkLQCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“More New Country Now” @buzzbrainard have you heard the new EP #MidwesternGirl by @LaurenDuski yet? It is so Awesom… https://t.co/ZclLOqetnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I played Oregon Trail as a kid I would put in the names of all the people I didn’t like and then try to kill t… https://t.co/7btISvSq3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Retail job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Seasonal Sales Associa… https://t.co/dAKW7ROKcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final: #Blackhawks 7 - #Coyotes 1  Peeling gets his first NHL hat trick.  You think you’re out and the ‘Hawks pull you right back in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YahooSports I DO NOT like the look of the updated app. Updating right before the NCAA tourney is a bummer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBruceGord @BringBackLee In the 8th year of his contract? Pretty much anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash April is constantly trying to trip Sanders up. Maybe, she is upset that Sarah doesn’t give her any gri… https://t.co/u20YkMf1dU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Whats an eye glass case What's A BA-LD EAGLE without at leAst 20-20 vision T toT is how much to see]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very thankful to receive an offer from Georgia tech!!! 🐝🐝 @CoachCollins @CoachWiesehan https://t.co/lCQm2zfAhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guttersniper @VisitKC If you are in town for the weekend, O’Malleys in Weston on both snake Saturday and St Patric… https://t.co/9C30HBuINh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Did you invite President Trump.  I’m sure he’d be happy to toast you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL I’ve been using Common Core Math concepts everyday since undergrad. Super easy to do once you figure it out and… https://t.co/XDvjKiyEYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeannaTrump Oh you did baby I'm so turned On and impressed i totally want to get on My Knees Beside you and Join y… https://t.co/yHWLUhpvsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giopal @CPbeacon Columbus just got robbed 2 nights in a row by goalies...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Nothing happens , just like cnn can not except defeat now !🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnaB3 @RoyalFamily @ClarenceHouse @KensingtonRoyal Like the parasites they are?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyzann @SeanTPendergast How did I not know about this when I got married!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods It's fascinating that democrat party is collapsing by virtue of the vacuum created by Hillary and h… https://t.co/r3aqY9vPb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClancyReports @stetayen @LobeLog I'm reminded of when Bush tried to install Chalabi (sic?) in Iraq. Several of the… https://t.co/yiYDhr9uxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephmurphy0904 Good morning Stephanie. ☕️☕️♥️😘 https://t.co/TWcpSBnQp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a 8 #mile #run today before my day got started. Indy the has some flat and smooth running along the canal/rive… https://t.co/ACIbCDt0Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us not forget who Robert Kraft is BFFS with.  Going DOWN like flies... #ImpeachTrumpNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perez doubles down the right field line to score another one!! The game is now tied at 3! Alan Smith scores from second! #FiredUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnathanRoyale @Rustymabry @WhatTheFFacts I won't leave Canada or move to a country with over 1,000,000,000 peopl… https://t.co/EO0zTXh0tG]]></document></documents></author>