<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Llego la hora de echarlos a todos para afuera de una vez, en Venezuela y en Cuba. @FelixLlerenaCUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday March 3 - Daily Yahoo!:     Roger Stone judge: Why wasn't I told about book?;     Kim pays respects at embal… https://t.co/EGDPZMc3Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 New Alert 🚨Subscription packages now available on the website! Check the link in bio. Boston Hempire. New England… https://t.co/zaFK3jvf9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was Justin Trudeau, I'd start my presser early and pull the cameras and live coverage from Andrew Scheer. #JodyWilsonRaybould]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniScotchIrish @AllieKatz2 @eye2winner @Lonestarmomcom @Yakekoge @FactCheckU @lisalbarjas1 @waconia3 @DaddyJim52… https://t.co/pvIoBmRoZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New wreck: this one causing delays heading into durham on Hwy 70 and Miami Blvd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dubs964 @sldebord @Big12Conference @BaylorWBB @ncaawbb They were all there? 9k .... doubt it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Harland Clarke team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/7kWrf5VGuW #TopWorkplace #SanAntonio, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this show and I’ve been watching it everyday for years so I absolutely HATED to see this. He’s handling it j… https://t.co/YN2Qz5drVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @IvankaTrump @EricTrump @FLOTUS Fox debates are awesome it's not a pane… https://t.co/FKDDu65KUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamTarver6 U Sir/Mame are a Retard! I never Claimed Anything. You did. The Burden of Proof is on You! Where did y… https://t.co/IOZnL36P8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemeterDragon I that shot the large majority is real I. The center of frame then some added to cover the screen. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Youngwood crossed 5K. Time 00:38:36, pace 12:26 min/mile, est. finish 8:26 am https://t.co/xtMroUsd6R #runDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@will_doran @dabrams2021 It was an issue in the Ossoff/Handel race. Ossoff lived a mile or two outside the district… https://t.co/Pl4BDjUrRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardonMyTake Fruity pebbles, Reese’s puffs, Cinnamon Toast Crunch, and lucky charms or cap’n crunch. Don’t @ me]]></document><document><![CDATA[things men over 70 love: werthers having their dick out in the locker room]]></document><document><![CDATA[You'd be surprised how long it took to get this picture @ Lansing Brewing Company https://t.co/T53MRez8B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a wild month and a half my peeps. Some severe diet changes and cutting out beer have led to me shedding 2… https://t.co/9kJliVCv6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsharJawad nawaz sharif claiming to be sick and refusing to go to the hospital]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good article from @dstaples on the #Oilers D-development. To me, the 2 big misses were Schultz and Petry. The lat… https://t.co/TyNZZ3hwaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimrome make sure you check out Jack Edwards call on the Bruins Hartford Game last night! Get some whale blubber!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Are mental? Did you have this objection Presidents Bush and Obama used the same damn law to declare a sta… https://t.co/JCEulRctPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need to cut out some of the anti Trump guests. They are predicting a financial doomsday. This will only happen… https://t.co/zECf84XxSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[... he created a beautiful arrangement of motifs and melodies, heart warming songs and gut punching arrangements. T… https://t.co/BzwtpzgD5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanpierpont My corner doesn’t seem to be too badly affected. I think that’s because I don’t tend to follow peo… https://t.co/vzXA5Anmqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is @jimmykimmel still available? This show needs some help. #OscarsSoBoring]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw something on a disabled thread that was sort of offensive. And the person wasn’t trying to be offensive,… https://t.co/7k1MHPiFW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshjmac This about ruined the rest of my day... completely mind boggling  Let Clint handle it https://t.co/ahUTc2lS5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurrisOptics @mlynda_scott @Dr_ASchroeder  got us covered @thebenschroeder]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Ironwood schools are delayed two hours today because of the cold @wluctv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franck_Aubry @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/rV5H8Kf69m]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I think of when I see Michael Keaton is how he is Schmidt’s pen pal on New Girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[But y’all some hoes who can’t focus on one person, too busy “living life” when you ain’t doing shit but being what… https://t.co/v3sfjBFryt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day the universe got me a blown tire today so let’s see how the rest of it feels like 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems that all criteria for hosting the Open SoCal championship game has been met for the higher seed, Clovis We… https://t.co/pTgIqqAZkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus We should all keep two cultural icons in mind this year: The Black Knight from “Holy Grail,” and the… https://t.co/LYxreHOypk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in the tech nerd world. In the entire world, the one with the Wikipedia entry is. He’s an Australian Rules Foo… https://t.co/mHJKxYbqpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstooltweetss @shiftedshaped @MickstapeShow Clearly an offensive foul 🏀 #outsidethecircle #feetset]]></document><document><![CDATA[Health Rock https://t.co/38K6dDBj3W via @YouTube this psa should’ve been directed at university students cause I ju… https://t.co/EN81bPDLen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indiana, I'm passing through you because you're not quite what I need right now.  I'll be back later though.  Promi… https://t.co/geVTUKva5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DionLimTV Ok. This just blows my mind. LOL! That’s about the most-ultimate sign of fandom. My friend, that’s amazing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Brownlee Resevoir, Idaho in Huntington, OR https://t.co/etsw5tuboO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard72462445 @AppSame @AOC it’s cool how you put 8 digits after your name just like every Russian bot does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to travel halfway around the world. Adios, mi casa. @ Arden On The Severn, Maryland https://t.co/0zhft15KBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle and move on. #comedy #tee-hee #grin #playful https://t.co/jbOe3uf2dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoESSB Ya I definitely bailed last time I was invited. Weekends are very hit or miss with me for work. I'm glad pe… https://t.co/w2R7V0xDN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I avoided the HEREDITARY trailer until the movie came out and I will do the same here! great experience. lots of cl… https://t.co/DpbQo8Ou72]]></document><document><![CDATA[A major professional sport ....  needs a professional body controlling its rules .... in my opinion time for… https://t.co/5UKIZ1foaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gsong94 @BeatriceHazele2 @krassenstein Because of Trump new legislation should be enacted. No one should come off… https://t.co/wKx5n5wpjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️  🏀Raleigh Egypt ✅ Even though i was shocked they didn’t even make it to state i said early eliminat… https://t.co/U7nTbzYT9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illicit69kitty Fine. Just paying bills then off to work. Hows your Monday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacksonville is widely reported to be the leading team @NickFoles to sign as free agent franchise quarterback.  Not… https://t.co/Dzh9y6x0ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a minute since we saw snow here in the Seaport ❄️ https://t.co/MXa9aygXAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The milk ain’t clean. Where did this “sports tape” come from?  A third tape allegedly featuring R. Kelly has surfac… https://t.co/XanjZQ6MZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaseballBros Someone tell that kid to catch the ball with two hands, and the coach to throw the ball with one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neal’s BBQ and Flubs open on the same day?! You know we had to do it to ‘em https://t.co/NMj9fUkvN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Trump Betrays ‘Forgotten’ Americans https://t.co/JKMVIqZ4dp Break America while you golf again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joetron4000 Pretty sure she applied only because her boyfriend's brother could get her in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jose_madero De esos días que recuerdo la canción de "Huésped en casa propia" y ahora "Final Ruin"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt’s gotta get his head checked for even thinking about getting between bob and that shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump and his cronies have suppressed the internet it has totally shut down on my end in Buffalo New York]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KARAinFLA On the contrary, Rudy Giuliani is the fool and a big one at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiverBornA @NikkiGlaser Fuck it. I am going to block your prejudgemental ass anyway. You seem to WANT to get into… https://t.co/uC7Ic82ABs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas felicidades por tu cumpleaños, querido @JoseMario_BMA. Es un honor contarte como maestro y como amigo. Un gr… https://t.co/pfk0V1gXBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cousin Ski Trip 2019. Hopefully the start of a beautiful tradition! So much laughter, good food, and shreddin’ the… https://t.co/vldNNbpaRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yb dropped a song. A damn in my feelings one, then it ain’t even hitting how he supposed to...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cHaOs667 Yeah this is a good point...if you don't need a lot of hierarchical data, all of these formats are overki… https://t.co/jzCHjTSYzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been in the shower since 5:15am....... it’s now 7:33am.  #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/9zZReF4VyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHanlon jazzmaster —&gt; compressor —&gt; overdrive —&gt; fuzz —&gt; chorus —&gt; dr z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianBrown21 @WorldofOutlaws @FVPparts @caseysgenstore Rain in the west. Snow in the east. Not a good start to the year again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonnienorman @ToddSStewart @frizull Much thanks to Bonnie - her large group of followers really helped get the wor… https://t.co/xLI947cCmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin @dbongino @TheRickWilson Rick Wilson is a midget and a punk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussBeTheMoney I love watching him play. I used to like Grant Williams but he’s a hoe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the work to see your dreams fulfilled. #socialmediamarketing #loveyourself #digitalmarketing #consistency… https://t.co/nhSWuCSI6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democratic Republic of Congo with two parallel multi-dimensional selves abusing the moon Nazi base in the back that… https://t.co/p2u3tDjozC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @SenJohnKennedy Continually trying to discredit a mans character, has no effect on what he has been charged wi… https://t.co/On43zUDjzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pixelpreaching @MrChuckD #FlavaFlav and @PublicEnemyFTP tried telling everyone this in 1986]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Review: Sex, love and aliens in eternal wild child Gregg Araki’s ‘Now Apocalypse’: “Everything in… https://t.co/1Qv0agwZog]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered the @MorpheBrushes x @JeffreeStar brushes and sponges and they were supposed to get here next week, now t… https://t.co/EXBtiMstxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aelfred_D “This movie takes a stand against everything you represent.” I mean, what is she basing that on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart literally broke when i realized i typed “succesful” instead of successful and posted it on my snap story... i’m so embarrassed.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[No fake beard look, book your beard enhancement treatment with us today:  https://t.co/0iPq3KJ8AH  Natural Beard En… https://t.co/kspMpDxuf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump They want full control and Trump is an obstruction to that. The man is doing what the c… https://t.co/BsabU0tcIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRowland9 @LadyLibertyInEx @GOP @POTUS NEVER! they with them, not us, they only follow orders of their donors,… https://t.co/gI9DnX6ovx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ufc @espn @francis_ngannou @cainmma So pumped to see Cain back. Been way too long! #UFCPhoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean what did she expect.. 🤷🏽‍♀️ sorry but the woman had it coming to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnchormanV2 You need to chose a better example lol If RDR2 came out the same day as Spider-Man, God of War, Unchar… https://t.co/pNcPApnlkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeslaJoy didn’t realize I wasn’t following you - great tweets. @motterstedt33 check it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quand Martial va devoir se justifier auprès de Mélanie après son « Montre moi un eins »]]></document><document><![CDATA[You, Peter, and Davy, on the 20th Anniversary Tour, was the very first concert I ever attended...never got a chance… https://t.co/fT4nIPb70u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collegeftbfan @pooraggies @JchipHubbard @TAMU_UT_Rivalry The people in this tweet were alive the last time Texas w… https://t.co/G67fiHg1mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEShop Its all entertainment Becky Lynch will be at wrestlemania's main event for the  women's championship!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stackable chevron fever!  #stackablerings #stackableringset #weddingbands #angeluccijewelry #diamondrings… https://t.co/HINr4pJ4FB]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFFICIAL: Justin Schultz is back for the @penguins after a more than 4 month absence #LetsGoPens https://t.co/IAmtgOLo3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[YEEEEEES! So proud of X5 from SCV taking home First at JAMZ Nationals! #jasperchoreography #teddgood #proud2bescv]]></document><document><![CDATA['Why would you lie about that?': Republican donors don't understand why Trump would lie about 'Tim Apple' flub https://t.co/YjssvW4GiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trojan JROTC Inspection Pictures pt.2 @HGHSJROTC @cathyiveygray @HazelGreenHigh  #trojannation https://t.co/spDtxPt3LH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_FOS Like if after infinity war which did insane numbers they took the Russo’s off and someone else did endgam… https://t.co/35PZUC7h4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo This time of night, all we hear is radio gaga.  Radio blah blah]]></document><document><![CDATA[all star NBA é um baita evento!   Tu vê que os caras se divertem e é um espetáculo impressionante pra quem gosta do esporte.]]></document></documents></author>