<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlexBielak @drinkwillibald @WR_Record Overall sounds like a good meal. The setting looks appealing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Neilson responds to the allegations re: Danyiel Walker, accused in sex abuse charges of minors “To think that… https://t.co/xRLa0bb5EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Recycled Lobster Rope Doormat,  you can, too, here: https://t.co/nqLUW4f3Cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer to the rescue? Or warg-Bran saving himself? #spoilers #TheKingsroad #GoTRewatch2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now own Pure Moods I-IV 🐬🦄🐋 p.s. if you’re at SXSW come say hi: I play Saturday at @shiners_saloon for the Future… https://t.co/3M35dd7XsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motherofcakes I am an Aries and what’s why I am not feeling any more than I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Any updates to share regarding the outage? Flights are starting to board, but no updates on system outage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paz_e_Perigo If Russia deployed the missile in venezuela and Cuba, it could cover half of USA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can hear my roomate bangin is it rude if I politely text him to shut the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS The style,features,graphics, I WANT ONE! #GalaxyS10Rocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a break from submittable for a while. And I forgot how hard it is to do this. https://t.co/rX8d4qOA4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USMCLiberal @FoxNews Thet love crap like this...fear, anger, anxiety, and this was a perfect dose for this network and Dumps nutjob base]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space news.  Our floor director has fun with editing apps.  @erniebjorkmantv @channel2kwgn https://t.co/d0x4796KBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me..my eyes are great but if I saw you by accident and I didn’t mean to see you.. then just take it as I didn’t see… https://t.co/XA1h5PglIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to sound like a needy millennial but I’ve made my bed two days in a row now &amp; would like some recognition]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sharpenthesaw today Gators!! We’ll see you back tomorrow! https://t.co/eREp4LIcdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Terrae0218 @teeheeheemcfee Wow, I just binge watched that again last weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now you can say..We beat Duke 2 times!!! Yeah!! Woo hooo!!!...without Zion, and, and now Bolden, and Zion.. Okay. Y… https://t.co/3iIqnFbdd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blanche de Chambly by @Unibroue at @waltdisneyworld — https://t.co/MCMTgshMZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m officially team #SansaStark because of @SophieT in the #SuckerVideo @jonasbrothers 😍🔥 https://t.co/R3jLmlK90Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost 1AM and I’m on my way home from a night out and all I can do is smile because one of my clients accompl… https://t.co/cbXRISCEVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cast Member Patty on the bus this evening from EPCOT to Coronado Springs with her trivia all the way home was aweso… https://t.co/qhPckfTtBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaiahosborne35 @GREXbeatz @ChampagneDrip Fuck... if someone’s got a spot I might be widdit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have gone from never ever listening to a podcast before to being TOTALLY OBSESSED with the #Iditapod #uglydogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond If you could be cast as any role in a musical what would it be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shampoo bars are great! @lushcosmetics makes some and has a variety so you can pick which is best for your hair. I… https://t.co/qtBn3KL4h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had SO much fun visiting the @MorpheBrushes store at NorthPark with this one today! I’ll for sure be back! Maybe… https://t.co/c67O0VSxEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @nbcsnl I am starting to think he believes SNL is a news program, but it isn't such a str… https://t.co/O2CoEP5Gzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Frankly, no American should be doing business in Russia, and Russians shouldn't be doing business here. They attacked our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is DJT TODAY, Rachel. He works for no salary. He’s donated during storms. He had all out for PR. But, they didn… https://t.co/a0LmRkRc7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some pictures from our outing to #homosassaspringswildlifestatepark today! #manatees #alligators #birds #nature @ H… https://t.co/b3F9Cat58m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckeon_brendan @CoachJeffMoore @coach_croomMX @Coach_RMcCarthy @RonDiGravio @CoachWilsonSTM @Coach_Ander5on @CCSU… https://t.co/djhZruYYkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the quote hits 45 RTs I’ll hop right the f on!! OR.. I’ll keep close eye on https://t.co/3PHrY5pbYz so once we… https://t.co/Uh2R3em3tI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Qlik, can we get our amazing #QlikFederal SA @BI4Fed a #shoutout for this incredible #QlikSense App? 🚀 #NASA +… https://t.co/2BZxFElzUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DALvsTBL I see you Dallas, sorry for your luck! @TBLightning @SouthwestAir https://t.co/0jwdFQzJu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The difference between Antonio Brown and Le’veon Bell is that Bell actually wants to play football and Brown wants… https://t.co/oJsvo0uhJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#admitmoviesyouveneverseen Shawshank Redemption Young Frankenstein and Citizen Kane]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS HAS MY TEAM GOING CRAZY!!! Great for those #keto peeps! Low in #carbs and high in #protein If you love caramel… https://t.co/rYx7RNESaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t ask me for the hw you weren’t willing to do. I’m not stressing for 2 of us I stress for me myself and my boyf… https://t.co/16VZjmuDjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got to see the youngest boy (a 8yr old) that attends ELAC. I am still in disbelief]]></document><document><![CDATA[That view though. #ayearinthelife @ New York, New York https://t.co/P8fACxxIeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot When the GOP invited Bibi to the floor of Congress to rant about sitting @POTUS44, they became the problem… https://t.co/jE3maev7Gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NERevs game is underway!   🚨Live stream below 🚨  https://t.co/OW7gHHOG7g  #NERevsinFL 🏝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PainOutlaw Yes you do! It’s incredible! Win or lose us fans rock the fortress! We definitely love our Knights!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/64RqDBcEB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well It’s been 23 years since I lost my best friend .. the strongest woman I have ever known .. you gave me so much… https://t.co/hwJfkTdaRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump when delusional and disfuncional @kristendoute says she is done can she be done forever please and… https://t.co/GxC50McGP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could win some resources to keep the Grade 5s active too @jtrampleasure Have your students decide which of your… https://t.co/9MZem7s9zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden We can say the same to you vets, EB! Thank you for sticking around for all of these years! As fellow huma… https://t.co/rf9kjA3GJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marwbm1 @mattgaetz Matt does have a girlfriend he’s stalking @AOC n she thinks he’s creepy, because he is Yuck just another Nazi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_melissalee @heatherleegee @ShoshanaFlax @ebritter2 @CassieMalmo_ @TalkativeTara @aliamaria9 @thejamietan… https://t.co/3ef7zrXsst]]></document><document><![CDATA[of the world’s Muslims.  But as violence continued against the Rohingya by the State and Rakhine buddhists, when re… https://t.co/wSSoVvoY19]]></document><document><![CDATA[so you’re saying if I squirt this shit up my nose I won’t be sad anymore...I’ll have 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunningly beautiful!!!  #VoteKathrynBernardo  #KCA @bernardokath https://t.co/fHacC5bUAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CP3 Hey, saw the 3rd destructive incident to happen at your home: between the deer, Harden and now the mascot, dud… https://t.co/1p00LsfP7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “You know Umbrella Academy is based on a comic written by Gerard Way, right?” My bf: “oh yeah I heard the show… https://t.co/TkljnlTFhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yes please!   Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from office  https://t.co/RaJElEuiXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[i pray i still have my circle when i reach this age bc nothing hits better than these kinds of moments. shit really… https://t.co/Z1unGuPaT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianeWUtah @EPIXHD @tander_mina @LelandOrser You look smashing dahling.  Paraphrasing a fav song “Every other day,… https://t.co/puqT7eEfsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100ProofCharlie I say you stip shoving and say it :) but thats just me 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in to @TeresaTomeo’s show this morning at 8CST when guest host @sherrybrownrigg &amp; I will talk about the… https://t.co/YGcZBMcMQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaberries Wasn’t there blood on the trail and police yesterday? Try Bronson Canyon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge my sword to the realm! I just entered for a chance to attend the official #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How… https://t.co/xSa7niYfXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Listed in #Orlando #FL. 3190 DANTE DRIVE 207! Please retweet!  https://t.co/8eO6cFWpck]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s Monsta X, we know.   If not and if it’s someone I like, I’m fucked again. Lmao 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejonlindstrom OMG you having a great time with Ryan &amp; Kevin Jon #GH55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AffairValentino I wish there had been a pic of Rudy in that outfit . I am sure it was passed down . He would have been so darn cute!! 💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the opportunity to go to Pink concert last night but turned it down. APPARENTLY I am the only one that didn't go..]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good way to insure a good night and sweet dreams is to send your sister this picture (which is not my cat!!) as s… https://t.co/TP5MLN9Qwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to take a break from being a therapist yesterday to be a tattoo artist. I got toe create this fun Star Trek log… https://t.co/XvLb1G4DST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld The #OpioidEpidemic is real, west-east. Meth angels are prostitutes who use crack breakin'down veneer of… https://t.co/jLxOwRHUkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been up since 5:40 (thanks Palms) and have had a whole pot of coffee to myself. Way too hype now and thinking… https://t.co/C58x40PDv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stella stared at me like a maniacal murderer again but I caught her yawning. @ South Shore, Chicago https://t.co/akhyPsq3Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warnerkyle29 @NHLFlyers @RHartzy18 Ahh I’m battling the worst cold, thanks for catching that and the kind words👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day crafts with our 5th grade reading buddies from machatz_class ❤️ @paulroadschool @ Paul Road School https://t.co/P7Lhlioghi]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th grade Hawks having fun discovering Lines Of Symmetry in different shapes! #TeamSISD #HawkPrideSISD #unstoppable https://t.co/J8o5Pv0c8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone keeps bumping into my tattooed arm. I have another arm you can bump into instead 😖😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We have improved the readiness of the force; we have cut years out of acquisition schedules and gotten better pric… https://t.co/2JJ6ogl8rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heystephanie Feel free to reach out to us about our story! We’re a couple with a creative project launched in 2017… https://t.co/i20XOmWPj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 Lindsey don’t know shit about kids or what they need.  Lindsey is a lonely old spinster!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @suziday123 @Cbp8Cindy @cazij @JackConnie @thatsVeryKari @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG @ccatmpt @simplysallyh… https://t.co/1HmS7AKs1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter @aaroncarter Happiness is where you find it live life because you have this oneI hope you have a great… https://t.co/zJhgHECMGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s supposed to say a Guide to Cooling Off! Type-o I didn’t catch ! @austinfoodwine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Head on over to Pickleman’s for today’s profit share!!! #ShamrockWeek https://t.co/Pvf9AsebPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motherhood is like a rollercoaster, filled with lots of highs and lows. Let's get real, it hasn't been all rainbows… https://t.co/3e2iozNfwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @JerryFalwellJr @AOC How Christian of him. Beware of false prophets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: anyone traveling between walnut ridge and Jonesboro, there’s been some kind of accident on the highway and tra… https://t.co/nhCdHfOb0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSpringer Hard to tell, but looks like they are running with 11 moose on that team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ElizabethMay Blaming others is his way. He just happens to have people blaming others for him. Blame shift is cla… https://t.co/yNXFu3PVEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jess_stroot i agree, but the mint ones are absolutely fantastic &amp; commonly overlooked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRoKhanna @DonaldJTrumpJr Loved it every time @DonaldJTrumpJr ‘s name popped up 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta James 3:7 All kinds of animals, birds, reptiles and sea creatures are being tamed and have been tamed by mankind,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseAnnDeMoro This does not surprise me.  I think that Fox likes to enrage the centrist Democrats. It's kind of am… https://t.co/8Rm1IdqoQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Never feel so comfortable that you assume there is nothing left to fight for.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time I see you I'm giving you a high five Cause hugs are over-rated just F.Y.I.  Most genius song writing or what?!?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is she doing out of jail?  Oh that's right, Comey didn't do his job which AG Sessions in turn didn't do his jo… https://t.co/Gh77jlPV8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread by @yashar: "1. I want to talk about ADHD. I was diagnosed with ADD when I was 13-years-old. To say it's mis… https://t.co/XTkkMjQqP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Putin_Potatoes @maxfish1000 @mikehalv I have way more reasonable conversations with Trump supporters than Clinton supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/bWJfl80juu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait #DavidIgnatius is not still saying give birther a chance. #Khashoggi @MSNBC @Morning_Joe]]></document></documents></author>