<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#StCatharines councillor @karrieporter is next up on the panel, starting with a history of the working class #UbuRoundtable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found peace in the #trail. #running #ForestFriday #runner #burlingtonma https://t.co/i1MeLyHt5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let the children come to me; do not prevent them, for the Kingdom of God belongs to such as these. Amen, I say to… https://t.co/giRKBSOeI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh my god i am so in love with my boyfriend. and i also love him so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad that I got to capture this moment with our Abuelito before his health declined. Thankfully he is still… https://t.co/LbujvoDHZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it when I’m supposed to be packing a suitcase I feel the most desire to tweet or do absolutely anything else… https://t.co/qjrY0Khg93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve 👍🏻👏🏻👏🏻 vamos #valientes necesitamos mas de estos en Venezuela. #VenezuelaLibre #FueraMaduroDeVenezuela #FueraMaduro  🇨🇴🇻🇪 unidos ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed an all-time favorite in #PhysEd this week- PARACHUTE!❤️💙💚💛 @BakerElem students had so much fun with this cl… https://t.co/hW1zSRK2Nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleeMayorga @TeaByAli But, shes keeping her husband so happy , she says so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayehasenW Like zero composure? Hmmm I think a healthy amount of nerves is an indicator of care and interest. But… https://t.co/gBZbYxQW02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone come to SoCal and attend this event with me https://t.co/qUv9wlNniN]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the sticking points is that some who are working on the bill want to remove language in the bill that allows… https://t.co/AFBqPaxAJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from this “Smooth Operator” ❤️ #walkerkeengriffith #redforbaileebyler @ Stewarts Forest, Conr… https://t.co/Q4wTAX9ewv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunkKinze Thanks! It’s amazing what these boys can do when they get to play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ha! Me @gerryvisco cooking #spaghettiandmeatballs for dinner with marks_invisible_spectacular I’m #italamericana a… https://t.co/2b5jqm4G9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil bye bye now Twitter, I got introuble so I now have to delete this app ✌🏽✌🏽✌🏽✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliasoreheart wants me to write this long essay about my 6 months of travel thus far and maybe I will one day, b… https://t.co/2YVrE1I10n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EspinosaSilis En estos días de pésimas decisiones políticas es lo que le da alegría a Twitter, imagínate el gozo que sería leer a Peña bebé]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seananmcguire Mine is Ladyhawke. You may have been to one of our parties at Baycon in years past.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea this would be the last time I sang with Tucker Jensen but I am so grateful for the opportunity. Heart… https://t.co/q646gmKiAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor baby has a 101.7 fever. Ugh my poor little man  #Booger #Ryan #3YearsOld #Flu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tri (Delta) and tell me we’re not official members...🤩💙#happyinitiation #sistasista @ Laurel Hall https://t.co/dlpqHHks4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This season of #RHONJ was too short!!! But at least it ended with someone getting tossed in a pool in true Jersey fashion!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Go back under the rocks you came from.  Come on Mueller we’re counting on you to throw this treaso… https://t.co/gHw79bIB4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[My moms way of getting me to move home is using the cat.. 😂🤦🏼‍♀️ “you know she keeps looking for you wondering wher… https://t.co/qBpbgB5lnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did the #GoogleRihanna + my birthday and honestly, I love this look. https://t.co/FuLMCRY4HO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I’m crying I got the wrong pink for my braces 😭 I thought it was the same color from last time 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ Accountability and gettin’ the job done. Can we show this to the U.S. Senate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I got something from global news  .. and now I posted some things  it is late news  ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy will have his mama and sister at Bernheim. They will be great sights to see! Can’t wait!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall @dbongino DNC wasn’t all wrong in leveraging Clinton over Sanders.  DNC knows Sanders would have bee… https://t.co/gHux6Uxi1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh just washed sheets , pillow case &amp; comforter feel like heaven on earth right now - https://t.co/OBCpjTPrz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and alyssa laying right next to each other sending each other tweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brad_Marr @Jeopardy i’m so sorry to hear. but yes it is nasty that’s why we need to continue to advocate for early detection and a cure 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[😇💓Ámate, reconoce lo valiosa que eres y tu misión de transformar el mundo!  🙋🏼‍♀️Hoy es un buen momento para armoni… https://t.co/a8n8yABX3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I strongly think they should make the eastern part of Queens  County  part of New York State , considering the fact… https://t.co/nsVPbF5BFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFoofinator THIS IS THE BEST PORTRAYAL OF THEIR FRIENDSHIP OH MY GOODNESS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseCracka He cries on cue. Hopefully he'll be arrested, charged and have to pay for man hours for filing false charges.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennaxkills @CCSantini @VenusLux I wish more women would admit that because the make it seem like it’s a taboo or… https://t.co/gWym8Kyqhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMagi Happy Belated Birthday John! Hope you had a fun day in the studio ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC  and @senatemajldr since you guys have time to take a "show" vote on green new deal, make sure you… https://t.co/YUZM3l6ctv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyPWags If you don’t think I’m live streaming Friday’s interview from the office TV, you don’t know me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Victory to victory. Day by day. Let’s go! Upward bound. #SharingLifeLessons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t lose your integrity chasing that bag. Some bags just cost too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sight of Paolo’s dresses literally makes me cry cause I’m fucking broke and I want to be a princess]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dedicated Gluten-Free in New York City guide has just been updated. There are now more than 40 completely gluten… https://t.co/DwAvVuwIms]]></document><document><![CDATA[God to have this woman in your corner! #TheOscars #JenniferHudson #LadyGaga  ROYALTY! 👑🥂🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Runn4UrLives @JalenReeves_10 @suevee85 @Copy_Beethoven @Yo_TheOrangedog @natti_p07 @sloopydeb @Pomm_Mom… https://t.co/aztyFbJhCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legendary coach Scotty Bowman is our guest on Episode 102 of The Red and White Authority to reflect upon the life o… https://t.co/C25K4ckcU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Col. Martin for being selected as the KALB Golden Apple winner! Can’t wait to hear him speak at this pr… https://t.co/kLkkk85AGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, "I don't really wanna do that one right now. Hmmmm, I'll just move it to the bottom of the stack of papers."  3… https://t.co/388zPFTGOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back inside. Something in the other building, not mine. Now to try and go to sleep at some point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #FacilitiesMgmt jobs like "General Utility Worker - Detroit-OCS" at Aramark in #Livonia, MI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moontallica Same. Throwbacks to that time my friend and I were watching The Texas Chainsaw Massacre and I laughed… https://t.co/7IZG5QIIwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to whoever blasting dembow in my building rn, i’m in a great moodt lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Hillary is our next president in 2020 , then we can get a special council to investigate her past . Then we wi… https://t.co/DSiKQ7jGIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uninterrupted @AB84 @steelers If you are a true lover of the game and are a true competitor then you know these co… https://t.co/MMV93gy1G2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm making Caribou Lou, Jungle Juice, Pink Panty Droppers, and a playlist of @andrenickatina and @TechN9ne for my 3… https://t.co/ntPu6qm6tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Au bistouri, les commissions scolaires… vraiment ? https://t.co/I8twxcdCdC via @lp_lapresse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFordFANatic @MapleLeafs I would be so grateful for these for my dad! Hes a die hard fan and i would so grateful… https://t.co/VAf9uv2leX]]></document><document><![CDATA[flowers are honestly one of my most favorite things in the whole world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was/am his baby girl...he always gave me a Valentine. From Franny Farmer French mints to the extra large… https://t.co/38EsNyDGLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[❣️Que esté día esté lleno de bonitas sorpresas y mucho amor❣️  #FelizJueves14Feb❣️ #FelizDíaDelAmorYLaAmistad❣️ https://t.co/hHvuWE6H5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrosecloseBobbi @PresidentsMouth Thank you. I did say that pretty much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravoliciousnes Oh, that's so weird I could have sworn it was Tues. It's my fav!! It's taping I have it on auto re… https://t.co/tz8DxEWEbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we have a wall, we won’t need the military, because we’d have a wall.   Huh.   #IllegalNationalDisaster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmarchives @BTS_twt Again me, ok if I can help, here I am. I don't work. As always the best of the best. Do you ha… https://t.co/ygdcGS3YGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Word then be selling them used 😂 I ain’t buyin no shoes another mf had they feet in 😂 y’all niggas really crazy out… https://t.co/cihvSPMWJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @realDonaldTrump Childish vulgarity from the left as usual]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Doctors advocate surgery et al. Medical MANnipulation albeit hyeract obsess-compulse tardive diskinesia seeki… https://t.co/c1CY9tGAfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reunited and it feels so goood!!! @ Momo's Nightclub https://t.co/JiF7un4jVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marc Anthony - Tu Vida en la Mía (Official Video) https://t.co/xE22jH1G4W via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some bitches are annoying af and think they’re all good and shit but really wanna be playing victim https://t.co/bQFu7csHv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should really embrace social interactions more. It’s good for my growth in moderate doses. Lucky to be in an envi… https://t.co/3GtcH7w0pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoevaldes So damn what! Sounds like you’re more upset the wine cost $20 than you are about her age. Your attempt t… https://t.co/FK5F3ryxzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnBurroughs2 @JGreenblattADL She didn’t condemn israeli policies. The slogans she’s been using are typical antise… https://t.co/qWgrBxlzex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk idk idk idk I’m sitting in my car crying but not because I think I failed but because I JUST DONT KNOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever wanna cut your hair, dye it &amp; then move out of state? because that is the point of mental breakdown im at currently 💁🏼💁🏼💁🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie’s talking in the confessional like she’s #TheBachelorette hahaha #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[No cramps yet finger cross I’m not getting it peroid and there’s a baby in the oven]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting the cars tour @DaleJr @JRMotorsports @AdamLemkeRacing @EarnhardtKelley @joshberry https://t.co/JoXxpie6nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you struggle with Plantar Fasciitis? We can help!    👣 👣 👣 #advancedclinicalmassage #manualtherapy… https://t.co/9YrInIq8Ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all females are HILARIOUS. So Saturday I’m walking to my car. This girl calls me over there. She asks where I’m f… https://t.co/TMYhAxsrBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGkee Sending a lot of love and appreciation to your ♥️ this morning...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris There are actions which will make harm from AGW more containable. Those actions involve difficult ene… https://t.co/kHeNapcW7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GladisBaricako @aimbertrandik @nsabiyumva_ Lol ke nari muri 4eme secondaire j'avais 15-16ans. One day nari gusoma… https://t.co/9g2kRwLqSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love #Sunday mornings because I always get a #homemade #breakfast courtesy of my wonderful husband!… https://t.co/ltXIoh9Mfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m here for the sunny monday morning commute in NYC. thanks twitter jnj morgan.stanley 🍎 @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/4Hs0Hyzd4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahahahaha This is so amazing these fucking people are so amazingly stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some $$, a personal chef and driver. Then and only then can I have a mommy does NOTHING day.  #kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[the one time i watch a whole season of the bachelor and i get this,,,ARE YOU KIDDING ME i am never giving a white m… https://t.co/uJPDxqCumD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauraharrier @essencemag #blackwomeninhollywoodluncheon #blackkklansman #instafashion #instastyle… https://t.co/wGH0mcBpIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My vocabulary is extremely limited under pressure. Super motivating, I'm sure. 🙄#goluke https://t.co/TCqyahRXnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. I'm a lady. I'm a grandma. I used to teach catechism and deliver communion to hospitalized parishioners.… https://t.co/cv8svZi1Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smbgrvn Wait not the $140 pink chain are you? They had one when I got mine but it was $$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chize20 @somethingicanre @KamalaHarris We are in the circular revolution.Which means climate warming. Polar ice ca… https://t.co/KNWGDboRIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The big takeaway for me at Gerald Epp’s talk last night was Dowel Laminated Timber, DLT, the latest in mass timber… https://t.co/hJVnkWrE49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goddessofoptics @crjfactsonly @tedlieu @POTUS Not when its another witch hunt! We should investigate the investigators!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending our morning discussing instructional strategies to maximize student engagement by exploring all different in… https://t.co/FlniE1i89k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @bothao to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. I will be posting books tha… https://t.co/x6JcfjOlDQ]]></document></documents></author>