<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I hear the Churrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrro’s guy at Camelback.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahernandezamama @NBA @NFL @ahernandezamama NHL offers the winning all star team one million to the winner. Those g… https://t.co/owDeWM6muK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/e89k8x8etq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/jrjtl0RS98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Charger by @BoleroSnort at @saltgastropub — https://t.co/wuwIxhKISL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xnar256 Hopefully by then, the wall will be built and ICE has deported illegals by the truck load. Message sent, i… https://t.co/CUAbAUOjpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Comp games this morning.  Countdown twice (Countdown suck in D2, IMO) Matched against teams of 3 or 4 as all solo… https://t.co/jliswKrZPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GRCosplayKid @Tama_Tonga @Tama_Tonga it’s a snow day... AGAIN. Come pick him up. 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite brand collabs with my favorite childhood show? TAKE MY MONEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notameadow @ThreddyTheTrex The Surface Pen experience &gt; iPad pencil experience. But you do you😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfrutando de la presentación de la Orquesta Sinfónica Juvenil de @ssp_sonora en el programa Gobierno Abierto, en… https://t.co/Gg6PHh0GQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the day they were called trailer parks now they’re called trailer hoods.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Handing out some new t-shirts to team members today! Look for them around #kingsport if you’d like to join a winnin… https://t.co/VfqvqZn3Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally have no idea who's hosting #TheOscars and they're starting rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipReiderson @RealMamaEagle @frankandrus It’s one of your wonderful traits. We love that about you. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @amyschumer feed a giraffe a carrot then immediately 180 away from it was the only thing able to give me e… https://t.co/SjrrUGEjYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3WinstonSalem Uhh, if you are man enough to risk working out under a #Mutton (@Jameswillbo) Q after the game last… https://t.co/cb3PyEPmCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justgavinhere I probably have some bias, but it’s the best concert venue in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterBurnsESPN The test of time should n your first clue. The wheel keeps evolving making it top 5 for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[So in Universe when they try to make it so they can dial Earth and bring other scientists to Destiny via the commun… https://t.co/y2IS0IuqB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindo visitar a la familia 😍 en Indian River County, Florida https://t.co/zWs4rOYmyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @JackWonkovich live it up brother, you me and durham gotta get together soon ! 🚫🧢 https://t.co/wcGxlKF4qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salute Lebron passing #BigMIKE on the all time scoring list... https://t.co/ziJeM3GyVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YearOfTheViolet @WrestleTalk_TV TNA did that once with @IAmTarynTerrell and it worked out so well when she faced… https://t.co/pjJ4cKKKiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaivanShroff Remember when this grifter keptbscreaning "release the transcripts" of her speeches.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listened to @miguelzenon’s last album, Yo Soy La Tradición, with @SpektralQuartet. Beautiful writing and playi… https://t.co/hfbqSYixPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another study that highlights the need for athletic trainers in secondary schools. #AT #athletictrainer… https://t.co/xodKzZeitM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirtle Some veteran jerseys in the lower bowl! Talking Rookie Clarkies, Felix the Cats, early Sundin’s, a Timmy Ho… https://t.co/AxAchtrwNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Marvin Menzies wife #unlvrebels #unlvvssjsu #unlvvssanjosestate #unlv #rebels #runninrebels #unlvrunninrebels… https://t.co/gWSMfZx5Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @realDonaldTrump @DineshDSouza @DonaldJTrumpJr @charliekirk11 @LouDobbs @TheDemocrats Assault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyWest_ @dylew_7 @PerfectEffort14 Congrats bro!! #RepresentThe828]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Gaetz is Insane in the head his he needs to be disbarred for making threats on Michael Cohen and Family]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wrestling tastes vary greatly, that's why I'm excited to see both @JoeyRyanOnline and @danielmakabe wrestle twice this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love requires forgiveness, truth, high expectations, and patience.” - Kiese Laymon, How to Slowly Kill Yourself and Others in America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith please go on @OTB_ESPN with @TBob53 ! Snoothcie wootchies! #bong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chubbythug Lmao because these bitches ode stupid and shallow, the ones you talking about never worth the attention from us kings 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @AlitaMovie last night...epic world building sci-fi that never condescends. @Rodriguez well done! Go see… https://t.co/lDKperM2MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaneBaldwin Be strong brother you’ll see the light differently and if it was meant to be she may return if not the… https://t.co/UAZYHAepCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesGrantFL Yes, sooner than later traditional public education, historical catalyst for assimilation and communi… https://t.co/U4SIAc8BFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout @SpiritAirlines for the most dysfunctional terminal of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how a racist looks. We, the People, must condemn any and all language by racists like Meadows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A career money launderer like yourself surely knows better then sit try to deny the criminality of… https://t.co/1Fx0WhXk46]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basche42 Seeing meetings is just a matter of scrolling for me  I’ve always found time travel to be a tacit admissi… https://t.co/hVJRVKBO21]]></document><document><![CDATA[#humpday🍑 #whowokeyouupthismorning #godisgoodallthetime #blessandhighlyfavored #iamaking #jojosenergy… https://t.co/OX2jJ6lczp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home from the #pmjtour at roythomsonhall.  What a FREAKING AWESOME SHOW!  Time to wind down with a… https://t.co/YyREH6Sh0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankmSounders @WAYouthSoccer @TacomaStarsSC @DrColleenHacker @nubber4747 @coachfewing @alanhinton11 @hopesolo… https://t.co/hDmFyQhn6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MookieBlayloc11 @JohnBoschFF @BirdDynasty @FF_TravisM @riese_adam @DynastyOuthouse @DynoDiagnostic @DynoCrossroads… https://t.co/87tu1j7qWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The world economy could increase by $2 trillion by closing the gender gap.” - @DianeKazarian of @PwC_Canada #IWD2019 #BalanceforBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seattle_Amy Asparagus server...   or fancy ass smacker.   Perhaps it can be both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenAttiah @washingtonpost @JKhashoggi @PostOpinions @Hala_Aldosari Honoring a pie hole of the Muslim Brotherhood… https://t.co/5amjr9AdTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Chris for all you do in keeping our store safe every day. #takingcareofpeeps #orangeblooded]]></document><document><![CDATA[📞 954 825 7359 or private message me before 7pm est for today's 2 NHL and NBA best bets.   Today's free sports pick… https://t.co/BCSIKGNNfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dickerson_97 Hahaha it does it’s own thing sometimes. Hope you guys are doing well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A manuscript, if it actually exists, is not testimony submitted under oath. #movealong]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand how a big Mr. Flanders mustache is considered “professional”. But a full nicely groomed bea… https://t.co/5zX1sM97xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Field Service Technician - https://t.co/XztQgKLFK4 #Manufacturing #IronCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsNom @IllegalScreens Trae is a better play maker than Luka so far 🤷🏻‍♂️ Luka does everything else better. I c… https://t.co/vyMpjg8Cxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was also ridic with Steve motherflippin Bono and Elvis Grbac. #realgoat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxANT @wyamercy @GrantDeters @metsygirl203 @ChrisLoesch @Newsweek Also, I'd hardly say middle America shuns Wal-Mart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fantastic few days!  FORZA SAP was talk of the town!  Limitless !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Socialist Pope is now sending talking points to our Bishops,  from our Bishops 2 our Priests!  YESTERDAY, I heard t… https://t.co/fJwsxTuRpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning with the kids. Hanging out in bed, watching Pokemon. https://t.co/kiCbD7NoP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeCarrollAZ May God bless her as richly as she has blessed me through knowing her story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Great Neck Senior Center in Great Neck, NY https://t.co/2szpwaJQ5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the The Nielsen Company (US), LLC team! See our latest #IT job openings, including "Software Engineer #32823",… https://t.co/Rhrpbn8mmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary time flies.... https://t.co/E3yWll3lz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way to get ready for an Army Ball is to go on an early morning run. Too easy! @USArmyWaco @ArmyWaco… https://t.co/hkbUb3pjxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEDTalks will watch while driving -&gt; don't worry -&gt; auto everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just so you know,  the media would much rather cover celebrity sex scandals   than politics   which requires more i… https://t.co/0QLVfy9gQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trekcatcatcat @ansonmount I like all three honesty but @ansonmount has just knocked it out of the park! https://t.co/q5cQ13U3xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socalfoodieguy @AzarDillon @TomiLahren @RandPaul "The Constitution that I interpret and apply is not living but...… https://t.co/scDKsk74fJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RLElam @bunnie1129 But sadly the terrible policies from it are still in place and very active.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I don't like Green Beer. I'm still your father. #AndThenITappedOut https://t.co/Nqx40zkbXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think once I get shit figured out I might take Spanish classes again. I have a buddy in Cuba I met online and I e… https://t.co/IZFBJ5OPA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stubbrighton @timloughton Because this is such a regular concern? I think the government has a lot more pressing c… https://t.co/KYqeqJ8ZlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamiyaMccary you gotta be dumb as hell to say what they’re saying, but recording it is another level of stupidity. they’re asking for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djohnstonuga @jeffdantzlertv tonight was like listening to John Williams music to Star Wars without watching the movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr Pelosi belongs in a home. She is also a liar worth millions and has a wall around her compound. Dem… https://t.co/M3W884CYfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met Carol Denvers, Captain Marvel, and showed her my support @ Disney California Adventure Park https://t.co/IZZcFJU9l9]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLIMATE AND WEATHER-- TODAY IT WAS 70 DEGREE`S AND SUNNY HERE IN LAS VEGAS = the south got slammed by tornado`s and… https://t.co/wgwgC97yYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[my hero's include: @AOC @jessdiggs @RhiannonGiddens @SpeakerPelosi @ellenlikesbikes @PattyJenks @rebeccarusch… https://t.co/k2dTsolkgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible that Lindsey “Lackey” Graham thinks anyone actually believes that garbage? What a hypocrite!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cavemanprod smh i delt w dat shit my whole childhood lmao in a black house u not allowed to feel any emotion BUT happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phoenix👍👍 #Arizona👍👍 #theholybible #Amen🙏  And it shall come to pass, that whosoever shall call on the name of the… https://t.co/1mmJNocw7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family and Good Friends...you don’t need much else in life! Thank you to these amazing people, @bobsaget… https://t.co/2dbkUO5DCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[G’night(hopefully) from the ‘hill. #wellleavethelightonforyou @ Springhill Medical Center https://t.co/iJlGJGZpCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Batusi_Hero I have loved Garbage sine 1996!  And, I really like Weezer as well.  I have varied tastes that sometim… https://t.co/pwIGY9XN8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP You’re Trump's puppet. At the Munich Intl Security meeting, you send greetings from our Dotard – it’s met with… https://t.co/u0KqW6TfrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bomar19 Packaging error? I'd think you could calibrate without it, honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTammyGillis @TaylerMccollum5 @SirenTV @ElinePowell @Fola_Evans @RenaOwen @gilbirmingham @Graeme_Duffy… https://t.co/AGhaCpEel0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch out for this one. Eyesore &amp; The Jinx  https://t.co/MW1hleDf4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mosaic Crush by @reubensbrews @ Casa de Wood — https://t.co/rjEH6rpVtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xdankmeister @rogerclark Yeah it definitely gives you a jolt for sure.  Way past the point of just waking you up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottthebowler i was unable to express my condolences at the time  i have no words for your loss  be strong man]]></document><document><![CDATA[unbreakable kimmy schmidt is now over and now i’m sad but it’s definitely one of my fave series on netflix of all time please watch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome!  But this is no surprise. It's because we are Hokies.  It's because #WeAreVirginiaTech.… https://t.co/0LyW2zn2nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows This guy is a idiot. If President Trump gets his emergency bill through he should declare marshal l… https://t.co/nZ4F8vg6J9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimarPerry  @JaydenHampton  the good ole days 😂😂 miss playing with y’all ✊🏾 https://t.co/uLawcmcl5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dunkin #drivethru was about to approach the drive thru speaker until I heard "Chew hush". I went straight home instead...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romans 9:17 For the Scripture says to Pharaoh: "I raised you up for this very purpose, that I might display My powe… https://t.co/JLh691rbAO]]></document></documents></author>