<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t decide which dress to buy for a wedding, so I decided on buying both. Someone stop me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwillfixit @dublinraspjam @gdcfpday @RedbrickDCU https://t.co/kZXmOpMlz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching children to fundraise hate should be considered child support and punished accordingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homewithnarry @HarrysFanGyrl I'm so sorry ,🙄 . Not really . 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just seem a commercial about self driving cars. They don’t work for ppl with dark skin as myself. Lol! So not onl… https://t.co/YsV6jLaA0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yupal29 @MohamedMOSalih @DaraTorres @JennieFinch @WVUIzzoBrown @alikrieger @sydneyleroux @KristieMewie… https://t.co/UzqBEmdVfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[where’s @jadejenius . Visual concept by @romeoholloway #jadejenius 場所: Hollywood https://t.co/Kl31l9nPLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best advice so far from #TSPRA19: If you're not happy in your job, do something else. Love what you're doing. The b… https://t.co/TeWTZjhvND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor you can't do things while I'm in Disney. My phone does not have the battery life for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/jLWubCeKA5 https://t.co/q4nb9x9Fzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another layer... #abstractart #abstractpainting #mixedmedia #mixedmediaart #acryliclayers #paintoncanvas… https://t.co/ybSEA2MUjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sales and my GM ♡ @ Hilton Orange County/Costa Mesa https://t.co/ZNAdehgvMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanShipnuck my ex-his is a USGA rules committee member. I think executive committee. I often traveled with him to… https://t.co/yf1uM6XnGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting to realize that I have a high quality threshold for historical dramas. Probably why I end up watching… https://t.co/BiyBDrH090]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amandatutorials @ABHcosmetics @norvina1 @amrezy @ColourPopCo @BenefitBeauty @BenefitUK @NyxCosmetics… https://t.co/NEfzYdpanB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo from Spring Ball Day 1.  I see you #4!!! #LetsFly ✈️⚡️🏈 @jmspiewak https://t.co/XIuK9PDgIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does @CNN still have reporters from @BuzzFeedNews on their panels?   Why @JohnKingCNN ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kensieallyn_ @IvyAlexuss @Madisonraine3 Yes. My aquatic science teacher in high school told me about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated @CodeTalker This is one deep abyss in which we find ourselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "RN Clinical Nurse I/Amb - Charlotte Medical Clinic - Allergy" at Atrium Health by a… https://t.co/SOcQ1TMSm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO Or...My sis was those kids, cleaning streams, picking trash, rescuing turtles by the age of 8...my parent… https://t.co/fTnNzMMPXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna get behind the Kimbrel train now. I think we actually need him. Let’s go #BravesCountry! #goBraves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysc0 I mean if you’re talking micro, I’m almost to 1,700 on IG. https://t.co/w6JDJgWLUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[johnnie walker released game of thrones whisky and oreo released game of thrones oreos and honestly thats all i need to live on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remi🐶💙 #boopmynose #greybeard #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #lovethemback #petsofcanidae #dogoftheday… https://t.co/B4lFjMFc0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#safarilive Hi Safarians! Finished watching the replay of the sunset drive and am very happy that our cute little P… https://t.co/X7pgJOcuOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimesSport @WelshMinor Like it or not.  Martina Hingis got booed off the court at French Open when she tried it]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you start something else, the idea gods will start firing heckling 💡 at you for what you intend to write.… https://t.co/Jev8jTKfyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely love this man lol amazing voice and falling in love! 😊 going to be covering this song of his here soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshGrahamRadio Beyond excited for you, and so jealous you get to have that first experience in Cameron!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like, I’m fairly good at multitasking but she seemed shocked I would not have been able to discern from context tha… https://t.co/Y0fKnunuMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beat the Brewer #omahabeerweek - Drinking a Robber's Cave Series Smokin' Coconut Caper by @blueblood_brew @ Sean O'… https://t.co/twCvqKZBN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andylassner @JudgeJeanine What a ridiculous comment.  Do you really hold an actual job? Oh wait - Ellen Show 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken Starr’s zealous pursuit of Bill Clinton baffles me, given his penchant for covering up sex acts that were FAR f… https://t.co/TtNfPrpdRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Thank you to everything who has supported @sole_girls by donating their used shoes. So far this week we have c… https://t.co/ujz8LCtCyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is charged with filing a false police report....publishable by up to 3 yrs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thread about #HigherEd #Disability #accessibility. @cedric_gathings @MarshalluPres @marshallu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes What does finding a straw in your garden have to do with socialism? Unless of course, you are expecting… https://t.co/dpPsvHEeHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @knomo, I want to love my laptop bag, but the handle has started to fray in under 9 months and it doesn’t actu… https://t.co/oHtAWrp7el]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleyteich Damn ok...but you won’t be when the time comes for you to write that check  👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panerabread I’ll do halfsies on a giant salad. With my friends who like salad  😎😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What happened to your love affair, your soul mate hahaha😂😂😂😂 Donald Trump, Kim Jong Un fail to str… https://t.co/POpVN2ESet]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you miss friends and really want to talk to them but their heads are so far up their own asses because they cl… https://t.co/VnkLBSbijG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ll be on a boat about three times this summer all in different places &amp; I’m so excited about the idea of it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefJosheola @StomperGouldie @PWGifs Owens wife Martha won’t let the @WWE induct #owenhart to the hall of fame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Abby Lowell, You lie with pigs (Trumps), you get all muddy. Except pigs(Trumps) enjoy it! #FireKushner https://t.co/vdTvs9YelV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls tell us what NJ's doing 2 reduce lung cancer, NJ's #1 cancer killer? #lcsm @NarjustDuma @ShereefElnahal @CDCgov… https://t.co/tgFandJv0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me during regional conference because it also falls on St. PATRICK'S DAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See @jannarden in her new Comedy coming to @CTV here is the first Epi. @ZoiePalmer plays her sister. https://t.co/kd4R7um3Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Hannah G said “i always make people better and then they don’t stick around”  I felt that on another level. https://t.co/H2imNGMtNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @_criminologist did you see this? Your study is big international news!  @Cambridge_Uni @CamCriminology]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IKEAtkinson @waflanagan I can agree that it’s great AAAND it’s dated. It’s definitely a period piece at this time.… https://t.co/PxmLr3LLla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuJunc @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump You’re correct about this and wouldn’t we all love it if we could go back to… https://t.co/eXnVadu50Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DimashIfied @lesleyc39651585 @Only_Dimash @dimash_official @WorldsBestCBS For an eternity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thsrenegadelove Fyi you can get in gel caps so you don’t have to taste it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump It is not debunked. We have the professional investigation still going on. I have no emp… https://t.co/cZJSPftaAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clandestinique Lol supermarkets carry stuff like foot fungus medicine and adult diapers. I'd only judge you if the beer is shitty :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Signoft40118032 I will be the best of me always keep you next to me #LouisTomlinson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenkerson_der @Adam_Morfeld Self-reported monitoring only works if there is adequate oversight, which unfortunately there isn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love your face. All of them.   #Delicate #BestMusicVideo #iHeartAwards @taylorswift13 https://t.co/Iqteyc9KIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrisaMandujano @Chiiiiiona Me, Doug, Yami and Cesar is trying vegetarian rn :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure these two were the only 2 KY fans there. https://t.co/Od5Ht7NBRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atchisonredmen soooo it’s gonna be -4 with a windchill of 15-25 below 0......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odysseuslahori That’s real mean but the best way to return in his case🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful for this beautiful Friday morning.  #morningcommute #StaStrong @ St. Francis Barracks https://t.co/YvpnsKXI1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@honeyburns @anothercc @DocGiani @sparcharge @heatfin1 @BrinsonEb @eGolf63 @SamOrtiz76 @Shye1Luv @doodldoo… https://t.co/uwBfhAZwwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just woke up to my prof canceling class AGAIN. Swear I’ve only seen this guy twice since the sem started.🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyWeaver21 That is what my mom said.  You never know I might like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we really even friends until you’ve made it into one of my password combinations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women's day!  Myself and the portrait of the great cellist @ofraharnoy one of the artists I had… https://t.co/aBlnfM2UyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything bad that happens in Kings Landing is Cerseis fault 😂😂  How can one person mess so much up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichJLaverty They even have changed the rules apparently to make that a dead certain pen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who revealed this to you? When one eyes are opened, love can sour. Kim sent you love letters too.… https://t.co/aAcJhszqo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do #saudi guys love to snap while driving? Most of my friends in/from #SaudiArabia snap looking out of the wind… https://t.co/dgc0tx2f1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you read a piece of literature that introduces (with such reason and sophistication) an all new position on re… https://t.co/e929QaoB0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanking our night #MET team for all their hard work on the seasonal sets #Recognition #D104 👏🏻👏🏻 https://t.co/lp8ZzS7QU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever just sat and thought about all the great people in your life. bc man i’m a blessed little booger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m that person coughing and sneezing on the plane. But it’s cool. I’m making lots of new friends.   🙄🤦🏼‍♀️😷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to be scooped in a PJ and taken to a private island -taking applications]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenDuckworth @EnvDefenseFund Thank you so much. At a time when there is so little to be proud of in our government… https://t.co/dukhbR98z1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un gusto enorme saludarte omarchaparro #nomanchesfrida2 @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/ttQ239qTCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @BacksweetBranch He really really want to be relevant really really bad. Damn Lindsey. https://t.co/gMGIAUR2io]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pissed because my car is a pos, but kinda happy because I now have an excuse to buy the truck I want]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall really like thinking yall r entitled to somebody else’s body and what they choose to do w it]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a @BowlingForSoup kinda Monday. #girlallthebadguyswant #almosthadyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just need to say I got all of the last five right on @MaskedSingerFOX so I win right? I guess T Pain from the first show literally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCSD_Trustees hearing many schools participating in Technology SLA (w/ outside companies) pilot per #AB469 have op… https://t.co/IvZGYEf38i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can y’all believe they made a whole museum based off a fake moon landing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lullaby_va @shopmygemstone @lullaby_va @shopmygemstone y’all please thank you 😊 @Kimberl38218406 y’all I have my f… https://t.co/w8fcaUzFeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The children of today are the annoying assholes cutting you off in traffic tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @maureenfox How cruel and juvenile! Hard to believe these are grown men charged with serious responsibilities!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Have no fear of perfection- you’ll never reach it.”  - Salvador Dalí  The Dalí Museum  + new #ReneMagritte Exhibit… https://t.co/3z3J6ScnUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the furry members of The Julie Kinnear Team - dogs and cats and even a horse are an important part of our fami… https://t.co/HYvOAoqIkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesfromCO Those days are long gone.  Sorry to say that, but it is the true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling up to Bucknell area and I honestly don’t know what I was thinking when I almost committed there...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎵 Baby's got back...🎵🎶  With....Lucille BALD👽🛸  #CloseEncountersOfTheNudeKind https://t.co/vb1THFBrX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnamacbabe I will soon as I get home lol 😂 you have a really long weekend 😃 not cool sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our project on “romantic cybersecurity” was even published there last year. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official! He’s officially a #mastermason #mastermasondegree @ Michigan https://t.co/81XIVLCtLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention @CampbellAPS teachers! Do it! Contact me! @msdrabyk @MrsSillKinder1 @MissBelber @Miss_McAleer @ms_croce… https://t.co/CxaB0q9kMX]]></document></documents></author>