<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JayMenardd I just listened again, you right af..lol &amp; he w/ his MOM nigga. I gotta find the whole thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyToobin @kate_littleton Better hurry before they build a wall to keep invaders from the South out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipTaylor16 No O-line in college or pro’s so far.  Murray had the best line in CFB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing photos! And if you don’t know who @simonstalenhag is, you must must must check out his art!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quests this is typical of FOX News these days. When they start to turn on Trump we will know we are getting closer… https://t.co/QTAWHsoYgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[A los cultores de la intervención Armada les debo preguntar, quién de ustedes está seguro de que no va a ser avasal… https://t.co/c8irAz7FmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWBChicago @JussieSmollett Excellent reporting! The Chicago Police Department played these guys like a fiddle... Bravo! #Jussie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champybeats @gotquestions Lol got questions I'm done I used to read them before I found out the church fathers were a thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776Stonewall The DNC lied, cheated and stole the nomination last election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeeeesssiiirrr!! Its an honor to be invited to the Under Armor Future 50 camp. Back to the lab!😈 #UAALLAMERICA https://t.co/RLAhnkOTKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering why @vincentcruzin was never highlighted in jump sections. Big boy throwing big stunts and well - big jum… https://t.co/3GctITeqGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like Obama, Clinton, and Bush. Such a terrible problem when presidents try to fix something congressmen won't agree… https://t.co/Kfmoyqyc2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fef219 Nah I'm too antisocial. I just blocked and reported his number. It was some Columbus number.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep watching this block over and over again.  Sooo good.  #GreekFreak https://t.co/IaqBU7SmSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread brings back so many memories. My mother used to produce educational videos and Apple loaned her a IIc f… https://t.co/AES0Mykz1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/EmNtOsAraQ happy #valentines day !! I hope. Everyone has a great #thursday @ West Kendall https://t.co/5UUb41obxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[when the younger kids don’t know about the music you listen to #SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the Lottery to win $30 tickets to #FreestyleLoveSupreme on @TodayTix! Enter here: https://t.co/erNOE3y9fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[mcdonald’s sells a lot of burgers but no one is calling them the pinnacle of taster an cuisine]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's gonna be a hot one out there today! A balmy -28°C this morning.   I may need to dig out the Banana Hammock wit… https://t.co/QH1bt88Zq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AOTD- Day 69- Incendiary- Thousand Mile Stare. In tribute to Aleister Black and Ricochet's amazing turn at… https://t.co/EBltL7KcCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Have you made a selection yet on your prison outfit YET? Did you ever think of staying in North Ko… https://t.co/us4o0y7eZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Shoshoni, WY? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/9EnPGytZ89 #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyShapiro13 “Michael always says K.I.S.S, keep it simple stupid. Great advice. Hurts my feelings every time” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Derek_Vasquez @RickPainter @prageru Basic government IDs are free. No charge.    No racism (not that there was any… https://t.co/ZTO3PNjD2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reem_theDream_ But if I’m completely sober 🤷🏿‍♂️ https://t.co/0ONyvBnorY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedclark A combustible #cigarette contains 250 harmful chemicals. Nearly 70 of these are carcinogenic. Suggesting… https://t.co/B3OkLhon4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/ggL1FTT7n2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what outfit to wear tonight. I think ima just buy something to wear BRAND NEW NINJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @gtconway3d "Listen to a Trump speech? I'd rather go to the theatre," said Lincoln]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 225 N 2ND ST #Allentown #PA  #realestate https://t.co/tzEh3vkv7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rasslinmrk @PWTorch It’s just sad that they misuse their call ups and fail to make new stars then dip so deeply in… https://t.co/FLZt0s5CQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Radcliffe @lvlightsfc @AustinBoldFC Very cool @Jeff_Radcliffe .  Do they still have those cool kits?  How can we listen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super catchy! #NowPlaying Motokano by Juliet. #jpop #dancepop https://t.co/Ro6FsUiAMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 153 Pine Tree Ln. #MyrtleBeach #SC  #realestate https://t.co/Suc0NB21fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen @BJBennettSports , people from Ohio literally will not speak the name of Michigan like the Wolverines are Vo… https://t.co/HBszdEmXpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigJohnDrummond  ain’t dat lil buddy who said he going for 300 rushing 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gehrig38 @Barbaradye921 That is their ploy..tell a bunch of crap and hope it sticks to the vulnerable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning good people. It ain't over. @ Gwinnett County, Georgia https://t.co/BeaeQSCDex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PROVOCATIVEWOM3 @mass_mistermv @maryjanesosexy @Bum_Bum_Sweet @Follow_mee18 @kosnude @Mierdafavorita @KrissyShamz… https://t.co/rKpAvYc2nB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy BDay to the homie and non local one_and_ownby — Some good times have been had brotha. Cheers to many more 🍻🤘🏽… https://t.co/QYr4Osqiq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t do Twitter on any other device than my phone. Does anyone else suffer from this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenLeo_1 I'd just continue to distance myself from her, even if you get caught lying. If she calls you out, ther… https://t.co/Siuy99QB2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi personaje   #pokémon #ResidentEvil   #Creditos @DraxS10 https://t.co/v0WwxZ5IxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @TIME Why do you think folks will be disappointed? Projecting?   Mueller's accomplishments thus fa… https://t.co/UNDm4K9B2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st Birthday eve #Bailey! #rescuedog @ Studio City, California https://t.co/WzGtPG0QHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check the link for Exclusive Presale Access + the chance to win FREE VIP TICKETS!: https://t.co/23fi9cdRgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Besitos De Fresa by @citybuilt at @shoprosablanca — https://t.co/EaDY7PRWpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGirlsAddict @KayleighCoxx84 @M_DelRay @TranSensual The most beautiful sexist woman in the world Kayleighcoxx.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@partimixx People looking in from outside: heart  Me, who knows what you’re really like: bee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 what are you going to do when you are traded to a team with a terrible qb that wins 4 games a year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EffinBirds @shelleridge @bigkstone @EffinSupport Haha thanks anyway but don’t mind supporting greatness with a few… https://t.co/ImNYDkavfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all, I finally landed an artist alley table at C2E2 next month. I am opening up my pre show commission list at… https://t.co/R8bc9U0NhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waylonlsmith @F3Alpha Where do you guys meet?  I don’t see you location on f3 nation yet. Have some sad clowns I want to connect out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't go one day without thinking of you Lisa I want you in my life more than anything.. you're always going to b… https://t.co/mzdYQmOS8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manuelrojasrod Salió a votar el gorpe,   porque le han dado hasta con cubo del agua.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man if that @gamestop Pro day leak is legit. That’s very underwhelming lol. All my tax money I got and not worth dr… https://t.co/b52Ht9NL1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgreeWitMe @Timcast Go look up what happened to Dan Rostenkowski?  I can ask you which state are you admitted to the bar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@at1simp @CjFraud @StealthPolrBear @thecjpearson @JussieSmollett @realDonaldTrump By all means. It was a dumb thing… https://t.co/VUL2vpddLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NYFW #NewYorkFashionWeek #Fashionable #nycStreetStyle #StreetFashion  #Fashion  #FashionWeek #NewYorkCity #NYC… https://t.co/4fNlyDIurL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesvarlack @mrsbcardenas @Flipgrid @googlearts I will definitely check these resources out! Thanks for sharing. #RGVEduChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesssss. Who comes up with these stickers? Fun find walking through the city last night. #yesssss #sticker #city… https://t.co/l2gamtTxsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimiuorio chemical engineering: because I wanted the American Dream - raise a family, save money, retire early. An… https://t.co/ikCAQ9WqNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting To Save 9/11 Victim Compensation Fund https://t.co/GZo78mAoNG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time recording for #Friendetta today with @QforQuijote and @ScarizardPlays!  If you want a shot at bein… https://t.co/YfWwrPExE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_wizzy5 I tried bro... I was like maybe I just haven’t had it in awhile so I got some and it was so un satisfying smh it’s weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama we all go to school Mama we all go to school I’m writing this essay Because learning is cool Mama we all go to school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@763brucem @nextlevelbb Placing in the zone. Most hitters have a hole in their swing. Gotta put it there on big pitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Eyes Like the Sky by @burialbeer @ Goat Island Bottle Shop — https://t.co/cTE2QLsxJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@folha @mafia_summers !!!  Não entendi! a saída do Bebiano não iria deixar a Ala militar Nervosa e fazer o… https://t.co/67qS5Cb0He]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howaboutafresca Who is the person more famous than Robert Kraft that people keep talking about that is worth more… https://t.co/XvfoaRyO8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our PTO sponsors a monthly bonus as well as gist cards for semester perfect attendance and also year-long perfect a… https://t.co/mLX0pORMiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alxp12000 It might have something to do with both Flint's mayor and Michigan's GOVERNOR being women and Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justiincarlin No but if you asked someone how old their baby was and they said 0; you would probably ask when the… https://t.co/MTUPO5UH6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett Smollett makes $100,000 per episode of Empire and there are 18 episodes in the current season which… https://t.co/PjklInAfpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t think it was possible to gentrify VHS but 2019 continues to deliver.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna get off work smoke and drink a beer it’s been a long as week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Raspberry Thunder by @MuskokaBrewery @ What's cookin — https://t.co/Q8wTovlWPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@littlebeastling @titlenine It broke my heart when the article suggested that well-endowed women try sports other t… https://t.co/MxVcjNDjwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenJustus3 Old rule if you had you only had 6 on the LOS you got a penalty. It’s now the same as college is my understanding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been through and I’m still going through some things I wouldn’t even wish upon my worst enemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niagara Falls USA has one of the most amazing 4-season tourist assets on Earth. Its an absolute shame that its one… https://t.co/f1VE965tEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guitar_picker55 @real_defender @realDonaldTrump A 2 year old on twitter? https://t.co/rPOUbSD0NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordy1975 ¡Muchísimas gracias, tocayo! Ahí vamos. Te mando un fuerte abrazo, amigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two brothers that died without collecting a dime of Social Security.  Who gets the money they paid in. The g… https://t.co/zzTXcLdZAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooooof.   Well. The dark knight led to The Dark Knight Rises and probably to the Snyder DC movie universe. But I’… https://t.co/nSPs1RX4ZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoceroPR ese problema no cambia..estos gobernadores no saben que cuando son elegidos son del pueblo completo no im… https://t.co/YodHSDnwDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kings in town. (@ Gila River Arena - @gilarivarena in Glendale, AZ) https://t.co/G5uoRHc9NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@septemberlaura @SXSWMF Follow these hashtags: #sxlines #sxnoms #sxdrinks #sxwin - also follow as many amazing SXSW… https://t.co/Oz8Xpr83U3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Song Spotlight February 25, 2019  Featured Songs For February 25, 2019 Henry Mancini - Baby Ele… https://t.co/fG3OmwRtCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andycauto Hi Andy, the game show got canceled for the weekend. But if you’re kicking around the autoshow i’ll be d… https://t.co/1eNYDPIhY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masked special police unit accused of killing over 200 in Venezuela https://t.co/MS3hWy2WFb via @MailOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: @KaceyMusgraves is so goddamn CUTE it hurts. I have a big fat crush on her and her music. Thank you and goodni… https://t.co/EFzey2nZrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean23Roberts @KXnOMorningRush @HeatherRadio @TravisCreates #23... LeBron?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dogwood Winter by @foambrewersvt @ Foam Brewers — https://t.co/8EZqGia2VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If imma cut u off why I gotta tell u bout it? I can cut u off and not say shit what u finna do bout it 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must know a thousand people who when Marie Harf comes on Fox News they turn the channel!!# hire someone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think 2k19 is a good game, your ass throw away your whole console]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allielabutis dont need a mom to yell at you for sleepin when u got allie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Homesicknovel @Carole77777 @DorisZelaya5 @RevLDReed @IsaaMobile1 @jlshine5 @careharrington @RichNChrist57… https://t.co/mvhLzVAxfO]]></document></documents></author>