<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Biff12345678910 @amy38797571 @troylaneroberts @politico Proof of Collusion is a fact based investigative book, and… https://t.co/qKL4OblX4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beta Club Induction Ceremony 2019 @ Sylva Bay Academy https://t.co/RJ3ZLsXQAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to a few years ago (1? Maybe 2?) when we all decided to bury my sister and abandoned her to the elements… https://t.co/f6RYg258Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Kylie Jenner is the youngest self-made billionaire, I just want to know who is the youngest “non self-made” billionaire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ughhhh Imma have to write a whole ass paper later today that I haven’t done research for :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: When asked if he will run for president in 2020, John Kasich responds “I don’t know” 🤷🏽‍♀️ #sxsw https://t.co/l0VFizUgfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paige “I was going to order the mushroom Swiss burger but I remembered I don’t like mushrooms or Swiss” 😂😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoopiGoldberg Praying healing for you! Miss you on @TheView Warm and Healing thoughts your way]]></document><document><![CDATA[What they (comically) refer to as a "Public Fact Finding" review for the shooting of Junior Lopez by the LVMPD is a… https://t.co/j4QVCw7n5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loves_TheLord2 Yes I know he was that is why Janet left like she did... I heard that when she took the baby this m… https://t.co/j3lgMHMZ7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel Jesus in this Denny’s tonight.  @__READYTOFLY__ @ahandmadeheaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it crazy that I don’t really care for school as much as I used to? Like I’ll get it done when I get it done but… https://t.co/zNe5AQedXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Did you read the Wikipedia entry I sent you? Did you read that Mussolini WAS a socialist party member b… https://t.co/dNayPwsHjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUNDAY BRUNCH SHOE CAM: Finally had an outfit to bring these beauties for @louboutinworld “Rainbow Naseeba Latte”… https://t.co/c9NaRaKwMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my1blood We went to donate blood as the Dr says that he has too many red blood cells. To my shock we are told that… https://t.co/eYl7XAkH2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think it’s funny when someone misses another person (not even romantically) but won’t try to contact them...like what]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s really freaks out here who just search xxx*****cion so they can talk shit to anyone who thinks he’s trash 😂… https://t.co/KMIkG67A7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNRTennessee @TheTNStar #tvasucks #dontdrinkthewater #itwillpoisonyou #shannonneedsanswers #shedoesntlookliketomhanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @wackyvorlon @iMikla @devoopes They came with resistors welded to one of the leads, so I'm good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs @AnnCoulter She and @MittRomney are Traitors to the @GOPChairwoman and to 63+Million Americans That… https://t.co/PughHu07YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way to end the regular season than heading into the Big Ten tournament with a W on senior day.  It’s a… https://t.co/lDwGqa0tXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn What you did was make an ass out of your self by quoting a vicious dictator. The socialism that is bein… https://t.co/Hj2WctV3o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told a little 4 year old my brother is coming home from college today because it’s spring break and he said,… https://t.co/uM8ZKDTMhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bisouuTK Damn, they took lane assist away from you too, Queen?! https://t.co/WlBvt2AJ8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonGovBrown The oath that all elected officials of Oregon must sign.  Therefore, any laws that subvert the 2nd… https://t.co/0y0qhaSvPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleShaniques #AMJoy You are so right, which is sad commentary on our country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Chubby cheeks are ALL the rage this month.  😁 @ Southborough, Massachusetts https://t.co/eiSLRfZbaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No you are not fighting for everyone! You are a liar and only about yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy You’re not alone. My friends who wanted trump are simiar to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero like... Can it be @Dodgers Baseball ⚾️ Season already? 🤓 #Modelo cómo yo! 🥳 https://t.co/WFMLh1Lj9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bluffed so fucking well with 3 high and then showed my hand 😭😭😭😭🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Josephlee1211 for winning third place in sports writing for @kspaonline regional contest! @phsboosterredux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monica Lewis completed the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! Time 03:05:24 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/TONcvEtGcq #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odettepeek Thanks for sharing Odette - I loved our conversation and so glad we could share it with others on my #podcast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not happy.  It’s another  example of the far left hijacking the Democratic Party. This will continue as they become… https://t.co/9NOV1lXz2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenTurieo @gordonkorman No More Dead Dogs was my first @gordonkorman book and I’ve been a fan ever since! I’m now… https://t.co/qGzzpFC9gO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webgirlmorgan @MarenMorris @hillaryborden @RadioAmy @RadioGirlMorgan @C_Buswell @jackieRADIO Love this! 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[#513goonsquad #justiceforgabby #LLG #13strong #forever13strong  #mentalhealtheducation #mentallyhealthyschools… https://t.co/IxhdqmuRpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confirmations! From JFKjr and Q MAJOR FF and Fires in CA https://t.co/z063cDqHbZ via @YouTube many many thanks to Q and POTUS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @realDonaldTrump After the collapse of The Vietnam Summit we heard crickets from him.  After he ca… https://t.co/X0VT5xGvuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my fellow Planning Commissioners and newly elected City of Indio Councilmember Waymond Fermon at the City of I… https://t.co/ntqxjwPGGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump U ain’t going to prison because of an Oxford comma bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PmTatertot @roxannelwright @Deccopainting @TheWestBlock @PierrePoilievre No, but he left a lot of messes to clean… https://t.co/BMRl2PApDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/CUNBBNjbx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you're tired when you climb into bed, lay down, and shut your eyes before realizing that your glasses are still on 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gcouros All-Time: Jordan &amp; Linsanity        Right Now: Steph Curry &amp; Jeremy “Linsanity” Lin (Don’t Judge Me)]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥Modified Pistol Squat💥 @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/mgOBBWh370]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProdigyRepV2 haha the only thing disgusting that day was the humidity, made me feel like a piggy too! Glad to see… https://t.co/334tVjEcfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaspar Someone send this dude “The Myth of the Vaginal Orgasm” and see how long it takes for his head to explode]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It didn’t cost you shit to believe in me” wow these niggas really don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the chatter about pg, the bench, and new folks in our roster - last nights game is an important reminder t… https://t.co/KBaJormmcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickKyrgios 😂😂😂Got to love em even do sometimes they gives out wrong news🤣🤣beside if they listen carefully what he… https://t.co/BdOEigpAbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @michrees for spearheading and @sbruyns @SACTVDSB for hosting! What a beautifully orchestrated harmony #MusiConTVDSB was! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MechaelaMariz HAHAHAHAHAHAHA SIGE SINO BA YAN TARA! 😂 Hype nanaman si mariz. Chill lang! 😂🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkempcpa Hoping that joke didn't come off wrong. I was suggesting that *of course* you understand what it's like t… https://t.co/HBAt90GXaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If trump paid I taxes he coud buy his piece of our history "trump wall"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DasFunnyStuff @lisajew62 @eugenegu @JeffreyGuterman @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Simple fix.... Remove YOURSELF… https://t.co/JdbsCDG6eN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @JimRobertsonQB to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, just the covers.… https://t.co/dtaYFYbgkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gondo Staff engaged in activities afterschool in a workshop series for Mastery Grading and Learning led by Adriana… https://t.co/BCLCrTARC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheddar always thinks he wants outside until I open the door and 10° weather hits him in the face]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF? He has to be high on something. Why can we all see this but the complicit GOP cannot or will not? Terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brimajr @IronicChthonic @FatherLefty @danielmarans @PaulBlu @AOC That is such a good point. I call that money well… https://t.co/akKH9SSxDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[OmniSci will be at #GreatLakesBI19 this Thursday in Detroit, MI. Stop by table 10 to learn how our GPU-accelerated… https://t.co/OzIN9q7GRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KP06108051 No. Wish. She will be ok tho. Glad it’s not the flu. She is asleep now. Been sleeping a lot🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LVNancy @pinkk9lover @realDonaldTrump @ElbertGuillory Please WATCH THIS VIDEO..]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA travelling alone doesnt mean someone is lonely, eating alone doesnt mean someone is lonely, being alone isnt a… https://t.co/3n7J5M7l25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton @DonaldJTrumpJr Yeah your right 2 years, 2 million dollars spent for nothing.  They haven’t found anyth… https://t.co/PbQhw12Y3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncmb2323 Wishing you a safe journey. I admire you for bringing awareness to such an important cause. Blessed be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inewsource - Thank you for your excellent investigative journalism.  The public has the right to know what their p… https://t.co/5M1Kqbott2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transcendentalism video projects build connections in the classroom. Students connect through music, arts, media, a… https://t.co/P41I9cq7j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad you had fun and will be coming back. Out by 10 should come with a warning label: Addictive. In a good way.… https://t.co/IyoBpC1cNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan He should pay for that out of his own pocket! People went without pay for food, rent, meds and he spe… https://t.co/c1MHRalC3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work with the best peeps in the world! Someone even got up early and brought donuts! 🤣😆   Thank you Ami, Susan an… https://t.co/zw0wBbEaBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so unprepared for how incredible this caption truly is until the end of the video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little Puppy Found With Mouth Taped Shut Thanks The Man Who Saved Him @Dodo https://t.co/kfwTTjFYaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing’s worse than being cozy in bed about to pass out listening to the rain.... having to take a piss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougDavidsonYR Better than forgetting to go. It's ok, it happens. I bet Kristoff is laughing his ass off. 🤗❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[went to Taco Bell tonight after a couple weeks of not going and the guy said “hey, it’s been awhile” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me caga que me desveló dos días y mi pinché reloj biológico se acostumbra.  Güeeeey que me de sueño a las 8:00pm as last months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poly_cyborg @LauraLogan0510 @maydaymindy9 Right. I usually don't say anything if it's in person. I just happen to… https://t.co/sLX1wExeDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t be answering my questions on here and that’s why I fucking hate y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Yes u are so stupid the joke is going to be on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it worth utilizing this platform when we hear every day that conservatives have been banned, had their followers… https://t.co/LUIgvzZwlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trojanchad I just paid $18 for 4 and that wasn’t even the most expensive! Crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is my best bet to find some small, inexpensive gold chains? Will a craft store have them?   It’s for final to… https://t.co/nCHqx0uHop]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom know this is true. #oldestisbest @ Gatlinburg, Tennessee https://t.co/kSlhCtX5Ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN Unless your are born in America you should not be able to hold any seat out three bra… https://t.co/wB3IlTBChv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing all the street art in Denver 🖼 #Denver #colorado #milehighcity https://t.co/iMBkNKlJNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[11:11 you make it feel like christmas music video cmt awards nomination. hey meant to be got one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big investors look past Khashoggi to opportunities in Saudi Arabia https://t.co/Xc1GNGaBKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[STERLING TRIED TO DO THIS ONE TIME AT SUNRISE BAKERY AND THEY GAVW HIM A SLICE OF CHEESE 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Oh you mean she shows the same hatred as Trump. Hummm, imagine that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/XBwe36ucB3]]></document><document><![CDATA['The Heiress Duet' by Nana Malone https://t.co/TrJEMq2fzZ via @MiaY2706]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millanpatterson widens the tent for the Republicans. She beat Travis Allen and Steve Frank.  It shows improvement,… https://t.co/yV8p2ppvTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ground turkey taco salads for the week for lunch!  Already made breakfast sandwiches and froze them as well! https://t.co/E7GNeiFLnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The SEED OF SHARIA.      Ilhan Omar’s District Shown By FBI Data As Terrorist Recruitment Capital Of The U.S. - Dav… https://t.co/BJKBNXUpWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta He's hitting the Trump campaign trail  So technically he's still with the white house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelMemes9 He can do whatever he wants to me🤷🏼‍♀️ come to me sweet Mischievous God 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re acting like your family wasn’t already broken up before that 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>