<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@zionshoe1 @DukeNBA I think that’s been a take away in college basketball the last couple years especially from the… https://t.co/MvrPVue4gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go through the truth behind your pathetic ass poor me story shall we? 1.) wants to get pregnant on purpose by… https://t.co/ps70kdwxey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday @JoeRado_ 🎉 Love you, hope you’ve had a great day and felt all the love you spread sent back to you❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmyrossum @realDonaldTrump I know Emmy, this coming from the biggest pathological lying con man who for years was… https://t.co/Q0HQm8F3SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby shower is in a week which means my little girly will be here in about 6 short weeks!! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannykanell @AdamSchefter @PFTCommenter @BarstoolBigCat How do you know @BarstoolBigCat @PFTCommenter are not ther… https://t.co/cw54Rb0Hjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s actually been a really blah day. Trying to process all of my emotions and feelings has me just completely blan… https://t.co/GQy9vmzH53]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hairbystephmm #someseriousfoils #cqsalon #lajolla #villa2000 #norcal #goldwell #schwarzkopfusa  #movie #classic https://t.co/DvWWogjp1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amnesiacglaive @Greytothebone Pffft like I'm afraid to get arrested for something innocent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call for abstracts for EAS at AAA 2019 in Vancouver. Submit your session abstracts to bscelza@gmail.com by March 15. #EAS2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHOGossip Dorit is the one who made poor choices.  Two dogs?  Both taken back?  She should never have a pet again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FAKENationalEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar I need help Bryan I don’t know where this will post but I got myself in the wrong menu so i don’t know… https://t.co/7ebZDOPk7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Don’t be so generous, it’s bigotry and racism motivating all Repugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooo i’m obsessed with solange already and she has an aquarius moon. im going to try to marry her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @BennieGThompson Yes it is a problem, how about giving work visas to these asylum-seekers. Trade deficit… https://t.co/BImbgZdKiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still laughing &amp; getting in trouble like we’re back in grade school! Forever fun with these girls! 😊💜 https://t.co/qBZyMkTxh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhall_viola More importantly, young students love VIOLA! Way to spread the word 👌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Santiago_9999 @TruthSeekTeller @fekerksa_en It hurts everybody but them. They were educated by the wrong IMAM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Saginaw, MI? View our latest opening: https://t.co/CcXsg3X9Lb #SocialSciences]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saturdaysun2009 @DeplorablAnnJoy @OleMuzzy @JamieJALFT I don't need a Sunday school lecture from someone who can't… https://t.co/L9JIXnEBO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all I’m 121 &amp; im a 5’5 freshman in college. Relax with the description ma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmcguire56 Planned Parenthood is an essential health care provider for many low-income women. It’s unfortunate… https://t.co/0U5q9QghUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@achievethecore Be curious Love learning Practice empathy #candyheartchallenge  #CoreAdvocates]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chewy wishes everyone a hot and spicy Valentines Day! 💗🔥 #hotandspicy #valentines #valentinesday #shihtzu @ Hillsbo… https://t.co/kcHMDc67Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all don't even know how lucky I am to have this queen as one of my best friends! What a beaut 😊🙏🏻💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think I’ll start taking theraflu sore throat just to be on the safe side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just out of curiosity, when do boys start taking dating seriously???? Or like, actually commit???? Asking for a fri… https://t.co/ij0kxH2Tr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expert traveler level 5: able to accommodate clothes for 2 adults for a 2 week vacation in ONE carry on!!! Bye bye snow!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[... but on my own behalf I will not boast, except of my weaknesses— though if I should wish to boast, I would not b… https://t.co/8hElJzETAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weedouthate @JohnWDean Typical narcissist behavior, difference with trump is the power of presidency to harm milli… https://t.co/gk36NyvMMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raeganpellant @haleyearsley @norvina1 @jamescharles @JeffreeStar If she's so great she shouldn't ruin it by leachi… https://t.co/spou512T0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markilynncupp I’ll let you know if this gets played on the jumbo screen 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulWhiteleyPhD As someone in the midst of this community I can tell u that the majority of ASD couples who want t… https://t.co/vGEntml5rP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoogsterSU2 @funder And make a referral to Adult Protective Services for a welfare check on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING EVERYONE:  rise up4righteousness... https://t.co/nOjLyDKPCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are always the priority. This means then that you will always have something to bring to the table. If people c… https://t.co/5UNqPPDPyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwuuc #RWUPresident is announced. Welcome to Dr. Ioannis Miaoulis!!!  https://t.co/odXjiBKh77]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to get back outside for a walk/run. #recouptimebefore5knextmonth @ Buffalo, West Virginia https://t.co/QEUDn5WgHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraciFisher1 @Nike I am shocked! I have only returned on pair of shoes in my life- Kids LeBrons because of a fault… https://t.co/cNDM1z2Nvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Tiger basketball 🏀🏀🏀 entertaining, scrappy , supportive of each other, awesome teamwork, each player is unself… https://t.co/wM3hWscEbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @MikePerryavatar And every single one of them must be voted OUT.  Vote for @TheDemocrats in 2020.  We took… https://t.co/QCAW0lDviA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larakate @taylordelo We will be holding office hours staring next week in the lodge on 5.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfgwinning @MoRomansSID @HannahBradleyCU @nsminnich @nicoleleighty00 @DannyKambel I’m in that boat this year and i… https://t.co/ksZDcFELSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making our way back home, and already reminiscing about the incredible opportunity I’ve had to visit New York for m… https://t.co/cOC20Me3i0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BugamiBojang @ScottRHan @Johnny_Abruzzo @tuffsies @AOC Not one of the democratic presidential candidates has menti… https://t.co/PyE0e2ZPsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHS_VHockey defeats @LivCHSHockey 5-0 @MichHSHockey @MiHockeyNow @Churchillgames]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tatum_Hawk @jgkragt @MarkTheOverseer @MissJennifer116 @Timcast It’s gremmar, you idiot. #DUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kim She is horrid. I can’t believe she was elected. It is embarrassing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth!🙌🏻❤️🙌🏻#godsplan #godstiming #patience #spirituality @ Novi, Michigan https://t.co/4kmXNPGv5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂Obama has no plans to endorse a Democratic presidential candidate for the 2020 primary, report says https://t.co/npRhH87VSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[He picked a girl who wouldn’t say she loved him over one who was already in love with him and he wants to act surpr… https://t.co/McrEbctv8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat Don’t ever apologize for your face; loving yourself is the greatest strength.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelsCumber @ElenneMigo @yellowbelle @DestiniLozano @Lanasanette @marykk196051 @JazzmaCumberful @JilldarWu… https://t.co/lxxfsBf9aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 5 MTV Cast Members for THE CHALLENGE https://t.co/eFuVJhDNr2 via @YouTube  Bahahaha I love you so much… https://t.co/poGCBtKZSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDXToddDiskin Mostly chocolate, sometimes cheez-its, usually a box of Honey Nut Cheerios.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kanswercity @embea22 @RealSaavedra Amen, Ronnie Raygun was a dirty word in my house growing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jettheadpb @RepAdamSchiff @jaketapper I want to see all these politicians that became millionaires while working f… https://t.co/Bn4Ur3ZVlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Voices In My Head/Stick To The Plan by @BigSean on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/tQpVRsVGk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning awesome.😍  #HighSchoolStudentsInspire @MDCPS @MDCPSSocStudies @Jason23Allen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @doccrimson anyone who calls themself eminem  already has one major problem   They are stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently I missed a hell of a play... but my hair smells my orange and mint now, so there's that.  🛀🍊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably not the best move to cut mostly all the good bits from 'A Discovery of Witches' in that @AMC_TV preview tr… https://t.co/WO6ft9YPoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Market watch. February 2019. @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/qYFQQISJL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siriusxmvolume @JimShearer @goodymade @SIRIUSXM Violet by Hole &amp; The Gold Medal by The Donnas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie is pointing fingers as to why Hillary didn’t win, he should reflect on his actions or his lack of genuine su… https://t.co/7pHBG8Nur5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life saving liquid❤️ Have a heart save a life🙏🏽 Valentine’s Day drive @SmithsonValley HS Super easy way to save liv… https://t.co/7Z6xACaQzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriMoreno @TracyPereira20 @jillianne_gray @Fiery01Red @TheSavvyChef1 @Julianna_glass @DivaVinophile… https://t.co/runNgJ6PFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirpoovey @CagedWisdom @twtmpodcast Wait a minute. You’re doing this and not taking me or @brandon_mullis with you… https://t.co/qp67NPC8Y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @UAPhxIM and @kristenyoung and Dr. Emily Mallin for this important high value project. Past winner of t… https://t.co/TOEcuAX2j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chidimma_rita @queennnv_ Y’all do know NOLA is driving distance from HTX 😘😊🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being this talented. Perhaps @theacesofficial snapped https://t.co/E44K31iRD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am so tired of spending 40 hours a week at a job that barely pays my rent. what is it like to have money for groceries or essentials]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard someone who works here say “genital herpes” loudly then the response was “Oh god!!!” Fuckin VA you always surprise me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A key to any US/China trade deal that addresses structural issues (IP theft, technology transfers, etc) will be how… https://t.co/b0t23ytPzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like my best friends, i have to make all the effort. But when were together its great. Or like when she told me the… https://t.co/oQ7WW8FO8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[US intelligence officials believe that King Salman has been kept apart from his wife Princess Fahda bint Falah Al H… https://t.co/Ts8MXJxFSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF Friends! My pen and ink seahorse illustration is available on notecards and coffee mugs! . 🎨 visit my @etsy sh… https://t.co/BYYlHpHLJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_djrocklee Yes, we can certainly help you in developing your dream app. Please see our PF: https://t.co/VwprlzJ6qa… https://t.co/BidimpLnyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing my @ConsumersEnergy coworkers supporting their communities and walking for warmth today!!! #CEvolunteers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff @56ocelot I beginning to think Trump is untouchable. He spits on the constitution daily and all we get… https://t.co/ETw3u7min9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lifespan teacher is so cute, shes a lil hippie with long blondish/grayish hair and she’s so chill and down to Ea… https://t.co/WCnGVUOH6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[brandon really got me macadelic on vinyl, the most thought out gift i could’ve ever gotten 😭🙏🏻♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're here! The first autonomous vehicles in Sacramento are officially rolling on the Sac State campus! @SACOG… https://t.co/AFJLCA2vXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleClark “Uh oh - surely that kinda horrible luck can’t happen twice.”  (To my BFF about a new boss, hopefully not being terrabad.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thread is just him being a narcissist psychopath and I mean that in its whole hearted textbook definition; I tr… https://t.co/edE0d5w82v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauleyP So happy to hear your family is safe, but very sad for those affected &amp; those who lost their lives🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her: Were you ever tempted to quit [being public] when you were dealing with all these opinions, or did your mentor… https://t.co/T1H0BWwuP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TatianaMoylan @AnitaKnopov @doctorORbust @UpToDate , @mdcalc , PediStat, @EMRA_Education / @emresidents has a bunc… https://t.co/kfnxbqoBeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: a star is born was mediocre at best, the weakest film out of all of the ones nominated tonight a… https://t.co/sF1gQ8xQ6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying for #peaceofjerusalem If we have peace in Jerusalem we’ll have peace in many places.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a #BestLesson: @HenryLouisGates makes half the class defend Booker T. Washington and the other half of the c… https://t.co/BikXsswmz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never seen a group of people bond more than mall employees who want to close stores early and go home]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyladina This pictureeee thoughhhhhh... I mean...wowww. https://t.co/BgwKcoCV6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[No @seanhannity - he won't! Another FAILED campaign promise... #Wall #Coal #Deficit #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me waiting for something exiting to happen in my life so I can tweet about it instead of just retweeting @halsey https://t.co/z4AkUBX9dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a sign that said “road work ahead” today. All I could think was “Yeah, I sure hope it does!”   I’m not okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yxcr_ Lol. People say he wasn’t shit from the beginning. You get what you ask for, so if you know he trash and he… https://t.co/uOMFKI93yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought my AirPod case and my airpods arent even in it, day starting off well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I asked for a Russian cold-weather hat from Eddie but I decided I'd buy a German cold-weather hat instead.]]></document></documents></author>