<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Disappointed that covering your ears with a pillow doesn’t work nearly as well as I’d like it to. Also disappointed… https://t.co/m0KNJf80iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's burst out laughing a bit. Robin, thank you for being a big part of my childhood. RIP. #hilarity #chuckle… https://t.co/EHlGEssCBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edgar Allen Poe: Nevermore. Dolly Parton: Yes, because the horror fears us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelATC @archivalistic @QuinceMountain @Way2gosassy @JamesFrye @GMTminus7 My recent professional phone photo con… https://t.co/AaHpClvwa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the person who left #paczki in the break room this morning! #FatTuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not saying our wedding is Legend of Zelda-themed, I’m just saying there might be a couple Zelda things to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uyyyy No!. ¿Donde están las autoridades ambientales?,deberían hacer un día sin buses de TRANSMILENIOS🤦🏻‍♀️🚒]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the great pleasure of meeting the #beautiful @sydwilder at @bwwings #meetngreet @ Bridgeport, Connecticut https://t.co/h8lONmfaY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your the collusion mr Trump and your fake news as well if it looks like a Duck quacks like a Duck  it’s a Duck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Add compassionate to smart. Because who wants to be around anyone with such a small heart that they do… https://t.co/UToOtDa207]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Penske @DISupdates @keselowski @MillerLite Did you have any Miller Lites?😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[dear customers at walmart, pls don’t yell at me i’m sensitive and will go to the bathroom to cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggha kiss ya queen first and then dap you , he don’t respect you or ya relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Jesse1Sandoval @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump En Venezuela no hay ni nunca ha existido un socialismo bajo esta Dicta… https://t.co/dy5hgvt9CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun time seeing @cncomusic!! ❤️🎶 https://t.co/hAiv62fOnt @christophervele @ErickBrianColon @itsjoelpimentel… https://t.co/RR9Rkatx4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gutter U.K. media needs to take many seats, on the ledge of a cliff would be my choice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @CFCurriculum to post 7 covers of nonfiction books I love: No explanations, no revie… https://t.co/c7QZ1BJs8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danjlevy @EmilyHampshire_ @annefrances @olreid @SchittsCreek Tonight @BeaconTheatre was Pure Joy!! We all need mor… https://t.co/WPUZNSErpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The negative narrative surrounding the DoS was started by the U.K. gutter media and most end with them.  Obviously… https://t.co/ua6zHjRfS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I discovered her music in the 90’s and have bought all her albums since.  Glad she is finally getting some recognit… https://t.co/A1PtojTqqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[April Culley started the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! https://t.co/CLTvhyA2mx #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asketchyfish Parking restrictions are suspended starting at 4! Slightly less of a mess?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConanSalaryman I like these coworkers of yours! https://t.co/CyaCR0Rute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TooBexy4MyShirt How????? They have cancelled so many times this semester? We’ve literally had 5 days off in 5 weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millbrookmagnet HS staff members were judges in @MillbrookCTE #CupcakeWars @SO0ver @MrsCTChance @WCPSS @WCPSSTeam… https://t.co/hE9uy1E4oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you want universal healthcare which is a politician determining the best course of care. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Valentine's Day, let’s spread love and kindness as much as you can. V-day! https://t.co/t5ZigWGvLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so much opportunity for an advisor to make a positive impact incl making sure both can explain their wealth… https://t.co/eB2LLEzGOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraK93322487 This is a travesty. Look at that sweet smiling face all eater to please and give love. How could t… https://t.co/m8GzVonYUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvnewinfo @NCGigiH @chuckclj @Peaceinourtime8 @TRC @jonz970 @rdrhwke @wwwillstand @JjRedWave1 @garway95 @JVER1… https://t.co/5jU7lIcXrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we here already??!! @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 Asking for a friend 💋 #TS7 is coming!!! 💞💞💞 https://t.co/BRTHsCJykG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an inspiration is poet Lucille Clifton #poet #poetry #Inspiration #gratitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be in this weird space of not knowing whether God is telling me to leap or that I need to go in a different direction . But I get it now .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AslMewes Yes, I made the pattern based on Adam Savage’s model, and cross stitched it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offered on the sensible house option.  Bidding war.  We won.  Secretly pining for the crazy house option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PaulDouglasHale  Worked As A #InfectiousDiseased #EmergencyMedicalTechnician in #Atlanta  And Hosts #CDC-… https://t.co/A59VNn9gcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Ten victories in a row. @StLouisBlues are so hot the ice is gonna melt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to our friends @Chilis for donating lunch for all our golfers and crew for the @FrankCrumPEO Invitational… https://t.co/OOxdWoFwvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how when someone’s character finally comes out, we say...they’ve changed!  No, this is not true.   Their… https://t.co/2tEJuJh6Bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men #love #diamonds too! Don't let them tell you anything different. You can #prove it when you pick this up st our… https://t.co/OkCehtk7cM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 208 Oostanali Way #Loudon #TN  #realestate https://t.co/CrjCwGl9N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silverclaw16 @FLOTUS @GOPChairwoman @WhiteHouse https://t.co/I24A45hQ88]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Overnight Blues by @FoDoBrewing @ Rams Head Dockside — https://t.co/GO70dzXqJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being mad isn’t how I wanted to end this day.. it was such a great day and now I’m mad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OverlordViper @admitonefilmadd @FivelFox @SammyHain @BrianIsSuperRad @IdiotAtPlay @TheNerdyPumpkin @HauntedDriveIn… https://t.co/922noknAJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdog73 @truthfully24 @AP @amazon @nycgov Check out Virginia found a way to take care of both the local needs and A… https://t.co/kK4duVYgQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud momma moment today ❤️  #daughter #mother #motherdaughter #school #rosedesvents #speaker #podium @ École éléme… https://t.co/QowwIyO36R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamilton!!! @ Straz Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/ftwCg2Pt5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who exist in nyc without drinking some form of caffeine daily are a different type of people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl fighting brain tumor receives more than 50,000 letters from dogs around the world | https://t.co/4gFp6cG7p1 https://t.co/s6cGwCRlkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDevinK @Four_Pins Go figure, America is not as great as it used to be. We'll be back to greatness after the next election. #POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadiL_ You don’t want drama but you’re trying to cheat on somebody you live with. Boys are so messy 😂😂😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThreeColumnsArt All the evidence wasn’t presented. It was one-sided.   https://t.co/hU2UwDPyln]]></document><document><![CDATA[DECADES of research demonstrates that outcomes for ALL kids, disabled AND their typically developing peers improves… https://t.co/aftNjdrgj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter @DiviResorts' 6-Night Caribbean Family Vacation #giveaway for a chance to win a magical stay to Divi Little B… https://t.co/iPoWDEQnnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicBergerIV @dbongino @DLoesch @OliverLNorth @NRA @NRATV https://t.co/9iasFq1LZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plants, plants, and moar plants 🌱 #plantsofinstagram @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/VY5BMX4REb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP4Liberty I love you, man. But...  *puts on fashion police badge*  Brown leather and black kydex? Really? Did you… https://t.co/HerX0o9AUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleuthacademy @browardschools @reimagine_bcps @danielgohl @Russ_Schwartz @principalkp @Science4UsSays… https://t.co/z0D9OUKGz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pastor friend once told me it was sometimes Godly to say no, because you can’t be useful if you’re exhausted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostAIO @stroworId @NMC_Sneaks @Looperang @Ribcagee @won_0925 @nagisa02]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a just breathe bag in my classroom. A ziplock bag with a silk flower and a birthday candle. I’ve taught them… https://t.co/SRBM7fSTkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[my optometrist knows i'm an anxious wreck so when he picked up the phone i said "hi" and he was like "young lady i… https://t.co/AZD8XIhTXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zether @ArktinenJenkki @ruetenik Holy crap, I’m so sorry about that. I’m actually glad you shared this story, perspective...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @AnnCoulter She likes to hear herself Rant! Tell her no one is listening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman MARK I READ SHE WASN'T QUALIFIED TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT BC HER PARENTS IIVED HERE ONLY 5 YEARS WHEN SHE… https://t.co/C7HOPwa5kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick12865787 @SunandSipCups @JadedDragonMMA @gunav8r64d @AOC From a Russian troll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how you got your shit together @_DomoWilson1 but mad respect for you. I recently lost my great grandmo… https://t.co/aEFmmrUbe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[H.I.V. Is Reported Cured in a Second Patient, a Milestone in the Global AIDS Epidemic https://t.co/PyDrqVw8Tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think after all the women I’ve dated, I’d be use to the attitudes/tantrums. Nope, still surprised every time. 😭😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannynAlyssa was working at MGM on Friday and they opened the pool and it hailed LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Koji262 You are a good father! I feel YOU  will teach her well! Teach your children well! Crosby,Stills,Nash&amp; Young. A truth  song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@00Hex Thank you!  I’m hoping the meds and the inhaler will do the trick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I occasionally drink spiced rum with Pepsi made with stevia and cane sugar. Usually it’s just a cola with Splenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe how this Mother held her cool...yikes Id be in jail if some skaterMAN talked to my 14yr old that way… https://t.co/iq6aT0s1O6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaVogt5 @SpockResists @TwitterSupport @StormResist @KassandraSeven @porpentina2017 @TrisResists… https://t.co/sqxzEtqaH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fletcher Class of 2019 #Wrestling, #Football, #Track #CollegeBoundWrestler #futureteacher #Future #Coach… https://t.co/1HfU6IjHc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got you worrying bout me like my mom worries when I don’t answer her calls..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @sar_oso Little Putin looks like a dog when he surrenders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of that time I thought he was waving at me at the store. 🤣 To be fair, I’d just worked an early mor… https://t.co/x0SZv1GteG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like those Balenciagas, the ones that look like socks #missjustineenyc @ Public Hotels https://t.co/W1mlPvyh1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping my future shines as bright as all these random lights that are placed so close to each other ☀️🌟 https://t.co/5cUT1OAJwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your waiting for your car to finish and literally baking because the sun came out to play]]></document><document><![CDATA[We appreciate your #dissertation Kate. Thanks for dropping by #AXSChat. We are here each Tuesday at this time and p… https://t.co/SmqspXPuN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internships in publicly engaged settings! Check out this year’s opportunities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👊🏼 Get up, Thrive, Do work! 👊🏼 #bebetter #dobetter #bemore #accomplishmore #work #dowork #werk #betterme #me… https://t.co/DGiymwvX3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleSamsChild No wonder our students bully if the teacher is an INTOLERANT BULLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWinChat Congrats on your first chat, I had a great time 💕💖💕 #WINChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alguien despiérteme mañana diciendo que fue broma y está afuera esperándome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thinking entry hall or possibly dining room hmmmm #french #chest #lamps #diningroom #hall #fashiononashoestring… https://t.co/Pge1IDAmar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench @netflix Oh man, it's so good! Philosophical and funny and moving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving our @projectcure partnership with Walk Strong Foundation, &amp; their $12,500 commitment to delivering… https://t.co/Q2lm04lM1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockyko1 There’s this looser on here throwing shit at someone when they are down &amp; out..not herself...I'd love to personally find him..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitlinCurtice I still don’t know. I only JUST figured out what a subtweet is—though I’m pretty sure I still would… https://t.co/PiCSmgnd5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class B: Roncalli has cut it to three, 54-51, with 6:35 left. #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FJrean @PlayChoices They implied that he died. Haven’t seen him the whole book except in flashbacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn more about our life changing products here https://t.co/rzFyglOlJl #healthy #SaturdayVibes #2019goals #health https://t.co/FLAtxL7tfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pig is a lying bigot, not Jewish, and really really hates Jews https://t.co/8r2fv5W8LQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @TereOrt51687394 @janaplauen @roberta_lanzoni @zetakaty… https://t.co/2OHuy3uP7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[life gets a whole lot easier when you learn to stop stressing over the things you can’t control.]]></document></documents></author>