<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[just drank a whole bottle of wine. dare me to not talk to my cat about all of my problems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferlegge86 @JussieSmollett What...no comments. Your buddy is in jail! Love this stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Is Inciting Violence Against Abortion Clinics https://t.co/rNHjVnu3B2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marceelias Always remember, @NCGOP @MarkHarrisNC9 is and was a Southern Baptist Preacher when he supported @GOP Vi… https://t.co/Ehs1x1GlBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tarot day 79: I had a positive though not specific reaction to this card. It looks like rain or a meteor shower. P… https://t.co/jZH2qa4UaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss gave me coupons for the hardware store but I forgot them at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nephew, his wife and their group @TheCrescentSky made it into the top 100 of @CBC Searchlight contest. Have a li… https://t.co/lEXhLxXBtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the meantime, I will focus on strengthening the connections I have with ppl who mutually follow me. I only want… https://t.co/FdD1CJ06Ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylortholen @fortbball @UnionHSHoops We could all still be together, but you playing too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confession: I’m a parent who freaked out about Momo. Kids in my son’s first-grade class were Googling it and scarin… https://t.co/WPtxgQZGRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porn is gone from Tumblr, but here are the best alternative sites https://t.co/92EcCvXsiw via @dailydot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyElisaG @jfc_3_ @patrick_oshag @ROIChristie @morganhousel @david_perell @EricBalchunas https://t.co/4VQLWH6vlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reeighan Just being outside more and just more active outside of job/school]]></document><document><![CDATA[#burtonusopen2019 #vail #vailcolorado burtonusopen2019fans @burtongirls #snowboarding @ Burton U.S. Open Snowboardi… https://t.co/yiooz3ZvjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNOWwayVEGAS! Blizzard,how will we survive! @ Seven Hills, Henderson https://t.co/mMU2avUnJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[AAA discovers benefits of @Salesforce @ServiceCloud  https://t.co/cJarpfTIPE via @srchsalesforce]]></document><document><![CDATA[When deciding on #technology, sometimes you are better off with a product that's 9.5/10 vs a 10/10. Being the lates… https://t.co/1lmldpKL5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou They are not scared and no how to spin it to their base...look what Happened in Bill Clinton's impeachme… https://t.co/SQ0R9gQtjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHemmer just said he back packed from Saigon to Hanoi 25 years ago. 50 years ago he’d been carrying another bac… https://t.co/vbbtVTCJxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow this lady dropped her sons hat on the train seat and a man grabbed it ran off the train gave it to her and got… https://t.co/I1wh0vo7wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old news from 2015, but still cool: Elon Musk named SpaceX’s drone ships after spaceships in Iain M. Banks’ novels.… https://t.co/6m2qw1srZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why has Andrew MCCabe not been charged? He was dismissed for lying under oath at a minimum of 3 times! Why is he no… https://t.co/caHf5wxBIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fooditor mine was sadly stolen out of my car in Oakland 2 years back. RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jack in the Box - @jackbox in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/Wp1tOo1EhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichealKeith10 @steph93065 Seems these children are better off without such awful parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipRucker Trump never thinks the leader of a country is responsible for anything. This SYE from his belief he h… https://t.co/sWNRPUXeca]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Better NORFOLK 2020, please stay tuned. This is a PAC that will seek ways to empower citizens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Black Panther or The Ballad of Buster Scruggs win any Oscar's, I will lose faith in humanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Que orgullo mi Universidad y sus estudiantes! 💪🏻🇳🇮 También por ustedes estamos aquí luchando y les agradecemos su… https://t.co/gzvxNxAldX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s World Glaucoma Week!!  A reminder to get your eyes checked for the “silent thief of vision.”  Glaucoma can be… https://t.co/1oi6JnOUkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@varneykgrn Completely agree. But thank you for your support and coverage all year Mr. Varney. Really appreciate it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been wanting the 17” model to return ever since they stopped making it, so of course they’d make one right aft… https://t.co/YzcasQsXLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now more than ever, you need to read Viktor Frankl. https://t.co/S8p5wUMhw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancymck1211 @Kokomothegreat Unbelievable and u wonder what is wrong with this country those people has had ignora… https://t.co/M6D9UlRQWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry dad, it’s our couch. No idea where I’m going to sit today.   #lazysaturday #couchdogs #dogsofinstagram… https://t.co/gXMt5hiPPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CPAC Darling, is the wind blowing today? I would like to watch TV. Classic Trump mocking the new green deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseDresserG Te falta tomar tus pastillas para la idiotez, a no, tu eres idiota de nacimiento. Me pregunto porqu… https://t.co/j18Tqa2SeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Concrete Jungle” New York sour https://t.co/SnKv1j6KSN. Thanks Branden!  #dranks #whiskeysour #newyorksour… https://t.co/odwUPZHpjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanover’s White has a tall act to follow: His NBA veteran dad https://t.co/L0gBQKtHHu via @VNewsUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look back at the @Vol_Baseball / @IndianaBase, trying to keep the records straight. https://t.co/inknSEXDgO @SeanBarows]]></document><document><![CDATA[See the story where the numbers of Domestic Terrorism Threats  outnumber the threats from Islamists?  Report indica… https://t.co/xKye7oUpLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amazing minds of our University Relations staff allowed me to play with this new toy today...the 360.  Thank yo… https://t.co/XznZLSp1T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst thing you can do is lie to a SINGLE MOTHER!!!! all these hoes out here including some of the bitches you were… https://t.co/A3ni9hjKhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather @SpeakerPelosi If there is a criminal in the White House, everyone who doesn’t try to remove him as quic… https://t.co/0buiPNVSpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think they should back the teams up instead of bringing them closer to the goal line. In the 5th overtime, you st… https://t.co/vLvt4Xvfi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:39 to go. Northwest leading it 60-56 with free throws coming up for the Bearcats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us Fridays at 4:45. Walk in. 20.00. Ages 4 and up. See you Friday! Class, parties and camps too. #lego… https://t.co/T2ZGRPD5w2]]></document><document><![CDATA[January 23rd 2009, bet LBJ and the Cavs -5.5 on the road vs a terrible GSW team. Won by 1 #noeasybuckets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today will continue to be frigid, with highs up to 20 °F expected, but the sun is shining brightly this morning at… https://t.co/KU0BvhPQjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaunaSallai @RealTT2020 Trump would have the support of all Americans but the problem is the hacks on the left and… https://t.co/bIHwJMUbA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin @davidharsanyi On a positive note, we’ll have fewer hipsters in LIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassBaller What was barking Becky jealous? Did she want to visit the dog pound?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megynkelly Oh get over yourself sweet pea... b*lls#it sanctimony at its most nauseating...🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sprintcare They’ve called that number. In times of death or major crisis, great customer service would be to conta… https://t.co/dL6fnKUNc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyangsamsPS4 That was a great doc! Was one of the things that got me started on a ketogenic lifestyle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot @VeldaMcConnell2 And being able to ride your bike all over the neighborhood without parents helicop… https://t.co/hfGC3X1dTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KC_Sass But sometimes it’s the best thing in the end. Key word is break. Not busted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncalvinabney @LoneStarBeer @MillerLite @tecate @CoorsLight I also like Bud heavy. I just can’t drink 24 of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @SenSherrodBrown @Liz_Cheney @RepAdamSchiff Of course anti-Semitism is wrong! But this country has bl… https://t.co/rSwWzAOIPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dynamiccookie @PokemonGoApp How many photos have u taken? I’ve taken upwards of 500 and still not jack shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to snowy white Boston ⛄️ #home #citylife #snowday @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/stQpyWHYo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @jennifernettles. I’ve had the privilege of working for her on two solo tours and sugarland last summer… https://t.co/5vaXS25Lvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabidTicat @Lons I TOTALLY understand people getting angry (I have 3 beautiful younger sisters) and I would want t… https://t.co/sZVn1y88I6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pain is temporary. Being a little bitch who quits is forever.  Two years ago I got 10 stitches in my thumb and took… https://t.co/3ioBwODOeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ybbatreece @IlliniMBB Put them to the top of the power rankings im about the hype 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to get highly stressed, try opening a can of pineapples with a damn razor knife. https://t.co/vulOZTjYrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alphawoman @amcoslane @LeftAction Left wing propaganda. Stop watching that guy Maddow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sugar Baking cookie and beer pairing #craftbeer *not pictured: banana cream cookie - Drinking an 151 Anniversa… https://t.co/G83BPtFw6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so the 2019 travel begins. #B764 #EWR - #HNL #United https://t.co/vJuXiToj4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenny Robinson also pitched for the Medicine Hat Blue Jays. https://t.co/DYaz9wZuZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: I teach students graphic design skills. I have worked with other staff members in allowing students to use thos… https://t.co/MK1Glp4t5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnbrockman I really thought I put my heart into each story I wrote this week. You will have to tell me what the… https://t.co/kJ0TvUb6SB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael20818399 @SaltedLime65 @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch @foxandfriends @FoxNews You’re so naive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianJacobsPFO I'm just so tired of this growing faction of basketball illiterates who don't think that we need Ji… https://t.co/VMaDlmoG6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last thing a kid needs is to be interrogated when they walk into your class late. Allow them to quickly get int… https://t.co/0XWyi6qXck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild bird chicken in east Peoria (where the old slim chickens was) is giving out free 4 piece tender meals today. 👅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had a technical interview with one of the world's largest tech companies. Soaked in sweat is an understatement]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will not stop making faces at babies when their parents aren’t looking &amp; i am willing to die for that right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrNealDunnFL2  Dr Dunn, we are hearing here in the Panhandle that Trump is going after Tyndall rebuilding money fo… https://t.co/eGnooGm0nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@balt_hon @CBSNews Elijah should be more about his beloved Baltimore which is now the nation's most dangerous city]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larrylarraldo I heard it I think I like their last album better but I got listen to it again. Tame is coming to mo… https://t.co/hhSBpw7zRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, 4 SW Dodge City [Ford Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 4.20 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches out here shadowing real bosses but will forever be the employee//: ur the one in the corner of the pics sis!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank goodness @mlb is on top of the most important stories. I'm glad to know that...two celebrities I don't really… https://t.co/7GFqWierpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkcurlyhead No need to close yo eyes I want you to see and experience it all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanchez is a disgrace to this club...hope United ship him off in the summer he doesnt deserve those outrageous wages]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostyweather How about this: there’s no such thing as “weird.” The assumption that there is a “normal” way to fee… https://t.co/2IrWEpZipK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well big thanks to arborclimbtree for hooking me up with a replacement cable very quickly, can’t Thank you enough !… https://t.co/PWbwgfNjSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a good effort and turnout. Would absolutely love to see that for all of our home games in all of our sports.… https://t.co/OEYDYtNUbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundaysnuggleday with apparently_hannah 💕 ✨ @ El Cajon, California https://t.co/Z1o1GNPeea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit so sad they keep remolding the Summit like they wiping away my childhood and shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You as a American representative for the people of the people. Your sitting in your high… https://t.co/Odw4meCow7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking in some alone time. #sunset #atardecer #beach #losangeles #winter @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/m28d1qGP6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hendrick88Team I need to stop looking at twitter during the race.  Sling TV has a huge delay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @OfficialHTM on the Hall Of Fame! https://t.co/XapEVKGi47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints - Siloam Springs AR https://t.co/AbXDXohNaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[As juicy citrus as the color implies with just a hint of sweetness. - Drinking a Fresh Haze IPA by @deschutesbeer @… https://t.co/X48dRdQdNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s non-binding, and it’s just a list of general goals. So why is it so hard to agree on even the IDEA of saving t… https://t.co/ggd8U5VS6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[To everyone complaining about @JBHolmesgolf  winning the @genesisopen ... when was the last time you played for a million?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris From The New York Post: The California Department of Justice paid more than $1 million to employees w… https://t.co/mCFgJG5xkf]]></document></documents></author>