<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheBInstitute Fruit pies are strangely regional. There’s even peach out there in the wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to staff and students at St. Bonaventure for engaging in the Water Drill challenge. Cheers to conti… https://t.co/GV1TbhrlRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javieraibacache @Lilosilvag Metete a hollywoodunlocked en instagram y en el video que un muchacho sale contando Ellas comentaron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burton2thistalr I know! Someone cursed me I think. I’m buying coffee now 😂 But hey, at least the coffee didn’t land on me 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOW’D YALL MAKE THIS TWEET ABOUT SMASH TOO  GOTTA SAY IM HEMKIN IMPRESSED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luco026 @realDonaldTrump not in the least bring it on and while you at it bring the evidence for dems too]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom, after she lends me a coffee thermos to use in the car: “Don’t lose it.” #TheOConnorsAreWeird]]></document><document><![CDATA[WU. Snapchat! (Your students are probably already using it.) 👻 🐶 #RCSLearn https://t.co/3TbMU6lsBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbaraBann1366 I wonder how cases of Coke they could have paid for with:  bond money, anger management classes????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent v-day cuddled up and watching movies with this butthead ❤️ https://t.co/4r8Bq9Uqee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for taking the time to judge @KUGradStudies 3MT competition. So happy that @kuengineering graduate studen… https://t.co/3G5LWaxvbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katyac_h2o @MyDogSnowy @pebble_dev Dictation still works on iOS, but not for replying to/sending text messages.]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 or 16 how hard is it to have enough common sense to know not to fuck your ‘sisters’ man/baby daddy/ex/partner. B… https://t.co/355IhRT9WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@embird502 I’m so glad!!  He’s amazing. I hope you’re doing well too :) miss you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current company honoring the amazing dean of my alma Mayer @UFJSchool is mind-blowingly awesome. #GoGators! Cong… https://t.co/HE3taPUpwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future #nomorestraws #savingtheplanet @starbucks @ RBC Centre https://t.co/Hi7sTHJH6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandma with all her favorite things in one picture :,) https://t.co/uld490lRzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jy1967a32 @BrantJom @Alyssa_Milano You won't win...WE ALREADY DID HUT GOOD LUCK... YOU HAVE NO SAY IN OUR BODIES..… https://t.co/5vnZIDFIDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me as a child: "When I grow up I'm gonna buy candy whenever I want" Me as an adult: "Ooo, snap peas are on sale for… https://t.co/03gBKgSHBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodNight (@ The Room Of Requirement in Hogwarts Castle, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/NxspP8kZGz https://t.co/ux55S9WrVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time i made coffee for christian bale and he was wearing flip flops and a fedora]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t cried in so long &amp; now that my mental breakdown has finally kicked in I can’t stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[And also the heating/ac is broken at the label so it’s freezing there too. I just want to be warm😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babsdraws I apologize if you have answered this already. What is the music that is playing in the background of… https://t.co/UWshr3Ir8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEFIVE Trump is placating, manipulating, slamming the guy won't bring Otto back, they understand what Trump is do… https://t.co/24SEVDVZG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now on Good Day Columbus: A Columbus Police officer shot. Investigators call it an ambush. 3 suspects in custody.   https://t.co/GH77qNIdDb…]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad you are a #WildcatforLife @CrystalRNichols looks like a great night with @UA_SBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perks of being a work #travelwarrior who makes frequent trips to #Austin?  Seeing some of my dear #pinksocks friend… https://t.co/k3tvrRXhR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I’m a dumb bitch for doing my homework the night before but I’m a good bitch because I actually did it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Standing In The Sun by Jessica Lea Mayfield https://t.co/aTuHvh6hno]]></document><document><![CDATA[R. Kelly is in custody amid charges of aggravated criminal sexual abuse in Illinois  https://t.co/ohOBTZxVdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Occultist crust trap incendiary heat missile of a rabid font abandoned in a gutter except I fucked up and need to c… https://t.co/L3L23X69ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is the young lady sitting in front and to the right of Chairman Cummings? Her facial expression’s are EVERYTHIN… https://t.co/URXarfPgdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crisp beautiful #Tecate morning! #SpaLife #RDsOfInstagram #travelmexico #Morning #SavortheRanch @ Rancho La Puerta https://t.co/ErijHnPfck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWA4th @louismerryman I can vouch for the “big and strong” assessment! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt so good after my HIIT workout the other day. Pretty sure my jumps were as high as my cheerleading days... 😝… https://t.co/7C5RerWXn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @Bren_O1967 @TonyaRBlue1 @Lonnie_Hammer @HammerDownHard1 @evesdadisbest Happy Saturday Gizmo!🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethMacFarlane These parents watched their child suffer needlessly for over a month and still no change in their t… https://t.co/Jbdv1dXIrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to my forever wedding date, my yenta-ing partner, my Coconut. Thank you for always being the… https://t.co/j5gjLvnfhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews Your hate for single parents and gay parents are abundantly clear, by all means keep digging. Hopefully… https://t.co/y65RiLIdfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selenag27477225 @Will53879379 #FBRParty #TrumpResign #TrumpRussia #TrumpFakeEmergency #25thAmendmentNow… https://t.co/xRjEtTUR8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will bring all the emotions out of me and I truly can’t wait... 😭😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of best friends is getting married and just asked me to be a bridesmaid and I am so motherfucking excited for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg What an ignorant statement from you Fred. I am one of many who are PROUD and LUCKY to be American.… https://t.co/OVvUQhDnQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[For My Love, my son Jack who loves to read @TheEconomist. Remember when we sang Mariah's song in the car and we had… https://t.co/GD2qcjoN3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m celebrating International Women’s Day at the @HHHSchool IndigenousWomen Have Always Been Leaders Conference. https://t.co/0ngctGzaCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_wats17 You've always made RH proud Sammy!!  Chase your dreams!!! #RHCometPride #RHExcellence]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m delighted and proud to announce that Graham Woodward, our school @NatGeoEducation Geography Bee winner, qualifi… https://t.co/nRnXLclptv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBegnaud @CBSThisMorning All I can think about is all those survivors. His anger scares me. I can’t imagine wh… https://t.co/LbskabB4So]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimieAlexander What kind of maintenance put marks like that on your body?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making our way through the mountains! #PortlandBound #NewChapter #NewsLadyAdventures https://t.co/QrYPDDU2lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craignorriscbc @OntarioGreens @MikeSchreiner Thanks for your (quick) response (and coverage of the issue)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for @marmstrongx3 to come back to TX so we can get a big ass margarita after I have this baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstein Connecticut's full of insurance companies that will never vote for a Democrat that pushes for Medicare fo… https://t.co/IH5kF32BP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Night Special Needs Prom hosted by New Life Baptist and held at Westview Primary tomorrow night! @nlbcgc… https://t.co/sngVxZQ9PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I found the Make Time For Happiness Sweepstakes and I think you might want a chance to win, too! Enter here: https://t.co/7FCheAxlnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love WWE but they need to put these guys from NXT out in front of the right crowds. Hunter said all their names a… https://t.co/KNs3VT1nJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainsLogAz Been there,  lived through it. You will too but of course it hurts some]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA @realDonaldTrump 2020 continue to MAGA. Politicians are liars and thieves, for the most part. I’d still l… https://t.co/aPPj4PelXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had sunshine!!! And I had a new shade of lip glow! #grandeur #lipglow #sunshine #moderngems #jewelrytrends… https://t.co/73z11bfB5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linaesposito2 @aaroncarter I can't really say that because @aaroncarter  is like a brother to me but I understand what you're saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to congratulate your teammate Kyle. #2ndplace #DaytonaDay #NASCARonFOX @dennyhamlin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to get rid of Spectrum. I’ve been living here for 2 years and I’ve never had functioning Internet de… https://t.co/0BpxYscIPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers top trending worldwide in 2019 because of reuniting with new music is BLOWING MY MIND! I am so h… https://t.co/cHcfvepCro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattsRoadTrip @traveling1223 Thank you Matt! Thank you for your wonderful tips! Have a good week! #RoadTripChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this awesome contest by @TheRogueEnergy! https://t.co/pUupENLIAQ #giveaway #RogueEnergy #contest #gaming #gamingdrink]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always amazed at these kind of people. More worried about their tv show than a severe weather emergency and peo… https://t.co/tduAtmx7b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have something really funny to tweet but it’s gross as hell and i don’t want my friends to make fun of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melindacrow @RoarLoudTravel I’m fortunate enough to live in the midst of all the artwork in the Plateau 😍. Can’t w… https://t.co/go1FoSfX32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing up for women ✔️  This legislative session, with bipartisan support, I passed a monumental bill which would… https://t.co/oFcStcSL1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tabloid’s Malia Obama report draws rebukes on social media - The Washington Post https://t.co/CPzWIqiEw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you think things are starting to fall into place and then life hits you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to hear they’re appreciated. EVERYONE. 💙 #wearepatneff #thisispatneff]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sage Restaurant &amp; Lounge - @sagewhittierca in Whittier, CA https://t.co/XOpPS30OCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Louis Bound! I’m so incredibly excited to join the St. Louis Cardinals Communications department as a Gameday C… https://t.co/iAdG755KDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisVanHollen Let me know when the grassroots give up their cars airplanes and stop cows from farting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Why isn't he charged with rape? These women were trafficked. How did he not know that. I don't believ… https://t.co/yOw8ki83Rk]]></document><document><![CDATA[DISNEY WORLD EPCOT !!!! FANTASTIC DAY 2 LATE POST !!!X3 @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/DpXP1SBnQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam3339 @ACTBrigitte I knew that way before she ran. They just turned a blind eye to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019-02-13 – tiny lights https://t.co/uGHdAZpxDr https://t.co/lpTKJ9vAwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeviqueira #POTUSatCPAC #DubiousVeracity #BovineExcrement Two unrestrained hours, a rambling stream of conscious… https://t.co/ubFGRdROHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Similar thinking on streetcars! You can easily commute in if you stay off of the Queen or King streetcar lines w/ou… https://t.co/6uZraqe85L]]></document><document><![CDATA[the one where the roommates celebrate galentines day 💫💗🤩 @ Big Grove Brewery &amp; Taproom - Iowa City https://t.co/XWmYer7Y6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBillingsclass @jloughlin23 @MrHExperience I’m looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the fuck did my parents choose to move to NJ out of all the other warmer states?]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW I'M NOT SUPERSTITIOUS, but we lost one home that I attended in the past like 5 months with my hockey buddy ole… https://t.co/YXABfveGsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YNB @malcolmbarrett Really hope that is something that changes soon.  Sorry you’ve had to deal with attitudes like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you take a selfie, hold a baby, get nine people in the frame and make sure they are all looking (and smiling) i… https://t.co/kz0yDWxtVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oilfieldtrash14 @RThaens @jebel06 @thomaspearc3120 @MoooPapa @DatoFreddy @PigglyAGoGoMAGA @StevieRayHubcap… https://t.co/20wh96ny4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow since December my life has only been heading towards better. The only difference? Lack of toxic friends with on… https://t.co/EeJZujea6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_drazzari @CaththeWineLady @DavisWines @boozychef @jflorez @rr_pirate @jillianne_gray @DemiCassiani @cuvee_corner… https://t.co/ovBuf94d3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presenting my research on asynchronous online discussion boards and feedback flipgrid #booksnaps bitmoji… https://t.co/aHEPSh0kbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASEAdvance A4: Typos, I use my notepad on my smartphone to make sure everything is spelled right before I copy an… https://t.co/wScJ4a7Jp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blanshardbill @CBCAlerts Regardless of any punishments possibly handed out in the afterlife, it’s still necessary… https://t.co/rpmQM9qnAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing in line for beer. Definitely a first for me. But we met this lovely can. #smartmouthbeer… https://t.co/WJgjpJBtNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC  I am no longer a Democrat but who the hell do you think you are threatening your peers? You better back the F… https://t.co/hmVoNhbtmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you a nerd when you get this text: “hey can you or your friends help me with a poem I have to write about… https://t.co/fAEqYtH1LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltoonaCurve 🙋🏼‍♀️ #BoyzOfSummer #PutMeInCoach #CheapSeats #AlTuna #LetsGoBucs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resin #paint pour on the top of a wooden #jewelry box. Cant wait to finish and get to the bottom. Its going to be s… https://t.co/JYhiRrLvGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is often how our conversations go! My husband is very supportive of my #adminlife but I definitely get this fa… https://t.co/KCK64m1FUb]]></document></documents></author>