<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Up watching these new recipe videos has me wanting to make a dish right now 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz didn’t your president have girlfriends? He even paid off a couple of them. Oh I get it, the only differe… https://t.co/OER177PKmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBarr_ I want to check out Anthem but I'm worried that it's another Destiny game]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would have to be a Federal charge, because Chicago is the most corrupt city in America. FBI?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theahl action on #LeafsNationNetwork and @nhlnetwork with Mike Zigomanis and spence_berk ft. @TheSoundTigers vs… https://t.co/kvYWCogNEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The purest heart and the most genuine person I know! To the love of my life, I love you forever!❤️ @bweedenx4 https://t.co/AkobNZmyJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodOlBillDoyle @cbcasithappens @Sheila_Copps @JustinTrudeau @janephilpott @CBCNews @CBCAlerts @Puglaas Well, I di… https://t.co/VMIR7IAUoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennmac415 @EpochTimes @AOC No, the plan is to bring in illegals to replace the natives! Much more needy and Democratic votes. Europe 2.0!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I’m listening to the Jonas Brothers in the gym right now and actually liking it scares me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomAhink @jordanhink @Istate_ALL_IN @WideRtNattyLt I’m offended you don’t have the percentage by your battery level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncle Frank, my father and Grandfather Luther Allen I believe circa 1954. @ Blanchester, Ohio https://t.co/yokizBg35S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h1ding_ Pretty sure Obama allocated hundreds of millions of dollars to that shit. You think you can fix pipes over… https://t.co/DyxRRfT93Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence @realDonaldTrump I'm pretty sure @Jim_Jordan has no interest in the possibility that @realDonaldTrump may… https://t.co/vXaoBfvf55]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man has an album in the works I can feel it. He isn’t headlining Rolling Loud for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwhiteburgh Same energy you gave to quip! Give to them do a good investigation full of  Bias under tones! Remember… https://t.co/RpXCBYwvZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mob on the Run - 1987 Documentary - Las Vegas https://t.co/i3ooipDUdM via @YouTube @RobFaiNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Yes. We must Pray. Heavenly Father.. I Thessalonians 5:17. Because God Almighty can hear us! He wants u… https://t.co/OU1K3EtLLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/Fz9XxxBHmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embarrass ? Lmao me and my cousin got beat like this every day @AtgPaco]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣HAPPY BIRTHDAY BRANDON!!!!!!😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 BFF's Forever 🙂🙌🏽😎🥃✊🏽😁🤣#happybirthday @ Hollywood https://t.co/92TXiyxlha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DopplerDan @WGALMattMoore @NWSStateCollege  @MaryEllenFox43    Over to snow at 9:45 in New Franklin (Franklin county)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes stop the dam funding. Supporting that insanity is in itself is insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale This gif is 🌲, Brad.  Thanks for summoning it!  🤪 https://t.co/mpk3PGXBrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rejectionking I'll start screaming "Free Press!" If you take away my Anarchist Cookbook and Jihadist magazines (like Britain does)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xwarriorbloodx He needs to see a barber before he needs that mess on his neck touched up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Every EOTP tweet should be reported to twitter for threatening violence against others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said they are of while on duty at the American Embassy in Beirut, Lebanon🇱🇧!! Thank U for yr service, cuz!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. Remember, only YOU can prevent a forest fire! Cook your food at home and then go camping! @ Port Term… https://t.co/EY6iarhoXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murr noticed me again!!!!!! Brb crying forever 😭😭😍😍🥰🥰❤️❤️ #ImpracticalJokers #murr #jamesmurray #awakenednovel https://t.co/RuC6CfrdfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you knew how much positive impact you had on the lives of others, how would you feel about your own self worth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaInigoMontoya @KathyGavin7 @waltshaub @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Man try the news it’s been saying this f… https://t.co/j4JGc1vOeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You know that same FBI investigation exonerated her. So did the Senate investigation. I know your… https://t.co/dU6vCIRWsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading China Miéville’s “This Census-taker” and haven’t loved a book of his this much since “Iron Council.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Most of the heroin comes into USA from south of the border. Not hard to figure out how to greatly red… https://t.co/EjiViolFxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summershamrock @WWEUK @BeckyLynchWWE But I have loved Becky since I saw her debut match in NXT back in June of 201… https://t.co/ZEXzuCbirk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to my favorite bed hogging, chocolate/coffee ice cream loving, (deathly allergic but) dog app… https://t.co/xnApKiz5lC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaAlanna @Song_bird11799 @sarah_perni If y’all start fist fighting after this debate falls apart my moneys on Murray]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The filing of the phony police report is not the issue here (yet).   A report could have been made… https://t.co/W658bqzHmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @foxandfriends w/ @kilmeade @ainsleyearhardt and @SteveDoocy Keep up the… https://t.co/l6Y6H9A5IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagaRabbit @CNNPolitics Well this is the dumbest thing I’ve seen from a Trump supporter today...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runthistrain Who put that Forever 21 “I can’t adult today” pic up there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldendoekd @MikeFender5 @bellwetherdude @cshuler233 @arkiegal411 @EricJoh37288055 @JacobJMP2 @HTWells3… https://t.co/94c9yuHdtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since unc_basketball will be out for some @dukembb blood today, I thought I would donate a little #opositiveblood… https://t.co/QJkbKrhq9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guerito_Zac Den follow actual news twitters not pop culture twitters brah lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake news advisory. You all are afraid of what @POTUS does when out among the people. The overwhelming response val… https://t.co/h3cROGYdKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are correct, a living wage is not a gift, it's something you earn by hard work and dedication to your job.… https://t.co/OvGz6AW1M7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Float with the clouds and enjoy the day. @ Meridian, Idaho https://t.co/NOJbrM4W8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM JUST SO FED UP WITH STUPID LEFTIES N PEOPLE GOING APE OVER A MAGA HAT THEY DONT EVEN KNOW WHY THEY HATE TRUMP… https://t.co/gIXhTRJCdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cereals  1 froot loops 2  cocoa puffs 3 apple cheerios 4 shreddies 5 oatmeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaAHirsch @WendeNGibbs @docroc99 @rhwiggins @MGHIR1 @JNIS_BMJ This looks very interesting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Trump is just a treasonous traitor to America that should have been removed along time ago so sad that Russ… https://t.co/5sXzErHVOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that’s just practice, I’d hate to be his in competition opponent. #mma #KO #Roundhouse @ScottCoker @danawhite… https://t.co/ASPbxtf16B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaraj No. I've never seen it help make anyone less racist or biased nor have I seen it make teachers more effective with their students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I thought the Bills got AB I hated the trade.....now that the Trade looks like toast I’m disappointed.....gues… https://t.co/LqLTm4teFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brothers and sisters, I do not consider myself yet to have taken hold of it. But one thing I do: Forgetting what is… https://t.co/VdVBS0w6Sw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic!!  @TODAYshow @GMA #ValentinesDay #SanAntonio #MarketSquare #DancingGranny https://t.co/SOzhUTmNyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrkbenowen What about John Podesta..... How long did he get for what crime....oh wait....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life hack: get really hot chips aka flaming hot @Doritos and you won’t eat the entire bag 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karatloz @dylmdav Think we just found the casting for the Columbo reboot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to have kids. So once their old I can take them to the strip club with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Chairman Kim is a ruthless bloodthirsty dictator who care about no one other than himself. Wow, he… https://t.co/zshjA7HnwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry for your beliefs. #JefferyPage #avantgardeprovocateur @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/RgbGCqxxgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went out to Gustavus for my birthday.  Always a winning place! @ Gustav's Pub &amp; Grill - Tigard, OR https://t.co/wmuA70p58w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ethan_Narber I know there's a lot of concern in NYC of over-gentrification to the point that most working-class an… https://t.co/hyJSVzuNT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiekfitz she said she rather have a Wawa sub ...where did i go wrong 😭😭😭 @skipper_jenna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flyby! @USCG flying in front of ☀️ rise before #skyway10k @10NewsWTSP #Sendto10 https://t.co/7HoJHsnkHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s say most kids don’t start truly watching NBA basketball until they are 5 years old! (Probably a lot older but… https://t.co/vuPxpDP5zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foresstfire That is definitely my way of expressing joy when something is fantastic haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest blown call I’ve ever seen, clearly the shot wasn’t off in time. Hate to see Collin’s season get cut short b… https://t.co/OznoUJlfbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAndyBiggsAZ @realDonaldTrump Only bystanders to the 2568 gun deaths thus far in 2019, right? @GunDeaths https://t.co/MQGoMMYHS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL REY SUPERÓ A JORDAN !!  El (F) LeBron James anotó 31 Pts este miércoles 6 de marzo Vs Denver llegando a 32311 en… https://t.co/UajCdylfm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan O' Neal destroys a Merc in "Driver" - '78 - HQ https://t.co/r4yYbcPVrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPhilIvory Wow, I don't know if I can get my head around this incredible act of generosity!  Maybe I'll follow… https://t.co/aBc7GGZq9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an athlete, this moment can be missed at times. Thanks @LeVelleMoton @NCCU for reminding everyone!!!… https://t.co/63eLdF1YUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroyNRowan @NerbasBrosAngus I doubt many people run as many different contemporary groupings as I do with as many… https://t.co/D0sZURW08a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico @RepMaxineWaters Love her! Maxine Waters a true patriot, a real leader, and has always fought for the poo… https://t.co/sgpVmGJW3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drfixus NYT saw decrease in 💓 attacks after flu vaccine. Vax reduces need 4 meds, prolonging drug effectiveness. V… https://t.co/ROQHN0rOq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look in to @IndyCaronNBC control room. @IndyCar @GPSTPETE #FIRESTONEGP #INDYCAR #GPSTPETE https://t.co/52SySlijcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[ghosts of governors past @ Leland Stanford Mansion State Historic Park https://t.co/9qvY5gaJWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe this to be the best simple tech I've seen in a long time. We can now close a can and drink it later. Good… https://t.co/EBMQVreA0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Synthon61 @AgBioWorld @mem_somerville this one works for me https://t.co/lXHesuGiko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all talk about moves y’all wanna make, we just make them.🤫 @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/1NHqV6pww5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night at Playstation Theatre seeing @InFlames_SWE and @WTofficial in New York. Lots of fun! https://t.co/cSfGzuqGtx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look for this guy back on the shelves of your favorite fine beer seller/cellar.  I like this guy. . . #Repost… https://t.co/vlut7A52FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how NMU evolved on closing in inclement weather https://t.co/8ayviZ9eV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What in the...I thought that you never, ever fire into a vehicle. Both drivers should be facing charges. https://t.co/DEYREM8Wy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_of_Europe Europeans. The U.S. saved all your collective asses in WWII. We rebuilt everything. This is how you th… https://t.co/MdqNPFBgET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronbergcomedy @GenoBiscontePA @InHotWatershow this is practically a buffet for @legitnewsguy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pkrprncss @CruiseNorwegian Yes. And don't forget to shop in the plaza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YohannaLoucheur @Mark_Brough @andylolz @timdavies @IATI_aid Data quality + clarity of code list is part of it, as… https://t.co/LCokb3ZJcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lakers @SpectrumSN That’s sick!! But we still lost!! https://t.co/rtZzlucvU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter  Aurelia aurita (also called the Common Jellyfish or Wire Transferfish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler_Mason2016 @BigCind @whitemoreliam Exactly. Innocently saving them for posterity, to always remember him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PANDAWATCH! (@BayleyCron doesn't really have the dramatic Brian Fantana face happening, but still...) #sandiegozoo… https://t.co/rjXY1Fq1xW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#365DAYSEVERYDAYIWILL! #IMPEACHDJT!🤥 #NEONOTZIRACITSSOAB!🖕🏽 #DRAINSEWERFROMTRUMPS! #COWARD! #LIER🤥… https://t.co/pk1xghOcwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUMP WORKS ON THE POOR EDUCATED THATS THE POOR MINDED REPUBLICAN PARTY M. MCCONNELL L. GRAHAM C. GRASSLEY J JORDAN… https://t.co/9vC57kR9KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Are you that stupid? Seriously? I know Trump is a fascist dictator wannabe and you are one of his lap d… https://t.co/i7wnGcQ8y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[just found this video of my brother faceswapping with @LanaParrilla and i thought it needed to be shared https://t.co/tFHMM7Htl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/Ff0RbHoCKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliveLikeTupac @niceguynaj @Playboy_Laker @djk1001 @SellyCisco @Shahne_Ash @MidWestChris1 @HighPoint34 @primekfc C… https://t.co/tXLdKh5DwL]]></document></documents></author>