<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TWITMO_INMATE @RealBiddle @uniquedeehan1 @KevinGina1 @WandaWomanHere @SmackYeti @fcfootsteps @PatriottDefense… https://t.co/QhuPWBZyjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do NOT want a relationship, I don’t want a fuck buddy, I don’t want shit. You boys look desperate af triple texti… https://t.co/UcDMABK90c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also thanks to @KreweOfMuses for the little notebooks. I caught 3 of em, so 1 to NJ, 1 red one for my purse, and 1… https://t.co/ykUVLU3sVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @JasonMMarkey and @MlleLepa to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no… https://t.co/6RrO2LPhb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISU_wildlife If only Outlook had an Undo feature like Word or Publisher!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelSkowski I feel like she was probably drunk, no excuse of course but I do think she is worth forgiving. But not… https://t.co/0cyGGp4KSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends: “Kate I’ve seen you naked more than I’ve seen myself” Friends: “kate I’m on my way put pants on”  Frien… https://t.co/iYYUHIYhRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want a huge story start investigating him and sex harassment claims by victims???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonGallaway I can’t wait for the Crown to start up with her as the Queen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[School has me so stressed out. I actually hate my life because of it. I need a day off. But not even a big snow sto… https://t.co/xfkVB4YCFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sixteen Democratic members of the House judiciary committee have now written to the justice department in light of… https://t.co/MMDMd0nX2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezralevin @IndivisibleTeam @ewarren This thread has been sticking with me. Here's the thing: when I talk to voters… https://t.co/91YFcD0vzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[no no no no no. I am absolutely, positively way too far behind on sleep for daylight savings to be this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome #Daytona500! Congrats to @dennyhamlin on his win for @JoeGibbsRacing. You can see the emotion in al… https://t.co/qkwPOfPMkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have openings today n tomorrow for nails n pedicure also facials #8325843162 #3047woodlandhillsdrive #kingwoodtx… https://t.co/0Dor7KuLoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[NASA Renames Facility in Honor of ‘Hidden Figure’ Katherine Johnson https://t.co/j1JUWzE9Sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to this family service building fucking suck big fucking balls! Employees are always so miserable at this place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad I had time to get my @NKOTB fix this morning before work with #HangingTough30 #theway #gma ❤️ my… https://t.co/gk0daKCVnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why when the second guy jumped, immediately in my head I was like “YEET!” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bootlegbane Oh wait, you mean you can relate?! Ok. Text me! I’m confused &amp; so curious! Love you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first day all week without rain. Time to get outside!  #trailrun #getoutside #BayArea https://t.co/wMnjIGtbYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune of Love. Best song ever! Magical voice of @RajBarm43223561  কেন যে তোকে পাহারা-পাহারা দিল মন কেন রে এতো সাহারা… https://t.co/F6uo1rX5XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kimbri9000 @LaraLeaTrump @uniofgothenburg @beaglefreedom Awww..  so sad !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAX team so excited about new LAX Technical Operations Center with a prelim plan to be completed by late 2020! grea… https://t.co/51P11bRPaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAEMIN 태민 'WANT' Dance Practice https://t.co/KA1t8C6QNn via @YouTube ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreagast3 Jajajaja yo tampoco me he tocado la ceja desde el viernes 😛😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday the Chinese people gave me an omelette with shrimp , beef and chicken ... I’ve been in the toilet ever since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crace33 @bmacfischer @NashaniGilbert @andypottsNLI He told her to keep them 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las palabras de este señor valen mas que las de la bola de periosicarios del programa de mierda ese, llamado  el ch… https://t.co/RqwqkJ5Ny8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckRossDC @realDonaldTrump @DailyCaller It's time for a total revamp of our election laws to get dark money out… https://t.co/F41ovaxdDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnfouganfife @douganbren @deborahjshelton 😬😂 https://t.co/luEu4ZuC4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sententia Vera Cultural Hub is fostering a culture of sharing know-how, that is, professional development for all.… https://t.co/Sx00pibmiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope. Never again. Never, ever. #movingforward @ Old Saybrook, Connecticut https://t.co/dJmSs88Ue6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was telling a man yesterday about how I’m hosting a baby shower at my home this evening and his response was “Wow.… https://t.co/BNdxGdzzOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACMawards @carrieunderwood The Real Artist of the decade!!!! Happy Birthday!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The magic of low tide... 🌊  🦀  🐟  #oakbay #golfcoursebeach #yyj @vgc1893 #salishsea @OakBayTourism @oakbayliving @… https://t.co/mNoPy3Sbl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedLieu @POTUS 10,000 coming wk after wk 3000 dying from drugs monthly, coming through Mexico 1/3 women and gir… https://t.co/DBnYoJrGbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it a coincidence my tax money dropped the same day Warped Tour tickets were released? I think not]]></document><document><![CDATA[People screenshot things I say on here and report back to my husband.  We just laugh at the absurdity. Also because… https://t.co/tjeDiplwMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a strong, independent woman - I AM FULLY ERECT!!!   #gameofthrones #HBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until Friday comment and tag on this post a woman who inspires you to rise, and when she makes her first appointmen… https://t.co/dFPjgs5F3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let me get this straight, #BurritoBecky was eating at a Mexican restaurant and didn't want the man to speak Span… https://t.co/TK0SaSTkic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_ShaManagement @IGotPeace @impettyasfuck @500Ells Very true!  Every time Shiloh looks all concerned about Drew an… https://t.co/vxJFl2V5F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do white people look so old you 18 but you look like your 30 and have four kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LafayetteBOC I am working to change something on my schedule.  I would love to attend!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyValentinesDay to everyone ❤️ I know some people think this holiday is just a big money day for the card and c… https://t.co/G2WyJTAfqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilynussbaum I want someone to hoist her aloft in a large-budget dance number.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rustyrockets @JKCorden Thank you @rustyrockets !  You are correct; surrounding ourselves with positive thoughts he… https://t.co/ruh9BiZbTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[katehudson arrives to the @kissie326 gala @ Beverly Wilshire, Beverly Hills (A Four Seasons Hotel) https://t.co/9vmM8GddaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThunderND Me if we get busy in the slightest tomorrow https://t.co/2yqei8JbCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been an incredibly short week and I haven’t posted much. Getting ready to close for 4 days to visit with famil… https://t.co/8cH162WPe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making learning fun with  “sumo bots” @ChilesElem @HillsboroughSch  this morning! @10NewsWTSP School of the Week Po… https://t.co/qpjkDZSPNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaylencaylen Giiiirl I really hope it was actual beans and not something else XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ana_Dia11 4:41 am no judgement the insomnia is back lol and clearly it’s 1:41 am where you are https://t.co/5U198qmGiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they did CJ and will continue to oppress all that will follow them - DC was built on the backs of slaves by the… https://t.co/3C8qRi1Ak8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Après wine in a sippy cup🍷🌟 #blessed @ Tamworth, Ontario https://t.co/CoBwNmHUnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍1963 @BeeGees ❣️🎤🎤🎤🎶  5️⃣6️⃣ YEARS AGO⤵️ ❤️‼️ https://t.co/Sp2lDGlGRo https://t.co/2x8FbLCiuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Lil Darlin (feat. The O'Mys) by @ZZWard on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/MaQTP9yW0B https://t.co/2joNWOsfoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day with the Little’s EP #tinytownies no one does it better than Ms K https://t.co/LPW1cHMKKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisPappinMCC Lakewood Ranch, Florida. Between Bradenton and Sarasota :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it that it takes a good person to die for people to realize how genuine and real they really were? We need t… https://t.co/2wur3j9cW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis I thought it was a great film.   Maybe not my choice, but certainly a worthy contender.  The acting was s… https://t.co/wOC5aTLop4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ @wouterhoetink Wow what an amazing young man. His parents sure raised him right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Grove | Stitchfix | Pop-Up Red Carpet #Fashion #LosAngeles #TheGrove #WorkYourPlan https://t.co/RNqqTBxwg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dawn_Rivera @OneBrokeMom2 @SenGillibrand @KamalaHarris Everyone else has..i.mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have actors / theatre people on here so advice needed:  the character i’ve been with the past 2 months is pretty… https://t.co/2WBls364k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FairyDusted50 @lisarinna I know sweetie. I just tweeted about that. WTF was she thinking? She word vomits more tha… https://t.co/GSoqApfBGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[These mighty Brawlers killed their Core De Force Workout last night! #coredeforce #coredeforcelive #beachbody… https://t.co/NxqaP9XWch]]></document><document><![CDATA[How funny Zooey’s dad didn’t win an Oscar (Caleb Deschanel for Cinematography) but her TV boo was on stage for his… https://t.co/lJt2uGLhHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Don't see the Smithsonian needs that much money to maintain.I love our history but not to this extent.… https://t.co/49VWANUZ2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️50% off STARTW NOW‼️ . The entire officialbetterbodies site is 50% off for ONE DAY ONLY!!! You must use code: ‼️P… https://t.co/c2rpz1Iw9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy (64 mins after) hearts day ❣️ mine is full from the 12 hour days we spend pushing towards something a little… https://t.co/w0gUw4gwWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[after pulling my hip so bad from trying to show my tattoo, I think it’s time to start going to the gym smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumplingheart Right?!? Look at it’s silly little noodle legs. I need it 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Março tem: - Meu aniversário - Jane the Virgin - Queer Eye  Melhor mês 💛 https://t.co/lqsr5PSdgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @Viviane6677 @TereOrt51687394 @roberta_lanzoni @evakoosiglesias @PucciaPatrizia @gabryluce… https://t.co/ekz7QcuqjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why not black and white all around for all of us working people on this holiday 🙋🏽‍♀️!! @busylittlequeen with the h… https://t.co/dYwlwPPTxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Florida Department of Highway Safety and Motor Vehicles https://t.co/VaXbAWGQIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to @kevinszamlewski for being the OG Cat Daddy and for starting a movement 🐱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who wake up everyday and put on a full face of makeup, do their hair, and wear a super cute outfit to school… https://t.co/MviH2MjfsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t even front. It don’t mean shit without that W though!! 🤷🏻‍♀️ Wow man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarasilv_1 all i think is like imagine when you’re not able to care for your parent and someone is doing that to t… https://t.co/vqeMUukKFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoraBro48052347 @timand2037 the german people never said anything. regular americans are speaking up against the h… https://t.co/IF88fGchB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your dad tries to prove a point at practice by telling the girls his favorite day of the year because it’s The… https://t.co/fF7giSB7eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[drunk celebrating the first birthday of a cat with leukemia 💗 miss blair if only u knew how much ily]]></document><document><![CDATA[The studio looks like I have been having so much fun. I’m back at it tomorrow. #sewinglife @ Tracy's Sewing Studio… https://t.co/m3jIqQhy74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acosta Looks to me like this was pandering to our own homegrown wannabe dictator @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning twitter. I just looked at the date, and realized I'll be 37 in exactly one week. It feels in many ways… https://t.co/XahXNlR2vA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh @realDonaldTrump is the laziest man in the county. Many stats - yikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nadine_E82 Ahh ,this is so very true , but I'm missing him so much and I'm on edge everytime I go on here just in… https://t.co/WxZqYuDIWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so disappointing to see the lack of standards and self respect that some teenage girls hold.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetSetJamerson Heheh! My trick I to buy a large sirloin, trim it and then youll have a few good steaks for that price!! 💫😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[eternally grateful that @neonandnoise took a career changing chance on me for @ladygunn and let me write about musi… https://t.co/rGc1H1RMHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[From V Day 🌹🍫🍓 to a Caturday win 🐱 🐾  over the top ranked team 🍊 to NBA 🏀 All Star ⭐️ Weekend to Prez Day (no schoo… https://t.co/BqX69sjimj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast at the @grasslandsaf networking reception / fundraiser for The Mass chapter of @nationalnow 🔥 thanks to… https://t.co/l3zSOFpxv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Sixth Grade News (via https://t.co/tjIkCotl3K) https://t.co/TqtswqzA59 @CalMum_Raiders #thecalmumway]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years ago I attended @SWChicago My very first tech-related event ever! @MysteryBaer and I were on the same team..… https://t.co/rEhhU1FZPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuagates @TravAdventure Those frequent flyer miles really do pay off. Thanks for everything you do. Thank you f… https://t.co/MeDllBWRNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studio stacks ➰ keep your friends close 〰️ and you totally deserve the moon and stars ➿ yes I use a silk ribbon to… https://t.co/kAuGAKTE5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaxophoneThe @StormIsUponUs Are you sure he wasn’t “shocked” about the President?]]></document></documents></author>