<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey look how cute my mom is. #feelsgoodman ruthannraitter @ Chandler, Arizona https://t.co/oQdpvGizlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latercera Que despreciable este tipo de periodismo. Metiendo veneno ahora en donde y cómo toman sus vacaciones per… https://t.co/XjsTIaoLnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could probably make a decent paper mache out of the Taco Bell receipts on the floor in my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF 👣 #FootPrints “ From $30/Night Motels To Condos Downtown” #GODisReal On This Day Exactly 5 Yrs Ago, I Took My… https://t.co/wvgEmJPiwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molly_knight Crock pot recipes are easy as hell. Roast any vegetable (potato, Brussell sprouts, broccoli) and just… https://t.co/CZIK7JOqy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonLearnedHand @thehill @DonaldJTrumpJr Did u know BOSTON MEDIA STARTED USA? I got fake news,called freedom Most v… https://t.co/jHQg52q7YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supreme Court says constitutional ban on ‘excessive fines’ also applies to states: In a unanimous ruling, the Supre… https://t.co/aSWfQdQ42f]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @realdavidmazouz huge fan of #Gotham hope you’re having a great day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compared to 2018 with Movies a lot of people saw: Dunkirk and Three Billboards Conversation starters: Get Out, Lady… https://t.co/vDebfWlnPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@analogfusion @TheROSTOVRipper Wasn’t there a bank robbing one that he was in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[C- I find what I have become to be as something I have to accept.  I can not go back now.  I really think that I ca… https://t.co/V26cXOedrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[54 Sings Alanis Morissette! @ Feinstein’s/54 Below https://t.co/LaXO0rba8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know the feeling like when you’re watching Curb Your Enthusiasm but then you have to look away because you c… https://t.co/gQh7KDfvRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gomez00023 @latimes @PopsBoosty I'm stone to phones. And I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth, but that's… https://t.co/o0Wxj07faX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-Pittsburgh cop charged with lying to FBI had relationship with bank robbery suspect's mom https://t.co/l0AKPuDvbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaaaguido @Gatekeeper5150 @StephenCallan10 Just wanted to make sure thanks champ :) &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think Golden State takes a lot of threes?  The NCAA record for most 3-point attempts by both teams is 108 set in 19… https://t.co/jku34eQzof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh we’re all going 10 under and there’s a cop in the shoulder? SLAM BRAKES. Like cokmmmmmmeeeeee onnnnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharonVonberg Give us luck and Hilton for Howard. That’s essentially what you just said but reversed. Now stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fest. Congrats on another hell of a year, @GasparillaMusic! #GMF #gasparillamusic #tampa @thepharcyde… https://t.co/NYC4UDYNwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[التصوير الزايد. مني ضد التصوير بس احس من عدم الاحترام كل ما دخلت محل او مكان معطي الناس ظهرك وانت تكلمهم. برضو هرجة… https://t.co/mlJX9ZbQFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here in ky we can’t even fix pot holes or buy kids textbooks in schools. But we have hundreds of millions for a fib… https://t.co/yYmbQnzyVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they make the Tom Brady movie, they better put this situation Robert Kraft in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shaolin_Prophet @SenMikeLee . Anyone pro choice is absolutely a baby killer by and through Apathy. It’s facts you… https://t.co/o3mZd5AyHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@primero_humano @poshgodneedlez @TalkLegendary @AllAthletesO WAIT. LAVINE AND GORDON’S CONTEST WAS SO GOOD AND ENTE… https://t.co/0jHRLlnAv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to do it every time my dude leaves me. @XtianJauregui https://t.co/Yc3Zbj2DCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was forced to check my newly re-acquired Les Paul in its hard case at the Logan Airport #AmericanAirlines termina… https://t.co/zghbLu7YBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcm @CHC_1927 saw it last night. lols. The best version of #DrJeckleMrHyde ANYONE ever did...so good..thanks @tcm #TCM #TCMParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @ChilisMexico in Garza García, Nuevo León https://t.co/ahy8ns5X3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VelVelHoller Planes, Trains, &amp; Automobiles is my pick https://t.co/fZD3v5P0g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabelamoner sessions Part 2...with special guest plutogoodboi @ The Hit Factory Criteria Recording Studios https://t.co/GZJdxj9DgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Didn’t Sarah Sanders say she was leaving the WH at the end of 2019?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoapJenn Makes no sense. I’ve replayed it several times &amp; is a cluster]]></document><document><![CDATA[The original baruto the perfect cells baruto streammmmmm💖 https://t.co/YvMYjTplmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority @CPAC @TuckerCarlson @IngrahamAngle @JudgeJeanine @FoxNews @greggutfeld @marthamaccallum @foxandfriends… https://t.co/uvaLwK4IEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔻🔻🔻🔻🔻THREAD 🔻🔻🔻🔻🔻  Excellent dig on #5G #EMRadiation by @prayingmedic. Much research about deleterious effects of E… https://t.co/cOesU4tRut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMickeyWiki I remember having a snowball fight with my mom in there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddisSaltyDog You got this brother!👍🏼 I’m packing now to head to the mountains]]></document><document><![CDATA[#craftbeer #beer #ipa #dipa #beer #draftbeer #growlerfill #beerlover #newenglandipa #hazyipa  #stout #porter #hefe… https://t.co/BfoygQCGiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dark forces messing with the cosmos is the new "Mercury in Retrograde." Can I blame the dark forces for Trump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love these kind of pics. This is a party bus passing by.  #singer #singersongwriter #entertainer #vlogger… https://t.co/ZkNSiagad5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Cabell Midland for advancing to the State Tournament!  Lot of work put in this past year paid off...not… https://t.co/CRmjwQZ1vy]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are 4 in our family of 8 rescues. Wait, looks like I can add a photo of the other 4... 3 are in #2, one is a… https://t.co/bnDnsPLKQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The government of Venezuela denies the violence against its people and the humanitarian crisis, enough is enough, i… https://t.co/E8PP5vUKeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hunteroach1 @granthompsonn I’ll let this explain itself. https://t.co/zic6tzTejR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShuangEsther @fransaraco @Neil_S_Parmar @nick4iezos @SlackHQ Y'all are freaking incredible... I'm loving the lust… https://t.co/y1iBCYNGLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed taking a boat under the Golden Gate Bridge. And the boat served Irish coffees, so it was a solid experience. https://t.co/vWmNBxaDVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mihai7Oprea @MarkRedbeliever @BeckyLynchWWE @kimberlasskick Dude...I wasn’t crapping on what you did. What you did… https://t.co/UfB5PZgb6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud to say that I used my own money when I bought my escape in 2013. Couldn’t say the same about my siblings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍃🍃🌺The Hidden Garden🌺🍃🍃Jasmine Rice, Baby Lima Beans, @MuirGlen Organic Garden Vegetable Pasta Sauce, Basil Leaves,… https://t.co/FYRGQj96Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Don't Let Me Down (Feat. Daya) by @TheChainsmokers on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/rshOtYWgAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Gone Not Around Any Longer by SISTAR19. #kpop https://t.co/N5ZGVi0Psa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmagical1 @City_Chief @PepTeam I’ve been blaming him since the game started with the wrong lineup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizadixon @space10_journal @RonDeSantisFL @OshaDavidson @insideclimate If I recall correctly, Germany has had some… https://t.co/z8mDah6d74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_Isitt @JeremyLoveday Ridiculous idea. Why don’t we let them buy booze and marijuana too while we’re at it?? Le… https://t.co/QtlGakgnbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmixsports Pinckneyville.  NCOE is pretty nice for postseason play.  WF will always be special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee I think that AOC should definitely not have kids. So, she is right on target. Kind of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people are trying to follow today’s game at Penn, hit @ewattsdele with a follow. He’ll be live tweeting the acti… https://t.co/q0y9pFabei]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about condemning the woman who left in the first place? Some of the dumbest liberal shit I've  ever heard   https://t.co/RMUFYQQXWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@911CORLEBRA777 @CatsChocolates @LouiseMensch @thespybrief @lauferlaw Tell Louise she got zapped and duped by ModRu… https://t.co/VzLTpylLNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyracuseToffees @WolffsBiergartn @EvertonInUSA @EvertonUSA The fact she wears Blue is all that matters. Everyone c… https://t.co/BwsLiIBGej]]></document><document><![CDATA[02.13.2018: Storm, heavy rainfall, atmospheric river? Bring it!  The toughest of tough showed up this evening to ta… https://t.co/Qs5zb0aI4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KodakShmodak no I don't agree.  If someone molested by child, it would hurt and scar my child for the rest of his… https://t.co/4DtR9mq7sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you look back on your life you’ll either smile because of all you did, or hang your head because of all you wi… https://t.co/sOQrqv7sFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollscolvin @USD480 @MeadowlarkMavs @PVEPioneers @SunflowerElem @Cottonwood480 @MacarthurElem @EMS480… https://t.co/rlhezWisRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posting this on the bulletin board at Lennon studios lol https://t.co/cZRHmS3Kuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianmcdonald75 @AOC Which was my point exactly. But AOC seems to think otherwise. She will bring much entertainme… https://t.co/dg9UzkyJQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilAPerry I thought I saw from @Tommy6Rings  they were going to FT flowers not Gostkowski?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saltygirafe The robits have had enough of our shit. This is how it begins...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#arnoldexpo Day ✌🏽 missing my boy joeydecaminada3 this year but did get a pic with his high school buddies!!! My br… https://t.co/jPFkTqSePa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder when you sleep- Are you ever dreaming of me? • FLOURISH ☁️• 📷: karliefoxphotography • newmexic… https://t.co/uY54GmU9yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJennTracker You should’ve just forwarded the “annoying bitch” tweet on to her. IT’S ALWAYS ABOUT THE FOOD 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember the chair dance I did t get to do in hairspray? Well Victor/Victoria is a whole other story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan Omar attack Jews instead of Netanyahu's policies. Big difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asiageoff You know What would be cool? You and Steve P together playing something off trilogy Emerson Lake and Palmer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a  word “no”! Citizens unfortunately have no input government policies Big government has usurped our power. The… https://t.co/4awT0jomGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK OUT! During the #Lighting game against the Blue Jackets last night, a puck *JUST* misses #NBC Analyst Pierre M… https://t.co/wkP3Ix12LE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend a measly 2 hours looking at commercial real estate in Central Asia and Google Ad Services just fucking assu… https://t.co/5rGNeGBaz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinKahl @MaxBoot It was like me pitching to the 1927 Yankees and expecting to get a win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayakauf @NYC_Patch Amazon wasn't going to hire anyone from Queensbridge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 Good. Nice to see you first thing after I wake up. How are you and your family doing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vivka Grey bravely related her story of abuse by Zak Smith an hour ago. @MandyMorbid's strength is encouraging othe… https://t.co/MaUmTuwUmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta You have always been a straight shooter Greta. Can’t say that about everyone at Fox, but I can honestly say… https://t.co/6p2lEeH3Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rschooley I don’t know about tomorrow, but you may regret the Amazon packages that show up with MAGA merch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possible #BucksPV siting this morning! I haven't been in there for a while and @MinskysPizza is nearby 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Great American Popcorn Company in Galena, IL https://t.co/eS2ukEj6dg https://t.co/qFsAN9gSPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertStock6 @markusrayburns @herndo5 @ThatSportsPaige The situation matters most, if a girl is obnoxiously scream… https://t.co/nQ8xVWSPRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we enter into the household of God, we come to realize that the fragmentation of humanity and its agony grow f… https://t.co/kkIA33MIXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m aware I’m different ppl in Albany be looking at me like damn this nigga rocking pink vans yes nigga it’s more t… https://t.co/HpjQO7YwMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaeDowns @BikeNewton It sounds crazy if you don’t bike-commute, but if you do you know the best work days are… https://t.co/HK2L8XfPVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, #LeavingNeverland on @HBO might be the sickest, saddest doc I’ve ever seen. So many enablers - many stage paren… https://t.co/yWm7Sqzhot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSki521 @DXFlyers So you didn’t watch but will just make assumptions about wether or not the contact was intentional...ah ok hate on]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the little things...  Went to Goodwill the other day to drop off some donated clothes of mine, and I had to lo… https://t.co/YTZYTFWSxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will protest if he withholds info. @MoveOn @TomSteyer @womensmarch @UltraViolet @KremlinAnnex @IndivisibleTeam… https://t.co/SqmtpfPrXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s the baddest First Lady. Period. End of story. It’s not up for debate. 😍❤️ https://t.co/EOqXuFZcfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#spiritanimal #idetectnolies  #getintoit #pride Leave it to a black woman to make it plain. #yourloss @ Central Ind… https://t.co/mRpLMksZDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is such great news for Denver media. I am damn proud of @daveburdick and the rest of the Denverite crew, and I… https://t.co/0Q4NTxOhGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite @DIRECTVnow's DVR screwing up AGAIN, finally 24h later I can watch #DragRace. Watching the intros now ajd a… https://t.co/I8sGlDZSDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tax season is here and the best part you can use your refund for the purchase of your home. Don't waste it in nonse… https://t.co/fsYfdgaLD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1RealLori @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @RealSugarLily @GrampyAndGranny @45WeThePeople @busylizzie48 @HarrellRyan1 Amen 🙏]]></document></documents></author>