<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@doumindifi @Eevildebs @tronNYC @RepSwalwell @DHSgov You we're lucky to be born in the US where freedoms, rights, a… https://t.co/0iQTSFvoaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puppybreff annoyed you don’t live in Michigan because after reading this I realize we are one of the same kind haha ❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBL_Peyton leading CBG teachers as they prepare to “sprint” today. @ccps_gifted #CBGAcademies #empowerment… https://t.co/eKAzXxdVUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’m addicted to @NBA2KMobile ! Reminds me of when I got my #gameboy as a teen and couldn’t put #Tetris down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math &amp; Sci instructional coaches learning to use the @ThePocketLab sets purchased by @jasonmerik through a… https://t.co/fTQTaQdrOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Republicans such as yourself have already sold your soul to the devil as you cont… https://t.co/fATSgCOD06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leesheriff @brycherrera1 Don't sweep this under the rug, a crime was committed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsfanmurph1 @RealJessAmore I really would. I’d scare the piss out of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread by @SethAbramson: "I'm confused. After we learned that the Bush Administration lied about WMDs, progressives… https://t.co/MnvDkBdUr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielkrow1 @USYankee1776 @curt_quin @804StreetMedia @RepWilson @realDonaldTrump @jemelehill How funny😃. There's n… https://t.co/zLe72aKIn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge shout-out to @HydroOne field crew who were out in blizzard conditions today restoring our power! 🔌👨‍🏭🌨️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biggest shout outs to @united and Mariott for helping me get rebooked to get to @CareerLeadershp Forum in Chicago today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AlexMair_ @seventhsonbrew I missed you being here!!  Ass Cat was like ‘where’s the guy with the car hair??’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@findthesocial @RoscaAlexander @KeatonStromberg @TommyHorrock You guys did amazing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember your personal power.  #Smile and help the world get a little more #happy too. @FeliceCohen @carenglasser… https://t.co/FFMA69aJMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me driving in all of this rain today #Imgettingthereinonepiece #Safetyfirst https://t.co/psjzR4RuAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelainlouky Happy to bring the right WOMAN to take my place! Let your voice be heard! #L1C4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Roberto Padilla for being recognized by Education Week as a 2019 Leader to Learn From… https://t.co/aeBVKsjpHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any one else remember falling asleep with the tv on when you were younger and walking up at 2 am to the George Lope… https://t.co/EFgAbKKOmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[decided to go to park city Utah just because we can ✌🏻🏂 • #kidswhosnowboard #girlswhosnowboard #snowboarding… https://t.co/IzPPkPDPzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a future teacher, I would much rather stay with a kid until there parent is able to pick them up than have them… https://t.co/zY45t8tPVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiveSeven99 @SenateGOP Please remit to me directly - I'll send it in - promise.  🙃🙂🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @WNHS_Wrestling for a great day. Euton, Potterf and Goldsmith earned 1st! #WarriorStrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Essence It was epic! Definitely will go down as one of the great wins!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought a cute ass pair of boots, can’t wait for them to arrive on my work week. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorLorenz @real_farmacist There probably is but I doubt you’d like it. 🤐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LourinOnTV @KristenLoweTV @joecharlevoix @girlscouts @upnorthlive @MaraThompsonTV @annmarie_kent They must've came… https://t.co/gHfXW1CM5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta Again, you’ve gone too far.  Even departed conservationists can’t escape your self-righteous criticism. I don… https://t.co/uFv64yYeNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rideamc OMG I don't think I could have handled goat tongue, but maybe would like to have been the goat that kissed Norman]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going to show the PG parts of Get Out.  This is why @blackishabc is so damn good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect #FBF and #internationalwomensday post ———————————————— Last year @ciroc @followemve @iamMaddieMey honor… https://t.co/HeqMIt9gaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[☘️ L U C K  O F  T H E  I R I S H 🇮🇪  . . ➡️ FOLLOW @lauracristinax (me) for more! 🥰 . . ‼️ New posts every single… https://t.co/qmcap93vIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexhortdog95 @KETV Now you see why I don't want to return to omaha,  THE SNOW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-Whale Watching Pit Stop 🐳💙🍻💙🐳🍻💙🐳🍻 #socallife #greywhales #turks #danapointharbor  #iwasntdrivingtheboat #cheers… https://t.co/R18V7QqCu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen Bro. Amen. Bless u Nero. Heres one for u this morning. Listen to How GREAT THOU ART..m4a by Queen Regina #np o… https://t.co/bDNOfH3FGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since people were asking, any disciplinary fine “must be paid to the State Treasurer for deposit in the State Gener… https://t.co/OunLS3Omvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DucksForDuckGod @JbkJbk1234 And all of that being said, I do acknowledge that a lot of this does (likely unintenti… https://t.co/qlirnukUGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBloomberg Mr Mayor, There has been a threat to Rapper 50 Cent by Emmanuel Gonzalez, Commander of the 74th Prec… https://t.co/nOmIZksIVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow and the @GOP is more comfortable with that than they were when a solid respectable patriotic black man was… https://t.co/2TR0xrPPWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in high school pretending I slept through all my alarms when my mom came in my room to wake me up to go school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouTelano Bought my copy after seeing Mark Levin interview Sydney on his Fox TV show.  Can't put it down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendagarrido16 @drugrift Brown eyes are the best in my opinion! Your eyes are a lovely and look sweet like carame… https://t.co/TrhCpEhCSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shay_da_bess @TheMedicalShots @noguava 😭 Beyoncé round here literally snatching edges 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just preordered Papa D's new book! I am so freaking excited! #MAGA #QANON #QARMY #DRAINTHESWAMP #PATRIOTFAMILY… https://t.co/dcC8s4gEZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im actually about to freak the fuck out on the IRS if they don’t hurry up with my tax return]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jonpardi #burningmantour2019 #Fresno he was sick. Me too @ Save Mart Center https://t.co/BVhmJ2llnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonallendc I liked all of them except The Favourite. I really liked BlackKklsnsman a lot. Liked Vice the first tim… https://t.co/wU4uVbnTx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Good morning, anyone around for a Red Bull? Coffee isn’t strong enough today.” https://t.co/GViQkLdRpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinHart4real Wow. How talented. 👁🖋🖌 His artwork is absolutely amazing! That looks like a photo 📸 of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Spring asserts itself, my tongue is drinking in a winter wonderland - thick, spicey and celebratory - Drinking a… https://t.co/I5Dw1NDnZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon!   Pottery Barn decor.  #comingsoon #realestate #realtorlife #scituatema #scituatemarealestate… https://t.co/jMHok91P7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a two-hour delay today! ❄️ Only got to sleep an extra hour because, well, kids 🤷🏻‍♀️, but I’ll take it!  .… https://t.co/xrzSllFZFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boys just told me there’s no “bro code” in 7th grade and they can date each other’s exes lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emeldas_shoes Thanks , but I really don't need to fill my H dreams anymore . LoL that's why I can't read any fanfi… https://t.co/WjJCy4UM0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyFieri found you a great dive to visit: Tom Jenkins ft Lauderdale Florida. Amazing food. Very authentic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 WOW... THKS T-PALS  YOUR ALL MY  OBSESSION  OF SMILES!! I WISH I COULD GET  PAID  BY  TWEETS WE WOULD A… https://t.co/KBjoMx09yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK GOD  FOR UNANSWERED PRAYERS! Sometimes God answers our prayers not by giving us what we want but by challengi… https://t.co/kEs7jGEvSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @morgfair Mitch McConnell is a despicable disgrace. He has allowed all this corruption to exist. He i… https://t.co/NZYt6auig3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air max 97 silver bullet $170  -size 11 in men’s https://t.co/41jCod9AsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the plane heading back home 💖. Thanks to all my beautiful people for a blast trip!  . Vuelta a casa después de u… https://t.co/QF5i61Y4JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have great freebies for you! Free Cellphone! Free Tablet PC! Free Smartwatch! All for FREE! https://t.co/8Avc6XWf0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin @StaceyPlaskett @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Sis don’t play ‼️🙌🏾‼️🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[your people, your environment, your time start to look a little different when you start to value yourself a little… https://t.co/2mje4YAmWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuban Cigar Manafort Russian Collusion meeting held in Kushner's 666 Park Ave building]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taniapdx @thehill Ha, I just noticed you claim to be British. Why on earth are you on here stumping for Bernie? Do… https://t.co/SqEBtogci1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every meeting we have I fall in lil bit more in love with this company and everything it stands for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hollywood can solve anything. Except its own lack of creativity and diversity--Homer Simpson #TheSimpsons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nino_triqui @ChairoMexicano Jajaja yo lo que quiero saber ! Es quien sostenía el cartel que leyó !!😂🤣😜 pobre chica dorada !🤪😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimStoran Hi Jim, we have vast experience in mobile app development and would be happy to assist you. Sent email f… https://t.co/qJdBEH91U4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This class is filled with those who are principled, generous, expressive, perceptive, engaging, and spontaneous!  T… https://t.co/3m9lCH3XoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Operational Risk Consultant 5 - Wells Fargo Securities Operations Shared Services… https://t.co/2XOb8XEgn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im planning a wedding and now a baby shower lord help me lmfao !!!!!! I’m so excited with work, school and all this… https://t.co/9tHADpxHT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ɛʋɛʀʏ ֆʊռֆɛȶ ɨֆ ǟռ օքքօʀȶʊռɨȶʏ ȶօ ʀɛֆɛȶ PC: @dawnvgilmore @ Malibu, California https://t.co/hXpNJsJTVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[También acompañada de dos caballeros a los cuales les tengo una tremenda admiración y respeto, a mi izquierda Eduar… https://t.co/HmJabh3C9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you to everyone who has reached out to me following my tweet about what I’ve been dealing with for a long tim… https://t.co/0vzUNsUfRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna see State Champs so bad next month but I have training for work 😭😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job is now open at CVS Health in #LasVegas, NV. Follow us and turn on mobile alerts to hear about jobs like th… https://t.co/2VVaC7wD3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my lord. After sobbing about this while FaceTiming @alexgrace99 she texted me this morning with THE greatest new… https://t.co/tmWkM3htb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle ever talk about @potus has chosen FOREIGN #INDIA  visa workers over American workers?  How @potus pr… https://t.co/XAB6gWSy89]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Conference Championship time with @KCXCTF ! Good luck team! Let’s go get em ! #GoFire #KnoxProud 🔥🏃🏼‍♀️🏃🏽‍♂️💨 https://t.co/eWq8HfKZVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/tVpO8vmaTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Girbeagly It’s stupid high school bullshit, you wanna go get french fries in a hotel lobby one night you know wher… https://t.co/tZKHXXdUTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKeithBritt @TrumpTrains600 @RL9631 @Juju_rja @nancy_hamm1 @OrenIShiKiddo @barkmartin @BrendaNord5 @R3Thorns… https://t.co/6Jv7QnzUQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexican night! I love the food, tastes good 😋 #mexicanfood #tacos #enchiladas #raspberrymargarita #foodstagram… https://t.co/Vhk0Bgiurv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliverdan @kethlenkareng Se eu não brigar pra comer e ir dormir não sou eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are a badass and a patriot &amp; blessed to be your friend ❤️ @DrChrisMetzler and]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol is this from the same court that also found Jacob Anderson not guilty??? y’all should know Waco is trash af and… https://t.co/4KFI3RO6jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have little brothers so getting to talk to Joes two little brothers while we’re in town makes me feel so co… https://t.co/jEJHmsSFjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 #BalanceforBetter #getgutsy Here to be inspired! https://t.co/V8WBBTJaLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimsDnc @vmingist Why u sad?!?...🤭 Sorry I had to.. Awww...they're so cute 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaBruce616 But yes! A lot of good talent this year. #AmericanIdol is a lot better than The Voice again!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[37. How to: heart to heart energy healing routine; 02/27/2019 YDCtv 💙  https://t.co/gdawKRsqkX… https://t.co/hVX0QW0BiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lame_media @CoryBooker Because in America it’s easier to blame the black man!  Trumps done nothing to correct anyt… https://t.co/g3Cv54Ryoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[But really though..I need him to kill the spiders for me. No bueno on the eight legged creatures from hell in the b… https://t.co/gO3iP6sb2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the person that stoled my package from amazon enjoy it. I hope you know how to bake. #amazon #peopleareshit… https://t.co/mr8Briu1vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you #Love someone for over #25Years and are actually family and blood relatives with this person who wasn’t a… https://t.co/xjTe64uP6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDXToddDiskin Now reading about Team Hawaii, who after a year of poor attendance moved to Tulsa Oklahoma, in what… https://t.co/wBl6oUnwZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we can adapt and be contented like St Paul, we are always joyful. Through the carrying of our daily cross, we… https://t.co/31eNk1tzV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy! Why is this just coming to light? This is sad and disgusting. No wonder the Russians are blackmailin… https://t.co/BzBNemv8sU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do you want to bring me back a glass of water from Denny’s?... I own who I am” @aka_barbraJ]]></document></documents></author>