<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GaryParrishCBS Some people apparantly believe Duke is somehow unbeatable but also not as good as everyone says. Th… https://t.co/decZWPurnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski What a cute name.. Thats because you keep them exercised. Dad is 87 and STLL plays a good game of tenni… https://t.co/2eENLNSyIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“let’s make a documentary to ruin michael jackson’s legacy because it fits our narrative” https://t.co/WvOdrIISua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bringbackfear @BetterBrainsB @crashpalace @Dismay00 @12nighthorror @MsChaunceyKR @PromoteHorror @JustEm_78… https://t.co/Lp5WDrqDc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be prepared for a couple days of windy conditions in @Ptbo_Canada as gusts of 100kph possible this afternoon, 90kph… https://t.co/5oZBIktJ6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstory: NPR is doing a segment on Anger. My story begins with 14 day hospitalization from Sepsis, Diabetic Ketoa… https://t.co/v3325KeUzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old Dodge in Williamsburg, BK. Shot with the Nikon F2a &amp; @Kodak Gold 200 film - pushed. https://t.co/8Qp5DqE32W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc730 @leighsales @Bowenchris Bowen is misleading ..a person with only dividend income of $65/- receives a franki… https://t.co/djRKxfiOLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAGA people are good law abiding ppl that police each other and would prevent or banish anyone that misbehaves. It… https://t.co/4m5x8NW7cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite @brianstelter He had a Dem Strategist. He had a Dem Representative. Oh and the president of media matters… https://t.co/GHPUxPDjy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pfrumors That would be stupid!! These Teams GMs need to know how to build a roster instead of a Name!!  Bell reall… https://t.co/7jgArsjtJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually enjoy going lighter sometimes. Feel a better burn... my opinion. #gym #gymshark #gymmotivation #fit… https://t.co/AzvRRNjswQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hiereus @amandabarren No, his 6 NBA championship rings will take care of that. Championships stand the test of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinlieberman I accept this endorsement though I know I can’t live up to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING Lowndes County Coroner Greg Merchant has identified the victim of the #Columbus tornado as 41-year-old Ash… https://t.co/t16Dl3uEho]]></document><document><![CDATA[This explains why @IlhanMN and @TheDemocrats ramped up the hate rhetoric]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone else feel like everyone can hear what you’re listening to through your headphones when you’re in public or is that just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then we get to shoot for some of our favorite peeps and tonight it’s for Kyshona Armstrong who is pla… https://t.co/jbSeG9SOZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as the Cavs end up top 4, you can’t go wrong with Barrett, Reddish or Morant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BryantUniv students...did you hear 👂 the 1st 5️⃣0️⃣0️⃣ of you get one of these t-shirts at tomorrow nights… https://t.co/8642YQ3fDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredDudley619 @AB84 Act like a little baby back bitch and get what you want... sounds exactly like how things are… https://t.co/jL2j6ng29S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was suppose to do hw after my game today but my team had other plans.... 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrightRain @projectedxyz @geogiroux @Spatial_Punk @billdollins @Brian_Bancroft @pcrickard Even slicker would be Pr… https://t.co/N4IfsTnHnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/x8luBQ6EYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[End Q1: West Washington 14, Crothersville 7. Cable Spall gets one at the buzzer for CHS. https://t.co/S7XaXD39vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kool &amp; The Gang - Slick Superchick https://t.co/PUY6GeAtog via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsea__landis 😂 “Young lady whom I have yet to meet: please be God, Jesus and Holy Spirit to me. Anything less,… https://t.co/WjXu7H4Cx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avindiolap Ese es un problema que tengo. Soy muy rápido al hablar siempre y como docente es donde me ha provocado… https://t.co/0a26H55PZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simmonds17 I hope 🤞 you’re a @NHLFlyers player for life, but if not, thank you and good luck! #StadiumSeries]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancer is a lifestyle and mitochondrial disease. Live a life so you and your family never get it. . . #bluelight… https://t.co/AlDoXWsqdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @girlscouts It did not help her much because she is dumb as a stump. #aocisdumbasastump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaellopez gets an early K for @ClarkeBaseball #Pride 0-0 vs Baker t2 @NAIABall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I hope this young man’s ok. I don’t think it’s funny at all! 😡. That’s somebody’s son!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five benefits of volunteering from the D-fam family @WestHillsMS! 1. Helping other people  2.  Helping the communit… https://t.co/psy6HT1XuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[4/3/17: Raw after Mania in Orlando wouldn’t let him talk 2/25/19: Raw in Atlanta can’t wait to hear to him speak. #Raw #RomanReigns]]></document><document><![CDATA[SF Yang Gang out here at Sunday Streets in the Mission! #Yang2020 #HumanityFirst https://t.co/KyiRI3utxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soybean Oil: Lurking Danger in Processed Foods https://t.co/apCaO8sNXy https://t.co/kj5r53Digy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schlaf @joinpursuit Yes! @JukayHsu is the man!! https://t.co/MYFZ2T3O1t cc @MaddeyTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, serial rapist Ben Rothlisberger likes to aggressively exercise power over those he thinks are beneath him? Shocker! #Steelers #NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s make a list of Democratic Presidential Emergencies  Gun Control  Increasing the Minimum Wage Climate Change… https://t.co/kPNhcr54fc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStateOfTheU These people would be out thousands of dollars because of things they’ve already booked. I believe… https://t.co/d8SdJLBcH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was more of a VH1 Top 20 countdown before school and a 106 &amp; Park after school kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For the Private service jobs he could have taken instead of helping the United States will it's af… https://t.co/vDDjlNl2UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished watching @PrimeVideo “Breaking the Chain”, anxiously awaiting the ancient Native American teachings,… https://t.co/0xMLmPeE9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored for the opportunity today @aba_baseball to speak to the @erie_baseball HS team from Colorado about how to h… https://t.co/EqOQalW96n]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s now 30 straight conference road wins for Gonzaga. All the Zags do is win and yet no one wants to talk about… https://t.co/ZvLj8scjYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Michael left it wasn’t the same anymore. Still funny but not the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm interested in attending this #VR event in @AltspaceVR. Join me? https://t.co/5swL4wcYVF @AndrewWilliam23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Millions were never pouring in, schmookums.   Are you off your meds again, schnookums?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaylamccann @MarieCLuby There are wonderful track maintenance people all over the world. Get them together. Bring… https://t.co/w3N9HwNsKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTru1222 @Manning4USCong @KamalaHarris @MomsDemand I get the idea but it doesn’t apply to the scenario though. It’… https://t.co/byzQC9vVMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta 80% kill shelters? Kidnapping dog out of houses and yard to kill them. Shut up commies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 60 of 365  The look on your face when you have been cutting back on dining out then you get a craving for tacos… https://t.co/mwzizdyifE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2KSupport hey 2k support. I recently bought a PS4 pro and I’m trying to transfer my 2k data to my knew one but Eve… https://t.co/N9fsetnUMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantMyers44 @PickensHighGa @pickensad @chris_parker222 Congrats Coach. You will be great!! GATA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunchtime (@ Auburndale Main Street Diner in Auburndale, FL) https://t.co/ONYDUFTkIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This vlog about nothing goes through a different style for each of my type of videos hope you all enjoy and prepare… https://t.co/kWsZ0CHldP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to this hard working group of young ladies! #hardworkpaysoff #theyLift @johnpacheco34 https://t.co/GGDBI9CzAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake ass content 🙄 hey Miranda Lambert got married and Katy Perry got engaged!! How about you talk about that inste… https://t.co/gByNUeNyld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alliedarling07 @CornerBakery What’s wrong with McDonald’s? You eat Chick Fil A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephensonLance Was the biggest all-star snub once again. Sad! 😭🏀  #Goat https://t.co/LK3QV1GBiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like this Bruins team. Grab another scorer or two and your a legit contender]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmorelli This is when The City finally started deprioritizong the car, we have a way to go, yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDonBacon You voted for the tax scam for the wealthy that blew our debt up substantially. Stay in your lane when… https://t.co/d289fuDbOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[some people are so blinded by their entitlement to their own opinions that they forget to respect the opinions of others]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undergradwoman @HouseForeign His family thanks you. Your country however thinks you’re a pathetic excuse for an Am… https://t.co/ZOoRWBfHz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RespectableLaw I'll do you one better:  George Farmer and Candice Owens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliteuser26 A light dusting of snow barely a cm.. before the ice pellets arrived lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine jigsaw. #wineglass #redwine #winebar #winetasting #princeofwine @ Downtown Long Beach-East Village Arts Distri… https://t.co/qflGUbo3lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crfeldman @SiobhanFTB @elizabethweill This is remarkably hot garbage, what an asshole. “I can’t talk about it but… https://t.co/XGQfh3gA8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yandreaya how would you like one of these: Legend of Zelda Master Sword Letter Opener | ThinkGeek https://t.co/AFGeCJKadA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe because he’s an authoritarian, murderous psychopath. What the hell is wrong with Trump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Dios nunca ha revocado este mandato: "Y Dios les dijo:" Sean fructíferos y multiplíquense y llenen la tierra y som… https://t.co/KED5N4y2hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[friend: what do you look for in a relationship ?                                             me:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where honor and appraisal have to be spoken, it’s always ok. @PokemonGoApp and @NianticHelp learnt from all previou… https://t.co/CQPbV2UuYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @AmBeachy If a public employee has difficulty doing the assigned job, that employee should resign or… https://t.co/KGtb6ARivE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwest *Happy Friday* Hudson! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/7VDp7FnKlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great walk to Indian Ladder Falls with the family! Not pictured: Nana, sitting snugly by the fire. #nanas85th… https://t.co/xP7QF208P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President they should’ve asked you to help build the railroad you could’ve send your children… https://t.co/KSZnx7buTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive never felt more driven in my life. I’ve come along way beating depression and all my addictions. I’m excited to… https://t.co/WrpeC24GhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardThe3rrrd Hmmmm, not really. I think we remember things vividly when we're very young because they're new. So… https://t.co/JqisfRr3mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, I dont have to drink to have a good time. But, bloody hell, it helps 🥃 https://t.co/2NW4mr0bcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehojo This coming from a guy that doesn’t know the first thing about meteorology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyHarvey @MarthaStewart Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/Ajvb8tF22M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday Night Crew 🔥#martinibardoral @djkaosmusic @djrzspinz @djoz305 @joey_tracks @ Martini Bar Doral https://t.co/eXibdfEpCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[PINK ON BLACK🎟... YEA JUST LEAVE THEM LIKE THAT⚡️ . . . . . #adidas #adidasshoot #julianwilliamsactor… https://t.co/PBs6mWMEWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dougs1978 @BreitbartNews Of course they are litigation is something they love and something that is destroying this nation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenrodrick I thought you were going to say a AAA guide that only rated Hampton Inns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna tweet the lyrics to All Star but I was watching on silent and hadn’t realized the song was in it😂 this… https://t.co/HjCeE5lcvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. I genuinely feel dirty right now. And if you know me at all, it takes A LOT for that to happen https://t.co/6VRLCh5H41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love love love my nephew!! I’ll be there in 3 weeks Em!! #emmetnorman @ New Center, Detroit https://t.co/fiiXY0BXPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #afl team in Columbus will get a name at 11:30 am today. https://t.co/cCtJ1hjfWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano He died dummy that’s how he’s gone. It will happen to all of us the bright and the dumb like you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consider this the official petition to have @Interpol play “Leif Erikson” tonight at @TheGarden! Please and thank you in advance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado Heard he's in the high limit room playing 100 dollar wheel of fortune.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to explore Monterrey, Mexico 🇲🇽 while in town for a wedding 💒 👰 🎩 👏🏻 https://t.co/kjLFIADHFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMadison Well you couldn’t let the fries go to waste that would just be wasteful]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish more American soccer fans watched more than EPL and Champions League.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At each Present Moment,  I AM either a student,  a teacher or a lesson... https://t.co/sI585Pk3Hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @newbelgium crew and @goodbeerhunting were all celebrating with @beerkulture tonight. I’m a little jealous of ev… https://t.co/OlE1dRtw0t]]></document></documents></author>