<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cynthiaDboo I already quit! But now I’m just broke and bored so I’m praying for this job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please  vote ❤️ for this kid!  He is not only a phenomenal athlete, he is a phenomenal person!]]></document><document><![CDATA[pet peeve: when people use their instagram as a shrine for their relationship with their s/o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great work to our 2018-2019  #MorrisJays BEST Students of the Week, Week 20! Great job showing Bondurant's BEST!… https://t.co/84BgNAixkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Though the earth may try, to tell me You're not faithful Though the earth may try, to blind me from Your goodness You shine through]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking about baby teeth  @caro_bridges : I still haven’t lost all my baby teeth.   Me: really?! Your only supposed… https://t.co/lUfCN4nwgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No abortion is just a distraction issue. Please resign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’re basing our belief in a higher power based on atrocities that occur then faith in anything should be 0.....… https://t.co/Ke33bXf7Ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st STORM WARNING of year for @lakeeriesball in Florida!  Excited to see all their hard work in game action startin… https://t.co/M2c9LLWVgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Rent: Indiana's Iconic, But Languishing, House of Tomorrow: @atlasobscura https://t.co/diErwvOC02]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet men and women are equal in sexual jealousy in the following way: They are equally jealous of men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to find an amazing Dr. for my breast reduction... I’m over this lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Misinterpreted??  He was speaking English.  We speak English.  🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@featTerry @aimeeclarke It’s like mourning the loss of a best friend in a way]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could “laugh” at things on Twitter like I can on Facebook honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @nrginnovations for the new bling   #safetyfirst #bling #racing #offroad #style @nrgoffroad https://t.co/T6PSb78Czq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dor de cotovelo: temos.   (Culpa da bengala e andar um monte com ela hoje)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrowJackson34 @EdgeDaDon718 Yeah that’s a strange one to bother a broad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning to love myself has been extremely difficult. All my life I was  made to feel like I was not enough; was no… https://t.co/bni5KxnZm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urbanbushwoman9 @MadalynSklar I learn something in pretty much every tweet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSIWX @wanewx @wxnewsdesk Yes, unfortunately I didn't think to take an exact measurement with a ruler while I was… https://t.co/kEejJjliLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eltonofficial #EltonFarewellTour was able to snap a rare shot! Lexi was just telling me a story about when rock wa… https://t.co/BBKygduq8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you deserve to be sitting around people who love and care about you and I have to be here alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theslumflower When reading self help books I generally skip around and read chapters that apply to me only.  Why?… https://t.co/MQHbZ7SPGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call to Worship @ The Salvation Army of Staten Island https://t.co/Rvtf2VfTsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is sooo Punky! 🐾❤️@pdorsey #labradorretriever #shesneverfull #Punky #therapydog #Dogs #CounterSurfer]]></document><document><![CDATA[these lines are so much better than the ones heading into a music festival #lmnl @ Onedome https://t.co/lE8gqmBB9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The closet cases who support gays at least ostensibly, but feel there is something wrong with them personally being… https://t.co/oyGHRpDYLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris NO we are not flourishing we are sliding into the pit of debt, desperation and the sewer of piss and… https://t.co/EvstHiUoG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHave4Testiclez 😭😭 why are we like this 😭 “cross me once it’s 🖕🏽 YOU” &lt;— the accuracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSSacramento It’s the CDF CYA Camp theory. Pine Grove still operates one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 You really are a POS. You don't threaten family .]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so lucky to have Ms. Charles as part of our faculty. How amazing is she!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatLakesHello @TorontoLouise @triviainsfire Where exactly did I say I need uninterrupted sleep? I personally don… https://t.co/qlnWKn7Udl]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP leaders called the budget a “liberal wish list.” Many disagree with legalizing possession of 25 grams of weed]]></document><document><![CDATA[021619 The snow did not seem to bother this vermin at the Field Club Golf Course in Omaha, Nebraska. @ Field Club O… https://t.co/bzfx5JKaU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 books in 7 days, challenged by @MonaLisaLvsHeah. I'm sharing 7 covers of books I ❤️, w/ no explanation-Day 7-“Sno… https://t.co/Pd9nbDgTuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CloudFloofLizrd Been there. My mom didn’t like it when I let my eldest go rock wall climbing. https://t.co/erSEWnZr6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#karaoke night usjbruins 🐾 spaceykacey this girl may be your biggest fan!! Hope she did you justice 😉Everyone did s… https://t.co/9ftMUG5kPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also supposed to keep raining for another few days, so yeah this town may end up in bad shape after this :/ pl… https://t.co/SLrPrmZ1om]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all those struggling with their mental health, whether it be anxiety, depression, PTSD, or any other mental diso… https://t.co/MTy8oLV455]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @StormyDaniels, hope all your shows are going well. Whatcha watchin'? #TeamStormy 🙌🏽💅🏽s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASjanedavis This was during MTSS and it was one of my homeroom students. She made me laugh in front of the who cl… https://t.co/1OLSVd1QDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Kicking off #WomensHistoryMonth with the @JLWilmingtonDE Women’s Leadership Summit. @SarahEMcBride shares her… https://t.co/MW0KYHQ5W6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t we just live like the reality tv stars... can I just get paid to hang out w family and friends... ugh 😑… https://t.co/ujv7pU8fcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now... Thousands of teachers marching on Annapolis asking lawmakers to fully find the  Kirwan Commission’… https://t.co/1s3B28mkwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[nation's 2.1 million farms receive subsidies, with the lion's share of the handouts going to the largest producers… https://t.co/LOnTtjk6C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harijati Good evening honey. It is cold here. Dixie is all tucked in asleep. Have a wonderful day ♥️ https://t.co/q9CQRNEYhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously the girls that work at the Englewood @Starbucks in front of Meijer are absolutely amazing! Some of the sw… https://t.co/M2WG9tGcB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't profit off of how other people perceive you. I get it you're trying to have fun, but what you're posting as "… https://t.co/SbarxUzVQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It shows her in the morning, getting ready, her hair, what little she has of it, is sticking straight up from her h… https://t.co/Ld5cPTgB7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystalchappell Awwww poor Buck... my little guy (dog) went thru depression when his sister died... got a new dog… https://t.co/PMA2smMZJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReynoldsburgBB just took the lead on a close one! Up 15-13 with 3:40 in second period]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSeriesAAA check your stats for 2009 division. NJ Rockets Black are 3-0 not 2-1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son and I love them! But it’s what cookie butter is made out of! And cookie butter and apple slices are sooo goo… https://t.co/dgzlUPIULW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @mschlapp You don't like Trump your prerogative.  BUT DON'T BULLY THE PEOPLE WHO DO. YOU HAVE NO B… https://t.co/CIOLLpITxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s getting me through this week? Knowing on Saturday I get Royal Tokyo. Also I get Filet Mignon tonigh… https://t.co/uKc5ehNmmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felix Auger-Aliassime. While the #Raptors regroup and redirect, this kid is doing it all and doing it brilliantly. #BNPPO19 #Tennis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump You are a despicable  human being, so very well characterized by the people you choose… https://t.co/ITHYo5KFGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in NOW to see @AmberMcReynolds of @voteathome talk about The Voting Experience live from D.C with the Bipartis… https://t.co/RFSX1ZOHkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EngineersWeek2019 at Liberty Elem SLD #paperplanes #firstgradeawsome Great designs but can they fly?  Oh yes they… https://t.co/0I7v0dw4rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k4_kindergarten Look at all these happy faces....my heart!! @k4_kindergarten @StJamesOCSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Going home. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/LQVx8K1Wtt via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger You however are under how many investigations including your finances, tax evasion,… https://t.co/iAUjEtFTej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building a chain reaction in K3 what fun we are having exploring cause and effect @burntelmps @PeelSchools https://t.co/jtUIuqgB4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebration with friendly people at parcrittenhouse on my “most favorite “ list. #celebration #parc #eat #vaca @ Pa… https://t.co/jWLaVtZhVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do’s and Don’ts brought to you by MARINA your Realtor and Friend...I’m here to serve and California Association of… https://t.co/Va9vdTx5Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t @dustinlynch ever get nominated! He works so damn hard &amp; for it not to get recognized! Really! It makes me mad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House Date:  Saturday, March 9, 2019, Time: 11:00 to 4:00, Address 1131 Strong Drive. @ Rancho Charleston, Las… https://t.co/FBOi77704K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missvorn_ this girl at school I asked one simple question! Lol https://t.co/6eOoq6josj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agraybee @kweansmom My stepfather was driven out of Soho, as a millinery manfacturer, to Williamsburg. He eventual… https://t.co/WhiuLZhOBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a business woman. I do not use instagram as a dating website. I use instagramforbusiness . Please respect my D… https://t.co/FcuOgvtJWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imaginez si c'était un boycott des familles anglicanes ? Les merdias se déchaîneraient sur ces derniers.… https://t.co/YIpQv8ux4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marge Carson @ Mustard Seed Furniture Consignment https://t.co/1b2CA3Y0Ri]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s about taking the opportunity to get to the difficult conversations. #NotInMySchool https://t.co/BIGh2nYnC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam! 2 releases you need 2 listen to on this New Music Friday: @SuperDuper808’s EP Vessels https://t.co/7jgPLqq0yv… https://t.co/nGekWwdWQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the holidays are over,this is so beautiful,i wanted to post it 😊😀😆 https://t.co/97tv3YwSYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alisand3 Will you Write up an FEC Complaint/Investigation For Foul Mouth, Disrespectful Rashica Tlaib WE HAVE A VO… https://t.co/w7InNec9Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dog_feelings I thought I was your valentine! You’re allowed more than one, I’m sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen 2 beautiful people on a screen at the same time?   #TheBachelor just did that.   Colton &amp; Ben 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HNIBonline @MassHSHockey @In_The_Slot end of 2 @AustinPrepGHoc leads 4-0 over Hanover NH. Saracco, Taber, Cioffi a… https://t.co/108MAZgoGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wkyc @Robinswoboda @maureenkyle @holliesmiles The morning looks brighter already!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CowxGolf @worldcenter What an incredible thing to say!! Thank you so much David! Honored!!😊⛳]]></document><document><![CDATA[#knixsecretshow #knixben #knixbrooke Had a great time last night. @ Marquee Theatre https://t.co/VUkn3NUt7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍋🍋  Eyes: All brushes used @MorpheBrushes  P Louise base in shade rumor 2  P Louise secret sinner palette… https://t.co/FpRU5gy61p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas swear they don’t fuck w a bitch... then y’all break up &amp; what do know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what I’d do if Hunter didn’t stick by my side through everything, he’s really my best friend🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[So are you proud of me that I didn’t drop any f bombs last night, @TheCartelMatt? 😆😆😆 #WeAreCartel @ValhallaMomma… https://t.co/yEaTaTLNxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping Dream Chasers: Social Justice with @MeekMill and Michael Rubin. #SSAC19 https://t.co/iTdED3tbRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Adult #ChubbuckGang was rev'd, ready and eager to show #FilmMaker Mr. @chncyjcksn what the #Southeast has to offer… https://t.co/YjD1yTgTFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@va_nessa92 @annaandmitch @taylovessarah13 @bflygirl133 @lyssalovesswift @adiamariemusic @AStilettos… https://t.co/9Zj5PEKBjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m getting up and getting ready wherever the wheel takes me that’s where I’m eating at 😂 pho sounds good but at the same time jacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was deaf from my left ear bc I couldn’t hear clearly when I had my earphones on. After trying my extra… https://t.co/9AKxumREhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took like an hour nap. My daughter still sleep so I’m about to go back to sleep too lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former White House Senior Advisor and Amazon Web Services Leader Frank DiGiammarino Joins Booz Allen | Business Wire https://t.co/ra12bAPt3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darreldrowland He's pathetic.  I hope we can redistricting his butt out of there after the census.  He's deplorable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kybballking @HardenRoger @TotallyTwitched You all should watch a game with me and my posse!! You might learn something!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You madame......are crack'd Ethics for who?  What gives you the right to dictate ethics to anyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/G7P60SpDSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh!!!! My brother just texted me about this and was like we’re going for you bday!!! So excited, always wanted to… https://t.co/nbQTxOSSI8]]></document></documents></author>