<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HaedonMeyer @kylamb8 Funny, their non scorers must be better players.  They are a guaranteed player in the tourney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patriot_amer @SenFeinstein Excellent retort..I am sure ur4 followers r cheering u on..I do read and watch the news… https://t.co/nnF7C0NjmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dressed to impress for the Obama Dinner.  Congrats to all the winners last night!   @coloradodems #ObamaDinner https://t.co/veoJZPEYI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@page88 Otherwise Blameless is now an all-time phrase ...  Inside the Beltway justice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was my handle back in 1993 on the internet. #StardogChampion  https://t.co/bVe93S5A1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABathingApeUS Disregard.... Was less but after double checking not nearly that much..... Keep it up Bape Fam💎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cody_a_hill @DustinMulvaney @SaveTheDesert What's the NRI process? And to your knowledge is there any sort of exis… https://t.co/6UkwGd37d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @alejandrosanz •  •  •  •  • ¿Cuántas veces hemos deseado un cuento sin final?  @saulquiros @casalimonmusic… https://t.co/rwGjY7G6pz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salyers_maryana Haha! Good one!   Breaking news! Jussie Smollett is now a suspect. I am waiting for @KamalaHarris… https://t.co/j8AjAFAQCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carl Rutherford is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $299.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a… https://t.co/tnuhNfBIgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That off &amp; on because a mothafucka don’t know right from wrong shit intolerable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @benshapiro @AOC We’re all gonna die anyways,  might as well piss some libs off in the process!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg DWS is still in office?  Yikes @FoxNews @CNN @TuckerCarlson #tucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fence companies stock tomorrow. @darrenrovell we need numbers. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nights now that Overwatch League is back 👌🏾 #OWL #NYXL @ Sunnyvale, California https://t.co/uchSBA3Jdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baabybean How the hell is that okay?? I’m trying to understand. I can’t even leave faith alone unless Leslie is there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thuggin wit my shorties @ Northeast Houston, Houston, Texas https://t.co/6Ot2gl8QrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamvick They don’t know. But what the infectious disease doctor said it could be. And they are testing for. Sexually transmitted Zika.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeakBrewing Bummer. But I am planning a trip back home to Long Beach NY so will try it then. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[February was not a fun month. Really hoping March has better things in store. Will see how work turns out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is perfectly within her Constitutional authority to challenge the President on this.  Take some time and read i… https://t.co/4MbWr1XwUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lancer_WR 672 qualifiers. 336 place winners. 42 Champions.....out of over 5,000 wrestlers in the state.  You have… https://t.co/he2r8BuVxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the stone?!  #infinitywar @prevailactive  This cover will be available at @KimzarKollect… https://t.co/MKA2atWg33]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a rough day. Fell down and then went to class to realize I dropped my damn wax pen. Thankfully no one took it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Person called me yesterday and said "oh my goodness I love what you're doing, I'd love to partner up with you and d… https://t.co/7xcvwOdyPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geekmystic I've seen it a couple of times. It's not enjoyable, though it is interesting. Weird to see 2 attractive… https://t.co/GmPEetcAXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans frequently talk about the threat of "voter fraud." And polls show that the message is having an impact… https://t.co/dO2z7G7pNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevShark @DavidCrossUSAM @DougKass Who is blind of “others” everyone but white people? Haha! Rev I expected better… https://t.co/LzTrN1BlSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhenTheGoingGetsToughIAlways chew thoroughly before swallowing Jessica's cooking. https://t.co/Mxo0PCdLiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trvlady Um. You’re joking, right? There were days and days of hearings, and ultimately the House impeached him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Abaco to Nassau March Madness Continues tonight 7pm at Change Ministries Nassau @ Atlantis Paradise Island https://t.co/3tIYw0w2o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Let's see how much jail time you get for misaapropiation of campaign funds by you and your left wing nut boyfr… https://t.co/uk5yFPtHDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I purchased some wonderful winter stouts and ciders at @cbc_newton tonight, they could use our support during Austi… https://t.co/RrOEoQI4kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning first world gym probs... #stillfinishedmyset #stillputtheqorkin @ Elizabethtown, Kentucky https://t.co/ptpM3U2N6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LGBTQ: Kansas legislators offer potpourri of anti-LGBTQ bills to bar recognition of same-sex marriages, defined as… https://t.co/biTbZxa4fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the international commentators are up in the nosebleeds. #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @MTA advertising barrier to internet access is more offensive than that gum that sticks to your shoe. It was no… https://t.co/Klx2qQd7pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird....Missouri  In Marquette, it is illegal for more than 4 unrelated persons to occupy the same living space.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you constantly have to tell people and assure them how much of a real/honest person you are, you straight up lyi… https://t.co/T65sjvzcF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do seniors really need to take 3 AP classes? - “Stressed out: Anxiety a bigger concern for teens than drugs, povert… https://t.co/oXAG8705sT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allow myself to introduce myself to introduce.... myself #austinpowers @ Wildwood, Missouri https://t.co/jGYkwHA9E5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Firestone Walker Restaurant and Brewhouse https://t.co/dtOxSjWb7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OscarRunnerUp 1. Cooper 2. Dafoe - - - 3. Bale 4. Mortensen  5. Malek  Snubbed: John David Washington- Blackkklansman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang you, Emma Stone and Ryan Gosling, for making me feel things. #LaLaLandIsDelightful @RyanGosling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday boy is very excited for his first birthday breakfast date with Papa. Yes, is probably going to eat everyth… https://t.co/jzlJXji4vL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LairdsApplejack You had me at sage. The sage is a little small but it’s from my deck and the drink is delicious 😋… https://t.co/50gw5dlq4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right lmao dudes be hurt 😭 like foo she gotta have some hotties as friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellwetherdude @MikeFender5 @goldendoekd @EricJoh37288055 @arkiegal411 @JacobJMP2 @HTWells3 @Brown_EyedLadyJ… https://t.co/vamaXM8sXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday isn't for another five months but my dad bought me tickets to a Yankees vs Red Sox game at Fenway Park… https://t.co/z4Tg4Qlpv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miz_cracker My beautiful 73 year old mom.  Strongest and kindest woman I know. https://t.co/dJK8ALHqaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which innovation will bring the most impact to healthcare in 2019?  Answer here to win an @oculus GO!… https://t.co/7xvf6aCgvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular Opinion: Twitter needs to stop saying to vote for Bernie just because he has one h**l of a Sugarcoated-So… https://t.co/JLcQA71xta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliievrodr It is hard to learn to open up your heart again when you thought the first time it has happened it was real to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glendaboza @castillo321 @DiazCanelB Coñooooooo que rica la papa , sobretodo cuando no tienes con que acompañarla n… https://t.co/SwpoTsUg8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[All tied up at 1 after 40 in Adrian!! Up and down game so far and looking for the next goal to send us to the NCAA… https://t.co/yUX9wmfxd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in the bathroom and the woman in the stall next to me is sitting on the toilet hollering “SHIIIIIIIT”😳 I don’t… https://t.co/Y8yrWvtmj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was interviewed by @TheWallStreetJ today regarding my support for @realDonaldTrump during a visit to the 2020 Campa… https://t.co/k0dD6PVnQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnitaSchelde @AndZyberto Polecam peany o komunizmie autorstwa Pana @AndZyberto z lat 80tych. Bradzo ciekawa lektur… https://t.co/P36jxdeqsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Kole Porter by @BilobaBrewing at @bilobabrewing — https://t.co/W10abLZDCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubenol7 Necesariamente tengo que comparar, porque en lo personal lo que mas me molesta es la doble vara de medir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#levelup  #friyay #tgif  #fitness #jojosenergy #lifecoach #celebritytrainer #charlesjojotyleryoutubepage #yoga4soul… https://t.co/NrH7y2BMog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@applesirius77 @vidman @CTVKitchener Because that person is me and I still doing it, plus with a Kubota tractor, no… https://t.co/9hnX1BiaF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shirts are on the market now thanks @MyRacePass  and @JamieBall5J  for making this happen https://t.co/JQJ3JFdObW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction What a bunch of crap left action is . Everything Hannity says is true. You can’t refute his facts, so y… https://t.co/RBw3035wgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 17-0 run by @CalMBBall ends. Bears lead Stanford 19-5 with 11:58 left in the first half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KopelmanWX I live along the Cedar River Trail near Czech Village and saw lots of runners this evening around four thirty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[F*ck us we’re Irish #getnaked @ Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania https://t.co/XFbfnma5AH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump gets the same amount of the vote he got last time 46% and loses handily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a picture of me trying to keep up with @bobbybooshay216 📸: @OrvilleMPhotos @ Magnolia Cleveland https://t.co/9FvFi1Jo6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilvalle3 The whole staff is dogshit, just look at the clowns on this staff.  im convinced that the organization n… https://t.co/Q4Wg7C3qxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoccerCooligans Atlanta WooooooW😲 #NoPatience in the 🍑 state. https://t.co/AMEDRJra0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's time Mr President,,, arrest all of the traitors and tell them YOU'RE FIRED. It's not ISIS tha… https://t.co/EUMCWKRYpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlueFanatic4 Last time we played and y’all won the regular season matchup...Luke hit...never mind 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keenvol87 @SmokeyLowdown @BigOrangePruitt @SEC Look at the comments. https://t.co/iZbp7ahr1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[aprendi morando em outro pais que a unica pessoa que se importa comigo vai ta em absolutamente qualquer lugar que e… https://t.co/CiqQbdFxzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kKostyy Or even put a series of these out through MLBAM and focus on educating people about the game within the ga… https://t.co/bG4wWtJpTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a drive up to St. Jacobs to check in on our new table and to see some awesome stuff @timber_barn and… https://t.co/njyBbgd1o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#classicshow thank you @Robert_Townsend I hope you get your roses while you can still smell them for what you have… https://t.co/d84FsTYna4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolverfan Even more impressive is the fact that it took you more than 2 months to come up with your very insightfu… https://t.co/GBnU0zFkxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Liberals ignore real environmental problems like homeless on the street and force the public to focus on a weather cult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Center - @aacenter in Dallas, TX https://t.co/41IbqrA1rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones No shit, wit.💩🤷🏻‍♂️ #Facebook #FB #Facebookistan #greedy #little #buggers #cash #cow #privacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty straight forward IPA, slight hoppiness but no bitter aftertaste - Drinking a TSB IPA by @TwistedSpikeBrew @… https://t.co/6lv8oJ4ZFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, that's the depth of the GOP. No longer Party of law and order. They are the party of graft and dark money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnctilMathew @senstalk_ Do you wish our team were a bunch of porn stars that you could rt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DiscoveryDistri is the next rising neighborhood downtown: https://t.co/3ENaFirT1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Coach Davis. She also runs a competitive hoops league and tourney- the best one in KC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @FoxNews Saw this while on Instagram.. This needs 2 go viral!! #MAGA!!! #1STAMENDMENTRIGHTS!!!… https://t.co/5LAnyZfI6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieTrunk @Richie_Kotzen @MonstersCruise So jealous. Glad I'm going to see this cat in May. Have fun and be safe everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i peed and farded and shidded but y’all ain’t ready for that conversation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cliff Jumper IPA by @CountryBoyBrew @ The Derby: Piano and Dessert Bar — https://t.co/zVmHrju2H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs It’s the guys with the crosses on https://t.co/Wu4w6Xqk1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are responsible for the problems in Congress. Trying to lighten our load as citizens with term limits weakens us… https://t.co/LXcuazxrAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_is_so_nice We’re gonna sell a “Beefcakes of Richmond City Hall” calendar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[13th-seeded @FFLadyBravesBB tries to complete its incredible run Saturday against No. 2 seed Mechanicvlle in the Cl… https://t.co/ftkTE4kGdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlistairMay @john58wilson @PeterNimmo1 On the other hand, if a), then the terms of leaving would be clear (Governm… https://t.co/bv8OyjpMpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was wonderful to host @ppixelpprincess and some of the other young leaders of the Society of Women in Space Expl… https://t.co/rOcR0qrVoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite having grown up in Detroit (and my @Tigers will be coming to Philly this season), I have always been a fan… https://t.co/D1WkittjEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearance Sale spotted in Mobile Alabama!  #browns #BrownsBackers #DawgPound #GoBrowns #KardiacKids https://t.co/BjnIzJq7Zk]]></document></documents></author>