<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We have 1 week left exploring this beautiful country! 1 week until we head back to Australia after spending a year… https://t.co/tgm7y7Yl9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop rushing. Stop trying to get to the next thing and learn to enjoy what’s right in front of you. ⠀⠀ .⠀⠀ .⠀⠀ If y… https://t.co/3qIbZDT5UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean no harm y’all will forever and always be the best band in the land 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABBLs training with support from the awesome staff at Pathways. What a great way to monitor growth and drive instru… https://t.co/CXLL0VZpJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“where beaches meet biotech, fishing meets finance, and cafecito meets coding” ... sounds about right #miami https://t.co/y982XBkU2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins @SenAngusKing @DHSgov Seems no one has anything positive to say to you anymore sue. How about that? 2020 real soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[celebrating 100 days straight of working out 🌟💖⭐️ https://t.co/lzTbhQ2TVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It all depends on how we look at things, and not how they are in themselves. - Carl Jung  Sometimes going upside do… https://t.co/HRUfuWzu0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eyespiration Seen at #Pier39 #travelphotography San Francisco https://t.co/1dJmUgelnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsblksantaX @BlkSantaX @D_resists @Eathbound420 @sisley_davis @Shaken0Stirred @whyknotmeagain2 @MelliRolli… https://t.co/jiB5AkFDgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartland is hiring in #Charlotte, NC! Read about our latest #Sales job opening via the link in our bio: B2B Sales Payroll Executive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding word patterns with Dr. Seuss #readacrossamerica https://t.co/cdARujhSN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHS Dabbing to be Different #FCSDab @FCS_SEC @standandria https://t.co/koEg3vIyx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You made a memory that will last this young man life!! There need to be more people like you! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 4 of the @YouVersion Plan Celebrating Advent: Embrace Jesus In This Season. Check it out here:… https://t.co/SeLwWnH79O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrissguccii Well today ain’t Sunday &amp; you thought bout it rn so go]]></document><document><![CDATA[We lost an hour from our weekend but we get more sunlight now🙌🏻  . . . . #silviambeauty #blogger #houstonblogger… https://t.co/JH1cgxU9Ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRockbeats @RapSheetHwood https://t.co/0Jnx60dIjx 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats… https://t.co/F9XHqdmnMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC VERY impressed with your questions to Michael Cohen yesterday. You were prepared, and actually got information… https://t.co/pxUTjOFj4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRossBowie @goldengateblond And it was in the day, A-Rod set his (wait for it) CAP for J-Lo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love this place! Come check it out. #BeerIsMyFriend #Cary @ Der Biergarten Cary https://t.co/TLl4FtmfDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrRachelAlinsky @SAHMtweets @HopkinsKids @DrScottHadland We are so proud of you!  #HopkinsAdolescentMedicine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AleMarcanoS @nakamartinez @NicolasMaduro Es una prueba irrefutable de la inmoralidad e inutilidad de esos Organism… https://t.co/ZOLTx4LypJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art #poetry and #livemusic don’t miss out @pelotonlabs tomorrow from 5 to 8pm @ PelotonLabs https://t.co/ls3PMUMFw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itskelsiem Hahahah I post about it all the time. I’ve dated too many guys with black mustangs and they all turn out the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyMountViews @funder All men a screwed up horny pre teens. The difference is parents that teach there children… https://t.co/wBHVynayVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyAnnWells @sheri_lynn95252 @lovinlyrics @LoverMusic44 @TennWhiskey40 @mleitten @br_infinity_ke Same to you!! 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[White hot chocolate.  #williamscafe #HamON @ Williams Fresh Cafe https://t.co/5ROf6QZm2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono Maxie U R lying to women. It’s murder of a child to commit abortion during late term pregnancy. Medica… https://t.co/LwHCs2KKnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait to find out about the "secret sauce" for schools from @dhudgins #ncties19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGBecerra Sorry if you think your a good lawyer wrong the top lawyers look into this big time. We will caught you… https://t.co/mfpFPnxK4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceyhoey @SimianGiudice @Teresa_Giudice @BravoTV Joe and Teresa...Peace Out https://t.co/L8l5BgVcZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanSams @KamalaHarris Even if this is true, this is a bad tweet. A comms director should know not to compose a hipster coffee shop tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accountemps is hiring in #AnnArbor, MI! Click the link in our bio to apply: Bookkeeper #Accounting]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 hours till @DanAndShay tickets. 10 hours till #vegas gonna be a great weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday, March 1 • 4PM-Close • Mention Lompoc Elite • Bake Sale • Thank you for your support‼️ @LFC4square… https://t.co/KXVy7n0Aip]]></document><document><![CDATA[All signs are pointing up. #morningswitheddy #joyousperspective #mondaymotivation @ Savoy, Illinois https://t.co/IwAu4dGnmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 92nd Birthday to my Daddy in heaven, how I wish I could tell you I love you one more time and get a hug! You… https://t.co/gsg5nFVilD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melanie_Z13 @boxycharm This is what they sent me.. https://t.co/EeoirT6BgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at RDU Park &amp; Ride Lot 3 - @rduairport in Morrisville, NC https://t.co/RWaboDgPM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soirée-bénéfice de @revivre_org au @vieuxportmtl le 15 mai prochain. Soyez des nôtres! Le vidéo de lancement de l’é… https://t.co/PhIP9lN1qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne My grandparents story is your story just 72 years ago. It's why I'm Pro-Choice and will always remain so. I… https://t.co/jicLIrOgOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Don_TheCon @ladyred1956 Hey Thank you, I didn’t know this number! Great information! I will call now if they are s… https://t.co/HbnEzm57ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StollmeyerEU @Mattscharfstein @StateDept @JessikkaAro Meet Racist Merica]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Made with Love by my Cute Lil Irish Mother in Law #Birthdaycheattreat #birthday🎂2019 #blessed🙏 #irishmomsrock @ Br… https://t.co/Y6ZFmPXQ9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratitude helps us to see what is there instead of what isn’t. 💖💯 #facts #morningvibes #mood #positivity #blogger… https://t.co/bJd5BuIn0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[What quick impactful response to students that will set you up for success for the day.  This is a great way to tak… https://t.co/cKDdlJ3tvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will strengthen you and help you; I will uphold you with my righteous right hand. Isaiah 41:10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bijancbayne @alexconnorwrite @ampomata @planetearthx2 @G_Dolman @ChrisPopeWrites]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @DrDenaGrayson Well Daddy has been known to say Jr was not bright !! 😂😂😂Kettle calling the Pot]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gorgeous valentine. And my amazing Invisalign teeth. ❤️❤️❤️ @ Liquid Libs Bar at Liberatores https://t.co/UapP01B8Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d say this, but you’ll never see another positive post about Obama from me again. After watching hi… https://t.co/16kgPVdIks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited @maes_0523’s new hood, and the leasing office lady let me have a cutting of their Golden Lemon Prayer Plant… https://t.co/YV2R4ng5CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[He conocido a personas increíbles en Los Angeles;  gente bella en  teatro y tú eres una de ellas @roserubio tqm. Lo… https://t.co/7vrl0h9gW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been doing my card readings lately and they’ve been telling me to find some alone time to sit and reflect how… https://t.co/bbM9sohpnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me why Annie Leibovitz was doing at the Beto O'Rourke rally last night? I was near the stage and I… https://t.co/sfR5YMdMsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greeneyes2471 @gwenstefani I was just explaining why they probably dont want to get legally married not to mention… https://t.co/iSTQMGtLH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robgalb @III_SeanK @iiiorg @III_SeanK  is a knowledgeable and engaging speaker. What a treat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whydontwemusic if y’all follow me i’ll blast cold in la along the las vegas strip #COLDinLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be attending @Health_Affairs  Briefing: Consumer and Health.  #hcconsumer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diddy #JessiVMusic invites you to come watch me #iSing tonight #RocioDurcal #ComoHanPasadoLosAnos at  #LaVeranda 🎤… https://t.co/agPHweUuzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first gallery showing/debut book launch 📖📷 Saturday, March 16th, 2 pm, @MabeeFarm. Original poetry and local nat… https://t.co/YIlaTAb3Vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, but he'll probably use all his "influence" and time reduced for good behavior or medical reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @DudekLinda @delgeo1 @hey_butter @Msgargoyle13 @poppij @NOW1SOLAR @agavecorn @Valkyrry… https://t.co/72hjyJF9J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahdgaf_ @Storm6lenn espically at nelson’s you love your dawgs there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tnanks @RTB_HRoss This is awesome and along with your book “The Improbable Planet” should be required reading for t… https://t.co/QZHaxSnR4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥Wind damage report: wires sparking with a possible pole fire in Colebrookdale Twp., Berks Co. #pawx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torimsidesoc Finally figured out how to phrase my book length reply: "We need family positivity, just like we have… https://t.co/UPf2C0AZ2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of fluids... starting to feel puny #feelingacoldcomingon @ St. Johns County, Florida https://t.co/P3dQz4JE1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles Plz don’t be sad james we love u the tears my heart u don’t diserve this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totallywillma @ericfisher No...please be rain! Our managers are treating us to a nice lunch out on Monday. Don't want to miss it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's relationship with AIPAC goes back years. Former Massachusetts Treasurer, Steve Grossman, along w… https://t.co/P5P3FoBHaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[MND will operate on a two-hour delay today due to area weather conditions.  Be safe getting to school! 💙🌻💙🌻💙 @MNDCougars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched a sweet movie called hello 👋🏻 my name is Doris.  I am that quirky lady 😂😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/jJfOGSv291]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apex coming out at the beginning of the semester was a really bad thing for my time management]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today #henryfholst discovered NASCAR and #mlouiseholst discovered Polly Pocket. @ North Carolina's 9th Congressiona… https://t.co/GjNVK8vS42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGFEwebcomic @PalmerReport Howard Shultz needs to gain the experience of politics.  He's an arrogant prick who I… https://t.co/HUh3t8uXh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Of all the hearts I’ve loved,  Yours is the only one that makes mine smile.” perrypoetry  . . . Happy Valentine’s… https://t.co/4Jo1lzV1Lc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@principalest Will this be for teachers or just administrators? I really want to attend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw two Instagram posts in a row of people expecting a baby. Why is everyone getting pregnant or married?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mykaila_marie @jadeybadwiii lol I got outta class and had like 75 Twitter notifs 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO VOTO X #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para 1° lugar en #TopOccidente @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 7]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sigh*..things are just tough at the moment. Hard to concentrate. Hard to get excited about anything. I see everyon… https://t.co/b5bbHvHftd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_ndirangu97 @EKMontie @Cukeygirl @McFlat29 @BTS_twt I’m off to get outfits ready. Where are we having this shindi… https://t.co/a3yACGg1SV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We almost made it to our usual walk in the woods, but had to turn back on the driveway. Otherwise it was a lovely d… https://t.co/S2PUhuLcJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It bothers me so much when people can’t bother to communicate how they are feeling directly to someone. I’m so sick… https://t.co/65C3GQCSN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil works hard but kris Jenner works harder https://t.co/C0USXmG8ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariusHollenga I love the idea, but I can see myself wasting SO much time thinking about it, then locating the song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VParadisoBCA @LindaPeters64 @OrganicRoadMap @JulesHalvy @AfropolitanW @veggievagabonds @carpediemeire… https://t.co/2oO5TLnwmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Chicago Police -#JussieSmollet is in custody... https://t.co/dEJNj2imaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost anthonyswordsofwisdomforwomen with get_repost ・・・ . IN LIFE, IF YOU DO NOTHING YOU GET NOTHING. @ Glenwood,… https://t.co/XMt2tOlgTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Tribune: Hours before Aurora mass shooting, former mayors met in Chicago to discuss strategies to reduce gu… https://t.co/YEpWNGfRER]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Florida Governor #DeSantis to #Amazon: ‘We welcome you to come to #Florida' 👍 https://t.co/2amWxNwMA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HWN8qdKmHf She's her parent's daughter, plain and simple, except she been overrated and overindulged since much young.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hall90485733 @Nephewhamza @BowmanNancy @shaunking I’d put money on Roy Moore...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le Madison Square Garden #madisonsquaregarden #newyorkknicks #newyork #newyorkcity #basketball #nba #sacramento… https://t.co/zSWmrBCfqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreBernier @fox8news  Clear sky and a few little pink clouds at dawn. Four degrees. More snow due this afternoon… https://t.co/XbhfLWu6zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment your students put the pieces together for their life journey #studentengagement + #futurereadiness = suc… https://t.co/vGMrQwuUwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hunde_Haus That is unconscionable behavior on the part of the LEO handler. Hit the K9 so hard he broke it’s leg??… https://t.co/3f6jcjPJ5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 82 days I will turn 19 and I can finally make those “what up I’m Jared I’m 19 and I never fucken learned how to read” jokes. Excited !]]></document></documents></author>