<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sfzombienation @LondonBreed @sfbos @JeffKositsky @SF_HSH @SF_DPH @MattHaneySF Oh my Gosh.   I know  this women.… https://t.co/N7rlPnmAGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yusuf_bektas91 @tennagersex @EmpireLesbian @AmA2jena1 @beauty2love1910 @sjerhera @WaledApple7 @gDQKnJyhcJ51xn2… https://t.co/ykXQKXXOj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fix this problem with ThinkPoints.  #strategy #cso https://t.co/RzE94zKTNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO HE SAID I NEED SOMEBODY TO HELP ME NOT HAVE A BIG HEART I AM CRYING]]></document><document><![CDATA[...so if Bryce Harper is worth 330 mil how much is Mike Trout worth? #JustAsking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @AmericanAir, just because your gate agent at PHL A24 forgot to call group 4 doesn’t mean she can be extremely… https://t.co/ZohQLNqhPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmace30 I’d be lying if I said there’s any excuses for how we are playing. Jets beat these guys 8-1 and we stumble… https://t.co/WA8r3mqG4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamdevinnsmart @meltedmarbles Welcome!  I’m an Independent and I welcome your decision...America first!  MAGA 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[not quite finished with KH3 yet but if i has to score it now... it would get 7/10.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InTendysWeTrust If Jesus didn’t think drinking was ok, he would’ve just let that water be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McneilDarius2 @NBA @KingJames Prob has that Minoxidil treatment in lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practice makes perfect! Thanks universoulcircus #brandongraham #imbrandongraham #choregraphy #dancer #choregrapher… https://t.co/eS11wwZLOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonOMac @jeubanksMD @medicalaxioms @S_P_MD @MDaware @Disfordilaudid @ShreyaTrivediMD @AlliBeanMDPhD… https://t.co/7NqvJzovyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @THEJNL @THEJNL jnlfusion for let us be a part pf your project. Hoping to serve you again soon!🎤… https://t.co/1SVc3jf18a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oasis65 @89Nich @JayB7897 @AMSweather i said 3-6" and i have 3" still snowing 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wherestherevolt @maybe_or_nah I literally live across the country,never heard of this child before,but I've seen h… https://t.co/ZN9OxLGBK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why I bother. I admit my feelings and STILL get tossed to the side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmills87 @Michaelsonmoney @amber68555487 Lol just look who retweeted. How many accounts is she up to... and when I… https://t.co/ELCQEerdve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure whether this is norm@ Colesville,MD 17mi NNE of  WhiteHouse,but this winter,xcept for ltl snow on Jan 29,… https://t.co/sjCMBd7Hwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepEliotEngel @Jeannie_Hartley By saying the obvious, that AIPAC lobbies our reps to do the Israeli govt's bidding… https://t.co/gFBONF7C8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GucciTowns @Ab0ut36greeks @BleacherReport @espn_macmahon Our problem is the front office trading like our last 6 t… https://t.co/8Ro4hPASvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianCastro if we keep looking in the past how do we move forward as a country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHODesusAndMero @AOC @Showtime @desusnice @THEKIDMERO You mean ignorant-idiot guests]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Tie his hands behind his back, maybe he'll stop talking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wassup Gamers! Time for another late night stream! Come join me for some Fortnite fun. https://t.co/r6Epo3fsBV… https://t.co/w8nmTbEZmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slrussell He just had a tendency to hit these impossible shots. I was at the Kentucky have where he went if in the… https://t.co/Ie3gG3KEaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This ASSHOLE, killed 5 pets! Lock this dirt bag up for life!!!  https://t.co/gD5JGQ4cJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandy45_2020 @Jamierodr14 How did he get elected, and if you don't like it leave. Nothing is stopping you I love o… https://t.co/RuczDwfCKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been using medium off and on I like the platform; I like how the audience is built in... however I have seriou… https://t.co/BH6xs6HnHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBerenson Thank you sir for going on to @joerogan show for making yourself and book look completely asinine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six California police officers fire shots at rapper asleep in car, killing him https://t.co/dWQBiKUU2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@802DisFam Hard to turn that down. I probably would’ve done it again too and just hope for a minor concussion lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk like you mean it. #laughter #laugh #smirk #cute https://t.co/Yjm4QgtJwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ofbating @NateMcGonigal @grodhome @yespeezy @NJMDiesel Hooooooooo train]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go ders. - Drinking a Barn Rocker Ale by @OysterBayBrewin @ Arooga's  — https://t.co/cJXS3Gy6dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“https://t.co/qLDvOhdc01 has also competed against its rival Alibaba in China and abroad... On Monday, Alibaba anno… https://t.co/D5e7U3V6YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheClimateHawk @SenWhitehouse @WSJ That’s a list of propaganda that is pushing an agenda and incomplete in their c… https://t.co/0TnYbSiXJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaineGardens excited to hear Bill Cullina speak at Smart Gardening Conference in #GrandRapids. #Gardening #Plants]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @KerriStowell #fox4 reporting the wx! you're doing an awesome job!🌬🌞🤘🏽🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: 10 years on this thing?!? Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/NtjW6QqdnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[On farm meetings need to have a specific goal. Meet with the staff and get an idea of any immediate issues. Then wa… https://t.co/atZCEFiDz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you my mans &amp; you see a chick throwing that ass back on me? It’s your job to hold me up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please, y'all. Love is constant if we show it in our actions and our words. #BeThere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress That an economy does not have enough opportunity for people to buy their own bread and/or lack the cultur… https://t.co/Yx0g6zPKjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛑👇🏼👇🏼🛑 Once saved, God maintains our salvation, but we are responsible for our daily walk, striving to become more like Jesus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hollywoodwatchs I'm the Captain America you see but don't hear. @HermelaTV walked right past me. I write about it… https://t.co/Y6EUOEpigU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew I was supposed to die so I think I preemptively split the codex into three houses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peytonhughes17 Didn’t they go undefeated that year? Or did y’all beat them at wsf?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspired by @Principal_EL this morning as he shares the importance of knowing where your children have been, what t… https://t.co/wPRcqv7tdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeanniemcbride_ great job on the evening news-look great in light blue too-#Fashionista keep up the good work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericfisher. Hi Eric..Update. 51F for our high today in North Weymouth. Beautiful stuff!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cegriff3 @RyanAFournier They might just go with the crowd that celebrates the Confederate flag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellie @greycroftvc Yes to health and intelligent primary care! https://t.co/xmpOe1QeeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[35-27 score for a 4A Iowa State Semi-Final game. I feel like I’m watching games from the 1950’s when I watch some o… https://t.co/AAqvkhoUpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’d die for katya but since the two white brians have their own show and are doing all sorts of gigs, I at least ne… https://t.co/o2dLotuT0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingPhelan I dropped some heat on him and he ran off with his tail between his legs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graham Souness was definitely on some sort hallucinogenic drugs watching that game today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOregonRA @TR0771N @Carterdsc @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/IjkMEppvYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_AminThaabet @lackboys3 The "good old days" for Jews of 1933 through 1945, maybe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting rather tired to have to reset my individual doctor provider care in HIV because the doctor will not represe… https://t.co/3nkpBkO5Ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringer @HaleyOSomething This is funny and really well done. Makes me smile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[13:30 left in 2nd half and I’m turning it off and going to bed!! Can’t watch anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Gibbs calls Daytona 500 his biggest win ever https://t.co/rQ97Hc6yI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsWeezah @RowdyJeepGirl Chicks were the extent of my attention span 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it mean when you see the same person in your dreams consistently?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the opposing team’s coach stops down the game on his home floor to honor one of the greatest. #MFFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume .@brithume Why would you even call them journalists? They are not journalists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the same load configuration as in the deep squat, half and quarter squat training with comparatively supra-max… https://t.co/igQuEMTQYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making the 3 hour drive up to @HollywoodSTL today to play in the @HPTPoker Seniors Tournament. Yeah I’m old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Obama issued national emergency over a flu outbreak in 2009.  Surely incessant bo… https://t.co/ieZkiE1Wfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodeefarris If it counts for anything I ate a burrito, corn dog, Chimi, and a bag of hot Cheetos and let me tell y… https://t.co/wxgCO416XV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TgMacro @AndyTowersPLL Just saw B Miller @ the Sandstorm tourney in Palm Springs. Such a good guy and absolutely f… https://t.co/8obLu99mGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost the only pair of sunglasses I’ve ever cared about in Miami two years ago. Went to the eye doctor today and the… https://t.co/KQd2k0qUzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing all a very happy 😃 and loving 🥰 Valentines Day! https://t.co/tTdtWkbphE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old School Concert @ Talking Stick Resort Arena https://t.co/AtbDEJJU4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBenediktM @PlugInFUD @elonmusk @thenewjimcrow @realDonaldTrump FYI: Once a convo on @Twitter dot com gets to the… https://t.co/F8KudzXxeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GracieZitny You are amazing in all your own ways. Other people don’t define you, hun. We are very successful for o… https://t.co/whJDcuNSvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamtarsha @tomwassell @ciara Never said I matter. And as far as @Ciara is concerned, I don’t matter. As far as I’m… https://t.co/oASdIaU4wG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized the bonus match in WWE2K19 Showcase should have been @TrueKofi vs @WWEDanielBryan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xbeaudouin @PierreCol Voilà :) je parle de la marque qui exporte vers les US donc même combat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveningStandard Yo, @EveningStandard, this is fucking... https://t.co/za77TpMJ2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid but unspectacular - Drinking a Failed Resolution by @dblnickelbrew @ Percy P's On The Bed  — https://t.co/wXBQCBU0iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this mean that @WilldeFries is going to launch a wedding planning podcast? People are talking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Illegals housed on the Mexican border waiting to storm the USA now are asking for a car so they can… https://t.co/hxFafH78pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay guys this pancake maker was seriously a HUGE deal and for real that machine after a week of research the Inter… https://t.co/AIW0S8Ntyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peace, Love, Tech, and Mindfulness @AngelaWojtecki #Neotech2019 #NEOTech19]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is all part of the plan. Say “GOOD” to the pain. It will grow you ten fold https://t.co/XObCsNwqSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an ingenious idea!!! A party on July 4. And with fireworks, too? Wow. I can't believe this has never been done… https://t.co/x5de69Uote]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #MaduroCrimeFamily in #Venezuela have shown this weekend just how EVIL they really are. The people BEGGED the V… https://t.co/1YEb9jwv0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puljujarvi Yamamoto and 8 1st round draft picks to Tampa for Kucharov 😂 #LetsGoOilers #GoBolts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not allowing myself to be caught up in what corporations are telling me to be excited about and instead focusing on… https://t.co/X4qoaqQV6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelackmeyer @Babatikidido @mkimball011 Steve, STRAWS are the latest trend. People have been drinking WITHOUT st… https://t.co/RptagLVBhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rubyripper #scrapps #gloweyes #letitberight 🖤🖤 @ Lower East Side https://t.co/lb7isShrkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IPOT1776 @realDonaldTrump The Celebration of all Celebrations. Hey I see Paula Loves Children got tagged by Q for… https://t.co/alPAh96C3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcfireems @FFBehavior How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/X9hSNm6FX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Runt Runt and Squiggle waiting on treats.  #cat #catsofinstagram #kittens #kittensofinstagram #treats… https://t.co/0w1nJqCyF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show but @mrjaxtaylor you are kind of rude. You can learn from @itsjameskennedy  (he did invite you golfing,… https://t.co/Hy1305Ynwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesolithicguy lol that’s a understand.. I remember as a kid I was just happy to what anything. Now my daughter ask… https://t.co/KP1qhGhahi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ashglaze #stoneware #ramen #bowl #oxidation #pottery #ceramics #minneapolis #minnesota #detailshot #ochre #ash… https://t.co/0BDdsBvdcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianmoorre @gil_in_atx @TaylorTwellman Think Ohio State lost to Rutgers this season. 👀]]></document></documents></author>