<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Are President terminated payments it was from his personal account or business account that means he didn't doing a… https://t.co/TeU4DfosXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeresaMWalker @KaylaAndersonTV @justinbbradford @govertime 😊nothing wrong with Mikkie but yeah I can understand.  I Like Simmers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld @SkyNews @politico @RollingStone He got beat up as a kid. I guarantee you.  He can go with… https://t.co/zh72WOI7Xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tfl1967Tl @GovernorTomWolf @MeekMill Just admit you’re a racist you pussy ass bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sljm8D @tjusi2 @jimesilverman @AOC In *many* places, especially rural areas, you have little, if any, choice in un… https://t.co/NLNPm2deSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKalei586 @thebestcloser Only when maga needs media it's not an enemy of free people.  Fucking morons.  Boston lo… https://t.co/EjfPQg0JrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She is in Atlanta filming an episode of the Walking Dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Salty_Soccer Atletico/Juve probably most interesting...  I can't resist any opportunity to watch Pep's team play though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony Navaratan is a prime example of the hard working Cambridge residents I want to fight for. Tony immigrated here… https://t.co/EauAZDHabx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway how the fuck are people supposed to get to work? EVERY UPTOWN TRAIN IS CRIPPLED WITH DELAYS THIS MORNING!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kristennetten @elonmusk @RPMTESLA You and me both. If @28delayslater gets one I’ve already asked to be his date.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work hard at everything because I revert back to one quote, “Hard work beats talent, when talent doesn’t work har… https://t.co/90AX9r47JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashleyfox2122 Buenas noches hermosa! See you en la manana! Bright and early! 😉😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevefromSC @andicanderson @ByronYork @NewYorker Wikileaks was public a week before Stone's call to Trump.  Pollin… https://t.co/e7eOanHcF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't need no love in my life #Aventura #DileAlAmor  #Bachata #InMyFeelings https://t.co/Lxa8o9Ho2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Labiosrojos_gt Buenos días Muñequita. Feliz inicio de semana 😀🌷🌹. Saludos!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember as a kid 1st getting fascinated with the likes of #hurricanes and #tornados? I checked out a book from the… https://t.co/Fl8dLS4G3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickieStarxxx1 @TraccVision I was thinking the same damn thing! $300 a week? And she was doing him raw too? Damn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the creator didn’t think that way why the change??? I guess anybody can create their own superhero based on cre… https://t.co/ZpYSRCQyTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true. College readiness is more than a guaranteed credit. @WFISDschools #IamWFISD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssa_irby @AMillionABC @OneDayAtATime I’ve seen @OneDayAtATime and love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[DILLY DALLY RALLY’S WILL NEVER RESCUE REPUTATION OR CESSATION FROM REFUTATION OF MALFEASANCE, PERJURY, NEPOTISM OR… https://t.co/WdTkmHvwU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith The King of La ... it’s not easy being King check with me when thy kingdom come 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittPenguin44 @CupersLee That wasn’t the question...the question was, how would he have stopped Wilson from breaki… https://t.co/NUpqOzlD9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MhxVxV6xGV   Damn can the @FlaPanthers  get this guy a tryout?! 😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK WHAT JUST DROPPED! The White and Red “FOCUS ON YOUR OWN GAME” shirts!! This is my favorite saying to all the n… https://t.co/wdn6GCn2Gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KlNGOFCASH Sir., I want to tell you, thank you. You're helping people, even those who don't win, you give them hop… https://t.co/8RyyK7cpK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Registered Nurse - Emergency Department - Part Time Nights -… https://t.co/RnIYaacXHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gerrrty @jeuasommenulle Here’s a different view. Protesters numbers appear heavier than the other video. Imho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aacuna1 Good Morning! Nice seeing you on @AmericaNewsroom Great job on @FoxNews Prayers for a safe day in the field...God bless!  👍😃✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is next level shit.   @sandraamstutz is very good at this. https://t.co/o7AjDHNVXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREchatLIVE A1. Today it is a 65-70% male dominated business controlled environment.   Women are more committed to… https://t.co/3pg0bEf4Cp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich Again, that's not the point. That's like telling an arsonist that he did a great job while watching y… https://t.co/00rd97rGkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Darry @patbonin @morininfo Est-ce que la glace dans l’arctique baisse en continu depuis des décennies? Oui. Rater… https://t.co/WUxaAp3M1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielWHouck And obviously if the injustice of the prof is extreme enough, then it really can hurt you. But I take… https://t.co/6LW4xdR4sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as it fits the narrative, we will go with it. The left has lost its mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week has been a bad massage, I need a happy ending #MiamiNights @ Four Seasons Hotel Miami https://t.co/TyuQJz3Io2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncGold @Tommygarv17 @hardwoodheroes @cbaker_25 That would be pretty cool tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone going to be live on Twitch practiceing some Apex Legend may get some Guild members to join stop by if… https://t.co/0iGx4vMEJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning #snow coverage on @fox29philly #fox29goodday.  We’ll get you to work or school safely, join @KarenFox29… https://t.co/6QFiV3gz8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats actually admitted they will never agree with our president, These Liberals/democrats are attempting to bl… https://t.co/rwiOIHACOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never thought i would be in the same building as @BobanMarjanovic ... dreams do come true ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@30kTmay Lol man same way you used to get on Myles Turners head I’m bout to be on his]]></document><document><![CDATA[The minute amazon announced it would invade NY, real estate prices shot up in Brooklyn and Queens. It is a very goo… https://t.co/vawZOC9oQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC doesn't realize the last time @TheDemocrats went this far-left circa 1968-72 with soft Socialist McGovern, Ame… https://t.co/3PjF5Vpkai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fperez1776 @wherepond @laielkha @IsraelFrontline @JudeanRefugee @amirshah316 @Meir_Lipa @BeccaElkaim @2Whistleblow… https://t.co/gpk9b3hWKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mistress_Neena It must have been a bit funny to you... Tounge in cheek. Next time go to Amazon books... Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patty_Elle Thank you Patty and have wonderful blessed weekend 💙💙💕 https://t.co/qy3jWPZ8bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katefroelich01 Yes, my mother lived in Georgetown (suburb of Austin metroplex) in the Sun City development, as wel… https://t.co/H3wdPTHC2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes when its late i think i can summon satan w voicemail by poppy playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juliococo Por que son una guabina, con su dualidad Uno chavista el otro “opositor”... pa mis cojones, estos lo que… https://t.co/oolNdz50va]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarRobRod @MayoGolfPT @mattkelly02 @mikereinold Yes, VERY high incidence of radiologically defined FAI... But most… https://t.co/n4o4lbf1Nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rookieuserIm Why are you always pointing fingers? And why haven't you awnser my last question?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely have the best boyfriend in the world.. ❤️ @Nicholas_Jarmon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone "Simone" actually means stave tarnisher in old middle Welsh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@superskarunner @existentialfish "News" network. They never claim to report the news most of the time. It's mostly… https://t.co/wovtBz9r8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriceSikes @CurivariCigars I have a bottle of the 18 yr.  really liked it. Just opened a bottle of Zavala 23, and… https://t.co/ZvNFMzAyMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSchiraldi @FitzTheReporter I had a plain old-fashioned this morning. I blame/thank Fitz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, no doubt the brain *is* complicated, but that's beside the point. https://t.co/P3HAttp1zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[El chavismo no logra contrarrestar a la oposición con su concierto   El recital convocado en respaldo a Nicolás Mad… https://t.co/cmumMkNr3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don't understand how [George Miller] does that, I really don't, and it's my job to understand it. I don't unders… https://t.co/zxFLcjzItM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Coffee before #TacoTuesday small group #HighlandsMG @highlandsal (@ Starbucks in Montgomery, AL) https://t.co/3Al3ukdnTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#southridge #jawdroppingviews #motivationmonday ....#hughkaptur #johnlautner #stevemcqueen #bobhope #williamholden… https://t.co/1AOn7rtgSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @GodFirstGina @KPWood09 @WFO777 @helper2 @jonz970 @rdrhwke @halciber @mirkin_d @cmc8083 @texasrecks… https://t.co/xlQWC23IPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[That JJ RAWLINS directing traffic&amp;not politicos like OBJ of Nigeria. https://t.co/edtpdZFMjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am no different than your  Cat or dog I have complex emotions individual needs and preferences. Please consider m… https://t.co/BzEbbFTBGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Alita (@ Regal Cinemas Hollywood 24 @ North I-85 - @regalmovies for Alita: Battle Angel in Chamblee, GA) https://t.co/bGc71lr9dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BalazsSimonBalu How do you solve the lack of magnetic field? You can't just atmosphere and hope for the best. That… https://t.co/WyQ075gKHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrittanyxoxo @pinupglam @BigBreastPics @karlaclijster @bb_boobs @BoobGlam_com @BoobsRealm @bigboobiesworld… https://t.co/IxhjnonyYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really!! @ Galaxy Theatres Luxury+ IMAX Riverbank https://t.co/x5A7EMg8eM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shake Shack’s chicken sandwiches &amp; chicken nuggets &gt;&gt;&gt; Chick Fil-A chicken sandwiches &amp; chicken nuggets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It is absolutely clear that the BIGLYEST security risk to the country is comrade drumpf and everyo… https://t.co/SudAYprjK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoked to check out this @PWXwrestling show #BattlefieldX. First time seeing #PWX love and thanks to @HighspotsWN I… https://t.co/J2w9R9EdCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another trip down 385 for the Devildogs for a visit at Ridge View. Spot in Upper State Championship at stake. We’re… https://t.co/w4k0VnwFzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayAdjacent!!! @TomKochABC13 @SamicaKnight13 @ABC13Elita  @KatherineABC13  @ChelseyABC13  @JeffEhlingABC13… https://t.co/uLQh3Mkas0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inside the Marketing Evolution of Giannis Antetokounmpo - @frntofficesport -  https://t.co/OdUhEWPTEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing that DeLaRosa and Giorgi can play together should help people understand that Kofi and Giorgi can play toget… https://t.co/n67FOqeU0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again @Colton - you are asking a father for his daughter’s hand in lifelong marriage, but yet you don’t even know i… https://t.co/Bqz81wrUvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Loses every Stanley Cup Series for the next 50 years*   https://t.co/BlrVsTzzn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning friends and happy Sunday everyone from my alternative music station. It is game day today for my Houst… https://t.co/nImFmupfmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slackamania before moving to NC how many UNC Duke games did you follow? Intrigued by how many folks outside NC love THE RIVALRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markhachman Nice! We just had a really good wild Sockeye Salmon from Sprouts: $11.99/lb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FairwayNation #mortgage #firsttimehomebuyer #realestate #florida #StayPassionate #RayCombs @ Ray Combs Homes, Fair… https://t.co/NUfpF3zsem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Daniel hating on everyone, you were just on their side like 2 seconds ago 😂😂 his character sucks #SDLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m already a light sleeper, so this constant loud thunder isn’t doing me any favors 🙄 https://t.co/tmbmiGroa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because someone likes an artist doesn’t make them a legend. Tired of saying it. People still talk about pac an… https://t.co/gbdMGTTTMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twistedmic24 @maydaymindy9 Thst being said the APA intends to look at suicide among psychologists as there is some… https://t.co/nOQop7R34r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jm3aux @_courtlandroyal Man me, you, Courtland, pastor &amp; Mrs. Donna can go beat the knicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cultivateawe : Inspiration, Awe. “Spirit of Tuskegee” PT-130 Stearman Kaydet training aircraft used by Tuskegee In… https://t.co/uATUe4DNCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sabino_StuCo Car Wash Day!! Support Sabino student council n get car washed at ACE Hardware on Bear Canyon n Tanqu… https://t.co/IpD3a7P8QI]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the list @UBmenshoops' own @nate_oats   Well deserved and should be the winner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burnaboy @DEDUKEosy where do we get tickets from? can’t find Atl on the website 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isaiah 62:5 “As a young man marries a young woman, so will your Builder marry you; as a bridegroom rejoices over hi… https://t.co/JW7QtI5tyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FullCountTommy @MATrueblood Love to hear that. Appreciate it! I’ll check out those stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lmchristi1 @carldemaio @realDonaldTrump @bretthorvath  yup, heaven forbid people learn about REALITY.… https://t.co/0i2kiY86fA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you enjoy preparing food for dinner parties? Now this family has a space just for that! 💜 Browse a “hot list” of… https://t.co/ZCmCBaAmsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eduardo_sg14 ya mamaron tus donitas #donitasbimbo en Coahuila de Zaragoza, Mexico https://t.co/J6OrxawYf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BATMANONFILM You don’t know ANY music post 1986. https://t.co/HTjcH1HeGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honour of #NationalCerealDay I wanted to show of my collection of various cereals I have 😁👌 https://t.co/wMa3PpO0oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nitagale If you have an Aldi's, try there. Surprising what you can find there.]]></document></documents></author>