<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[BBC News - Gene therapy first to 'halt' most common cause of blindness. https://t.co/8uxp9bO3yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonahlobe Really cool! Although i wouldnt say ancient since they were still around 500 years ago 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christianllamar @ChatByCC So if Trump wrote a personal check for the non disclosure payments (as politico reported… https://t.co/NVSQBcvoY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW where did 4 years go. WKU you had been my home for the last 3 years. Thank you for all the amazing memories and… https://t.co/N8qJZfQogr]]></document><document><![CDATA[McConnell's support of Trump's pro-Putin foreign policy was paid for by Russiahttps://mavenroundtable.io/theintelle… https://t.co/Zy7bA46QpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone need an ambassador? I think I’d like to be an ambassador of some sort.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WtqFgZKBS2  His co-rider William Dawes Jr...wait he murdered his niece in OC!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles @msmorgan1968… https://t.co/HX5NZZCfYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[From last night’s beautiful wedding with @ananavarro @ Indian Creek Country Club https://t.co/3D3oGNMsvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Here we go again left double standard still in her committee while Steve King is not!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweatsntopknots @DadSays4 @Shamusroan13 @MomO5Tiff @gentlemanvet67 @SMaxwellStory @DadFiction @MrsTyler78… https://t.co/2alwyXadLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[her embrace of vile and hateful stereotypes and slurs that have been leveled against #Jews since ancient times." 2/2]]></document><document><![CDATA[She wants to inconvenience - bankrupt - the nation, but don’t dare ask her to even make the slightest inconvenience… https://t.co/sOpTiYEFiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZagMBB @KillianTillie The height and extension of his jumps showed the decision to sit for so long was correct! Gr… https://t.co/sgG7oTZJQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hood_StandALONE @Legendvrydes Judging that video he don't look like he could defend his lady if something popped off in public]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball Chris, Trump has a damaging case of low self esteem; this is where his wild eyed, spittle flying, vitriolic behavior comes from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck a character limit. Pure love can promote you and destroy you. Elevate you or completely break you. It's the mo… https://t.co/m5WViSlQ08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyBr15464234 @DineshDSouza @mja11842 @Debber66 @1stLiberty I guess they ran out of names to rhyme with the other 4, Cindy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't gotten to Instagram to get started of your G=rated pics yet  If you have to enact that for me please do i… https://t.co/tkLTHD5ymJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[people in campus dance teams are lowkey a whole different breed of being]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite part of the #gameofthrones trailer is the awe-inspiring music playing over impending chaos* and doom. p… https://t.co/0thaf0agRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk if I’m sad or just really tired but either way I’m eating a muffin on the toilet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the #techindustries faults for @california it’s raising costs it’s greedy landlords &amp; high taxes that’s the cause of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t say clearly that there is enough evidence RIGHT NOW TO CONVICT TRUMP on several counts your not much o… https://t.co/Z7524skCRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bday is 8 days away and the one present I wanna unwrap is a @ChipotleTweets burrito .... add guac 🌯🥑]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fresh evening full of flowers, fashion and female power at the @freshstartwomen gala #loveandlight… https://t.co/XkUJRSJIgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEBOMTZ @RepDebHaaland @NationalGuard @USArmy @usmarin @usafrotc @indianastate @IndianaStateBar @IMPD_Chief… https://t.co/28dwwBQemK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Trump is incompetent! Kim will    totally play him with flattery and tell trump how wonderful he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to team https://t.co/IycESdbgIw and well wishes to all participants in @Persistentsys #Semicolons19… https://t.co/UZ3CyyW64z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yea nvm. She ain’t hit back so don’t do this lol. Fuck their funds kings. Spend your cash app money on social me… https://t.co/NTit3bTByX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAAdvocates @NW_Spotlight @BHSBlueTrain @WHSFB Absolutely. The Blue Train is a staple of the state.. surprised any… https://t.co/YL8v64VJEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How about you paying and lying about that Pussy you grab? What about you being a liar? What about… https://t.co/W2zWRP3KVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathrynTownsend @TillerWills1111 @drmistercody @realDonaldTrump I think you were going for a burn, but it didn't land.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estamos resueltos a ser libres; esa expresión es la fuerza más grande e invulnerable,  LA VOLUNTAD. Jamás el mal la ha vencido.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCBeerBill @fremontbrewing @BeerBBQBourbon @Buffalo_Theory I remember opening a bottle of the 2012 when the Seahaw… https://t.co/sNMElsuuVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does one cope when oppressed by toxic Christian capitalists?  Is the person or the society maladaptive?  We nee… https://t.co/fz3NgQgieE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frustrating when you get the hungries after midnight and you're in a hotel with no car to make a run for the border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:59 2nd  Wheelersburg 18  North Adams 9  Burg has already matched its first quarter output as Tanner Holden contin… https://t.co/Sp4FLTpOrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matibarrio Te hablo del tenista, como de cualquiera que juegue un deporte de alto rendimiento, todo el mundo se en… https://t.co/VC9fPEDcWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[XFL will soon announce initial broadcast package https://t.co/BIzSze9PVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend only at @beardedbeastofd ! Free product automatically added in cart. @ Elgin, Illinois https://t.co/oSkt2fkgO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Album Spotlight February 22, 2019  Featured Albums For February 22, 2019 Within Temptation - Re… https://t.co/cnDa4wrXeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbucks23 And only thing that’s shitty is the weather, everything else I’m gucci lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EspanolBosch @AndresJujol @jordiPuignero No es cuestión de suerte María, es cuestión de responsabilidad con una pa… https://t.co/usB6m1mnZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home 24 hours after getting to Dallas! Great quick trip 🛫🛬 @ DFW Airport https://t.co/VbuIpxOWmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd time down. Amazing how fast kids pick stuff up. Mama not as fast. Great snow on the ski trail. @ Port Wing, Wis… https://t.co/rlDy8XGvoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maynard032 @UKCoachCalipari He ticks me off in November and December but by God if he doesn't have shit together by this time of the year]]></document><document><![CDATA[brb @yokoono @StellaMcCartney #bringbackthebeatles? https://t.co/YmthkHmjQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leahlangleben Sag only gives us basic benefits. I remember when you got a pair of shoes once a year so you could h… https://t.co/DougH58uAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo he dicho un millón de veces, y se han reído, oero allí vamos. Es LEA 2.0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing was ever as cold as when lil Wayne said, "bitch, real G's move in silence like lasagna"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every episode of Airwolf was nearly identical, but I loved it anyway. I often fell asleep waiting for them to get t… https://t.co/aYttOFOvCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoganknows @dbellwth @gman416 But wait coach! Drew said he was going to have the biggest turnaround in college bas… https://t.co/5FRn64PI7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peebles with the ball, 21.7 seconds left. Trimble leads 56-53 after Weber splits a pair of free throws]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pingpongman at the Pikes Peak Ping Pong Club, below Pikes Peak “ Elevate Your Game” https://t.co/MZAyj4uisj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath @AnnCoulter That means you should move to another country electricity and gas and pretty much every… https://t.co/dcHlQtFZfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolizziThomas I don’t think she is that smart. However, she DOES know she will get away with it because democrats… https://t.co/ebJUhQegdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go @rcladylakers - Lady Lakers take the win over Clinton. https://t.co/P0txjIsn1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroadStBull Was there any explanation by Gudas as to what he was doing? Looked like a bizarre set of circumstances]]></document><document><![CDATA[I complain about both my jobs a lot, but they’re both extremely easy and it’s still a miracle neither one of them have fired me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lying TRAITOR actually thinks someone is still listening to him... lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReitzLee Well, if you weren’t sure we were going or not...I think this seals the deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bodean221 @ariaflame @Tigersclayco @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump Let's get back to North Carolina: Republicans are cheating scum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenLL11 Nah, I’m breathing just fine.  But just pointing out how gullible his followers are to believe this is n… https://t.co/Hn9HE48uu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenThomTillis Why vote on it in the senate? Let the house vote first! Bad strategy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things to do in Denver @ Colorado Convention Center https://t.co/iUpqBu3lIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelMComedy @BretHayden1T Honestly curious... what's a booker to do? Would you rather a show have the funniest c… https://t.co/tjEgXszzId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Finnattentive Hell yeah! Kinda liberating and it actually  had the opposite effect people would warn of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m still young because it still feels wrong if I’m not carded for alcohol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @RalphNortham has not resigned yet is so frustrating. He’s insanely arrogant and a hypocrite. I voted… https://t.co/LHXUB1HhGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gf is prettier then any other woman on this planet point blank periodt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really excited to announce the second set of #KeyForge! Super proud of the design and development I put into this o… https://t.co/Bk4YTQNQ1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally bought dental tape instead of dental floss! Wtf is dental tape! It feels like it’s floss for giants]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know we have a movie theater? No 🍿but lots of cardio equipment! Get your sweat on and watch a movie at the… https://t.co/LsWE5Ptpc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the odds that the DNC will open without a presumptive nominee? @FiveThirtyEight @NateSilver538]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Bump Day for Blake Snell #4 🦖⚾️😀👍🏻 as the Rays beat the Twins 1-0 in a combined 2 hitter! #springrays… https://t.co/7eqHD5zVuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharpndpensel I haven't had any issues with it.  Newer or older phone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fulfill your potential; know your worth; set a path toward success. #leadership #quote #HR https://t.co/TeJF0olzUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t be prouder of our response today. This group has raised the bar for us for the next one to follow!… https://t.co/jjx8QwEhDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mackall, Schumacher and Coleman all won, so this statement still holds true. I'm clearly clairvoyant and I did not… https://t.co/viXjCSaPEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[People stay identifying themselves with their body so much, like “hey this me I’m wearing a $350 tee, with the fear… https://t.co/mqi5KIys6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @APrecourt I like this pricing! I hope we get to see this with @AustinFC please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XcelEnergyMN power is out in Inver Grove Heights at Cahill avenue and birch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back and biceps today 💪🏽 - 1. Pull ups 5xfailure 2. DB seal row 4x12,10,8,8 drop 15 3. Lat pulldown 4x15,12,10,8 dr… https://t.co/M392Qpy2oQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFagan1987 @RealSaavedra We know her kind, and it’s cool. I get it, some people will make assumptions about you ,b… https://t.co/nJYoV947UJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judah47 All of these Major Winter Storms such as WS Gia, WS Harper, etc were once large LPA’s which were traveling… https://t.co/h1jSc1gbxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sippin' on purple smokin on dank. I got everything u need and get everything I want. C'mon tell me baby what u think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The meaning and the purpose behind some events are unknowable.  This is the ultimate test of our faith - @TonyRobbins]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY HAPPY birthday to one of my bestfriends in all da world !!!!! I love you so much! I hope you have a good ass… https://t.co/NevrZD4nph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway this is un-fucking-acceptable. WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU ACCOMPLISH THE PAST 8 YEARS? This line was shut do… https://t.co/oym6sHert4]]></document><document><![CDATA[WV Supreme Court to consider 2 questions in Farmington No. 9 appeal in a class action suit against Consolidation Co… https://t.co/uTf1PnD1yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Don_Pep Después de haber visto la de Marcos Rojo vs Bosnia todo lo creo posible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeMBB started their run too late. Kenny Williams and Colby White were a force in the second half. #DUKEvsUNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The personal needs in our community are overwhelming and now is the time to respond. Take a moment and consider wha… https://t.co/QeQ7FctCLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously, Baby Goebbels has been setting the tRump white supremacist agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting that late birthday Pew Pew with @CaptainRoBear - scratching that @Borderlands itch - stop in for some fun https://t.co/Z7pDQDVVKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamSmithHoops hey sam.  Everyone talks about Z.Williams, but wouldn’t Morant be more of a need/fit for this Bulls… https://t.co/uOAIqaMwsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trae Young’s averages over the last 10 games, before tonight’s ejection:                 26.4 points (.440% FG)… https://t.co/I4TQ3bGVzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love my dad bod but it’s gotta go for the summer 😔  2 weeks in, 5 lbs down  - 15 more to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @SenMcSallyAZ @Scotus Open McSally's mouth...insert Kavanaugh's foot. https://t.co/91wvB2tpcq]]></document></documents></author>