<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@awealthofcs @longwalkwputter Bank of America came out with a 50 year mortgage last decade. It was a big tell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Trans Am by @HGBrewery @ Hunter-Gatherer Brewery @ Owens Field (Curtiss-Wright Hangar) — https://t.co/oT13HdqfG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wrongheaded idea that New York would ‘give’ $3 billion to Amazon: To the editor: Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez… https://t.co/LaN8zBxemn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leon_Krueger7 @CesarAlbertoSR @AndresCitizen1 @joselui15920574 @RodMesa Pues nos vienen pelando la riata como la quieras ver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick interview setup and some broll for ND Research video. Wireless drone communication. #sonyfs7… https://t.co/B5wUa612pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blankenship Agreed re: supporting. But the Danny Rand character was too much for me to handle. I wanted to like it… https://t.co/kMK16kQ2U5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizzaroV @MotherCussr Ya about once a week something great comes to me and I had to F it up 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Niko man would love to have you slinging those footballs to Zack...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like NCAA refs get paid and extra $1000 every time they call a charge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because nothing says Valentine’s Day like doing something yo know you’re not perfect at but you do the best you can… https://t.co/53pi4WlFOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Exactly what experience does Ivanka have with security? Our White House is filled with nepotism, wh… https://t.co/h2BTgix3j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickeyKnox_xxx Good night to you all and hugs and kisses to her as well 💋😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneofmanymikes then there’s  the ridiculous contract that the phil’s offered the .249 hitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t this the thing u slide over your calculator https://t.co/j9JomrIzkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only two days left to help us send this little man to waltdisneyworld. Let’s do it! Go to https://t.co/2WBr489MDB a… https://t.co/h56f4vrzjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriots the coach and quarterback cheat at football and the owner cheats on his wife!!! #newyorkgiantsfan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteeIDicc Getting help mentally and a decent amount of therapy is essential for eliminating eating disorders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmayemsinger It's somewhat of a cliche but maybe he knows that dogs are excellent judges of character.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHudema Passing moist air through underground pipes creates condensation within the pipe which can then be used… https://t.co/LQgIPigKzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the @AOAPAquaticPros board of directors sharing the AqP program with participants #AqP #AOAP2019 https://t.co/0QU98Lu3RR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letsssss gooooo, back in the lead of the worse division in maybe history &amp; the 8 seed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dani21013 @letstrytomorrow I call mine Dean and refer to myself as Bing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @EmergeAmerica @emilyslist @runforsomething What if she’s a Republican?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex is following me around work and shoving me into shit and cussing me out and calling me names. I really wanna… https://t.co/AnMy5tYqay]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to be less insecure in Toronto... I’ve yet to see a city that isn’t NYC or LA that even remotely compares.… https://t.co/lN8TquSZdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@qirahsoka @TeamAhsoka EXACTLY. They took full advantage of the fact that there are people who thirst for him and j… https://t.co/H7LRG4hEEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKaufmannjrn @PressSec @realDonaldTrump Okay. What's your point. You and countless others don't like My Preside… https://t.co/Rktkgk8X5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@minddog @MegRaeGrady HAHA I think about that episode often lol... well played.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never understood the 10 mm socket jokes until I start working on my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Businesswise, the Gleaner's strategic mix of serious and almost tabloid-oriented  stories ensures the newspaper's p… https://t.co/HQgPKnTz04]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWVS #NEWYORK POSTED 📈 #X no face no case 🥶 #gangtivity @ Ginos Pizza https://t.co/HqNw6TmqON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisakers Manafort selected @vp because Pebceis a traitor that puts his whack job religion above country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 6 minutes and 51 seconds into the first episode of @AHWAmySedaris and #AmySedaris just became my idol. I’m obs… https://t.co/FpVY4tvvMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the Call the Midwife series 8 finale just aired today in the United Kingdom on the @BBC, this season are now h… https://t.co/NhkUL4FyUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieAnnDobbs @NotJackKemp it’s actually her tagline now https://t.co/CXExIwja67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monty Tech calls a timeout with two free throws pending for Emily St. Thomas, who has 10 of their 22.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir any suggestions for people trying to get home from Las Vegas on Flight 795 that is canceled?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOAT @JerryRice taking time to hang out with my lil man Dash. -  #DashJones 🏃  #HeirFootball 👑  #Heir7v7  ~$HOW… https://t.co/fqpv398j1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Park Planetarium https://t.co/vBVNhnqDWE via @YouTube @NickLucid This clip perfectly sums up how arbitrary an… https://t.co/OPKqHzD5XR]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do i see multiple mutuals on grindr right now.....hoe hours i guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since @rkelly and @JussieSmollett have tarnished black history month. Repost and respond woth a positive figure we… https://t.co/gnzAbfHalX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Because it’s not needed. You promised something that’s not needed. Ports of entry technologies needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm seeing more notifications related to #voiceacting being all "block this person", "don't hire this one". Blackba… https://t.co/gXAnpU9WHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MosulEye Exactly! ISIS and their affiliates have held territory and insurgency all over the world. The internation… https://t.co/wQe9aSlGxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man of God, your people have feasted on junk food all week. Set the table with the main course today and invite them to “Come and Dine!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Whodidwhatnow3 @trypticat @Mousekewitz1988 Haha 1 follower I’m not sure why I’m even bothering trying to explain l… https://t.co/69t6Rvhs4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitCityFC @MorseHunter @MSUmsoccer Welcome, Hunter! Downriver representing! #utfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t even realize they have a whole Apple store right in the middle of Grand Central]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaoticmess17 I can see the sadness in your eyes but I really hope your day gets better.  Sometimes I try to make… https://t.co/xyax5VS2XN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lovelylisaness Someone is gonna come along and sweep you off your feet, trust me 😉 just give it a little time. Happy Valentine’s day ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic #PresidentsDay honoring Post. Special edition of PAIN 1 hr 3 Co Qs and welcome FNG Hasbro! #AYE… https://t.co/nDY2mSACih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom Your state govt does not take care of its people. California govt has always stole and robbed from its… https://t.co/cVxNrIfrfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@999KISW @ryandic I’m not worthy of Ted Smith’s friendship anymore. I’ll settle for a Miles relationship, I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent way too much money having to get a new phone, but this camera is sick!  #pixel3 #camera #night #photography… https://t.co/dCpAHT1ur7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maple Grove wins the Class C Far West Regional, 44-38 over Oakfield-Alabama #preptalklive]]></document><document><![CDATA[This road is gonna take us back now, you look so fine I don’t know how to act now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAVE THE DATE “Heart Health” February 28, 2019, Free Health class at Pure Health Chiropractic. Call to reserve your… https://t.co/kzgmUa0KCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jack In The Box's new fish sandwich is da shiznit!!!  That's right... Shiznit! 😎👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBFBay @SwordsStilettos @JackieSmith114 We sure did! Come to the next session at 1:20!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you plan for? C- I have plans for the year and next few.  It is the same each year Z- why? C- I am doing… https://t.co/5kFOY2ZZs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ps 34:5 Ps 123:2 Isa 8:17 Ge 22:2 Ge 22:16 Ro 5:8 Ro 8:32 1jo 4:9 Isa 55:7 Ho 14:1 Joe 2:12 Ac 3:19 Col 1:9 1ti 2:4… https://t.co/eKcvrE4HBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Boy, I liked that interview. When we elect a Democrat as Pres. and a Democratic majority in Senate and Hou… https://t.co/6lGNmVyfuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @NBAOfficialRef for ruining the NBA, you guys make games unwatchable!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@140VGM Reminds me of some of the aquatic ruin stages in sonic CD, I forgot what the zone was called.. similar motif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewjodonnell @GCTigerTracker Pants I’m ok with, belt otherwise indifferent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domestic Terrorists and Jussie Smollett are pieces of Shit. Both cause considerable harm to victims, and undermine… https://t.co/CrF8B4jRiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I was looking at my Instagram, I noticed several ppl have started following me that I don’t know. I look at prof… https://t.co/GoKNtaZHSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusicalMoore6 @BigDaddySkye @TMobile @SamsungMobile @JohnLegere Yes I like yo roast them with there lies about Verizon and Att.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're on the smallest stage EVER and your solo comes up!  #Guitarist #Fender #fenderguitar #Telecaster… https://t.co/EFjW9zB9yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreed15 Yes.  But only in short 5 second bursts, and then he throws up. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBPipeline @jojothejet6 @Phillies @IronPigs @ReadingFightins @Threshers @BlueClaws @crosscutters @ToddZolecki… https://t.co/2iE1pOlGNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storm’s acomin - Drinking an 90 Minute Imperial IPA by @dogfishbeer @ Peniferella Moon Base / Remote Office  — https://t.co/sM7puor38z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReefManJohn @BBCNews @NPR Agreed, adhering to science/based is our credibility. And because so much is at stake I… https://t.co/zxhoObKbvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phylane21 @dangisthatlexi You should've expected this based on the spelling of "you"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some humor. #funniness #giggle #smirk #comic https://t.co/tbNqs9M5Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore this to work today and nobody noticed 😑 Maybe next time 🙃 @youthmachine @ Dogpatch, San Francisco https://t.co/xciqfPMxHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haydenwilberger Clearly Tequila is the answer  Arizona &amp; Meredith agree https://t.co/uypMZxJSQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamwandasykes @realDonaldTrump Yep, sadly he was able to fool so many people to vote for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RAND PAUL IS FLAT OUT WRONG ON THIS! YOU NEED TO BACK YOUR PRESIDENT MR. PAUL OR SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES IN 2020!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGAmbrose Not a coincidence they all come as we have a steady centre back partnership. A lot of our “poor” perform… https://t.co/4JWUqKE94X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyleyAngus Also if possible Mortal Kombat by Warner Bros. https://t.co/vQflJtPe9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normalmente haría mi maleta antes de irme, pero el camión sale a 7am osease tengo que salir del depa tipo 6:40 y po… https://t.co/sodLMilSOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennesseeDonkey There will be an an apology statement rolling in the crawl at the bottom of the screen in the morn… https://t.co/fLElEmXWwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Buckeyes freshman Justin Ahrens warms up for Michigan State, which features older brother Kyle. @ Breslin Student… https://t.co/0viGtmTUGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelinaPompeani ps hope to finally meet you 3/7  when @ @BlueJacketsNHL . I like how you seem so enthsiastic for al… https://t.co/4a0TGZxVEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeyWrestle Which would have been a better dual this year: PSU / Iowa or PSU / Oklahoma State?  Was at GIA today -… https://t.co/vg4AOqhy10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomradman @hintze_steve @LittleMissFlint @realDonaldTrump Last I checked, the City Council of Flint was responsibl… https://t.co/Ua3wIX9dat]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think of this 0.63 ac lot home I found on Zillow? https://t.co/8slmcn7p8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mama said you’re not supposed to have showers beyond your first child and I felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How did Obama get away with giving $1.7 billion in cash and gave Iran access to $5.7b. If he can d… https://t.co/aiukyjifqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[She and the rest are asses when they pass bills for abortions then turn around with gun control they are sick ONE is a Second Amendment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe Actually, she is a dembarrassment!  But, there are so many she gets lost in the crowd...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moira @Amtrak Is this train 66? Trying to see if I’ll make it back to New York tonight or not…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam22 Let me find out Tommy, Chuckie, Phil and Lil are out here gang-banging.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asknbid @BertelSchmitt Yes, which is why the new cities aren't today's cities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazminfinn I’ve see a lot of people move and change their lifestyles. Dunno what that’s about, but I support it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise taxes on the rich and corporations and we will improve things foor the middle class and poor https://t.co/0YktGVXCWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Zapatero: "Algunos d los actores q dirigen desde la Casa Blanca la oper #Venezuela, son los mismos q dirigían la o… https://t.co/7OGCebkhcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selfcarepapi You really don’t have to see anything you can move about your day it doesn’t even concern your ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[— Paseo Nuevo, Santa Barbara  The fortress will be abandoned, the noisy city deserted; citadel and watchtower will… https://t.co/u6IH1WPkJW]]></document></documents></author>