<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ADKwoodswoman Of course they did... you rock. Btw thanks for the post today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Love - Alone Again Or (Original Version) https://t.co/8THewIi8Hy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFlakeStaff The Holy Scan Remains on My Head/Mind-Trump help. You can Hear U.S. Govs Speak on Satellite as That… https://t.co/wpCZPba31k]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's THERAPEUTIC THURSDAY! Roses are Red Violets are Blue If you have pain Dr Davidson will Adjust You Happy VALENS… https://t.co/GaDcHqtSBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out that Emily Deschanel, who plays Bones in the show Bones, is married to the guy who plays Rickety C… https://t.co/mQ01csOaDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeannaMarie208 @DrJaimeFriedman @DrJRMarcelin @EmmyBetz @NicoleNugentPhD @meganranney @shawnsidhumd @DrHowardLiu… https://t.co/A9Fdgwzgom]]></document><document><![CDATA[#colbyexposingsecrets (how many of these can we do?) Lmao i vaped my brothers vape skksk i was bored but yea...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or the Dems worried about future presidents might do....it's all about President Trump and the hatred we were all t… https://t.co/kGwWWVQiy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @LisaVanderpump ..... We Believe You!  Dorit is not fit to be a doggie mommie!  #ImWithHer 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel @JimmyKimmelLive @MittRomney Hey Jimmy! I hope you're Jewish. Trumps saying we Dems are antisemetic. F… https://t.co/S9ZfXUuiSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karen’s Killer Book Bench: CRASHING INTO HER, Love On Cue by Mia Sosa #Multicultural #Romance https://t.co/W4VaV35t0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[The slut joke aside, I need to know what kind of citrus this is. I have questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessianicVegan @EventsVeg @DrJSchumacher Thanks for your suggestion! Several have requested and I hope to get some… https://t.co/BcwNzoNbZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErisLovesMovies Yessss... it’s the being on my own for a couple hours and being exhausted that’s making my mind go… https://t.co/pzdCqBHA6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are getting old and are worried about the creases and wrinkles, the #bestsolution is here for you;… https://t.co/c5alCfT5yC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarlaShine The Russians are spreading this anti-Vaxxer propaganda and you are falling for it hook line and sinker. #Traitor #Uneducated]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather outside is frightful... but this SNOW is SO delightful!!! ☃️❄️ #Vegasweather https://t.co/D33X2PD1y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I make mistakes at work and I understand but some of these mistakes other people make absolutely blow my… https://t.co/65csUSVczk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zaal’Koris Vas Qwib-Qwib saying he had the option to serve on more respectably named ships like the Defrahnz or the… https://t.co/ZOJ34mzQFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dailydaysspoilers #dool #days Mon Mar 11th  @matthew_ashford @lucasbrentley @oliviakeegann @TMegiaAI10… https://t.co/rX7VxTf4K1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah because Cook does take a lot of time to say with it being a one syllable word]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourmusicsucks That's all I am asking for right now. We have to know each other before we can take it to a higher level hon ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Agreed. As a contractor, I am feeling the same huge sense of dread I was feeling December 23. He sa… https://t.co/7vQIUmjTzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[LORD, Help me to WALK as You walked...hold my hand. Help me to SPEAK as You speak...Guard my tongue. Help me to LOV… https://t.co/FmNEszNSiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling under the weather today making me look a bit like Kreig here. If you’re feeling the same, be sure to get so… https://t.co/nmfQB7Ypgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@63chevyman @MrsRabbitResist There are things that are part of my life that I can't rationally explain. At least no… https://t.co/faIFltM1S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making #Herstory, join me in congratulating @chiquitae126 in becoming the FIRST WOMAN ever to be drafted in the NBA… https://t.co/Q642Bbete2]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is definitely in my top 3 favorite carpool karaoke vids now  Jonas Brothers Carpool Karaoke https://t.co/wOdZ6XXXjn via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[#billyporter wears tuxedo gown at 2019 Oscars: ‘I’m not a drag queen, I’m a man in a dress’ #hellya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I legitimately could go out and explore the city. But, like, I have $20 😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodsNWO What are you doing Timothy why are you on my page like that do you want me messaging your people I can sta… https://t.co/bUxbwMiy9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @ChaseRiceMusic #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries.… https://t.co/BNaKeQv9nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay the girl working at starbucks said i was cute even after i was working in the cold for 5 hours, so 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fo you commemorate your anniversary and your friendiversary? Phone stands, of course. 💕   As always, check my b… https://t.co/yzdWeALv90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winny_atheart @Absolover @AussieKerrie @Adriana53871022 @L_Ithil @Malirensch @C_licare @TinaBull6 @abouttomellis… https://t.co/eBVpO26HdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!- MARDI GRAS FAT ASS TUESDAY! EVERY TUESDAY NIGHT- DirtyBurty Presents #dirtyburty16 INVADE "THE HOLE" TUES… https://t.co/5CEMoYZKid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, where's Claire? *frantic search* "Oh, there she is." @ First Unitarian Church of Rochester https://t.co/cVHRpYlKw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomLanktree Who would want to carry it around? Innovative for sure. Trying to figure out what problem it solves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomsThoughts @PeteButtigieg Yes and Woot! The correct spelling Buttigieg! Now for pronunciation. I’m projecting a rise in the polls too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @KevinRickard4 @cpoole27 @ChristineBemis2 @MrCoachEli @ElizaWallace27 @BarbaraGruener @RitaWirtz… https://t.co/RhaMYnQ1rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got really drunk at home yesterday taking tequila shots. I think I past out before 8pm smh, woke up at 11 and reali… https://t.co/NrnLoZgYyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, health care shouldn’t be just for people who can afford it. Blocking care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/pOxqbMvSOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude, WTAF. I’ve been trying to get from Sacramento to Reno for 12h now. DRIVE SAFELY PEOPLE! 30MPH!!!!!!! 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week if anyone ask what im watching on tv it’s going to be @latelateshow &amp; @jonasbrothers #theboysareback… https://t.co/YQygQjLWNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to nicki minaj on the M train with my feet on the seats! YA LIKE A CANDY STORE AND IM A TODDLAAAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of  how you feel about a person,  always do what is right even if it seems to be the road less travelled… https://t.co/1RjL9yC6z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We began our day by watching some of our talented and dedicated Bureau Valley basketball players being interviewed… https://t.co/FgqhZxv9nA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo hoo! Congratulations on your new role @JennaBushHager - what a joy it’s been seeing you fill in on the 4th hour… https://t.co/V5epUchpC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[At EdCamp Boston.   Yes, on a Saturday!!  Love this form of PD! #edcampBOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartyCheddarCat Wow Cheddar fabulous job. Can we see video of the wheel and you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until they become conscious they will never rebel and until after they have rebelled they cannot become conscious. - 1984, George Orwell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Schmoedown for wonderful live event! Great commentary by @markellislive (middle name ‘Edward’😉) and… https://t.co/U8dXbx9y45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmberBrownWV I have Cline and Roberts. They don’t say much thankfully but it still isn’t much better. 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I think OC Transpo is the worst form of transportation, then I take Via Rail and I remember how much worse it is 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said therefore unto you, that ye shall die in your sins: for if ye believe not that I am he, ye shall die in your… https://t.co/dGM10shH5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last game ever as a DU Pep Band guitar player. Thanks to everyone who came to all the games and supported our panth… https://t.co/7wMzN6lmUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to force spring by wearing pastel colors.  My feet are freezing. https://t.co/T8bPe9KZax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another view of her sexy toes #feet #barefeet #barefoot #bare #milf  #footfetish #footworship #toes #soles… https://t.co/n51DE1tX8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld For low income women, this could be a death sentence.  Planned Parenthood is the only healthcare option… https://t.co/kwX6AqTqP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylejguy5 shhhushing the Cassell crowd was one of those #uva #acc moments❤️ #allinthefeels @UVAMensHoops #wahoowa https://t.co/VxtHasEd7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Tuesday! #MyrtleBeach #Sunrise @EdPiotrowski @MyMyrtleBeach https://t.co/CpBTsweMOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for the Mercy and Grace God ! Mercy is deliverance from judgment. Grace is extending kindness to the unwor… https://t.co/dwxKG9xM7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff #BadJokeTuesday This made me think of Dep Pini What are Ninjas favorite type of Shoes? Sneakers! Have a Great Day Everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐴Like our photos...Follow our IG🐎  🏇These photos were taken by me!🐴 🏇Photography by: Connie Wheeler 🐎@WheelerConnie… https://t.co/GkzE2YwBoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faerymere @StormHour @ThePhotoHour Happy Valentine's Day to you! https://t.co/yOiia6uUaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little video from our Gainesville PGF trip.  These girls keep the fun in playing competitive ball.  Great weekend… https://t.co/bAa2i6MTXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @EyeDrFigueroa @POTUS The Unions need to realize their Democratic Party is going through the back door to ruin them! #SocialismDestroys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hundreds of documents are being made public as the state investigates Central Maine Power over record-high bills.… https://t.co/Dgnk1qyV6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basquiat1998 @Hye_Mike we doing this with the m3 when it's nice out at shell?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #Gracie for #CutestPet at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/HnVutU2ew6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan u need to address the national debt u promised to control.  u lied to us!!!  fiscal conservative, needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hair y’all niggas be growing be saving y’all cause y’all heads be shaped weird 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anastasia_Tash SAME. I think I’ve watched it at least 3 times. All seasons 😂 I heard it’s supposed to be coming back on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg tell the news of Luke Perry is not true 💔💔😭 I loved him in 90210 !! Oh no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to our crazy family @StellaNews8 🎉 @CBS8 @thecwsandiego #morningtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@om_caroline @Dama_Targaryen @DeputadoFederal @cirogomes @ptbrasiI Sem dúvida, quem elege é o povo.Foi este povo q… https://t.co/o0qbdgBGkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FairContractNow #CTUACTSstrike #CICSGreed #WhereIsShaw #CICSSchools #KindaBigDeal #AreWeCICS https://t.co/lAbpWxBEMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social experiment: catch pneumonia and be isolated in your tiny dorm room for a week straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarryMoore So with the cut why can’t the wall be funded, built and through with! Proud of this President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, it is possible to fall in love with them even more. 😍😭💗 #JonasBrothers https://t.co/RjlfU7rL1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanpeters you have amazing talent I would love to be able to have an intelligent conversation with you. If not, i… https://t.co/uEdBhwIGdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Only thing I agree with you on, Then and only then will we find out just who really colluded with Rus… https://t.co/7oQiK4VgQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy but beautiful weather as the Pineapple Express rolls through! https://t.co/y89s8WP8In]]></document><document><![CDATA[ay profe, como le explico que por mas que avise que cancelará la clase, como quiera nadie iba a ir 🙇🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcn4eva Could a fellow #Patriot get a follow back? Would appreciate it! #PatriotsUnite]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needed this Friday motivation!! We have got this people! Go out there and crush it...be kind...be awesome!!… https://t.co/vwucG4zsyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Star_Gem @TrinityResists @JohnFKennedy My grandparents immigrated here from Sweden. Shortly after arriving my… https://t.co/9SIZxEJUgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RepAustinDavis for your ongoing support of the students in the Mon Valley!… https://t.co/2gdXWrfkPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ookiee Yeah. It’s crazy that it’s just accepted now. I have had many Lyft/Uber drivers from Sac and even some from Redding. Insanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet all these upperclassman and niggas over 21 be over there side street pimpin 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let my silence speak louder  than what my words have.  Maybe then, will everyone see what  I’ve been trying to say.… https://t.co/KJhX7h6Bbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Benefits of Playing Music Help Your Brain More Than Any Other Activity @johnrampton https://t.co/iLQH9W6iLd via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Vote with our President in the emergency at the border.  You know it is needed.  #SupportOurPresidentTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wwefastlane @WWEAleister this intro is fn badass!! Along w/ @kingricochet will be the NEW #rawtagteamchampions yup… https://t.co/lLguvu3KMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro I am starting to believe more and more she is a puppet controlled by others.  Have you seen her when sh… https://t.co/0yg3jswKRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myhood #neighborhoodmom #reallife #blessedchaos #basketball #springtime @ Our House https://t.co/zjnTvz6yOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Fat Tuesday and another year that I’m thankful that I no longer have to deal with the HELL people put themselv… https://t.co/U3WBl86HmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉At Sociallyin, we host free webinars. If you think we could be of help to you, go to https://t.co/xoU8eFy9O1!… https://t.co/IBQxX7nZjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les conjectures ne sont pas nouveaux. Il n’y a que les acteurs qui changent sur la scène politique… https://t.co/TO1d7CtqYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing you a month filled with much love, joy and peace. 🙏💜🙌🌟🦋🌷☘️✌️ #positivethinking #positivevibes #truth https://t.co/Zzuj10AvAt]]></document></documents></author>