<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[:LOOK.ANYONE who makes you feel selfish for taking care of yourself, can👏🏾DIP. 👏🏾 ...And that includes family.… https://t.co/uaTMdo7xbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[He knows all about Epstein’s teen sex trafficking because Trump partied there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy St. Patrick's Day Dessert Ideas (Perfect for a St. Paddy's Day Party) https://t.co/ggjuMfd7un… https://t.co/IR8hizpwrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GroovyHistory Beautiful. You should see "Wild Orchid." She is great in that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HermannTLombard @ParadoxBeer @GoodBeerTweet @SommBeer @bodyfit67 @badhopper @cellmavin @wolv54b1 @lhtetrick… https://t.co/NWZbppsgTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a diner in Texas listening to an older couple say “how many of the others were made up for personal gain” refere… https://t.co/ClMcVDXvb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanaKStewart Will never happen, Alana. It's why I haven't watched this mess for over 10yrs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISO: someone to go to rfoc with me for dinner  It’s grilled cheese night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods He played his card and lost at the table of “ .... freedom and justice for all” #MAGA https://t.co/zcedY6dCy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[apparently there's some confusion if i tweet something sad ab missing someone it prob ISNT about my ex lol. nice tr… https://t.co/Ct4VPwUBp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta No that was clearly not the case because the overhead bins were still open when i boarded,people were still… https://t.co/kCwuTeXNf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis hola show perro!! Es mi cumpleaños 🎂, me pueden cantar las mañanitas por favor, buen día e inicio de semana!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snifflesnack It's normal for the paat to rattle you in early sobriety. It even can do that after being in recovery for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll say this right now. I promise I’ll go to war for my child. Momma bear is someone you do not poke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here in Kansas City, the children will have to go to school in July at this rate...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am surprised by this. Looking customers in the eye and saying hello decreases shoplifting, and ensures you the cu… https://t.co/z3ROXqphRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the feeing when I imagine a strong and dramatic modern in my head for my future dance class 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn girl. Smh... Yes, rejection sucks. But have some pride. Accept the signs. Take the L and keep it moving. FckN… https://t.co/jla1oNu9VD]]></document><document><![CDATA[TY @StreamableL for your expedited recording of @poetry4kids Famous Poets: Dr. Seuss - A special presentation for o… https://t.co/k5ETfx0CFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robbie47737658 @LarrysTwin99 I get sick of obsessing about someone I like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/NFQWwhWOfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBakhand @haseofspades I should binge watch just cause lol. I'm tired of Bob's burgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[*and sons *and all people @ Grand Design Wellness https://t.co/NsubG3b8xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also these girls kept calling me cute and saying I looked like a little Isabelle with my cap and goggles and her si… https://t.co/KYWOWvp6kM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want some chocolate chip muffins... but like... leaving the house is just too much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corruption is alive and well with a corrupt “attorney general”: Ken Paxton and his corrupt, conflicted wife, a stat… https://t.co/F8396bzx1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelt2019 I love that he was 1 of 3!!! Of course he was. Leo is perfect.:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's picture of the day. @ Hesperia, California https://t.co/SrWV1mXHAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Clara CA Tue Feb 26th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Showers Lo 51 WEDNESDAY Chance Of Showers Hi 61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNinSeattle @ShannaBurnette I totally carried it down the trail and took it home.🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I thought I was all that when I got to 200 followers. Today I hit 1,000 and think I am really all that. Until… https://t.co/TFksfmSYzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta go to a Drake concert, a Beyoncé concert, &amp; a Moneybagg concert &amp; I’ll be content w my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trapsoul by @brysontiller is still such a damn vibe https://t.co/icuE1GBXZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[has water like not been hitting right to anyone else lately... or is that just me??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock And yes anecdotal I have tried to self taper out of fear. And very slowly. The biggest symptom? Chest pai… https://t.co/a8Nup77ubz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @FundTheGap Paloma and Myriel for receiving Honorable Mention for their NYC tenement project for… https://t.co/Uti4t6ks8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7thmanontheice Ty. It was amazing. Mmmm soo good sooo full. But always room for more wine 🍷🍷🍷🍷🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@activist360 @Lawrence @RepMarkMeadows Gop are so ignorant, they forget video cameras have been in existence for a very long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My job needs to fix this damn vending machine who carries cash anymoreeeeeeeeeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[QOTD: "I like how you have been dressing up for Valentine's Day for days leading up to today."… https://t.co/KMNaMcT0dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marvellousways Yikes! I had one run across the bed toward me once. I shrieked and ran. 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@an_DREA5 Sooo are you under the impression I'm gonna be checking you out... mcscuse me bitch? All ur getting from… https://t.co/fSxeyEHlaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSF_MPS @GeorgiaTech @APSphysics When dear friends make science so utterly interesting! @Sabetta_]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible poem that could be used to teach perspective. https://t.co/J1RxdYC8Fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phl17  my Flopper, sorry to say he’s going into kidney failure. https://t.co/9JDJ7GCFQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AmWriting #Fantasy #KidLit #MG #ChildrensBooks #DreamsDoComeTrue #booksigning @BNBuzz #RainbowCrystal🌈💎 https://t.co/neyKAyAHR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[DO YOU BELIEVE DONALD TRUMP BELONGS IN PRISON? I know its a stupid poll, but this is close and it shouldn't be.  FL… https://t.co/p4qiUQnrda]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world got better and brighter this weekend 💙 Loved celebrating two extraordinary people become one @hnconnolly… https://t.co/lhrd35d2E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Who is this Susan you speak of? Should I be jealous? Because I am. Devestated... crying beside my televisio… https://t.co/mykBTuM1zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howierayner ❄️ Ice running through their veins.   I’d like to know who they are.   Too bad more people don’t read… https://t.co/BqIh0WQxXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knightprowler71 @elle62055526 @fred_guttenberg I’m sorry Seth, but no. No we’re not; we’re not, until every person… https://t.co/vpfA51nmam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeniferabreutv @CityofSgf More info about the developing program here: https://t.co/irGJ9qNuBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your state known for #woodenblanks #NationalWomensDay #beachscapes #bosslady https://t.co/OKvvQtqDdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can feel it in my bones that TS7 is coming........ I will lose my shit..... #TaylorSwift #WHATAREYOUDOING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier this week I had the opportunity to speak on a panel at a briefing in the U.S. Senate on the Trump administr… https://t.co/FxMMZQcpKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrville This was unexpected and so great! But still waiting for Mercer to sing @SethMacFarlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Mustache You to Read with Me by me! Available at Amazon and https://t.co/1f1iKzL1ld https://t.co/kadpKAbouV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was born with a silver spoon in my hand it’s just old and bent and beat to hell but members of my clan have used… https://t.co/DcANNIOAbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiegoFinn98 when you realize you like single Finn better than taken Finn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying how I feel about someone or what they do to them is draining. Instead of tackling the problem. They feel lik… https://t.co/GOVROsmik4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday Afternoon with this guy ‍ Altar Girl Chapel https://t.co/LMdRV7dfhl https://t.co/PBuggEygyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is this "Love Light" in the Divine Light of this Awakening that will always take you to places where you need… https://t.co/JkfUNMPPnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite valentine! Still! ❤️❤️❤️ He brings me flowers and fills my car with gas, cleans the kitchen and does la… https://t.co/Y4Hmg2vxLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras Y’All #fattuesday @ The 10 Spot https://t.co/HDILxKzPdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylesaidthis Go to Instagram and look at dog profiles. They always make me happy. Start with @ sophiebeeandfriends (that’s my dog haha)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating as only a Beagle can eat🐾❤️😳🐶 #beaglesofinstagram #midwestbrew #midwestbeaglerescue @MWBeagleRescue @ Chicag… https://t.co/jUDkpjsXPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonmtaggart @BatmanGothamUSA @Kimperiale @itbmeang @FeeAngel223 @LinaCovfefe @clearimages @PantasticPuppy… https://t.co/W59Q2o87KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaricorSoriano I can’t imagine how scary that could be, but so glad your family is so loving and accepting 🧡💚 #YouDoYou girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJ_Denhollander @R_Denhollander Am I the only one bothered by the double apostrophes? https://t.co/C0LrBvfONY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natbourrus Ok. Mais au niveau concret des propo pour  les états membres.  Du genre commission, sanctions sur les r… https://t.co/4ULswxUZXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAaron03 @dcwheel28 I have 3 midterms Friday lol sooo that’s a hard pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kerry_Fehrmann Congrats to Ally on an outstanding basketball career...and to you and Peggy for raising such an awesome young lady 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kateonmars @walrusmagazine Seriously. It worked, and now I'm a Walrus reader. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah’s Ark ‘Blueprints’ Found: 4,000-Year-Old Details of Instructions  https://t.co/8XXmQobeYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNBELIEVABLE, what in the world are we becoming? Is this rotten brats mommy going to defend his behavior or will sh… https://t.co/ZwCtCJzLcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinncy I’ll be the aunt who takes you shopping even though she hates the mall, but wants to spend time with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ireyT2yuCE  Don't miss out - for the next three days my book is free to download on kindle.  #wedding… https://t.co/ESveQIiYqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twinpeaksgiant Yes it did but did you actually read the article? Nobody really knows what they talked about. If yo… https://t.co/YgI1Y3WXKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sumjazfi Wow! You can tell I have more print experience than broadcast. I’m not very aware when I’m in the camera’s shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the CIF SS Girls Wrestling  about to watch Alex take them all down #grandmais yourbestfan… https://t.co/e8Jirj1BEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @YouTube This is greatness!!! Love it! 🔥🔥🔥🔥 @joeymcintyre Griffin is adorable!!♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @mattdpearce It would be a places to stay away from for liberals. I'd love the list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GO BESTIEEEE!! I’m so happy and proud of you😍😍 @savwheeler4 can’t wait to be teammates again🤞🏼💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a love hate relationship with the fact that some songs take me back to certain times in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Seattle, what's your favorite local coffee shop in #Olympia? Ideally excellent coffee + seating + outlets to wo… https://t.co/b4spr5sbDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamabear_lu @TomRevisited1 @PsychoMetalHed @RodStryker @DailyCaller Sez you. You show yourself to be a hateful per… https://t.co/9N1rNRhbnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShadowingTrump UVA hired this guy for awhile. Not pleased as a VA taxpayer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles why did it just occur to me that you are a Gemini omg everything makes sense now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked my mom to take me to my brothers house ... how she figure I wanted to go to this car wash with her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter @TwitterSupport MY ACCOUNT is high speed DATA yet you refuse to let me look at MY HOME PAGE, TWEET LINKS ETC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2: I have accepted a challenge from @MrsAmySpencer to post #7BooksILove-no explanation, no reviews-just cover(s… https://t.co/poKIJTgWZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing at least 30m of yoga everyday to manage my chronic pain has its flexi benefits- I couldn’t have done standing… https://t.co/2tWGie2u7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssholeToMany @Arhamur_ @Big_Money_Robo I tried to get on but the servers were fucked up and wouldn’t let me log in online]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the Registered Republicans are at 26% of the electorate Below both Dems and Independents]]></document><document><![CDATA[SURPRISE, Owen Benjamin is trashing Jews AGAIN!!!! WHAT'S UP @ADL ?????? https://t.co/DnfYXslYIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just swiped right on this dude because he’s a carpenter and his furniture was...sexy? Not a pun, was sincerely turn… https://t.co/1VosdkI4Dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if there was a story where a lover is reincarnated into a new body, Mets her former lover from another life an… https://t.co/RGlO2ev2LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Rant: It is so difficult being younger and an entrepreneur. People constantly ask me “Well how old are you? Yo… https://t.co/B2FoS0LTQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briglacquette Yay Briget way to go! You are so deserving of rhis honour. You are very inspiring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love making new friends, but hate when I find out they’re the bored moms on Facebook who post a 50 times a day. https://t.co/7peP1RmTK9]]></document></documents></author>