<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[He that is faithful in that which is least is faithful also in much: and he that is unjust in the least is unjust a… https://t.co/GUVCVYCHjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorites from today. Landscapes are cool and all but I NEED MODELS!! Hit me up! https://t.co/qOClsgmLjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with this cutie pie! #papi #familyfirst @ Taqueria El Sabor https://t.co/yqyft3ExHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @IvankaTrump WITCHCRAFTW             W     COWBUDDHA     TH i S ANoTE Religion is Founded  Upon Beliefs stronger than facts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the woman on Winner Cake All who just described her creation as “artsy fartsy” - that’s not appetizing at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[However the season ends please just don’t lose to THE CATS tomorrow night or Big 12 tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spnfullofthght @WineAndComics @TopherHarless @megfitz89 This only happened because I really like milkshakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffaloRoam9375 The thing that got me was when I started to see myself shape up, once this happened I was hooked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier If anyone thinks were my currently in a civil war.. they need to wake up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@740coolmike Makes sense. Pretty sure I’ve had PayPal since buying my Tippman98 on EBay back in the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Into Chicago //  #whpweekend.     . .  . . For an Instagram crop 👉🏼 swipe . . . sonyalpha  a7rii  ISO 50  F/11  4.0… https://t.co/7rSUOYer2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s #SpreadPositivity! Just doing this so @chrisdelia can see me on the interwebs 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheDoggiesInMyLife #💜 #RescueDogs #AdoptDontShop @ Oakland, California https://t.co/lngVq24XpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1MinuteLifeTip...  Maximize your happiness #_dreweric #SelfDiscoverycoach #authenticity https://t.co/cebNCm97Ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DishingDisney LOL! While I was an usher there, I was Po (Kung fu Panda), Alex (Madagascar), and Ogress Fiona (Shre… https://t.co/7KsJZhB8hL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the past I've asked why should I forgive people for how they've wronged me.  The Spirit of the Lord spoke to me… https://t.co/0fgqNOlRzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Water_Malone82 That’s it I’m cutting it. That’s too far and you know it]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Carson City: snow, 26°F 92% humidity, wind 1mph, pressure 1011mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio Well Blazo, you better be finding some of those people with that extra money in their pockets cause y… https://t.co/S6lCdU5GAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[KNOW YOUR LIMITS -#Flashback to 2 years ago when I was just as helpful with my daughter’s chem homework as I am tod… https://t.co/rvhYrjAErZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BloggerFrank87 Everything you stated is 100% true. Good shit my guy. You really got it figured out. Time to break… https://t.co/vIcWn2zqCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XtremeEffect @XFL2kcom Highly doubt it, you say that like everyone loves March madness more than football, yet Sup… https://t.co/CTRtusTDCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Oh come on!!! We will never get them back for future generations if allowed to kill these beautiful anima… https://t.co/xrOONLbQic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoopbryJack @RealJamesWoods Here's some media. The New Yorker did an extensive investigation and expose. I'm sure… https://t.co/EV3sLxjTVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I played semi drunk babysitter for people in their 30s.   Mission accomplished  Everyone is asleep safely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra 1/2 AOC represents a a subset of a generation that refuses to appreciate the toils of past Americans… https://t.co/yhjcONkM0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laylamarlene Lovely ever thing just right love it, https://t.co/9rmlwR0wiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else find it odd that the same people who call the mainstream media “fake news” are putting a large num… https://t.co/j4KhMhpN8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubasl @Montchelle66 @Yoorrii9 @XBaderAbrahamsX @LJT_is_me @bdr_bdr9 @Zegrinder @Headsnipe011 @bonmarche946… https://t.co/cYLfR8vdDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My past times include, singing, being in photos, and grabbing piggyback rides from friends in the audience 😜… https://t.co/t8ko4xnO3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMonzoRadio why isn’t your podcast with Chris not called the new Natural Disasters?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where you’re able to switch that to “nobody is good enough for you”.. you start living different]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter What odds Ireland will beat France tomorrow 😀🏉😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Debates to be held over two consecutive nights because there’s so many candidates 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made an insta just for my photography so feel free to follow that if you want! If you don’t just know that you’re w… https://t.co/DvZzWc2haD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for TU’s immense database with endless articles to explore. None of my key words brought anything up. I’m n… https://t.co/hU1O5WhdTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Montana it’s been real 🤙🏂 @ Big Sky, Montana https://t.co/805ay5XXlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can't believe there was a time in my life when i went to the same bar &amp; club 3 times a week LOL wtf was wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/740UI9irHe.  #GoTime #Smoothie #Protein #Recipe #HealthyRecipe #Healthy #InspiredToBeBettee… https://t.co/VaxpZcErzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, New York! :) #Sunrise 06:27, noon 12:08, sunset 17:50 EST (UTC-5), March 3. Day length: 11h 23m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver just asked me what an aux chord was https://t.co/z9Oi6gw6Ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoSweetDivinity How about you stop torturing yourself and get an iPhone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbKC3 @struck_brett @ChadLeistikow He doesn’t need the one to get to Rim! Start cook in the corner dribble han… https://t.co/uV9w75cvTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t like this extra attention. I just   feel peoples eyes burning a whole through me.😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazlyn_victoria @dxyle Thought I was the only crazy mf who this happens too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/m2qGjZd6ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowes Wow. I figured you would say reach out by DM. Not that your first reply would completely address my concerns. Thank you very much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Modelo Especial by @GrupoModelo_MX at @oraclearena — https://t.co/QU9WZGCTFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[How tf is this man going to question his teams drive when he’s doing shit like this?? Man has lost his damn mind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[-50 degrees that night.  No one got shot but mr. Smollett gets attacked.  #FoxAndFriends]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I ordered my first @Tesla. I hope this is a joke. #Model3 https://t.co/pLIzE02SFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elankaroll @UIUC4Israel @SSI_Movement @ChabadOnCampus @IlliniRabbi Ok back to the gym]]></document><document><![CDATA[.......EXCELLENT marketing I’m giving this man my coins as soon as I get paidt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We’re waiting for the sun to come out because we don’t have de-icing equipment.” https://t.co/Om09EtL8V7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo hi Chris; why trump demand secret clearance for his son in law, when in Israel, Netanyahu is accused of… https://t.co/6dmAZhER0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC IS SUCKING TYRANTS DICKS A TRUMP KLAN THING, or they just like tyrant dick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going down on March 2nd. This event is open to high school and youth league coaches. High school coaches need… https://t.co/nwdXmBAFYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When shoplift crews repeated shrink your on camera floor, that is a blackmark. -Retail Insurance Expert. @#target… https://t.co/7chg20QT9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye today I did some sprints with my brotha @RodJesusAngel and I gotta say not bad for being 40lbs heavier than him… https://t.co/Xuz7MjSfN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness in the dark......let’s finish....what we started https://t.co/wO4ZImIrsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaCx3 @Tayferwafer Cancel everyone who makes cauliflower “buffalo wings”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tim_fall What is haiku form  again? I don’t remember due To lack of sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Region 2-2A Powerlifting Champion Yellowjackets!! Great job all coaches and lifters!!… https://t.co/Iq5itdYAxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rorymon Ah yeah I’m sure the little ones are keeping you busy.  That’s bad ass, enjoy the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should only come back if they have a legit shot to make the playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although it’s only 2games in 2days, @kkms32 is on🔥 at the plate: 4/5 and 3/3 respectively with 1HR, 2Triples, 2Doub… https://t.co/XHZW6449mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPlanktonguy For sure. Not looking forward to how my return from parental leave will go, especially as I was give… https://t.co/3spuYwNOF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, whole lotta people need to hear this, it’s a lot of names on my hit list 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@albertochimal @JohnPicacio @YalitzaAparicio 👏👏👏 Alberto, amazing article and retrospect on the subject. These have… https://t.co/RPWabeKvFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO The tail wag when you peek around the tree may be the sweetest thing I’ve ever seen on Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better way start week than heavy lifting of chest and triceps followed with 15 minutes of cardio conditioning!… https://t.co/58ter0fnik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proof that @univpugetsound students have remarkable talent. I showed off some #MicrobialArt by former #Bio350… https://t.co/SswSs4YZJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you guys act like I drive like this smh wait till I get a motorcycle 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zone QOD on @1037TheBuzz  What is your favorite college rivalry? Feel free to write in if you don't see yours here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBHomeEnt Just watched it again a few nights ago.  Second favorite movie of all time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not Radical nust gullible enough to swallow their own line of shit Thank God some of us can think for ourselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[5-star rated Bipolar Me is available on Payhip at https://t.co/GUs2It62S5 for $2.00 less in paperback at $13.00 and… https://t.co/OohO6lJrKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting day today @FBCConcordNC with @gordonfort preaching in our 10:45 service. Also, we’ll get an update on our… https://t.co/W4MJGIADCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parkercurry2 @tylerhood35 I, um, don’t hate it? Idk, from a tournament excitement perspective it’s not as fun, but… https://t.co/hR9C0UqlLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see I peeped it, pussy is power  That proud feeling we get knowin' that pussy is ours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy a 3 años de su muerte se le recuerda a este gran señor. Don Carlos Herrera Araluce con gran respeto y admiració… https://t.co/RgDsrEbwVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindacohn @NHLCanes @NHL Don, go to the Thrift Shop, buy a new suit, then don’t forget to take your meds. Still a… https://t.co/syqEfJBjTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirectorRB3 @the_moviebob @GraceRandolph @PNemiroff @enthusiamy @SquadLeaderAce @maudegarrett @amycassandramtz Mau… https://t.co/RuZohDwlcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatMcKiernan @bostonherald Congrats! Here's to following your dream. Best of luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the Magician in Residence at the EastLine Theatre in Wantagh, NY, I have the privilege of bringing a wide variet… https://t.co/2EmQiEhYZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spirits On Bourbon is now my go to bar while in town for the week. https://t.co/PdhguRGpwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Him: “Can I have a blowjob ?”  Her: “Wtf, No ?”  Him: “...I have Tickets to the Cardi B Concert tonight...”  Her: https://t.co/u9zFp1e8m0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breath in Breath out. Let go of the negative, believe in the positive. Everything is better and anything is possible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laissez le bon temps rouler to all the  Party people on #FatTuesday down in New Orleans! And Fat Tuesday participants in Mobile party on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @GOPLeader @GOPChairwoman @senatemajldr @SenateGOP @HouseGOP @tedcruz @Morning_Joe @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grace516G @jsoniatmerchant @jennycohn1 @stevesilberman If your feeding them into a scanner they're vulnerable2 bot… https://t.co/T88yT1A7Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting March ahead... Keynote travel: @Oracle #ModernCx - Las Vegas @SMExaminer #SMMW19 - San Diego K3 Mastermind… https://t.co/nazw4rOzxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @GoodDads for putting together another great event to spend quality time with two of our kiddos yesterday… https://t.co/NdBAVyRzKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siriusxmvolume @goodymade @SIRIUSXM Pink Floyd Echoes the screaming, and the father of song sound effects Spike Jones Cocktails for Two]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncthayer @GSchoeney In that situation one screen gets you open. You're given something you haven't earned. Good… https://t.co/mnK1ZHprJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU DO UNDERSTAND THE JEWISH CULT RELIGION IS LIE ABSOLUTE CRIMINAL LIE ABSOLUTE INJUSTICE JURISDICTION AUTHORITY R… https://t.co/mDutqXrDtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting lineups for Oak Ridge vs. College Park + weather forecast for the evening. Grace Fanset will start at pitc… https://t.co/cmJSIpYXQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se me cayó la toalla como #AndyBenavides #andybenavides video https://t.co/EepEURfKVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaidy_guti Bendiciones y pronta recuperación, #juntosporla2da 🏆 🦅⚽️🥅🇲🇽 https://t.co/J63554C696]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lake is wearing its mountain-range disguise this morning. https://t.co/ShVxdxAt5n]]></document></documents></author>