<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MsSheliaRay @BlackInkCrew ...take my chances. BTW I also am the only light skinned female in the projects and nobo… https://t.co/t1sFwPqj82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching reading to first graders is a like game of Mad Gab. “Sound out the word.” *sounds out the word letter by l… https://t.co/YejbSh4cfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend's so obsessed with me I want to punch him but don't get it twisted that's how it should be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preview and pre-registration period for Saturday’s government surplus auction opens today- Friday 9am-5pm off Steph… https://t.co/3EM2jvmT0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SealTeamcbsfans @SEALTeamCBS @SEALTeamWriters @justinmelnick Awwwwwww❤️❤️❤️🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelchatman #WHYiGive “The meaning of life is to find your gift. The purpose of life is to give it away” - Pablo Picasso!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then sometimes I get SO SAD because I know I left them when they were preteens (so I could pursue my own life)… https://t.co/Nz2ZZwcFfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Forrest for the trees Jim, Forrest for the trees🌳🌳🌳]]></document><document><![CDATA[The law of oneness is real.  Research it, learn it and experience it. 🙋 @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/zvS4p59del]]></document><document><![CDATA[F*cking D**kbag!!   Trump #Blocks Back Pay for Contractors Who #Worked During  HIS #ILLEGAL Shutdown  https://t.co/CccJl9YTNf via @truthout]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Victor Per  🇺🇾 🇺🇾 @VictorP71705138 for liking my poem! Happy day!💙💞💦 👍👍El camino al infierno]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ass was really sitting down at work thinking I left at 6...... I should’ve been gone by 4. 🙃💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious_and_Simple Received  a special gift from karencowdrey1 her delicious Bitter Sweet Chocolate Guinness infu… https://t.co/bMu0FCTb6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realGpad https://t.co/EAkprcPi2q Please consider helping me out by retweeting!!! ♡ :) #payitforward #anxiety… https://t.co/WAnbbmMArZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the guys at Hannafords at 7:30pm on Feb13th - it made my night to watch grown men stress out over which flowers to buy #Cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this! The Lord examines his Heart! Happy Blessed Sunday Everyone!! @ McDonough, Georgia https://t.co/mBEy14bsfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[should ppl that watch videos on full volume in public without headphones have rights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC I didn’t know Sarah had a stroke?! But it looks like she’s almost fully recovered. Good for her 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsaTeresa @Dax_x98 @EvaCassidyBio I swear by the moon and the stars in the sky]]></document><document><![CDATA[In The Valley Below has been a pleasant surprise and definitely has the most onstage sexual tension of any band so far this Noise Pop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I hope Kellyanne get arrested for lying and supporting a mob boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[VERO BEACH FASHION WEEK Outfit|Cottonways Vero Beach, Florida location 💕 https://t.co/cxbleyQAQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraB16901827 Thank you Sandra. Sending much love and many hugs my dear friend. God Bless!  😘😘😘❤️🤗🤗🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day! . Pictured is our NEWEST PHO ANGUS BEEF that'll MELT your partner's ♥️ by way of the STOMACH… https://t.co/yC7D153qO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alan_stoddard Then maybe update your LinkedIn page. I always do my homework. Divisive opinions from people. Who ar… https://t.co/6feBPDkjxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bckrda Yes, quite the pot meet kettle moment for @SenJohnKennedy . The hypocrisy is dripping from this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[COVINA: Chatterbox Comedy Night is TONIGHT w/ @benbrandfon @DaveMerheje @puterbaughs @Dputerbaugh @IfyNwadiwe… https://t.co/gxRhrEPoVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our entire room shouts in joy every time Mama Mia 2 appears on screen. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! So important for the work of the #WakeSCLT to consider. @krogers53 @wharris621 @WCPSSElemScie @WakeElementary… https://t.co/1yZJ24SaEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Erika decorates everything- including the paper plates 🔴 We’re at 10 days! 10 days until #jbjbday2019 #saturday… https://t.co/pKBlex2CqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's ready to pitch? calling all Kid Businesses...  Reposted from @kidsexpoca     🗣Calling all Kid Entrepreneurs O… https://t.co/4W5ONW3pX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love going to Casino add this to your jewelry collection or gift idea #casinotime #horseshoe https://t.co/wrkuOV83vl https://t.co/kckIf90UDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast My parking garage at work always smells the the set of Dazed and Confused. But then we’re a block aw… https://t.co/ywCmnl3qgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends boyfriend pranked me and signed me up for a service that sends goat puns like every 20 seconds. Make it… https://t.co/rsq5OEtdMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch Out here in California we have the same or worse!   No wonder the Dems want open border....  When il… https://t.co/qfhRKpopyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 119 of Snow in KC. Send help. Send reinforcements. Losing will power. The city is in shambles. The children are… https://t.co/svstsHpMdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews @m_ebrard Dichoso tú que tienes quien te cuide y respeten tus derechos y a los Venezolanos quien lo… https://t.co/TwTMxJ076r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cny_mama I got pregnant with my daughter when i was 20. I worked at a daycare at the time. When she was about 6 mo… https://t.co/shFkBGCggN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like every time i wanna do something she finds something  wrong with my life and uses it against me. love it for me ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards @BravoTV @MauricioUmansky Their opening was a bit offensive, “Americans don’t know Shit”- was rude. I… https://t.co/hwBY2X1LHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of the 7 Day Book Challenge. I will be posting the cover of a book I have read. No explanation and no review.… https://t.co/70rxQkzmn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Martin Yu crossed 10. Time 01:33:45, pace 09:28 min/mile, est. finish 11:06 am https://t.co/fDhRiOths5 #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then Jesus told his disciples, "If anyone would come after me, let him deny himself and take up his cross and follow me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my grandpa knows so many rules I’ve never even heard of. like if you’re in a state for more than 30 days you’re sup… https://t.co/m2VCVnxAta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olympia Heights FL Tue Feb 19th AM Forecast: TODAY Mostly Sunny Hi 81 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d When will Kelly Anne (sp?) wake up?  When the KoolAid runs out? She needs an excuse to resign. Her loss… https://t.co/8wmh8ZaHr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best seat in the house. (I’m terrified.) //Scenic Design: Courtney O’Neill, Lighting Design: Christine Binder, Cost… https://t.co/Oq6VSve8DY]]></document><document><![CDATA[so ur moms can post on fb about me, but I’m blocked😂 I’m 19...19!!!! You are a mother. Grow up🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seabiscuit7 Yes he walked to First Aid! Can hear him saying his horse finished 1st without him]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you have landed @DTWeetin and need to catch your connecting flight at B10 to @FlyYOW and no one can find the g… https://t.co/S5yuYw3JjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelTalesLife @KaraDiDomizio Whale watching is on my list to do this year 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stuartbrainerd @MichaelEMann @MeetThePress @hmcghee @MSNBC @Morning_Joe @ProjectDrawdown ...applicable economic mo… https://t.co/dB6sbalt4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drvox @AaronCosbey 1/ There 7 whereas clauses in the GND, the last tells us the point  Whereas the Senate/House re… https://t.co/WbcxL4ERJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kological @BretStephensNYT @IlhanMN Oh, I see. Well Hitler responded differently, according to his experience. The… https://t.co/OaJJBdajlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’ll get up at 7, and be out by 7:30 maybe even make some breakfast or stop by Starbucks   Me waking up at 7:48… https://t.co/Vhub9eSfWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i guess my body thought now while i’m recovering from surgery it would be the perfect time for my wisdom teeth to start coming in 😭🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon They are beautiful animals I love my doggies too. I love my  Tustin 8 months old. https://t.co/zqa2ThXkgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 What SciFi movie is he talking about? Is he the star? What an asinine thing to say. He needs to leave… https://t.co/J6UeayfzKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposed to have a party of 30 at 1:30 and 6 of them are here. 🙄🙄 come on people I need money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow from yesterday... ❤️❄️⛄️🌨❤️ @ The Garden oasis https://t.co/TgL96cR0vS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Ladies! Enjoy your Thursday please. UPDATE: I got temporary custody until March 21st! Only temporary b… https://t.co/2EMdJqwjAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding out that I live by Dunkin Donuts is one of the best news I have received in a while 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again, @AccentureHealth’s annual #digitalhealth consumer survey reads the tea leaves for the future of healthc… https://t.co/j2lpEJj8Z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone Venmo me, I’ve been nice all week and I’ve worn pants instead of jeans everyday to work. I deserve this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consider my hypothetical balls officially MIA.   @nightcatprod always entertaining. #wtforecast https://t.co/jIk6vcV3x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[All prettied up and heading out to see @erincostelo tonight! #eastcoaststruttin #fridaynight #torontolife… https://t.co/y60Camb40w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrackerBaze @PressSec @realDonaldTrump What is wrong with you?  How can you be proud of this administration?  It i… https://t.co/Dv0X8BQw9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever grateful to be part of the DISC study in #cysticfibrosis with @vtangpricha @trzeek @RuthEGrossmann @suzjudd https://t.co/1MtTRKkoKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordantylerxxx He was so proud of that birth defect that he sent me  2 videos and 2 photos of it. I feel special . 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizzytrizzy Remove this video and stop blaming your friend for your choices made. She didn't tell you Khole to sle… https://t.co/gXqgJeCAn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two recent opinions by Justice Clarence Thomas should alarm us all https://t.co/yr1Na7lprr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting my #hermana #supermodel @librajiminez at @thechukscollins #womensday #blackhistorymonth #fashionevent ne… https://t.co/SKdW5jOmxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cat_Chronicles Good luck today with your @aafstallions !  Hope my @aafiron #ForgeOn 😀Good day for watching @TheAAF !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KmetkoG @Clear2Insanity @TweetNathanRich @GrowingupinSCN @AftermathFdn @LAPDHQ WHAT THE HELL?!?! Sorry, l don’t me… https://t.co/KwJY6oXFPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fast, all-natural relief for anxiety symptoms: put 2 guinea pig on you. Not a cure, but surprisingly calming. https://t.co/0tQqXQXdzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones @TeraWHunter How we know what we know about enslaved people and law has changed. Today, we examine wh… https://t.co/ZR9QpR8crV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babylira23 it’s been pourin all night and supposed to rain all day today 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Motherhood Penalty: Why We're Losing Our Best Talent To Caregiving via @forbes https://t.co/G1542cJ3Bx what?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, here we go with another invention idea I have that won’t ever happen 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDXJenni I wish I could knit though! I’m a mediocre crocheter. Would blame being a lefty but... it’s not that good an excuse heh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tbone7219 Dude I HATE the fucking Steelers, but you’re one of my favorite people on here. 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give me all of your foot stomping, banjo plucking, French-cursing, telling 15k people to shut the fuck up, Canada-l… https://t.co/sp8FVaE4Fv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceGThomas In cap hill theres no room for ANYONE'S bullshit they never use 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet Doesn't this maniacal, meandering, unhinged, untruthful "speech" remind anyone of those videos of Jim Jo… https://t.co/vHkHruR4bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a makeup brand at @JeffreeStar reviewed and loved it, y’all know the Jeffree Star approved logo would be smacked on my packaging ⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I need to wake up earlier so I don’t have to rush getting ready  Also me: spends my extra time laying in bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing place for innovation and collaboration! Thanks @GACyberCenter and @GaCyberCrimeCtr for being gracio… https://t.co/pOtNjiLE2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger @valkayec Daddy can buy him into those private schools but he can't change the transcripts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @KylieJenner @foxandfriends Jealousy is a hideous thing. I’m sure she doesn’t give a crap who is hating on her!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesDavidCamp3 @WYMT @AndrewWYMT @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT @ChrisWKYT @Kentuckyweather @AdamBurnistonWX… https://t.co/9mfvwlBJCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shoq When the flea egg falls off Of the animal, it settles into the carpet, where the vacuum doesn’t really reach.… https://t.co/lyRxx8gDkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news! Everything in Seattle is totally different, but the bathroom at the University of Washington School of A… https://t.co/ohwvd25uD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@behindthewoman1 Every woman should do what feels right for them. And we shouldn’t judge each other for those choic… https://t.co/K9e5Vafsue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catannemcgee My character was questionable at best. Both of us. Love you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Yet as a dictator you want to overthrow our President.  What an Oxymoron!  You have traits as a tr… https://t.co/L4Sp3fwtg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you to the E-Boyz for an amazing night! @rell_island6 @maine_savage23 https://t.co/scIRPz6YGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t trust Lebron as an A&amp;R, but I do trust 2 Chainz. I’m ready for Friday. #RapOrGoToTheLeague]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougJones @SenShelby Congratulations! #Tatiana cc: #Alabama https://t.co/mGmCURVRzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biloxi fire chief Joe Boney shows Biloxi Council how new equipment can limit cancer-causing contaminates from enter… https://t.co/hXgKBE4vci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagospedpac I’ve started adding to all of my students’ IEPs who need the consistency of adult (whether para or… https://t.co/HcSC6K3bvd]]></document></documents></author>