<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@flea333 @Lakers True words, true words. The last 5-6 years have been disgraceful. Every year similar to the last.… https://t.co/fJZBhgLafH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump #MAGA🇺🇸 @PressSec https://t.co/pD0PEKgQE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not bad, not bad at all for the former @PDAGoldenEagles ace. Future is bright for the talented lefty in Conway.… https://t.co/2YFjHHHJzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJentleson You mean telling them the truth? C'mon Adam. You can't be this blind.  And yes you have seen things lik… https://t.co/g39V5wJTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realdavesommer Hey everyone look at these two!!! Whatever you do don’t look at my boss.   They’re by a sign. It’s… https://t.co/FuxfPW63uk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sport would be cleaner than the corrupt sport of Olympic Weightlifting that the International Weightlifting Fe… https://t.co/Vq7aL2HocH]]></document><document><![CDATA[April 15th 16th 17th if yo birthday on one of these days DM me let’s have a lil some 🕺🏾💃🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living wall lovers-seat... hand crafted and conceived by our creative genius, one-of-a-kind phenomena oferbenny… https://t.co/BoDcZ67QnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I wish I was one of those people. What a comeback for the buds, glad I didn’t turn it off!!! #leafsforever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Free Free Free Free TV's for the taking. A Presidents Day offer. Right outside a Horry County Recycling Center… https://t.co/3MqRhXQggo]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what we go through, and no matter how little we may have in this life, w e must rejoice in the Lord and p… https://t.co/RhpGXae2FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found the photos from my first book release by @iamdanifresh. Seems like a billion years ago.… https://t.co/Bq9UigJi9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite Absurd, ridiculous, idiotic bullshit.  There are no limits to @CNN Derangement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump #MarALardAss won’t go over well.  We call it like we see it.  If you hang out at Mara… https://t.co/L5a8BZji7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol It's an easy guess  what Congressional Republicans will choose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frank Zappa &gt; Lou Reed - Drinking  The Hemperor HPA by @newbelgium @ Sith Temple  — https://t.co/c71qGPgOql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fullerdoc97 @NBCNewsHealth Are you aware adult stem cells can uptake SFHR's from undetectable infiltrates containe… https://t.co/q9Hi5vM12k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Politics_Polls @QuinnipiacPoll If Texas is truly a purple state in 2020, American politics will never be the same.… https://t.co/D4U22P764z]]></document><document><![CDATA[This how I be feeling when ppl who I don’t fck with no mo did some fck shit to me 🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/JIoU7i7Ghp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Christopher Robin in my room smoking cookie inna Russian Cream about to cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever get so bored that you go through old messagesto cringe at yourself 🥶 https://t.co/upI9URgd3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin everyday I will expose you to the world keeping Angelica a slave and raping her. You are sick… https://t.co/uP1s5v1G2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SongBird4Trump @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Well done!! Hit it out of the park again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What colors inspire you today? . Openings available! Book online or call. Hairbyangel. com 661.645.6177 .… https://t.co/UxMrTOSZ0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[if I listened to any of yall faggets I would have offed my self along time agom..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hudsonwest *Happy Friday* Hudson! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/x5CBwYOK5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothyBuckSF @gravityblankets The Amazon ones are trash. Bead distribution is all weird and construction isn’t great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love getting notifications like this. Thank you, Thomas for taking the time to let me know how my agency is doing… https://t.co/Cp2WynzAF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[What dream last night was. I made my Mother debut at @sfoasis for JLo vs Selena. heklina’s team was so fabulous to… https://t.co/dvV8m74dx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @APlayersProgram committ @niccolomannion visits with the media after the @PinnacleBball team captures the… https://t.co/gaZJeD0S0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@admireabl Not sure what you mean, I wasn't tilted, we just decided to play whatever on r66!  Thanks though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Foothill Transit Bus Stop in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/JtiiuKKRcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, @NHLNetwork’s NHL Now will feature its all-female broadcast with hosts @Jackie_Redmond, @JamieHersch and… https://t.co/mqNwqCHZVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Song Spotlight  Featured Songs for February 19, 2019  Melly Mell Tha Mobsta - Stop Playin'  https://t.co/y57f3vDjd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurs better WIN TONIGHT or else it’s gonna be WAR!! Glad I won’t be watching and all ! Got more important things t… https://t.co/TcZcyqgr1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Iceberg Twice the Size of New York City Is Poised to Break Off From Antarctica https://t.co/8ZfwNjJNfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewkrier @Mexplosion612 Charlie Daniels shot me down. Disappointment abounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, #BillBarr was sworn in on 2/14 and less than 2 business days later the #MuellerReport is done... that's it? Mue… https://t.co/kTGJEMI4Fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our keynote speaker - Aerojet Rocketdyne's COO - Mark Tucker shares his insight on Reinventing Your Operations in P… https://t.co/NWmX89cZyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES COMRADE @realDonaldTrump ...YES WE ALL ARE NOW, PLEASE GET THE FUCK OUT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjaco3444 Ah a simple copy and paste can cause some dude to get his panties in a wad. Tragic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is called oversight. There are separation of powers Mr President so get use to it. This is not a dictatorship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot woot! Huge congrats to our hockey ladies. Check the story out from Brennan and Drew!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea so I think it’s final I’m not getting my account back... really just a shame #instagram #instagramsupport could… https://t.co/pG5Cih8psD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY If Jordan had, instead of whining abt Cohen, offered to nude wrestle Cohen, in front of Congress now, the… https://t.co/XS6ADPz37i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_christo @beaglefacts Very nice. And Scrappy is aging like a fine wine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ShinerBeer when is the sea salt and lime coming back? Need some with this crazy Texas weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoletteMpls That's clear. I like em cuz he's not afraid to hit either side, like me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despertando Consciencias. Hoy en Radio 540AM a las 12pm    Pasa La Voz Alguien Puede Empoderarse.  La Nueva Poderos… https://t.co/UJ36uI66YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te quiero. (Creo que solo te lo he dicho un millón de veces). #love #loveislove #enjoymylife #moments #timelife… https://t.co/tXqphKemG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You look like you don't feel well, is the most perceptive greeting I received today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SILKY SMOOTH! Glenburn’s Clayton Stucki goes with the finger roll and sinks the layup to give the Panthers a 9-2 le… https://t.co/BLjY2phaKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean how many memes can you really make about a medieval siege weapon? Turns out a whole lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsDtheTeacher I can just imagine the laugh you all had today about this and how much it freaked me out. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgar224u @autkidd @MackTrucks @NextranUSA Looks like someone has a bad case of the grumpies this morning. I sugge… https://t.co/g0t8QkyHNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@todonoticias Es importante que todos viajen con seguro medico. El tema que muchas veces la gente piensa que no va a pasar nada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lukelakers @BaronCorbinWWE @Stonebraker1985 @ScottDawsonWWE What else is he supposed to say? ‘Yes sir, thank you s… https://t.co/PkZTubmGNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riverfront Park is *still* underwater. #Nashville https://t.co/6mqlXHE9H6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to commentary and ideas regarding Rail transportation in New York State #ourfocusislocal… https://t.co/EIUHAoZiPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it science shows ignore microbiology? Yes, 95% of all multicellular species died during the end-Permian. But… https://t.co/adwWkqt4Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if @C_h2o_man wants to see Oleksiak and Reaves go at it like I do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fued with @S_ATL_Wrestling  Tag with @rbonne1  Manager @emcsweeney1215  Trainer @svrtsrmjnvn  I put over… https://t.co/ecdp4vpzLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Do you know that the people do not directly elect a president? The States elect the… https://t.co/QvcfGDAE98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her job is to "see all people" and comment intelligently and not degrade or judge!  Especially our allies!   Not to… https://t.co/1yOyZKEy5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports radio has become nearly unlistenable. This WEEI vs @GlobeChadFinn thing is silly. More ‘look at me’ from EEI… https://t.co/5N7VDjADzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nzgrant17 @kdrose0718 @LoveBling6 @Josiegirlz5 @jkkc40 @WhitestoneArt @GaylynnJohnson @RhinoluvsUSA @fglaus… https://t.co/Da8exJqBpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Online learning platforms like that where you don’t have a teacher just scream, ‘Nobody cares about you.’”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xpander4 @AdamSinger 100%. The only fruit I eat is berries, apples, and occasionally bananas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a good conversation with @CURegentKroll this morning. While I don’t agree with his stance on the issue of footb… https://t.co/gDoL86QzhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence @brianstelter @ananavarro i’ve never agreed with tucker on anything. but here we are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/r691j0cU9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedmatrix @brielarson @SerenaLFischer @RVAmag Something seems weird about that whole situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaferWeigel Your father was a great man. I remember meeting him once at a baseball game. He was so gracious and to… https://t.co/t70xlYCNf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gilbertKTA I needed one during your EDC cut too but I ain’t cheat on you😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another guy getting love @ BCHS!! Much deserved hard working dedicated player. When we said you wont be our QB he j… https://t.co/QLckL7VUFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Bove My top 5 are...  1. Cinnamon Toast Crunch 2. Cap'n Crunch 3. Honey Nut Cheerios 4. Cocoa Puffs 5. Fruity… https://t.co/Od5aAO0eK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedarflats @JonMontag @OkiTimes @zappafaye @ElkValleyBrew @ManvsAle @mtravis63 @TheStraightHops @CasaskullMark… https://t.co/WDU8EtWylv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trueukfan @bulldog5704 Well we didn’t get enough practice.  Maybe if we had shit 32 of them. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMelyyMel @hollydaudy Whoa chill it was a joke lol, and I don’t trust nobody lol...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love melody because we can be having a different conversation on imessage, facetime, snapchat chat, snapchat phot… https://t.co/m7tsn1dg7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent question since we already know that there have been "thousands of sexual abuse cases" coming from their d… https://t.co/GbPJAcUBdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhhbutwhy @tsesque Your Birthday is a paid holiday where I work #CollectiveBargaining is a wonderful thing #organize #1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive Affirmation of the Day Today I am the key to my happiness and the happiness of others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Mercedes Benz C300 Sport has a great balance of style and price. Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE… https://t.co/WiNP8yp2OQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump said a while back, he loves his generals, problem was, they didn't love him back, proved disloyal bunch, perh… https://t.co/tjltAIijuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidplazas @freddieoconnell @EquityAlliance1 @goscar @norakernel @Tennessean And ...  https://t.co/W7m50w44Qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy to get snarky about NBC's #ElvisAllStarSpecial. Actually, most of the performances were pretty good. I'm just… https://t.co/phh8eCjjDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Feral By Nature: Plum by @blackacrebrewer @ Black Acre Brewing Co. — https://t.co/RrALoHPHSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its okay if she doesn’t text you back tomorrow fellas. She wasn’t going to text you back the other 364 days either. https://t.co/2fUBsJFjKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tale of the 2 @blundstoneca. On the left the boots I purchased in 2011. A week ago I noticed that the sole of m… https://t.co/EpDW8S97uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Jon Snow thing doesn’t work out, I’ll be around.  #stepfatherofdragons?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor @USNavy janie, just another snowflake, who thinks his opinions are all that matters. My family has 4 Generations of patriots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I’m trying to study in the library before this test and this random guy wanna have a whole conversation 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨Wristbands🚨🚨 Support the @HS_Lady_Hawks basketball team by purchasing!!  $2 a band You can place your order with… https://t.co/2EpTNLDIYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for what you do 24/7! Thoughts and prayers for you from the #GoodDayCharlotte and @FOX46News family.  -Tu… https://t.co/awMlI4qtb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am straight up having a pretty shitty day, if anyone is down to talk that would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ray Fittipaldo's first 2019 Steelers mock draft https://t.co/5WbubKzOVE via @pittsburghpg @rayfitt1 #Steelers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetripleplay18 The Padres did give Hosmer a pretty hefty contract last year to this exact date]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monica The Magnificent vs. Madison Sex-Kitten (Bikini Boxing Championship Rematch) Who will win this fight? Comment… https://t.co/OySkX4gagR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dame una razon para amar, dame un aviso de paz. ♥️ https://t.co/W4p8E24FGg]]></document></documents></author>