<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[No drunk couples fighting at work tonight so I guess it was a good Valentine's Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachBach007 @SarahGould_SA @duganjames @keanothedog @JayValenz67 @andrerucker51 @hey_butter @terry313401 @delgeo1… https://t.co/eVIem2tWXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teck’s life has been a series of firsts. First deaf honors student at @UofSC. First deaf student at @ColumbiaLaw. O… https://t.co/a4T7vQ1cr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is relative.  I'm sure most 80 year olds find me quite fetching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @borgesteach for helping our lil gophers be accountable for their actions on a daily basis! Discipline… https://t.co/DCBmWKwd8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ghost Daisy is dressed up as a bunny. @ Asheboro, North Carolina https://t.co/15q7iis4Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @MarianneHofer @hadip @codeorg I agree.. but what is sad is if you are sixty, it's hard to find a good… https://t.co/dPVka10S9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most #retail businesses would benefit from executing the principles outlined in this article on how Best Buy saved… https://t.co/AAXSsQacEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of being a woman! Sad the majority of women around the world still suffer violence and systemic discriminatio… https://t.co/JX5i7ThWEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!  I will be watching this every day until April 14.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with high school and college buds in sunvalley.  We made his delicious Cajun ahi over roasted root… https://t.co/QLLJk6YpJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @bobclemente5 @HillaryClinton You get paid for these crap comments? https://t.co/3jfI2YRlF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jules_John that bright thing is the #sun. We have missed it in #RVA. #AXSChat #RuhGlobal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't always agree with David Brooks, but this is excellent. #CountryOverParty #PeopleNotPartisanship]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q. Can a handicap (a non-strength) be a strength ? Ah, but more importantly, what does the form of such a question teach us, tell us ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealmark60 @RiceStreet607 @curtsanderson83 I couldn’t deal with ONE husband much less TWO 🥺 I’d like to know wh… https://t.co/0JN2xA9svV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter seriously prepared me for college lol all these concepts I learned on here I am able to understand when I read articles / textbooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[William Bieber of DEA Los Angeles said during one of the arrests this am of medical professionals in connection wit… https://t.co/jBJfuFzV3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quonky @StevenShattuck @CauseVox That's amazing!!! Did you thank them via mail, email, phone, all of the above? Co… https://t.co/vg6Uz7OHpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yooocaitlin I haven’t looked in a bit but I recall looking previously and seeing sulfates, parabens, film formers,… https://t.co/ZBDgKYZmW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepChipRoy Thank you sir. God bless you and your family. Keep fighting the good fight. 👍🏼🇺🇸🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I recognize an actor but don’t know where from I go to their Wikipedia page. The answer is ALWAYS “The G… https://t.co/I3UTE8nNHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can also get text messages from @PhilaOEM    They will text you info on specific lines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your husband see’s a post @AdamWylde ..it was yummy! @joebatista818 https://t.co/aNn2n9Uncz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremysroga @SophiaW47285349 @KTHopkins The Swedish men would be shot: Swedish women &amp; children would be sold into slavery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love options. I love refreshed. I love bright skin. I love consistency. I love feeling good. I love jeans that fi… https://t.co/i5p8eXvYOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Culture of Death-baby sacrificing for the idol i Women's Rights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just supported The Toronto Zoo’s Toronto Zoo Polar Dip 2019. You can too! https://t.co/fvH5OtBWMy # via… https://t.co/tphqDT6VER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Kels!! Bride to be! @ Bourbonnais, Illinois https://t.co/hwnRADl9mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[U make our morning happy when u laugh. Love to watch u every morning @RobinMeade #morningexpress #HLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh, it's called comedy. Liberals have lost all sense of humor in the age of Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only note in my phone is a page for potential inner lip tattoos lmaoooo k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abellekat @houseandhens How embarrassing is it for someone else to pick up your garbage?? Bc you don’t have the in… https://t.co/9Hhzh5ro62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLadyLudovica @Whitneycatalano Oh man, this is SO TRUE. It’s all about exposure and the lack of it in our cultur… https://t.co/FdixjsovrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CisforChelsey I’m crying over all of this. Esp the fact I threw out all my merch that could be worth it now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Please investigate the advanced programs available in public schools.  There aren't many.  Without the Epic… https://t.co/zcCOvw52Cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all watch that movie on Netflix called thumper that girl with the blonde hair carrying a duffle bag and is on… https://t.co/IHzE5vMZnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@htherese8 @ike9_Eagles @AldineISD @drgoffney @tdavis_aldine Thank you...Appreciate your support!]]></document><document><![CDATA[got paid yesterday and immediately bought 2 sets of tickets to 2 separate concerts I get to drag Dalton to this yea… https://t.co/RRVa5O2SQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t people why don’t the absolute most from life?! 😣 everyone should just wanna be GREAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2702_hd @XKerrigan @SWHR33 @L2702Ops @Tammyha2758 @cjgabridge Congrats 🎉👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeRoyce @everythingloria #OneDayAtATime, Black-ish, and the new wave of issues-driven sitcoms https://t.co/EgIWqRr8oM via @Slate]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What would you do if fear wasn’t in your way?” Rhonda Henley 🤔#Herndon @Cisco #WOI2019 #ImagineYourPossible… https://t.co/cOLHtfENxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you a secret... I have none.      Please excuse me while I go melt a little, and I'm not even the one… https://t.co/TVKILQj3le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mxntis_ today i spent an hour looking at books in the library with my boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I meet one of my male friends’ new bf’s I’m STOKED and wanna be their friend if you ignore me you’re gonna get slapped]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJOlson @shallbe2cool4u HAHAHAHAHA is it weird I kinda miss these days only cause we were with each other list… https://t.co/qSPOp6rZnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Manor High School!  Job well done!  On to the next one...@ManorISD @Manor_Sports https://t.co/27istKbVxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Based on the Academy’s record of picking Shape of Water and Birdman, I have a sneaking suspicion that The Favourite… https://t.co/2H2B1ottuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched this @TheBethPhoenix @EandCPod @EdgeRatedR @MsCharlotteWWE @gailkimITSME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Test tube baby part PC OK PUAHAHHAHAHAHAH PART ALEXA OOOMG.       😂😂😂😂😂😂 I HOPE THEY AINT DO NO A YO PUAHHAHAHHAHAHAHHHHAHAA AHHHMAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[insta_thaniel and I brought NOLA to New Haven last night.  A true homemade spread: fried oysters, fried cauliflower… https://t.co/o7esZQx68W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomansDay truth from @lisaoliveramft https://t.co/wot2GqZYu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve been in the car with my mom for 12 minutes and i just realized she’s been talking non-stop the entire time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjosoprano If I’m not passed out I’ll watch from behind a pillow lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best season for my two faves harry and smith is so hard to get through because aleksandr petrovsky is in it too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn today must be “don’t pick up the phone for Erika” or some shit 😂😂 this be the third person son 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[used to settle for less than I deserve till my ex’s homies started to gas me🤭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/WLaHkb1KYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i didn't get much of a chance to post conference trip photos while they were happening--too much to do!--but here i… https://t.co/wYKFkG9nZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canadiandaws83 @sfpelosi @HouseGOP Yes, they are in the same room. They just don't like that they are not successf… https://t.co/75Yu3UXmr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDollenmayer Amen!! @RDollenmayer so true I needed to be reminded of this everyday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BretStephensNYT Why are Christians so afraid of a woman who wears a hijab? I wonder if what she said would have be… https://t.co/fq1RWDWAVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cross2225 saying he loves the term “crippling depression” just rocked my world, I am changed]]></document><document><![CDATA[He gives power to the week and strength to the powerless. But those who trust in the Lord will find new strength. T… https://t.co/kER8mlHbuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ideas for @ChefNikkia’s new kitchen #ComingFa19 @IROQUOIS_HS #IroquoisBelieves #LetsEat @AcademiesofLou… https://t.co/wBHM2pPrz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u need flea &amp; tick meds, please go to ur vet &amp; get prescription it’s far more safe 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser He sounds more and more like the know-nothing Trump every day. He distinguishes himself from Trump with his… https://t.co/783BC147mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SnakeCitySimon, does Souixsie use an epipen if she breathes in cobra venom? Or would it not help at all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nose stopped up and I ain’t got a nigga to coddle me a tiny bit 😭 yeah I’m over winter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just overheard right now in my actual living room: "Elton John is the one from Grease right?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chesse47 @DonaldJTrumpJr Jr, I wouldn't allow a lowlife full blown POS like you near my fur babies. No way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents: “be quiet when we’re sleeping.”  Me: *shuts every door carefully and gently, tiptoes, is over the top q… https://t.co/Z68OPAy3pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunnyDe19776003 You are rude and uninformed. I'm from the Gulf Coast of Florida. Everyone I personally know has su… https://t.co/vxOGYaOSEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foes4sports @NJAHPERD @CoachFoe @IAHPERD @SHAPE_America @jlobianc See you soon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this sweet talk about where is the action.... action speak louder than words.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinnershells We almost went down! I am friends with Amy and Cliff Cody and Amy said y’all were there. I was like… https://t.co/4RquK5FHIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren’t unnecessarily mean to your best friends love interests, are you even a best friend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 @TacosNSlurpees Wowwww man, I love this tweet and these responses.  Y’all perfectly explaining all the t… https://t.co/N3tlzQOpI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALBUM OUT NOW ON ITUNES, GOOGLE PLAY, SPOTIFY AND TIDAL @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/ETvRx1GhEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike from Mousekeeping was by far the best part of our stay at POP! Century resort. He bent over backwards to help… https://t.co/wQ2LGMyYbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaPenney @ellstar @joe_cressy Which ones aren’t serious? Which of the diseases now protectable by vaccinations h… https://t.co/XxhM0DHUXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend and I got into a drunk argument about our hypothetical future dog last night hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did you have me move to _____ to live with you, if you were going to be hooking up ...behind my back ...😳😳… https://t.co/H10QURof8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #Rust_RYS19 #RUST_RYS2019 #Rust_RYS19… https://t.co/W0PBKLlYEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholasFerroni Testing, testing, testing, testing, testing, testing #6WordTeacherStory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRoKhanna @SenWarren @RepTimRyan Great start. Now how about a full audit of the DoD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not fully. this obviously breaks my heart. i will be though. as long as she is]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should add that nothing bad happened to being this on.  An unrequired act of kindness!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic @realDonaldTrump I read and understand economics- I also understand blind hatred of the president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting The AOB Teach Significantly PD Day with a great Welcome Message and Prayer.  We are so grateful for this f… https://t.co/VGKeYHCfIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray my future in-laws aren’t as ignorant as some of the older people in my own family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching goodmythical.morning with these sweet things🥰🐱🐶 #furbabies #goodmythicalmorning #rhettandlink #youtubers… https://t.co/4q9B5IHQGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuomoPrimeTime @ChrisCuomo @RepMattGaetz Can’t deal with seeing his face. He was so heartless and out of place in… https://t.co/bWBPNtPheR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s Show Wrapping Up with the New Joey Newcomb Hit “To Be a Yid”. On @1640WJPR .com with @DoniGross . ( Hey D… https://t.co/dazAazKomb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dominion ICE= DICE! Means its dicey if these machines are used in any election! https://t.co/DeggvJ3PtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @NewHopeGeorge love you loads old man, hope you have an amazing day. thanks for always being so kind… https://t.co/9ljYXRnIIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose They will answer for it, not to man, but to God himself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think tonight I will read something to the writers group and see what they think and then do a last minute review… https://t.co/ccbhErCzY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few items from my #craftstorians WIP hoard:  a baby quilt that needs bound,  a baby quilt that needs started, an… https://t.co/3oewh7wOFJ]]></document></documents></author>