<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Since our CFO is asking, let’s ask: 1. How much would FL taxpayers be willing to give Amazon? 2. Does Florida have… https://t.co/ASjtGXkmhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday hopey!! I miss and love you so much! 💗 https://t.co/0Oi218lrWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funko let me down. Was hoping for a full size #Yoda pop or scene, but instead he's only a mini and focus is on… https://t.co/rYeKLLHE2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StegerPatrick Your own sales people are s good measure of weather you’re building something people actually want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShariefWDSU Remember when I bumped into you at Lucy’s? I felt I needed an MRI after that too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIP OF THE DAY: No matter how important and successful you become, always be kind and respectful to others.… https://t.co/EUUzu1moDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzanier468 @MediaMan666 @billyrunaway @tomservo10 @StuartGrist @andrewcf_lt @WarrenPeas64 @CulturalGutter… https://t.co/tS0TFd3EYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[MJD's mock draft: Four QBs taken early - https://t.co/YyX3Vu8K1A https://t.co/hKtvQYTzhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump And how, would she have ANY true concept of American values? How would Donald?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd @marcorubio Really guy? What is wrong with you? You seem to be randomly quoting bible verses.  Ask yourself If that's normal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plant biology makes me want to slash and burn forests dawg🤧😣 https://t.co/E2eiUcbrjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cut in the order of getting off a plane, you’re a scumbag that has no place in society]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flyers, if you’re trading Simmer, please give him to a competing team to get a Cup. Preferably a likable one like N… https://t.co/lSrAbCr4tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaLgoesWronG @CherryBlossomHQ @brand0ngr0ce @aigadc Good chatting after the panel last night. Happy to talk more about this if you want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VA_Blues I will definitely check that out. 👍🏼 Love is the force that animates creation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Sorry, think you sat on the hot fireplace poker you heated yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Jones Open Wrestling Practice Tonight. 6:30 start. Dedicated Motivated Gym. Come on out. https://t.co/ihg5UfG87U]]></document><document><![CDATA[More like the @DNC kicked @amazon @JeffBezos out! They don’t want his money or business? @realJeffreyLord]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's a stop with a clickbait I'm going to take a nap hole the answer is yes we should build a wall and anybody who… https://t.co/WUiIFS5I9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whooz_ur_daddy @ghost_kitty @IAmCleisthenes @goddessgurrl @Richard_Stands @kitchen5203 @JCoker13 @ShitShowResist… https://t.co/nShLpRC6CD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the @WeAreWaveTV team for crushing another month as the 4th largest and fastest growing sports network… https://t.co/V7ptSMVhGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oli333 @Imafrayedknot1 @tictoc @KassandraSeven @RepRashida Yep erases who has done more for blacks and Hispanics… https://t.co/AIEpq163nY]]></document><document><![CDATA[no internet till the new pad Thursday so I’m clocking into work for 24 hours tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quoi?!?! Chef du Parti Libéral du Québec? Ben...là j' t'occupé!!!😨😨😨#coderre #PolQc #PLQ https://t.co/U1tSdEZ7I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Loved 'em. Couldn't wait for the next school book fair to buy new stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Restaurant Associate - https://t.co/bQOmfytzva #Springfield, MA #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[#New Release  💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL 🌎https://t.co/zhGl5xFiWP 🌎 https://t.co/nybi2t7T7g 🌎https://t.co/yeJ5Ge1ocE… https://t.co/R3XCyJ5mJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why I sold my timeshare in Mazatlan 5 yrs ago. No more Mexico for me. That’s why I want to BUILD THE WALL so… https://t.co/rXHMAEQbtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temas basicos, elementales pero no por eso menos valiosos! @karygf26 @ANDRESIBARRA99 @JJRASCON @ReneLunaS… https://t.co/yyDcLFbaiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is the amazing official poster art by Joel Robinson for the New Jersey Horror Con Spring 2019 show! We will ha… https://t.co/BfhT6fCjIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilcal8 In all seriousness because I am curious, what does NBCSN do that tops Fox broadcasts https://t.co/VSIJEd1Res]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKfromCentralPA @gerrybhoy007 @BreitbartNews You say that as Trump is the one doing it.  I guess Republicans don’t either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mildly nervous but if I can't get it worked out I'll ask my dad to buy it and just pay him back the moment I get pa… https://t.co/qZ4G6WvEsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeanneNaramore @MrMonroe17 What the hell going on with the Republicans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itmechr3 @Cato_of_Utica @ramsincanon @WillWBloom @TOfromthe360 @rachelzibrat I'm co-chair of CDSA, so I feel confi… https://t.co/5DuMBcx61y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at the Woodland tower right now with nothing to do until it stops raining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your income tax back invest it in something you love to do that can benefit you, or save it where you don’t tou… https://t.co/TtcicmsOUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJaredTyler @BigCMen @LukasDaken Oh wow that's awesome and they are all adorable ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmvelliaris This is probably my biggest weakness as a human. I'm always on some "miles to go before I sleep" stuff… https://t.co/NjOIofUcla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting down to the last few #stickers #bucees @BRCBColorado buceestexas bucees #coffee #mileHigh @ Black Rock Coff… https://t.co/lSS54WeqZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanPayne32 Didn’t see it. I’ve seen a bunch of articles where the info is just surface level info. I want to see… https://t.co/sanbv0MJRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will illinois would stop taking forever to give me my 13 dollars back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, it's that time of the year again. We are in Atascocita @Lowes selling  @girlscouts cookies. We'll be here… https://t.co/FZNClmD09G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked into my reserved space and parked for the night (@ Flying J - @pilotflyingj in Austinburg, OH) https://t.co/jHojAYBOTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it 📍 Emporia 5️⃣🅰️ State 🏀 Tournament begins next https://t.co/3r52zUeuSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump So much for "The Land of Opportunity".  Oh, thats right, you can BUY your way into America now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a pic of my chicken legs and holding a dice piñata with my cheese fingers at my fake bday party in Mexico https://t.co/b1VcsJ9Tmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld I've always found it amusing that a person needs a license to be a teacher but doesn't need one to be a parent. 😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:59 Q2 | 30-second timeout Bradley, it becomes the media timeout.   Braves - 29 Valpo - 38  Crusaders have hit eig… https://t.co/GCyImBtCw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beach #sunset #lajolla #clouds #californiadreamin #californialove #seabird #seagull #instagood @surfangelbook surf… https://t.co/Kq7qNhdBZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealzeyonce I miss u more I’m going over ur house Sunday to have brunch w Mimi big and b]]></document><document><![CDATA[You took to entrepreneurship like few other undergrads. 90 minutes into hearing me deliver Lec 2; #ENGR145 you were… https://t.co/RaAG8d9gCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom and Dad are back and they want to prevent you from visiting the most visited sites on earth.  https://t.co/31psTojuHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck Angelina1 marry meadow mookies kill Paris rockys https://t.co/FGlqGYDSK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal @RepSwalwell #DismemberTrumpCrimeCartel https://t.co/MJcawRvMUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic crowd and conversation at today’s Community Meeting with Commissioner @StrommenSarah, Commissioner… https://t.co/Luqxvw53LZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what you need to do when a teammate is having a tough day. Grab them, push them, pull them along with you.… https://t.co/CHyhMoomjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sir_ThomasIII if you don’t come to New York you softer than nylon.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizaskinner I also like the Exterminating Angel homage, where everyone's trapped due to reasons beyond any of the… https://t.co/E5W9eipkcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[honest question...why are ugly ass out of context tract homes like this not perceived as being ridiculous and absur… https://t.co/3aM8WxBKGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your favourite place to be on a Tuesday night! "The only place to be on a Tuesday night" "Tuesday night? This is… https://t.co/QHjgYIs21v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeTimePiry Say no more I get and like you said if you need him to close let him do his thing. That’s why I feel we’re better with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[215kg/473lb Front Squat from yesterday! This was exactly 3 Months after Total Hip Replacement. Thanks… https://t.co/9kOI4kLFqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover How Forever Feels by Kenny Chesney. https://t.co/YOQF3CNyRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky4Trump @kjune65 @RepAdamSchiff @RepJerryNadler They first harassed him for the Rusia collusion charade. Havin… https://t.co/8QJAK61lvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkillMammu Lol thats so true man. Some arent determined to get a better time if they have the best time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I’m in public and people next to me talkin sports but don’t know what they talkin about lmao I be ready to jump in]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun time at #GlenAllenES with our @CapitalOne #coding club! Can’t wait to see with these #4thGrade and… https://t.co/iGQqSl0cdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Wtf? Has your account been compromised or is this a paid endorsement? Most of them have been the “ot… https://t.co/h516wntCiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, @schubbard26 wins in the 26th Ward, which means there will be Double Hubbards in the BOA: https://t.co/MijBQLA6ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bye Vegas. Was nice to see you for a couple hours. @ Bellagio Las Vegas https://t.co/Mq3ezUoPDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon County Brand Stout (2017) 14.1% by @GooseIsland @ Spaceships Huh? — https://t.co/iDcrvsWFlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[With women in combat roles, a federal court rules the male-only draft unconstitutional https://t.co/ZSU5fa63i8 via @usatoday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSTRodB I swear it’s like the people who make these do absolutely no research on how GMs draft. Dorsey doesn’t dra… https://t.co/X4MpcFLlx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worry , is like a rocking chair . A lot of energy spent and you don’t move an inch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lrauhoff @ChanningBullock I’m aware. you said “90% of nat circuit debaters end up going to prestigious colleges”.… https://t.co/eKDqv0GKEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tuesday’s ~ Good Morning SunShine!!!  🔉 🎶 Let’s Do It Again 🎶🎶  ~ The Staple Singers #G.O.AT ~ They don’t make Mus… https://t.co/Zldsmyw5Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My battlefield this is Where it goes down!!! #warready #fitnessjourney #gymlife #stronger #Comehard #fitness… https://t.co/do6uYiKE4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Cheap shot that doesn’t amount to much just letting off steam.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck. Off. You. Sp*rs.   COME ON ARSENAL!! IT'S DERBY DAY!!!!!  #COYG #TOTARS #NLD 🔴⚪🔴⚪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceOlley @SenSchumer @senatemajldr Everything you name except trees is human caused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omaha_scanner what's going with the 5 police cars spread out with their light on on L street on 84th? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfLRE @MichaelBreed to be honest they should have never messed with the rules to start. Rewriting rules to make… https://t.co/Odryd0OC8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either my thumbs are getting girthier or I’ve developed some sort of dyslexia because I can’t type words for shit w… https://t.co/epmSFEMoJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[PIAA District 1 6A 2nd Round:  @dwesthoops vs @AbingtonSenior  @ValleyBoysBBall vs @CheltBasketball  @PHSRamsHoops… https://t.co/8ZeNrfpQEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not Conservative politics. This is stupidity. Ontario went barrel bottom. Expensive and unsustainable suppo… https://t.co/RwXEosq20W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC JUST LIKE HIS BUDDY TRUMP BOTH ARE FAR FROM BEING 2 of the most smart boys they claim! BUT SPOILER ALERT YOU… https://t.co/SSuMqDQC6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @IvankaTrump @EricTrump @FLOTUS https://t.co/TNjfuVCNCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holder_1064 10 year 250 mil. Then have incentives in the contract to earn another 50 mil like winning MVP, winning… https://t.co/Rt9kPnqNZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachCWheeler @thecoachvogt @slade248 @CoachShiffman @rdsmith86 @chowan6464 @dacoachmohuddle @bensonbuilt9… https://t.co/CkSDWflgsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is @MeLlamoTrevor in some Sim action #Pirates https://t.co/lAVc9Oc1Qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back from Morgantown. Doctor Ma came in and said good news. The new spots in my lungs were either cleared up or alm… https://t.co/Bod7RAXY8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBig_Easy @PGATOUR @APinv On behalf of so many may I say, 2 of golf's greatest gentlemen in these 2 photos. I'm… https://t.co/pS2Eybb52U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandySchoenberg @AOC Who fed her the questions? You do the really think she thought of them by herself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @fxp123 What no I'm not hiding anything in my mouth I don't have anything to hid I did not eat your eggs 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabbbbss Aw you think so ??? That’s super cute. https://t.co/4cUaoAYDxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think people make up exchanges with their kids for likes then my 3yo niece says (referring to her mom b… https://t.co/TYmEP9S5sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coyote at Falmouth Heights 02/20/19 #coyote #coyotesofinstagram #coyotesofcapecod #mammal #mammalsofinstagram… https://t.co/vL8JXpLEWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMarbukh @molosgatos @eliotwb @rwindrem @TexasCentral @TXHighSpeedRail No, I’m going to @AldiUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the best thing about it :) #future #noidea #comic #happen #loveit #message #happinessquotes #happy… https://t.co/LmV29xZzz2]]></document></documents></author>