<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Little People, Big Dreams: Jane Goodall by Isabel Sánchez Vegara #bookoftheday https://t.co/6ySbQWIjH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @autumnfallsxoxo @dakota_skyexxx @SainzSainzz @ParkerJuliaJP @ElenaVega91 @KaisaNord @EllieLeen1 @LilyLanexxx… https://t.co/A2ubjSVdpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[o tempo é muito bom mano só ele te faz amadurecer para você saber quem fica e quem sai da sua vida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity / That was Pretty Lame - Wake Up. Its Right in Front of You &amp; Everybody Else. #CreepyUncleJoe Says it All]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season tickets have been ordered!!! 2019 is going to be fun thanks @pwrocky #huskers #HuskerPower]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about we contrast Fox with literally the rest of reality?  Get your head out of your ass, you unfunny hack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who ever wanted a quesadilla tonight my bad I didn’t know where the cheese was at!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton @DolarToday Too late! They want to fight the US Military. Please intervene before the regime’s force… https://t.co/4bYeZ4CiJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I'm sure #SchiffForBrains will, but that's ok, that will lock in a win 2020 for the Prez.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything about Jersey is slow paced! Their people, there drivers, their food, their service, their air! this yall… https://t.co/6T2d6a8Cvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDesbarres : Good morning Michael... Have a great day and show!! #TheUndergroundGarage... @littlesteven_ug… https://t.co/DtQhOdHv7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[...bueno. Y esto cuando lo aprendió hacer? @ Hunters Creek Village, Texas https://t.co/lhDBn3d8HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told you I am a elemental warlock,  now you can believe me and stop calling me a freak behind my back thank you… https://t.co/DFqru2DrKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#108ing at Camelback. Adolfo is the only interesting guy in the lineup though. @fromthe108 https://t.co/TJdzeQMANC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mel_faith1 @LaylaAlisha11 @SpeakerPelosi She’s having mini strokes I swear it looks that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @usmarinecorps are always there for you when you need them! Even at the cuse_mbb games! #orangenation @ Carrier… https://t.co/zEJkghNU47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 19th Birthday @Ty1erPowers I hope you know how much I love you.  Here is the poem I wrote you before you were… https://t.co/kVpR3AjPAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to quit going to the movies so goddamn much. Hopefully I'll find another romantic partner soon to occ… https://t.co/8iDyAvAQtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolynMack21 @MrOzAtheist @bobmadras @charliekirk11 What makes you think that he (or any other atheist in this th… https://t.co/1CmgrjN0i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring your $10 to purchase Wrestling Team State Finals t-shirts and wear to Kalamazoo this weekend!!… https://t.co/2gzQhzKvwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I were a lefty Catholic,  the Francis era would infuriate me.  This is your moment, and its owned by a bunch of… https://t.co/qffliEgnI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sublimelight312 @DGunn01 @sarahkendzior @sublimelight312 you put a like on this.  Do you think Comey could arrest… https://t.co/LfwfagXfbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michaelflyfish1 @BoyGiuly So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One ! !    http://www.oceangrownseeds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Please pass the coffee, oh and have a great day! https://t.co/yy7L0bDGsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the one and only @kmalecki7 !!!!! 🎉🎉🎉 ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 📸: @skeletonnbones  ~~~~~~~~~~~… https://t.co/scmyb27AWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 forget that, I’ve just seen I can create a park on there. Cheers anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now it’s @TerrierMBB turn as they host Lehigh. Tip coming in 15 minutes. BU without 3rd leading scorer Javante McCo… https://t.co/kQX9DrQm5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preparing for Sxsw Atlantic Records 1on 1 let’s hope for the best 🙏🏾💯⏳🎤😱👍🏾🙌🏾 @ SXSW https://t.co/mMmCQAQctB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry @DrPhilRoe #Trump may have some Policies  that align w East Tenn but completely opposite w morals, ethics, Ch… https://t.co/C0sZmKfnBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradCorn24 @360FFB @ChuckDownfield1 Stephanie Morgan had a glove unlike anybody]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarcesLaureano @olympia8 No. No lo ve, no lo oye, tampoco dice nada al respecto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture A Day  from 2014 - February 19  #leicaphotography  #blackandwhite #photography #dailyphoto  📷 ©John R. Fult… https://t.co/778t223EEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrU_LegACy_ @AmeriKraut The numbers above are not solely the city of Philadelphia, but the entire metropolitan are… https://t.co/yyLQIDEKgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This good advice if you’re one of the 5-10 best players in the world. What’s not listed here is the 10% scholarship… https://t.co/CkPS7t5d73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #NorthWakeCounty on I-540 EB between Six Forks Rd - Exit 11 and Falls of Neuse Rd - Exit 14 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powder weekend in Park City! @Deer_Valley @PCski https://t.co/l9vkNVpqaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 under Contract up at the NE Boat Show.  23 and 25 Regulator’s.  Thank you Tim and Bill!#regulatorboats… https://t.co/hdu2RLcdXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing time for the Huskies... #GoHuskies #HuskyPride https://t.co/8BScNInSrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayblue4ever @rzalmj @GameSpot Even if one would have to pay a fortune to buy that IP from them, anything's possib… https://t.co/QXDqSiHr8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me being very pensive — thinking about the wonder of RCTs.H/t @boricuawonk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s #Vinyl record calendar is largely forgettable. But it was part of a “Special Sale”. Probably a close out sa… https://t.co/IiDYxkQWVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Watch is suggesting I go for a brisk, 25-minute walk and be sure to stand and move a bit each hour. "You can still do it!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro live in Alberts and I had to park by Aztec Corner that’s really wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Long Live Rock And Roll by @OliverBrewingCo @ DCBG Hopfest — https://t.co/jSHYZGcaUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[To merkin-wearing, faux bully bearing, Brylcreem smearing Jr, It is because I love America that I hate Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philiphutcheson @MikeOrganWriter @LipscombMBB Depends on what 3 categories you’re measuring Mike. Points, Boards,… https://t.co/30sAnPg2oU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregTaylor302 @LanceWilliams99 Yes they do, but if you are gonna pay them make it an investment and perhaps the sc… https://t.co/C2xV50nrsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunsetting in the bay. #AfternoonShenanigans Post #LeaderSummit2019 #vExpert @MyVMUG https://t.co/MYhD2KbUyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Can I Play That? sketch on #SNL the other night was PERFECT. Like, terrifyingly so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halsey- Without Me Cover By: Mindy Davey https://t.co/lVYIlK12T2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update 3am PST - we boarded another plane to replace the one that got hit by an owl on takeoff, only to find out th… https://t.co/zqp9QyKaWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C1231Will @NYPost_Brazille Willie great minds I posted the whole story a month ago check out the Wikipedia it's awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @katyperry @innoutburger Most of the clips I’ve seen on social media of the show this year involve th… https://t.co/CjKKIjyyeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detroit has a brand new arena built for hockey. Hope they can pull it together because this #CHIvsDET game is a howler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elontimes @teslamodel3fan Two good reasons to software limit the range.  1. If a warranty issue arises it’s a simp… https://t.co/p5ncZY7LnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm since this was at liberty the answer to my question is already answered lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poeticpantry MUSIC LINKS   https://t.co/qDa9s2VUry  https://t.co/Y96wqQFfLI  https://t.co/V17QORcOPW… https://t.co/DZwYuYfYVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drlenapearlman @DrP_Principal @LRKnost Doing some cool research on this in 2018: often kiddos living in chaos at h… https://t.co/mwafqLCry1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't believe #Boeing has had two crashes in less than the last year. I bet it has to do with their software / se… https://t.co/QGAC1cuo5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet the Time God! He’s friendly! #GOsnapshot @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/WpvbaI0iLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21Braxton How u live your whole life in Utah and two years in okc and cheer for the thunder over the jazz?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the job at Sinclair Broadcast Group! FINALLY 😭🙏🏼 I start March 4th!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same way she arrived at the conclusion: Since NY was giving away to Amazon 3 billion$ in tax credits to move th… https://t.co/UxR0vhr5IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[7) I informed him that I didn’t know which gym I would join, but I certainly would NOT be joining 24 hour fitness,… https://t.co/9mncDnPpNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWECritics When He was burned by the undertaker. He was all bandaged up standing next to Kane screaming Dead man- Kane is coming!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will preach the gospel.  I’ll die and be forgotten.  As long as you get the glory! #TheSend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cambridge, MA: MIT Park. Or Industrial Park of Cambridge. Warm, 27 degrees Fahrenheit. SW wind 7-10mph. Rain on Sun… https://t.co/9wnc5hoTNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#celtics lose 5 of our last 6, I’d be quiet 🤐 when we beat GSW by 30, I be talkin again ☘️ #friday #raininjunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamShatner I would bet good money that there was no meeting, and this is a cry for attention akin to phishing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarratedWatson Check Jenna Sudds outfit from yesterday (in Toronto) and today (Ottawa).  Did it change? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends called me out on sucking ketchup packets while eating my burger😂 am I the only one??😅😅😅😅😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday lookin a lot like this https://t.co/8jWQf8PHIm https://t.co/RcvrxclQCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a 分 桃 (Fēn Táo) (Blend 5) by @jesterkingbeer @ Starlight Park — https://t.co/DYIWPVrTNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aFePOWER Crazy the pricing we get from keystone and Meyers is better than going direct even with this 20% off.   N… https://t.co/xImTVwEzRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily Kushner  and Trump are probably going to build a Trump Tower whith the Saudis paying for it. Lord o… https://t.co/pEM3xBuAiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiasazand @MarshadeCordova The Joint Chiefs of Staff declared Climate Change a national security threat years ago.… https://t.co/kGLv72e29S]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Everything can be taken from us but one thing: the last of human freedoms – to choose one’s attitude in any given… https://t.co/hgIN0SKMRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The solutions I can offer are sustained wins and/or a re-approach game day. C-Unit was successful bc it was the big… https://t.co/yLjysDF5TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Without Russia lying for you, you are going to be toast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter I’ve always said you #cantfixstupid, just need to let it die off.  This is a start!  #ClimateChangeHoax]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of niggas who told me i don’t get hoes cause of this tweet is hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BPhillips_SB There are instances of danger, specific to the head/neck, in essentially every youth sport. I underst… https://t.co/ni5OjMiUXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wouldn’t even take the chance to play again. Take the money and run right off into the sunset just like the @NFL… https://t.co/tCSIw45QGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my Coaching fiends, especially of baseball and softball, these are RULES TO LIVE BY. A lot of these rules ca… https://t.co/4dG09FPfPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember: one day you will wield the baton, and one day you will be on the receiving end. Wield it wisely, that tho… https://t.co/fZPV4hFdja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clampigirl Oh good. I didn't want to have to get on a plane to California to find one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#charrodays2019 #charrodays #brownsvilletx #beauties #defiesta #charrodaysfiesta @ Brownsville, Texas https://t.co/6wx2Lq65FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[If TRUMP wants to eliminate OBAMACARE, once and for all, allow US citizens to write off healthcare insurance costs on their taxes.🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Please get help. Medical or therapy. Life is worth living. Your well being does not dwell in another person, but within you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLyons_Den @nuclearcarly i have no idea, honestly. i just know it’s not mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer Release!  Stratus Cloud IPA, single hopped with Strata at 5.8% ABV.   Described as “passion fruit meets pot”,… https://t.co/fQKVPWFKOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3WinstonSalem  Pax of 12 for an old school beatdown at #Mayhem With bear crawl merkins, the multiplier, and the l… https://t.co/gORmrB9fzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[FAA declines to ground Boeing 737 MAX 8, says unknown if two crashes are linked - CNNPolitics https://t.co/fEnfufsbqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsg3897 @BrennaFlanagan2 That's more of an opinion piece to be written, Brittney (and one that I fully support bei… https://t.co/WhOECuCw4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 Actually, if money wasn’t an issue than I would get rid of pay-to-play at the club I work for. #SoccerChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt @realDonaldTrump @VP @SecPompeo @robertcobrien So I guess Trump is also right that Kim didn't have anyt… https://t.co/CVKcVpN161]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gnats. They fly around to annoy and distract you. Rats. They crawl around looking for an opportunity bite you and c… https://t.co/4XuKpc5KJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you forgot... It isn’t the #responsibility of the historically marginalized to educate, coddle or sympathiz… https://t.co/AvrR9O1M8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Derbyologist @sdsuemk I had a feeling it might have been the case.  He made up like 6 lengths in what felt like 1/16th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pkibbe Not playing around this morning! @ Providence Village, Texas https://t.co/ZGlVUCyxpw]]></document></documents></author>