<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When the boy just won’t take no for an answer 🤛🏻 #twd https://t.co/9SOAoHRhY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My professor said the same thing 3 times and I still didn’t understand a word from her mouth....]]></document><document><![CDATA[• what can I say? I love coffee 🤷🏻‍♀️ • @ Hidden River Roasters, LLC https://t.co/zxM7lXsrY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovParsonMO’s Cabinet is a great group, including a bunch of amazing women.  Thanks to @MoCommissioner,… https://t.co/WQx3q44d0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore a Paul Pierce Celtics jersey to work and a customer just asked if he could "Buy that Jersey right off your body."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several years ago it dawned on me: should something happen to my husband or to our marriage, i would be royally fuc… https://t.co/2L1ubZG2po]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still getting used to having married friends &amp; doing things w married couples. It’s still so weird to me🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna smoke some dope and take a couple shots 😩 I need new friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darling-Hammond cited these policies in high-performing countries: -Equitable resources to schools -Mjr invstmnts i… https://t.co/PRvgLXDitQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @TCPalm @Patriots What is it with old White Tremendously wealthy guys?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a child, I was fearless. I thought nothing bad could happen. Now I think of all the things that could go… https://t.co/J3sQdqRhf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TealHeather Good Morning Heather. Hope you're having a lovely day ❤️😘😘  Such a cute GIF - thank you!! https://t.co/hfYsVqCbMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know who in their right minds, will vote for Trump again. He is clearly a narcissist, biased and vindictive… https://t.co/jMpZh2Ro5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CentreCourtInc I’m enjoying watching the progress on my daily walk to the streetcar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you really turn 21 if you didn’t have the balloons? 🥳💕 @ Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania https://t.co/MdmnsIOVM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people who challenge you and continue to push you to realize your WORTH are not your enemies. That’s the real friends. Learn THAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWStweets WHY IS SHE ON THE COMMITTEE AFTER HER PASS AND SHE IS NOT IN PRISON? A PROVEN LIER OVER AND OVER WHAT TH… https://t.co/YS6xnKpV6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briaunapope Exactly!!! “Reality TV” is actually a distraction from reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradTakei @GeorgeTakei Actually it’s a battery.  Assualt is when you think someone is going to touch you; battery… https://t.co/4bHyBofGM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn weather is ruining Laken’s plans tomorrow. Supposed to be going to University of MN forca cheee clinic, but th… https://t.co/NQ1L16FGIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonimiz804 @aympontier Grâce à Macron, notre démocratie ne sautera peut-être pas tout de suite, malgré les multipl… https://t.co/TQaJOr3u7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unanimous—the Montgomery County Council votes 9-0 to ban outdoor smoking at bars and restaurants—with exceptio… https://t.co/sVl5alkNKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great, it's #InternationalWomensDay, so we all get to hear extra backlash BS today. BTW, since I know the question… https://t.co/qI5K2tGHGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some fun at Ulta today. Big thanks to @imlianaofficial for doing such an amazing job! #jamescharles #morphe… https://t.co/BWjd84Ux17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes.  How ironic, drug money builds the wall  to prevent more drugs from coming into the USA.if damn democrats have… https://t.co/eRKihBWxUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life knocks you on your knees, you’re in a perfect position to pray  - Unknown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Washington Township, Gloucester County, New Jersey https://t.co/fQh3ZZ32XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and one last thing, Calvary, it seems there goal is to make people “Christians” if that’s what they want to call… https://t.co/0LT4aAMZU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[COME ON @CeeLoGreen!!!!! Yessss!  He better SANG on this new @OffsetYRN “North Star”  I just had a whole concert in… https://t.co/84b8eBekvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏠 Open House 🏠 🗓Saturday, March 9th 12:30-2:30 . 📰Gorgeous Home in Desirable Area of Flushing...🏡 . 📋Spotless, Upgr… https://t.co/MCkxQaSGTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has got to go! @IlhanMN the whole point of Islam is to infiltrate every nation and force the people to conform… https://t.co/PFWnNOT7Mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[No a single person at work cares anymore lmao. Someone was bitching at me about their table and I looked this mom d… https://t.co/na2qMH1Lw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tigerwrestling Amazing coaches, alumni support, parents, environment! Thank you for being great hosts @BearcatsWrestle]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most heartbreaking things in this world is when one of your favorite bras break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cla1re24 @GoddessLHG love #julianmcdonald goddess gowns! Grab that cutting edge! 💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💋 @ Los Angeles, Californ… https://t.co/1l4UxqOzvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUAndRead Hey go watch my video, https://t.co/QUUj3oHaP7 I got pretty good content ! Subscribe if you see what you like 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Computer Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/yTed4gCIaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globalnewsto .@Toronto_Fire still working this fire - long cold night for the crews - thank you 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosienKC @YNB I think that was my favorite thing...strong, smart, badass women. It's an incredible movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Kar-Jenner/Woods/Thompson thing is causing more drama than Trump’s National Emergency declaration #America]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the best big sis anyone could ask for! I love you and I hope 21 treats you well! Thanks for always being my icon💕 @___EKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristyBean88 But as much as I can't stand Sonny anymore part of me still wants that Chad and ''Sonny bunny'' good-bye scene lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell I said that very thing to my 14-year-old daughter tonight. “Look at her arms. They are hanging by h… https://t.co/AZw9TMJpV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[On god ill be in shambles if Ross or dollar tree goes out of bussines 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve spent the last 5 months watching through Cheers on Netflix, and I’m finally on the last season. I love it so m… https://t.co/Xnd7S2ioY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to the @SloverLibrary today for the Opening Reception of the Virginia Glass Guild's 2019 Member's Exhibition… https://t.co/4E4KGRcu9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving our "Readbox" door for #ReadAcrossAmerica week! People can come and "check out" students' favorite books fro… https://t.co/JdiXK0HbVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2 @glammalg11… https://t.co/SU0Cqqs23R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all my wonderful friends and family. Wishing everyone lots of love and wonderfully surpris… https://t.co/kBUnQSGU1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t build God’s house without building people because God’s house IS people. @ihopkc #hillsongkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheColeGalotti Umm same that’s why I asked you to be my valentine yesterday on Instagram]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INAImexico no funciona la página de https://t.co/SClzGsbov2 aparece un error constante al elaborar la solicitud “e… https://t.co/1A1jYkyaIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the morning in Athens for the #youngdems Platform and Bylaws Revision Meeting! Just 27 days until convention!… https://t.co/ub70VCMqs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oceana Investigation Keeps One of the World’s Largest Fish Factory Vessels on Illegal, Unreported and Unregulated F… https://t.co/KBOyUNevSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cayoba1 @jcsosazpurua @TaticaLupe Mejor presentarse como eruditos analíticos y no como lo hace tu; eructo analítico.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren You support Trump; you don't give two shits about military heroes. https://t.co/qgLvj9dqTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dasza01 @parscale @kimguilfoyle Very, very sad 😞 that this is even a thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgebby Can you tell I wanted to go into sports broadcasting HAHA #statsonstatsonstats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieJewell11 i love you so much annie! i cant believe we’ve been friends for long. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your talents and dedication to nutrition education for the public shine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diets a low key stupid. If you want a change, if you want to be healthy, make a permanent lifestyle change, not a d… https://t.co/8T5CG6sEGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending all the birthday wishes to @CesarDomboy today. 🎂💗 #Outlander @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/rNwMja400g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I dated a dude with green text bubbles AND I thought he was the one. I really lost myself there, didn’t I?]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this funny. LMFAO! This is how I'm getting through high school. :D It's working...somehow.xD https://t.co/U5dgiIrm7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@upton_5 @noregretsejf71 @Scubasue88 @autumnbreath2 @LadyLightly @wendiwendy @katwoman75 @neverenoughglt… https://t.co/oITu69ByNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Conversation Robe⠀ ⠀ When my daughter was in junior high/high school we joked about her Conversation Robe. It w… https://t.co/88SXaKyNWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gnakishi03 @MKL712 @BethP9999 @IamSydneyCat @ruthhill74 @LSTNMovie @denise_yorty2 @LisaColang @BobbiSchutte… https://t.co/yLFFskx6G3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being in Vegas is seriously the best thing ever. Just wish it would distract me from being sad about my dad 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioDB somos miles de cubanos esperando que se le dé solución al parol, señor representante estamos sufriendo y n… https://t.co/BtwFWparhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badprophet90 @BradHurt6 @iheartmindy @Oswarez @pot_incorrect @JacobAWohl Bingo]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like the pre-workout i drank earlier is just now hitting me. i start shaking if i sit still and didn't sleep… https://t.co/DbdGuC3YBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComperatDustin Welcome to Twitter!  You’ll find all you need to know about our @HoustonTexans and more! 😜 #wearetexans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias a nuestros muy apreciados clientes quienes ya se han vuelto amigos, 🙏😁 por sus referencias y por hacernos d… https://t.co/sq8sMXHEjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish there was somewhere i belong but there isn’t. nobody likes me or wants me around]]></document><document><![CDATA[#putyourdukesup 🥊 #drpetti 👊🏻👩🏻💪🏻 .....And you thought I just worked out in the OR😉😘😊 #fighton ✌🏼 #spabella… https://t.co/195EJifS7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is tragic! I’ve heard many like this. Solution would be to fence the bridges, sadly, to prevent this from happ… https://t.co/nUulyNqqBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talk about being too heavy for 2 in the morning. @CharlotteCKA https://t.co/8vqpme39cJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is absurd that fantasy players are scared of drafting Todd Gurley. He’s finished top 5 in three out of four of h… https://t.co/tmN0ZElUo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just evolved into being on the radio🌊 a little more! 🤷🏽‍♀️😉 Happy #NationalWorldRadioDay🎉 #MelodicallyIT… https://t.co/yCgJ2AqH17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyMillsTV @SPECNewsROC We were there selling cookies! https://t.co/cwjh1K0iit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdFantasyLG @K9sOfLivePD @lt_gray @LivePDNation @LadiesOfLivePD @SheriffChody @Sgt_LarkinsGang Yay Cowboy Gray!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngiTaylorKISS Some places literally started stapling bags together bc of this😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heart dissection Day 2 #plentyofgloves @ Dr Lee's Science Lab-O-Rama, East https://t.co/fxm98QkVf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan0666 @kat21_18 @realDonaldTrump Just another day in the Trump WH nursery!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdequus They are brilliant. My two pairs are upwards of 5 years old, I wear them nearly every day in the winter, a… https://t.co/Rrxa4KCui7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActuallyDontGAS @sean_spicier Btw, I'm following him. I know it's a parody, I thought people would get I was parad… https://t.co/sduZhPQsQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God, thank you for sending my boyfriend to me. I appreciate your cute blessing!!💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internet is out at the house and I’ve got shit going on offshore - to the office I go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devonlevasseur Look, Devon, you’ve got to fight fire with fire. Tell them you’ve *no use* for their moralizing. Th… https://t.co/SivYycW3ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[That the formal living room in my grandparents apartment belonged to another lady because my grandmother didn’t wan… https://t.co/WKN1Ir0J6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went a little crazy online shopping this weekend but I can’t wait for all my boxes to come in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[😡 This makes me sick to my stomach seeing these posts. It should be banned...#SaveOurWildlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fox6TedPerry But it includes room and board so he should be able to bank everything he makes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We worship!!!! @ Victory In Christ Christian Center https://t.co/IEO0FdDk2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t imagine having a kid one day and other children treating them this way...our society disappoints me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I got a text from a number I didn’t recognize and when I looked at an old convo it was some guy from tin… https://t.co/V2MxeCdFtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErewhonMarket The health store you can go in sick and scream “take advantage of me” and still they wouldn’t. 🙏🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenneth Tobey #vanheflinandkennethtobey @ North Carolina https://t.co/mDEVeRJ2m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I will be wearing a minimum of 5 layers in tomorrow morning’s live shots, thank you for asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Pro aprons are so cool!!!! 👏😄 thanks @raul060376 !!!! @jenjenilani @DianaSundermann @david_huntsman… https://t.co/LbP5rr7ZTB]]></document></documents></author>