<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DrPuls I usually find things like that right after I get back from the store with the replacement. #Hopethathelps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliStokols @NicolleDWallace Time for him to go. GOP where are you? Support an addled traitor any longer and the pa… https://t.co/KMzc0VmA4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seeing #CaptainMarvel today and I’m hyped. I’m seeing some reviews, mostly from the male demographic saying tha… https://t.co/ku1kNDHw6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las feminazis reciben ayuda directas de los gobiernos locales de izquierda, uno de los motivos para no preocuparse… https://t.co/uNS8DUpIyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the #Oscars, the brilliant nominees get back to work! What a pleasure working on bibishortfilm with… https://t.co/N4ur2ZSs6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamfan40 @nburzych Yeah because the FA’s are going to be just as good as...checks notes...Bryce Harper. Come on man, lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on over to @VCA Coast Animal Hospital in #HermosaBeach. 💞 Our #PURRsday Adoption Hours are 5-6:30p. Learn more… https://t.co/zh3uuuHMGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla  Model 3 now $35k. Once you  drive one you’ll never go back.   It’s like driving the future.   When I drive… https://t.co/CPhNRLC0U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruins playing crazy train pre game against the hawks, just signed there own death wish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me Right Now😭😭😭 #sadpeoplewillrise😭#Depressionwillgodown https://t.co/7Pjf70hY54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupremeOne3 Secrecy? Auto correct obviously... but yes, weirdos none the less]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another milestone for our program, with tonight’s win it marks the 13th time in the last 16 years Rock Bridge has w… https://t.co/PNVk4CvOol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluegrass_jack @MrsTylerKSR @FakeBarneyKSR NO team's fans should EVER chant overrated. That chat is basically sayi… https://t.co/ugdZKANiJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the aquarium. #aquarium #downtownaquarium #octopus #ocean #rockymtnrestoration #contractorsofinstagram @ Northwe… https://t.co/Odcd7Rn5df]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenBlankley Yes, make updating our policy to include non-discrimination for sexual orientation and gender identity a top priority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the opportunity to shoot for Ayleks the other night. More photos coming soon from that as well! https://t.co/0L4PCX7edS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#please #movies #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram #teachersofinstagram #tutorsofinstagram #poetry #poems… https://t.co/6J3YkOhUl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class Notes: Great question in this article... Is our #learning organization designed for efficiency or agility.… https://t.co/oYgQrcJi9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheath24 @NHLGIFs Prototypical Pavelski goal. LOVE it. I screamed when I saw it live lul]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess moshing &amp; edm is a thing. Cause these folks in the club were moshing moshing lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mp16 made me this awesome shirt for Disney!!! #GoBU #ProudToBU @ Chelmsford, Massachusetts https://t.co/uhsKoewrV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling strong physically and mentally this week #Powerglide @ Vent Fitness https://t.co/lSm5Dh2MtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Panzer AR-12 Shotgun from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $500! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/YpPxmd7yLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis If we’re serious that climate change is the real threat, we need to consider nuclear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anastasjoy @StudyTruthNow @HillaryClinton @arenasummit I never saw a ugly women but I saw some that wasn't as good looking as others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennClarkRadio I'll take Bell 10/10. Just on field alone, better runner,pass catcher, pass blocker. He had off fi… https://t.co/YNkpjugKbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aún en el #IMSS cd.Juarez, excelentes doctores y enfermeros pero pésima administración, porque tantos servicios sub… https://t.co/b6eosXAdu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[***REDACTED*** (A notorious $tsla bull) is in my DMs this morning to give, I literally can't believe I'm saying thi… https://t.co/sTk1ucCaVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/2qujTxTw7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CancilleriaVE Tienen las armas ,el pueblo es evidente que NO los quiere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USNavyMomPA @asa477 Because you were a coward then and you are  cowards now. Drills are necessary now so that when… https://t.co/OM9UibeEvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate9Fan @supercars @Ford And missing that Ambose guy in NASCAR, what a personality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/pH4EU5wdJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for listening to much Ghost band amaranthe halestorm hinder zack brown band Ghost band Five Finger Death Punch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgreid @ceclindgren A generation is usually 20 years. Get ready for WokeGen sequencing where your sequencer is tie… https://t.co/tedPILBNZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT Has anyone considered that this Jared thing may be an intentional distraction to get the media to move o… https://t.co/a8mB2eTuD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUPONT HOSPITAL​🏨 Open House “A Day in the Life of a Healthcare Professional” Saturday, February 16th 10:00 a.m. – 12:00 p.m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[White land owning men are quick to set constitutional precedents to benefit themselves politically in the short ter… https://t.co/36L7j3wGqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on two years here...YES!😠  From Discover on Google https://t.co/y73YIrNtPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleClark Signature Gathering Business has a strong future in Colorado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Btw Sec player of the year ... should be Grant Williams .... just look at his numbers ...compared to everyone else… https://t.co/764jQOQjmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama! Mama I’m coming hoooooome!! @hahacomedyclub SATURDAY NIGHT https://t.co/pqcsHricY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOceanAC @VisitAC @HQ2AC @LilKim @djmistercee Should have a city wide tribute to a lady who helped others for ma… https://t.co/LbTlUrj6kA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bergen now has Norway's largest fleet of hydrogen taxis. #driveH2 #kjempebra #Norway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Todd.....Please, Please, Please, Please, Please, Please, Please, Please dear god if you can hear me, please l… https://t.co/bmJVLVitwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's fairer than lilies of rarest bloom, He's sweeter than honey from out of the comb; He's all that my hungering s… https://t.co/3PhkvLlrnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack SHES A DRUNK. YOU CANT TALK TO A DRUNK.  YOU EVER TRY AT A BAR SOUNDS JUST LIKE HER.   GO TO BED NANCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicHerald Great. We can just call it male on male from now on. We are venturing into the ridiculous. #Rome… https://t.co/GX3ML415qc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely incredible match . the WWE Women making history happen once again. The Inaugural WWE Women's Tag Team Ch… https://t.co/LVgjyhzLIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estás declaraciones serán para ayudarse o que buscarán? Mantienen los mismos asesores que cuando Peña? Es auto sabo… https://t.co/BTe1dDzGwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickgalgs @Villanova_Alum You should track down and confront bradley cooper about his decision to transfer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC Yes he has, and it’s: #SkippyTheBushKangaroo https://t.co/V8085bhbzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toughest pill to swallow.  Thanks for the fun and thank you @oshea042 and @_Linnny_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoCatXXX Like this dude believes we’re in a giant dome like in the movie the Truman show. Like are you kidding me?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattOswaltVA David Spade with a Neil Young song lyric supposedly honoring Cobain. I am pretty sure that Kurt would… https://t.co/bP5I9vqKAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving to feed my music habit 🥁🎸🚌 . . #musician #music #guitar #drums #rock #gig #rehearsal #practice #loud #deaf… https://t.co/8qZtJnlzUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestRecipesUK @OfficialSPAMUK @SPAMbrand  SPAM® is so underrated as a quick meal staple.]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to beat @crackdown 3 by tonight but having a night out for abit #xbox #Crackdown3 #mixerstreamer #gamer #outandabout]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah Phillies have zero money left now haha he keeps putting up a batting average of 249 like last year we will be j… https://t.co/OM1FqxPaeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMarksDG Seen this on Facebook, thought it was interesting, not sure if it has any substance however https://t.co/kK7HxqOpDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a long time since I've ready any poetry. This brilliant book Kumukanda by @KayoChingonyi makes me want to… https://t.co/uU7C74E50s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehumanderek @WarrenBuffett That is what I do. I really like @Vanguard_Group (VTSAX)]]></document><document><![CDATA[the most conor gray-core thing i heard from him was when he dropped me off home from the Counterparts afterparty an… https://t.co/YTpsCQd3fy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell is harmful to America. Vote out GOP in 2020. https://t.co/t9tXsvEARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[AUTHORITY IRONDOM SECURITY SYSTEM HOMELAND SECURITY. USING THE JEWISH LIE. CLAIMING THEY ARE AMERICAN LAW ENFORCEME… https://t.co/ddO0RTr8jQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help support #thewinnerwithin #girlsconference. Enjoy #goodeats for a #goodcause Join the #vesselchallenge f… https://t.co/JLU2dLROc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOMORROW THE DAY PARTY  SUNDAY MARCH 3,2019 DOORS OPENT AT 3 PM TO 9 PM COVER: $10 AT DOOR  MUSIC POWERED BY APOLLO… https://t.co/ZWmJUu0cUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Monday morning batshit crazy tweet fest just starting. Lies on top of lies on top of lies. The off… https://t.co/3DGFxZGSpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastrnak our on ice this morning with Kim Branvold, as well as a stick in his hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a gift. Celebrate them all. #fiftyisfabulous #friends❤️ #TheLibrary #stregisatlanta atlasbuckhead 🎂🍷❤️… https://t.co/ciFT3XlcXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelven91 Silph road said an hour ago but my park is the same nest as it was last week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lightning_kf I call them the CtC as well. Worst heel stable since League of Nations. The crowd goes mild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaffaDiiaz Tierra de los alacranes Durango. La tierra de Pancho Villa. La tierra del cine]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of our @FOX29philly viewers said I was dressed like “Dapper Dan?”  Was that an insult or a compliment? 😂😂 FOX 2… https://t.co/bMzK31GvEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro it's not fair how talented your entire family is...y'all are awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericarrache I'd have to try it or at least check the specs. Details have been released?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @WCCO So what? Is this suppose to call him out for something....he’s the President, if he wants a golf simulator he can have one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hartcoven @securelexicon @MylesSuer @psalvitti @bmkatz @mdkail @ciomentors @BevInTech @bjonesnDC @jasonsparrow… https://t.co/lnsnRkwBAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VCUHorns Fun back and forth game. First half was rough with all the missed shots, but it’s been awesome here in the second!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need this when I head to Houston with Coco. Like I swear people stare at me while I say “okay coco I’ll be back i… https://t.co/6RVKPfOJwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only gotta make it through to Wednesday and then I have 6 days off!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the N.C. Forrest service and the USDA for the trees we just finished planting in the greenhouse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burninburnout @IvankaTrump Says the dumba$$ who follows these two brothers. What a dip$hit you are https://t.co/nH31lF4F5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Grant Williams for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/INbeEOKg8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[• @launavaughn • . . Worship set: - Overcome - Here again - Great are you Lord 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻 @ Hope Fellowship Church https://t.co/G8o2rrAgVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregoryggtee It’s eating into what should be going into paying teachers and support staffers. Even worse, I’m sure… https://t.co/SGQu5P5rI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine @robsmithonline Utah has done this for yrs. They keep trailers on school grounds for mormon children… https://t.co/56Kxq75vTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Lol u work on deals to get Results and Trump doing good job!U boy Obama had 8 failure years and u gi… https://t.co/aeSB26pNfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heather_1201 Fuck social norms and expectations. Lights shine in different ways for different things in many diffe… https://t.co/P9cXjnHXcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump "He is a racist. He is a con man. He is a cheat."  donny, he's talkin' 'bout youse. #MuellerIsComing #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arkansas juniors will be taking the state-provided ACT test on Wednesday, February 20! #NoLimitsAR https://t.co/F609vMfk96]]></document><document><![CDATA[👤💭 Ice cream 🍨 Nice treat to have treat delicious thing you can have all by yourself🍨👥 https://t.co/sFPTCmZdar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homesafeIL rocked last night! I was reminded why y’all are one of my favorite newer bands!! Can’t wait for the nex… https://t.co/iLRlM11pLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sick marine mammals turning up on California beaches—  Warm waters reduce the amount of bait fish in the ocean.… https://t.co/hgFzj7US5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio’s most under-appreciated line on @paulfinebaum  re: Tennessee: “Of all the states in the SEC it’s on… https://t.co/LJZHVfVql2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdDearien I just got here and can’t take credit. But, thank you. And just know it will continue to get better and better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone who hasn’t been before, #CycleForSurvival starts off like this... https://t.co/gVGddxP1KM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's what's wrong with Canadian politics @CBCOntarioToday big money corrupts good people. JT meant well but he an… https://t.co/wdI8mk1Pgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to watch the @pbrvelocity here at @Rupp_Arena . @PBR #PBR #bullriding https://t.co/71Yohwv6Dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to the airy port ✈️ this is my first time leaving the country, and I’m doing it by myself. :,) I’m nervous as shit]]></document></documents></author>