<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Right when I feel like I can’t take it anymore - it’s Friday - 😎🕺🏻 https://t.co/PyFTwuTPdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Journals of Ostinyon are currrently under consideration and will be unavailable for the time being 😊.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the reason I procrastinate so much is bc I still get my shit done regardless]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blue sat on that spot where they sat so many nights in tears. Tonight they were all #alone like so many other time… https://t.co/mLjL1v0NnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOTALLY SHOOK.   Just learned that Bradley Cooper is married.   Is Gaga the #sidechick?  S/N: Gaga should never be a #sidechick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THINK KINDNESS A Niswonger Community Read Event  Monday, February 18th 7:00 p.m. – Lecture Hall This is a panel eve… https://t.co/n4lsuirs5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @1flwpbmll Judge , if you’re reading this, you should apologize to America for erring in favor of the ric… https://t.co/rNTW7AAy5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethGoodenough @cheese051 CEO is the same weekend as SDGQ... adding Speed Running would be a pretty bad move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome opportunity to be introduced as an honorary observer, and walk within the ropes with Francisco Moli… https://t.co/5NcrXyBIaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried more when Jim &amp; Pam got married than A Star Is Born. I’m not quite sure what this says about me 😂🖤 https://t.co/k5T31bmRc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I salute the people that came directly from work to come here and drove hours to come here, they some troopers. I h… https://t.co/yrNJgMqMZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paula_White @Paula_White Hey...Good Morning and Happy Sunday! Hope you and @TheJonathanCain are having a nice week… https://t.co/2czv7VcGV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillsboro 410 using additional school funds to get all students reading at grade level at end of 2nd grade and more… https://t.co/juw7805XG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Okay” he said after forever “Maybe okay will be our always.” “Okay,” I said - the fault in our stars ✨😭  @ the lom… https://t.co/lDQ3A2ZqRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popcseagles answers wit Luke Allen’s second goal of the match. Now a 3-2 match. #POPCS #tapps https://t.co/TahhelV7Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming in, I wasn't so sure, but it looks like @FlowHud can definitely play with @GALancerAD. The Lancers do have s… https://t.co/f15avFc31x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Ask the people and corporations who benefited from your tax cuts to build your wall  @POTUS @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personally I’m finding no Ministries perfect. Just need to find one that’s right for you. A lot of times I do not a… https://t.co/a8ydEhAWlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If scary movie,white chicks and most of the late 90s and early 00s movies would have came out nowadays people would… https://t.co/lOTn6reSxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both sides were wrong. The reservation system was a disgusting system. Federal laws were created to allow them to h… https://t.co/6Gzg0JR0tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing the stars back would bring the event back from the abyss it’s in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey didn’t si(esta) you there ;) @ Siesta Beach https://t.co/Y74YamWe3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee State's loss eliminates them from qualifying for the OVC Tournament.  337 teams remain!  #SurvivalBoard  https://t.co/ykzZK8TAMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/YmHL8IGlfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorbynistaEdith I left Labour because it had become a neostalinist entity. Had no joy in doing so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s not revealed is that the quartile numbers sampled went up significantly from 2014 to 2014. If your N has ton… https://t.co/NMQvfaEDDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hace rato me encontré un rasguño en la pierna y no tengo idea de dónde salió. :v]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍤 scampi.... (at @Maggianos Little Italy in Skokie, IL) https://t.co/y0ZEHq6S2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Infant mortality among blacks in the US is higher than that of other population groups. In the end, its… https://t.co/Lomd33QIps]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son Lil A is celebrating his birthday a day early by throwing up... I guess there is no need to figure out where… https://t.co/aXqlxOEsa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA_Langley @NASA_Technology Counter rotate gyro concept https://t.co/xCCKYPcLuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todos los videos infantiles - sin excepción - son casi tan lisérgicos como cualquier opiácido con los cuales se dab… https://t.co/VdqDWRb9mQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @realDonaldTrump if you aren't guilty then why are you wasting so much time trying to make sure yo… https://t.co/vEfMOgt77F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwolsen78 This one didn't seem too preachy or easy to misconstrue  "This moment is a gift, that's why it's called the present"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had to confront my coworkers that I share a room with about how loud and lengthy their conversations are and I… https://t.co/145k6pSDfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSchatanoff Hmmm. I really liked Black Panther. I'm sure it will win something, though probably not Best Pictu… https://t.co/NrYlR4XkUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[so it’s 5:45 and i’m at the front doors of heb trying to get in. tell me why 3 people have passed by and looked at… https://t.co/yeFpQwlfzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turdfurgitsfun @tama_chang @zapzapzap99 @petterflam @GopuThe @robert_wunder @king_teco @Andradejuca2 Yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early voting starts today! We are sign waving outside of Shands hospital #Chad4Jax #jaxpol #jacksonville #duuuval https://t.co/UlxWijrE6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods There a pattern of bad behavior. If one thing doesn't work, they move to the next target, on their list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink #d20 Short-Sleeve #shirt on #Etsy: https://t.co/LWPynOG0lF #dnd5e #etsyshop #vectorart #indieartist… https://t.co/cLizfYuOu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mina_baby @Jose__suave @Antiks_ @taysvpreme @StillComup Reese and finch could only do so much 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYTD_Blue @_tylerwade Strangers walk up to me and say “Jake sucks” every day at spring training.  I assume they li… https://t.co/mG0FAa7DNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka Self-proclaimed "Leading Classes" love conspicuous consumption to celebrate their successful sacking of t… https://t.co/gDUpnvcjpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don`t have the sketches this year but next year I want to paint a grand canvas of the aurora borealis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh oh. Nextdoor found out about the 10 story apartment proposal in Uptown!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz Except your voice Howie.  It doesn't count.   . . . . We don't need another narcissistic billionaire… https://t.co/aeKljDQ4k6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pakistan shuts down airspace to all commercial flights after it shot down 2 India 🇮🇳 War Planes.#BreakingNewsNow… https://t.co/de4eOKDmZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrellowens retweetfor vets! 11% of homeless are veterans.with ptsd and mental health issues. I am trying to help… https://t.co/hEjXOT6kvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to put on the finishing touches to my Antonio Brown painting. @AB84 #AntonioBrown #BillsMafia #Bills… https://t.co/fhWnt9jFov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton If there was a real border and you’d done your job as a senator meaningful immigration law we would… https://t.co/QU7L0MCtPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin like you mean it. This is just how GG was when we got back from her vet apt. yesterday.... #laughter #tee-hee… https://t.co/Q0jm7Mb0gQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorPRather_ @hdgamingtherapy @CopperMtn A ski slope with too much snow? In Ontario, we complain about not having enough snow...😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday supporting the Fam! @TorrenceWatson @JavonPickett @Mark_Smith_13 ✅🏀✈️ https://t.co/V0vKY6D0uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfredoAlvarezz @AlfredoAlvarezz se asustan por la Foto en la regadera? https://t.co/Ryuru2ZqtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJonSports Enjoy a beer or two on the tour. A friend from high school use to say their is no such thing as a bad b… https://t.co/W5wO7kfTt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only true if you connect with every Tom, Dick or Harry that sends an “I’d like to join your LinkedIn network” messa… https://t.co/a6B5IXHuB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also submitted a job application then withdrew it because I decided I didn't have enough experience in a particul… https://t.co/rfQoIYJvSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that this happening on a transit system is incidental, but it still feels a little like #transitlove ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThePrincessChronicles ...that punim.❤ @ Paterson, New Jersey https://t.co/MXG5amkTBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kjnchic His longtime aide Reggie Love played for the 2001 Duke championship team so that’s prob your answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetboeren @Circuitcat_eng @F1 @F1Help No worries it should be fixed by Mexico 🤔..... 🤣👎🚮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeyBank_Help I’m honestly no longer interested in you “fixing” things. You guys continue to jerk us around and we are over it. #pissed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiTrump4Ever1 @MSNBC @VaughnHillyard The cows are sort of obvious. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had someone approach me on UVU campus and immediately start trashing the dirty Libs and their stupidity.   After ex… https://t.co/LAlybcMuAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know almost every brand of Carts has failed pesticide and heavy metal tests lmao keep on poisoning yourselves w… https://t.co/v8ToL0bdLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deleted @ Pennsylvania's 10th Congressional District https://t.co/LyuuKcdmTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting day at USF. The inaugural Global Health, Diplomacy, and National Security Symposium was a success! #USF… https://t.co/IVBQlW3krV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy dancing behind me was like “hey white girl, hey! Hey!”  I turned around because he grabbed me and he was li… https://t.co/gUSV9wKBWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody forg er ta I exist then someone shows someone my art and they are like ohhh yeah! That duuude yeah i reme… https://t.co/FFZwaiVBGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEADS UP: Viral Facebook post about Uber sex trafficking incident not what it seems, @TampaPD says | @WFLARyan has… https://t.co/sh5OLcrhhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoustacheRollie @schneebs @ThatsaBadTake @stevenhood14 @agilson78 @JeffPassan How is doing something baseball play… https://t.co/vpJ4QXI5il]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasterCroissant @xforcades4 IM SCREAMING MY HEART IS SO FULL RN AHHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a couple you should own a minimum of the following:  -One, oh one, The only way is one One, oh one, The only way… https://t.co/8klEv4ImJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @SDHSAA has agreed in principle to move the 2019 state football championships from the DakotaDome to Dana J. Dy… https://t.co/9dXCeWlG2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiaLaneHD H a p p y  B i r t h d a y ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! https://t.co/lvFfSCzgPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DravenIM Let's be real. Season done, game has far more meaning to players like Brodzinski and Wagner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reviewer_news @DuckDuckGo Went outside a few days ago after ice storm,dish was an icicle,Hulu worked crystal clear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleCaliro @authorlindsayc @NicoleCaliro you totally just dropped a ‘Modern Family’ quote at the end and I am loving it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now watching the pilot for the late, lamented show Manhattan and I love how immediately and vividly it creates a sense of place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Every time he does this ... the more he squeals the more guilty he is]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt the amazing @ellekingmusic and one of my favorite photos. my mom also loves this photo so much, I made her a p… https://t.co/L1YxkL8x2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to hurt in order to know. Fall in order to grow. Lose in order to gain. Because most of life's lessons are learned in pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year I look forward to the mstamich conference! As a teacher it’s a great time to connect with other science… https://t.co/Naq4bd98Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE WATCH THIS...If you ever doubted what a complete moron our President is, you won’t anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I strongly believe that just because God says no doesn’t mean you should stop praying about it and asking for it. M… https://t.co/SaHVX3RssQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united what’s up with flight 3555 from EWR.  We’ve been sitting for 20 minutes at the gate with the door closed and no updates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmweb @HKYhatguy @TamithaSkov @PeakToSailPhoto Hope you have a hot potato in yer pocket, eh Don't forget to post o… https://t.co/FqoTtIEANo]]></document><document><![CDATA[imo pretty impressive of Kentucky to play 16:30 second half minutes and commit 5 fouls.   🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Goonie Juice by @jailbreakbrewco @ Exploring For Gas — https://t.co/LjYDaU2oRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeCathi @GOP @Jim_Jordan Jordan should have screamed when wrestlers at Ohio State were being sexually abused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I pray I see it as my personal opportunity to spend time with God. I believe to really understand the heart of… https://t.co/BpCLBQ0RG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC   I support you. But if this article is true, you will lose my support and many others. Do not target Ds.   Oc… https://t.co/sKFqO37MCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper reacts to Trump's golf trip after declaring emergency  https://t.co/DWUILt4jIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow I am becoming more convinced that the extreme crazy liberals today are just a ploy to make the more… https://t.co/GohqqnkfEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EgilLinell THIS NOTE IS LEGA-L BLOCKS FOR A-ll debts public And privAte TENDER BLOCKS ZONED FOR                   THiSANoTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon I promise here is the snippet #Oscars #music https://t.co/CE6TTI4fKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[But we are top of the league again so who gives a fuck!!!!! Up the fucking Reds #LFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyHarknessXXX You and your cock are perfect but if I could make it bigger that would be awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two hundred and twenty-five ice cold showers Hurricane hit my cell, ain't get no power]]></document></documents></author>