<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Off topic but, the most annoying thing about Netflix asking “are you still watching?” Is that I  have to find my re… https://t.co/76kTUAbybm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My "Sebastian" ready for his haircut💈🍼😆 @ Mar Vista, Los Angeles https://t.co/b83VBKO7Cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irrachionel Twitter is not going to happen and the dog's bed is next to my friend. (Hmm, I like this.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[25th &amp; Kimball in Southwest Philly, 1965/2018 https://t.co/ezBPDPbPGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the joys of old newspaper research is coming across these absolute gems of adverts (thanks @HannahPalsa for… https://t.co/MWA9Wiwb7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i just did this niggas birth chart without his birth time and i damn near threw up :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter how much music I dl, Apple Music will play the same 12 songs anytime I hit shuffle. So annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTVBananas the manner in which you presented this argument is extremely condescending bc of the fact that you’re m… https://t.co/cfzbCf5JDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics I’m Ontario we raised it from 10.75 to 14.00, there were lots of protests from small business, who… https://t.co/RILaudNonq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this me every night with baby in the bed? Sometimes I wake up with him perpendicular to me, feet in my ribs.… https://t.co/qZ0A9F3IW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eat this.. it doesn’t have much cheese in it....wrong! Lies. Lies lies. https://t.co/6ziw5CH8O3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TerrificTushyTuesday Repost from @danielled1983 Off to Vegas tomorrow. Can’t wait to be back and the weather is go… https://t.co/CaVLas1F2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidthornburgh THESE ARE ANTIQUATED AND DRACONIAN RULES, SIR. I DESERVE THAT QUARTER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrouderMedia I have a lot to say but I can’t collect my thoughts lol. Every point you made was valid, but I can de… https://t.co/5c1A0ZlXUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notting Hill giving me all the feels. "I'm also just a girl standing in front of a boy asking him to love her."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekPa56710094 @khanhakim_k @akomama_tm @PatGrant7777 @SUPERGOCHOo @Lee888123 @stradagangelica @meerbakker… https://t.co/58naoJk9Yq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @TrumpTrains600 @PencoskyRay @tagruber @MichaelLeeFree3 @Alan13778263 @Carolyncorneli8 @Lathenerd… https://t.co/p200vNhnja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to make cacio e pepe.  Eh.  Not so great.  Need to try @ChefMcKee version. @ West Linn, Oregon https://t.co/yVPrRL5Nyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent Clementine to school with over 200 Valentines. I think she came home with even more than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSearcaigh I will vote for whomever the Dem nominee is including Bernie.  It I hope the Bernie supporters like you… https://t.co/0XzLkBdFDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamhatesthis knows me so well!! He combined my love of flowers and books. He had these made from my two favorite… https://t.co/IhI1UkZkPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red This 'mander is frosted  Crawled back to her pond She's pretty exhausted   #ValentineASpecies… https://t.co/ys7kGZDtq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't we get rid of the Confederate statue in SA &amp; now ya'll are including it in your #WallpaperWednesday ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like it’s possible to be in a relationship and not abandon your friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have some of the most uplifting and supportive people in my life. If you have reached out within the past day, yo… https://t.co/c6fOA36m8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I #tweet @janetwongauthor @pomelobooks so excited to be here @SylviaVardell #TALE2019@# @TXLiteracyEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #birthdaysurprise - Kristen, Blair and Ryan joined us for dinner! How lucky an I? #friendsarefamily… https://t.co/KIyEQ8ZboD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecdancel Natawa ako sa define. I dont like your idol. That is how u define it. To judge me as a person based on a… https://t.co/t9XEP3iskW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yrfatfriend I’m all about being vegetarian or vegan, but damn, does PETA ruin it for so many people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seressia OMG. I'm still looking for the notebook I left at my sister's.  It was 3 months ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalGeoff2 @DucadiSpalato @doctoralexa It has nothing to do with the color of ones skin or sexual orientation… https://t.co/H6W3xWE8qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackWagnerhpk @erinkrakow @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV Whose that guy?? Hmmmm. Bill won’t like him. Bill n Abigail should b together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone file their taxes yet? If so how long did it take for your return SOS need a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey we don’t need to see Trump’s report cards and SAT scores to confirm he’s an idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silviadomi22G @shahnaqi84 @Soledad30777243 @tesamarylagvaz1 @RosaTrunk @Felic0508 @CristinPereyra @AlbertoJor18… https://t.co/0fwzi0n0ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_man72 @JayInslee @ThisWeekABC @GStephanopoulos This picture is worth a 1000 words! Wanting to save the world is… https://t.co/rwJ6X3p5o9]]></document><document><![CDATA[– Jag är chockad över att höra att fler banker runt om i världen deltagit i att praktiskt taget försöka dölja brott… https://t.co/i5lLTv9A5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lordstanley2016 @HowardA_Esq @dvorakoelling That would be my dream ticket! #Resistance]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: hey Sam...you awake? girlfriend: *half asleep* ya me: look at this girlfriend: ....hehehehe...send that to me *… https://t.co/vEWVB3OeJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dog is basically doing live action MoCap for this scene and should get an Oscar. Ugh you can see every emotion… https://t.co/OXoLkeWOIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton Good that means trump should not be allowed to walk around without impunity, correct @AmbJohnBolton?… https://t.co/Un9Oxmi4t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The use of the LBGTQA label is also problematic, as much as other labels (conservative/traditional anti-LBGTQ that… https://t.co/OJ9oY2J572]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add to Goodreads ➼ https://t.co/bw6x8JmtUT Mr. Rogers did not prepare me for the people in my neighborhood. A cut i… https://t.co/17FPLzyJcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning I am watching Captain Marvel tonight. This will be the sole focus of the day. #IWD2019 https://t.co/IboDjjidFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ivanmruiz44 Dude!!! I’m so jealous! Was it amazing?I’ve never seen them live but honestly it’s my fault I’ve misse… https://t.co/Gac4JrfPmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s History Month is gonna be Phenomenal!!!! Tune in💯💯💯 #womenhistorymonth https://t.co/YCWlfs6xE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cookiesandnaps I was watching Christy’s live from yesterday’s matinee. I believe is a troll. You need to have chri… https://t.co/XiHdw7kUOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Why are they giving this airhead any publicity. Really sick of hearing her craziness 🤬🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya'll. When these babies #writefromtheheart I'm reminded that I already have all I need! #jesusandtacos… https://t.co/rAgsiVOqYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @JohnLaprise @TheAtlantic Good Grief He is a nasty pig]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was R. Kelly lol but I’d love to see Sade, Teedra Moses, or Vivian Green in concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trim_obey Studios have used every tool to give them an Oscar advantage and had the power of the purse at the top o… https://t.co/4IYxNkzj5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoninaW @DrewDavisHere @JoePulizzi @wallykoval @ExecMatters #ILoveUs! 😘 #CMWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassiepaigemcal bitch. Me too. When I went to the doctor for my ear infection, you would’ve though I broke a limb with how much it costs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuanAntunes7 @JoshuaplaysPKMN @JeremyMartinCo3 @Lynette_50 @GoAldin @pizzalover4189 @obi_twan @IzanagiGod879… https://t.co/gFwfopGtVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[i did this once with my mom’s giant bottle of kirkland’s vodka she got at costco. i was afraid because my dad alway… https://t.co/UQcStLW2JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2 fave women ❤️ @LeighanneReena thank you for always being so good to us @ Zappos Theater Planet Hollywood https://t.co/B2AndZ2yTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenaiswriting But then what about chili?!? Beans become soup-like once added to tomatoes. But are separate on the… https://t.co/uR1PSj7fw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This event will bring about some much needed change...sooo much  dangerous propaganda out there pe… https://t.co/cZXP23sFx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peidays306 @realDonaldTrump Lol, trumpster completely misses the point. 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris   Why is media allowing Sen Burr to get away with saying his committee didn’t find any collusion wh… https://t.co/0LOWAqhQiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for the #MysterySkype @DinosaurNPS So cool to learn about your region! @ESCRegion11 https://t.co/5P2DaaU7F5]]></document><document><![CDATA[La séparation des indépendantistes en petits clans minoritaires va mettre fin à l'indépendance du Québec, Bravo au… https://t.co/9eSW1XSsLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waynekthompson EXACTLY how it should be done!!! You are a true leader of men @waynekthompson !! WE NEED MORE LIKE… https://t.co/GVvCB213QM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yellow shirt in the balcony! Our seats were perfect! @juliannarengle @emmalee_elane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find yourself a friend who will take ping pong ball baths with you 🏓 @ SPIN https://t.co/fNXg33VtQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadeChiefsPres @MiamiDadeChiefs @MGPDFL @ChiefNoelPratt Two great leaders! I appreciate the partnership you both h… https://t.co/tlEAnNFpzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump THE republicans should THROW a fit, Schiff is the one that told NUNES to stop aside .… https://t.co/KmMQCNV3Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Olympic cyclist Kelly Catlin has died at the age of 23  of suicide. Get help if you need it. https://t.co/OtV6HM9pAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyTrey2115 I meant feel free to reach out for one and I’ll make an extra special video :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigkstone That’s me with my husband. I always think before telling him things bc he may recommend therapy if I tal… https://t.co/ju98aHWMdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Ziggy, the kitten who loves to bake! He comes early every morning to watch my kitchen proceedings. No, he i… https://t.co/8aBjhVR9WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fodderfigure @CrystalDawn2400 Can I add also, how often does autism take the blame for "behaviours" that in typica… https://t.co/SKNgwebCBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how lucky I am to work with this brilliant team of marketers? Extremely! #slopesmarketing #siliconslopes… https://t.co/726N6NkKWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would just like to thank @_justsavage_97 @AllisonD_O_C_E @ShannonChaffers for helping me and letting me bounce id… https://t.co/lQ3qPUP7sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly can’t stand going to Kelsey Chevrolet anymore. I think i’d rather let my little brother change my oil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LidiaJozkowicz Słowo honoru legiendy i noblysty powinno wystarczyć "rozgrzanym" sędziom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickgs11 @TravisAllen02 The rumers of a fallen AZ I believe are false but I have not been out of my guarded, fe… https://t.co/UB8iUvzcZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xrayfm Yep! He played the best Hall &amp; Oates cover but I didn’t catch it. Do you know who it was? And the hilarious call-in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boothesrval More close up vids of BOO the Majestic, please -? I can live vicariously. My 3 little cats are much lo… https://t.co/JH1nJgVpYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewABC17 @P2Cham @rbhsbruinbear Go Sophie!!!  Go Lady Tigers!!!  🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻🇱🇷🇱🇷🇱🇷👏👏👏🖤💛🐯🏀🌈❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Introduction to Performing Arts class created and developed their own podcasts this week. https://t.co/Mr498tgRad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @TuckerCarlson Time for the Republicans to beat the Democrat Party at their own game: a “Global Poll… https://t.co/9QNttV9gPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[In two-child boy-girl households where the sister is older than the brother, the brother ALWAYS turns out to be sin… https://t.co/cwMoKggqy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REM977MP @Derfesorus @Pappiness @realDonaldTrump You libturds aren’t even worth arguing with. Trump will win again… https://t.co/VEBZGqcWWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveHash @SEIAgal @SenBlumenthal Maybe God created abortion to spare some children suffering 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mars, Incorporated signs multi-year extension to its partnership with Joe Gibbs Racing (JGR), as primary sponsor of… https://t.co/5Lpb0l60Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaDrivenDev @CrawliesWithCri Wow! Appreciate the history. Thanks for sharing. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, damn #AndyandRyan @JainaLeeOrtiz  @sipijungleboy #station19 move over Ryan, there’s a new stud in town and hi… https://t.co/oaqtcAnFvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $50 Roblox Gift Card Offer    Win $50 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/loPa7DeMwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love the way so many of the decor’s natural design elements flow within the landscape of the Versailles Gardens… https://t.co/vXrFkm7h14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah just asked me what food we ate in the 80s. Um, same thing pretty much. 🤣 As a child of the 80s I can testify… https://t.co/kp73hDqJDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaviDGoel @DrPhil Yes. We didn’t want to interrupt your dinner.  But you may have seen us peer out periodically th… https://t.co/8ewZ6JazTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaxReformExpert @RyanAFournier That poor specimen of a woman should mind her own business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m soo tired at work. But all I wanna do is get off work, chug some pre workout and beat my own ass in the gym 😂😂... then go home and KO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imnotdevdev Dev, i appreciate tf out of you 💕 i want to say yes, but i need to be responsible if i want to make it… https://t.co/RUOYkAejuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ça serait fantastique de participer à une émission en France. J’envie souvent la profondeur de vos débats/discussio… https://t.co/3YX1Qmtoko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a hero for homeless animals and have fun doing it! Our golf outing is being held on April 8th at Cedarbrook Coun… https://t.co/RSxZn0OOvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Don’t need to watch anymore. Give them their own class they are neither one or the other sex!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateCasey @BravoTV @Andy Thanks so much! I missed it when looking at the mazel onesie a couple weeks ago.]]></document></documents></author>