<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sylvia_ritter FYI your Disco Dingo is being used with even proper credit and by-permission etc:  https://t.co/CsuPfZSJni]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night I won WWE's Tough Enough... . @RealKurtAngle congratulated me.. . I am blessed that I had the opportunity… https://t.co/MRGf6vPY1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's the over-under on Trump's Eight Paid-For Abortions?  I'll go over. Way over.  #Vegas #Bettingexpert… https://t.co/TAanB5JMvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveWestly How would you know people are not going to be hitting them intentionally?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an honor to celebrate with charli_shuler and @jaydshuler this past weekend! So excited for you two! ❤️ May G… https://t.co/4j6YZ4aegj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait for those summer nights when we can have bbqs at like 1 in the morning 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Album art is now working with the Media Player on IOS. Powered by my own machine learning database called MemBase. https://t.co/SFJ0IC9PFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a tough time trying to figure out how someone can proudly wave the flag of another country, but consider it… https://t.co/SsATusBjI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Class of 2019 on earning scholarships to attend Bethune Cookman University @ Booker T. Washington H… https://t.co/vl7Hy6EShU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know where #LexusOfLasVegas home of #JamesJohnsonSellsLexus is going to pop up in #LasVegas  . Good to se… https://t.co/1P5Tg5u9op]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YYZStefan It’s late February and this bullshit weather will not let up 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even to work yet but a bitch already feeling this nap imma take later🙌🏼‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chbmeredith @pwilliamsNHL That's 2 games worth for them haha  Solid evening all around.  League avg at 5552 now.… https://t.co/aTo6HlJIH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoy sharing my travels to Israel with my students at #UNT. From the great food to the criminal justice system.… https://t.co/jnT117JLV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es de princesas verte linda con maquillaje pero de reinas verte hermosa sin maquillaje 😍 #instaboy #instaboygay… https://t.co/QU0aICuO8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE if you could’ve been like any hardcore wrestler who would it be??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Skunk Works by @Launchbrewery at @launchbrewery — https://t.co/u9JciwtX20]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will remain CONFIDENT in this; I will see the GOODNESS of the LORD!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randymac81 Just for the actress who plays Mahershala Ali’s wife. 10!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again. Day 4 of testimony of @NCSBE evidentiary hearing for @MarkHarrisNC9 @McCreadyForNC #NC09 election… https://t.co/gVENRbX6iW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to give Omar a trip on the Allah Express straight back to Somalia and she can take her brother husban… https://t.co/4IjtY4drma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deer removals planned in Clearfield, Jefferson counties to combat disease https://t.co/cdxz7EMaSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day today was a great day to indulge in a little waldeinsamket.  #loneliness #peaceful #reflection @ Wynnefiel… https://t.co/HlVa1EdiwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeMorganHope @twicetheMF @bigkstone @steelyonsports @JessiStone @Just_JD38 @RJ_Young idk who all to tag just ple… https://t.co/6IJiOHbuAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Big Chest got what he wanted: He's a Raider, via pending trade when league year begins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harrisburg 74 Cedar Crest 71 despite 28 points from Logan Horn @LoganHorn033. Falcons will host Cumberland Valley i… https://t.co/8iXsQfzjBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is some pictures of my two favorite Girls in the world my amazing wife Priscilla and Daughter Angel I wake up… https://t.co/9nBDi8J9A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m biased because she’s the best but I’m sure anyone can see how perfectly @Sienna would be to the current #Raw roster]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are considering it, just do it. This is the best god damn player on the planet. Give him what he deserves or… https://t.co/3IuddVNqv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[But did you see the diamond @ladygaga was sporting? OMG #TheTiffanyDiamond #TheOscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Panzer AR-12 Shotgun from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $500! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/AiI9guOC7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[ayo @JoeBudden of the @JoeBuddenPod you guys gettin them @JussieSmollett @Therealkiss jokes off on todays pod is wh… https://t.co/DmtmCqX7l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvin_knapp @bfoxxie Saw him beat Bloomer at Portsmouth, OH in a Lucas Oil Race last summer. Great race at a bad… https://t.co/bDZRyGIGXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiev1969 @RoobNBCS @osoosoband I’ve never heard them. What do you recommend?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You should get you affairs in order. @SDNYnews  is coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished this custom piece for a former West Village resident. The weather wasn't ideal for an outdoor drawi… https://t.co/NqQDp9lomL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaMbINiT0 @EvelynVazquez51 @EndColonial1sm @denisselebron @cucusahernandez @maver23 @Tony51Martin @1Fashionisima… https://t.co/dpfWDI9PML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this ROLEX MEN'S SUBMARINER DATE 18K BLUE DIAL WATCH. for $23,919.99 on OfferUp https://t.co/UOtiQV3fYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karakillmer @AnnieIlonzeh @NBCChicagoFire Outstanding job on tonight’s episode, seat of the pants and loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @_parkermichelle vlog!! WALT DISNEY WORLD: fam vacay to Disney https://t.co/VI2jjA0MQd via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 We need answers to his involvement with the boy he paid off, using taxpayers money, regarding a sexual… https://t.co/MSGLVbtXY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drag this racist fools ass into the CPD tonight. He should be prosecuted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deaux6 @jimmyval11 @vfl_g @liamstokes5895 @bhogan9 @RondoHive @marchmadness Where did he say road and neutral games were equal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NOLA cutting off nose to spite their face... AD plays the 4th qtr and the #Lakers lose this game.  Thanks… https://t.co/UuZpNpvm15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Once again @MeghanMcCain doesn’t chime in on topics of blatant racism! What’s the problem Meg?!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeBagley Bags NEWMAN Only 4 points out of chase right now STILL GOT A CHANCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress can reverse it by simple majority vote. I note that the National Emergencies Act does not cite the provisi… https://t.co/N6FkumxVYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NjPhillyFan no bc comparing someone who’s 18 to someone who is 22 and been in the league 3 years already makes a d… https://t.co/gMzZdQgik8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ian Connor like the Kanye of clothing.. He put on T Rex Global cause all of the sudden everyone on that now]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tributes will pile so high, only one worthy of such praise will be able to see them in their entirety. Join us… https://t.co/yJD03vsxZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnRobertsKC I don’t hate Jack but I’m definitely not the huge homer for Jack that you are.  That’s what makes i… https://t.co/s8LkHsqHPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice video and agree with you 100%. Stupid is stupid does. Will it ever end?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I predict the FIRST sunny 60+ degree day there will be a record amount of sick calls, I’ll be one of them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to receive an offer from Huntingdon College! #gohawks https://t.co/5O6KcZU9fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shop yours shopwander.lust !!   #travel #ecomer #passportcover #motivationalquotes @ Facebook HQ https://t.co/lOZ3Fnkkgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHH01NJ @njdotcom Funny how these Left looney ppl just recycle the same story on rotation. Next up, two scoops of Ice cream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that it’s got nearly 400 samples to mess with, @dropmixgame is never gonna get old. Give me the ability to shuf… https://t.co/H38YMpzMnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mon_ique @oxlamb @omdohmydog1 @PGadoury @CTSNOWman1 @ParisParamus @_CTWeather @SnowballManny @John_Jamason… https://t.co/Cf8fK4XKSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdaholic3 Don't worry. I bet he ends up doing less than 2 including the time he's already served.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know to be anti fast food burger man, I still fall prey to legendary grease pits... it’s the onion rings. 😏😎🍔🌭🥓 @ T… https://t.co/GnnshwClQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NOLAwhiteboi Feels like you wanna make that ass clap as your getting fucked hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you see my forecast on @KHQA News at 10pm it will have you doing this. #ILwx #MOwx #IAwx https://t.co/AXSR1ttFRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @NBCNews Good thing @NBCNews is fake news, and the real enemy of the people. Oh wait, that was yesterday. #SAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple is hiding the “manage subscriptions” taskbar the way I didn’t bring up my mom’s spare change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is with tennis shoes on that have grip.... do not get out today unless it is ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY... PLEASE. 😬… https://t.co/Y3aiI5Xhcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#life #positivity #positivevibes #positivethinking #positivethinking #motivation #motivationalquotes @ New York, Ne… https://t.co/8oUJM1D9Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkGess (cont) I think most people just forget and don't take that into account, and/or far too many that just do… https://t.co/9OA1SkIZYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiriusXMFC 1985 I was in Auckland  NZ and I woke up at 3am to watch the FA cup final and Man U won on a brilliant Norman Whiteside goal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew_Callari I’ll never forget it. Still get chills everytime I watch the highlights]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, it’s actually listed as the “Safari Parka Raw”, whatever that means. A rose by any other name and all that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreamasenda I preferred Dirk blowing off Lebron after his 3 streak 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianFoster Everyone feels they’re entitled when they walk into retail]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Tagliareni and Katy Temple speaking on New Jersey’s New Voices Bills that protect student journalists and advi… https://t.co/OkDtlT69kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, when he has her locked up, and he finds out that she can't unfreeze Arendelle, he is told that if anything hap… https://t.co/WoBvj9YTke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out a copy of Poe's The Pit and the Pendulum multiple times as a 3rd grader, until a librarian stopped me… https://t.co/uuPE10OwQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[to morons on Fox News that just want to spread his lies and conspiracy theories. Hannity, Tucker, Dobbs and others… https://t.co/EizGmuBOmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’ve taken the deep dive into my #sourdough hobby, our kitchen just smells like dough at all times. This is not a complaint!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most unrealistic thing about Aquaman, is when he pushes a submarine to the surface from a couple thousand meter… https://t.co/ytS25rUkYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so cold in Chicago every time I go outside my boobies wanna fall off 🌨🌨🌨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use being busy and hyperfocused to ignore my psychological problems. When I’m not busy I start regressing into ba… https://t.co/qbsszRQTSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monte Vista CA Sun Feb 24th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Mostly Cloudy Lo 41 MONDAY Chance Of Rain Hi 61]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump We demand a president I'm our White House and not a 8 year old brat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdcoley3 Lmao was it someone from Houston? Apparently what I'm reading some shit went down with Scott Foster]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind every great Data Scientist who’s delivering productive output is a solid set of Data Engineers bringing thin… https://t.co/ritUSjPwCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so messed up it’s crazy. No one will ever get what I truly want and need in life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 86,400 seconds in a day. How will you use them?   So many of us get seduced by busyness into thinking tha… https://t.co/wyPwyMKskM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEastres @Tiff_FitzHenry @thedilleyshow And #rKelly going down the same day https://t.co/boCFplgBHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy and relaxed I am seeing Georgetown Hoyas getting the win in their last home game at double OT even though… https://t.co/wolaM5kiIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @iheartmindy Democrats pray on the weak. They have no idea what to do when someone fights back espec… https://t.co/KpKpI3yeqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am becoming more convinced that the extreme crazy liberals today are just a ploy to make the more “moderate” libe… https://t.co/t1si7jLtqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadLife88 @Rory_Spencer You asked how hard it would be and I gave you the answer. It’s why you don’t see it happen… https://t.co/ajo0W1ZjJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soundofmaddie MR JOHNSON I GOT THE SECURITY DEPOSIT ITS LOCKED IN A BOX AT THE BOTTOM OF MY CLOSET   -me every morning for no real reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say about 5/4ths of people struggle with fractions.  I’m in that group.  Kye can teach me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @GaetaSusan Well rumor has it that he only likes chocolate milk for his source of protein!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksbull @charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Would you let him grab your crotch… “They let you do it.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calimccammon No, and now she's drinking coffee. I'd she keeps this up, people are going to think she's in recovery!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoBomberZ1 @Sportsnet @reavo7five @JeffMarek @JasonYork 1/2 full of idiots, who moved here from other hockey marke… https://t.co/PuuQ2lRTaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Jackson pointing out Rondo sitting away from the players side of the bench like he doesn't do it every game bu… https://t.co/TnBtjw9Bg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a week of rainy weather finally getting back in my groove!!!! https://t.co/oX0rMPxOoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are appearing quite panicked. That is actually very sensible. And, uncharacteristic. Well, pri… https://t.co/rHnDqKkcfa]]></document></documents></author>