<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Saw this in one of my @lyft rides in NYC this morning. I’ll let you guess whether the driver was a woman or not. I… https://t.co/yk1ZtW180P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thing 1 is in middle school that doesn’t  do this anymore so we will only have 2,3 and 4 for a while till thing 5 g… https://t.co/3SnyZT5l1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve Irwin was my hero and he’s the reason I plan to work with exotic animals as my career. I miss his beautiful s… https://t.co/OKg5k19lms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nights_la deleted Twitter, Facebook, and my Mail app and life has immediately gotten way better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spankingland When I first started in Bdsm cupcake was basically my idol. I stalked her so much on Twitter until I… https://t.co/zIcsJMTkJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunny Sunday perfect to stop by 4 Evergreen, Cabot  OPEN HOUSE 2:00-4:00 March 10. #dougwilkinsonrealty… https://t.co/or6nKbznQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @dawsonabner7 @artist180 @doutingthomas4 @Grams17anon @Missy4Trump2020 @HazilEye @Toddscrypto… https://t.co/RD50cw7JMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinch hitting for @BradTeague is the one &amp; only @matt_whiting! https://t.co/tNT1Fhw4Zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9Dasy @Mike_TheCop Once I got “But I just stole this purse so they’re not my drugs, right?” No -now u just caught 2 felonies....👜💉💊]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do girls have time to do their make up before work 5am too early to be doing all that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TOPFan394 He did stage his attack , he is a dangerous and prejudice person. He wasted many man hours of the police… https://t.co/wyYe0FYDWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Glenoak Boys Basketball Team  on there Win over Akron East! @GlenOakBBall @K1nd3l_R https://t.co/nAzeCCf8bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been going ham on my website all week. 😵 I keep making to-do lists as I think of better SEO or content, and it… https://t.co/2Axl9HF6wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere @verizon @ATT @comcast Very true!  Did you arrange for daylight savings time so we're wouldn't have to deal with them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[having to spend part of break in Cambridge was honestly the worst part, i really don’t miss that place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’d be lying if this picture of @WalkerGunner didn’t make you miss summer weather.. https://t.co/8gmCkfGrAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u are supposed to watch #IWD2019 campaigns but u join a party and meet the most amazing women!… https://t.co/z2uNXjXbTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Costuming doing me dirty in these black dress pants bc it’s either too tight in the thighs/too short OR swim in fab… https://t.co/q1wVILm6rt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealchrbrown @Ryan_AintLyin @TimTindallArt @COOCHIECOWBOY @AOC This is disgusting. They are using these people.… https://t.co/5mwMp33DNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michele_pickens @PalmerReport She said no matter what Mueller or the Committee hearings produce, she will not allo… https://t.co/tT8WBYAF53]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg helpppppppp I have a SQUIRREL in my house ! SOMEONE COME GET THIS I CANT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smileymegs1 Gosh I know it but it’s sooo irritating having a stupid # in my brain!! I need to frisbee my scale out the window 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @McConaughey, UT Mens Basketball's biggest supporter, for showing up to the game last night!… https://t.co/IDdI5ha3DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMoone78 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse How many times we got to tell you the change in NAFTA and trad… https://t.co/nNJ7yTqges]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched it 1000 times and it keeps getting FUNNIER 😂 also, I could totally see Nate doing this to Keenan lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[the universe is infinite and yet my body fails me on a daily basis in the very easy task of making serotonin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoMartelle @stradlemonkey @Brooksidefilms @Mark_Lapping @Biggybadass @KITTKARR83 @dfeague @elecporcupine… https://t.co/qPqx3nART4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabbyMitchell @EmesArmy That is exactly Grace’s point. Many people don’t. They are helping a loved one, without th… https://t.co/kRX5DmnE25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasaDCastilloTX Me, too but that sangria swirl margarita of yall's next to it, tops a big beer EVERY time👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[lena dunham, debby ryan, and melania trump are all tauruses so i think that means the whole sign is cancelled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monstershockey Tip a Monster event was last night and so much fun! Thank you to all the Monsters who had to endure… https://t.co/iskmVPKXkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKBenham @skjask @IlhanMN @lsarsour @marclamonthill Setting aside the fact that the Hashemites are an imported dic… https://t.co/nAp6Zx0LW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Micati Haha! We’ll see! 🤷🏻‍♀️ I’ve pretty much exaggerated though for dramatic(comedic?)effect. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just tripped and hit my nose on the wall ..  it's now gushing blood ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHDems Support President Trump and build the WALL protect the American people who voted for you and pay your salary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Static space lover by foster the people hits different than any of their other songs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princessresse07 @CourtneeHendrix I’ll never go back to sew ins im sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanRGallagher @FrankIero Omg your adorable but at the same time I 100% understand lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great question @glouie00  let’s try job shadowing, internship across areas, and supervisors sharing their superviso… https://t.co/bK0bNLlFlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallyRedsox @LeeHunter72 @JohnWDean @LannyDavis I wish I could watch it!  Work gets in the way of all the fun! https://t.co/VG4dyzSWtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Gov. @GregAbbott_TX. Mr. South Texas 2019! #sd24 #txlege #86thLegislature https://t.co/zNc083OObR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JScottRasmussen NO! I love Columbus because it’s awesome! I don’t know WHY it’s awesome...it just IS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aldrpeg4 @realDonaldTrump @SenateGOP @HouseDemocrats @ALHouseGOP @ALHouseDems @PressSec leave the ISiS lover where… https://t.co/oQAlx3cttw]]></document><document><![CDATA[dude why tf would jordyn woods KNOWINGLY get involved w tristen? you can’t tell me she had no idea khloe and him we… https://t.co/GjJKIttKmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Digital Marketing on a Shoestring Budget workshop by @camptechco at venturenorthptbo hosted by @ptboecdev… https://t.co/KQZN7YYE72]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s freaking crazy!! I LOVE IT!!! And Blake Lively to go along with it, even more!! LOL!! 😂😆😝 @blakelively… https://t.co/XEcBntpNka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeaMichelle1982 I’m going to the pinball tournament again on March 9 in Chicago to see @TellEmSteveDave @BQQuinn !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congressman Gratz should be charged with witnesses tampering.This has special meaning for me.I taught spec educatio… https://t.co/7MkOOKUFLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorenamexicano Yo la semana pasada use un kimono que pidió mi hermana y la verdad me encantó... ya empezare a comprar 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver just wished me luck trying to find myself and finding a career. Five stars for the free therapy session.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommajessiec If you eat cake before 9 am it has no calories. It’s SCIENCE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump Me too😢 amazing we could go from such class to such trash😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh it looks like someone has discovered some real dirt on .@amyklobuchar 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Benito 11yrs old not thriving in scary shelter. Desperately needs rescue foster or dies 3/11. Give this senior a ch… https://t.co/tPvJFAsS7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotivationMonday ... Face your fears, but always with a little help from your friends. ⚫️🔴 #robioUS #oneccps @ Rob… https://t.co/ni3PYWt6tP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janelle_Isanan @alex14999 @LopesBarstool Tbh I didn’t see the free condoms so now it makes more sense lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@novapetty20 reminds me of dad getting mad about us buying new makeup 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCREDSKINS @rikincanton @L_Mac42 @king06cobra @ECU_ALUM @Chrispack1976 @gcupcakes4 @ecs26 @STX21 @touchet_troy… https://t.co/PS9U7rnUlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiatolentino Same same saaaaame. I bought two plants last weekend and now I'm like...do I need...more plants?  I need more plants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We conquer our giants when we look at them in the light of God. https://t.co/ce41jQDGn0 via @GregLaurie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cons: - Just realized I slept through my alarms for my 9:00 am  Pros: - now might as well sleep for 20 more minutes https://t.co/6FGucPSmIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read this. Think about how much “grit” we have (and still use) to survive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Medicare? Social Security? Snap? Tuition assistance?  EPA? All of which you want to cut and continue to… https://t.co/n4PQr7VreO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does all the toxic people I let go of, all of a sudden want to come back into my life.?   It definitely has to be a test, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a terrific Tuesday! Everything happens for a ‘Riesling’ 🍷 @galenglenwine https://t.co/ZzryDD7zr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter always gets my early announcements. Voices drops on March 29th!!!! #newmusic #voices #vibeoutandfallinlove… https://t.co/Z4KqFCWsQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dumbass lady decided to cross OVER a barrier to get a picture of the jaguar. SHE CROSSED A BARRIER THAT SHOULD… https://t.co/6TZexBHxQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[In business, you don’t want people to vote on your popularity. You want people to weigh your integrity and the valu… https://t.co/hsWZ8kAdcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@va_nessa92 @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 @andherestoourr1 @GetawaySwiftly_ @superswiftfan89 @stringoflites13… https://t.co/s59lUcOyNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey toad man...looking in a mirror at your behavior is a good thing. The real problem is that...YO… https://t.co/RmI5APAzr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[barely slept last night &amp; I could still be sleeping rn, idk why I’m awake rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surgeon_General Spiderverse is fantastic! The animation and story are excellent and it has an awesome soundtrack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_huntswoman I will sing it to you in person, I can't promise it will sound good, but I do promise 🎶 emotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it actually fails most of the time for me @GimmeBuilds!! It definitely spells the words correctly, but it s… https://t.co/MEVWdVA77o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for it! After it’s asked then when #Trump starts talking I can watch the color slowly drain from the f… https://t.co/Wb1NP9KVIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueThotz @ToutouleNtoya @ValeriaBrownEdu @EdPsychMama @gyazo @edtechsteveh Sorry I don't think you got that sugges… https://t.co/ktmxLmS7WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre orgullosa de nuestra Peña y del amor por nuestro equipo. Nos vemos el sábado! #HalaMadrid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the nuts and bolts of @robwdavis’s 18-month investigation #pollutedbymoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworkers really be requesting days off months in advance just to be declined and I come in and ask for days off… https://t.co/hg01BeduEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of all the hw I have to do and decided to go out day drinking instead lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonMillerinDC And when they get here in a “temporary” status, they won’t leave when Maduro steps aside (IF he ev… https://t.co/AyYA2mFDjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am childishly excited to see my first float parades of the season. Hail Oshun &amp; Cleopatra! Have a great ride! Throw us lots!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#naturephotography #outsidephotography #photographer #photography @ Pryor, Oklahoma https://t.co/9Cibn66qom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BklynActiveMama Hell yes to supportive husbands. On another note, who is giving you crap? The blog world is ruthless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[craving some almost burnt tortillas on a plate w frijol and chorizo handed to me by my dad while I chill on the cou… https://t.co/R9Aj2gn7Hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Restaurant Hourly Team Member - https://t.co/rVkp8KQenM #Restaurant #Cullman, AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope--got a bill for considerably more than that!  Last year I got a substantial refund! Getting close to same from… https://t.co/DQN7F7oDaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickVrusso @winterplacewv @WintergreenVA @massresort I'm not a skier but my father in law was and up north they wo… https://t.co/U7STiV2eQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we are in LOVE with this city. Chicago we are enjoying all of you. Tenisyn has ZERO fear. https://t.co/mt6MK8ev1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started watching Danny Phantom and I forgot to go to sleep oops 🤷‍♀️👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertC05664739 @blakeshelton @LaurenDuski She was one of the first to play in Oklahoma at ole red]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sent urgent prayer bulletin. If you get my emails go open it.  Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday!! God will carry you through every storm and give you the strength to make it!!! AMEN 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bio advice needed....Anitra has it. Thanks to @themomonthemove for the worksheets and help in creating compelling bios. #FlockPresents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another rainy weekend in Brooklyn.☔ #rainraingoaway #viewfrommywindow #brooklynviews @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/o7bSdVkOiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be at #seya3019 @mtsu @WestEndPTSO @MNPSLibraries @westendmiddle https://t.co/DUmuNLREFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY FINISHED FILMING THE LAST SEASON OF OITNB AND I HAVE SO MANY EMOTIONS RN 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have to reschedule therapy because you got anxiety from making the decision to cancel it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dammit @SykesCharlie before this is all over you are going to make me a fan aren't you? https://t.co/bOeFJooThZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you weren't able to experience the Blizzard of'77 first hand, you have no idea how long and draining it was.]]></document></documents></author>