<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Last 3 days I have literally been team no sleep #beingadad #sickkid #exhausted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my co worker is having a debate pls LMK 😭‼️ https://t.co/1CU6l5NeYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fl_cracker94 I heard the story from shannon lol   and i didnt say she was drunk, i said you were TRYING to get her… https://t.co/TekJtAviDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill We the people of the U.S. have that in u as our POTUS NOTHING.I know u damn well know very little that's a… https://t.co/eD7DlmZFTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂💀 This just completed my week with having a nickname like "The Bandit" I don't blame @AdamProject243 for putting m… https://t.co/wPF2q1S0fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Chatman09 @DeanBuchan @KyleSnipes @mattfinniganco @ChrisMCameron @GCIGreg Omg ted valentine is the worst! No… https://t.co/YRTT2VXqc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDanCrenshaw Thank you Dan. No one seems to be addressing the disenfranchisement of American citizen votes.. this is outrageous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still selling my organs so I can fly home and meet @CupcakKe_rapper in Moncton next month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleSturino I never said he didn’t have a right to leave. Both sides can be right in this case, as long as JT… https://t.co/dnz95tAEyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tullyspucks Section 209 Row F Seats 7-10 ... Give these girls a puck to keep them off their phones! @SyracuseCrunch https://t.co/0dElPEj2xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wRaldri @wrangler3chevy I "think" just the fire truck, but it was one of the few Richmond races I missed over a pe… https://t.co/tNzgHvobVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @PoliceNG @inecnigeria and DSS should pick this @Iam_Dr_RAS guy up,I warned @inecnigeria that Chima Amadi had p… https://t.co/muEBzzJgTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Romi_Rain WOW! What the fuck was he thinking? Well probably a stupid idiot. But he got what he deserved. Hope you got him good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BW_Jones @JBarnesRTR The NCAA Tournament every year is not a reasonable goal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @AOC @IlhanMN Yeah you both are racist as hell fucking clowns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand All you pro abortionist I dont care if you get an abortion but get health care insurance it most lik… https://t.co/GFCwTVsqw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[gang gang, can we make it to the gym 5 times this week or nah? 4 in a row so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NARANJERO75 @cynthiagarama @lopezobrador_ @HermesDCenicero @libera_radio @Darbelom @GermanPalafoxM @jjduartebravo… https://t.co/dnZJY1zvSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JabaTrindade @hfernandes0 @DressaDoSantos @BonoroV @_molinaustra Ai ele votaria no lula.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandane Lol it's okay you didnt but I appreciate you making sure I feel the love! You know me! With the green and… https://t.co/33fwbCiQvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#good morning everyone. thank you LORD for another day of life.RT.AMEN! https://t.co/kSwkPXbWD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AOC speaks of #citizenship. Its important. Obligations and rights. This is so much more valuable than the exh… https://t.co/gAn9BIDTLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peta messed with the wrong guy!  On Steve Irwin's BD donate to  @wildwarriors Est. 2002 by Steve and Terri Irwin a… https://t.co/KVaHAkUn8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all rest days are created equal. Had a great day of skiing at elkmountainpa yesterday and got to test out the b… https://t.co/wjv1TyJOFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dodgers @kenleyjansen74 @HyunJinRyu99 @russellmartin55 Welcome back baseball ⚾️, the best game on the planet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_SummerMan Still Brazy and ANTI are two of the best albums of the decade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE When I think of classic cage matches him vs. Hogan is still near top of the list. RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StohlerRacing @NfldPark Lmao .... try Victoria Swan... who even runs this account 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what makes me proud to be a part of the Grand Valley Ag Society,  its not about me and you its about the ki… https://t.co/2ZjLXnCkl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellringerwins @GulfstreamPark @thepressboxlts I’m actually in the “good” part of my “good/bad” handicapping cycle!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest reason why I’ve had good success at Plo8 tours is that unless I have 14 outs or more it’s more importan… https://t.co/VGrh53wh2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thunderstorms, snow, mist, freezing rain and lightning. Welcome home Tim, signed Mother Nature.  P.S. I switched to… https://t.co/9TKQrUDtpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Diseases This Degenerate 🔥👿Waiting You Billy                                            @ThomasPKennedy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ummanas_zaman @Alacoque6 @Myira_Khan @BeaumontElaine @Shrink_at_Large @ActAuntie Coming in contact with that stuff… https://t.co/0p0S8CUu4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @politicususa And it didn't burst into flame's... 😈 can do this now....  Can we say "worshipping False Gods"]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MichaelCohen your apology to your family was heart wrenching and very heart felt! Thank you for your truth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex Very likely he just committed a federal felony (witness tampering) since there is no precedence that tweets a… https://t.co/H7lAgG02aJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just realize how lucky you are and how much you love someone that you just start jumping around and screaming in a parking lot????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter is still here. #J560 (@ Kalamazoo and Burton in Grand Rapids, MI) https://t.co/vf2NBqFEyo https://t.co/vWQhjXdtZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarStecker @MTV awesome Sky, i'm so proud of you. you really are going up up up, can you #Blame me for wanting… https://t.co/kpU1tmvRWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Wynnewood North Neighborhood in Dallas, TX https://t.co/RG17aFlwdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jj051301 O Mary, I love you. Thank you for also being my mother. Pray for me, O holy Mother God, that I may become… https://t.co/RSP6dZfzKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why i have not one, not two, but THREE different pictures of me dabbing on my instagram in 2016?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sundaymotivation I am actually looking forward to the Oscars tonight. Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper should be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LOUD_besos Yeah i seen a few people talking about it the other day it sounded bad lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Romans58 @cigar_hoe They are scared to death about Roe vs Wade and now they are pushing the women to a massive division.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @Jim_Jordan @chucktodd Not like we have any evidence of Republican/Trump/Pence collusion with the Rus… https://t.co/MlRjkTdtUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ @iamjohnoliver I have been to some pretty cool places like Thailand, British Columbia, France and Scotlan… https://t.co/muN9EbWJL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Union break.. #theatre @ Maple Valley Jr/Sr High School https://t.co/cIW7x2SYxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que hace la bandera de Chile en #UmbrellaAcademy ? La o el tramoya es de Chile o creen que tenemos buenos boxeadore… https://t.co/yx7VlczH1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im about to go to sleep without an alarm set for the first time in a very long time. https://t.co/NRuKZMrgsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice job @NBA vince carter talking all game.. blake gets tossed.. Fixed ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Young people want Creepy Uncle Joe far away from them....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Howe Yep. We can’t help you guys play in the weak side of the conference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He and the Republican Congress passed a tax cut for the ultra-wealthy that added $2 trillion to the national debt.… https://t.co/OLjeWiBsZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDeniseGray1 @NoDelusionsHere @menamac @Reuters The idea of secret gitmo trials for Americans is insane.China does… https://t.co/ijB39EWWnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justthetipky @UKCoachStoops Right?? Multiple schools had more than 1 card. If they needed help with ideas all they… https://t.co/XO4HL4ckEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomasg_grizzle @DeFrancesco_A @GrahamsGains @jiggypuff420 @WolfOfWeedST @Grit_Capital CAPITAL 10X 🚀🚀🚀 10 BAGGERS 💰💰💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how @mophie sends a discount code, but then you can’t use the code on something you need. Brilliant 👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love everything about this except for the fact that Nickelback was not a band of the 90's???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nombre andan criticando a Rayados y quieren poner a Daniel Lajud de centro delantero jajaja, larguense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh @danicamckellar can you figure out this math problem I bet you can hope you respond @ Readington, New Jersey https://t.co/4xi9ZOIvHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky State Route 8 faces a catch-22: Too dangerous to drive, too remote to fix https://t.co/L4RU6dwKd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPippus @psaball15 Except I have SMU ahead of Rye (avoid OUA matchup in semi and reward a 1 loss conference champi… https://t.co/JFGo08FucY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsteroidPhilS @scottEweinberg @80sAllOver I did this recently! Once they're done with 1984 I'll relisten to those and add to the list too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy I got to watch the Daytona 500 on a plane 5 miles above the ground. #technology #daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[AGAIN!!! AGAIN A DEFENDER SLIDES UNDER HOWARD AFTER HE'S IN THE AIR!!! WHAT THE HOLY HELL?!?!? @BIGEASTMBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcbittick @DanCrenshawTX And it would show that the diplomats had secured the agreements before the principals met. Saves time, saves face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At approximately 9:15 this morning fire broke out on Bergen Street between buffalo and Ralph Avenue photo show the… https://t.co/VtQ5jEkQ8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow I have achieved degrees on 3 continents, but I have NEVER been exposed to such racism as I saw in a local p… https://t.co/aWUr9gQP0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southampton cannot win this game. Relegation for Fulham is inevitable, but still. I can’t help but think of the possibilities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not all that bitter anymore personally, sympathy for his injury took most of that away. Just find it a hilariou… https://t.co/W7bsLd9R7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@defactosound My thought was something exploded and splattered everyone to death. haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Careful dear, that socialist waiter will be grinding pepper on your food next.Given rental costs in Norcal,You do r… https://t.co/oQSBkNHeuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll take care of that Florida stalker for you beautiful. I'd protect you with my life. I know Joe's holding you do… https://t.co/DRqygtzW93]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know. America is much better than the UK. At least we are diverse enough to have ISIS voices high in our governem… https://t.co/reE73VRVZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanickedWaddle Saw that earlier. Me too man, looks like actual footage from that Portland game 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dlstoke Tulsi Gabbard isn’t even a serious candidate though, tbh. I feel like Warren is regionally popular, Gillib… https://t.co/jH6JbdX8eV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm thinking about having children to up my Twitter brand. Nothing seems to get liked and RTs like adorable quotes… https://t.co/p03TGO4jHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant trust a you if your a grown ass man still asking for chicken nuggets at fast food spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥇 TONIGHTS SALES! 🥇 RARE COLLECTIBLES! #EBAY STORE LINK IN BIO ⬆️  #TwinLakesSilverFrontier #silver #gold #coins… https://t.co/T9fPau0Lvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enabling = The removing of consequences that could be the catalyst for someone with substance use disorder to want… https://t.co/pWPuvtV6AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd Annual Virginia Drug Tested State Championship will be held at Tysons Playground on July 13, 2019.⠀⠀⠀⠀ Open to… https://t.co/sCuwfrQxF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost She’s also raising her children “genderless”. This obviously not a sane person]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was bibbidi bobbidi beautiful night celebrating @AKIRAchicago @ Beauty Bar Chicago https://t.co/no2mUasgzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We still fondly remember @GadiNBC from his time in New Mexico. But our loss is the rest of the country’s gain! To f… https://t.co/3VjCiYGgCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had self control when it comes to food my body would be looking so good 😭😩 but idk what that is. I can go to t… https://t.co/aKZb5ANoLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pink_lady56 @realDonaldTrump I'm Following You because You are one of the 200 #MAGA #WWG1WGA https://t.co/xUT1sH6Bai]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MySithName  Darth Kreager (Left) and Darth McCall. Two good friends on the Dark Side of the Force.   #Sith… https://t.co/H3CSfQy2ib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pferrada1 a continued mentor and friend. Tremendous team put together the @gsurgstudents global surgery meeting wi… https://t.co/1qx5jbTTVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We figured out who the characters were, what they wanted, what they needed, what was in their way and how you build… https://t.co/lzEbf3noor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrangeGrove55 Since 1955... "Man and the Moon" TV program (Tomorrowland) Davy Crockett TV Show (Frontierland) True… https://t.co/sv7HHkhIJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Saturday, I plan to be near the mats to catch some Division II sectional wrestling at @STVMAthletics. I will get… https://t.co/qbzjfePBO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congress moves to act on gun control amid partisan debate about background checks https://t.co/QY4G1h00IW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless we're talking #7DeadlySins, #Aggrestsuko, or #Aico  #anime #Netflix 📺📽🎞 https://t.co/TxhUTr0xVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Unfortunately it is true. But I live in the south and I see it all the time. But thankfully they are seriously outnumbered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #SundayMorning be sure to follow great people like @cindymillergolf @allenmillergolf @caddyforacure… https://t.co/aPTrINbXsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StegNCheese Price is high, yes. Market value calculations are done by Spotrac not me. I think he has potential to… https://t.co/GfOKBwR2PG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewRangel44 “ give us the cowboys!!” Anytime y’all win something head ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the year was #1975 We were at #delaneystreetbaptistchurch #orlando #florida We were at our first… https://t.co/V7cXrJW7Eu]]></document></documents></author>