<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MavericAtlanta @ParliamentAug @ParkerAllenXXX @Tigger_ReddXXX @JakeMorganXXX @atlas_grantxxx @DiceInPDXXX https://t.co/yLOauAPBzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey @Niki20181 @benshapiro is a spoiled rich kid who has made a living.playing the dual victimization card..he… https://t.co/YMGpvOXlCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @mikethemiz @shanemcmahon @WWEUsos Guess you can get a DUI and then still win championships]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @sheehan32 at Quarterdeck back to back days get this man a punch card or some BOGO offers. #PokeBowl #PhillySteak 🍴 🥤 🥘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at “Base Camp” with @clarkwendlandt for last couple days, looking forward to seeing the Granddaddy store and c… https://t.co/IdVtyhDPNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can move the famous viral dead shark to her final resting place but we can't help a beautifully ALIVE soul who n… https://t.co/zRqIdDoQeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poponjer @MikeSirois CBB was great this season. Not sure Ricky would’ve beaten any of the other final 4 in a vote,… https://t.co/KP6cCtAfsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our latest Key Hourly Development Graduates Ruben, Jakob, Adriana, Graham, Wayne and Rita.… https://t.co/IDQFwxo2FT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the Steelers should.... uhhh... retire Ben, sign Foles, and keep AB... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw 5 people on snap that had @ChipotleTweets last night and now I’m in desperate need of it. 🌯🥙 @lovealissaellen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@transitapp How is it that you @stminfo realtime data for the 66 north at 5:13 has shown 4 minutes to arrival for t… https://t.co/p11EStvjGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaeDowns @MassDOT @MBTA Andreae great news - look closely at #RailVision Alternate #4, it includes the possibi… https://t.co/QgrVORGgQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty good Wednesday night ... if you can’t be here in Vegas make sure to tune in watchdirtvision @ The Dirt Track https://t.co/YgQYKwbo8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Bryan, I know we can count on you vote for Maaliya this year and hopefully  Morgan DeFoor next year, lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DoliaEstevez you ever did a follow up on this very interesting article: Will  Carlos Slim Be Allowed To Compete A… https://t.co/IVwLISGcPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmommi @PressSec @POTUS Denying people the right to serve, who can do the job, is bigotry. Do we deny people with… https://t.co/iQrb8JqsZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally some sunshine for these two!!! ☀️🐾 @ Elmira, New York https://t.co/efIkD9REIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doth not all nature around me praise God? If I were silent, I should be an exception to the universe. - C.H. Spurgeon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats more divided than republicans. Going so far left that they will fall off the earth. No chance of them winning the presidency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelidaLopezc @lopezobrador_ Que infantil sra presidenta, déjese de tonterías y romanticismo y mande arreglar las c… https://t.co/WZmwYSHWEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnapCreative You can only make a decision based on the information you have available. Things like weather patter… https://t.co/q05SYCnqWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I almost slipped and died trying to get water cause the bottom of my feet were sweating; fuck this swapass stat… https://t.co/zvK3lGFna3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill My guess is 100% of people who wants socialism has only read about it non really experience it The real… https://t.co/3SV3r9DDHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE SAID 👏 UNTIL SHE'S 6 👏 FEET 👏 DEEP 👏 SHE'S 👏 GOOD 👏  #CONVICTION #DRIVE #PURPOSE #IMWITHHER #ALLCAPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mila now conflating the Smollett case with a defense of Kavanaugh. Sheesh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachcecil7721 San Francisco has a much better resume and i doubt they get in. Wofford might even struggle at large.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethanhein I look at these criticisms and I think they are perfectly valid. The problem is in looking at it as a ‘c… https://t.co/Sk3YDHZyCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @MikeLevinCA this teacher from Indiana appreciates you defending our profession. Chances are most people hav… https://t.co/Ok2IVw2ESA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein was a pimp who offered teenaged girls to wealthy and powerful men from his Florida estate. He maint… https://t.co/uTkDNmzRZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briteeye777 broadcast the list of 54 enemies within Senators. Tag the evil bastards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafasolanoperez @FelipeCalderon Q pendejo eres. Nomas quieren robar más. Y ya tienen experiencia, pues ya robó 6 años. Cuidado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alphaxblood are you wondering what was in the bag? it was a piece of banana bread]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 Report the teacher to the authorities,  talk to local media! Let us know if we can do anything.  #RightToVote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roccopalmo What happens when the Metropolitan is the problem? #PBC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coltin_Reed @959theranch @music_terrell That was a few hours ago. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke doesn’t think tonight is a must win game. “If we lose, we lose.”   What?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep @3wombats Relax kick back put your feet up and watch the show there are more petifile dentist then… https://t.co/Lx6MWwBFud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grymm_cheshire Hell yeah- you can replace any meat on any food item! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andelawson @Britpoptarts @MsMollyRachael Except anthromorphization of animals has been going on since the talking… https://t.co/0HvP58Lzv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @senatemajldr @RandPaul I know this is sarcasm so here’s a little more for you. GOOD!  That’s a new… https://t.co/rP7LNyv52O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#acoustic at @KensingtonPubPA 5pm-8pm, start your weekend with us. #livemusic #philly #weekend #FridayFeeling… https://t.co/8EClgWelqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld Just heard Sharpton (godfather of racist hoaxes) say that IF smollet is lying he should face consequen… https://t.co/hdgXQzRtWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 16 don't miss out on this high art explosion brought to you by FilthyGorgeous and FEVA. DJ's LB3, La… https://t.co/CGRU5mTFBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wait for this like Newman &amp; Kramer waited for those in season peaches 🍑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonilhouse @CFBEditSupreme2 You're right about him holding the ball too long. Idk about him being 230 tho? Most pa… https://t.co/TXaYHMEyuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildMnNstar ok i like it, n that would be something being dumba is out cause of the fight..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenía un buen de no sentir la sensación del agotamiento físico por ejercicio, sin duda alguna me gusta, al rato vie… https://t.co/8Nj410N8W8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_hummingbird @jeffm10000 @AOC Fuck her she cost us $27,000 here in New York City.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianlilley @JustinTrudeau Trudeau's Clitoral Rhetoric isn't different from the rest of his imbecilic narrative. J… https://t.co/KYW8wFM2wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoLoneRangerz @PhillyHotspur @espn @kylekuzma Stats don’t lie https://t.co/4JSHZQVaJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeGamaldi Corrupt PD. We need gun laws to strip HPD of their weapons. They're armed thugs. Blue Isis. Murderers.… https://t.co/X34bg9Kbnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseStarhawk @AFTVMedia Can't be offside from inside your own half....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeSharp Era mas facil un, "me equivoque" que andar mezclando tu desconocimiento de matematicas con el machismo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles Congrats on the new contract! Thank you for bringing it home for us in Superbowl 52. You will forever be… https://t.co/dsfdRwsDIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megoftheworld @blwarren @MY_Wiltshire @ElisaCardnell @offthekuff @RepDanCrenshaw Meg you don’t live in Texas. #MegoftheSwamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii PRAY FOR GOD TO BE WITH YOUR MOTHER YOU AND YOUR FAMILY AMEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Announcers just talked about not being able to figure out a weakness on LSU's team...as they try desperately to han… https://t.co/GxF1dptvLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akachela @WaltDisneyWorld @AdriSutes They did give me a discount on the hotel. I’ll ask and see what they can do. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch You should get a award for funniest parody account , keep up the funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillardNorthHS @Husker4274 Mike, congrats on your daughter making the state tourney! #thebank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniachocron así funciona la propagando política castro-comunista ... lo triste es que he escuchado entrevistas co… https://t.co/G2oSbWhd3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[News flash: Last month I took over the role of CEO of the @DupontUndergrnd, the community arts organization that ru… https://t.co/d17vf6Re16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puedes leer la nota @aurelio02 #southbeach #wine #fest #food #miamibeach @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/5MCzgiIBOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every wing joint’s ranch tastes different and regardless of how good the wings are, if the ranch trash then the who… https://t.co/4vMh6liJtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougMolitor Seems that the GOP could’ve used superdelegates in ‘16 to not lose control of their party like they di… https://t.co/YN6hR0MDO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[People drive like PUSSIES. With the exception of senior citizens, if you are going to drive like a complete PUSSY,… https://t.co/9ekvhQXRIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaoooo this fucking correctional officer told my boyfriend “ that’s your girlfriend? “man you have to be paying her” 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GadowskiWitold Szanowny Panie Witoldzie chcialbym prosic o kontakt w sprawie druku ksiazki o ltorej Panu wspominal… https://t.co/fMqAf0Mrz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieJoyce @tonyxrandall Amen. I need this statue for the SEO shrine where my "vast and extensive network of Twitt… https://t.co/ZCTwGieQFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BasedChasen I mean why would he lie. He thought Kepa was injured so he tried to sub him but he wasn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPPTCE @WattzzD @PatriotCanes @ScottRickhoff @oldairforcedude @jackhay86865097 @TOMRJZSR @DavidMFarr2 @VirgleFox… https://t.co/IRhmRipPu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoDen111 @seanhannity Because Buffet has already been taxed on the income he invested to make capital gains. The w… https://t.co/UDHWVOH2rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Single platforms warranting a dedicated PEO continues:  Navy Appoints Admiral to Oversee Columbia Sub Effort https://t.co/dTG4cJgZyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShellyCov @smalltownandrew @gatewaypundit Jussie Smollet’s legal team best retract their previous statement saying… https://t.co/NFmJ1tcBB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debilu2 @TIME Even The Washington Post Admits There’s A ‘Bona Fide Emergency’ At U.S. Border https://t.co/fHFf3eQcMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRedbeliever @BeckyLynchWWE I realize that. I’ve watched wrestling my whole life friend. It’s annoying as hell… https://t.co/3y2YlHqUK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerClark41 @NY1 Kids got a free day off from school. Did they need it? Parents, report from your nabes? I unders… https://t.co/uVX1HGNOp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Matt Gaetz, and Dan Bongino all took a selfie with a sex trafficker, and the media isn't talking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from Chief Lanzas @fc_gfd_1075 to post the cover of 7 professional books, no explanations… https://t.co/T2ZZYqU9qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen @AOC This sums up the millennial liberal perfectly..this is your brain on liberalism #MAGA… https://t.co/N4mgHUQdLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warriors! @ColtBelcher @RaneyNathanael @ryan_smih @devinjackson32 @BlanscettA https://t.co/rtSiqIGhdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[GroupMe gets me dude🤦🏻‍♀️ people don’t understand ANYTHING after you explain it to them five times on how to take a… https://t.co/PgYs2RtV8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dusitbookworm @NatGeo 25 billion possible planets in our galaxy and trillions of galaxies. Maybe someone nice will… https://t.co/qKWNGCRS5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falling                                                                                            For        You… https://t.co/0L8LmFBgR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamCarney @maxwellwise Yep...huge week...y’all continue to piss off teachers and educators and won’t keep tour han… https://t.co/6jpM1GTl98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocksWithSocks @collyntaylor @LivinNThePast I can’t argue with that. They’re like 1a and 1b for me. But there’s no… https://t.co/MskkRMoOEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a one issue voter, like many. My issue is how expensive #cheese is nowadays @KamalaHarris @SenSanders… https://t.co/KaxwBUylok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyItsMoog @emtothea Do not try this:  - at home - if you are not white]]></document><document><![CDATA[Co-hosting with stevenprawdzik on The Sports Project 94.9 FM now! @ W Y G R Radio-Business Office https://t.co/fpcpgF7nI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely heart wrenching.... the sad thing is the kids that did this are only gonna get a slap on the wrist. Also… https://t.co/vLMYZ97wMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:30.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesomeness Ride with Awesomeness people! Thank you gciocci and ericgell #zanescycles #getoutsidect #wahooligan… https://t.co/j6tSB2w7uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SOYCarlosMota De acuerdo con mi tocayo @G_Casillas , el riesgo alto es en caso de que se pierda el grado de invers… https://t.co/eZoSGBhs5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wadegarrett1527 Yeah.. The PAC -10 is a juggernaut this year#whatajoke😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton tweets approval of 'immigrants and women' line at the 2019 Oscars  https://t.co/Jd6WbiwFpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some positive steps forward at the planning department today ...toward a lot severance for new construction of semi… https://t.co/xBTVser9jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilllChabbb @NightlyPolitics @AndrewYangVFA @AndrewYangVFA #Yang2020 all the WAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swazikills @chlxeasea In my opinion, Rihanna loss her crown when she started dating that white guy😐! ...or is he Arab...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ijwmpabarn___ @ImonlyKaty Lmao this must happens every morning lol 😂they just sitting there like it’s normal lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y- what do you think now that you helped defeat aliens? C- we need weapons in space, and worm hole technology as we… https://t.co/eNn0mAey5z]]></document></documents></author>