<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Melindapre0902 Unfortunately no, hes living in the birthing area. Packed in like sardines. It's actually usually q… https://t.co/ObcOIaX6ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariannaDC3 @MahgdalenRose It's gonna love ya back forever on phones About fake news. Its in ya schools, not on th… https://t.co/1JxkWDOhsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jake_PSD @CinchGaming Because if not then me and you 3 minutes in the hells cell brother! https://t.co/rPeFdkZszp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat Hello sir!  I know you touched on this subject sometime ago but it would seem that YouTube is back at… https://t.co/DjEu8yOsdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollinsworthPFF you know about the #law...will you please help us understand how this can be permitted to happen w… https://t.co/pFliKDKgta]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really not trying to brag, but THIS SHOW IS TOTALLY AWESOME!! Get on over to @ob_playhouse for THE WEDDING SING… https://t.co/952RTEGKG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nikki , the people are freaking out about the far right of the 593's strength]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seantorresm @Ann_Saari @VMware @RawlCoria Thanks mate! We’ll do our best. #LeaderSummit2019 #VMUGAdventure #VMUGLeaderSummit2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerrDonCantrell @God_sgirl @RevenuConsultnt @realDonaldTrump @codeofvets @RealMAGASteve @Cruz_Crew125… https://t.co/Ofm8h9VDvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWCompton @TimRandall63 @ORWarEagles @DereckRush This guy is amazing.  Makes it look easy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[14: Suoermarket bagger, ISP call center (twice), college IT guy, 2 web agencies in Chicago, Apple Store, teaching a… https://t.co/udlBLna1N7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamdzurilla @Dodgers Yup.  If Bryce Harper has really, truly wanted to stay in Washington, he would’ve told Boras… https://t.co/SlfVfqRvxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This plan (the Traditional Plan) is not of God.” - Cheryl Jefferson Bell  #GC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maze_dreamz your clothes know they can't contain the sexiness of yours so they do the right thing and fall off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlatterDominic1 @jordigarciatv Tu dale pa'lante saca los trapitos al sol]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Thank You! Please continue your efforts to save our country. We are behind you all the way!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sickfadebones @DetroitRedWings This is fucking terrible. Nyquist was worth way more than that. Bye Gus 😓😓😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Computer science paper presented in 2013 charts the growth of #netnography and finds it directly related" to the "e… https://t.co/uIYMHA47OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UPS if no one is at the site of delivery to sign for a package, how quickly can it be picked up at a UPS location]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #JussieSmollettHoax not only hurts black people and gay people, it affects ALL victims of crimes going forward.… https://t.co/Lx1NNYaazr]]></document><document><![CDATA[ManU coulda jumped to 3rd.. now were in 5th.. 2pts behind Arsenal 3 behind Tottenham who dropped points geez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieSabotage is making me want my pashmina so bad right now. Their set is giving me heavy forest vibes and just… https://t.co/fEWiff8nC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[But without faith it is impossible to please him: for he that cometh to God must believe that he is,… https://t.co/ctGKkFMDey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QCHspencer Miles looks good. Lamb. Hard to say. Watching Rockets Celtics now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexis Smith in A Little Night Music. My dream musical would be in the past!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day, $10 for feet pics $20 for a lunch date (you pay) $30 for a dinner date (you pay), my Venmo is matthew-perry-62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaywonk @AOC How about is it possible? Or even, does it make any sense? NO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirk_84_eby No ones says that... 90% of the citizens of flint have clean water now and the rest of the lead pipes… https://t.co/5os5dtNFBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatoInstitute @eachus As @jordanbpeterson says, with ample evidence, "equality of choices does not result in equal… https://t.co/7q5kMU4y3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[#20min4amy #20min4bobby Dreaming of warmer weather... 🚴🏻‍♀️ always looking for donations to #endALS… https://t.co/h0sA4yf4ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Mayer needs to feature Gary Clark Jr. on the next album. 💯 @JohnMayer @GaryClarkJr https://t.co/DymOq8gOIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's really great that my parents went so hard on disappointment that I've become desensitized to disappointing peo… https://t.co/SCv3rtsA6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/O to @robtheoriginal for killing this 3D #jayz haircut... 🔥🔥 #orinigal #levelstothisshit #picasso #staycaked… https://t.co/VuhRJy7ui7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a writer reading this you already know Twitter is awesome. But maybe you’re a writer reading this who kno… https://t.co/LFcDA1EYWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm home! #HugeBigShot #IDoThings #Skeeter #Lucius #Daisydog @ Pahrump, Nevada https://t.co/ctgLrMZZ9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LOTMpodcast Movies then are currently out as a perk for subscribers but I doubt Disney is done with the vault for good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markpeterlee And thank you for seeding the digital convo. Need you on my forthcoming podcast to unpack RTR. Let’s DM for more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD NIGHT EVERYONE. MAY GOD BLESS &amp; KEEP EVERYONE SAFE IN JESUS NAME I PRAY. AMEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[High-sticking on Florida's 3rd line LW Dryden Hunt who has the name of an 80s movie villain  #NHLBruins #NHLPanthers #MetroBoston]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Crossmans on your home purchase. #AZVHV #ArizonaRealEstate #yourValleyProperty… https://t.co/lmjhT9iiT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help @realDonaldTrump Preserve Our #Sovereignty #BuildTheWall #MAGA https://t.co/Q25YAnRXET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pintandrew @Pabst_Beer_8 @oriolesrise @PhillyGrinder @scotyvonnendave @The_Shadow__68 @JennyMiller521… https://t.co/7RZ8UlkKib]]></document><document><![CDATA[To wrap up #ValentineDay here is an #earworm for all my friends: Joy Division, "Love Will Tear Us Apart".  https://t.co/2vGCbIyWMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely excited for everyone to@hear/see/read this story I’ve been working on. Stories like this are why I wanted… https://t.co/4nUorRu9Pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeyondMeat campaign stars investor and NBA star Kyrie Irving   He's one several athletes investing in the vegan br… https://t.co/ycTJOSTJBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianneLimaTV @wpri12 @RIHouseofReps Power went to your head, but not to your brain. Representative Lima needs to… https://t.co/xSsuHu5p0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Background - last night my @netflix streaming suddenly stopped working and I was unable to sign in via my 4K AppleT… https://t.co/x3B68OEWfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceron_leyva @martincvmed1 @JoseAMeadeK Más los míos. Meado es un corrupto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidneyDiongzon 😂 - the guessing game in the filmmaking world when it comes to this abbreviation cracks me up every… https://t.co/4oBBLv7jpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my last day @12News taking portraits of our staff. @Sony @SonyAlpha #sonyalpha #gmaster @GodoxPhoto #westcott… https://t.co/Eqp5FQmSqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliegrothman @TommyHicksGOP @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @GOP The turn coat republicans need to realize it’s… https://t.co/LJEk9GfwHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shrinking pop songs: The short story of streaming economics @qz obsession https://t.co/a3b6zE54V2]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Porque creen que nos importa”. Era terrible. Pero es que ha empezado a pasar lo contrario, que te miden. Creo que… https://t.co/TiEZ5CQpha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinichiello @ej_whyte Imo they just changed his jersey without him taking a picture in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019, day 67  3 new pages including a better version of a big reveal, big improvement imo. Getting to that point wh… https://t.co/8AukUTuQrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[No doubt. But in the end, an ugly GWG might have been a better fit for this contest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[keep voting for @CalleYPocheOffi for the #BritishLGBTAwards ! Here's a direct link to vote: 👉🏻… https://t.co/n5hz6pOo45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is good. @ Cooper Mountain - Aloha North, Beaverton, Oregon https://t.co/od7tBsfS2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm curious.  Were the “veiled threats” made against @Puglaas from males or a high majority of males in the Liberal… https://t.co/1gSre5S4bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When am I going to figure it out?! #figuringitout #TheProcess #youliveandyoulearn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, @Patriots...got any new Pats-themed Valentines memes for us today?  (Our significant others are eagerly awaiting them.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @DrTerriC for a great chat.  To the pre service teachers—go be the change.  To the rest of you, have a great… https://t.co/SUDu7XFDUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y le explicaba que mi terapeuta me dijo que para tener una vida plena, encontrarle el significado a la vida y ser f… https://t.co/VfpzhHdumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamoneHardy Oliver's tape doesn't match his athletic traits. He is a wow player. Many Wow! plays along with wow...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardRioc Jajajaja son como pinches 7 temporadas jajaja la de bb pues ya la había visto casi toda me faltaba 1 te… https://t.co/XGRVEpRYtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard this girl doubting herself in my Psych class about being a nurse. So I told her hush it and keep doing everything you can]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearts and fire custom design by jfjxnfa #jayfederjewelers #whosyourjeweler #hearts #fancydiamonds #saleevent… https://t.co/CwQM3gDP4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[some stupid hoe was on my ass for like a mile so I break checked her and she actually hit me lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 Oh yea let's take the advice of  an idiot who dont know there own sex.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyGold @eric_ulrich @errollouis Ulrich did the only thing he could to win the race: he consolidated the 20% of… https://t.co/KLFrD71EoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haters are going to hate on the @NHLCanes but it doesn’t matter #takewarning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe it or not....that's a big truck! Hahaha @ Kennewick, Washington https://t.co/VAE8XRVte3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A las 5:23 am hay 12 grados en @pnegras, 53 Fahrenheit en @CityEaglePassTx. Hoy se espera cielo parcialmente nublad… https://t.co/ZXTVwylSim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliusGoat I've repeatedly seen Europeans marvel at the US political "spectrum". Every time, they state that US De… https://t.co/XdkJqz8quW]]></document><document><![CDATA[YESSSSSSS GOING TO THE MAC CHAMPIONSHIP!!!!!!! #stormpride #letsgouv 🏀🏆⚡️💜💛💯‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC welcome to being a politician Sandy! What!?! You thought it was gonna be all rainbows and unicorns? Especially… https://t.co/sYxrh6FJFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at Pepper's uptown with lead guitarist Michael Garza of the group Bullet Ride and my nephew and br… https://t.co/qBOkAUlZ67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirllan28 @SancadillaNorte @HoustonDynamo Jajajaja 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 bien dicho]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:32.2°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielE6952 @jayjhisaurus @seneca @andshewas @robbiehowell YOU HAD A MOUSTACHE IN 5TH GRADE?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexandria_root thought we were friends but... https://t.co/jIaYn994mL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GianaLynnMusic It’s tough. It took me 9 years to get a steady rotation of income while at the same time working a… https://t.co/9nCmvBlHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin you've bought your way on this piece of garbage of an organization @ARTGP that would allow someone to kee… https://t.co/Sfl5ye7FOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#centralpark #newyork #newyorkcity #tvwriting #screenwriting #amediting #amwriting #amrewriting #writingmusic… https://t.co/1K1R7O8dxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookHookah The 25th Amendment is for president ‘unable to execute the duties as president.’  It is not to be used… https://t.co/Gxja3dZNS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screen captures from my dash cam of billboards in Philly this weekend celebrating Bryce Harper https://t.co/6KZWswwVn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasant enough... Thx Jurek! - Drinking a Krušovice Imperial 5.0% by Heineken Česká Republika @ Rad's Pad  — https://t.co/bKuECLlosU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlainTruth20 @ABC @Samhez4Christ @Evonhez @IjeomahG @realDonaldTrump @JustinWelby @FoxNewsOpinion @BBCNews… https://t.co/7nM6gWRFJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many who call themselves feminists should take a lesson from you  https://t.co/mAgyn1fwqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 8 - Examiner Today:     Nikki Haley's eye on 2024;     Trump threatens debate boycott     Via… https://t.co/HccbKDTnM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lojesa @dogomoreno Gracias! Ya la había visto, muy buen trabajo de @gismendez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Destinee! Nails the double pike and double tuck dismount! Just a bit shy on the front full but this should score well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @realDonaldTrump You have a tough job and you are doing fantastic]]></document><document><![CDATA[you can have all the money in the world, women will still cheat on you 🤦🏽‍♂️ crazy world we live in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaraSorrenti Democracy is the taxi ride socialists take on the road to communism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rams secondary what? Locked you up for 4 catches and 36 yards in a must win game?? That rams secondary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How We Increased Organic Traffic (4X) With Technical SEO Ξ FTF https://t.co/SovRsbJh8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are persistent you will get it, but if you are consistent you will keep it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SE APLICÓ EVALUACIÓN A SEXTO DE PRIMARIA EN COAHUILA. @mrikelme  https://t.co/atfSFnRpMA https://t.co/3MplEWafPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @nytimes @AOC What else would you expect from the NY SLIME newspaper.]]></document></documents></author>