<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Found some videos on my sisters phone and you will not be disappointed watch them😂😂 https://t.co/ilYZ8BvTbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love being in the presence of greatness 🏆🏆🏆 #BayAreaUnite @sanjosesharks @warriors 🦈🏀🖤💙💛💙 @ SAP Center https://t.co/VrdBu9LZ8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[The basics matter! They make any fireground task simpler, easier and more importantly get accomplished faster, Whic… https://t.co/RGholdXb3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch AKA Starting off strong on Intern Day Off #dukefamily https://t.co/SBM4NFhYh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[UAMS Midsouth Black Expo | February 23, 9am-3pm https://t.co/z1ZXMVLCUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official!! 9th Roccos Tacos Restaurant is open for dinner tomorrow at 4pm. Roccos Tacos Naples is here!!! https://t.co/HAVctxEaEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaitlinDenman @HarrisonBearHug Ok you’re right. People are always selling farm land and chickens on the Nac buy an… https://t.co/nHmUmqVWmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @CoryBooker The real issue: If you don't do the crime, you don't do the time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over here dreaming big dreams!! #edchat #kyadmin #driven https://t.co/iut0ZGgWPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @TLA_Moonshot for Click Clack Moo interactive performance for our K and 1 Ss!  @TCEpirates @IRSuper1… https://t.co/hIffIPwjQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Global_Witness Friends, I am a former Soviet attorney. If you live peace, please read my No. 92- Ripping the Mask… https://t.co/o5q00sWdle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, I had to go to bed, can someone please tell me what I missed on the app last night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This eucalyptus leaf is really ambitious in her coloring. #eucalpytusleaves #montereyrectrail @ Del Monte Beach, Mo… https://t.co/j642B5IRNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an AU where he’s paying attention and olicity is all google eyes and he’s had it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already want that hour back and I don’t think we’ve even officially lost it yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tools of the Trade by Industrial Arts Brewing at @Strikers_Lanes — https://t.co/veFovGONp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quepedoalan @aandresyourself Yet people that didn’t buy VIP still get in it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #character #doodle #sketch ! ❤️  . . . . . . #watercolorpainting #watercolor #watercolor_art #illustration… https://t.co/xBTrW0KVDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never take the words “you don’t want the smoke” seriously again.. simply bc I just watched a bitch almost get… https://t.co/3D1E1PaSJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I had a table come in at 9:45 last night. Keep in mind we close at 10. These people took 10 mins to order and th… https://t.co/dHLnapwPwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ambitious Alcoholics? Something took over as I was reading for the lovely @crazylittlev 🤣🤣🤣 #pilotseason… https://t.co/ofKoDyH1Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had some of the most fucked yo nightmares that I’ve ever had last night. And if you know me you know they must have… https://t.co/Nou3ATR64G]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏻👏🏼👏🏽👏🏾👏🏿 to the woman who became the movement - thank you Rosa! #WomensHistoryMonth @prattandwhitney @MAKERSwomen… https://t.co/FoYYEgMa0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone else want to punch Michael Cera in the face or is that just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[El camino a utilizar #AI es primero recolectar los datos, organizarlos, analizarlos y después inyectarlos en toda l… https://t.co/YrH1BtDMtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A who bird at dusk #hiking #owls #hikingfortordlands #sunset @ Fort Ord https://t.co/X8Gh7II6dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to @apalesky &amp; @Plano_Schools. So glad we were able to highlight these awesome students.… https://t.co/PutN6D03E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Mueller's report comes out next week does that mean @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @IvankaTrump and Jared (to… https://t.co/gsHTWZ3u4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humanworkplace Agree. Humans are naturally creative. Plus I’ve been a designer for decades and never hear colleagu… https://t.co/O003oIkcx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My morning regimen all-in-one superfood supplement to start my day 💥 It makes my skin glow, gives me naturally ener… https://t.co/MilI0AlAsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t_k8484 @SethAbramson @CNN @PeteButtigieg No; I watched the town hall after I repeated my thought that he may be u… https://t.co/7oZMXe1RF2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandonkscott @BGisBrandonGray Craziest sh@!t ever seen in my life honestly... had to watch it twice to fathom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Indiana Jones Epic Stunt Spectacular! - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/r8uNfr6peF]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/K9tDCftkRv please check this bluegrass band out? @RSAnsleyMusic @brandedgrass @ShelliBernard7… https://t.co/OOa6tDhgGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @DsOchoa He may not have claimed authorship, but since the evangelicals have proclaimed him to be the 2… https://t.co/MdagKKSVVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantaCombs @DKGlobalInc @cbi777 @waycooljen @greenwisemarket @Greg_Tish @sweeteabourbon @biggreenpen… https://t.co/68nJIYgI0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I texted my boss yesterday asking if he needs me to come in today and he said to text my coworker.  I texted her tw… https://t.co/J5RpB0EBAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They still thin they are the one percent who knows everything but by their results they are over paid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goleft00 @SenSanders @realDonaldTrump I CARE...the SOB IS CORRUPT....he is using his position for personal profit.… https://t.co/xxMIfMLNMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizmh70 No. It’s actually pretty easy when you love with all your being ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmalee_marie_d Okay but could you imagine having to raise you in boy form? Lol ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Box seats for #Rachmaninov magic tonight: @STrpceski plays Piano Concerto No. 3 with one of the best orchestras in… https://t.co/lftZLgudUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a W is a W whether by 1 or 30.....Way to go Rams!  So proud!! #LetsGoVCU  #GoRams #byebyeDayton]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FOX5MORNING Happy Valentine's Day to my wonderful husband Charles. Thanks for all you do for us. Not just today, b… https://t.co/6ROTW8Tm2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is in her citadels; he has shown himself to be her fortress. https://t.co/5Z02K7gMDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revive85KC Right? I just read an explanation on why he’s not getting surgery now and omg. It’s annoying to see tha… https://t.co/KyGYht4Ioo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIA @TheAcademy While this is different than how I picture the CIA, unless you wrote this in some code from an und… https://t.co/ElM5EpPPiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe, tapping me repeatedly: “I’m just picturing myself as a lil salamander, ‘thp thp thp thp’ with my tongue all ov… https://t.co/lSHB3GEqgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creative, witty and much cooler than I’ll ever be, @ZealousCMS is a marketing/branding rockstar! ⭐️… https://t.co/0doSr06IEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick visit to see gpa. Nearly 1 year ago he was found in his place.. Suffering a stroke a week earlier. It's been… https://t.co/9r9GgdKSCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sashakatz @krassenstein @EdKrassen Terrible!!! How this 🐉🐉🐉🐉🐲🐲🐲🐉🐍🐍🐍is in 🏦🏦🏦is beyond me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The president millions elected was Hillary. You stole it from her by committing treason. And you'r… https://t.co/8tLLkmjBlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anthony_Pham15 Maybe you could... idk, sleep at night like a normal person???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBobGibbs WTH? Who do you think you are... God?  You Lie to protect Trump constantly and you have the balls to t… https://t.co/G4cXsB0J9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jeffgordonweb  waited for 2 hours to get Jeff Gordon's autograph and still did not get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #MardiGras y'all ⚜️ . . . #nola #endymion #laissezlesbontempsrouler #throwmesomethingmister #midcity… https://t.co/G1pdxNuQlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if Jessie’s Girl was Stacy’s Mom and her number was 867-5309 🤘🏼🖤🤘🏼🖤 @rickspringfield ALWAYS puts on a fantasti… https://t.co/Pgfp6mFYKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took so many pics @OaklawnRacing @Txfleming ran cell phone down to 20%. Luckily restaurant staff at Carousel came to my rescue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dirty_Water @cspanwj I called the 800 number in my Polaris Hot Water Heater when it wouldn't light. I got a guy wi… https://t.co/bQ2lsw0Ele]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GemmaAnneStyles How do scientist know that dogs can't see colors like us...did they ask the dog???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Encouraged #transformationtuesday Long Post⬇   I wanted to post this because I know that this is where my life a… https://t.co/fFlNJtDXbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DONT DESERVE MY TWITTER FRIENDS. YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE AND I AM SO GRATEFUL WOWOWOW 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajw0709 Obviously he didn't do that much damage since they got their HEA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is violence against women who reject you a funny joke? This is the real reason why women feel umcomfortable and… https://t.co/MQlOTY5eL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Lambert just killed it, with Queen, in the Oscar opening!! #WeAreTheChampions #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still alive! Been taking a break to handle some other business. But I did want to stop by and share this with y… https://t.co/yV2L1LaUKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorman boys vs Desert Pines 7:00pm at VALLEY HS @BG_Basketball @DP_Basketball 🏀✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[A LOT. ♂︎ ♡︎ . . . . #selfportrait #selfie #cropsweatshirt #sweatshirtszn #blogger #fashionblog #streetstyle… https://t.co/eRUqEVZYYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @simplysallyh @GailBenzler @CaththeWineLady… https://t.co/1dYK1zrLPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angel_leeeee I squint so it looks like I’m not staring but trying to make out shapes in my environment 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNLosAngeles You can see his dick in those shorts and u know what? I ain't even mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @FoxNews @realDonaldTrump And Donna and the debate questions. Acosta and the constant temper tantrums. Come on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having last minute #surgery tomorrow to remove possibly infected #shunts from my #brain and lumbar. My top 2 co… https://t.co/flEoplhgEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HumanistReport 🤣🤣🤣🤣How is the earth round, I can see the horizon.  🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jd_2355 @alllibertynews @justinamash I wish congress would let the judiciary do its job and start doing something… https://t.co/3YBevu1jPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone, I worked on this. I think it's gonna be pretty good! Who wants to see it with me??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evan_yon Dawgs have better recruiting class, better football team, beat you in Florida in BASKETBALL and took your… https://t.co/gdR0WYBROZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisHouck Insane. We have a known traitor, who is still dangerous possibly being allowed into America. Congress… https://t.co/9W6eKa9VCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my mommy such a nice bday gift I can’t wait to give it to her ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to leave my house Thursday not pregnant or with my child I’m :( but also I’m 💃🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make mad the guilty and appal the free, Confound the ignorant, and amaze indeed The very faculties of eyes and ears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their response was, you seem like you’re doing a lot better! And I was like, yes, yes I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleVicary @hallmarkchannel you guys had a category for best talking. how could you NOT be the best?!… https://t.co/Qf49X7vLOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get them confused, a mentor is not a sponsor. Which do you have? #HBAimpact #HBAsf #GRIT #leadership https://t.co/xIxlfDJTZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP We need Bernie to get off his expensive soapbox. You don’t drive an 18,K sports car own 3 very large mansions… https://t.co/PExZjX08ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/BRdXBVxPMB! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/VSFr4OYGyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of love today for @RonWellman &amp; @John_Currie. Excited about the future of @WakeForest @DemonDeacons! 🎩🙌… https://t.co/Dg9Oy3qPlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact- at northwest I was SHIT ASS drunk in heels, and my gay friend actually taught me this is the best way to… https://t.co/B0l9gUpFOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeleStar11 @ProTrumpGirl @RandPaul @sodagrrl Rand Paul has four more years.😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[But honestly though. I’m super pissed about all the money I’m missing out on this weekend.😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backt0nature Love this so much. Made me weep but in a good way. Thanks to everyone who rescues these beautiful cre… https://t.co/ZXzsHU9JMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyliecosmetics Valentines Palette https://t.co/hDOMc5gDEM 💕 https://t.co/6sMfpOdATm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeelsRebeccah mmmmdelisous Story life and times of Reid McQueen aka RebeccaHHeels #GreatestDetectiveAlive]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you re-email someone? Like, hi Steve, I emailed you and you ignored me. Don’t do it this time? https://t.co/0MVz7VcEVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you #valentine (@ Giant in Ashburn, VA) https://t.co/IlKi3EaY95 https://t.co/M4MNyeqJ7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st  Birthday to my soulmate 💓Samuel, who would’ve thought we would make it this far we were just kicking it… https://t.co/3H2RIRR9Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m just saying if i could marry a man with a heart and face like @jakemiller i’d be set]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan Bella y hermosa q esta mi gemelita 🥰😘💋 Love You Nay Nay 😘💋💋 queen_siomara_1340 Grandma sent me this 🥰 @ Hartfor… https://t.co/L0l3YU7NSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I so called it Lambert busted up another relationship! She and her husband deserve each other and I don’t give this… https://t.co/zCgHAROlJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller @Trump_World Please investigate them all @LindseyGrahamSC !!]]></document></documents></author>