<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you think the BS that Cohen, and Congress, is emitting during this hearing, is far more detrimen… https://t.co/ftYsYeQ6I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey La Crosse-area friends!! Be sure you’ve got @KQ98 turned up tomorrow morning 9-10am! I’ll be live with… https://t.co/YAyXjF44zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jure2 @WalshFreedom @mschlapp @marklevinshow  should have Joe on life liberty in levin]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@people thanks for sharing this story with your readers and letting them know how they can #BleedFortheThrone… https://t.co/TJnUoqR0s3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hollywood_52 Can’t have great things if you can’t do the little things!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody knows what waits for the dead, some folks just beleive in the things they heard and the things they read. No… https://t.co/VMq8oBdYCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PazBoguslaw Ale musi Pan przyznac ze zabawnie jest ogladac nabzdyczone miny myslicieli omawiajacych Miedzymorze na… https://t.co/SarVm09ExM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @GOPChairwoman A diaper wearing dude is the future of the @GOP? Seems legit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SeaWorld Lighthouse! Another beautiful day in #beautifulfla https://t.co/r5fBEDemKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoWendyO Taking profits doesn’t have to be “total liquidation” of a position.  “Scale” out of positions by “cl… https://t.co/kskcBtYBDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flights purchased for a post-defense trip to Puerto Rico! Happy graduation to me! Hit me with your recommendations 🤗😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEMIvik Have a beautiful Sunday Viktoria!! ☕️☕️♥️ https://t.co/0ygb54oY2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimmahWrestling @davemeltzerWON Ask your mother. Oooooooooooooh faced! 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathinator That’s frustrating. Life is not for living! It’s for WWF solo play!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImYancyButler Such a beauty. Love you when you had the long hair and still love you now, @ImYancyButler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallascowboys @realjerryjones THERE IS NO EXCUSE NOT TO SIGN COOPER LAWRENCE BYRON JONES EARL THOMAS THEN ELLIOT A… https://t.co/WYtjWHiJj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen had nothing to lose, he’s going to jail. At the hearing Wednesday Republicans on the committee didn’t… https://t.co/veM4oONNPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know people backstabbed you, but this “fuck everybody” attitude ain’t natural]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ippaku @AinoaSuicide I'll pick one up for you and bring it over.  Which one do you want?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamTomHolland on @TyltEnt—Tom Holland is the best Spider-Man https://t.co/ZAN2a21m2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked like a mile from G to Jetro to meet @RearAdBsBlog instead gave a pod stroke to Biz and got a 🔥 shirt from… https://t.co/NcG20TMUff]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Snowball effect has taken shape for the #ShadesOfHaydenBatMitzvah @ The Glen Club https://t.co/bgeuk57G0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 White privilege means I have the power to bring awareness to social injustice, criminal injustice, raci… https://t.co/2jqan4M1Hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[- - HERE ARE THE BROMBAL WINDOWS LAYOUT IN ITALY BEFORE SHIPPING TO THE USA. WE ARE READY FOR BROMBAL WINDOWS, AND… https://t.co/TCflzyD1mO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonesomereader @MSSciarappa Not everyone... just @MSSciarappa 🙏🏻 It’s just so much fun. I won’t rain on your parad… https://t.co/F3sgtxNFvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Live And Let Chai by @eagleparkbc at @EagleParkBeer — https://t.co/oopAyXqOP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky, on the road in bad weather, winning by double-digits at halftime. Kentucky looking awesome. MU showing it… https://t.co/LqL9HTdmeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lay Your Hands In Me Blood On Blood Never Say Goodbye  It’s My Life Who Says You Can’t Go Home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how things go with the NFL and the optics. Trace McSorley is considered undersized at QB at 6-0 1/8, 202lbs a… https://t.co/hrdMbzIp60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eh, jakoś tak wszystkie nominowane do Oscarów filmy są mi strasznie obojętne.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLoganRyan My 5 rescue dogs appreciate all you do! #AdoptDontShop #RescueDogs 👍🏻 https://t.co/WX09Yclt8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Tri-Rail-Fort Lauderdale Station https://t.co/rLzPGGr8xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just crying because I can’t escape what could have been - Jorja Smith 🥰😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadie_bodybasic Good morning Sadie and happy Tuesday from my alternative music station 😘😘💖💖💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are in congress. They. It's on Law - they pass resolutions - they write new green deal proposals  THEY DONT KN… https://t.co/xlOVWdfmfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I ordered this shirt, yeah I got it in the mail, yeah I’m gonna cut the sleeves off, yeah I got a “beer babe”… https://t.co/f20RF7Nkrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wallstreetbarbers #wallstreetbarberstudio #barber #barbers #barbering #ncbarbers #fayettevillenc #barbershop… https://t.co/5vaXDZm6rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏠There has been a list of properties I helped my clients buy and sell in the last few weeks 🏠🏠💥💥💥 Thank you to all… https://t.co/xtXDw9TE0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[What  R Kelly said on the interview was a joke. He did committed those evil acts. It will be better if R Kelly woul… https://t.co/pwBpufoIcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know what smells more - me or my house. Maybe that's why I'm still single. It's not even MY house! I have n… https://t.co/LIqNqzEaVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dale Jenny Timmy Andrea Amy at Stevie’s. @ Stevie Tomato's Sports Page Naples https://t.co/F39fEa5Yi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todd puts on a good show.  . #exhibit #photography #photo #photographer #washingtondc @ Reeves Center Municipal Bui… https://t.co/bure7Nsi5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestStephen @Kathleen_Wynne @JustinTrudeau Sad but true ,Ontario is condemned to years of bad self interest govt.… https://t.co/q2osw2xmbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @SenWarren Your answers prove, you are not qualified or capable of being in charge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Page 2 - Jackson-Madison County property transfers - sponsored by FIRSTBANK https://t.co/jwf7FuGOqW https://t.co/jdrSQsuLxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markballmd @motzermd @DrChoueiri @brian_rini @NCICCR_UroOnc Sweet! I can suggest others lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESbeINSPORTS @JoseHDonGoL @Jaimefmacias #RealMadridGirona GOOD MORNING  SALUDOS SI VEN CASEMIRO ES UN TIGRE PORQUE… https://t.co/nZL1Fof4UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Kamala as a Democrat deciding between all the candidates I want a woman to be president I would like… https://t.co/RAALis3vYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenas tardes @apcandiani @EChiabra @michtrujillotv @AnavarroT52 @AzaleaIniguez @elianamoreno @normaribeiro… https://t.co/jlOsxHLDqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carriebear421 I'm sorry for your loss of your friend😢😢😢😢  Prayers for you and Kim's family  ❤❤❤❤❤❤🌷🌷🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I be creeping. What’s new. And someone went to an EDM show recently. And I’m just like damn I would have fucking… https://t.co/VSmdtR2yI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TumbaBurros2 @RustingMan No les da pena venir a exponerse con suposiciones absurdas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scales12er @TheBaconDiaries Everyone knows that a pool cue is way too short an implement with which to joust. Bett… https://t.co/PiRa1uNuUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Play date. We still clean up ok. #winterball #goodlife #south @ Greenwood Country Club https://t.co/SHOxIE5Y57]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re not a real college student if you don’t procrastinate on every assingment and then force yourself to work un… https://t.co/alEsHwSLeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlarsonuf and I represented @StonyBrookEM tonight, teaming up with the Stony Brook cath lab team to review the sig… https://t.co/wqZQ9C3sJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up obsessed with my Monkees 7” singles as well as the TV show. Peter’s playful goofiness made me more comfortable with my own. RIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrodieNBCS I concur with those saying Jones needs an extended rest before the post-season; and that’s why we have… https://t.co/gTizN5WZfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stairfax @gravitypriest whataburger is superior https://t.co/JGhItdy2WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local kids honored for calling 911...unbelievable story of an 8-year-old girl’s brave actions. @KUSINews at 6,10,11 https://t.co/Ke1UHEy5cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's roll into this morning shift the right way with country music, a hot cup of coffee, and a king sized Reese's!… https://t.co/R5aQPyrNGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astronomolly @NASA_NAS @storycollider But don't you need to sit next to your laptop while it is plugged in to the… https://t.co/n5VxMUESH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simplylisette @sianoresist The Orange One sold someone else’s story though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oakland Teachers Strike, And West Virginia Teachers Say Trust Issues Persist  https://t.co/JVDZA3dWE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoFascistLies He was saying "you" can't. By saying "I" can.   But, yes. It shouldn't be done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get knocked down, but I get up again. You're never going to keep my down.  #WhatILikeAboutMyself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joy_HD632 Rockport Works would be my own recommendation. Comfortable and durable with composite toe... https://t.co/FEfXc0LCpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrevorFSmith @blairmacintyre Honestly completely plays to our unique strengths as *all* the processing happens on… https://t.co/f4B5ymE06V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1a The Catholic Church demonized the LGBTQ+ community making us feel unwelcome and ugly. Who knew the REAL demons… https://t.co/jS4cHMVzf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning one and https://t.co/rfxRLjKjRc's https://t.co/05EWdyjp9X's currently 19° F and light snow in Warren… https://t.co/sji5JEyyjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandeebeechess @EdPiotrowski @jimmbsc @VannagrammyLiz @RareCat @PicBallot @HariG_IN @jamiearnoldWMBF @StaceyALee… https://t.co/dVUWRgKHtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuckumentary You're an asshole for making me go down that hole, but Bonny is rich.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MathewWNorris @Katie_Beth_M @causlander @JSWAN_ @INSenateGOP Was this a panel to discourage participation in the g… https://t.co/6QpZsgvXTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oopsadoop @JHNabors @jkheaton @LovelyLu #HappyValentineDay and #ThankfulThursday y’all. Hope each of you get somet… https://t.co/b0zq6Rajvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Big Ben to Josh Rosen. Don’t think Business will be Booming much longer 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@og_dbl_lo_g @PollyPapaya @PerfumeFlogger @callkurt @KristyLyn11 @DesignationSix @CIAnderson3 @Nikki_WVU_49ers… https://t.co/BZ4lynlESN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxkellerman Is games played a strength for MJ, though? Isn't there something to be said for availability and longevity?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenrysCamera looking to take advantage of the Sony trade up event. Disappointed to find out that none of your Otta… https://t.co/m8qqdMb1pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentMTiberi @TeddyMuzika @JasonJackMiller @The_Steel_Trap @jrtiberi @redroz0595 @StefaniPlume @ggd583… https://t.co/9KAxEQVH24]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Luka’s success. The best college players WILL be looking at this option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Evangelical Republican Special PERSECUTOR Ken Starr and @FoxNews @AlanDersh got serial child molester and… https://t.co/br4tMrJcSp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just what the United States of America don't need is two more shameful clowns running for president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan @Acosta @PressSec Damn, Trump says Dems hate Jews!!! What do I do now???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is sometimes scary. I just gotta remember that there is always a bigger picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SvenErikAlhem När politiken styr vad som är brottsligt kan vad som helst ske. Nu ser vi att arbetsdomstolen inte a… https://t.co/duCtBOMdCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @xamoLAammE Joe liked America better when we sent our pro abortion theology to other countries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebastianComedy I was told 2 look out 4 the " Irashman" - heard He's a real pain in the ass!!! https://t.co/bM9EJWF8Sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry. I’m having a really hard time understanding the part where you said “losing all of your hoes” I’ve never… https://t.co/i4Ypcxjlt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgingFoxes Hey, I'm a CBC reporter wondering if you can give me a call to share your experience with the earthq… https://t.co/kHVwB3OpMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day DEMOCRATS still NOT COMING OUT AND DEMANDING TRUMPS IMMEDIATE RESIGNATION there is enough to impeach NO… https://t.co/JUgiQRRZLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Create in me a clean heart, O God, and put a new and right spirit within me...  https://t.co/ZY35ffC0vl https://t.co/14Dr49ujCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOING HAVE PLAINES FALL LIKE FLIES\KILLING PEOPLE FROM SHIT HOLE COUNTRIES  DO ANY ONE CARE\\\]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @CookCountySAO @AJGuglielmi @charliekirk11 @dbongino @RealSaavedra @Thomas1774Paine @michellemalkin… https://t.co/TssWL9paEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willwilkinson @BulwarkOnline Do you think of "the progressive master narrative" as being similar or disimilar  to… https://t.co/m1yZI4qv4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnterStandman2 this is fucking beautiful chris and this is why you are a leader of mine. this is what i want with… https://t.co/zCa14UUNgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[New saying I learned from @TheJimCornette  "Lost as a ball in tall weeds"]]></document><document><![CDATA[This discussion demonstrates the increasing vacuity of Twitter. My original tweet had absolutely nothing to do with… https://t.co/HCYP8jqrR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a white sox,,,with Bulls,,,,have b,,,j,,,Armstrong https://t.co/z3HSL73Lou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing Metal Gear Solid 2, controls and what to do seems like muscle memory]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls always find things out,   they might not say anything right away,   but they know.]]></document></documents></author>