<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[These are good but the Baja Blast just doesn't taste the same as it does at Taco Bell !!! https://t.co/WBjmvDzTb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most days are great and I do so well and then my bad days well they’re hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Educators: please take a few  moments to answer some #research questions regarding #2e/ #TwiceExceptional. Thank yo… https://t.co/KpTSRxiUFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who eat “Crunch” chocolate bars for fun Bc they actually enjoy them are monsters and need to be banished immediately 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deconciliiss Love that your are covering argument with your 6th graders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want an SGA president who understands how the student engagement department and the university as a whole works.… https://t.co/wlZoSYiCcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜👁👁Azarath Metrion Zinthos👁👁💜 Thanks futuremrs_hardman525 for working her magic flawlessly every time! #NewHair… https://t.co/aYHW9iFD4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to convince myself that driving 3 hours to br just for sushi this weekend is ridiculous. But I’m not seeing any down sides to it 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[view over our heads walking into the hospital today. worries every time I go in or out. https://t.co/pmUTy1tVdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to take a sec (so just sit right there), to unpack the stubborn patriarchal root that is pervasive in… https://t.co/vIkhhuRj5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all hurt the people that god sent to heal you , that’s some shit I’ll never understand .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can think of a zillion worse things that have been commercialized so a day to pause and express love to ourselves… https://t.co/dw9nYMj7Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y los españoles hartos de oírte y oírte y oírte y no verte hacer nada de nada...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1st birthday @sustainthemag!! Helping launch and then becoming an editor for this site has truly changed my l… https://t.co/e4W4nh3BMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is merry. A deer who decided to come for a visit. | 41 Pictures You Need To See... https://t.co/T4xOsxTtjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my girlfriend so much she literally means the world to me💕 I thank god everyday that she walked into my life ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck yea, if I can watch Fantasia as much as I want, @RobertIger you own me, contractually!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahDitkows1 @HansEworth @Harifamily @WestByNW @justinamash @jaketapper Not exactly sure what evil you are spea… https://t.co/fFBjqw4A6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on expanding and condensing logarithms with a tarsia! #MTBoS #iteachmath https://t.co/RHOWToSG7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck @DecaturMBB!! @MakennaGantt and I will be cheering y’all on from San Antonio! 💙💪🏼🏀🦅]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coastal waters being mined seems like a MUCH bigger problem than an octopus #Svengoolie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or maybe I just do irritate everyone around me and I’m right about how I feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[proud to be a part of this #thebarbarouscentury 📚 https://t.co/b0TAJiWjPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one should ever have to hear rocketman 5 times in 2 hours yet here i am]]></document><document><![CDATA[#joy #happiness #life #lifestyle #journey #mission #health #nutrition #food #diabetes #prediabetes #newyeargoals… https://t.co/lqRVzW4N1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for some #FBICBS ???? RT if your watching @FBICBS @mperegrym @zeekozaki @JeremySisto @SelaWard… https://t.co/3CTpVHxfD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennis_e_moore I’m happy to put you on the agenda for the next Board of Aldermen meeting so you can ask for a brea… https://t.co/Nvd6esqJof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madz said “no mama I don’t like bows at all” this morning after I put a bow in her hair... lol I guess I’ll try aga… https://t.co/WWbM7qxM9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live now @ https://t.co/lcfw744b3E playing #Fortnite 😍 #FortniteSeason8   Come say hiiiii 👋   #twitchtv… https://t.co/Ecj4EuBV5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enhancement to behavioral health specialists of $6.5m provide increased social workers (more dollars in last bienni… https://t.co/4CiiYJOwZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mentee just told me that he got into his top choice MSTP and I have all the feels 🥳😭🤓! I’m so happy and proud th… https://t.co/VE5ChLOwSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ✨The Diva's Room of Solitude✨🌟💫 in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/ksn6BQciqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @POTUS couldn't make an intelligent order! Let alone an executive order!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cracking of a flag in the wind, I feel, is the second most American sound in the world (the first is gun shots, obv.).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophia #dancer #proudaunt @ Richland Township, Cambria County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/SzVjFFz2I1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I woke up when I started getting weather alerts on my phone and immediately went to Twitter! Already hearing th… https://t.co/ZUb7gTvH3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demiikyless Always!❤️ I say I have a lot of favorite teams (which honestly I do lol) but SICk6 has been sooo fun t… https://t.co/r2o3zfeHqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabriel_lima_08 @joaoamoedonovo Cara, ele disputou uma eleição e perdeu. Na verdade não teve chance alguma. Isso é… https://t.co/Ugbg6Mkreb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be on your guard; you will be handed over to the local councils and be flogged in the synagogues. https://t.co/CKoiVrw9Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of Love the Bus Week @SES__Principal. Students delivered cards signed by all the bus riders to their drivers.… https://t.co/hOJwOvGdtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letitia Wright has youth but I’m taller and have reach going for me. Most of the other famous Letitias are, well, d… https://t.co/z5NVLO3y9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Valentines2019 the year I finally experienced a real, love-filled celebration!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS I still believe it's time for the truth about Hope's baby to be revealed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just getting in bed. After working. This late you know it’s because I’m doing what I love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I just did what every food company wants you to do, I looked at the serving size which was 5, I said to myself… https://t.co/e7h0jqmDU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[FDA Accepts Genentech’s Supplemental New Drug Application for XOFLUZA (baloxavir marboxil) for the Treatment of Inf… https://t.co/FuVmCPyFYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback from 2006, Rio and Max, two of the best.  💜💜🐕💜🐈💜💜 #tbt #tbt❤️ #tbthursday #throwbackthursday #throwback… https://t.co/exk0A14zRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So called Alliance between #UK and #USA produced a major uptick in wars, conflicts, genocides, and untold pain and… https://t.co/DhkdmJJWsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear ex boyfriends will find ANY reason to text you. “I drove past your house today.” Yeah, and? https://t.co/RMVSU2hwG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN When is CNN going to accept HRC's 2016 loss. Get a mirror for God's sake. You can't make this stuff up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad to say goodbye (for now!) to our friends today but we did it up right at one of our favorite places and topp… https://t.co/j6EhvMR4Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take time for yourself. Working women "Do-Do-Do". Always on the go taking care of Family, household and work priori… https://t.co/tw1uDk9GV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gailcarriger I don't see how this could be unpopular. With all the awfulness in the world, funny sweet fantasy tha… https://t.co/pUedVZiMX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhodysbroker @buynothingman @saldotwit @MrAndyNgo @liberalnotlefty @RashidaTlaib @IlhanMN She has nothing.  The le… https://t.co/zjMIUyGoqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulgreenemedia @hallmarkchannel @stevegeelow @MediaVillageCom I missed you in this Christmas season’s movies, but… https://t.co/pVWrN5j6mJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday Jack, hope you have a great day💛 miss &amp; love you honey 🤩 https://t.co/GkQKN1HnmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[my name is not "big butt" and it sure as HELL ain't "big tits" stfu stfu stfu stfu stfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @MileyCyrus You foolish immature has been. You must be hanging with @Alyssa_Milano]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Gonzalez on the Aerodynamics of Exceptional Schools | SXSW EDU   @Lightinglamps #LamplighterLeads… https://t.co/j6nI1y9FR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abruno77 The visuals are amazing -- and they don't stop! Given your taste, you'll be sitting there at sundown....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing in a crowd here at @AustinPeaySB!! #LetsGoPeay #APGovsCup @APGovsCup https://t.co/aZoaS2HGUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t call it “sex”, I call it “rootin tootin around” because I’m a mature adult!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is Bloody Sunday. Bernie will spend the entire day talking about that one time he got arrested and paid a… https://t.co/xUp2GbRmGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan I also think someone who just retweets and does not have an original thought is suspicious]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElGuerro97 Bro fr tho sell feet pics, it’s a weird world out there so make some cash out of it 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say it again for the people in the back!!!  I get so weary of hearing, “We can’t do that for kids because we can’t… https://t.co/e3tqrQ5CLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reason2sense @powertoimpeach This has NOTHING to do with the wall F’n Moron....it has everything to do with Guns dumbass deplorable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BermanNDP Poor little souls. My heart goes out to their devastated parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Texas State University PACE Center offers peer mentoring, academic coaching, career exploration and many resour… https://t.co/FpSpQdDR7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some internet troll named joshua (that i met via twitter) really had the nerve to comment some nasty, fucked up shi… https://t.co/kCtgZppLAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherryColaZing Yes you can. Go to the review tab, I think. There is an audio feature. It should show it. It is set… https://t.co/Wln70wtTTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Middlest got her 2nd University acceptance! Deciding will be tough! Still waiting for a few more. She’s happy, though 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GyngerPope Come to Dublin w me. It’s not Scotland but it’s closer than here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AyannaPressley @IlhanMN Thank you, Thank You, THANK YOU!!! What a breath of fresh air you are!   Keep fightin… https://t.co/b8IKzYECUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, let’s interrogate what we are doing to support students that carry social identities outside of and in additi… https://t.co/wC00GHczBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our newest associates! Welcome to the family. @JohnnyTBush @DanielMooreTHD @THDTHEHODGE https://t.co/cAtBmx7fwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art comes alive @PS66JKO  @MuseumModernArt  #vangogh #ProudPrincipal #welcomespring]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t think my boyfriend found this funny but I sure chuckled. Stay tuned to find out if I’m still in a relationshi… https://t.co/czj8KJfo2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot believe choupette a CAT is getting a 195 million fortune from Karl Lagerfeld! A CAT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For it is God who works in you to will and to act in order to fulfill his good purpose]]></document><document><![CDATA[From yesterday - Drinking a Chopsecutioner by @TerrapinBeerCo at @disneysports  — https://t.co/gkW7kiDuB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrumpCorruption #TrumpCorruption #TrumpCorruption #TrumpCorruption #TrumpCorruption #TrumpTraitor #TrumpTraitor… https://t.co/DyICLUaptM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travistritt What a beautiful picture!  Happy Valentine’s Day to the both of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizzie_McD Yes! They should be available at a majority of our company-owned stores!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSteministas @ElenaCH Thank you for sharing, @TSteministas   Arizona can be the 38th and final state to ratify the… https://t.co/r9RMLKAq5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get cheated on don’t be stupid and cheat on that person just to be spiteful, it’s just going to make shit bad 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what, our 9th or 10th @needtobreathe show? #ntbacoustictour #needtobreathe @ Canton Palace Theatre https://t.co/FQr3y0agmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themfspirit A deposit or sending references to MAKE it happen, then it won’t happen.   I’m really confused by this… https://t.co/s479GpdtPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Screw this guy and any veteran who supports his cowardly treasonous ass. He couldn't give a shit less abou… https://t.co/MY81rZpOAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/7Ke1SDwwWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not usually into the celebrity chef branded restaurants but the @GordonRamsay burger restaurant in Las Vegas is… https://t.co/xQhd11Zqk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t talk shit &amp; I won’t have to bitch slap you next time smh 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know anyone in San Antonio and I’m tired of being stuck in the house 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback to that perfect balayage! 👌♥️ #btconeshot19_warmbalayage #behindthechair #btconeshot #btc ⠀⠀  #lanzalove… https://t.co/lGm7JD3VT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/JWL7KXV1BL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ouch 🤕   Man falls through gym skylight during wrestling match -- https://t.co/a2blNBYEej https://t.co/dyZIArY9hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbygriffin96 @bakwoodzboy95 Ouchhhhh and I didn’t know, I expect a full report Tomorrow ok thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway when is the Manhattan bound F going to hot 21st QB? Please answer ASAP as I need to alternate travel pl… https://t.co/sFK7KORRbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some dude just decided to invade my space at the bar. Guess what bro? I’m not moving. Happy International Women’s Day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess when I provided the deposal testimony, and mafia is mafia, I became President who is excited to jail them a… https://t.co/siFQi2M6xv]]></document></documents></author>