<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'M A FAN  @daniel_suarezg  @bobashmore52 @ Las Vegas Motor Speedway https://t.co/b83onKC8DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stop listening to the new song the dirt by @MotleyCrue @NikkiSixx @thevinceneil @mrmickmars @MrTommyLand #TheDirt #MotleyCrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[For several days now I’ve been fighting the urge to text a guy to tell him I miss him. I know that wouldn’t be productive or healthy, but...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so he declares one then leaves for Florida to relax and golf....fake emergency apparently...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homejames4 @HeadsweatsCo @Headsweats It’s the only place I go for my hats (unless given to me for free).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j0nathanzarate @premierleague Ese de Manchester United vs Liverpool no me lo pierdo por nada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like. Yo. This is huge. That’s worth almost $100K, maybe more if you count the interest associated with the loans I… https://t.co/SiWnDjISVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a longtime #DTLV resident, I wanted to thank @CityofLasVegas for their recent work beautifying and improving Gas… https://t.co/Cynj65KOQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to a fitness consultant at the Y yesterday and let me tell you... I'm definitely considering some consulting s… https://t.co/Fz1WsSenWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Or, is it taking a few swings in the golf simulator at the White House during Executive Time? ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imgod256 @HarryO1975 @dijoni @Fresh_Flames1 @Cofe6370 @MZMITA007 @angelaw676 @uniqueloves @trueblackpower… https://t.co/TBaBm3cALC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for Above and Beyond Experience...? Call Allpro Contracting True Certified 5 STAR remodeling company.… https://t.co/SLwJA4XBoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orlando City opening game ⚽🦁 #FaceofCity #OrlandoCity #Soccer #VamosOrlando @ Orlando City Stadium https://t.co/kjzakUR7gT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanessaBorneWWE Ironic. Usually it's you getting the marriage proposals, V 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebakerlaw @ws121 @amyklobuchar ...or #KevinKline Step In Whereas They Each Played Fictional #AmericanPresident… https://t.co/5RBfhymUc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blackhawks make minor-league trade, acquiring Spencer Watson from the #Kings in exchange for Matheson Iacopelli #NHL #AHL #ECHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to Jake, who gave me one of the more thoughtful interviews I enjoyed his senior year at Olympus. Great… https://t.co/APf78sgFKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part of #CaptainMarvel was Maria Rambeau. Lashana Lynch had the strongest performance next to Ben Mendelso… https://t.co/6mrYByPfCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going home for Easter and I’m actually kind of excited??? Better not be a damn tornado tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrometeoNuclear @fernandeznoroma @lopezobrador_ Parece un twitt genuino pero alguien mas me acaba d decor q es una… https://t.co/39HeVjxWRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Football: To be clear, new NJSIAA rules would limit “full contact” to 15 minutes a week during season. That involve… https://t.co/ignRfHlfO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:25.7°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @LoleskyWX, I’m looking for a go to meteorologist for @GatorsBB weather. You In? This pop up stuff is killing us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Menos mal que los agentes de Twitter solo son agentes de Twitter ya que estaban empujando para que firmara por mont… https://t.co/5Eg7jwhRPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismcquarrie I recently made a short film that’s about 10 minutes long, it’d be an honor if you could watch it!… https://t.co/EiVEHKyxqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandySchendel @MandySchendel and my Valentine’s Day has just been made !!! Thank you for sharing this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Romiiinaahh Omg my aunt left some at my house for us yesterday. It’s SO GOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that I only have to work the next two weeks and then I’m off for a week for my birthday 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPostPol Hillary Clinton, 70 Won 2016 Popular Vote by 2,864,903 Won 2016 Primaries by 3,708,294 Media: go away.… https://t.co/2amcSR9nzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching #SaturdayShowcase: 5 @Vol_Hoops at @AuburnMBB live from #AuburnArena on @espn on the #ESPN app on my @Roku… https://t.co/R8IBKe9V2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13m5 @supernovaslight @Tesla @elonmusk @RationalEtienne Which podcast?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday, everyone is in the position to make a right decision. Make the right decision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Wayne is home to roughly 500 people, Black Hawk High School has an enrollment of 99 kids. They now have won a… https://t.co/6oiTm0NNUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así se burló @Cinemex del hijo de Alfonso Cuarón  #Oscars #Roma #AlfonsoCuaron #MeDuelesMéxico #Autismo https://t.co/JlhIuqAwcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to put this out there.. Full focus currently on Fortworth but I will be an F/A ICR for London.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction What’s even worse is the left propaganda machine, such as msnbc, cnn, and the others!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariannaa88 I don't know what's more inappropriate. The question or the wrong plural phrase lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestigePrince9 @daveyyyyyyyyyyy @frankyjosh31 @stephenasmith @Lakers @Suns @KingJames Even the great MJ did not m… https://t.co/RfyEsfDNXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is that MASKED devil in pic. 2019?  Hey, all the better when President Trump takes it in 2020.  Two blows to he… https://t.co/tTHju0YtQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@airasiabig Hi, did you change the schedule of the final call sale? Not the first Monday of the month anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markesoto @Angelrdz66 H.Long!!!!! Hell yes.  seeing him and Lyle , A.  you know there were dishing out some pain.… https://t.co/nMPnsuZWFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregWildSmith Have some faith in me here man... The problem isn't tagging on off (which is easy). It's knowing whi… https://t.co/AFKQy2il0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blown away by the Daytona 500 yesterday and now heading in to some client meetings in Dallas today.  Back at it for… https://t.co/WZPSwjw8gS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imaging a person who wants to invest in any asset anywhere in the world or in the cyber space, due diligence inform… https://t.co/fN1S86KfeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since weeaboo is already taken for people that like Japanese things too much can we use weeweeaboo for people that… https://t.co/cHIaJxulK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mirá cómo se miran, mirá como lo agarra del cuello el Piri. Déjense de joder y vuelvan a River para ganar otra Libe… https://t.co/Hi8WX8pMuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was Bernie Sanders Net Worth before entering politics and what is it now? More Pay To Play Payola!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NV96308613 @ByronYork Trump denies this but then again he has denied things that prove to be true before.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewWaveOil He's got an unbreakable arm and he also played his best hockey with Segin 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatsBroadway just saw cats opening night in Los Angeles and it was amazing probably going to go in a couple weeks and see it on my birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into these two ladies in Arizona on Thursday helping sample some of the best tea in the world...@incatea Follow… https://t.co/oo2x3ylogF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPost_Brazille Team is so inconsistent....they are going to need Heron for home stretch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody not going to believe in you. As long as you believe in yourself all your goals can be reached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleRichards  the most beautiful queen of the Real Housewives of Beverly 💎 https://t.co/T49zyXG4co]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizWFB "Officer, I accidentally drank 15 beers and drove home. How 'bout a warning?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t use Netflix enough to pay $12.99, everyone on my account will be sick when I cut it. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollyspangler I couldn't agree more with this article. I love serving, but we've lost sight of common courtesy. I'… https://t.co/CA6RrytaOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn Hey @espn! QUIT BEING SUCH A DUKE HOMER! Oh by the way, THEY LOST!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just plain sad... remember when those promoting ‘choice’ said our concerns over infanticide were overblown… https://t.co/rg5cUtbHf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJansing Wow, Amash is asking real questions. First R to do so. Impressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[G'0D[D]Like FAITH..(n)TheBi'ble isThe[_"0"Unseen]Substance ofThings hoped4,TheEvidence ofThings Not Seen -Hebrews 1… https://t.co/V1E7kqeCue]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m going to bed. Yes it’s 11:30. Yes I’m old. Yes I’m whipped. Goodnight” #KibQuotes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain marvel wasn't better than other origin stories like doctor strange or iron Man, but it was definitely better than Thor]]></document><document><![CDATA[My assistant pastor on our latest trip to Israel!  charleskoeller &amp; I were together in Israel 29 years ago!… https://t.co/RwWnEv31dq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin Just like Spanky does understand the way Tariffs work.  It is not money we are collecting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at House of Blues - @hobcleveland for 10 Summer Presents: The Debut Tour With Ella Mai in Cleveland, OH https://t.co/LtgXTqHYOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyLynchWWE This needs to be your new theme! https://t.co/FFcWlq7cmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its starting to look like by the time we'll be able to enjoy a San Diego to Sacramento trip along the California Hi… https://t.co/BnhAne0E0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Saturday!   Snow coming in this afternoon! Hang on!  They keep changing the total accumulation 💥💥👊💪🤟🤙🤘☝️💥💥… https://t.co/7781bTCi7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannywood Hope you had a great workout in the gym getting Swolen, Jacked &amp; Ripped]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love having laughs on twitter with you motherfuckers. https://t.co/0hk9rpHLMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair @GMA @RobinRoberts Watch Ted Talk, with Dr terry Wahls on MS. Speechless!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel was one of the best movies I've seen in a long time. #CaptainMarvel #RepresentationMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@West_Side_Vonte Dawg had to hit one of these 😂😂 https://t.co/FF8YHeQTYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Bestfriend ain’t allowed a significant other.   RT if this applies to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hodgesreporting Has Matthew Ridenhour been endorsed by Pat McCrory? I saw footage of you mentioning the endorsemen… https://t.co/zJXLg80sQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fourth  - 3rd shot at 25 yds. I'll take that. I'm try go again later today move target to 80 yds. Both my boy's say… https://t.co/m9pQQaWXfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Observing a beautiful, partial rainbow out east within an area of showers. Just so gorgeous! A low pressure area wa… https://t.co/yvOLg9xDqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr CALM DOWN AND ENJOY THE RIDE 2019  - lost 10 cabinet members - lost 65 executive staff - 18% increa… https://t.co/QsEqavCL70]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cant stand the heat get out of the kitchen. #HarryTruman  https://t.co/rOdeY7Dzd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 My late father was a CEO who had gone hungry for days during the Depression. For that reason, he'd… https://t.co/2Od7Z3PkRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was a no brainier. Crazy what college coaches look for now a days. Sorry he did not fit into the prototype of wh… https://t.co/DUf3dYddbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When conducting a #LooneyTunesScienceProject, it's imperative to only use ACME products. https://t.co/tWZl4dTIkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 159. Senior night @ Kennett High School (New Hampshire) https://t.co/0R4fVrmvqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runnerantics @RunVermont Nice hamster 🐹 mill miles Sam.  #HappySaturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t remember hearing about the take a listener on your family vacation contest 👀🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilled brisket salad today with @Urban_Carto &amp; other great city staff! Surpringly good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciation post for my baby cuz she’s sick and I miss her 😢 https://t.co/FuVsI2ha8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akachela When I lived in Seattle/Tacoma we would always seem to get Paul McCartney and the rolling stones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aspensound @cgarro @Illustrator I still miss the 3D distort tool they had. And paste inside which makes masking in Ai look stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i changed my number so people can stop coming in and out of my life. it will be on me now on who i give my new number to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Robert Kraft using a university issued cellphone?   Gotta get the burner, bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariadorosario Can President @jairbolsonaro promote Rio's carnival to the world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer is for winners. #SeldomSober - Drinking a Bodhizafa by @GeorgetownBeer @ Temple Billiards  — https://t.co/DchgCjUBmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocaCola Best bottling company in the world!!! 12 years for me and counting....... #cocacolastrong #lakecharles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSheilaZ @JoelOsteen @TDJakesShow @CopelandNetwork I just asked not long ago how can Christians be a member of… https://t.co/Ve82S60B4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stuntin for my babies at home!!! #wearethecaspers #vloglife #miltownsfreshest #maaanidowork #idowork @ Mystic Marri… https://t.co/3IS8Mo0gn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggc_dfs @DFS_Karma What plays do you like tonight? I think my favorite is Young 18.5 points over and Paul 8.5 assists over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asfan91 @SamsungMobileUS @BestBuy @BestBuySupport @verizon @Samsung I just got the email its delayed officially. I… https://t.co/cEEkYojK5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tokenwhitedude It’s good but I’d say Workingmans Friend and now Daredevil Hall are better. IMO]]></document></documents></author>