<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@XxSwitchGamerxX @TTfue Hops back into d2 with season of the drifter for gambit prime and finds tfue and lupo ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkhos Why don’t you answer my question. Why are 2012 town cars still on black car system in San Diego. You made a… https://t.co/sp9JJeRxpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its too bad this idiot couldn’t get down there in time to catch it with her forehead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvCoRadio The ones that are his "boys" do, but for the most part, I think that most of his teammates tolerate him...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did the First Lady turn down your request for anal again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesús te amamos  Cuanto te amamos  Y te adora  Nuestro corazón   @bethelmusic https://t.co/gzXSdhoSvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still listen to the Into the Spiderverse OST all of the time. Always helps my mood no matter what.  https://t.co/nD6ygov1lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rafat Only if one is engineered as well. Most of them seem cheaply built (and lousy capacity).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSteveVander @TheNoahRing @AOC What about Omar ??? You need work in getting her the Hell outta there!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I felt + still feel bc there was no lasting physical harm, bc I have the most pro-gay parents you could imagine who… https://t.co/YFOLgmSURs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Huskyteer Enjoy! That’s my home state. And where you‘ll be has plenty of history from then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And you don’t crap without checking with your daddy Putin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AskAMillionaire Mentor Livestream Videos:  Justin Curatola 9/27/2018 https://t.co/SAwjebkX9i via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbirch15 You mean, my apartment that only my parents have been in? The one with a bed, chair, tv that I never watc… https://t.co/iw5qmyDYaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Trebek’s cancer battle. One local expert explains why pancreatic cancer is so difficult to fight, and the prog… https://t.co/ZGFc6J1WfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REaPRagone @JohnOberg I want tocry when I see this. And when I think of all the people who pay people who torture… https://t.co/ibSbnB0RfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[napkins ✨ linen cotton canvas in modern prints @ Frankie &amp; Coco PDX https://t.co/k7qBu77Wbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nunyabiznasbro @RepDanCrenshaw I've researched.  seen records.  You can't even state the most recent whites in Ame… https://t.co/Dj2fz7VXRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because the foolishness of God is wiser than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men.” 1 Corinthians 1:25 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyPrincess and #MyGoodness are tired today. :) @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/D1wc2hUQWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelStudios I read where the star advised it wasn't a movie for white men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“... performance hall that can transform into any of five vastly different stage/audience configurations — ranging… https://t.co/K77VDGfBVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @Lakers @JHarden13 Ain’t is not a word. You’re a journalist, do better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikey_Wagz You fell because you had to run for your life cuz a cheetah was chasing you haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moving the widget didn't effect it, I had to remove and re-add the widget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support this. Push for alternative energy in California. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy$]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry Gibb: The last Bee Gee goes it alone https://t.co/gok4KQUTmI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wjband I like it cause J’ville beat SIU 90-54 at home on January 12th. Don’t think the change of venues is going t… https://t.co/ORJRAUSa90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow The two guys who said they did it, the video of them purchasing the rope and hoods, the receipts,… https://t.co/H4kxP45rVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braswell’s making this 2-3 wing defender thing look easy. Excellent at reading NCST’s guards. He’s been impressive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGRTeams @704NASCARHeat @KyleLarsonRacin @KurtBusch @MonsterEnergy @gearwrench From the west coast of California w… https://t.co/L3CdRz2V1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl’s Night Out at the Castle, and my magic student Marissa Arciero CRUSHES Real Magic for the first time at the f… https://t.co/TZvzpKHI3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein But your vote doesn't seem to make a difference to the climate wars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy that #BlackHistoryMonth has been extended to March!  Let’s make it happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwj5596 @JB1544 you got the wrong idea of what I'm saying. I'm saying he can hoop and skill wise is a great scorer… https://t.co/y8gFqTk2mO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satisfying everyone at #cafedalsacenyc lidiaceseri @sdorewine aviramturgeman @ Cafe d'Alsace https://t.co/ib2Txfo21O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatetofly What a cutie pie.  Parenthood is not for the faint of heart.  That’s for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWIPE LEFT TO SEE THE PANORAMIC SHOT OF DOWNTOWN LA ! .  📸 @canonusaimaging 📸 @canonusaimaging 75-300 .. 300mm… https://t.co/rNMHzvdLKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastianbach @UltClassicRock Skid Row in Philly. Killing it at the Spectrum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom Sell it anyway you want to but we know it’s her obedience and indoctrination in Sharia and the Hadith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard My thoughts are...let all liberals get so depressed by Trump that they break the law so they all will g… https://t.co/5v5pPUyQ5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy never wanted to play again. If he did he would have been on the field 2 seasons ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattRogersTho @brandonSJ Matt Rogers—you are a gem. (Also, sexy AF. And super talented. But that’s beside the poin… https://t.co/HY6lAuXbpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[For International Women's Day I want to recommend just one book series that all fantasy readers need to read it's J… https://t.co/ljkoYSc2Dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[$9 for this bomber and it’s well worth it! - Drinking a Danish Metal by Amager Bryghus/@jesterkingbeer @ Sith Templ… https://t.co/Hah7exG4yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in the comments actually think that Mitch is serious about passing this. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[PEOPLE n AMERICA didn't @RepJimJordan just say not to long ago Ohio was one of the fastest growing State in Manufac… https://t.co/f59cMLhjPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felipe_J_H @QuancyClayborne I used "Literally" when I should have said "figuratively." Thank you for the correction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to Spring Break! A great morning hike with @LaurieYantis  No Better weather in the country than Phx, Az… https://t.co/xRSWNjKPq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que ignorancia, quien lo hizo? Quién lo revisó? No les digo, responsables de cuarta, que esperaban. 🤓 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late dinner with great friends! @ Turtle Jack's Etobicoke https://t.co/WC1ijL4rRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigCackChris @xNorfTownRebelx @WordofJ @thereyesmark @Jbeck73 @JFowlerESPN @AntoniettaESPN Stats don’t lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also taking a bite of a chicken nugget and a sip of sprite at the same time to chew them together is something I did a lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPEACH RASHIDA TLAIB - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/LvZyhp1nXs via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blur In Stereo by @FieldworkBrewCo at @brasstap — https://t.co/YlC2DQhAgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeRdzNL Neta neta me asombra donde está enfocada tu preocupación ... Que pena para eso querías ser el gobernador ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronDayton Listening to it now at my desk actually.  The one that is standing out for me right now is "Into The… https://t.co/cz9EP7W1zz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legit tagging everyone I can remember  .... I just have to give shout out to everyone from tonight’s stream, all th… https://t.co/WjZXRA5b9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC!  lookin for something to do tonight?  head over to the Financial District and catch @RynoMusicNYC and i at the… https://t.co/B0EPyqfLQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmplifyPhilly @GNageshRao @djjazzyjeff215 @DjAktive @joshbwc @wxpnfm @sxsaviors @SXUnofficial @SXSWHIPHOP @atxconcert @OpenBarATX 🙋🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24To23 @ILoveChubNoHomo It was like 65-70 degrees but in class it's colder because the AC is broken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwaggyB_23 @DanTown22 Yea, I’m saying that’s his choice and good for him. The Sox made an offer that protects them… https://t.co/kpSRuCU3zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Anti American enemy of the people. https://t.co/Y9x1e6Dt5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it’s because #TheMasters starts exactly one month from today... But today is the day I officially got really… https://t.co/RcnJl5fc9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neon dreams #gassaver @ Bakersfield, California https://t.co/BhHHorMhO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottcross23 @NickdelaTorreGC Him &amp; @judfabe . These boys have some talent!! 🐊⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Gee, only 37 indictments and it is not over!!! Did you know that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordan_Kuehne There is gonna be a whole lot of quality coaching in that film room this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaylaRimpson Tell him you only date men. U already have 3 kids.... .lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever journey you’re on, I hope you find what it is you’re looking for  It’s all love]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marincin and Oshiganov will be good for a -3 tonight what is Babcock thinking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yandreaya No one:  Yandreaya: YOU CUT ME OFF IN A GARBAGE TRUCK. DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW HARD IT IS TO CUT SOMEON… https://t.co/Ap8C7dSsng]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only place he's athletic is a wrestling mat, but smooth stuff from my man @josh_jonesss here 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clmorganwx Meanwhile another rainy day in Western NC. #ncwx https://t.co/98PN6cANdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to invest in @Boeing great value right now. Lion air had maintenance issues and Ethiopia crash had witness see… https://t.co/eKN1k4WAMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney is so beautiful!!! The land of Pandora is amazing @ Pandora-The World of Avatar At Disney's Animal Kingdom https://t.co/AkDBoQ3OFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KweeenieB That’s possible. We always took our kids and had to do early August.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyalkon But I'm sure no "parent" has ever "used" a child to do anything harmful to anyone else. You never know. #trolling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammmi17 It may be real to some level but there’s way more to each of these story’s.!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well renowned storyteller Beth Rebert (tonight as the Wolf in the three little pigs story) entertains students and… https://t.co/GY0PXI3h2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonathan Kelly's defense counsel Mike Bianucci says he will call two witnesses to the stand]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of the Second Sight episode of @HDTGM is that everyone from the audience KILLS the Murray voice and it is legit joyous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corinadurann They were hella nice to me and we’re like   “that’s dope that you like their music and not many guys… https://t.co/3RIvF8PaT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REALAli99999 @RobJayHerc @ABCNetwork @starwars To be real, no movie is finished by the time the first trailer come… https://t.co/17lSYJNh0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmused1 @willyerasmus @danroodt @MaxduPreez Hy is ‘n left wing joernalis soos amper al die joernaliste hier in ame… https://t.co/gCDAAQYjwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottD_redox @Canderson012 No need to marry! #DomesticPartner #DontDiscriminate]]></document><document><![CDATA[s/o @Ableton for this beautiful instrument. let’s work @joekay ! @Soulection !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is pay day and I'm going to be pampered with @SasiahHochle! This is my before picture of the mani/pedi!  This… https://t.co/thsolnD1Bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hearted that just about every complaint I’ve received has come from LSAT members or concerned parents. They say… https://t.co/FvKPisJVT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity at it's best. ecard, rotten ecard, ecards, funny ecards, women know ecard https://t.co/XQt6q1Mex5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHenryTigersFB @NorthHenryFB @Coach_Sticks stick don't know about this...😛😛😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll believe it when I see it, but it has been quietly Dolan has been more detached from the team since the Phil er… https://t.co/6xV1YalENH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or perhaps, another chance to lose. Let's be real. The country is a giant, complicated and measured group of people… https://t.co/zFkwxa9U8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealOpFlint @TinehAgent @thejenlife I would never confirm or deny. I have noooooooo idea 😇🤫]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason jeph and I are so compatible is cause I refer to football players as “the tall man” who “scored that tou… https://t.co/VaeS9ZSU0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream job. Scouting for parking lots and places to provide our services. #parking https://t.co/OSvfiq0TYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tony Reali and Ash Wednesday. A tradition like no other https://t.co/NlLgwthqp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very respectful player right here. Keeps matching me and backing out on purpose so I can’t play anymore @HazeeHype https://t.co/MHaOEg6GAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first sentences: ‘Elements of the 2016 British referendum campaign have long seemed familiar to Americans. Ther… https://t.co/mPcGJNQIUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at West - Pat O'Brien Chevrolet - @patobrienchevy in Westlake, OH https://t.co/IES9zRvHxT]]></document></documents></author>