<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie Yes! Indeed! Now convince the other members of your Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck Y'all, Fuck HBO and Fuck them wack ass grimy ass fuckers. If it's true how come yall testified when yall were… https://t.co/wj2ZRJHrXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[V happy that college baseball is back bc basketball is slowly coming to an end 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize the guy who plays Danny on Blue Blood was part of the group #NKOTBonGMA 😱😱😱 https://t.co/kaCuvhhCyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Big Love by @shewantsrevenge on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/3W3Oj3NAp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Great Poetry Race is full steam ahead! Fluency made fun! #FlippningForFlipgrid #Smarties #SeasOfAdventure… https://t.co/KvTHxvufuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgarciapruneda @vanesaoyervidez Amo que la combinación haya salido tan bien😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potitos68 Gracias por tus palabras, solo fui un instrumento para sacar lo mejor de ti. Y tienes mucho que dar toda… https://t.co/3uBWdc81YY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My newest #weightlossjourney #YouTube #video is up!  #youtuber #fitness #weightloss https://t.co/hN4rlEr5cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witchmoon131 @AlliedProgress @SecretaryAcosta Come on Witchmoon13. Both Crooked Clinton’s had many more nastiness… https://t.co/51kExx7paE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an overnight staff duty last night and every phone call that came in was about a drunk soldier. I just wish I… https://t.co/FU16SlxYZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anonymous - What You're About to See Will Scare You! https://t.co/7qzh9nca2B via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our sixth grade girls! They played hard all season. Division 1 championship game next weekend. #CYO… https://t.co/vIqAboIlJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The office is closed but there's still work to be done. Gonna step away for fresh air then tackle the last items on… https://t.co/7bnurDg78M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov. Ned Lamont has called for revamping Connecticut's sales tax system, offering a budget plan that would impose t… https://t.co/IgYl8qBXfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got up... and I made coffee for the first time since Friday - I'm about 50% better. But at least I can walk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just purchased my @wbnptbo #WomenInBusiness Awards ticket. Get yours before they sell out! Don’t forget to nominate someone too]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling you get when one of your “graduates” comes back to say hello and he misses you. 😢😘 Love ‘em all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History March 5th 1963 - Hula-Hoop patented On this day in 1963, the Hula-Hoop, a hip-swiveling toy that b… https://t.co/k0VE2FjlGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlonthefield VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥… https://t.co/5VSGuGM4iA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going back home to Texas soon than i thought! I’m gonna surprise my mama 💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crawdaddy12374 Yes it was traumatizing I have never thrown my phone so fast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make a plan to vote and let’s finish this race! #PhxMayor #TeamKate https://t.co/YfZXI65XkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@411fromdownund1 @yashar She said she wants universal health care, not Medicare. She is practical...she said Medica… https://t.co/RqO5BWsN1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Blessed Day! @willylevy29 @WlwBolivia @WLW_Arizona @WLW_Cuba @WLW_EGYPT @WLW_ElSalvador @WLW_GRECIA… https://t.co/0v3ubb60Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan with over 2.7 million people followed by Turkey (2.5 million), Pakistan (1.6 million) and Lebanon (1.5 milli… https://t.co/bFWGkKQPN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoGonzales_  so happy for you that you’re on the mound opening day!! 😘⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a little late but in honor of international women’s day i thank and celebrate all us Ladies both past and pres… https://t.co/1vkmXyg8yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankScottJr @CityLittleRock @LRpolice @littlerockfire Glad everyone was okay 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASHLEYFERNET no te metas en pleitos internacionales si no sabes sarcasmo internacional ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is our solution for cabin fever- build an igloo! The entry way is larger than it should be to take in our back… https://t.co/PtBQSqpWi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If it walks like a duck quacks like a duck looks like a duck it’s bribery your a lying fat pig!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I think abortions should be illegal, I also believe planned parenthood shouldn’t be shut down. They offer other… https://t.co/vgWyFSprR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stayguam @Jim_Jordan @DsOchoa True! #DeplorableJordon #BlueWave2020 https://t.co/eXOIWRIwjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ill never be okay with how much money it costs to *try* and make money 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let this be a lesson to all... do not store your adult beverages behind a door, you might forget they are there. Al… https://t.co/83wHI3TE3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 7 titles there is something here for every avid, beginning and undiscovered reader in you.  #CauzingElevation… https://t.co/ubVsC5cNRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beanson40358184 @ANTHONYBLOGAN If this enormous conservative-leaning but independent voting bloc actually votes, c… https://t.co/nwOOdGPMPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Are you Trumps new muscle now? Pathetic. But we know that's how you roll. What are you… https://t.co/EhghVx4HXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This interview is fantastic, @usminority. The country needed you! #LifeLibertyandLevin #WalkAway @marklevinshow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisoniseman I’m upsettie spaghettie that I cant go to the New York show to meet u 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing but positive energy in my life rn and I’m honestly feeling so good, no time for negative shit or drama I’m over it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer  Win $10 Roblox Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up,    Sign Here:… https://t.co/bLd3PwIK6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angelo T. Robinson #atrfineart @ San Francisco Coffee Roasting Co. https://t.co/cQ3P9LUtkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volunteer at your local animal shelter; it will make you feel good. Your kindness and caring will help an animal ge… https://t.co/qQt75CsNGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need a little help with that resting B face this Monday Morning?... Lady says “no worries!... swipe left!” Let’s ge… https://t.co/2kBQDOoE0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought winter killed the stink bugs? One just literally landed on my forehead while i was laying here]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sister’s dog is having a better birthday party than I’ve ever had and my parents flew to Chicago for it so there’s that]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday was February 14th and I am still getting 🍷🥤🍱🍸🍾🥂🍹🥡🥢fucked up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can attest to Jacquie's badassery - so happy I get to work with her and for an org that does so much good in such… https://t.co/0AAgkmdJ2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self taping a slate at dinner. Sometimes they ask last minute, cuz they probably needed it yesterday!  #doitnow… https://t.co/OvDYqHQNwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnochNawahine @USUFootball @MikeSanfordUSU @CoachCollinsUSU LesssssGooooo! Bring that game to AGGIE NATION!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really tired of people treating me less than how I treat them or at least try to treat them ! People get away w… https://t.co/PGs6BEJLJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting #vacation right !! #playadelcarmen #dreamtrip #withmylove ❤️ #nailtech #cannonfallsnailtech 💅🏻🥰✈️😊 @ Delta… https://t.co/IprO4HpEYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is in the air! Wishing you a peaceful Sunday morning where ever you are. If you are still stuck in the cold,… https://t.co/A9BcRZ6ARY]]></document><document><![CDATA[World #earthquake forecast, 5.0-9.0 Mag, 200km radius. See https://t.co/RqBRl60J9J via @TheRealS0s Paita District,… https://t.co/IPRVcP9Abj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreinMD @RealMAGASteve @fitzie63 The deep state is our worst enemy n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes having a 4 year old means I get to revive long-lost skills. I can definitely draw things that look like t… https://t.co/HaQY8a4go9]]></document><document><![CDATA[yooo i can tell my butt is getting bigger and tummy getting flatter &amp;&amp; my skin is getting clearer 😻🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcpeay It’s similar in Northern Utah. It was extremely frustrating to talk to anyone about history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @jidk1187 @amandadeibert @CatStaggs @ashleyn1cole @cmclymer @docrocktex26 @carolineframke… https://t.co/iAZyBuXMu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to judging this weekend at the 2019 Southeastern Mock Trial Regional hosted by UCF! #AMTARegional… https://t.co/1LAAZkiki7]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone have a backpacking backpack I can borrow uhh right now for the next two weeks? I’m desperate thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what? Sometimes life just comes at ya fast and says, “You’re a dumb bitch!” And that’s that on that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to know how much I love Tiana, I had the most stressful shift of my life today but I RAN to my apar… https://t.co/HcqUs3PTBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need another reason to look forward to warmer weather? This spring, 7 million Americans will experience @sprint's… https://t.co/QQcd95nR8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unifor6006HR @UniforWomen @UniforHR4All @UniforTheUnion @MediaUnifor @nbeardunifor600 Always love to see pics of u… https://t.co/g0whmcLLco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secularcitizen2 @Helenhs @JoeBiden Not voting Dem NO MATTER WHO is a vote for trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klept_hoemania I can’t take the shenanigans of drag race https://t.co/WaexHZrfX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops, it looks like I have overlooked one little thing that is turning 💯 this year, and that happens to be a certai… https://t.co/3DIg9e8MLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@herrmanndigital Exhibit A on why this is soooo true:   https://t.co/Ba74kZ25Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 DAYS!  WE ARE ALMOST IN SINGLE DIGITS! Preorder now to have Heart of the Devil waiting for you on your e-reader… https://t.co/VBbBoLZqOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then you just gotta rap either Trick Daddy’s or Trina’s verse on “Naan Nigga” to your significant oth… https://t.co/BUdoTeod4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contortion Delight   Never ending stretches of imagination  Graceful in dark and light  Touching the heart of one… https://t.co/h9a8f48UfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMcKimney @MassKURoyal @alpipkin @KimberlyMrsRR1 @weaselzippers Just can't stand that creepy Kamala Harris 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slide displaying the differences between traditional court and treatment court https://t.co/mXJRFm5CoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look at @RepSwalwell braving the snow to walk TWO WHOLE BLOCKS for coffee. https://t.co/c6a3mKy27D]]></document><document><![CDATA[&lt;3 #dreamgirls #onenightonly #missyouoldfriend https://t.co/QKz1ZprMRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep seeing videos from judging at #SND40 but just can’t get into it this year when so many newspapers are shedding… https://t.co/f5SWS2b628]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/5A3vWFZFgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna say it. Everyone out there saying Miranda Priestly is a bitch in Devil Wears Pravda? Fuck you! She’s a fa… https://t.co/tlLu6Nd3hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We dove deeper into our guiding question to better understand how we as Southern CA residents get our water when we… https://t.co/QFIxzV2Atv]]></document><document><![CDATA[at this point, snap flashbacks just make me realize how different of a person i am today than i was two years ago.… https://t.co/Jj5JIHDNZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can only hope that kid turns out healthy because the mom leaves his crusty father]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember these names when it’s time to vote😡. Evil will not win!! #votethemout #AllLivesMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Top_Sergeant You know Trump just pulled funding to protect our elections the same day we learned Manafort gave Rus… https://t.co/ecDTykUohg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/OrgkwHxE3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most who dream of their loved ones who have passed report being comforted by them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m this sore after hippie I’m worried to see how sore imma be after buku 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@O_Monah @Kandi a mini @tylerperry stay creating something and keep others employed #MoneyMaker]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 fight Tamara walk the dogs 🐕 on hercand season her at the same time 😂 https://t.co/xJqjGSMWX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I accept Cash or Credit Card with ID ” I’m available in Atlanta right now! https://t.co/yYb84NDgzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be thinking way to much at night , where my anxiety wants to mess with me 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[De acuerdo a datos de @Banxico el año pasado se disparó la cant de piezas de billetes y mon falsificadas. Acá les d… https://t.co/gLgkgenJcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudes will lie to your face &amp; then catch an attitude like he’s telling the truth 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We started Crazy Hat day off right with our annual Pancakes with the Principal breakfast. So fun (and delicious!)… https://t.co/sCODtyqzU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkamaro @steph93065 @LindaSuhler @NBCPolitics @CNN No, Russia is all about weaponized media. That’s the kool aid a… https://t.co/B2ew2JOsLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just accidentally chewed a multivitamin tablet... it was not a chewable ... nastiest thing ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[#essentialoilraresale  This kit is worth over $420?!?!!   See my bio for my website link ❤️ @ Los Angeles, Californ… https://t.co/IHD4uN9jXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need to know when are we going to start considering our dogs as “dependents” on our tax returns..🤷🏼‍♀️🐶]]></document></documents></author>