<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Kiddo loves Chick Fil A.  Kiddo was a little miffed when I bought nuggets for the dog.  I went to lunch with my fri… https://t.co/DqznXM6M9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamHincapie it was so exciting seeing the men last night at Tour of Southern Highlands in Woodstock Ga dominate t… https://t.co/eADED4W8g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support for “Soaking the Rich” Is Rooted in #MediaMisinformation -  #MediaBias #WalkAway https://t.co/fSbBk6aJd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get @RepAdamSchiff ! Please get on this show and set Hannity straight with REAL Truth !]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay seriously it’s 6am and i got woken up by someone blaring music ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pondering these amazing words this morning: “Others were given in exchange for you. I traded their lives for yours… https://t.co/c9zPG890fK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NASSAU, #Bahamas (CMC) — The Bahamas government says it has temporarily ceased all deportations to #Haiti as a res… https://t.co/ZWnKVE1Ejr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uranusthegod @TheGodOfDeathA1 Check out @Uranusthegod’s Tweet: https://t.co/lIFfXKKQcN Oh yes. Such improvement]]></document><document><![CDATA[My vocal range is from D2 to an F5. I plan on working on that and making it a lot better. I’m gonna beat Freddy Mer… https://t.co/tKXbojyetx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyParton @BTS_twt Why not collab with ventriloquism, her puppet, Farmer Bunny, and best friend @aliciabarnachea… https://t.co/Y4kaWi3syd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asistí en representación de nuestro Secretario @sepycsinaloa @juanmejia_mzt al inicio de la Primera Semana Nacional… https://t.co/M23yRSv6gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate when i have such an intense crush on someone that i’m over here googling our star sign’s compatibility https://t.co/Z76uYkWK0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWhitTwit Same here Amanda. True love = “I’ll listen to whatever crap you’re spewing as long as you do the same fo… https://t.co/27e64yMTjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indonesia hires Saudi-backed firm to build development with Trump "elements." Money has and will change hands in th… https://t.co/cMrbZKDXnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the lazy world of deconstructing foods that take effort into easy soups.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK, So it’s 5am here and for some reason I’m up ( just woke up) so my dumb butt decided to check YouTube AND WHY DI… https://t.co/Xe2OoKM5uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished editing my soon to be published book while on a flight. Forgot to prepare my face from weeping before the… https://t.co/npCEo6E5dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga is SO talented and So beautiful. she was my childhood, I listened to her 24/7 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate these amazing women this Sat Mar 9! #madonnasummermusic returns to #faultlinebar! • Magical all-Madonna a… https://t.co/ARV4VIFsFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dodson_Here @AcademicChatter Where do you currently work? Or do you do freelance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys who react like this know they’ve been jerks to women all their lives y las pobres hijas son las que la llevan.… https://t.co/T7VIxujHNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoehcarney @Whataburger Lol thats funny. For some reason just this week I have had a hankering for them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised @JessicaLynnDill that people take more pics of furbabies than spouse!!! Our babies are cuter 😂😂… https://t.co/DMfCKf1BrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And long story short my younger siblings and I all went on to become who we are today; college graduates, mentors,… https://t.co/bre7IJgcGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@exclamate_ you know who you are. your love’s as sweet as candy. I’ll be forever yours. love always. mandy]]></document><document><![CDATA[pre-existing conditions are already subject to discrimination-through drug pricing and insurance coverage condition… https://t.co/QIqlzEUQ0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiversongMS @PETAUK They can't get away w/doing that legally in the UK like they can here. They don't have a UK sh… https://t.co/2LDiqaGuTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say I’m jealous of all these snow days northern Az is getting? Phx is expecting 1/2 to 1 in of rain and… https://t.co/T7cCcRCVbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manistique Area Schools will be on a two hour delay Thursday, February 21st]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salmonprotocol @GadSaad @KamalaHarris @SenWarren Go crawl back under the moldy rock you've been living under. Peop… https://t.co/Kraf7Xntxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xx__maryalex @essextwo It doesn't get much more heavily seasoned than that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mac_franny @OccupyYouriPod She did not but she does now!  Damn near enough to make me try cooking again! https://t.co/F7IGSGZ8Qv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Party. But at least she learned to not be so trustful. Cause they threw her under the bus. Yes she had her legs und… https://t.co/XYQyacRfpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like a good chunk of my life is spent asking food-service workers to remake my meal because it has cheese. #diaryofapickyeater 🚫🧀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kayleigh Williamson!!! You are a true inspiration to us all!!! Congratulations, you are a brave little girl! You ar… https://t.co/qiHh9SBr1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO WHO IS LOOKING FORWARD TONIGHTS TWD??? I SURE AM I PUT JESUS SINCE HE WAS THE LAST ONE TO DIE 🥺🥺😢😢😢 R.I.P JESUS… https://t.co/q4oisBPNaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[la espiga dorada bakery 210 W Martin Luther King Jr St Bryan, TX 77803   ur welcome, aggie twitter https://t.co/gUkneez2lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Happy Women's Day..!! #InternationWomensDay #WomensDay https://t.co/9aIurVRT8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when @NiaJaxWWE said this in a interview: “Our bodies are always going to change, and we might not always lo… https://t.co/aE96tNXX52]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the award for most strange phone call of the week goes to the person telling me they own a dingo. https://t.co/nt5AmqlC75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCNews Come on most of these kids poo hasn't turned from yellow to brown and yet some daft jock is going to liste… https://t.co/ohaZEAIVPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newest viral internet challenge is throwing slices of cheese at your baby with the #cheesed. Why.... https://t.co/zeK8bSCABx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Commission is discussing whether the age for this ordinance should be 21, or lowered to 18. Under the current o… https://t.co/1gIqQzRwiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronCRPepper Did you forget to get Bekah her Texas Independence Day gift?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand how people will create drama over the internet for simple accidents. Some people are just so ignorant 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think you  are being funny- I don’t hear anyone laughing... well... some— laughing at you not with you. It’s… https://t.co/2Cilc2vx1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[you and me together feels more like forever than anything i’ve ever known]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview for a job right now I hope i get it. Its been too long not working I miss it and need out of the house. Wish me luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Air bnb is so annoying they won’t let me pay the other half of the room right now 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we’re talking about HEALTH and NUTRITION in class today  I GOT THIS I KNOW THIS lesssgoooo !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi  please get your priorities straight.  You are a @realDonaldTrump hater.  Admit it. Please work on t… https://t.co/Tnhn7ZJZrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarnetteJason @Amyfitzgeraldgo @switchbackkids @KidsInParks @ParksandPoints @NP_Geek @fullvanfun Yes!! Roaring For… https://t.co/c55wSZ0b8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to a future when my daughter can proudly be described aggressive and my son as gentle! #BiasCorrect… https://t.co/c8ee5wQet1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaqqerdz Café! No hay nada mejor. Y si te gusta con azúcar, a mí no, pues ya está, aún mejor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude he's got a check with your signature on it that you signed last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Whitaker u sure look like a guilty LIER Not answering Rep.Val Demings question. How in the world do u let urse… https://t.co/o1egVI7O6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEmSchulz @xtineschiefer @EWGrosss Can we get a 2nd show in Charlotte or maybe an Atlanta show in the works? Jus… https://t.co/p8ZRvUcrlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patty_guynn @MissINTJ @TNBeanCounter @EWErickson In your opinion; others do find it a desecration. And I wouldn’t… https://t.co/8MFKrIIgvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was looking at you and you was looking at me wooo wa wooo wa wooo🤣  Go Damascus go Damascus 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I cannot hear you when you are whistling SO LOUDLY past that graveyard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolelindsayy @ColinSherman How could I not know when it was literally just HIS NAME🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper U R one lousy American as you seek to conflate BS. Why do you keep leaving out all the monies that are coming in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momjeansplease I get paid in crypto. In real life. My checks come from India.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi @honoretmarais OH EM GEE YOU ARE LITERALLY THE BEST AND I LOVE YOU AND I HOPE TO SEE YOY SOON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richieg11661 @joeycham72 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump I doubt this would ever happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, really? I hope you never really face a devastating or terminal illness to know what it is really like! Your ac… https://t.co/FM9fAATbAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets It’s on the way from the Aurora Colorado Police Departmemt 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussD__ @_thatboyace_ I don’t eat rice cakes either. It just doesn’t seem appetizing to me. But I’m not judging yo… https://t.co/W93BVvUSIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eplacentia @RandiK125 @Salon Do you know how to have a conversation without 🤬?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤗 . . . . . . . #bathroomselfie #simplestyle #simplayny #longisland #casualstyle #keepingitsimple #targetstyle… https://t.co/yj4WNrDE10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile I need a little something to get through Valentine’s this year! #TMobileTuesdays❤️ #contest]]></document><document><![CDATA[A winter sunrise ☀️❄️🌊🥶 #silive #anbaardolino #ny1pic @NYCParks @NY1 @NY1weather #WinterIsHere  #winter  #snow .… https://t.co/8bzJW0PsWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re MY Captain Marvel.” — Charlie 🐾 @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/3hVuP3oJeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I just read that this retail- innovation conference, @shoptalk that I'll be at this week will have over ONE T… https://t.co/90xPEYeEsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keyahboo I mean Kylie ain’t no better. She’s done the same thing on multiple occasions. Birds of a feather....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the night ends, I want to wish my love MARIA a freaking happy birthday , I LOVE HER SO MUCH 💞❤️ @maria_ngc]]></document><document><![CDATA[just cause you’re young attractive and spending money doesn’t mean i owe you my snapchat fuck off douche bag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjoa5 My kid’s happy indeed! Now he’ll be walking around the house not knowing what to do with himself 😂 Thank you… https://t.co/VhK9OsAMk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[50% of brands do not have a social media strategy. @smwatx #smwatx https://t.co/6jHex67uwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There IS a lot of explaining to do, from the people that actually voted you into office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueMoonGoon88 @amandasapp91 you are VERY good at this and i love that about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[In life, if you have 2-3 people you can rely on 100% of time, trust your life to and know they’ll always have your… https://t.co/77nGA4zyim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christineestima lord, don't lead me down this path. nearly wrote something vulgar that were the next line of lyric… https://t.co/s5RiT25dxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[social media's got me addicted to excessive validation &amp; it's pretty damn disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Lambert -- Elvis Presley All Star Tribute -- Blue Suede Shoes https://t.co/k9dasn97tu via @YouTube.  DAMN!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALMENTE podremos hacer tours del Ron del Barrilito en Bayamón. Se inaugura un Centro de Visitantes en la Haciend… https://t.co/wcKkY9vx9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karmalita98 I literally just told you that in the kitchen when you are ignoring me Karma 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all who shared their fortunes with us last night. We hope that all come true. @ The Box https://t.co/oegPrTavzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iPlayMarioKart That doesn’t answer the question. Did you watch the doc?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logizzl Lol thanks! I thought it was actually a lyric I didn’t know from her😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justsanaa Is this ur natural hair. Because u vut is bald n u were hook. Not bad now. Nut it grew fast. If its urs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieWSM @NashSportsRadio hope it’s a great day, proud of that group and all their accomplishments!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@covfefemalt45 @BettyBowers @PaulLeeTicks @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Aaaaand follow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s just a disgusting lie, you are going to get people killed you fcking nitwit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Morning_Joe @JoeNBC Really, you speak for this judge now? @solomonsarah122]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ApolloMission27 thanks love ❤️ Btw you were so amazing tonight! keep up the great work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen @miggiepdx Xi doesn't need him is right. I've watched NHK, Japan to the World, as my exclusive TV cha… https://t.co/XSlOEGu5NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_celia_bedelia_ My only accomplished impersonations:  Da-viiiiid In Alexis’ voice Alex-sisss In Moira’s voice  They both make me giggle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_Feldscher @leighmunsil I thought a juicer was a dumb thing to add to the registry, but can confirm that… https://t.co/cLqF7oYEzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taradublinrocks She should’ve locked his ass up ! But I’m sure he can’t keep his big mouth shut 🤐So he’ll be going to prison soon !]]></document></documents></author>