<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VirusesImmunity So true!! Trainees - Dr. Iwasaki is describing something that is very common and can be debilitati… https://t.co/f65UBfOlx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[While my whole family is at home on this Presidents’ Day I’m here at Franny 🙃 happy monday 😑😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secretagentkay @frmnjss @GovStitt Unfortunately, without the permitting system there is not mechanism to enforce t… https://t.co/aMklzeD3MX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught up with @Sprint’s Base Marketing team to chat about the #SprintNetwork, #5G, and how to provide the best net… https://t.co/StXvab0EAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang merry. 9 kinds of people to date while you're in your 20s https://t.co/LU7Vw00X3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I make piña colada 🍹smoothie then the snow melts (see its happening 👀) and spring 🌺 will come sooner . . What’s… https://t.co/151dOKA0oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We encourage publication with trainees. That’s called paying it forward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noah was so flippin’ happy! 💙He kept tapping me on my arm then giving a thumbs up! 👍🏼 The best was him singing the… https://t.co/uTkLWTo9E7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie already inherited millions by her family, so giving her the title of youngest “self-made” billionaire is honestly the dumbest thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's getting glam for the #Oscars ? :: Playing with kkwbeauty makeup for today's look! 📲See what I used on Stories… https://t.co/rBY7sx3ouc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re going to have to bring Hermione next time. #dogpark #brewdog #brewdogbrewery #brewdoghotel @ Canal Winchester… https://t.co/Vcwlrudk7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i have my blinker on and I’m trying to switch into your lane and you don’t let me best believe I’m gonna force myself even if we crash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im beating any bitch that fw my babydaddy 😂 y’all can have my first one NOT this one period 😂😂💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAttyHuber @doj So, when will you address the unbelievable corruption of the last admin.? I insist on a 2nd Speci… https://t.co/YtQAmhGppQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WorldBookDay! The sexiest bookstore in the world: Tsutaya Books in Tokyo. There’s multiple locations but Dai… https://t.co/bJtO8Szxev]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Computer Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/depXeqG4Uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedbeardCaptain @psykotronn Eh, some lessons you gotta learn the hard way. I'm better for it. ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Product Alert!!! . These 3D wood signs are perfect for a baby or child’s room. We will carry three sizes to cho… https://t.co/xArEOlvNrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t watch Game of Thrones. It’s a trap. You’ll become obsessed and then once you get to season 3, it’ll just let you down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing about DST I don’t like is how dark it is in the mornings again 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please give me their HBO account so I can stop watching game of thrones on putlocker ):]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just need a good cry. 💔😭#brokenheart #howdoesgesleepatnight #thenerveofthisguy #heleftmesoeasy… https://t.co/7wBNIK4Yp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy so after watching many shows of the real housewives and coming up to learning that you adopted your child I j… https://t.co/w7ZaLN0C5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[In twenty years we should have been rid of the last plane, according to Alejandra Ocasi- Cortez]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one cares! All the evil you are doing will come back on you. God will pour out his vengeance on you and the othe… https://t.co/e5HPeNp6sO]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, politics don’t belong in the exam room. Your latest attack on Title X forces health care centers… https://t.co/A80zkE7UYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all I might be obsessed with borrowing e-books from the library. All the joy of free books and none of the pain o… https://t.co/YXSRCu31M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @VP @StateDept @TheJusticeDept @Fbi @SecretService ; muslim Rep advocating overthrow of US govt? Retweet. Gl… https://t.co/Is0iok275Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephBKNY @SonySquareNYC @NKOTB @dannywood @DonnieWahlberg @jordanknight @joeymcintyre @JonathanRKnight Love!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕺come here and rest your feet 🦶🏻in your designer shoes 👢show off your tan 👩🏽let’s drink some booze 🥃Club 96 🍸our si… https://t.co/5j3s2mA7D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fail Pin Number - - Autocorrect Fails and Funny Text Messages - SmartphOWNED https://t.co/nCXlqG4YFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to hit those legs! Shorts weather will be here soon! @ American Barbell https://t.co/vcCpikYhMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zef999 @LP_LaPresse Des gens se plaignent que la Presse fait voir que ces fascistes torchent leur idéologie   dans… https://t.co/N5QxrpepCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Becoming a woman doesn’t happen overnight! It’s a process for which you have to be patient but it certainly worth t… https://t.co/ean92BbjXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[too young too dumb to realize, that i should have bought you flowers, and hold your hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SexMattersUK @drawnoutofshape Lol “mud slinging.” I have identified flaws with an ideology. I haven’t said YOU are… https://t.co/KXUMctxc2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanfideljohn @SonOfGodAndMan @AOC @hmcghee Which is exactly what I mean by adapting to climate change. We definite… https://t.co/2yk2d8Nr5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @nowthisnews for highlighting the work of doctors and surgeons in decreasing death from #GunViolence.… https://t.co/OadupAmdAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iam_Shug_ You absolutely should be - congratulations!!!! Hope you have a great day today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjj_kiLi Amen to that. My thoughts EXACTLY. Notice what she claims was taken matches Kyle's to a T.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliceglamoure , you were spectacular hosting #divineacelebrationofwomen  with inthewingsaerial  at the bouldercirc… https://t.co/FeZXry6cAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t going to happen! They are going to be spinning their wheels for the next 2 yrs! House Passes Bill To Enact Ma… https://t.co/2t0efj6vb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re playing “Seven Nation Army” and all I can think of is when they play it at Dodger Stadium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of last minute RSVPs coming through New York today, there is still time to register for tonight’s… https://t.co/tYmdWYAUjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever not talk to the person you like for one day and suddenly feel like the world is falling apart? Yeah, this… https://t.co/INZ5lCpfkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Maybe we could go to @snowbabyice today?” @ Snowbaby https://t.co/zSiCOoBmSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobMcNealy @AOC Right. Aoc needs to take a tiny salary, just enough to get by. No she'll instead get rich by us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACT: Ther's NO CRIME DONE BY ASYLUM SEEKRS ENTERNG OUR BORDERS AT ANY PLACE THEY ENTER! Yet PROFITEERNG REPUBLCNS… https://t.co/l5wbORDZ9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@watdez @antoinettegaga @gwenblakeinfo @NoDoubter2383 @jtwatson1978 @nodoubt @NxDMarkNxD Yah. True]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travysaurus_Rex @pipibongstockin @KaceyMusgraves @Bonnaroo making chloe wear my rodeo belt and boots now bc of thi… https://t.co/WVTUNJkF76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASlavitt If you win the lottery &amp; get a promotion on the same day 45 is “elected” it’s still a bad day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Night Thoughts While Sick:  The rain is such a comforting sound to me when I am cozy at home https://t.co/3AtgGqZ7U1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn more about our amazing products here by clicking here https://t.co/rQocTkhS0D Ready to order? Check out our p… https://t.co/po2BIjDvc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NytoSports Pues tú lo has dicho. Para que los lean, tienen que acudir al nombre de una figura pública que NADA tie… https://t.co/LfLlGEoqeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blog Vacation March 11-25, 2019 Be Back Tuesday, March 26, 2019 https://t.co/Kn0LhEMzUg https://t.co/UpD3j7sAQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to enter Good Morning America Studio. @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/5Sxi60oCah]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPECIALTY SATURDAY here at #4410, Hasan &amp; Terance Driving our Truly Free Carpet Install Program! #TEAM10… https://t.co/F5kuCL56LE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7covers7days books I ❤️! This book I am using today at the MCSD L3 PD! #SupportingELLs thx @GingerFeathers2  for c… https://t.co/pKgu1KNrLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because our CAST is FAMILY! We  are Earpers! @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment #WynonnaEarp back on our… https://t.co/M9zuO3IwHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abmorgan @RashidaTlaib @HouseDemocrats Thank gawd it won't pass in the Senate or @realDonaldTrump . Yeah just what… https://t.co/t4jQxZ9RRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is fantastic 4tuning in 2 ur inner self. Uwill have a grounded mind to make conscious evaluations of your emo… https://t.co/YqxuSeLjKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsirishM @Ryukennnnn Wala ka nang respeto sa ate mo https://t.co/ZTKtQDJ6op]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’m stuck watching RDR2 I’ve entertained myself by doing psychological evaluations on the characters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuniperUponHill @AndySchmiechen @sfdcgeek @SFOhanaCoffee @ericdresh @sfdc_tc See you tomorrow, right??]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #FacilitiesMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. General Utilit… https://t.co/k70cSUIa96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewhunterm Rent recording space and describe how immaculate everything is.  Recording: "Oh my god you can't see… https://t.co/PFIQ9ZDzVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[i say fuck pisces a lot but ive jst been reminded that im a pisces moon ,,,, much to think abt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EltonCastee got it!! And just wanted to say, the day I met you at warped tour was one of the best days of my life!… https://t.co/L88V9ZrV8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a little bit of the aqua fit class in at #districtfitwpb before the fancy child wanted to get into the hot tu… https://t.co/vUIyrzJqKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Lie.  No, I take that back.  His lies are the only transparent thing about him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IFiniq I haven't seen the reminders about the breakfasts going out on Twitter beforehand. Is that still happening?… https://t.co/OAbj4MIm3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a patient  person, I just wait on karmic retribution. 💕 #WhenIGetBulliedOnTwitterI https://t.co/B77atan0P2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered what became of fashion’s fallen angel, John Galliano? NP, he’s alive and designing at Maison… https://t.co/1M3vGuWQBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring it on #losangeles.  Skill development for the plane. #hollywood eyesofladywimbledon @ihrsa faster_function @… https://t.co/UYZDQGB3Cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornabrit1 He certainly doesn’t measure up to President Obama in more ways than one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i walked into Moye and there were SOOO many kids visiting ollu and now i’m sad bc they were so cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kisharich85 I will say a prayer that your doctors are great surgeons, praying for a successful surgery. And a quick healing IJN Amen 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Semaphore89 We will never go back to all abortion is illegal. The best we can do is say no abortion after fetal vi… https://t.co/1zPFvv6FNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE the little fluffer nutter hyena cubs and their squeaky toy noises!!!  #safariLIVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEAsuka I was at that show.  I’m glad you’re fine.  You definitely gave people a reason to worry]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AldineDistrict I’m not sure what to do. I’ve emailed and called and still Mr. Don White doesn’t seem to have to d… https://t.co/lMDfJ1jLYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna make fun of people who care about the newest Kardashian drama, but then I remembered that I religiously… https://t.co/mvUcxEDt9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s what? How many days into Pisces season and I’ve already had multiple meltdowns. Sweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarra_Smiles @MKristen105 @Jackson__Lauren @APSuperGray @lizzielu18 They are beautiful children!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Look: Spike Jonze and Jesse Williams Captivate In MedMen's New Cannabis Commercial https://t.co/HaXuxbNFcJ vi… https://t.co/TYFWXopFfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have learned that when a young sapling takes rise in the shade of older trees, these older trees use their root… https://t.co/2IQnvYxasP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnersKnights @klpebefit We live in a great country that does not make serving our country mandatory.  Yet brave… https://t.co/0xTNdzGsUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too funny!     Susan Clemens in Aliso Viejo, CA says, "I don't have... #mirth #chuckle #smirk #laughable https://t.co/eORmK3bw19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YesJulz @newburycomics @RipeTheBand not ug anymore but still the og boiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @armonandtrey  My vote goes to Ar'mon and Trey squad @armytroopssquad on IG @armonandtrey @iHeartRadio https://t.co/G6zzZXta5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nique2655 @costareports @NicolleDWallace He definitely is taking uppers; close up photos show his pupils. Undeniable!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[bakit hindi ko alam na uuwi pala ako this march? 😂🤦🏻‍♀️ mga chismosa talaga amp]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s lowkey so sad that Ariana feels the need to do this just bc of what happened in the past :( ugh I love her I j… https://t.co/tdHnZUyi5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@just_ainaa @ShawnMendes This was even better the second time watching!  @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElonsBrain @AvaSchadt @WadeAndersonPT @gas0linr @ElectricBun @28delayslater @KrisPicks64 @EliBurton_… https://t.co/a2BPESMwjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entienden ahora xq el autor dla lesiva #Chinchero en contra del Peru hecha x @MartinVizcarraC va contra vientos,son… https://t.co/hzSMemJ21v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just can't understand how anyone can believe this man after all of this nonsense.  My only thought is people are… https://t.co/u1mOqOvsnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaBrighid I'm thinking a big mushy ass kiss..the lower back looks nice...but the back of the neck would have to… https://t.co/nl9AyltzzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyJoLambert @TxASL @jdlaboon Thank you.Obviously there are some legislators that need to hang out in a school l… https://t.co/Jv7aGidBFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[People wonder why I don’t talk about my problems, it’s cause if I told you what I hold on my shoulders and what goe… https://t.co/13eGIT96Ck]]></document></documents></author>