<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MattNBCBoston Happy Meteorological Spring, Matt! (Although winter isn't ready to give up without a fight). Stoneha… https://t.co/26GdWEoDxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenstatsky It brought Parks and Rec’s Galentine’s Day into existence, that has to count for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McConnel_leads your the leader get your party together and vote with the president!! Americans want the damn wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CincyGuy2009 @DGarrigan9 It entertains me for some reason but I don't try to be competitive anymore. I enoy Apex b… https://t.co/4qY5bnHixY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Lets legalize it in all 50 states at local and federal levels and get it over with. Start collecting taxes on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure Trump supporters will pay just as much attention to the Trump-radicalized U.S. Coast Guard admiral who was… https://t.co/Ug7JYph8HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packing for weather in the 50’s, heavy snow, a wedding, hiking, and my camera gear, while trying to avoid a checked… https://t.co/Hd8mKc2eII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior @GraciousMachine What is the correct pronunciation of your name, Ms. Kendzior?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Holy Father. Remember Today Peter was married. It takes a special spouse to be married to a soldier for G… https://t.co/CJBwggL7aU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @SenWarren what have you got to say about this you three?… https://t.co/SincmW8lQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyCanas4 @GammaIotaSigma Funny Pizza never came up at Florida State when I spoke to RMI students. Maybe they don… https://t.co/vC88HnPPby]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st game of the season! Right now I wish I still lived in LA. #LAFC @LAFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReclaimIguana @patrickmooney25 @SlimChiefin @othagreat @RazerCallahan @jjcastaneda @chicagotribune No gotta go.  Acceptance of history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People ask yourself what if Fox News actually told the truth about Trump for one day every show from Fox and Friend… https://t.co/c1zleOt9aY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I fucking love @orey. We just convinced him to walk over and take another birthday shot at 3:45am. 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[First game in the books as a Rockwall Yellowjacket with a win 14-0!  #FigureItOut @ctyner09 @Rockbaseball https://t.co/dBB3VfRVCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way for The Shield to Shield Bomb Baron Corbin to victory this will definitely be the last time we'll ever s… https://t.co/gW2pK2gaSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch 2018 Highlander Banquet Introduction on @Livestream: https://t.co/9SvYz8SAXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need help; it’s Feb, and the #Knicks are gonna land ALL FAs known to man this summer but - - - -  In Dec you told… https://t.co/ktND2lN1uV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Wawa in @nj_glassboro turns into frat boy central after midnight.   No judgement. Just observation.   Sidenote… https://t.co/1JpO2BLHYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeeOhEmm @Tims_Burner @AlexMiniakPA @Twitch @PetcoPark @Padres @FisherCats @MLBTheShow @PlayStation https://t.co/xhZFLFbQJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inkedtoothfairy Thank you so much :) that means a lot. It’s gonna be a long road but we will be ok. I know we will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder They are going to have to prove themselves for quite awhile for me to return... no credibility!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I did this today at Lifetime after my workout!  14% Body Fat, hoping to get that to 12% by 60 Bday - 89 days to… https://t.co/0pC12YjLzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live Like Jesus died for you because he did and he rose again from the dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delucadan Dan, what are your thoughts regarding the lucrative estates (publishing, musicals, etc) of artists like… https://t.co/LYTHMh7xAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Barbs Migos x Sean Kingston - All I Got https://t.co/qvdfb2Gzuw via @YouTube  Put some respek on his name!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is crazy. So much good stuff. (@ Jungle Jim's Wine Department in Fairfield, OH) https://t.co/d3o4c7E0gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellen page is just another example of liberal” putting their mouth in gear before they put their mind in motion.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCF_FB_Facts @pleviner @SubDestroyer12 @NCAACWS @UCF_Baseball Why would I be crying when it’s not gonna do anything to our ranking?😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love you like I do  Choreography- @bobbynewberry  Dancing - @NatalySantiago4 @BroadwayDance #bdcnyc  🎥- @ohneville… https://t.co/PIaNT3Z9hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today plz go by fast hell Friday come quick so me and babygirl can leave Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I use Azure Templates or Azure Powershell to deploy resources? Thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lakers stopped playing defense once Lonzo got hurt. Tell me again how this is the kids’ fault]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakthroughs in pathology dermatology and radiology coming in AI progress.  - Lake Nona Impact Forum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief Williams was a good friend enjoyed working with him we had a great working relationship   @UnadillaFireRes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day of snowshoeing with aenewbold and @lcolonelsanders complete with hot cocoa and taco soup at the… https://t.co/8wdYInpvbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only the dead I’ve seen the end of the war.     If you can not join the ride. Please help me, help the Veterans🚴‍♂️… https://t.co/ckIcUNx4IZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewaraven Yeah. I don't think he'll get fired.   ...but maybe suspended until Next Tuesday.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_C4 It’s been a rough patch for me but I’m hanging in there. Thank you for reaching out! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayday Parade was right, I am a black cat with a black backpack full of fireworks who’s gonna burn the city down ri… https://t.co/WwDW6qA5D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to be the keynote speaker this evening for the Tennessee Society of Professional Engineers Annual Banquet. https://t.co/1qpGFeN9US]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summerdru Yeah I’m not about to let you disrespect Tenya. Square the fuck up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuvernaFredo @TheNancyRoc Lollll se tèlman nou reziye nou ki fè maleng nan kangrennen... Yo laloz nou jan yo vle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamonIrsola @CubaRodrigues @Yusleivyb @OieranoEguia @DiazCanelB La pájara castrista adivinando , ud es chiva 🐑 beeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boporter16Bo @masnNationals @dankolko Welcome sir! Looking forward to your insight of the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton How many Americans would allow a stranger into their house through the back door and then have to listen… https://t.co/R1BCCh4eIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion @cristianafarias Reagan Judge Ellis's Sweetheart deal with Manafort, Republican Special Persecutor Ken… https://t.co/OdQYZzIR69]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York, Brooklyn Greenpoint. . . . . #theglobalphoto #newyork #building #color #brooklyn #greenpoint… https://t.co/uRw6ZsRwzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story of Mark and Elena breaking up because of selfishness over starting a podcast is the most on-brand thing ever lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Max and Femi are picking up from where they left off. Keep it up. #dpubb #playingpossessed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWMSJaguars Assistant Principal Michael Coates (@TheMan_MrCoates) leads the SPMT leaders in reviewing and analyzin… https://t.co/U0BkkR1vqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purdue with their 24th Big 10 regular season championship!  Most in the Big 10. @BoilerBall @BigTenNetwork #Purdue]]></document><document><![CDATA[3959 Wilshire Blvd 3959 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90010 https://t.co/Wpak7kvQvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwasports @dandakich On the back is not a call.  Doesn’t exist.  It has to be a push.  Displacing the player.  He… https://t.co/faHfXzxbNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gio_tbilisi @teslaownersSV @Tesla Hella bad weather with trees down and roads closed is where I’m living. East Bay - about 30-40 min of SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smooth_LaFlare We will take any win we can get. Praying for you brotha as always 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 worst jokes:                                         Kid 1: Does anyone have a pen?                 Kid 2: I… https://t.co/UFHUlH625k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helghast73 @HeartEyes4Brady Well, I’ll take the grey, wet and windy over this 15F degree weather we are having!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This show will give you new respect for how impressive Legend’s Theatre program is! BRAVO! Go see these amazing stu… https://t.co/6NndcOMDFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent article the examination of the party of @FoxNews and US Dictator @realDonaldTrump 🤔🤔 https://t.co/8PSTlclgAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BARBIE60 | Closed #InternationalWomensDay with a fabulous party celebrating the 60th Anniversary of @barbie ...it… https://t.co/1g2Wb7dHqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quincy_uk_mfc #quincyukmfc #mfc #myfreecams #mfcmodel #cammodel #model #hawty #sexi #bape #gorgeous #bomb #avn… https://t.co/wX18hirvuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, It's Penguin the Ferret 😁😁❤❤ #PenguinTheFerret  #Penguin #Ferret @ Olathe, Kansas https://t.co/1ktYmmKP5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle When will this shameful waste of tax payers$$ end😡🤡 They must be held accountable 😡🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Idiot. Why don’t you do the job that you were elected to do legislate not investigate idiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJM_JR @RuFan130 Tonight has to be a “get right” game for them. I have a feeling they’ll figure a few things out.… https://t.co/cIQZxGd46i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PauloCo59698908 @rihanna @Robyn_Rihanna_1 @Sephora @HarveyNichols @fentybeauty HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS… https://t.co/XoSHK17UfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready to grow and advance your beauty career? We have the tools to help you achieve your dreams! We are cur… https://t.co/StzQ6dqi8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATX_PATRIOT @guntotinchick Adjust to your chosen life.  There is no place here for an ISIS sympathizer.  Choices have consequences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big7nik QBs on reserve/future deals basically have like a 5% shot of making a 53.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonmasters If Intel hadn't chased margins for so long, or if VMs had remained the core execution primitive and all… https://t.co/ZoX4qcxHGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IPSunTzuPro More of a lifestyle brand. But I'm at a crossroads. Ever since I went back to school for building apps… https://t.co/6DVMfiW3sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending so much love ❤️ to my adorada @silviao @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/iYK4vqwHAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[11-year old Chris is very pleased with present life events. @ Luther Burbank Center for the Arts https://t.co/YMak1KvwYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JandyLynn Same thing happened to me when I pleaded with him in love. May God have mercy Tullian and Stacey and on us all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeafsAllDayy @DiasAndre91 @reporterchris @DFleetyy @voggzzz And because he’s an a hole known to both sides you ign… https://t.co/EfjL91yxRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Record healthy life anytime, anywhere with your friends in Step Tracker! https://t.co/dMY05l4bPz https://t.co/PKs3F9wUup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunDigest @Gearsofguns It’s honestly a little silly. Is a can awesome, yes. Should we have to pay an extra $200 pl… https://t.co/yMrLdoxQq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yifanwu @stevekrouse @joe_hellerstein I remember lunch and the group dinner, but for some reason I couldn't rememb… https://t.co/ve5E7Pn7hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @jjauthor DIDNT  TAKE THAT LONG. SHE SHOULD BE INVESTIGATED AND MADE TO LEAVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southstands303 @nuggets Nah just chuck up another 3... Should work eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was kinda excited for @Brewers baseball, but after the @AdamMcCalvy interview on @1057FMTheFan I’m freaking pumpe… https://t.co/8M215FIKG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The American people watch you on your knees you Draft Dodger ,, Tell us President Donny ,, what is… https://t.co/1JycgSMXY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliemason There is a special place in hell for airport slow-walkers with roller bags. #EternityInOHare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @CNNPolitics @priscialva US taxpayers are paying for millions of non citizens. These judges are ve… https://t.co/qEFe9iXyz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidsirias1 It’s spelled @JussieSmollett @GovernorVA @MarkHerringVA https://t.co/JYSTZIfy1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoesewellC @bfriend407 @hawkeyeinfw @KyleClark @9NEWS @GovofCO And if California actually left the union then this is a great deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arachnocapital2 @argumatronic i was always terrible at mental math. paper+pencil is the third half of my brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re looking forward to something more than anything in the world and you know it’s coming soon...#LetsGo🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛑THE CHECK OUT THE TRUTH SHOW. THE QUEEN WILL MAKE YOU THINK. 🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔. https://t.co/CmhjVYkD74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweetieWalker @JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Truth. Hurts. https://t.co/vzAHVyVafo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cheater Hops #5: Nelson-Citra by @sapwoodcellars at @sapwoodcellars — https://t.co/XxzMejpEUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @vladimirpadrino Little Marco got $22 million from two anonymous donors which was laundered by Conserva… https://t.co/zzLCN53HKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mp_pwcs We are so happy you have joined our Twitter Community. Love ❤️ seeing the students engaged in #nonfiction .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashElite I used to joke to my mentees that I practiced OLY lifts on the smith machine just to see their expressio… https://t.co/bi96bnhrEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tgirlfan69 @lithium66 @jockosrocket @kittysilk7 @SAMCRO1968 @Samuel_Verson1 @PassiValerio @CulitosNice @CyclingMan72 @rickstwit12 Lucky Guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManilanH Sure! Maybe 1% of your political work and activism is on Twitter. The rest is hard work, understanding, a… https://t.co/tFBQZbJ9FG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyCancerLady @myssissippi @RealAJBenza @HuffPostLife You’re exactly right. I really suspect that many who want… https://t.co/lKmiABqZql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tklforgiven @yourmumspants @mikenedie @Wolfpak561 @DB_Grimwalker @Dylon59556561 @Cern_lXXl @zypisfy @1CubbieKat1… https://t.co/ug4IVKPYYi]]></document></documents></author>