<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#JusticeComittee @JustinTrudeau @theJagmeetSingh @AndrewScheer Raybould told the truth. Trudeau’s dirty little secr… https://t.co/HnZiODDDpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open Houses...this weekend in Sycamore! 3 Great Homes! Check them out this weekend! Reston Ponds Ranch, Historic Do… https://t.co/CfYxnFjYUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuchiththaW @steph93065 @AOC Gore is not a scientist, has about 25 heaters for his mansion ? Flies his private jet… https://t.co/sFD92KVqQr]]></document><document><![CDATA[best compliment i got yesterday, "When I see a @PopeyesChicken I will think of you" 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge @kathygriffin @StephMillerShow @SheenaMetal @Martina @VABVOX @OhNoSheTwitnt @OneSillyFag  homo podcas… https://t.co/8Wd3FfZxuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:17 am and I’m posting about Mike Tyson 🤷🏻‍♀️😂 https://t.co/y4RyourPdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful interview with @DelegateSheree who serves our Eastern Shore community so well!   https://t.co/nDWuIQQkjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mad1son_pa1ge So instead of a boob job you’re buying a nutsack with ears https://t.co/0oX06xyGTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we make and crowdfund a giant "Stop all the PACs" superPAC? Or wait. Isnt that what giving to @justicedems woul… https://t.co/mr2DiV9TZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I moved in with Marco. I literally wear his clothes more than mine 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyythevegan I use this one all the time plus it has vegan protein powder in it https://t.co/XngmGy0KWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The infections smile has infiltrated Indy 🙌🙌 Good luck @iman_marshall8, I know you will kill it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people settle for less and are too afraid to follow their dreams , and that is why they end up working @ the s… https://t.co/0ba2T6NgaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[why say you want someone and be with them 24/7 and then drop them in 2 seconds for no reason??? i don’t understand… https://t.co/cpjUZqIkbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[But it'll only be a small one because I just got asked to come in at 4 am tomorrow 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanBallengee @WillGrayGC @ShaneRyanHere @Amanda_Balionis I mean I watch twitter non stop. Every second some news… https://t.co/Ivs78nB5IP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the home you have been waiting for! ☎️ Contact me for details. #lakenona #homeforsale #openhouse #remax… https://t.co/FnVNTJ20zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctor ordered I can’t fly for a year, @interjet doesn’t care! They claim they can’t do anything if I miss my fligh… https://t.co/vexy8DcSim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok i deadass was working w 2 humans ln who asked if Karl Lagerfelt created Chanel................]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerHillXXX I would like to see romantic sex!! Passion, romance stuff like that. Kind of sneak peek into what it’… https://t.co/YKaa1Zh5eG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is unacceptable for the federal government or any government to dictate how physicians counsel patients… https://t.co/w6zBqPD4Dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night #wine #wines #winesofinstagram #wineoclock🍷 #wineoclock #wineonwineonwine #wineoftheday #instawine… https://t.co/8JsagfPFGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really hard for me to talk to anyone who isnt offering me a chocolate croissant :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[my anger is being dampened by how absolutely lame i feel for flex-defending myself but ON THE REAL THOUGH if you’re… https://t.co/vko8Hc8T41]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I wouldn’t have been dog sitting, I would have told you to pearl the shit up” - Maggie Ford. A very Maggie Ford… https://t.co/i00xgV7aLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does everyone have pride in the city they’re from ? Or is that just me lol I love my city so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the support coach!! @Sammy50223077 would be loving this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challenge accepted from @Corona1515  Post covers of 10 albums that make up a soundtrack of my life: no explanations… https://t.co/6cHUZ3NLp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePsyren @_Pix3M_ @HalfTangible That's good. I like that. Better then I could put it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnyosmond You used to be my favorite singer but now I am in love with a peacock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sleep training one and potty training the other. There is not enough coffee (or wine) in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam_and_the_dog @IHaveGodsFavor @realTylerZed @DNC I read the article.  Some of it is exaggerated, while some is t… https://t.co/e73Hhep2ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkestLibrary There’s this pizza place here that drizzles on pepper-infused oil (not sure how many spoonfuls) an… https://t.co/IDrONeVVX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Matty Matoian of OK Produce for winning @Fresno_Chamber’s 2019 Leon S. Peters Award.  Thank you for the… https://t.co/1xzoLaSNyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[the biggest plus of us weekly’s sale from wenner media to AMI is messy covers like this one and i’m HERE FOR IT https://t.co/F81pI9DjiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of ‘Phantoms’ coming out, here’s one of my favorite clips from a few years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davenlr We are more responsible for our kids left out in the cold. We can do much better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to joining the @JOFOrtho team in #SanDiego this week and meeting lots of new colleagues!]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do i get sick on the ONE day where i feel motivated enough to go to my classes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe we had great night, but ain’t the type to you that I miss you. 😕  #follobackforfolloback #Realtionships… https://t.co/CBAe3vkod4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only goal in attempting to talk my parents into going to Charleston for our summer vacation is that I just reall… https://t.co/vjoDmYnA9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine going out to eat knowing the people serving you making 2.13 an hour or less, and knowing a tip is expected… https://t.co/nWxcquneKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SciATM highly recommend #SciGlass Walls Videos to actually show processing plants with  https://t.co/tZXsBUahmQ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoDronesCanada @kiteie @DianeMariePosts @lisa_m_228 @belle_levesque Well then get ready to struggle under the conservative brown shirts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA QUIERO DESPERTAR DE ESA PESADILLA Y TUS LABIOS BESAR , NA NA NA EH 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryann and I #read to Junior’s class today 📖💙💝 @ The Kew-Forest School https://t.co/49P13BIygo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom asked me what RT meant so I told her. And she asked what does ReTweet mean. So I told her. And she said I ne… https://t.co/113IaZTVLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth remembering as we listen to Cohen testify before Congress:  https://t.co/d3mz4jTre0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seattle Renters, If one more of you complain about high rent, please share with me your voting history the past 2 y… https://t.co/KKMgCGmFL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our newsroom is now decorated with  Sunpapers of years past, including this immortal gem https://t.co/4KX47WGNDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks owner cannot claim to give a shit about employees if his full time worker is pulling in under $13000 FFS… https://t.co/qcsaTmbaJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really good advice on how to relax before a big meet. T-14 days til conference!!!! #oduswim #goladymons… https://t.co/e8TgUocRWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilliarscreatio @Leon_Helmink @_HerbBaker Delta!! My Dad’s airline ❤️✈️!! DFW-ATL-AMS 🌷🌷🌷🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young Wheldon boys, following in their Dad, @danwheldon's footsteps! @kart4kidsproam #GPSTPETE https://t.co/WV2kXm2gAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGHSBaseball ARE YOU WILLING TO BE A PART OF SOMETHING BIGGER THAN YOU? #OpeningDay2019 #warriorpride… https://t.co/TQFxPVEDLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @AOC Don't give her a second thought, it's all crap... she's not that smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealroseanne awwww your ugly, bitter ass wishes you had the looks to sleep your way anywhere🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to wash my hair but I just don’t have the mentality capacity to do it..........]]></document><document><![CDATA[More of Lion Country Safari #lioncountrysafari #florida #animals #zebra #zoo @ Lion Country Safari https://t.co/WGXq54hddb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just don’t give up trying to do what you really want to do. Where there is love and inspiration, I don’t think you… https://t.co/5w42nAQg6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow i wish i had a blunt right now .. that would help me go back to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emma_Chloe0 Wow!  That’s really interesting. There’s an entire world behind blogging!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOMEONE AT THUS STORR HAS A TEAM 10 STICKER AND I MADE A FWCR AS THE OWNER CAME BY IM CRYIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icathler @humorandanimals No. But you could also get a friend to stand on the other side of the water with a camer… https://t.co/YtIEUkR9Xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I'm telling the pigmentation of the eyeshadow quads in the wetnwildbeauty Rebel Rose collection is 🔥. I fi… https://t.co/Co8szq1OjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartyCheddarCat @garciapenelope_ I am pretty sure mama will do just about anything for you!!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get sad when i send someone hella tweets and they don’t even look at them or acknowledge them :,(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods You keep blabbing until the chickens come home to roost.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colors of spring to counteract the cold winds and snow. Acrylic, ink, pastel and graphite on Stonehenge paper.  .… https://t.co/aDrm17PFE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Srsly anyone tryna come for the kardashians right now better reconsider]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blackhistorymonth Inclined  by David L. Phelps is a site specific public art installation commissioned by the City… https://t.co/38oQZkFRWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @andrerucker51 @keanothedog @JayValenz67 @hey_butter @terry313401 @delgeo1 @poppij @MarilynHallett… https://t.co/EVOJl5o3vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loreestark I see Ron Jon Surf Shop or whatever it was in the 80s/90s that somehow seems the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[alissa delivered my water bottle and a fruit roll up to my sad ass in bed...soul mate]]></document><document><![CDATA[6:30am and I just got to work, yet all I can think about, is how much I can’t wait to get home to snuggle my doggos. 🐶🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winny_atheart @Absolover @TinaBull6 @Dreamer17439 @C_licare @jenniclarephoto @Malirensch @L_Ithil @AussieKerrie… https://t.co/WxyhKF9H0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, that dance scene in Umbrella Academy sure did succeed in making me cry. Yup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyOrrFOX29 come on Kath!! Anglesea is pronounced angle not angel 😇 you know this!!! ☘️#stpatricksdayparade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StayUnited_USA @RepSwalwell What is an accidental president? Certainly NOT one duly elected by  Over 60 plus milli… https://t.co/Dc3KN64u5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[[E N C O U R A G E M E N T . . . |happy Monday peeps &amp; don't let the blues get you down, you woke up today 🙏 https://t.co/eHajbLWbEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow evening at 8:30pm ET for Episode 9 - Building SOAP Integrations in Salesforce https://t.co/jQ32YD7uv0 via @PathtoCode__c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@80sThen80sNow THESE were voted out???  Yikes!  What beat them?  I'm going to HAVE to pick......Ghostbusters with B… https://t.co/e3cKFcxuLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time I was so mad at my mom (I was like 4 stfu) so I didn’t wanna leave my room to use the bathroom so I shit i… https://t.co/22K31v1hTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillQueenComic @omaha_scanner Hey! There aren't ANY in my neighborhood!!!  Whoot!  Whoot!  Oh wait, I'm in Sarpy a… https://t.co/ikEAGqN2P3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working on not being a perfectionist. Some days I’m like “I don’t have time to do this assignment. What’s… https://t.co/uz7c0DaRK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayersPhilFund @Ravens @RavensInsider @TheRavensWire @BmoreBeatdown @BMOREAroundTown @BmoreSportsLife… https://t.co/kaQEBcEiVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every school needs to recognize excellence! We bragged and recognized our new head custodian yesterday and he sent… https://t.co/AWkXUWMOPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arty morning tea. #teaofthemoment is uptonteaimports Mélange Noël. @ Massachusetts https://t.co/mif4qhgG0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s actually hilarious that there’s a pizza place on base called “Hunt Brothers Pizza”... if you watched Grey’s yo… https://t.co/uNzwvjrfdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Patrick’s Day is just around the corner @maryjanesmedical #stpatricksday #cannabisgirls #budtender #montreal… https://t.co/IPpEXzLSVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what. If he brags does that bother you. How about Nancy Pelosi never having a job how the hell is she worth 100… https://t.co/YPAld1tSo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[$1158.02 recovery by Peter, customer walking out by pro without receipt. excellent job Peter @nola_HD0963… https://t.co/kF7z8qHBHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been more sick these past 6 months than I have my whole life... lord just pull the cord]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danimansuttii She is a Disney villain obviously. https://t.co/3ByVAeBox1]]></document><document><![CDATA[👩🏻‍⚕️  For coaching and psychotherapy visit https://t.co/YIhs9ds9dc. Special packages offered for those that contac… https://t.co/03uzAHi4u7]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so good night to ye and godspeed and may we all find our personal "name of the song in the Flexi Blocks commercial"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going Green has Brought Positive Change ~ Billion 🌳🌴🎋 Tsunami! NGO @ftwglobal without further delays is prepared to… https://t.co/zEGk0w5zsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les gens sont déjà dans les bureaux de votes,loving the energy 🙌🏾#Senegalvote]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been looking at my test paper for an hour now and I can’t decide if I wanna do it or not🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@little_wow @WBURCitySpace @andyhusbands @sheryljulian @TheSmokeShopBBQ yuppppp]]></document></documents></author>