<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Asmallnotch @pptsapper @donjustino @nytimes @iAmTheWarax This is the only military study I know of from the 80s... https://t.co/N75EvvK8nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein The Republicans who say that God wanted Trump to be President obviously realize that it was not the A… https://t.co/jtlDObEEq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpkielcz @Bill_Shea19 As the saying goes... Plan for cars and traffic, you'll get cars and traffic. Plan for peopl… https://t.co/WV8snX4iWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 @UN You fools are backing a man who harms his own people, starves them? Keeps medicine from them? @POTUS… https://t.co/VQxqInP8hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone prove that the Kardashians aren't part of a plot to keep Americans stupid and caught up in nonsensical drama?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music from @hihatchie incoming and I’ve been preparing for this very moment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FantasyBlizzard The airport is at almost exactly 7000’ and the Bellemont office is around 7130’. The real big diff… https://t.co/sn6RsqBwdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a connection on @bumble bff. Quickly realized, much like with gay men, I’m also awkward at conversation… https://t.co/gErJZh5crr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/BZd5D5F9Oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders I used to eat sticks and pats of butter at school.  All the kids would pay homage by giving me their bu… https://t.co/VNGOutwZiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s pop music has 4 lines of verse and 18 lines of pre-chorus/chorus. Want to pop today? Don’t tell a narrative… https://t.co/bBRry6oVVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The equivalent of Adam Levine singing “girls like you” shirtless covered in tattoos with flame throwers behind him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still wondering if @TeganNoxWWE_ and @DakotaKai_WWE got/replied to fan mail in the last month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insanexvixen21 @SageModeJesse @scurkay @KEEMSTAR MAGA IS TOO STUPID TO OPEN AN AMERICAN HISTORY BOOK TO PAGE 1.  J… https://t.co/qte182zUJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grafitti y basura en Diaz Ordaz y Blvd. Rogelio Cantu bajo Puente Atirantado. Urge que hagan algo! @Cicmty https://t.co/91wvn7L4Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patty Smyth: 🎶Shooting at the walls of heartache... Cactus Jack: BANG! BANG! Patty Smyth: 🎶I am the warrior...… https://t.co/MqPOzd8AHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna find someone that will genuinely listen to me and my story one day. Someone to look deep into their eyes as… https://t.co/Fev5KuGFcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THE_James_Champ @jaybella175 Oh well thank god someone stole them then. Sheesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole state should be behind solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodkungfustartsinthekitchen  #WarriorUnlimitedMA consuming bone broth is a fantastic way to build the blood and s… https://t.co/Eh3eocYVGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed with @jodywhitaker on @DrWhoOnline thanks to @DavidTennantPod https://t.co/SuaaS3JCs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[•~||| c3 x fRESHERISTIC |||~• #fresheristicTAKEOVER @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/etxdrKZ74e]]></document><document><![CDATA[BACK UP VIDEO OUT NOWWWWWW Go watch that thang and tell us what you think 💙🖤📲 @mfridman94 @pugte_ @weare4vr https://t.co/6UGi2dyeIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eminem @kendricklamar @donaldglover @MacMiller @KidCudi @Logic301 you have all truly influenced my mind. I wouldn’… https://t.co/g84mcQ5vRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This what the 6’6 Samoan used to do before slap boxing niggas in middle school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaoswolf1982 @Matt_Abernathy Right?!? It’s also also goke we have joing. :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyMountViews @KayChase2016 @krassenstein He can claim whatever he wants. The reality of his financial state mig… https://t.co/BHb4DhIoXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COGWaterPower We saw a big flash and pop on Fischer above maple. Pretty loud. #myGlendale]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge biz opportunity! &gt; The Achilles' Heel Of AI via @forbes https://t.co/fuZOJH3L9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Apollo 11 by @celestialbw @ CJ's Beer Garden — https://t.co/wAmk2Xlniu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSu69365006 @Curate_Zed The analogous trim is the clitoral hood extending to include the labia minora up to include the frenulum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Oh Jesus...you must be kidding me. They should be ashamed.  Switch doctors bro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwingReports Still heartbroken from 2011. And 2010. And disappointed from last year's collapse...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricVonHaden1 @shirfire218 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @BrookeWagnerTV @KateMantychWX @SandhyaABC7 @SerenaVachon… https://t.co/hZxixheLEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[5557 W 6th St 5557 W 6th St, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/Yc4Vy3OaCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ross, Principal, from @DartmouthHS jumping into #satchat very, very late BUT just saw some conversation about Homew… https://t.co/jd8CfoW81r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I pass this golf course, it pisses me off again... Such a waste of city resources  @NYCParks… https://t.co/MnuzurZGgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmySalyzyn @petersankoff @acoyne That’s also tricky. Who is the client? The PM? The PMO? Cabinet? The House of Commons even?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Usman is putting the most dominant performance from a challenger I’ve seen in awhile. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gift certificates available. @ Tom Caldwell's Custom Tattoo's &amp; Body Piercing's https://t.co/SE1sDZVoLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KKiddAuthor Thanks KK for the @miragoto song RT! Have a beautiful night ladies! 😇😇🌙🌙🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDollyFox Hun you look fantastic. I have moved many times in my life and I know how hectic it can be. Good luck… https://t.co/8zXBW7nnJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unsuccessful boomerang. #whatev #skishot #sundayfunday @ Tipton Street Pub https://t.co/0YvC5rSE42]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas Penal Code sec. 22.01(b)(4). #topflightsecurityoftheworld #topflightsecurity #dayday #fridayafternext… https://t.co/ub0b823T1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Billionaire tech bro’s priced out the real fans. That’s what happens 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sugamama316 @NBAAllStar I been to plenty of nba games and a nba playoff game but it wasn’t nothing major]]></document><document><![CDATA[The KMS MATHCOUNTS team and six individual competitors competed at Keene State College in the regional Math Counts… https://t.co/qgz4inhRlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicocantor1 Saludos @Nicocantor1 hoy estaremos atentos con @HoustonDynamo, que seguramente va a tener una muy buen… https://t.co/qLvYihAlWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BbeaulieuB Si je vais voir les @Angels C'est un privilège de voir Trout alors je ne serais pas heureux de la défai… https://t.co/8ChgGgmcH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGJacksonGM @hagpogy @ErikJLarsen Dude how is that a valid criticism? Larsen is an artist is he not? Just draw the… https://t.co/qZ3hXQZ5fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susansellers3 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @JaneMayerNYer Thanks Susan. The crazysteins are lovely haters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins @sajidjavid she has not business on our country USA. Stay with ISIS moron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing people cry bc their dreams came true or of happiness gives off the most amazing type of vibe 😤😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure who Lauren Daigle is, but I do know that @floggingmolly rocked the night https://t.co/4slkKTPaEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allegantair @FlyFrontier You filed on that day.  Of course it took you almost a year to respond  so that says something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Harry Reid was one of the most respected politicians of his generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3badsheep Original Available for your private collection #ledlights #mixedmediaart #collaboration… https://t.co/DvN85oYtCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why couldn’t my mom be simple and just give me a first &amp; last name like a basic bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Ekaterina Enokaeva! enokaeva The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are T… https://t.co/IY8JAopOSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skinnyywill Lmao I read it at first &amp; was like 🤔🤔🤔 then I remembered his other tweets and was like ahh nvm lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Segun ud. El m-19 no secuestro, ni asesino. Por lo tanto ud si secuestro y asesino]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaiahJohnson05 @Boeing I don't worship a damn concept I follow a king https://t.co/94p2O6iowM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy Citing the claim doesn't matter to you. I proved Athanasius did NOT include many… https://t.co/6UUfCjK6DO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not big on prognostications.  But pretty sure @serenawilliams is about to put it on azarenka in @IndianWellsCA… https://t.co/J4LEiOHQbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston’s secondary was terrible last year, and all the guys are getting big money. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the state of California Republican Party need to use to gain traction instead of worshipping Drumpf. #LoveIsWar https://t.co/ifmcl1UzJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialChanceH Do we get to hear you say any cuss words? That would be amazing! Like “Oooh Danny just said a bad word!” 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be the best if the #Whisperers arc just ended like that? Lol. Got the kid back, we're out. #TWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m calling BS on all liberal stories of conservatives hating/harassing/threatening liberals unless we see EVIDENCE… https://t.co/E27uUxsgxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @KySportsRadio says “don’t worry the presidential trivia questions are easy, if you think about them!!”, you s… https://t.co/BDLLpxFRNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Front-End Friday Jeep style!⠀ ⠀ —⠀ DM for a shoot! 📸⠀ —⠀ Let me know your thoughts, comment below! 🤘🏻⠀ —⠀… https://t.co/finPeYXPrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HybridPanda Q: is there possible new game modes planned? Like something with bigger map or expanded objectives like Friday the 13th?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Será el 25 de junio cuando Joaquín #ElChapo Guzmán reciba su sentencia. Después será trasladado a una cárcel de máx… https://t.co/F3lFzmYTLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are we heading to Skyzone @iamirishdave and @ChristineKTV?  #RandomThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG... someone please get that sound bite on Trump getting sued in court.   Someone’s lost it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CadillacsHair @PhilMickelson @PGATOUR He might have good calves but his hair needs serious attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best pillow ever! Thanks coach Rob and Emily. #ffs @ Jackwood https://t.co/vzOb7RmzZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Your a idiot, if you believe this, you need to find a new line of work. Journalism is about being fair and… https://t.co/pklTcMTWeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sir, there’s nothing to be “looked into.” The first amendment protects SNL and their sometimes rid… https://t.co/W4ROwhUn4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanBBates @kenradio Probably not based on some light research:   https://t.co/sGwnM9Lq8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myabarness It makes me so mad! Especially when it’s a funny Jawn and I wanna watch it 36 times]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see #sensorgramseverywhere even Running in Palm Springs. #slowoffrate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwmtnews Someday 100% of Americans won’t be in everybody else’s business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know about the professor from Pierce that had a tik tok account?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norman dogged us in practice and most of the day today, luckily we still found a few good ones. Also made it on Bas… https://t.co/Mtoewa33lK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I don’t know if this was an intentional casting choice in Atlantis 1x15 “Before I Sleep” but it is awesome to se… https://t.co/elhoTSBCK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Landolph @quentingriffin_ @TheBrownsWire Congrats! Would love to have you as a guest if you’re up for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing ya headphones or ya charger really feels like the end of the world 🌍🚫🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamline gets two in the 6th and the Norse are unable to answer. 4-2 after 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MNUFC has won more Western Conference road matches in 2019 than they have in franchise history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I wake up in a cold sweat every morning with the realization we have been invaded by a horde of 'IGNORANTS' oth… https://t.co/lPCH5x7uuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the new @QuinnXCII album on repeat while I'm in the hospital 💪💪 fantastic music]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two huge matchups tonight for @PIHLhockey! I’ll be on hand for @BethelParkHawks vs @lebo_hockey for… https://t.co/MwCo4vNaIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Faking a hate crime is stupid. And with due respect, the term was put into place because of the rampa… https://t.co/FKwgszMYmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pistons stay hot, bounce #Bulls for fifth straight win: https://t.co/eULwEi44pj https://t.co/pcDGZnGnEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[who else can say they got more slaps than the beatles &amp; not be playin]]></document><document><![CDATA[#philly  . . Asking price 65k - my humble opinion. Will be offering 45k . Rehab 35k - ARV 120k being conservative -… https://t.co/xWY00B6xaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Beauty is not defined by the size of your jeans but by the size of your heart.” https://t.co/2bidpwDfpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simmonds17 I coach freshman football we struggled a lot this year with toughness this coming football season I’m g… https://t.co/lj3XPFAPlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homeawayfromhome #2wongsmakearight (@ Disney's All-Star Movies Resort - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL) https://t.co/GrqMfRHBuV]]></document></documents></author>