<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If my future boyfriend/husband doesn’t run my bath water with roses and candles then he’s not for me 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your ex requests to follow you on Instagram, and then proceeds to MESSAGE you... 2019 has no room for fuck boys byeeeeee 🙅🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he’s playing games so you play them back 😉 https://t.co/kMNMo4amgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StoneColdRoger @TylerPNixon Love how rich people start go fund me pages for their legal defense. I thought you wer… https://t.co/QbkwVpn6vX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something in its favor already: it’s self-published space opera that DOESN’T start with sixty pages of backstory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a TV commercial from @CocaCola that said you should have their new strawberry guava flavored soda for br… https://t.co/HgzNymrs0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMorning #DaylightSavingsTime Arras, BM, 0863 https://t.co/ozVqKMLM2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisTirchPhD I carry alot of emotion in my stomach.  I find that I have to hold my stomach around 4 or 5 a.m. be… https://t.co/SrQAHgg2i0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Another propaganda post from trump so sad he’s so weak and a loser liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSlyStallone I wonder what the dialogue was between rocky and Mickey in the street before handshake?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President strongly condemns anti-Semitism and hate.  “Very fine people” “Very fine people” “Very fine people” “… https://t.co/Gf6YuoeVeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating an amazing experience for 11,000 people - Experience Management Summit https://t.co/GIhVrQ0imk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @alllibertynews @justinamash @realDonaldTrump Just wish he would answer his constituents...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day @bythebeachbear @ Olivenhain Pioneer Elementary https://t.co/stwJ7CryrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larrybcm2019 @marathonbcm Getting it done is the challenge. Working on that mental toughness. Well done. Have fun in Glasgow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, 243 is a lie. 238 was a lie. Adding 4 pounds does not make this anymore believe. Why they will embarrass the… https://t.co/5vejmLYtVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two monsters down . This mama is on the move today . Thank god for my sister for taking care of my little little 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Restaurant Hourly Team Member - https://t.co/ui55fq2ppb #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allah SWT said:  وَتَرٰى كَثِيرًا مِّنْهُمْ يُسٰرِعُونَ فِى الْإِثْمِ وَالْعُدْوٰنِ وَأَكْلِهِمُ السُّحْتَ ۚ لَبِئْ… https://t.co/1AyDTAW3yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Donald,  it isn’t the democrats or the news that sabotaged your North Korean summit. It’s the fact… https://t.co/8ElV13FICg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun way to enter the building today! Spring break countdown. Thank you to our awesome PCC!#svmseagles… https://t.co/szflxQ1Rcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittykatya Watching it now. I got to the middle of episode 2 and needed a break!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magazura @jguaido Latinoamérica está destinada a crecer y a exigir más de sis gobernantes, no podemos seguir en el… https://t.co/Y2om0ybus2]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful sunny afternoon in a gorgeous lofty condo #luxuryrealestate #lispenard #nyc #condos #tribeca… https://t.co/eGNJ7FkJd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/a3o2k5zc7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to just go ahead and get a cute pair of glasses. Cause I’m very irresponsible with contacts. I always forget to take them out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so desperately hoping this puppy doesn’t have Parvo bc I just found out our adult dogs aren’t even vaccinated… https://t.co/sEakXXCEaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haley_Beans Don’t force yourself boo. when the time is right things will fall into place. I know everyone around y… https://t.co/oreIkw1Xls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SantosTrinidad Ahí tienen los españoles!  Como debe ser! Con el documento nacional de identidad es suficiente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 times out of 10 I will cry at the babies being born on teen mom, no matter how many times I’ve seen the episode 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How about the dark day for Israel because they also have a leader that is being indicted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dafforino @BernieSanders No, it's a legitimate question. Inferring that I'm just mindlessly repeating something I… https://t.co/ClynSKFzi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really beginning to dislike Twitter. Twitter gives morons a platform to be abusive, obnoxious and/or ignorant,… https://t.co/RYPkC9ihQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the names weren't even remotely similar. I'm just. Wow. I hope whoever is in charge sees this and issues our director an apology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealLukevans I use Audible so I'm listening to Angel of Darkness &amp; Christmas 1914 by Charles Olivier]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moms at frat parties? #powermovesonly @ Texas Tech Fiji https://t.co/RpLysxSgXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnefrancis Hi! 2nd from right is Chretien, but interesting interpretation of a merge of both Chretien and Harper… https://t.co/pG7HVO7xip]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can find zero motivation to get out of bed right now. But I gotta! At least it’s Friday!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsobelCarr @rebyj @BankofAmerica I was done when they tried to charge me to cash an insurance check drawn on their… https://t.co/xzNLhTk2cO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The politicians are all out for themselves.  They don’t care about our safety.  They don’t care what we want.  Veto… https://t.co/RlZ5FqMiJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Propyrion @GovSisolak @Nicole4Nevada @JasonFrierson This is a guaranteed win!  What an incredible group.  🎰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I apologize excessively it’s so annoying, you could probably run me over with an 18 wheeler and id be a pancake on… https://t.co/2olgTgbHgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How awesome! I just love flamingos.... They are so unique... Enjoy yourself. And please be safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__SG17 @RobForbesDJ @henrywinter @UEFA Yeah by his side 🙄 https://t.co/aPLj9XthT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat        Yeehaw boys at my school                 🤝              Hating black things]]></document><document><![CDATA[My back looks crazy tho. But also wearing these marks with some confidence cause now I feel like a bad bitch athlet… https://t.co/6kYNGjs5vW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monetxchange On a scale of 1-10--you broke the scale. But I like your new music!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drop down &amp; Get your . .. eagle on girL . .  #thickthighssavelives #spin  #philadelphia @ SPIN https://t.co/4lAhW3r5r9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I put some bags outside the door, woke up from my nap and they were gone. Big ass heavy ass bags]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon⁩ running scared from NY ⁦@contessabrewer⁩ is following the story ⁦with reaction from local businesses @CNBC⁩… https://t.co/AQmz39IlGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennygibo23 @JackPosobiec @JessieJaneDuff @SennenLegend Yes, leaders of other countries have let too many illegals… https://t.co/SweMcqClIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was gonna go get my nails filled but figured it’d be wayyyy too busy today lol #happy20th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsonDanielle All the songs!!! Push It, Do Me, I Want to Sex You Up 😯😯😯😯 at the top of my lungs 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Stefan!!! Another Aggie Win... Another Co-Player of the game! 🙏🏽❤️ LETS GOOOOO🏀#justagirlfromkansas🌻 @ Joh… https://t.co/MvjsfowlUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY finished up the video on the dispute between Disney and Universal on rights to using the Kuka arm today, an… https://t.co/cpjHSURFjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100_Disable_vet Nope. Makes perfect sense. I never realized how the multiplication of 7's was so easy for my football loving brother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And every offering of all the holy things of the children of Israel, which they bring unto the priest, shall be his. https://t.co/YzdyowYAuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Alcala210 Well I could have been sleeping still in Vegas for FREE😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson just nailed it.  Alicia Keys is about to..#ArethaTribute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Harbors!!! Feeling so excited and loving our sweet cabin!! #firsttimeinduluth #mnspringbreak… https://t.co/MQvb27pUdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see @Chubbss_xo out here liking my tweets but leaving me on read on Snapchat. 😢 https://t.co/aHwGubGVHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcademicsSay @jrieffel Violets are-  green:  |  0.8% yellow: ||  1.2% blue:    |||||||||||||||||||  98.0% ✅… https://t.co/xkoR9AwqD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did talk to the real Luke Perry about @Madonna he said all good things about her  I will not rt  the old tweets w… https://t.co/J0HmfYSG0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all of you “saved Christians” are getting into heaven 🐸 think of it as a fancy club with 10,000 capacity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevalley Shall I expound on all of the reasons? He’s an honorary #brainyfangirl, wicked smart and clever. He is i… https://t.co/oy5FYfVHI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJusChelss @sweetaskayybee Literally all he does is play the game he’s addicted when he wakes up for school at 6… https://t.co/qBvoI1aFkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Winston_Dunhill @PedroBriegerOk Don @Winston_Dunhill ... amole fuerte! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asthika @DrNDisis @DrChoueiri @DrRoyHerbstYale Great questions. I don’t have those data but I also look forward to… https://t.co/A1XEhPR7K2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rly feeling that part of millennial burnout where u just quit ur full time job by never coming in again and not say… https://t.co/VNZ7lVa2Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous seed bead necklace and matching earrings  🖤 5 available 🖤 $5 each 🖤  #karissparkleroom  #karis5sparkle… https://t.co/Od3P2eQRja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more days in this weather and I am out! ✈️☀️🌴 and it can’t be soon enough!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵Alex Cameron &amp; Roy Molloy #intheround @ Thalia Hall https://t.co/Kl4Vn65BiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I think this kind of behavior is a major blemish on conservatism and particularly on the Republican P… https://t.co/CJQ0F44KAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This from media nobody’s- 🇺🇸 None have started, built, hired /business(es) 🇺🇸 None have proudly made America better… https://t.co/UBmqvADOMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heywood98 Thank you for following me. I have tried to follow Q to no avail. I am 69 and sometimes my mind wobbles,… https://t.co/j2gkp0IXEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should have known today was going to be shitty when I first woke up having an anxiety attack. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caiti326 @CFL @TeamSheIS and cutest family awards goes to https://t.co/GdbrNKFcTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaLoder_ @RicSancho Great song! Also, I’m prescribed clonidine. Only thing that’s ever worked, paired with “… https://t.co/x7OOthuZrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backt0nature Either the wild things if you remember that book or an actual moment when a boy cries wolf? https://t.co/ApXD52hXjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forcing myself not to TEXT sum BS YOUR way . Gotta put the phone down😂 https://t.co/24h97gy1J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I finally cleaned out my purse and basically my bag is a bottomless pit of carmex, lighters, lipsticks, and lotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[People saying the MUSS was classless but really with roughly 500 students each enrolled in 4 classes on average the… https://t.co/bU99WCjmKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cortney_weaver @A24 Dang. We should have hoped harder. Why didn’t @TheAcademy appreciate the goodness that was… https://t.co/vQ4h35iO2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowed in and the power out. Lit a fire and brought out the family scrabble set.  #vintagegames scrabble… https://t.co/EjOrLqTeIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro choice. Pro life. Hard to argue for or against both. The American People know I am pro choice. I don’t change my position. Tatiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[飲ミュニケーション・ポッドキャストは忘れていないです。 でも…リアル・トークで、喋りすぎて、10分以内のは無理だった！ 3回も短くしてに頑張ったけれど、まだダメです。 英語の話することが長いな、私。（笑）  諦めません！ファイト！]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaywaydrug my ancestors blessed me with deep, deep, deathlike sleep!! they also made me dumb as hell. staying up t… https://t.co/aFJtXRT8NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLD! At above asking price ✨ If you are thinking about buying or selling, message me so we can start planning your… https://t.co/pRerD9s80p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaBo89025068 @fras99 I don’t find him hypocritical at all. He’s evil and makes no bones about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge amounts of moisture available as we tap into the AR. Be safe out there!! #cawx #47weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smileyface6689 showed this to me. Best thing I’ve seen tonight! https://t.co/KtEYfmoAao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Anti-Semitism.  Never saw that before Trump (she says sarcastically)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relationships are like music. You don’t drop an artist because you dislike one song, instead you press next and keep listening along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YAY I get more Jason and Jason/Carly tomorrow so I will watch! #JasonFF #SteveFF #JarlyForever #GH]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIG! BREASTS! SPECIAL!! Monday, March 11th $160 until 10am @tnt_adult_fun Tiffany 780-292-3167 @ NORTH 8103 - 127 A… https://t.co/du4mHMHIZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishSseb @csuros59 @IslandGirl544 @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump TWO YEARS...NO EVIDENCE‼️And NO PRESIDENT has EVER… https://t.co/LU5z5toL2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It isn't presidential harassment, it's called checks and balances. Deal with it or resign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyinternationalwomensday to the one who inspires me the most! Can’t believe you will be a college graduate in t… https://t.co/3bnTiQQmQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[in cuba I swam through a cave with the depth being 22m. I was nearly shitting bricks. most people know I’m terrifie… https://t.co/fhYmgBNu34]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first group of the GREATEST generation (WWII veterans) and their families have arrived!!!  We are serving them… https://t.co/kHhKBWPVAq]]></document></documents></author>