<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Where are his teammates? You know @russwest44 is mentally weak why would you not remove him from this situation? No… https://t.co/Gzut4oGyNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t save the words for a time that may never come.  Tell people they matter to you TODAY! #forgoodnesssake #love… https://t.co/Bc53FPYp9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the #SFGiants brought Dusty Baker back, I think they had someone in mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s do this (@ Newark Liberty International Airport in Newark, NJ) https://t.co/350ao4DqdD https://t.co/FXYzF7X0Jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric Thames hits a mammoth two-run HR in fourth to give #Brewers a 3-2 lead. Last seen bouncing around on the back… https://t.co/GkhNsP9d3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our friends up north will laugh at this, but yes, this is chilly weather for Florida. And probably the last chilly… https://t.co/zTCtQgvIip]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was outside for like 2 hours today and got sunburnt... it’s only February]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmcnally14 @NBCSCapitals Jensen is a steal! Watched him play against top lines this year every game! Easily a top 4 D man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher You mad? You should pick up a book some time, and read all about the eugenics program, in the U.S.. Should op… https://t.co/QQN86QhqzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fijis_Pet @MsMelChen No. We are bigots if we believe that. I am happily a bigot then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They added this sign to #bondcourt, but I’m one of the only people to flick the switch. https://t.co/FIIaZMbGI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not fast enough.    Thank you President  Trump!!🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻❤️🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[We just completed this gorgeous custom handmade blue leather floater frame for this landscape. What a combo ,ya? @… https://t.co/ZF8t7HSLFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eltribuno Sábado amanece en la Ciudad de #Salta aguardamos ansiosos por la ampliación de la noticia de @silviagonn… https://t.co/G2eVGQRUQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason God does not desire sacrifice and offering is that Jesus, the Pure Lamb has pleased Him completely, once… https://t.co/3J1roZ80vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying something slightly different...only 30 days to go until vacation, so there’s one more pre-vacation haircut i… https://t.co/uTGfNoezNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Girls: https://t.co/09o75MczYc  AA Girls: https://t.co/fhrBGfB7Kw  AAA Girls: https://t.co/XY7tKRjkHX  AAAA Girls: see District 6 link]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a 4 day weekend from school I’m back in the pilots seat to bring the Lady Warriors JV and Varsity basketball… https://t.co/uURBCaLkLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henrik Hmm I’m not sure what it would take to do that. I agree it would be super cool to be able to play around wi… https://t.co/H3wtCHXcFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to try out @DJIGlobal Mavic 2 special flying features: dronie, boomerang, ellipse, waypoints,and tracki… https://t.co/Ik2qtXz49p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Britt_Jill_ @BrowningArms @BrowningAmmo Nice.... a Browning over/under is definitely on of the guns on my bucket list!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cicistheories @davidfholt @CarrieBlumert We have a great multidisciplinary, multi-agency team working on holistic… https://t.co/ro4qGQ0S1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Uk seems to be leaning towards stopping weapon sales to Saudi and the UAE.  This is foolhardy as s… https://t.co/9OGlWJfqB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 1-Lot Liberty Keuter Road #TurtleCreekTwp #OH https://t.co/8Re0nrvANp #realestate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easily one of my favorite movies. The dialogue is so snappy and Mitchum and Douglas are taunt in every scene. Out o… https://t.co/4HmS4um1JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was that one steward basically manhandling Grealish when he jumped into the crowd 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need Channing to be a commentator on YES network with Richard next season. Like Desperately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bailey got a new toy and when you squeeze its hand, it says “I love you, yes I do” and I just think this relationship is moving too fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Philly with my main squeeze @ Independence Hall https://t.co/MgGpfy3ly2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edgerton ends Turner's 11-1 run, but Trojans lead 57-53, 23.2 left #wisbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFelicello @casas_jimmy @rocklandboces @SESPirates @RossCoops31 @AJBianco @TonySinanis @AngelaStockman… https://t.co/6mTcUpJg9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my niece’s birthday and I couldn’t be more excited to be home for it. Three years ago, I couldn’t imagine… https://t.co/NrgUjlT0m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is super awesome! @JJWatt is a great guy and I’m sure this is a day Brock will remember for a long time.… https://t.co/JbzfnPYPS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not hiring Cohen for a West Wing job will be one of the most epic and most consequential employment decisions the S… https://t.co/iWJQ6SHXMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascalAudet1 @arcosluisd @cafreeland @jguaido El Presidante https://t.co/l0GO9z3bmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What else would you expect @Yvngdevo to do. #hesbuiltforthis #RidgeNation #hesabeast @ Gwinnett County, Georgia https://t.co/2G4KDpVHQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seth_turner_ Absolutely. Has to be someone with pedigree like the two already linked with the job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DailyHaiku   You're called many names,  Cornered, silenced,cast adrift...  But we will prevail. https://t.co/J6nhCfJVtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_ramsey @Arrow Really going to miss you!!  So grateful for being able to meet a few times!!  Best of luck...… https://t.co/wDHxSb7Kgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello rainy Napa, thankfully weather supposed to clear up. Looking forward to a great birthday weekend with family… https://t.co/E9YgWet61y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StickStickly150 @idontlovethat “Spicky”?  Eddison.... lol https://t.co/lXfZmSwhxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillChristie15 @MikeStuchbery_ Would that be other circumstances that could happen at a Lutheran, Catholic, or Chu… https://t.co/yj7ukr7SPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to be streaming some Pokemon with some friends IRL Join in on the adventure later tonight  https://t.co/i9SutIFAEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends Ainsley, I'm sure you hear this every day but you are just amazingly beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNILAD Her own?  *Did not, and will not, read the article to find out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCalHeel89 @RyanJReynolds @Zona_Briggs Not a big deal. By the way we play baseball at 3:05 tomorrow on TV DTV 662]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gingwilson Congratulations on your new endeavor G-Wil! Keeping up with you made me a Childress fan...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday morning on a beautiful snowy morning here in Doyestown, PA. Have a great week! #frankdolski… https://t.co/FZL5YKcmcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s your favorite team? Oh the most expensive ones got it. Go sports!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, make us good stewards of the earth's gifts of water, soil, forests, and air. https://t.co/cjUwxI6Eba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your hurting the snowflakes feelings President Trump. Keep going!! I’ll fill my new leftist tears tumbler with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsedi205 @MashiRafael Me Encantaría tener el tiempo para compartir conceptos y criterios, pero veo que partes del… https://t.co/KmcfDhURsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stansigstad It’s not a total loss, I found a few people actually do listen but I prefer to stick with entertainmen… https://t.co/kjpXzpwEXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to read and retweet till it hits uneducated people. #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraytonToups Maybe just maybe someday people in this country will realize that guns don't kill people. And as far… https://t.co/NjUemiV13i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @johncardillo Of course the #Media doesn't care that innocent #Trump supporters are being attacked… https://t.co/oPAmXJ0aM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonWhitely @dalehansen that was an amazing tribute to your friend @johnmccaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abominations 😲😱🤯🔥👑👑 #morbidangel #treyazagthoth @ Baltimore Soundstage https://t.co/FfbRRkEAvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except that you have to clean out your dishwasher filter every week if you don’t.  That’s a fun job!!! 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mondaygrind #chuzefitness @ Escondido, California https://t.co/e0rVG20Mbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obulette is almost a given in #ModernHorizons right? Tons of legacy cards I could at least see: port, karakas, daze, baleful??]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My roots are runnin deep Ima take em back to the garden”... I finally put this up for streaming and download! Link… https://t.co/OYIl5ZOJh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayker My focus got blurry for a second &amp; I let my monkey mind take over. Thanks for asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityRochesterNY @Wegmans HQ is in Gates, you fought them every step of the way when they built their East Ave store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeeyee187 @TVietor08 @IlhanMN And who are you exactly? 😂 https://t.co/8YtYUaZsV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lophus89 @only_flip_flops She said “wide right” basically alluding the report missing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[with that being said, if anyone has any form of hatred for me that they want to release in the form of hitting me w… https://t.co/CS0v7jchTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the consultants and that used to say local sports don’t matter wouldn’t have liked tonight. So much happening w… https://t.co/YtYr8u1eyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Gross I think youre reading a negative inflection that isn’t necessarily there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll just be over here figuring out how to help from our 3rd floor downtown apartment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMRAYMOND84 @KennyEdmonds @BrdgstoneArena One of the best live performances I've seen, from anyone 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OANN : @AmandaBrilliante: Your historical segment on the USS Constellation is not quite accurate. Said ship was bu… https://t.co/DfhIQJprxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gotta admit. I hate that Jordyn would ever jeopardize a friendship and black ball her ass but THESE FUCKING ME… https://t.co/YggqvQQcJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which is better “shit a brick” or “poop an inside out geode”?  I made up the latter earlier today and it has a certain appeal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnePerfectShot We used to drive by that house back in high school just to freak ourselves out. It was hilarious ho… https://t.co/bmjBQ6nL1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[And what does that tell you largest cocaine bust in years it tells you how much stuff is coming across the border]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had suggested that MANAFORT shld have been listened too by the spooks. This says he was but no real proof was gle… https://t.co/eQr6KsSPD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 Two of the biggest threats to the health and safety of Oregon teens is marijuana and vaping. The Clear Alliance… https://t.co/loLOf9W4Hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiaMoNDzMoNieZ @gtoninn LMAO yeah, I’m not actually waiting right now, but that Clifton Park show at the end of th… https://t.co/CN5lnJofE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntrider825 @Mark_inFairport I’d take 0-19 if it gets me a top 2 pick and Housley canned :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like @Wyndham_Clark going with either the @FLATCATgolf “Slim” or “Svelte”. Either way, he’s right there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was shooting lights out at the gym the last 3-4 weeks... showed up yesterday and didn’t warm up, straight jumped… https://t.co/NbES4bd2uj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old chrome 97 Stromberg carb, $250 plus shipping @ Martinez Industries Co. https://t.co/xAj4VxLzjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure they built the 'Rocky steps' for the musical performances tomorrow. #DKPS #Pens #StadiumSeries https://t.co/petbgDN3vP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Good news. We have 1000 of her. I’ve had the honor of running with several of them. They’re just get… https://t.co/rpyx0bpuTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NIPSEYHUSSLE #APPROVED  #TIDAL  #DCOKAH  #FOUNDATIONSOFAMAN1 #FOUNDATIONSOFAMAN2 #ALBUMS #FOAM1 43 SONGS + #FOAM2… https://t.co/r4nVIwrONP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Scott gets it! @benmaller The Ben bino is my dude but I Love giving him S💩about Boston bootlicking!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horsechappy @CeeEfCee @tmlam830 Yeah, @CeeEfCee, don't be Johnny Jealous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackCarrUSA @EmilyBestler @AtriaMysteryBus @simonschuster Sweetness. Can’t wait!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantNapearshow The day after the trade I said it will go down as the greatest trade in Kings history. DeMarcus is… https://t.co/VIxAvEzjze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberblur06 @RE_Games @Cybrid101 Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music bo… https://t.co/L18UoLc7mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrsbabbles @FAIRImmigration If he w ere an American, they would've already spent the money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PornVoyeur @sexyindia @ChynaJoanLaurer I listen to your show the other night and I was shocked and mad about this.… https://t.co/K3EMsYoxzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton "The Old Sage"-  Guess we believe that they have case of forgetfulness "strange weirdness" Beware of the… https://t.co/BocFVRRHub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjones_ceo To quote the great Stink, doesn’t he have to be able to perform the act to be charged!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DovySimuMMA Im predicting Smith wins by TKO/KO by the 2nd rd man! Just my random pick for this card, plus a shock… https://t.co/IEeaPsYY5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking: Wayne co. Prosecutors office in Detroit received request for warrant in case involving Allegheny co. Cont… https://t.co/orfu0Ze9W9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jefferson, North Carolina https://t.co/zvSgl9Eq46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing to 3 of the worst teams in the league, with the playoffs on the line, not sure it’s fixable at this point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who said you can't go for walks in #Winter  #BAE @ Stoneham, Massachusetts https://t.co/0X1VZp9Qtz]]></document></documents></author>