<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Love my Mur Happy 40th Birthday Weekend. @ Ocean Drive, South Beach https://t.co/cVFB0BMocU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcranews there has NEVER been an agreement. Stop towing the line for the con man squatting in the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gah, #AAAL2019, why you gotta call me out like that? 😭 #PhDlife #LetsGetADoctorate https://t.co/1oHN0iInGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monocogirl @MSNBC Unfortunately they’re laughing at America too, all while our allies pull further away from us. A… https://t.co/LLRq30VKvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been counting down!! My sweet ST!!! Love ❤️ one of your biggest fans!!! 👍👍😘😘😘😘😘💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#T1391 #TeamMemberAppreciationWeek is Mardi Gras themed!! #LoveOurTeam #WorkSomewhereYou❤️ https://t.co/nY3bH3j4ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[We the American Patriots agree with Jeanine Pirro.  Fox you should defend her as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers going up for u Terrence.🙏🙏🙏Please get well..we need u out here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got word I'll be giving a digital storytelling workshop at the May 2019 Massachusetts @MassService Conference… https://t.co/EFD5nekHda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody still have lead in there body from getting stabbed with a pencil? Cause same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #caturday365 Have kissed your kitty today? #meowmeow @ Georgia https://t.co/2Sz03b9N0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th 🔞 Birthday Carlos!!! Have fun being an adult. 🎂🎂🎂🔞🔞🔞🎈🎈🎈 #legal🔞🎉 https://t.co/hOkwLgdyaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are back, Kevin is still goofy and the music is still jammin. The only thing different from 2008… https://t.co/pPh05y17fH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Hello...where are the dems on tha is one? Do they support drugs coming across border? Why yea.. yea they do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ridingdirty 😉😋 enjoying a day w/ the mamas. @ Chuck E. Cheese’s https://t.co/Gx8hlCEs44]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you curving me? Yes girl I ain't gonna lose my job for messing with an employee lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕#WonderfulWeek @SweetSheil @CarlyleL @LLHunterbooks @sylvia_stein07 @MaryAnnKempher @RichWeatherly43 @emeraldbarnes @damyantig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh! DC Super Hero Girls premier Friday March 8 on @cartoonnetwork!! Check out the theme by me, @mlewey + Dan Pett… https://t.co/kKhJYAy3kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crumps2 We got freezing rain last night then we're having snow up to 8-10 inches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz @CNN @jaketapper I so hope he gets busted for his pompous lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinTetley @CarlDunnJr It’s frustrating as hell when loved ones say they know what you have, but don’t understand… https://t.co/Akdld1tsqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect choice if you want to destroy your life and the lives of everyone around you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for a Spring #FashionShow💗🌷🛍️ Excited to host Apr. 12 with St. Peter's @quintewest #Catholic Womens' League… https://t.co/qAckioHyGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the last 6 months I’ve been stressing about health insurance since both my parents are retiring but they just c… https://t.co/D3KtmnwcMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCynicas If my cat said ANYTHING I’d have questions. Mostly because I’d immediately be afraid of being blackmailed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i couldn’t imagine having a child on this earth and not do anything for them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I really can’t w these silent Uber’s &amp; their GPSs shouting out the directions]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i accidentally ruin things because they’re too good and i don’t believe they’re real🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched a Star is Born🤔music was good but Barbara And Chris we’re better in 70’s!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did this fun lil galaxy jar on a super rad lady, I had a lot of fun with this one space jams are always a blast! Su… https://t.co/rfNK6AeVW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satire can be such a gift at helping us get at the truth. SNL has been playing well.  “For any other US president t… https://t.co/Z2VQENxlJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston I’ve worked 8 jobs since I was 17 and 2 of those were unpaid internships.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @ananavarro @ananavarro is my favorite Republican and my favorite Cuban person and one of my favorite… https://t.co/gQfU50KT1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday chillin’ with the boys #blackcatsofinstagram 🖤 @ Riverside, Connecticut https://t.co/mFo4QDUmxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annelinnwrites Just wrote to welcome you but here's another #Twitter tip. This is just my opinion but if you can,… https://t.co/JtTXUVze4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikkibal92 muchas gracias miguelito. i hope you have a great day as well🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poor woman sounds like she’s gonna pass out during this speech #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Book Harry is a 10+ on the savage scale but Movie Harry has his moments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time i got a bucket of 30 ring pops and i’m sure i was happier than she was when her got that ring]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more sleeps until #stemjourney! #stemeducation #informalscienceeducation #stemeducationforkids #sandwich… https://t.co/kkbtjwMZ5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even when @caelynnmk is crying all I can think about is how amazing her eyelashes look. You show him what he’s missing girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24_ballinMullin “She told me to go buy lemon ginger tea with honey and I fell in love.” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Ana😢💗 so sorry for the loss of your friend. I’m sure she will be smiling from heaven on your wedding day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CarlinaRivera Thanks for giving @NMICnyc a shout out referencing your volunteer days. @UNHNY settlement houses are amazing #WomenOfUNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get all deep and introspective at a gig... #giglife #musician #keyboardplayer @readyin10 @ Astoria, New Yo… https://t.co/bymUmHy6x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the jail transport bus driver gets done with roll call https://t.co/EVOUtccn69]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well hello new glasses! Writing should be super easy now, right? #newglasses #happyfriday #amwriting @ Tallahassee,… https://t.co/QjLecN9Ol3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to throw your ultimate dream party from @PartyCity? Enter here for your chance to #win! https://t.co/YKoLQzrQVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleKashuv @CBSNews , @NBCNews , @ABC , @MSNBC , @CNN will you be covering this?? Probably not. Doesn't fit your narrative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regional powerlifters. Joseph was 1st in the 198 lb. division, Garrett 3rd in the 181 and Rylan  6th in the 165 div… https://t.co/o9HiyM1ivM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews  shares what happened when he and a Univision team was detained at Venezuelan presidential palace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeCample @jericwilson @clarketucker Rest In Peace, Matt. You definitely made this world a better place by being in it. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is written that the calf will lay down with the lion, but this is a bit premature. Taking a catnap next to the b… https://t.co/KWkGAcOtDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kadusaurus Haha I seriously do still get nervous! I'm like, "But what if I want to put this sticker on something e… https://t.co/PGwmBB11Iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Basketball Striv event of the season for yorkmediaproduction. What a great opportunity to get to #striv at PBA… https://t.co/vSNVnY66ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @CaththeWineLady @Julianna_glass… https://t.co/jhEbHbY1EV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump @BravoTV I have the utmost respect for u and always have. Shame on the other woman. Camille was the… https://t.co/WZKwCJavL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klo143 Just need you to know that I read “Blagablagablaga” as Balaga and THE FIRST THING that crossed my mind was… https://t.co/9T8NIiYzeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capitalweather How long is it going to last? Trying to figure out if I should off a trip from Falls Church into DC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Wayne is a divinely gifted wordsmith. He is the greatest rapper of all time ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitterLatAm Personas en Colombia están llamando a ofrecer cuentas verificadas diciendo que son empleados de Twitt… https://t.co/Mn93uRZngS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look out a Original https://t.co/PkidBkTygo Nigga Arron born day dilio was cleaner than a clap doctor today in tha… https://t.co/q3ryWRo7rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @yashar You have to grow your own. Game changer! You will never eat another store bought tomatoe again!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Bärbel Opitz @baerbelopitz07  for liking my poem! Have a nice day Barbel!💚😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took this on ten minuets break at work. I had to listen to music favorite collide by @themodelyouth @AdamLusk11… https://t.co/4NRNjfeqLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyGo2014 @gerrinnesmac @BabyGo2014 very cool thank you and Morning to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[miranda said i could get the biggest Chanel bag in the store, if I want it]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thetoebro.  I'm literally covering my eyes like it's a horror flick.  My whole body is weak as I peak through my f… https://t.co/KjcZvjBrHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joecarryon This can’t be true. Obama has already dealt with innumerable shitshows in his life and sorry to say thi… https://t.co/ijQF0wibGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BertMontreal @VilleLine @dany010363 Le fumoir et la #RemiseEnQuestion sont à 2 heures de route de distance 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryCalviTV Good morning Mary. Missed the very beginning of Tony Tantillo’s segment. What is the name of the resta… https://t.co/PQu9P8TE7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m just imagining what this would be like with all the coinies in the front trying to open the pit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Q13FOX The cops better keeping in eye on this monster. That’s how serial killers start to kill. They start with po… https://t.co/fzRux053Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise I have no confidence in the republicans. They vote always with the communist party. They don’t care a… https://t.co/q7Kaly1RYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My BFFN @bjlamb406 on Amazing @SenatorTester #InternationalWomensDay tweet. 😭😁😁💖💪🏽 Couple of my heroes 💖👑💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up with no voice, thank goodness for pre-recorded Moodle lessons and hot tea from the @LOHS_LC 🤐☕… https://t.co/YiRm11KniD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#toyotatweetyourseat @BuffaloSabres @ffaso3 we billieve! section 101, row 22, seat 33! https://t.co/iD4tAg9bDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#worklifebalance Today we celebrate women and how they #balance today's responsibilities and desires.   I'm traveli… https://t.co/F5uZGMBAsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an infant sitting right behind me on this flight don’t be surprised if I jump out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful ❤Journey   Follow 🖇👣your gut instinct if you are unsure about something usually you gut is right there no… https://t.co/FgoJzYEsdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmkernes @kristyn_1 @NHS_Titans #true Norris FFA flowers are the best!! 🌹🌷🌺🌸🌼🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas https://t.co/ZGur275BmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!  These guys were good sports.  I can only imagine what the fans watching from the stand were thinking as they… https://t.co/FPK1P9yCvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Really!   When You Are Confronted by a Criminal. what Are You Going To@Do If You Need To Save A fam… https://t.co/bX4YXYP9si]]></document><document><![CDATA[This damn dog thinks she’s a cat..... get her a new sweatshirt &amp; you can’t tell her anything... 🤣🤦🏻‍♀️🐶💕 #Bella… https://t.co/IQAN0gtZUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceellla__ I love it when someone gets in your face then you defend yourself and they run off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OLIVlUGH @Chaserrrrs This thread is gonna be the reason I don’t get a job]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_Schiff I adore this lady belt lady. Take that you bunch of clackwankers. I wish she was on MSNBC !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpridgeo @StarlightBarke1 Nope. I’m sick of Winter. And I love snow but enough already!  Bring me back the 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSpeier Hey Jack, u need a better news source other than the Enquire!]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting read. Also reminds us that Asian Americans are a diverse group that includes growing refugee populat… https://t.co/q9hS0V9u8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[these are a few of our first ever messages to each other... then, here we are, a year later, THRIVING!! if ur readi… https://t.co/2SUHvphHer]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOLLOW MY ONLYFANS PAGE FOR THIS CONTENT AND MUCH MORE COMPLETELY UNCENSORED 🔞🔞🔞 NEW CONTENT POSTED DAILY. 👅💦💦💦… https://t.co/viXWdfWnjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset and cocktails! #FtMyers2019 Me and @SusanClerke know how to party! 😊 https://t.co/wBT3nDL9nE]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years ago Buhari was the savior sent by God to deliver Nigeria. Today he is a Tyrant. Lesson: Time flies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eweather13  Snow in HIG...middle of backyard! Photo @kmosk3 ❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotDreamerz Thank you for following me. Every time o did something stupid I would tell my husband "of course,… https://t.co/SlzR8nrujo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHHiiekivi @karenhunter @SylviaKAlston Ummm...My point was made, it’s clear you got it...let’s not dig to the abso… https://t.co/4RSE42j4UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ainsleymannino FIRST of all it was ur bday post SECOND of all ur ass looks fire in that pic and THIRD of all ur f… https://t.co/pOzFwZ0vY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you open a new pack of gum, where do you pick your first piece from?]]></document></documents></author>