<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@theScore @roybelly @FlaPanthers @NHL Here before the 25 people in the stands fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColorstormKid I used to bc it’s easier to balance tbh AHAHAHAH i fall everywhere when I headbang standing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh you must really like movies! What did you think of the Best Picture nominees this year?”  “I, uh, only saw two.… https://t.co/FqrvADdESJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Devil May Cry 5 launch day! I’m excited. Are you excited??  @DevilMayCry https://t.co/dtfEXv6AXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmydunncomedy Wise https://t.co/IEyyKCMPga your self a favor and get there if you can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRINKSUPERCO - OMG!!! Just tried original Super Creamer in my coffee this morning - SO GOOD! I usually hate cream… https://t.co/7ZMBSLt42c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreyGriffon @hypnotosov Though I keep thinking about sampling and photobashing as analogous techniques]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theauntysharon @SemiloooreAkoni @Real_kingAde @Bc_blackchrome @_valkiing @iamvictor__ @dreadnstyn @tolutezzy_… https://t.co/2T2XruT6YU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taylorr1114 No, I just block people who spam what wrestlers do in their private lives. Like I blocked 10+ people y… https://t.co/1vTlunkhu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ldogls @kaysintBB @HondoResists @illegitamatepr1 @GonzoBaggins @ToBeSafeNSound @KITTYBAYOUTSFAN @oldmanliver… https://t.co/EhdGQNUDNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Blaney Podcast was great as always, but the highlight for me was seeing @TheChuckBush rock the @NicePriceBooks… https://t.co/ZWvXvgagtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo @spann @StormHour @NY1weather @weatherchannel @AMHQ @WeatherNation  @511nyNJ @Visit_NJ @NewJerseyNewser… https://t.co/ivPXJLzqp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You never think of anyone but yourself. Even in this series of tweets you say remember I got Otto… https://t.co/tjiwfEEBvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS CHIC PISSED HERSELF AT WHISKEYS AND SHES DANCING LIKE SHES HOT SHIT 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats Pats… https://t.co/ZAHSG16Mwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theNickGalarza clearly can’t take good pictures 🖕🏼 @ The One Up https://t.co/c5PtEPe4lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisShort It’s attainable via several options to me. I am asserting the value and weighing the negatives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all really act like I don’t keep all the receipts. There’s a reason why I’m always getting notified that my iCloud is full. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a recording of my fave English football club playing in Germany on a Mexican channel. I love the times we live in]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hello winter? This is Diane. Keep doing your thing and don’t let the haters hold you back!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful ceremony and beautiful house. Congratulations! Thanks for the invitation @TampaVA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Grindin’!!! @ Dental Creations by Chadwick Webster, DDS, PC https://t.co/CL97KLO47B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @feministabulous That’s right, cover them instead of making guesses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacecowboy_25 @ImDBro @damanr '16 we know why...'17 both healthy... https://t.co/kbkNHfGb8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Points for @LAFC tonight!  What a way to start the season. #ShoulderToShoulder #BlackandGold #3252]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beirut - Landslide (OFFICIAL VIDEO) https://t.co/RhleuZQfDx via @YouTube https://t.co/hvQT3Uy4MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Judging by the results of his actions....certainly nobody's fool. Yet, alone in his struggle, a Christ… https://t.co/310KeUOwpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tashara A blessing! I teared up a lil bit thanking God for waking me this morning. Im getting old........]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why you are awesome! Keep connecting with those kiddos ! #gocrickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning folks! Have a Terrific Tuesday. Time for some coffee. ☕️♥️ https://t.co/r1DDd51gur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottFlorence9 @joferjeff @ScottLakeFoGHMF @MusicNmovieman @FrankSkuddler @RiverCityOtter @jakeisrepugnant… https://t.co/UbWJbsyPQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterCDavid @kcfan4ever84 @RealMNchiefsfan I’ll throw out the same offer that Seth did.  Anyone can shoot me a DM… https://t.co/PVjsB3IR0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianPaulStuart @thehill @PressSec @SarahHuckabee Praise Jesus! What a good Christian family, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidgraeber Perhaps it will inspire her bright young mind to imagine something better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfChrisMJones Biscuits (and bread in general) bring me so much cooking anxiety. Never mastered them. I’m also ju… https://t.co/cMroQhkGZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait for #hizzynationJapan and #hizzynationKorea Feb.23 - March 2!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG the replies to this. Everyone in the US needs to take a remedial constitution  class, especially every dumbass… https://t.co/9n54oe2x5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: First Erica Johnson bucket of the night 🔥 Hiram leading 11-7 with 4:56 in Q1. https://t.co/TzQTHE1Yar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bullsvs76ers #unitedcenter #chicagobulls @ United Center https://t.co/aTMN2dymXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelStudios Saw #captainmarvel last night. The best Marvel film since #InfinityWar. The send off for Stan Lee wa… https://t.co/4Tk4IVXiQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you take your eyes off the Lord, you’ll start stumbling. https://t.co/jCwj04Z5sx via @GregLaurie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @realDonaldTrump I'm middle class, and my family's wages went up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changes from last year’s @NBA2KLeague Draft to this year: Pre-draft red carpet and draft room tables. https://t.co/7zvHg8SAFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guffsafc73 @fight4orkambi @nhsCFwarriormum @ChrisMRiches @VertexPharma @Daily_Express @MotherhoodvsCF @MattHancock… https://t.co/jUqOZoZi5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmywaggs3 Don’t get me wrong Daytona is great but there is so much more going on in Vegas it’s a big sports weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamRackis Lol. The first time I used useRef I thought I needed to use ‘let’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liahhjay It was put on the internet for everyone to see and comment on..]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Arizona’s most vulnerable #students are counting on #education to be a transformative experience that helps them r… https://t.co/UdkhdP6GX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/giCLpk0PsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@schmxnderz I FELT these two tweets! lol Heartburn, and acid reflex are not welcome in this house! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where can I get these throwback shorts the team is wearing...I’m feeling the blue on the side!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InternetNitWit @BDPeacock How expensive do you think the kicker franchise tag is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattzollerseitz I have quoted that line for decades. Also liked how the film critic wanted to be sent to Cannes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una de las cosas que más me pesan de no hablar con la Ale, es que no le puedo decir bbcitAaA  :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jess_Slusser @cvanderark @ErkDay @EmilyLiebtag See you soon - round 2 is on me! Safe travels @Jess_Slusser… https://t.co/e1l6vkcrov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @nytimes There's plenty of room at Guantanamo Bay prison. Send her treasonous ass there. No pity fo… https://t.co/MrqsHoTyej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 I get it. Reflexively, if Brian Kemp and Kris Kobach are promoting #Dieselgate voting systems, polling… https://t.co/CU8LrxV7g1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure there are other videos out there as well. #CohenTestimony #MarkMeadows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luis Miguel - Como Yo Te Amé (Letra) https://t.co/eAYrX7hoxz via @YouTube #Musicmakesourwolrdbetter 🎧🎼🎤🎹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! I’m back in the studio after a sick day... 🤒 How’s your day shaping up so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of filing taxes: "Would you like to designate $3 to the Presidential Election Campaign Fund?"  Me:… https://t.co/vGBtDVWHyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalenaZito Deliberately leaving a paper trail to throw us off the scent.  Genius!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really makes me so happy to see my parents getting each other cute little gifts for Valentine's Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just signed with CHIEFS!!! Thank you so much FAM for supporting me and believing in me this whole time and thank yo… https://t.co/VE4e3yUfLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcmatz565 @dougthinks @DevinNunes Shawn the ultimate point being he wants illegal immigrants out of this country a… https://t.co/Bj5LpFOfa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rollin' the Bones #67  https://t.co/ppd9Gpi7Y4  #amwriting #writing #write #create #creative #utah #saltlakecity #slc #readmorebooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another night at the listening room and meeting the incomparable Richie McDonald!!!! @ The Listening Room Cafe https://t.co/hnbqkEWGRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recommended Weibo to you @adam_white81  lets play hashtag ways s3 tablet in chapters directions aphrodites lomilomi… https://t.co/UrkefaFX80]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a solid playlist. Chill hits on @Spotify 🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/7MGGC7TlMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WebiarPara @anitapatty_ @Milenio @MetroCDMX Libertad de género para el mundo 🌍 😉 y Mexico 🇲🇽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dani21013 Yeah right, it's just fun, I only follow maybe 5 in my state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammy73619415 @RaychelTania @cnnbrk @CharlieDeMar https://t.co/SkA57H0bIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh Rappers these days soft as hell 💀 who apologizes for getting some cookie?   DMX would never]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way outta town #AEAsea - hope you had a great day(s)! See you next time - I’ll add some more details tomorrow… https://t.co/d9GSuoyHHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib your music makes up more than half of my morning playlist &amp; I gotta day thanks a million for your work ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshantiAleyce Its not beer, its brewed though, no alcohol. Ginger ale is just carbonated water and flavor..try it,… https://t.co/2xfPLbRWxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just passed a “Christian Tours” bus. Jesus sends Greyhounds these days?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karencornwell18 @VisitScotland Awesome love the light in this, great work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @HLAurora63 Cherry Hill Psychiatric Meadows Hospital has a special room for Hillary and new experimenta… https://t.co/ZUqv4x13yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “I always feel like lethargic and gross.”   Concerned friends: “Try drinking more water and less Coke Zero.”  M… https://t.co/MuSsRD6vdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pic_pdsb I’m looking into it. Thanks for retweeting and letting me know. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayHMKishimoto @globalnews @CKWS_TV @lraitt Again I ask “Why did Butts quit?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[The EPA should regulate tiny doses of radiation? Tell that to radiation oncologists: To the editor: The article on… https://t.co/rri30fpriS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You didn’t hear that guy say he was a Foles fan? That’s why he can’t wait to get rid of Wentz. So much Eagle on Eagle hate @TyJohnsonNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I sit here and wonder if I'm being stupid or not. Being inside your own head sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last weekend I started the day before dawn with an air temp of -6°F, soaking alone in hot springs. After the sun ca… https://t.co/9gh0IYRCbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the ball keeps rollin. ALL the way through 2024. Keep America Great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouldn’t this be done to any politician before taking an official role?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pewdiepie So I'm going to need about $50,000 if you wouldn't mind please lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter is having one of her friends over for a sleepover... Why do girls have to be so LOUD?! 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early contender for greatest picture I’ve ever seen @TheJudge44 @JColeNC #GOATS https://t.co/FFBaKHmx8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinsonWoodrow @JohnLukeNYC @DavidDiehl20 @DjJasonRoga @SanaMello @annamariesporch @bonniebarnard @dorner_martina… https://t.co/malqzgxrdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RySanchez74 @AevilaRandall @Ruggles24 @Unexplained Just because you haven't seen it didn't mean they don't do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCKatie @CBCNews Rookie politician   Not been on the planet long enough  Needs better advisors   Is that enough or I can go on ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[So arrogant pricks like Obama don't end up in office again?? Yeah then I agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why is it when a story involving you comes out everyone is a liar??]]></document><document><![CDATA[For this reason a man will leave his father and mother and be united to his wife, and they will become one flesh. -… https://t.co/eJYDQfszOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bulls have Zach Lavigne to take over games. Celtics have no one. Where is Kyrie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NShakhraichuk @drmcgettigan @eaglebotics @STEAMatNBPS @FRCTeams Nice tweet for Eaglebotics by Nikita!]]></document><document><![CDATA[please keep my abuelita in your prayers. she’s having major surgery today 🙏🏻]]></document></documents></author>