<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[5. Be patient. We are fearful of the next exacerbation (flare-up) that may wreak havoc on our bodies. So if you're… https://t.co/i38mdarjHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks exactly TWO months since I launched my YouTube channel and I’m REALLY close to 28k subscribers!! I look… https://t.co/SF0xYSHKRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart is resting a whole lot easier tonight. God is good, all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgarzambranoad Disfruta cuando puedas, tu cena 🥘 o whisky 🥃 y recuerda que estos niños, podrían ser tus hijos.💔😔… https://t.co/tvaep1tS1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are grateful for the opportunity to speak on Trisomy 18 at this month's Parent Connections meeting with the Madi… https://t.co/6pQ1uBdgJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[been listening to less pop punk lately and more hippo campus and i must say i finally know what it feels like to be a la croix ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why I've been blessed 🙌🏾 #Goodmorning @ Kalamazoo, Michigan https://t.co/ec2qTt9Nvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live life on the edge 🤘🏻 @ Watkins Glen State Park https://t.co/X58COcqbL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@19rusInfo @andersen7474 Статья - результат вызваный бредом и галлюцинациями!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris Don’t hold your breath! One by one, every decent and healthy law is being slashed to pieces before… https://t.co/A775zqnBwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sam__Bordeaux @SonOfGodAndMan I perceived it as word salad. Comedy is so sneaky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! This is a critical issue for action. Read @FamiliesUSA statement on these important bills we discussed with le… https://t.co/mumJAQfWxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[With some aoiinetwork8 Specialists at the AOΠ Delta Nu house. Amazing house - fun visit! ❤️🌹#whyaoii @ Reno, Nevada https://t.co/MlD3U02OSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[how lucky am I to work with these amazing, gorgeous fitness professionals with @ucsdfitlife ucsdrec #cardiosport… https://t.co/Ch7PXmvde1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning rebuke of Andrew Scheer’s Conservatives in #Outremont by-election. His party, with no plan to address the… https://t.co/enLYKLD2Mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE doesn’t rely on your SWORD to save HER because SHE carries HER own💥⚔️💥.  #Repost chiarapesciph - - - - - - Coll… https://t.co/S67a2Clwxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[On vacation and the Airbnb has VR! Exciting to see headsets in the wild. Hope this becomes more common in the futur… https://t.co/gghs6i6mcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[De los 13 estados que conozco en #USA , #Florida es de los más bonitos! #IloveUSA #USAmysecondcountry en West Palm… https://t.co/qUBxOIVrFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg @mrjaxtaylor saying he doesn’t feel comfortable with those random girls around even when they’re not even reall… https://t.co/Yx28UCVYTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to switch games to watch the Iginla tribute video. And wow. What a beauty of a video it was. | #Flames⁠ ⁠ | #ThankYouIggy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#backtotheGYPSYthatiwas #HERfacesaysFREEdom #RISE #BlackLilith #GuanYin #kuanYin #QuanYin #GODDESS #wisdom #freedom… https://t.co/jSxlwlcTp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot expect me to eat only 3 Oreos. I will always eat an entire row thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHeathervaughn @BaumanKym @HHeldorfer @flybry55 Right? I can’t stop! The little legs! Pink toes! Squeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @ABowden320 Sarah Carden and Christa Rushing for bringing the Richmond Hill Middle School Band, Chorus… https://t.co/n2IESp2eiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump He must have some pretty dangerous goods on you for you or ANYONE of ANY party, l… https://t.co/U1T9BIJDke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marked for cutting 😢 Yes, He owns the land. Yes, he’s within the law. But, wow. My heart hurts. An entire woods, ev… https://t.co/m5ellcfumH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What we learned is that Ron Harvey is on top of Sara Rothschild who is Marguerite DeWitt and we need to find out wh… https://t.co/WXWXx2COmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBlackChannel He's another Edward Snowden, exposing nothing new, heralded as a revolutionary by fools]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pruebe este batido de chocolate de Fórmula 1 con un plátano y un refuerzo de proteínas. La Fórmula 1 proporciona un… https://t.co/rY4Gvi77hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #SaintJoseph, MI, check out this #SocialSciences job via the link in our bio: Medical… https://t.co/0tvmPm8p9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW: #DIY || Easy Marbled Moon Phases Garland.  https://t.co/Y6XUYD1kQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willowsmith333 hahahah it’s february 22 and my dad didn’t wish me a happy birthday hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniepotts deserves an Emmy as meemae on @YoungSheldon ! She steals the show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joyce_Karam It’s becoming evident that #ClayHiggins doesn’t understand the meaning of the word “returned”. They we… https://t.co/2AZ44xd2RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overwatch! Let’s do it! https://t.co/UgOss13VKk https://t.co/4wrlxJJQbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's picture of the day. @ Hesperia, California https://t.co/ZanbcBNoGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hstgerard @davidmweissman @davidcicilline @nicj9311 @BarackObama I see you are proving your motto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storm Lacrosse is underway! Great first day men🔥😤🤙🏼 I love seeing all the new faces! It’s getting 🔥 in here !… https://t.co/fHTx07ezTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re ready to roll!! If you are downtown look for us on the first float of the Order of Athena! 🎊🎭 https://t.co/krT7sZbbWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regretfully—I never saw one of his performances.  How Prince Gave All the Freaks a Dance Floor https://t.co/Qee1y3iHDo via @johnpavlovitz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trainee priests from Texas as getting into their stride. The Papal Bulls press back to the Texans’ half.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#simplelife #onelove❤️ #qualitytime @ South Riding, Virginia https://t.co/Om7bZ62KDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Autism Speaks Town Hall on Navigating an Autism Diagnosis in Sacramento.  What a great night! @ UC Davis MIND Insti… https://t.co/h7iuCuhIxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Oldest middle child. I have a sister who has a different dad,didn’t live with us who is 10 years older… https://t.co/GCUUQeLP5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen's opening statement, saying about Trump...  "He is a racist. He is a conman. He is a cheat."]]></document><document><![CDATA[robert garcia’s solution? build angels stadium right on the water. TONS of drunk fans’ litter and debris will be de… https://t.co/5NcGvwiQNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeFOX29 Mike, Mike, Mike. You used to say you wouldn’t talk about that “K” family. What happened? ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erindavis @cityoftoronto And thank you Erin Davis for all the mornings you got up so damn early and gave us such a… https://t.co/4xNs6jJ1uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Mueller Float? Is that like two scoops of vanilla floating in redacted root beer, sprinkled with indictments and… https://t.co/0OqVdzYiDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JABell27 @Breanna_clark01 @iAaron357 @dvdpeters @GenuineDCR @jkass99 @kate_germano @DarioDiBattista @conusbattle A… https://t.co/2SZ8kd1HLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich Actually, Newtie, Poll says Americans believe what Cohen says over what Trump says. You know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday brunchin’ with my bestie @honourhobbs 💗 @ succotash https://t.co/ik0Sh3uK2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes No thanks. I like the real world. I don't need to dive into a fake one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTrumpForce Ya think?  I think she failed at brain development period 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The US is orchestrating a coup in #Venezuela. We’ve seen this before - Guatemala in 53' Chile in 73' Honduras in 09… https://t.co/tWWJJSy6eE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Ash Wednesday my dudes 🥽 #ashtag #thatashtho #ashwednesday @ Our Lady Of Perpetual Help, Carrollton, Georgia https://t.co/pELj3PPJLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigga’s ain’t got to many chances with me! Act out once and we rumbling bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter always says I have DMs, then I go and there’s nothing there. https://t.co/jYXduobyq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why hello there kanebrownmusic. @ Covelli Centre https://t.co/Eizi0VyrUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it creepy that I want to have all my friends locations on at all times? mostly just so I know when they’re nearb… https://t.co/wVqWbba3nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanO_Appleseed Balance has always been a problem for me. I have to hold on while I use the treadmill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao i told little dude he better ask my cousin to prom the right way.. and i said use a pizza right.. and he said… https://t.co/cwUFpDHPxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿A las cuantas menciones @laorejadevgogh te comienza a seguir en Twitter? https://t.co/d28j0Nry3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobpigott Word. I'm trying a new food place every month....Note, I didn't say new food but a new place. 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay problemas para la conexión remota... Y yo que llegué con toda la actitud a la oficina. https://t.co/JSIU4HCHLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching video after video of people throwing their Vans https://t.co/4DfynutnL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennisChannel You should at least split screen the two matches but focus on Osaka/Collins match!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ty_the_np @Plasticdoe @Just4TheCause @maddpig @urbanx_f @EmmaGPaley @EugeneBu @Siubhan_H @mcfunny @Rosewind2007… https://t.co/yh0ZHEFfJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a mom, aunt, nana, or godmother with a male student at GCMS? Don’t miss out on the Mother-Son dance tonight… https://t.co/0o0wJdpBDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The soul becomes dyed with the colour of its thoughts  #marcusaurelius  #quoteoftheday  #fluidart #Arttherapy… https://t.co/paWWCT3sea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido praying for God’s miracles, breakthrough, sanity of righteousness, healing, freedom, justice, democracy, s… https://t.co/GenDNLY588]]></document><document><![CDATA[A better #tbt with the main man, Norris,  cheering the #colonels on to VICTORY at Rupp. 💙 circa2️⃣0️⃣1️⃣4️⃣🏀🏆#khsaa… https://t.co/raQTzNw2Ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bitsandbytes @NASA @SpaceX @Space_Station @Commercial_Crew I think Redwood Falls has the potential to get hit hard this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 This is good. All educators of every level need to ask themselves this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savvyfatty Watch that whole interview on YouTube. Chile...☀️💕 #BlackExcellence]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fear of being different prevents most people from seeking new ways to solve their problems. -Rich Dad Poor Dad #MondayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tin City in Naples, FL w/ @mattkensethis1 https://t.co/CwL8Xby6Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the record, I think that everyday is #LoveYourPetDay but it’s still a good excuse to post photos of this handso… https://t.co/k6tPfvb0Rz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anybody was incredibly curious, yes I am available tomorrow to be wined, dined and 69’ed :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanamongeau i’m not going to playlist but can i meet you somewhere anyways? 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s also insufficient to suggest that, like Asimov and his view of how train a robot class of being, slaveholders didn’t also presuppose...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quand l'artiste crée une pose sur une cliente de la communauté culturelle ; le tan de la peau ne peut que faire une… https://t.co/GIyM8UZR22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 I’m sorry Dax. Wish I could be there to help. Just this past summer went thru this with my own mom. Life g… https://t.co/Pd6if82cfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would a high-performing and exceptionally resplendent #WebDesign interest you? Openwave is a professional… https://t.co/SyvSLb2njD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alhamdulillah. I just got PB home. He's doing well and resting. Jazakallah to everyone for all of your duas/prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost alonsojlujan ・・・ JELLYFISH, music video is out now!  LINK IN BIO. Awesome job to the amazing cast and crew!… https://t.co/L4rSkTHDlH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbeRakov I’ve been debating letting my 11yo watch it because it was so amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Braithy99 @MC_squared_ A jury of Michael’s peers said he was innocent. These people have been paid and they’re sti… https://t.co/vzHLHMZ2ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilMurphyNJ I sincerely hope you will not entertain this! These people put children in danger by not just releasi… https://t.co/IVD0znxG1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think that I, a legal adult, am not excited about the @jonasbrothers releasing new music then you would be mistaken.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremynewberger That is such a bunch of BS!!!! Why would they give a moment of silence. No one died!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[*rips mouth hole of face mask open wider so I can eat chips peacefully*]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Trump-Pence administration's dangerous gag rule is designed to cut patients off from care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/wxk9rbKcYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheltieman3 Sharing your pain. Addiction runs rampant in my family also. See if you can hit an Alanon meeting. IMO… https://t.co/TPxCKFOcHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I found a parking spot where I won't have to move my car in the morning for street cleaning 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenGardner11 @PolitiBunny Andras Schiff- French Suites, or Italian Suites, or any]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woke_kid @TwitchyTeam How sad , I hope he learns that those things aren't important . Being true to yourself is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never will I forget  I’m still going to run my fade   Even if it’s two or five years from now]]></document><document><![CDATA[please look at the wholesome content my dad sends me https://t.co/rXFKLwwpFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really do not like anyone atm. I’m very hurt. I put my all into someone just to get played or mistreated. This ha… https://t.co/si3REq3Rbc]]></document></documents></author>