<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Putin to Turkey and Iran: We must crush militants in Syria's Idlib https://t.co/w2PRshFiLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning SMILES. Good VIBES. ...and whole lotta PRAYER. 🙏🏽 on this Itty Bitty Plane ✈️ hoping over to Jacksonville..… https://t.co/FHruCoHjve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the #mobiwrap ! I am embracing the moments where I feel like I am conquering #momlife milestones ✌️😎💪👩‍👧… https://t.co/xzlT2b85FY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Bet his so called memos to self after meetings with President Trump were fabricated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[boa sexta amigos guarulhenses, não esqueça de marcar seu amigo nos comentarios do moloko pra tentar ganhar um vip em!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad is on another level of laziness. he put pants on top of his shorts because he didn’t want to take his shorts off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oigan, ahora @MirandaProducc  Presenta la Nueva Temporada de  “ Por Amor “ Viernes 8:30 pm  A partir de mañana 22 d… https://t.co/DNjVFJlznk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures 🏰  #vanderbiltmansion #views @ Vanderbilt Planetarium and Mansion https://t.co/MgTn75gIsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is our Company Recognition for #CustomWireless Your premium retailer for T-Mobile. #WorkHardPlayHard… https://t.co/SD6OUG2lIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are extremely ugly cute. It would honestly depend on the day to determine the sway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJPalermo 100%!! Nutrition is a lot easier than most make it out to be, I just think there’s an over saturatio… https://t.co/lMI3VGTcOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[AC needs to step down. Trump let the camel’s nose in the tent, now can’t get rid of her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you already almost 8months old?! @ Rockwood, Ontario https://t.co/kou6USFbQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #TruckNutz convoy has arrived in Ottawa!  Naturally, looking a lot more modest now that they've stepped down fr… https://t.co/HFtr0x9rmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering today on Hallmark channel on direct TV Now !! Luke Perry LOVE in PARADISE !! You Want be Forgotten on O… https://t.co/iM4gHmNKOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imposible no soltar las lagrimas ante tus palabras, creo que era justo lo que teníamos que escuchar. Gracias… https://t.co/wSabi2R5NN]]></document><document><![CDATA[life been hitting me from every angle but mama ain’t raise no weak bitch so it’s coo lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of birthdays to this beautiful soul 😭😘🥳🎈🎉 @Little_Vee_  love youuuuu!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had something with bbq sauce on it and I got food poisoning and I haven’t been able to eat bbq sauce since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveAndyC I think he is spot on. Since last season I think LVP wanted her castmates to think she was taking up for… https://t.co/woT95H9s5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not be aiding the Saudis, Trump and Pence in a pre-planned character assassination. https://t.co/ypSjK1kdNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire Kavanaugh hearing was a farce.  Blassey Ford lied under oath; Feinstein and others accommodated the dece… https://t.co/fMaoOfDikF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#charlottecountyva Where even the cows are photogenic on a foggy #morning debs_daylilies #familyfarm #countryroads… https://t.co/NXxycErQxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhenIs2001 @chick_in_kiev It's a seriously depressing situation when we get sick and every path to healing is a mo… https://t.co/fpzO6BfAP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Rising Stars had a great time at DI and did a fabulous job representing Mt. peak! @MtPeak_Elem  #MISDHappy… https://t.co/Qd2BXbyHxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how many times this man has to cheat on Khloe for her to understand that he doesn’t want her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me on this Monday!! Today bitch slapped me but I took it like it a woman ;] https://t.co/bq7WPCHcY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's still Friday on the west coast...  So, lemme post this dope flashback. I often take pics and look back at them… https://t.co/Ro6suPWFfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to realize Helen Mirren had a great time at the #Oscars last night. Her Instagram is 🙌🏻 https://t.co/IZWkkGE1XG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmales1 Like I just can’t help but think...you really are DUMB dumb...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/3dlTdaaqXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pneprincess @Hector_Shar_Pei @kath_gunn @TatumTotThePug I grew up with a cat named Babs.  My parents have 2 cats right now.  Peg and Ollie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett You should be ashamed of yourself. I hope you don't talk this way to everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We would like to thank the “9 Pastors from The Greenwood SC community” who visited the venue of our upcoming March… https://t.co/kvQbUugvmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Hope California is returning money. Isn't there a private company to buy out the project. Fast rail wo… https://t.co/qzyZPkoeAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeeSzczotka Hey, I have it a shot once before, would totes do it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Kimberl38218406 @functionofbeau1 thank you 😊 I love ❤️ you have know idea 💡 love ❤️ peace ✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When are you putting in another Judge? We are so excited to see another “good one” go in🙌🙏🙌🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@picklepepppers Google it, or watch Conspiracy on Netflix! There’s literally endless reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorothyLucey I made one last weekend with a chuck roast it was so good]]></document><document><![CDATA[following @pazpaz on social media has been more entertaining than anything else lately 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain bubbles and ripples! @ Metz Stage Stop Cemetery https://t.co/KUHymOYjMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it that every time you  switch lanes, the lane you were on starts moving? #I4problems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @AnaAndrade305 @TereOrt51687394 @ElbaklySami @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias… https://t.co/9JsaaNxykJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracyelmore @dannumbers @dbongino Why are you so obsessed with his junk? It's really odd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning and realized I haven’t taken a rest day in 10 days.... I guess that’s what I’ll be doing today 😞😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ordered Denny’s on ubereats because I scrolled &amp; seen pancakes 😂🤘🏾 now hurry up &amp; get in my belly 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump @PandoraVT Thank y’all awesomely blessed beautiful &amp; prayers grace &amp; Love 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on an adventure with us to @pipsisland! We start previews today on the corner of 42nd Street and 9th! #nyc… https://t.co/BX0LLm3aYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When bae catches you checking your gains 😂🙈  . . . . #bodybyzizzo #physique #bootygains #trainer #bae #la… https://t.co/S6K31zDcZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaleBeers @GoExplorers @LaSalleMBB Absolutely!   #Believe see you Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@normal_militant @robdone3500 @julie_kelly2 @MollyJongFast LOL. You and your 820 big followers. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAngello85 @kylegriffin1 It's not a democracy if illegals are voting.  Or dead people.  I'm totally in favor of re… https://t.co/avNyOKsH1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoolS509 @LoLife_Story @LeVeonBell I won’t give 1 man that power over a whole team. If someone left a business, th… https://t.co/JT9AIJPaeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chloe tore her ACL in her back right knee so, as the saying goes, if the jersey fits, wear it, right?… https://t.co/ngsyqbew0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why this should not be the case. In Japan, there is housing that was used so many decades ago where the cost is $20… https://t.co/IcbbWaNcD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for @JRMotorsports in the #eNASCARHeat Pro League Draft! Go to https://t.co/b9CaNqdZ2o to cast your vote for JRM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldrsk8r @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Hey, Pip Squeak, I think you just called Trump’s next job. He’d make a… https://t.co/8Y6inkVrUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump 2) Mexico as that would run into problems with Mexican drug running gangs.… https://t.co/B9RFLYnt0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump ALL YOU CROOK TRUMPS HAVE DONE A GREAT JOB THE LAST 2 YEARS... CHECK THE… https://t.co/6kC72uCCGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So back to court to lose another round.  45 never gets enough of that.  He doesn't understand ther… https://t.co/37GkmhpHCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @LindseyGrahamSC Well, that ought to help with negotiations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MumblerJamie My superpower would be the ability to fly. Problem solved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a fun day at Seaworld 💙The dolphins are always my favorite 🐬 @ SeaWorld Orlando https://t.co/vJ1NCostIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[every female should shave their head at some point in their life..i swear u become a new person 🌻🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've watched Moana dozens of times. Today I'm crying because the grandma dies?!  I LOVE PERIOD HORMONES.  #HotMess… https://t.co/6OVBialVkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[somehow my dad n i r talkin abt natalie portman n he brought up her old snl rap skit omfg he rly is my dad we stan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy late birthday queen!! I’m sorry i forgot to post you yesterday/: but I hope your birthday was so special ♥️💕… https://t.co/LfRDC3AJ7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tempus_invictus https://t.co/AleXjxIkrm  Trump doesnt have the full say on what's spent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Fuck you McConnell!! Dont spin this shit to fit your purpose when you support a racist lying sack of… https://t.co/otNHxvEOWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ringing the gong to celebrate the purchase of a New 2019 Yamaha GP1800R! Thanks &amp; enjoy the new ride!… https://t.co/a0AA6T3LxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me today ! Thank god im home and no one has to put up with me anymore https://t.co/8vYN4Z5sKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldenJoseph50 Rock the bells 2013 was one of the best I went to early on https://t.co/wgCugJJibQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPGomezMen @Pelwchy @FGRMexico @ErnestinaGodoy_ @lopezobrador_ @Claudiashein @lopezdoriga @CiroGomezL @CiroDi… https://t.co/OYp11aB3ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drove to school 2 hours early to study more for an exam I had just to find out classes were cancelled today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders THE BENIGN NEGLIGENCE, OR THE DEMAGOGUERY ABOUT THE REPINOCHETIZINH OF LATIN AMERICA will keep US home.… https://t.co/Ld0YFmAB1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a world of ugly lately, but, like this lone urban daffodil, I still feel like the luckiest gal on the pla… https://t.co/wDAomig1Go]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Travis is a badass and what not for fending off that mountain lion, but let me tell you, he’s also witty and… https://t.co/nEb8qJka4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Kate-lynn Bull's video! #TikTok https://t.co/0OkPY3rF6H takes "do the robot" to a whole new level!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ended up getting so many blisters,but it was worth it #senioryear #2k19 https://t.co/v9ktNLSsPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on thru.. Hosted by: Yours Truly  PRESS PLAY.... 2DAY... The Hottest Sexiest Grown Folks Mid Day-Day Party in… https://t.co/UA5sVTrvlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I love being a single mom and other times my garbage bin is frozen solid to the ground.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Predictions about books using the historical context, fractions explanations using models... is like heaven… https://t.co/IfDM0cu7LF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr @dbongino Everyone that voted against protecting babies should go in delivery and see if they could a… https://t.co/RejK3S5e2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then she hit you with the A’s long as I can spit it back on your dick 😂🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg #BoysInTheBand on repeat while I try to get my work done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UMaryWrestling @umarysports @umary @NDHEADLOCK Wahoo! Way to grind it out @barny133! #BurnTheBoats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyElves Watching my words. Praying for our Leaders to have Wisdom &amp; Insight to remove Obstructions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is just plain Evil 👿 and should retire now she make such a fool of herself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to give away 2 bottles! So our two winners today are wanderin_wires and @AmandaShaw0906! You both have won… https://t.co/IxA6iFtgHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing students were sexually assaulted when they claim they told you.  Jim Jordan your going to be voted out of o… https://t.co/wJTgkHua4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to ask my therapist about it tomorrow, but what do my ND friends do to make morning transitions easier? W… https://t.co/vMWX6Uf439]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zorba4422 @DonaldJTrumpJr Do you know how many democrats hire ILLEGAL ALIENS ! All of Hollywood and company. So 🤐up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneunderscore__ Hopefully the SDNY has that asked and answered. If not, that may be the area where Cohen is withholding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need like 4 years before I start having kids. I have a little more growing up to do 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting read for anyone in VC. Congrats to all involved @HotelTonight https://t.co/b1EcK7Uzug]]></document><document><![CDATA[I waited patiently for the Lord. He turned to me and heard my cry. Psalm 40:1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thirty never looked so good 🤩 #happyanniversary #happy30th #phimu #phigamma #loveyou #phimuforever @ UMBC https://t.co/u4XPCRhhCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizziecrossing @bttrnot Ok i hope this is real cause if it is 😵😵😵😵😵😵😵😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey effort is effort and budgets are real, idk people’s stories and struggles]]></document></documents></author>