<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RevLouisBerkhof @jonmoffitt Right b/c moral choice is a work. To choose to have faith then becomes a work. Rather… https://t.co/Tf1sUvJt6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Hawks go up 12-7 in the first quarter! @PaulPkolin @BHBlackHawks https://t.co/AFgyJbCeBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Translation: damn, we don’t have any evidence on which to base an impeachment. The wrap up smear failed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMankiewicz I'm frankly more worried about President Schadenfraud than I am about an actor's personal problems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolChief @acalabrese39 that toe drag on NHL executed perfectly by Saad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney @JohnCornyn U r just a sh1thead @GOP.  What happened to u as u left MA?  Then u were just a greedy… https://t.co/ItoKOEN7c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over here turning up minding my business when my friends are hitting me up telling me my raiders got @AB84 holy shit 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @SecPompeo What progress - trump (and you???) now believes 2 brutal dictators who are enemies of this country… https://t.co/Ukc1oBcIFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I say to myself, "not my problem" --&gt; Shrugging of the shoulders --&gt; Overwhelming sense of joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You get $174,000 for the rest of your life... total $9.5 million.   Many work for $30,000 a year.   Have you s… https://t.co/xAiyofq7QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME | Ole Miss 39, Kentucky 38  Keldon Johnson leading the way with 14 pts, followed by Herro with 13 pts (7-7 from the field)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bazaar_Man Like me when i roll your bitch ass. https://t.co/JOIsCtFMxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tangerineswft Omg no!!! They were going to be saved and have a second life!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNECKMOFO Good news for you .. damn them tornadoes did so much damage .. I just watched on the news again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoJoLego Yeah so if I smell that or phantom smells I worry it’s a tumor pressing on my olfactory nerve]]></document><document><![CDATA[a corporate revenue scheme doesn’t matter boo, you’re loved by many people doesn’t have to be a specific person u h… https://t.co/ydM543ACCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[While in his high chair during dinner, and in the family room after dinner, Thomas was entertaining us by singing a… https://t.co/fs4oUrlh7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rock Creek Park - The Line in Chevy Chase, MD https://t.co/cWpnsuSWlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason why the education system is watered down, The teachers qualifications has been watered down. Half the te… https://t.co/g8oEnD98AJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoRules1 @gamermom742 @AOC Who are you? I just checked your IMDb page and didn't see anything relevant on your resume]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidNakamura @roripierpont1 "Mom, Martians descended from the sky and their space ship dented your car in the mal… https://t.co/76aGNhEOlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump MORE GOLF ON THE TAXPAYERS DIME!!!! https://t.co/56IKVRzHWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“white people have no culture”?  then how do you explain the millions of ukulele covers of i can’t help falling in love and riptide?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Land of yummy (@ Lindt Outlet Boutique in Toronto, Ontario) https://t.co/H6gS38r5GL https://t.co/a3nIpDuuyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Oscars: we got nothing so here is @QueenWillRock featuring Adam Lambert for no real reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥶 FIRST ALERT 🥶: A FREEZE WARNING has been issued. Tonight will be one of the coldest nights of the winter. Tempera… https://t.co/8JPvdASKap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haircut + Photoshoot Bookings Open on my Website   💥Link N Bio 2 Book💥     #Barber #barberlife #barbershop… https://t.co/GyJIFC3Biv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can jump in w that specific #wacist quote from @POTUS anytime you want #vague]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too fucking true. I will work to see him defeated and if he isn't, well, Belize looks like nice place to live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laurie Anderson, "Language is a Virus (from Outer Space) https://t.co/XpUfVRH9NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumpthendp OK but you have to admit that while it *looks* like they're preparing a soft landing for Mueller... and… https://t.co/H8wePtZu33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broadway musicals!  Matt resembles this leading man in this flop (but amazing) musical.  What is “American Psycho?”  #Jeopardy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detroit Pistons Game Warm Ups @ Little Caesars Arena https://t.co/VjDUt1fpnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maniuhg @CNN Of course, if it doesn't suit your agenda, it's fake.. E U will cease to exist because people like yo… https://t.co/ooH0ep4W4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[The caramel cloud macchiato is actually really good I want it more often. Does anyone know how the cinnamon one is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twtmpodcast @BrotherWdw @Parkeology @ChrisKinn2 @MMDisneyChalle1 On it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedDeadRedemption2 Currently on Chapter 6 and it has me lowkey getting in my feels with how things are turning out… https://t.co/LDQ12RVop9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budlight please cleanup your containers! Aluminum is very recyclable but is trash when on the roadside.… https://t.co/QWSxrB5zdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude is the freaking Paul Newman of cats. @ Montclare, Chicago https://t.co/jITzxhNdGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark_carnelley @SusannePan @orianthi @Spicy24 @laceylau @ItsMeganAndrews @MQuigley1963 @pursoot @RAndrewAuthor… https://t.co/f76IHZmrlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afriendlywhit Part of a large Mississippian/Pennsylvanian platform conodont. That’s my guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raw honey from the FL Keys!🌴🐝🌴 @freshfromFL #FloridaKeys https://t.co/G1P3n1mCWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sur le plateau de @CTVOttMornLive ce matin avec l’ancien quart-arrière du Rouge et Noir, @HenryBurris! • Interview… https://t.co/62VG0XqMAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdBouchette @JoshWilsonSB @the_spru looks like someone is going to massively overpay]]></document><document><![CDATA[The headline doesn’t really match what the article is saying. The article talks about everyone loving it, except fo… https://t.co/15EwBmUtZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait for it..... • • • Fellow @balancemma student bahir_gjj_selfd_mma411 crushing some box jumps during his primer… https://t.co/BxxhGcxZoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[How really disgusting , the nomination committee should reject that immediately!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southern American should be considered the language of love. “Baby I’ll be back! Gonna go get us dinner, Johnny cal… https://t.co/HiDJEKzENa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: Bible Prophecy Warns Us about Islam https://t.co/Nod2DvV4Dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMANSokol @MSigrist83 @ChannelFireball Yeah it's fantastic, but I don't have it in the top couple commons, which it seems like he does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought the @FitbitSupport charge 3 and I can't add any bank cards for the wireless payment. I've disconnecte… https://t.co/djI0mV6xtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignK27 @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/fbdxkQ0Sh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started making my own frozen pizza and while it means I'm a crazy person,  it's also mega cheap and insanely bett… https://t.co/LlEFyqYI17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1BlackCovfefe @Brownsfan252 @gleorod @nypost @AOC Once again... the person I was replying to was talking about job… https://t.co/kvhHwxBJc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future Marines 🇺🇸 Felt good to bring home a trophy. We came motivated and ready to fight. That’s what we do best. O… https://t.co/ohhBMBhACk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess everyone there knows Jesus Christ preached shoot first and ask questions later. Frauds who admire a man who… https://t.co/xiQY9fCkmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than ideal conditions, but the breds and pairs got their new sale tags today.  Gonsior Simmentals Production s… https://t.co/C9KTKLQo5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job by our Student-Athletes led by one of the best in the business @KamariWooten]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a bank of Number Strings for HS Geometry, Algebra 1 and/or negative numbers. (Or at least a couple samp… https://t.co/AB52i75LAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay!🎊 Here’s my awesome wife’s reverse-sidekick board-break!👊🏻🥋 HIYAAAA!!!  #ATA… https://t.co/PAGNWXw9Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTMommaBear2017 @SenatorTester @ABCFOXMT LOL.  What are you rambling on about-obviously you voted for Tester.  The… https://t.co/H0qcpoZlSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganDobson @benshapiro harry reid? He’s still alive? retired?  Ah, got it! Still politically irrelevant and breat… https://t.co/HxcMiFctwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrandtAgency @MountainWest @TheRunninRebels Yeah, that’s a stretch. Especially when B1G, ACC could possibly get d… https://t.co/iDmppUfnR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CathyYoung63 2013–17 according to an early review of the professor’s upcoming book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CwbrownCom Nice!! But who’s the old woman holding the cup standing next to you in the first pic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promise to live Our Promise! Do you? #OurPromise https://t.co/m8OlssNkeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[As much as I hate him, I agree with @SpeakerPelosi  - based on the evidence presented so far, it wouldn’t be worth… https://t.co/94D05hrT9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh, make your payments on time, pay off your debts early to avoid paying extra interest, don't run up credit card d… https://t.co/RsHNMPU5Uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[NAHHH FUCK MICHAEL HE CAN GO BACK TO BEING DEAD JANE AND RAFAEL ARE ENDGAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[0100100100100000011011000110111101110110011001010010000001000001011100000111001001101001011011000010000001110011011… https://t.co/1FXKQbWSlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ooh_stephanie @jennajameson Fuck what that says, you’re telling me you’d rather kill a baby than give it a fighting chance to have a life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right, a raspberry stout, interesting and funky in a good way - Drinking an Intellectual Property by District 96 Be… https://t.co/DPW4P7pkB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles when are you gonna get the Singles Repeating Black on Black Hoodie back in stock!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Encouraging meeting with @FBCPerryFL Church Council this afternoon talking about reality, perception, and ministry.… https://t.co/zIgK8pa39a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders HEY LOSER STOP TRYING TO SELL US YOUR BULLSHIT LIE'S TO THE AMERICAN PUBLIC, https://t.co/qfKHZZ9Ayn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnfel202 @LollllllaJR @Vrouwe @Ian_Flaming @mariamtayob @methuengena @mitsusumashi @speedymc67 @fladjah… https://t.co/UX4V0i4EtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinRyder13 @joshuagates You even look constipated like him:)...@erinRyder13 @joshuagates #BRINGERINBACK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisGriffiths @USMCLiberal @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews https://t.co/VZBlUx7vmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNC @TheDemocrats rather suffer more violence on the American People than stopping the flood of illegals - which h… https://t.co/qo3laYLAfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are on the market for a gaming room security camera I highly recommend this one https://t.co/IBv5MaitKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shanebaldwin82 @RealTlkFB @stephenasmith No lol, not a single person that has watched him play calls him a run fir… https://t.co/MlvlJFgI0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[got this piece of incendiary politics in the mail and laughed bc it failed to mention that she wants to tackle crim… https://t.co/EsCjcsKQaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibogost Platforms completely unlike Facebook, but with certain key features inherent in ubiquitous computing, have… https://t.co/AMkqzap0Bk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themikeypick @SportsCenter @mcten Something he's only done TWICE (this will be the 2nd time) since his finals stre… https://t.co/Pr0fz31T94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vic Mensa Freestyle w/ The L.A. Leakers - Freestyle #067 https://t.co/gzisIV1HrF via @YouTube  😬🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ChicagoVAMC  STOP USING PRIVATE/UNKNOWN PHONE NUMBER TO CALL VETERANS ABOUT THEIR APPOINTMENTS!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm still a @MillerCoors Man...but this is a good cause.  P.S. the Corn Syrup commercials are stupid, but if it hel… https://t.co/pQXSjd39bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure like to see that smoke when I pull in from work https://t.co/PAJvhqr5XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYPD has no respect for this city, its laws, and the people who live in it. They make them up, enforced when they f… https://t.co/fZrIvlZwJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler One day closer to Manafort’s sentencing and the release of the Mueller Report:) #GlassHalfFull]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year when all Mexican moms flex their capirotada on Facebook and get the “uyyy que rica, porque n… https://t.co/4VcGv0zxcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Mueller's office notifies judge of post from Roger Stone that could violate his gag order....Lock him up!… https://t.co/CdoXuUkbK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mslater_johnson I see your technical point, but we should think differently about a "market failure" that is a del… https://t.co/sdxLKQpc47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @JJaazzee1 I think we now know who the real Antichrist is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CometsBarstool Kanye West - BLKKK SKKKN HEAD (Explicit) https://t.co/pir1dhfzUZ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyBleier I’ve asked you many questions and have gotten good answers so I will bother you again. Antonio Browns… https://t.co/znEbjCDdKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[How was your Tuesday? I spent mine ripping apart a wall to find a leak. Homeownership can be a bitch sometimes. Tha… https://t.co/cHt9PKFNMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hjorimir @cconnie89 @mattcolville @sherlock_hulmes @therealjimdavis This thread needs its own adventure path.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLu44 @AngelMabel19761 Rib joints in Hawaii will be getting take-out delivery orders from a squeaky little boy… https://t.co/tzWdNf7F1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wreckitralph #RalphBreaksTheInternet  Is such a phenomenal movie and its somehow better then the first movie. Grea… https://t.co/GFvOLYZ7mp]]></document></documents></author>