<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A #gingerbreadhouse decorating day!! First time doing it!! I need MORE PRACTICE/EXPERIENCE!! My house doesn't look… https://t.co/zYuCTWea5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #IowaCity, IA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/SwCDbRlc2D #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnKing28 You are beautiful,  strong and brave!  Here's me and I hate selfies also... https://t.co/HK3QsEsjOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOHNNNY_NY @SHODesusAndMero @ToriUptown Just the thumbnail alone looks racist. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[everytime my alarm goes off at 3:20am it takes me about 10 seconds to realize it’s not a sick joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyfhjiang and I excited for @evanchooly’s talk on the new @RedHat Quarkus project! #DevNexus2019 https://t.co/hyTQKxby8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still havi#Vermont #handwovenbowties  #lesbian #gay #bisexual #transgender #queer #ally  #gaybowtie #lgbtqbowtie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first, second, and third editions of The Diary of a Young Girl, in their corresponding dust jackets, as issued.… https://t.co/lY6ar7dulE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was awake until 2 last night. I was out of bed at 10 to 5. Y’all best be on your best behavior. I’m talking eleme… https://t.co/YfOJYmEFV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[FedEx Unveils Future Autonomous Delivery Robot Game changer for urban environment’s last mile! #logisticsSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say! We like green eggs and ham! We do! We like them. Sam I am! Well green eggs anyway. #readacrossamerica2019… https://t.co/dsVn95EZpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nellied326 Right...and if kids are doing 3 or 4 work...does that really belong as homework?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ West Valley Girls Softball https://t.co/ARCYkNs2Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEADS UP TO ANY OF YOU WHO HAVE BEEN TO OR FROM CHICAGO RECENTLY, ESP. THE EVE OF 2/22 https://t.co/p5gDF3oPc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gttechguru Ha! Ha! Of course.  This is just the start of your Growth Zone adventure.  Keep updating so we can follow along!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I live for @KrisJenner this bitty is a legend idc what you say https://t.co/0z7rfouZY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nilereflection #Maddow Apparently not! It’s More government by gentlemen’s agreement and I can safely say we have… https://t.co/Y01MpwykBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet the sell out is tryna make me look bad cause I wanted to go home already 🤷🏻‍♀️😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never want to experience this much regret with a loved one. Gotta be Selfless with your love always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So they put power chains on my braces yesterday and my mouth has never felt pain like this😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more stars to review the restaurants. The revolution starts with @hooleil new critic at the @sfchronicle. All th… https://t.co/HeT5IL5UlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO, YOU'RE NOT. THE TRUMP CRIME FAMILY WILL BE GOING TO PRISON IN YOUR PLACE! ❤  💙🇺🇸💙BLUE WAVE, 2020 💙🇺🇸💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were waiting for daybreak to restart search and rescue. Now, they’re gathering the first responders to begin t… https://t.co/kg6tz5Aiuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished... such great thoughts , design, and hard work!. It amazes me how they can a few supplies and create so ma… https://t.co/mkx9IUV2XF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im really glad shawn read my mind. Last night i was looking at tickets thinking fuck im gonna end up going to utah… https://t.co/9Q1yyqRFik]]></document><document><![CDATA[At crutacos to try the taco of the week, which is butter-poached lobster. Have to check out on @ArizonaFoodie's Anc… https://t.co/YlOivss6bM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was so scary! The wind gusts here are unbelievable. We moved out of our bedroom and into the guest room… https://t.co/rGuwiTktve]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #InternationalWomensDay - and every day - much respect to these ladies: O.G. Louise (aka Big Louise to my Little… https://t.co/hznSTRDa2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe Ummm...like me?  Because...it’s a twin?  Is this a trick question? 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenatsma @kateracculia @ExcelsiorBay @valleybkseller @gibbsne .Thank you Helen. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making some #hot #salsa yummm @ Modesto, California https://t.co/BVGuiB0wxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MsHanReads to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Each… https://t.co/j3HSD5ZHkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[People not responding to business emails and messages in a timely manner is my biggest pet peeve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[«برنی سندرز» سناتور دموکرات ایالت «ورمونت» آمریکا از به رسمیت شناختن «خوان گوایدو» رئیس‌جمهور خودخوانده ونزوئلا امت… https://t.co/l2EyBp39w2]]></document><document><![CDATA[house shopping is so hard bc i find all the things i like in $300k homes. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bestseller!  "Don't miss this incredible dark, psychological suspense from Andrews. The drama parts of this novel w… https://t.co/nTN06QZ22c]]></document><document><![CDATA[U better werkkkkkkkk 🗣#locsbyki #myclientsarebetterthanyours @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/RzFkt8mW5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lepton939 @mkraju @jeremyherb Giuliani will negotiate himself into capital punishment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's your birthday tomorrow, and u don't know how to act but you want ur party to be Litty so u throw everythi… https://t.co/0BefxNttrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraOdette @skooks Nope. We are owned by the same company that has owned us since the 1960s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warms my heart! I you want to donate for the conference, please email me and I’ll arrange things for you 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NINOBROWNMIAMI Why not she can feed you grapes 🍇 she has two hands and to ass cheeks lol Grapes 🍇 👁🍇👑😎🎓🔑🍹]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marywag2947 @rpaulsenphoto @Edgeycated @SenFeinstein #VelshiRuhle Electoral College NEVER had a place. It was impl… https://t.co/FC2tiwk6ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@walmartinc A lot of disabled employees are ex-military.  Where is your committement to them? #TW #WalmartGreeters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland A 73-year-old woman in Colorado died on Friday, nine months after doctors wrongly removed her kidneys.… https://t.co/UFPqRuTU5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been at this job 92 days and I'm looking for something to do.  And it's only going to get worse. How does this always happen??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbharrison I think we can all agree that actually was the most dramatic episode in Bachelor history]]></document><document><![CDATA[I expect better from Sunny because she was a Prosecutor. None of us know if the current accusations are True or Lie… https://t.co/IKTqPhM00s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The catalyst for problem solving is leadership. #Leadership isn’t management. It’s changing the way things are.… https://t.co/g9utOdyDq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may want to check your lotto tickets: https://t.co/jQ8zB2OonO Ticket worth $200K sold in Cobb, $50K ticket sold… https://t.co/9yELdp9KTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for creating my obsession with jeeps #ilyroxy https://t.co/Eit4eZvqR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lscain3834 @milanpaurich @siano2020 Why has Mueller not interviewed the 3 spawns of trump and Kellyann or Bolton. That worries me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facts! These Republicans will go down in history as rubber stamping 45 treasonous acts against democracy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[how can you be so mean to and about someone who you used to be so in love with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you a teacher? Interested in FREE #PD ? Do you want to bring #creativecoding to your classroom? Looking to crea… https://t.co/aJVpvVpZ6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate: dude what is your life?  Me: idk man I would also like to know ok. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love walking around campus seeing student work celebrated in our hallways! #WritingMatters #CelebrateOurAuthors… https://t.co/mvK8taMjhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to lightening delays Varsity’s game will start around 1:30 instead of 1 today. @soccer_conroe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to the ones I love! We can appreciate more than just romantic love on this Hallmark holiday! 💘💘💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be Flawless. Be Bold. Be You. #deannamarie_label #💜💫 @ Chicago metropolitan area https://t.co/rPDxxh3wuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[C o m i n g S o o n 🎥 🛩 🌴 🌇 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/NvaZelI0CM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have the time to go out on a Thursday, Tina. I have to study to get into med school, ok? Please respect tha… https://t.co/skSGrM2V9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing that happened to me this week. After crying in my office over a family squabble, colleague saw me and as… https://t.co/BAhU2Op4E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had a real period in almost two years and I forgot how tired they make you 😭😭. So sleepy. #beingafemalesucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Exactly America’s reaction when you are indicted with the rest of your sleazy family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@presley_26 I sat in stand still traffic from Marks Creek/Hwy 12 trying to get to the Courthouse for 40 minutes 🤦🏻‍♀️😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t make it and would like to donate if you aren’t local? Send any donation to RMLcarlie@gmail.com and I’ll deliv… https://t.co/28XjLYvsXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The research is clear and robust. Teach a small repertoire of 6-8 strategies for kids to use flexibly as needed to… https://t.co/eJF7EBtOF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodfriendC @DesertMountain_ @FOX10Phoenix How can they see where the ball went? Doesn’t it blend in with the snow?? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFire45 @saradannerdukic Also..they have tech that can ..how do I explain this ..and this is also next generation… https://t.co/48QrW5kGMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[this morning started with me unknowingly using expired half and half and taking a huge gulp of my coffee.... yummy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you ARCA! We ❤️ you! #highpressure #lowpressure #flight #STEAM @ Thompson Intermediate School https://t.co/JrE6qh1UDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Andrew McCabe wouldn’t know the truth if it smacked him in the face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnnnylungz Yeah and how punk ass Waitr got my sister crying on the kitchen floor😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hope4Anaya @share_wishes @kidneykidsuk @RareDiseaseWLV @ARPKD @gurchrandhawa @NHSOrganDonor @Naomi_My_Story… https://t.co/JkodJE6kLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnergyDems @Sen_JoeManchin West Virginia is one of the most polluted states. Why has it taken you so long to wake… https://t.co/cpKGiYUoM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #StInigoes, MD #ProjectMgmt job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Program Analyst at SAIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of the home videos of me feature me dancing to Garth Brooks in a 101 Dalmatians t-shirt, no pants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets hope make up isn’t on the set list. #thankunext https://t.co/ZdQmtWkmk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#day3 - wrapping up #week1 of the template. Today was hard, and I was sore. But I did it. Exciting things are happe… https://t.co/wqEmNXkgH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents Day to a real President who cares about America! https://t.co/8GdRylLjBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @VP When was Guido elected?  A lot people think Hillary won the popular vote what if China recogni… https://t.co/T3SwHWJnH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así mi día heladisimo y lo que le sigue, pero con sol.  Feliz y bendecido día. en Waco, Texas https://t.co/e6gJqbAMgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shoutout to @JulieSilverMD #BeEthical campaign by Dr. Sims at #ACGME2019 as an organization that’s making an impa… https://t.co/LT1r7MNguq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tazisalady @FashionNova @xoBrittanyox91 @amber_alert1432 @MakeUpGeek44 Oh your so sweet Joan!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffreyes6 @xoStaceFace @KevinFrost_10 Bitch you’re gonna have a whole week when we booze and cruise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 judging ISSMA Organizational at Avon Intermediate West with Jim Crismore and Abby Tolar. Hearing beautiful mu… https://t.co/pkHyyoOy3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedbauer2003 Great question!   #Boss vs. #Leader: People users vs.  people developers    Energy sapping vs. energy… https://t.co/ZqtHp5ibU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traveling with people that don’t travel is hard work for me. I don’t like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFTER ASTROWORLD NEW YORK STAY RAGING ! ! ! 🎢🎡🦋  @trvisXX #astroworld #barclayscenter #newyorkcity #brooklyn TAG TR… https://t.co/LqlRuZJQqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I’m gonna go to Chicago over spring break and see Hamilton, yes I’m VERY EXCITED. I’m also going to the beach s… https://t.co/ZHaHsNOjgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittLeighJack @miche11e8 Okay but does he say it like brown- chicken- brown- cow,?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AisforInterval @LisaNani25 Ok, so you're friends... https://t.co/COaxgJa4uD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk I just feel like there should be more smoke since she hit it so long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tastemaker Tuesday!! Here’s a peak of The 9’s new collection which is live on our website right now 🦋 Use the… https://t.co/AqKuKWvvPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you better quit Lettin' shit slip Or you'll be leaving with a fat lip]]></document><document><![CDATA[VINTAGE WALL WOODEN PANEL https://t.co/KSqK0XsrzL https://t.co/1rGnyEwBcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Thank you so much for your book. Trump is an absolute disgrace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Not surprised, LBJ SAID "I will get those N to vote Democratic for 200 yrs" that's the Democratic Party!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamCarp48  To be fully informed and not manipulated or ensnared by propaganda by someone with their own agenda we… https://t.co/sQlF2FH0PT]]></document></documents></author>