<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCamaguey @kimguilfoyle @SUPERRANGO73 Our votes did not elect Trump. #TrumpDivertsDividesDestroys #25thAmendmentNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow https://t.co/SS8phXiUuc  Please consider having him as a guest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your leadership @RepGusBilirakis and @SenatorDurbin for championing an issue requiring more funding,… https://t.co/Qy5O1tJVn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[New rule If you want to talk to me FaceTime/call me. I’m tired of texting people]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does that do for me, idc about no damn domestic flights. Let’s talk international okurrrr 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂🤣😂🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣goooood one Jussie 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣I’m stressed to the max everyday and I’ve n… https://t.co/mur18aTojC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ulices Chaidez was here tonight on a private concert at Medusa Dallas 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[my parents give so much more than they receive, they deserve the world and more. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dparsons9 @BSHQ And as far as this reflecting a company culture that is broken, you know I am friends with Rob, bu… https://t.co/O6lzjxeRhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA I cannot wait until the crooks of Pence and Trump are taken out and President Pelosi restores order]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finally struggling in musicianship and I’m starting to question my existence in the world!!!!!!! Send HELP!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fun Modesto Symphony concert-Our Orchestra played full movie score of Pirates of the Caribbean!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fraser_DHEM Thank you Dr. Fraser! It can’t be easy on programs’ end either; it’s a hurry-up-to-wait for everyone,… https://t.co/QYMz82R0MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary  Only place I can’t grow followers, naaaww, th… https://t.co/NtWQ404bJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK catching up on @BachelorABC and WOW @CassieRandolph’s dad is giving me the pep talk I need!   LOVE EXISTS PEOPLE! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lolololol. Idc. Whatever you do to me comes back to you 10x. Remember that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iesha_griffin “Why you ain’t eat the sandwich cold tf wrong wit chu” 😭😭 cryyyy-eeeeenkkkkk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samigrey_ @JosilynBertrand I dont like the petting zoo, but this is THE gas station that my family never fails to… https://t.co/fDLYgpx49H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eula1109 @MoskitaMuertaOk Bien bien ,seria que xq una mujer ,no sea una modelo ,la trates despectivamente "de gorda "👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jersey_Craig Especially if you’re not legal. You only hurt yourself and family. They are not worth it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrfarmsga I thought that to myself after I typed it....it’s not like it stops at 5 on Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthAfrica We're not gonna visit your country until you stop the white genocide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 4 weeks in with being vegetarian and it’s going GREAT! But I’m just curious do y’all think I can do it for the whole year??🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pizza Week has been awesome so far! Writing 🍕 book reviews and 🍕 themed math games! #themeweeksarethebestweeks… https://t.co/0CK0oZkGhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday schedules with MARTA no make that weekend schedules ugh 🤦🏽‍♀️😩🤦🏽‍♀️😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever just look at your significant other and cry because you love them so much? Bc same]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now Helen Mirren?! Not even 10 minutes in and all my favorite women on stage. This "no host" thing is great! #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@only1joesmith @SWardArch I should point out that I’ve been to both the original Barnes and the new one, and I see… https://t.co/YlzA3YNey3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can drink crown apple by itself without a chaser. Wow. Idk if that’s good or bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[19 Days to go til #CrosswordMysteries #APuzzleToDieFor Premiers! We're getting there #crimebusters On Mar.10 9p/8c… https://t.co/XvGj14nGsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msbedlam_caz @DoItToJulia5 @ABRadFems @TeelaWild @MorganeOgerBC @preta_6 @FeministCurrent Here’s the witness list https://t.co/Bqq9ADJVMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corbynsmama @Gr8Pundit @PaulDoroshenko @IRPlawyer @drex @theStevilDead Pierre Elliot Trudeau also loosened laws on… https://t.co/55WtXlgfjR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDumitrac3 @McAllisterDen I can’t stand what they are doing to our men. What woman doesn’t want the protectio… https://t.co/drzgArTlw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[No es nada fácil desprenderse de la familia, estar en otro país dónde no conoces a nadie y sola. Quién piensa que t… https://t.co/GOYiHG4Q3q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueFactsStated What a joke....can you say Benghazi ten times, really fast?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilBobJ MAN!!!  You're all awesome - LOVE the replies!  Thank you!!  Don't make em' like they used to :)  Muddy W… https://t.co/RgwWC08ysn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nugsthecat That depth lol, these were actually pics I took before the last layer of sealing so it’s not as glossy https://t.co/RvdzC13m0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do u ever feel like you mess everything up bc me too im just done man, only care abt myself starting now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still thinking of Rachel’s voice. Her songs about love and heartache and the way she projected her voice throug… https://t.co/R65rUloeBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please stop ! You’re tearing up the Democratic Party when you do not need to.  There are many others more adaptable… https://t.co/56HJfMNoQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMERICA DO SUL POVINHO NAO SE LEVANTA NUMA SO VOZ. NAO PARAM SUAS MERDAS DE PAISES. RESILVE SE SUBMETER A BURGUESI… https://t.co/FIsdrbhEEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the @JambaJuice in Downey such trash? Anytime I come they mess up my order and I don’t even alter it...🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hbobrow1Hbobrow You didn’t really expect the obese carrot to comment on that, did you? Obese carrot encourages them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t own your message, you don’t OWN your message! https://t.co/zEEGLj1tRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just posted a picture of my cats and I are Instagram and realized my last post was of my cats also.... 🙃🐱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insertgeekname @derek_mafs @lesleyabravanel @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs 😂🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t had a good nights sleep in 2 weeks and here I am again not being able to KO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know why You never left me but through it all Lord, You kept me   Takes me back, always..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aoc #GreenNewDeal = helping evade the 6th mass extinction event. @realDonaldTrump #maga look it up, if you care ab… https://t.co/cF6JvWEVAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exclusive Listing . Custom, architecturally striking residences in the natural beauty of the desert. . ❤️ Ranch Mir… https://t.co/YrWqSBF9jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @DsOchoa Life.  Nothing less for premeditated kidnapping and murder.  We all need to remember that t… https://t.co/bkkik2d4oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeaGig139 @joyfulng A blessed new week to you too.     Much love De'a and Joy. https://t.co/FwJogaNeLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/rIzD3eOnMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to rally... aka see my best friends tonight @clarirmn0917 &amp; @vicki5193 I can already taste the flamings 🔥🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally taking off, 20 minutes late. Peace out, Minnesota! See ya in a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaceyDeana @TheView I have NEVER Heard a Democrat say “OPEN BORDERS”... WHERE...WHO⁉️ NO-1‼️  TRUMP is a LIAR DUDE… https://t.co/gLabNh1cug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brownstonedd Don't judge my candy choice. It's been my favorite since I was five. When I visited my dad my older b… https://t.co/yV2hh2NQIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the freaking weekend Whoo hoo! We made it through another week now let's go out and have some fun!😊❤🙏 @ Aldine… https://t.co/37zAdx8dHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want in life is someone to brunch with every week is that really so much to ask?]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want to be finally content is a @JeffreeStar star mirror. I’d wake up everyday and say ‘hi, how are ya?” to myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro he posed behind me prom pic style with the guitar , my homosexuality was threatened]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cargo plane crashes in Chambers County https://t.co/YhxllikWhK #texas #planedown #chamberscounty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin FIRST of all, STOP calling her a “Comidienne!”😳THAT ship sailed a LONG effin time ago!🙄😟😡🖕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always5star @RewardMyShoppin @travelpantspair @TravelBugsWorld @carpediemeire @travelwithirine @KaraDiDomizio… https://t.co/8NMAlUKLSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRuthPointer hey Lady...love you...been playing your music in Philly for years @wdasfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyBrigade13 @BTS_twt LOOK IF NOBODY FOR THIS SITE OR WHATEVER YOU CALL STOPS INSULTING MYSELF AND WRITE ME, I WI… https://t.co/Abj522VwwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I feel today... #Friday @ Queen Creek, Arizona https://t.co/57sGKpYpWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Feather It In by @FrogTownBeer @ Buzz Wine Beer Shop — https://t.co/f1a4oJ6JCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Belcamp, Maryland job and click to apply: Diesel Technician/Mechanic II - https://t.co/7Agr9Pq4oS… https://t.co/1IZWnIseVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going out for dinner on F-Factor is easy!! First- nedi martini thank you @healthywithnedi next tuna tartare with sa… https://t.co/WJwulSG77W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Voyage of Bullbeard by @BoleroSnort @ Main Street — https://t.co/2mSAaRrvGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up. Book a flight. Crush the day. ✈️ #springbreak2k19 #raktrip2k19 @AndreaJFilter @renayshoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askforupdog congrats !!!!do u live in pa because if so u get to get me pregnet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo proud of myself!!!  Thanks to the help of Brandon, I got my chart set up with the fib to start the work on my… https://t.co/IpiHHb3Jqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1/40 🚫☕️  Apologizing in advance if I forget your name or my own for that matter. Send me strength😳#lent #letsdothis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone who navigated the icy roads this morning and made their way to the Breakfast at the… https://t.co/4C5iKd9fsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got the coolest college professor 🤷‍♀️ #noonecantophim https://t.co/JFoubM4F7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇲🇽 A dominguear 🎈  #FelizDomingo24Feb🎈 #DíaDeLaBanderaDeMéxico🇲🇽 https://t.co/Zd7nw3z5Ct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @DHSgov American babies are the priority not illegal alien children.  Illegal alien parents chose to endanger their children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're and ATLA/LOK fan, the creators have a Netflix show (the lead is the same voice actor for Sokka) and it is… https://t.co/brJe2u8BxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey que bonito que me vean como alguien soñadora, alguien que lucha hasta tener lo que quiere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckeyeCuti @Donnielover6 @birdtracs @stacie9853 @Katie_Elaine012 @24loves75 @tnormandeau22 @moonrayvin @jessaugie… https://t.co/ic5adyE7Dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani ‘perfected the template’ that prosecutors could use to bring down Trump and his family https://t.co/2MAhs7L8Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cohen is your longtime friend and fixer. Less than a year ago he was a deputy at the RNC. Your cri… https://t.co/k30iiIEz9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any conventions happening closer to MA after the DC convention in April? #AskingForAFriend Want to see… https://t.co/5aG4uZNq4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one had a wall built like this man, if you're on defense you ain't getting through just ran over. #O-SQUAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s a clown but what’s the difference between POTUS hiring Ivanka or Jarred? None]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahRemini @TarynTeutsch @ywca_gla @YWCAUSA @worldywca @PeaceOvrViolnce @DenimDayNYC @LEILAGRACEORG Keep it up Won… https://t.co/TZVpIxTeQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep recieving phone calls about my cars "warrenty" bitch I didn't buy a warranty those are like 2 grand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lagordafmmx @CHAYANNEMUSIC @eticket @Sectur_Chiapas @CHICASDECALIPSO @ChayanneRepDom @ChayiFansCancun… https://t.co/LfC6HiN1QZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmyA2 Haha. It took me a while to realize Flo Rida was really just Florida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Paparazzo Casa in Paupack, PA w/ @emilyaskedwhy https://t.co/cVXgjafreA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! (Because Twitter just told me about it...) #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/LIWeFA9AKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Bucky Barnes! 🎂I even found the perfect party dress. @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/nILLQsH4SL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Communication. Communication. Communication at all levels is so important. Agree? https://t.co/ar3AnEX8PT #mergers… https://t.co/jVuNxSkBjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattTriano @stevewmorris The answer is that I did tweet at him to explain why it was uncalled for. He didn’t liste… https://t.co/PgR2xpOVje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirt(!) on Comey,BigTime,from back in their mutual employ @ Lockheed Martin.When Mueller  departed for HSBC;he brou… https://t.co/wqsZ3IGa7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for AAA to tow me and my 1999 Lexus home. 🙁 #idratherbejunkin   So fill me in. Are you heading to pccfleama… https://t.co/WxQSyau8s0]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way y’all, turns out after moving a full three miles closer to work and KonMarieing my life, I can get up ne… https://t.co/sN3Wt47YsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more vacation cheat meal while we are waiting on our flight and then back on Keto tomorrow!! #Burgers… https://t.co/SrhjTz69fh]]></document></documents></author>