<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This Valentine's Day, Cedar Rapids couple reflects on nearly seven decades of marriage.  https://t.co/FdtSIozetR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedMaryland @mddems This guy agrees with @RedMaryland  that I should resign. He also thinks blood must water some… https://t.co/nBP6YLRvLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFAAJFlo @jasonwheelertv I'm impressed considering all I have on is pantyhose &amp; a skirt. Ha! #iamup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee to get through SATs... (@ Bogue's Alley in Pawcatuck, CT) https://t.co/rnQmJoa3BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would lay down my life for spider-gwen &amp; I love these fan arts so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never saw #LukePerry in anything, but nobody should be taken at that age. Way too young.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whataburger would be nice right now but Hattiesburg decided not to have one anywhere near here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyzerke 👏👏👏 #Repost @tossitmovie with get_repost ・・・ @jennyzerke aka Marie #crushinit #asalways in andtheatreco… https://t.co/qblzlsjdua]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t build anything if trust and honesty isn’t the foundation of it all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenEagles is fortunate to have so many of our grads @MarquetteU! Scholarships make that dream a reality. Thanks… https://t.co/L75nvif7Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you order 25 more bathing suits and realize you aren’t gonna look good in any of them unless you lose about ten pounds lmfaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Francojuanky La cerda diabolica con sus pranes disfrazados de guardias, dando la espalda para no ser identificados… https://t.co/qQscVH0rol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveRamsey follows 48 people but has 880K plus followers. For all of the flack FB gets, I think this is a social m… https://t.co/U0VzyrmuCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan chulo que esta mi niño hermoso pronto estaremos juntos corazon😍 https://t.co/GFL52HInZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endlessly excited to spend 💰 💵 on @SaraBareilles on Friday!!!!! #amidsttheCHAOS #preordermania #gimmedat #feb15 #sarab @sarabfans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackWagnerhpk @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV Something is not right about Lucas.  Can’t wait for next week already!!!… https://t.co/fpMRWIyK4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP Putin’s plan is coming to fruition thanks to our feckless president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to the gym, talked to God, and took a shower and it’s just now 7 am. TODAY IS GONNA BE A BEAUTIFUL DAY PEOPLE!! Believe it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have taken a cycle class, solid core class, and pure barre class. And I can honestly say I wouldn’t give up Orang… https://t.co/ttSnpd6GQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saadiend Lol! The ticket to rock thing says 8/21 but dates are subject to change. Breaking Benjamin was on the dat… https://t.co/KhfmGFSxtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Em compensação tem séries que as temporadas sei lá quando vão chegar no Brasil já tem aqui..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my free chance to win $100 in points. Tons of wins here! https://t.co/SIbFffJgZS #instantwingame]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stripped version of 1999 got added to my work radio I love it but also I can’t escape troye sivan]]></document><document><![CDATA[facts where mine at tho cause we wasting precious time 🤣🤣 one day maybe 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear brothers and sisters, take note of this: Everyone should be quick to listen, slow to speak…… https://t.co/KR6vrviwYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iamthe2ndmouse I would definitely say you should suggest it!  Having a panel of different genders, backgrounds- de… https://t.co/cLiiWaAmAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmaLaineAuthor Excellent advice. Each of our voices are unique, our stories through new points of view or somethin… https://t.co/XhmXXFVaBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of having a cat is when he paws at my stomach/back before cuddling up and sleeping with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micahcohen @FiveThirtyEight @BernieSanders That would warrant staying home on election day for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @Jamierodr14 @SpeakerPelosi So she caved...Trump will soon have the Black &amp; Jewish American votes...thank you Nasty Nancy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not let my eyes close or the sun rise on me before I have the chance to thank the world best supervisor and b… https://t.co/R9di5xMxSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadian Radio-Television and Telecommunications Commission: Canadians Are Being SCAMMED - Tell the CRTC We Demand… https://t.co/7CLXy9GT97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltTeaPartyLove @KAG4All Agreed. That is the only way this country will be safe and prosperous for everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro life people must act now, not just talk, make the change. https://t.co/gvWX3npxyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marykk196051 @ElenneMigo @yellowbelle @DestiniLozano @Lanasanette @JilldarWu @JazzmaCumberful @Verartesdesenho… https://t.co/JAtwEc8nY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanknight @DonnieWahlberg @joeymcintyre @JonathanRKnight @dannywood @NKOTB https://t.co/ih4ekvnkA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing better than seeing all the WOMEN talk about all the other beautiful WOMEN, just filling my feed wi… https://t.co/5gDjhBpUCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a disgusting and disgraceful piece of legislation.  I hope the Arkansas representatives see it for what it… https://t.co/KQW4o9wfNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @kenolin1 They are also without moral compasses, sad to say. Our country is better than this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMurrayBook Retweeted and I nominate @DoRinda1007 @MalinowskaGr5 @NattySandell #winnerwinner?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel as though I don’t appreciate him enough. I love my dog. 🥰💕 https://t.co/dcVK2CQ4oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jumah Mubarak Brothers &amp; Sisters @ Spokane, Washington https://t.co/p4aLGvNUIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[today’s tea:            )         )        )     (      )     (         )       )      )    ) _(___(____)____(___(_… https://t.co/y0xego8PFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby earthquake! Super cute although I'd prefer to not wake up thinking Godzilla is legit walking towards my house.… https://t.co/JIBvLMNdYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurrencySam @GenaTorres_ Why don’t you trust us with faith. I don’t understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl really blocked me on ig &amp; i’ve never met her before in my life ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially cause I'm at a party people expect me to communicate to everyone like bitch yeah right ima sit here and be on Twitter hahahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy the beauty of the day...with #coffee #latteart #GPT #BK #mondaymotivation @ Cafe Grumpy https://t.co/ADFk89Mx4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson This is what scares me the most. The judiciary has held - so far - but as long as these weasels keep… https://t.co/7nrJjpy5i2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chicagofan76 @JasonRCloud @NBCSCubs @jolietslammers @ChicagoDogsME @ThreeGuySports That’s becuz the Sox suck.  Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park Place Apartment Building in Seattle, WA https://t.co/yVK6EuBGLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accidentally wore a Time’s Up shirt on International Women’s Day. Going to kill myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[My niece just dumped water all over my leg... pretty much just settled me not going out tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like marcus rn up af when no one else is + it’s 6am here &amp; 5am for majority of my followers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love her newer stuff too, but the album Down Fell the Doves from @amandashires is like an old friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AussieKerrie @Absolover @Adriana53871022 @L_Ithil @Malirensch @C_licare @TinaBull6 @winny_atheart @abouttomellis… https://t.co/yxPIa5Pr7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday felt like a playoff game ... but it wasn’t. 35 degrees and almost 18k attendance. So excited for this new… https://t.co/gHOLtsshS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Favourite: The Real-Life Power Struggle Between Queen Anne and Sarah Churchill https://t.co/VNIxKGjg1P     @KaraDiDomizio]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hello 7am. I thought you were 6. Well, I guess I’m up now....on a Sunday. #DaylightSavingTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukecombs We entered on Spotify My daughter and I are number one fans and we already live in Colorado and would lo… https://t.co/PWHQsCeXYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could @KaitlynnFish look any happy saying NO RAIN (for now)? 😂 #WakeUp11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues si, ya el jueves es mi último día de mañana pero saben que? Me pusieron de noche :( y que miedo estar en el ho… https://t.co/8dJSajqb0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch the #YouTube video in last post and hear #LozzaFox other talent - Music. His next album coming soon and canno… https://t.co/h5E01FGoSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The defense asks about the incident. She says Daryl lunged at JW over the counter. He asks if she remembers telling… https://t.co/1nRQLjXO0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficerSmith2 @LivePDNation @RealDustinSims Lmao. I needed this laugh 🤣😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeFromValley @justinamash @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Trump will never be impeached. He has done nothing wrong...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just give me a reason to wear vintage. @ Saved By The Max - Saved By The Bell Pop Up Shop Diner &amp; Bar https://t.co/jrmzOy4Dcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got that right, sister!! In honor of #InternationalWomensDay This woman and I have been there for each other fo… https://t.co/Nwq9BM1ycJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PacificAirPhoto Lmfao what greeter. This Walmart is the worst Walmart they don’t even have greeters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbmullings @KapeciaResists It looks like a lot of his followers think this too.  In fact, both my sons were born… https://t.co/4ojoL4Bi15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REMS_DrJohnson Congrats on your new arrival Dr. Johnson! Blessings to your entire family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@314MFMS @JSOPIO @PolicingNews @propacop @NatPoliceAssoc @FLSheriffs @GoodCopStories @FCN2go @BlueWalkPoconos… https://t.co/WwKsPrTU1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSlackerMcFly Tonight I Wanna Cry was the first song I'd heard by Keith. I wept. It was so raw and that's how I… https://t.co/tbd5CyARvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Avenatti to give up financial control of law firm after he's accused of hiding millions.  What’s t… https://t.co/DZLW6vqnte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why should you click on this story? There are dog photos.   Golden Gate Park reopens trail with new name in honor o… https://t.co/eOFv9IPrtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RacetoEraseMS @NDavisR inspired by @SelmaBlair I wrote this for #NationalMSAwarenessMonth #YesWeAreDoingIt #eraseMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForRover @Phil_Sledge Thank you. My heart is still aching about saying goodbye to Justin-Kitty. Not sure I'll ever… https://t.co/rrnj9CwlQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes I don't know what he has over them but I don't see any of the Republicans standing up for the truth.… https://t.co/UkpnZhXvDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[college is so funny I’m like let’s see how long I can go without eating lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJrNY @SadeABC Honestly, it seemed sketchy within the first 24 hours that the story broke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[very cool seeing the @innocence pop up in the @netflix show the innocent man! big thank you to the IP for fighting… https://t.co/WXBriZ8aK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gray skies won't deter us today. The Skate Ribbon is open from 10am-10pm. Lace up your skates and enjoy Maggie Dale… https://t.co/odhqpwxaJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have been a manager for a month and you can’t even count or make change with the money. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@underscorebriee @withconfidence_ Hey, sorry to hear about your windbreaker! Someone from the band will contact you shortly to resolve it 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand why guys talk so bad about female sports yet they/it can compete in them because they can’t… https://t.co/jyHyjlD8xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our new single "Rise" is out now!! The video is also a movie trailer for a feature film we made that will accompany… https://t.co/erJb8ki2co]]></document><document><![CDATA[THATS WHAT IM SAYIN! I almost said it over the intercom but they cut me off 😂 #donutsforeveryone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEALON3 Nacho Cheese Doritos, Bbq Lays, Cool Ranch Doritos, Fritos, OG Lays then Cheetos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I reached a lifetime climb of 500 floors and earned the Helicopter badge today with Fitbit! https://t.co/lvFLlF3378 #Fitstats]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG - Sarah H Sanders is clearly living in an alternative fact-less reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Time4U2Know @VincentCrypt46 This is just so amazing, I’m speechless! 😁 this whole thing, the Plan all the people t… https://t.co/mOsHp8zZPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InterestingFol1 @marjoryk2012 And they never forget when you screw up and seem to forget all the good you have done afterwards✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Good, the time to fight is NOW!!! If we don’t fight this move what will he do next!!!  Save our Constitution!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALAAAAA ESE RITMOOOO🤤🤤 @mariobautista_ @MarioBautistaMB #SofiaDeMarioBautista https://t.co/kMMAvsfJO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[...  It dates back to 1907, when it was built as photographer Francis D. Nemecek's studio.    Mexicans began to mov… https://t.co/pqoaeNqvvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bmillslc @vegetarianj @NoirAmnesiac @Ilhan Are you stupid? Its 14 million. Whatever you want to call it. The artic… https://t.co/jB61JJdtnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_Singa @JeffreyGuterman @CNN Americans can’t afford insulin and food.  @DianneFeinstein yelling at kids in fru… https://t.co/NIKz7rbSoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajohnsonn4 yeah doing what ? sitting there staring @ your celling or sum ? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I go to places and take pictures of everything I want but can’t afford.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabletopTherapy @KelliNDunlap and @eddyfate and @TheBodhanaGroup should contact you. 💜]]></document></documents></author>