<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Digz Don’t beat yourself up @Digz be proud you stayed true to yourself! Quitters Quit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atxnolasco Like call me a cynic but considering this is like the third or fourth time American movies have claimed… https://t.co/RoH4saDGff]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That’s really helped me get to where I am today.”  🗣@rwoley4 on his journey from LSU to Juco to @AuburnBaseball… https://t.co/jCDyzLrytm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TraitorTrump  ‘They deserve to know if Donald Trump is an agent of the Russian Federation’: Democratic senator mak… https://t.co/VtVJaj2F1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does pushing the clocks forward one hour make me feel like I just got off a thirteen hour plane trip?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBBSituation Too bad they were all peeking over the top of the newspapers to watch Ross the Boss. Check the receipts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaireCervenak @EdCampNEWARK @SchleiderJustin @justinalpertesq @ojfade @KeyannaMichelle Welcome to St. Louis https://t.co/rDcBI5UWFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of my family and all their hard work over the years building this amazing company! formula_boats formul… https://t.co/WOkcdVGsRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTyler78 @DandMe_MomOf5 @judyohtweets @KristinaNadia @riapanacea @LifesStyleBlog @Dapple_TXUSA @WarrenWattles… https://t.co/QJzr17jgsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eclecticbrotha Tupac was recording stuff in 1987 (and I’d assume even 1986). He had a whole career with Digital Un… https://t.co/DtvYMpvfKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @oliviaayala48 Yes, it's a damn shame! Especially when the only things most of those black boys can… https://t.co/uS72kZj2v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunDonPhotog @JoshFox46 @ProfCDP Hornets team store, which became the NBA Store over the weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Derykcasillas @Black_BanditKB Leos and Geminis over reacting at any little inconvenience]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason why this spring break trip gonna be so lit bc it’s with all my day ones 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeynuggs Hi, We can definitely help you in design and development of your website at an affordable price.  See ou… https://t.co/4JOwiGW77y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful #pacificnorthwest day to get outside and and run a few miles on the trail. Got in a solid couple hours po… https://t.co/p09G7IEi8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonzaga leads St. John's 31-22 at halftime of boys WCAC final. #DMVhoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE ~ @TrueKofi ~ @TripleH and @WWEDanielBryan:  I Am Tweeting My Prediction For The Main Event At #WWEFastlane.… https://t.co/ZxORcMyMNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please pray for my mom who will join me for mass for the first time ever tomorrow for #AshWednesday,  and an extrao… https://t.co/CkAx2TK3p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @RiderMBB Stevie Jordan on why the team hasn’t been able to get past the quarterfinals. https://t.co/MlYFAh0712]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going out on a limb but in 2-7 at Lapc we are on the bubble once again this week. At 192000 I feel safe to say… https://t.co/Rnf0UL48WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I feel myself stressing I just go to Cabin Fever 2 and play Fucc Shit, Pacc Talk, and Deep Sleep in that order]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Brand New Lover by Dead Or Alive https://t.co/WDMthcKzf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/4yWDkuUdw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica_thgirw @augustinew_ @_Team_DAN PLUCK THE 12!!! You can’t have a rule that says you can stack draws and then… https://t.co/DTfMzvYgjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus will be going to see Greta and Medea funeral probably on Sunday too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for @JRMotorsports in the #eNASCARHeat Pro League Draft! Go to https://t.co/qcTWTDGnn4 to cast your vote for JRM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for joining dairy king yes  MORE PEOPLE WOULD WATCH THEIR PORN THAN SOME TOUCHDOWN HIGHLIGHT AND THEY DONT G… https://t.co/X3etAaLMH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoViewsMovies @MGnPpodcast @thecinemaguys Glad I could help connect everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cousins for live....  #repost #wordporn #own #writersofinstagram #femalewriters #pisces #LOVE  #womanwriters… https://t.co/o0MNK3dHTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Author's Corner with Philip Gerard, *The Last Battleground: The Civil War Comes to North Carolina*:… https://t.co/u3EQ5rdAv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile And you still won't be in the Upper Peninsula of Michigan. That's why we're going to have to break up. It's not me. It's you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlbmprez @Yankees @Royals @MLB @MLB_PLAYERS @JPosnanski @clintonyates @Sut_ESPN @JayHarrisESPN @JaycrawfordCLE @Cubs What a group!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tourcaddie75 @KipHenley @jtedscott I’m bringing my paint today. https://t.co/S3jewGNKG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You had X squared over Y Tryna find the remainder, then add up I’m askin' my ex, “Why You askin' me about numbers? I’m tryna bag up.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fullmetalifrit @IrynaIvanova @LindseyPelas @ABC @projo @iamcardib and they blackballed me.!!! https://t.co/eAqK5BwvbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulosophia @LindseyGrahamSC @jaketapper called him a "political animal" capable of changing his stripes with new… https://t.co/fpSQrwNmpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the trade off with Allen. Never going to be super effecient but when he hits it's for big plays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardBarrow_ @RichardBarrow You're right about supporting financially. Easy to suggest someone else paying for efforts like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Footage of man being put in stretcher. He seemed okay. Possibly shot. https://t.co/9X3ecXKnXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s a communist socialist. we do not want him lol he belongs in Venezuela not the USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cwedding1 @realDonaldTrump Can we rent some of these floats for our parades?]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY TODAY! Be the 200th Subscriber to our YouTube channel and win #ValentinesDay gifts! Over $200 value! Subsc… https://t.co/5r1BYqPgQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ovaj lijevo od Westbrooka mi je pravi Vesko Mugoša, sin od bivšeg načelnika policije https://t.co/I4vWzFNazN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 He can’t do it by himself. He is not getting the support that he needs. He is still winning, just at a slower pace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Local4News What an idiot our strategic value is worth more than any financial one this guy is a moron ! #LockHimUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's gonna take Momoa ages to rip up Dune books according to those Amber Heard Aquaman set stories. That said, give… https://t.co/CG9aLy06YW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The human mind is the one thing that separates us from all the other creatures in the earth. #MiracleOfTheMind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandy25dandy again WOW some telling pictures online of u I won't tell😂😂😂 https://t.co/7TxvWxwiWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  @NatashaBertrand  @FBI Roger would be so much safer in jail until his trial. He is a threat to Ju… https://t.co/z8EgMOr3vH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly what I been saying!!! These people were PIMPING they kids! It was all fun an games till the man wen… https://t.co/6nmlx1nEMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#colorspecialist #goodhair #juanbestincolor @ Juan Best in Color https://t.co/i3jso9M6uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one is surprised, right?  @TuckerCarlson is a #Republican, after all.  He just happened to get caught.  @FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now let's hope we hear news of other Flyers traded at 2:59...cuz they need to cut a lot of dead weight]]></document><document><![CDATA[read about and how Nevada requires terpene information be listed on marijuana packaging, yet in Oregon its optional… https://t.co/gIKBalN4nF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__AsForMe__ @RonaldDPotts1 @Christianatose @AdamKeneinan It's also a delicious, life-giving beverage. It is true drink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouMerloni @SVcallahan22 The only show left on your station? The morning show is sucking pond water !]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CNNN ACOSTA--Why U- not Tell Amer bout the Illegal CRIMINAL-  Hispanic--"Protected" fr ICE for Deportation--that h… https://t.co/6Nd6TOc8cs]]></document><document><![CDATA[PJ Washington (15 points, 9 rebounds) snags the microphone and thanks the fans for a season of support at home, whe… https://t.co/2Am8aqsey6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SymthicProto My pip s song of Valhalla. I can blow out windows at 6K RPM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it was a bit warmer out today this sight of 11 pedal assist @citibikenyc's at my local dock would be amazing. https://t.co/qBTnCQjDLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome. So the timer went off and it said ‘end’. Guess it wasn’t a preheat timer. Here we go!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll bring foods... carrots, grains tossed in a light vinaigrette, dried or fresh fruit, and trail mix.  "If it’s… https://t.co/jK30PbhpxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes Immediately and forever I will move to Washington DC or wherever he hides and torture his worthless a… https://t.co/5oxvWNFtvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamJP1986 @SwankDADDY22 Did it on way fewer shots attempts so that argument is whack. It’s an impressive achieveme… https://t.co/gsEA796p3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkiTimes @zappafaye @ElkValleyBrew @ManvsAle @JonMontag @mtravis63 @TheStraightHops @CasaskullMark @ephoustonbill… https://t.co/Fw2swRfzts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badie_ThaTruth On and off the field...remember that. His glory is deeper than the jerseys we wear for “the man”. E… https://t.co/erXXd2NkWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trixie won all stars, naomi smalls deserves to win all stars. That’s the cold hard truth. Naomi was also robbed… https://t.co/jTeR14vVST]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandy___21 @StrangeFunnies Sandy think if I was at ya house as ya man we get in big fight I wouldn't be able to ha… https://t.co/fupH5xp2HU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@207_Melissa @Myhealthtoo @robreiner As to the dragging out, I think the reference was to many years ago “mobs” wou… https://t.co/vQB4fqCMaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of the cheesy plays. Please make it outta groups sasha! @onfireScarlett]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointed in the world we live in. (skip to 11:00)                                   Why I'm Leaving YouTube...… https://t.co/WBYcREXKru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending “How Women Rise” with Sally Helgesen. Interesting that most of the audience are women. Guys where are you? #HowWomenRise @NYHRPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of that good ole time music y’all!!!  Thanks for the pic Davina! @ Vieux Carré https://t.co/ezq8jUZXoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mountaingal456 I watched episode 1 last night I'm gonna start back up this evening pretty interesting so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcn4eva @jonz970 @DoingRight1 @clovis1931 @briantopping66 @Razorsmack1 @2501Wolf @AW95NJ @Lathenerd @raducom… https://t.co/zPgAIUNexz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanWHendry @matthewasears I see. I had to Google around for info, and reliable sources were surprisingly scar… https://t.co/5K01gtfqoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your CHAMPIONS get you a Killer Closing Gift!!!! #kevinfertigrealty #thechampishome #myclientsrock… https://t.co/vHLD1dLexs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChellaLocke @HempTemptress Can an 80's soundtrack be playing? If so I'm in]]></document><document><![CDATA[African American Read-In at Tri-C. I was able to see most of the readers, tho I had to get to class before it ended… https://t.co/ojSk1qyaZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public radio is not the voice from nowhere. It’s the voice from everywhere.  Wherever you are, whoever you are, @1A… https://t.co/IyNoKpzSZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever you do, work at it with all your heart, as working for the lord, not for men. ~Colossians 3:23 • • • • •… https://t.co/b9lyTCtUO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody PLEASE remix this song without every suffix being “-iana” and ill be impressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque nada dice policía como un uniforme militar y un casco de militar!🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @PrincessBravato That's for dam sure. Trump is not above the law and neither is the Russian republica… https://t.co/QwFoGYKUW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Instagram has spoken and the #Bamboo #gold #Earrings it is! #OmarTyreeBooks Launches The #Epic #FlyyGirl… https://t.co/1ChHEfpAR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me training to cancel anyone who drops dirt on Kid Cudi’s Man On The Moon I &amp; II]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I hope that the technocrats don’t give up entirely. There’s a lot of resources involved in increasing teacher c… https://t.co/c1a7Ejpa7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually no. I’m busy eating biscuits and sausage gravy. That’s how we in @ArkansasSenate train for the… https://t.co/HntXON096v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RabalaisAdv Rabs I beat you to it! Of course that’s only because you had to wait for @theadvocatebr to go press. I… https://t.co/rckutKviLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece. Thanks for the insight, Anna! As a journalist by day and screenwriter by night, I certainly hope to em… https://t.co/qQ1wOF6pWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@busylizzie48 @TheSilentLOUD @IlhanMN @POTUS SHE IS A TERROIST INPLANT IN CONGRESS]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Poetry $Alert$ "Astronaut Chick" available tomorrow...#PoetryWednesday #Poetry #ALottOfPoetry #AstronautChick https://t.co/yoa0JvuIbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consistently ask your friends how they’re feeling. I find that question holds a lot of power overtime for one’s self awareness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge finish for Aubre Fortner and Fort Lewis has its big lead of the game at 72-61. timeout Dixie State. 3:18 to go. #RMACwbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you need an example on how to live.. then you just shouldn’t have been born .” - Wayne at his peak 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lyft  astounded tonight. my wife ordered a ride at Terminal 3 at the Las Vegas airport. driver had no idea where t… https://t.co/4XU72F5wts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opinion: NASCAR's disqualification policy was long overdue but likely won't change the culture https://t.co/fBC4JlEcQg via @autoweekusa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielfrost @GeneHil12439202 @docrocktex26 Modus Operandi! https://t.co/EjeUGvmVUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hazzachelseafc Yeah, it’s honestly really frustrating because if you don’t have insurance getting help can be real… https://t.co/mGg5oJ3gip]]></document></documents></author>