<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Headed to the Shmoney 🕺🏾🕺🏾🕺🏾but I’m always up at the ass crack of dawn or all night lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Island City, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/ersO91D4rK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoked to be seeing @TheGloriousSons in Buffalo tonight.  Ready for a night of rock...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpaceDC I introduce; check/verify the Three branches of Government are actually separate from each other according… https://t.co/E7k1pJPysD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Yes it is and this is what the hate media compared @POTUS speech at @CPAC to...so think of how evil and sick… https://t.co/yGDcNUDJzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s okay to still listen to the Jackson 5. I doubt MJ was molesting anyone when he was 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA has been to three championships in the last two years and lost all three. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can this possibly be true after his lawyers "categorically denied" it and the president defended him? /sarcasm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rouzzegutierrez @dnaedith Conocedora! Qué buen gusto musical! Cancionsotototototota]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost I think Nick needs to learn the difference between racism and comedy.  Go ask the Wayne's brothers. https://t.co/Cf3VS6Mptu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey, sign the Rubio-Sinema letter to join @RepPressley in the fight to protect #Medicare #PartD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really came home to an academic honors certificate .. I’m a 4.0 lady 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jewelry Candles is a unique collection of familiar and exotic fragrances that are sure to invoke a sense of comfort… https://t.co/9cJMsdFif6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Russian disinformation campaign has had a singular purpose: confuse us, overwhelm us, cause us to doubt everyth… https://t.co/1AMe3zbmx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Pilsner - Drinking a German Pils by Smith &amp; Lentz @ Pelican &amp; Pig  — https://t.co/5IYFNcAc5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdSoundhead I see Brenda from Sausage Party when I look at this tweet 🤷‍♂️ https://t.co/EMPTLLEbOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@RetroWDW⁩ A modern version of the baseball games from the Disney arcades. I played the old school version at the… https://t.co/yH7EY6EzID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second period. #Leafs are more competitive, but no real threat to score. Forwards can't find open ice while being o… https://t.co/AYLdrvXrbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get @Rockies tickets and gift cards in the mail, it suddenly doesn’t feel like back to back Mondays.  Oh y… https://t.co/tRHPJGGJ0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol This humble member of thd @ordinaryfaces is grateful &amp; i am sure I speak 4 millions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattoak I feel bad for Hockey, but this is nothing but great news for the Sounders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomLegally @vijaystevens @HaakonPedersen @ForTheTweetz @BrianHelspan @TheBubbleBubble @SteveSaretsky… https://t.co/047jgTLnwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Injustice + time does not equal justice  I had great schooling growing up, never once was this incident taught in a… https://t.co/JeL68mgUg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost 80 chapters into a first read of One Piece and it keeps ripping at my heart. https://t.co/X4INzHYvoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridget123goooo @kyblueblood Love Westford. Use to cut through on my way home from work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love NFL Offseason, it beats every other sports off-season don’t @ me #Raiders #NFL #NFLFreeAgency]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/9/2019 - 01:41 Temp: 49.6F   Hum:  91% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 29.805in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeWml7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tipsy Dipsy by @slacktidebeer @ Locust Grove — https://t.co/lWv0Zwmivo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to tackle this 85 degree day! #Dabeach #Beachbum ☀️🙌 🏖🏝⛱ @ Ft Lauderdale Beach https://t.co/CbQl4W5fXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NACAC @SACAC_Info I loved the entire experience, including talking with folks who were very knowledgeable of the i… https://t.co/02iNPL0Nwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know how lame this is but this makes me so happy. I’m such a Puma stan it’s insane. The only shoes I wear. It was… https://t.co/aHEttqzTEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me to win this awesome BLACKENED Bundle and Metallica tickets from Revolver and enter to win yourself! https://t.co/cqTquRRwIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SA247LLC backing up their #PlayOfTheWeek with a suuuuuuubstantially discounted VIP month shows confidence, and I l… https://t.co/BwL8mUaCe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way back home from the gym, and I legit started crying listening to Self Care by Mac Miller👼🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredsprinkle That’s crazy, I had the same thought about it being stock footage. It’s like Netflix ran out of budget for aerial footage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woahhhhhh, #GreenBook was my 3. Did not expect that. Check the card! Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @krassenstein What?? Did they finally outlaw STUPID?? 😝🇺🇸!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind The "Let's get something out of this." phase of fleeting, dubious fame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reacting like this to a sketch comedy show...  #ManCodeMistakes #SundayMorning https://t.co/OTcHJy6CQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bamafanaticfan1 @BeckySmirks @realDonaldTrump Hmmm if ya think that’s somethin’ ...wait’ll yew see the GOP wannabe… https://t.co/YTMgqWGgPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadbaddy @Heliocoptero @yrysbryd @KotobaruSanSama @BahdlerBen @AprilLigeia @BrianSlimdog77 @Duke1CA @coelleen… https://t.co/dipELdc7qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tom_hirschfeld @squawalpineops There’s more Then one mountain to report on. The tweets and updates should cover both]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missremiashten needs to collad w/ @HydroFlask they would make the CUTEST bottles &amp; id buy them all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeonStowers98 @KebaAgostinho @B_Good_Man Lucky that us OL never hold 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open air sleeping porch of the mid 1920s by #rmschindler, alumni of @tuvienna 😎 #cali https://t.co/PSFmGBdQ8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodikantor There is one Presidential candidate who has this in their platform— @marwilliamson .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyOHannah The cop should say to jimmy welcome to the Detroit penitentiary. Or Drunk since day oneish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedarflats @JohanBBT @wrayzors @JonMontag @ephoustonbill @DRE_Go_Fish @cellmavin @OkiTimes @qblacklock @lhtetrick… https://t.co/ZHDijHtvAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall never in my life did I think I would ever hear R Kelly say some shit and sit back and go......I felt that I co… https://t.co/3i16yjOFLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to this song is like staring into a fire 🔥🔥🔥 👀  #NowPlaying "Bandana" by Freddie Gibbs, Madlib, Assassin… https://t.co/urG1WeBgIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh Girl Scout cookies are like 5-6 dollars. You telling me both these girls only had 100 boxes on the street? one… https://t.co/JkHdI0IEmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stir fry with lil_sketchy_b @ Clark County, Indiana https://t.co/uZN5LEeuhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never needed a team to win more than I need Duke to win tonight. I am so stressed. Is this what Braves blogger… https://t.co/ibJd2Cr7ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Granted I throw the old bone in the mix. I think marvel films are just okay disposable films. I have a fun time wat… https://t.co/ATB07IGwas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow I think from now on before the hearings start. The hating Senators just open with there hv ate spe… https://t.co/NsTkCOnyjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemphisPrideAS Mini Rain Hit Zero Deduction #CheerSportNational2019 https://t.co/pZwfy6K54N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just picked up my girlfriends cat from groomer and stopped at store to buy milk while keeping car running. went to… https://t.co/lyELgHYPqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Golden Grahams 2. Cocoa Puffs 3. Cocoa Crispies 4. Frosted Mini Chex 5. Cookie Crisp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, @kimrosamond!! Hope it’s the best one yet!! Have a gr8 day🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch what you tweet. One of your future employers may have screenshot the tweet mentally just to laugh at it forev… https://t.co/b0aZCZ5TvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother Earth is in a lot of trouble so we need to help recycle all the nuclear weapons and stop evil spiritual mani… https://t.co/nkPuNHcAG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer He spoke for her at the convention, campaigned, and voted for Hillary.  I campaigned and voted for… https://t.co/AZRypGVqOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joseph Ossai at Texas Tech. @TexasFootball   #ThisIsTexas #HookEm https://t.co/jUaBTqdCVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy unos cuantos abucheaban a la gobernadora, según una nota de un medio quien sabe cuál, se iba a sabotear la prec… https://t.co/7R9qlXQB02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este golpeador de mujeres el burro hablando de orejas perdón por el burro oh no es un chayotero]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow watch my boys Davey toe drag and shoot off inside foot. Love this #lookoutnhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[1-0 BLACKWOLVES!!!! (under review per challenge) https://t.co/2od6cFXSa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverLogical please read my story and share! https://t.co/syhbOgaj9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 DHS agents share anti-immigrant post targeting Rep. Ilhan Omar on social media - ABC News https://t.co/UW04ZaV00l (via @ABC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr What a waste. He didn’t need to stage an attack to make Trump supporters look bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started my twitter the same day I made my first youtube channel, so that's pretty cool. --- Do you remember when… https://t.co/4zPYsSExvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Russians remain banned from track and field: International track officials decided Monday to maint… https://t.co/F5Ddsup6HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a tough one. But top to bottom I like my overall roster depth. @WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[CON PASO FIRME Y SIN DUDAR NI UN MOMENTO, ASÍ SE CONSIGUEN LAS COSAS 💪💪💪🔥🔥🔥 ÚLTIMO ENTRENO MEDIO DE RITMOS DE CARA… https://t.co/hhONcVClU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[cast is pretty good. Jackson is a natural.  Lashana Lynch is great. Mendelsohn is Mendelsohn. I get why ppl are cal… https://t.co/jGGjfRiNRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AEWLane It ripped out a feather and stared menacingly at the camera afterwards.  I think that’s a sign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring (Leftover) Sum Ribs And Corn Bread Back Mmmaann We Going To Be Eating Good Baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyCrabz @sianoresist I am a 53 year old social studies teacher and I never have been as inspired by living polit… https://t.co/xh3yDG9wJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_kevstaaa If that dude quit basketball after last night...I'd understand. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to former Wilson Football star @CoachRodHill who has earned a job with the NFLs @Lions! Congratulat… https://t.co/YGGkC70tYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[that *definitely* makes two of us. blame @unhappyfinn for dragging me down the physics side of CS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspiration: "When fighting the uphill struggle, keep remembering the view once you get there!" #bradfieldweather https://t.co/Xc2hjUC8xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never want to return to in-store Blockbuster Video browsing, but I’m nostalgic for it nonetheless. https://t.co/NgTYQsZimG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Teaching Middle School Is So Hard https://t.co/YNK01YuKF1 via @WeAreTeachers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Natalie123xyz Then they shouldn't have been asking for so many changes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoiceOfVegeta I hear you will be at @emeraldcitycon! I will be hosting a Dragon Ball FighterZ tournament at the co… https://t.co/4gC4PK0Ug8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No girlfriend, but my tenants have gotten me 3 boxes of chocolates today and it’s not even noon 🤷🏻‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe Me If The Nails Looks Great, It’s NOT An Accident ~ @nailstudiobytom .. Tag and share with a friend who lov… https://t.co/rDKvY43yqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrible decision cowboys Organization to bring JW back that’s why cowboys need a Head Coach like jimmy Johnson or… https://t.co/lItG8xbO2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 out of the past 6 winners of the Oscar for best director have been Mexican. Makes me proud to be Mexican, gracias… https://t.co/VfhHqdmtRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Happy are all who take refuge in him.”- Psalm 2:11. https://t.co/q7Ym8A7vjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would hate it if it was the latter, because of how much I want it to be the latter]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS SATURDAY MARCH 2! Join @Dokken #Band in #ElPaso at SPEAKING ROCK! for #LiveMusic #Show #dokken #dondokken… https://t.co/51vfLlTaxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kobebryant @DwyaneWade #InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰💵🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/L6NMPExHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshNoneYaBiz @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump And not to mention that President Trump is the first and only president th… https://t.co/34tGcLZqoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like yeah, the 9-bangs and 9 flashes (?) are terribly disorienting (as they would be) but the complete blindness fo… https://t.co/0fnquRS0zW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungcodyc this playlist literally has EVERYTHING Anjuna has released. put this on shuffle and have a good time my… https://t.co/VjcmPd7RAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciaolimoncello These are violent movements that feed on hatred.  And we should not encourage or condone or excuse… https://t.co/hjog4f5kKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barrett, Reddish lead No. 3 Duke past Miami, 87-57  https://t.co/rc9JbBHEPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jungle Lord pinball machine at TNT Amusements! Call if interested  215-953-1188 or Email at tntquality@aol.com @ TN… https://t.co/vtxL0pSIJP]]></document></documents></author>