<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lysssgil @PruettJoshua I’ve gotta take Alyssa’s side w this one too. Kirkland bottled water is where it’s at!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched A Star is Born again, my favorite line “it was you I idolized, it wasn’t Dad” I so love this move!… https://t.co/ZUcpsTG31N]]></document><document><![CDATA['Bee-eye camera' helps support bees, grow food and protect the environment https://t.co/zWJLG18st9 via @abcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogDoPim Caindo as máscaras huh, Felipinho?! R.I.P. #RespingosNosÍs ou você prefere #3PingadosNosÍs?! Maybe, #ANTAGONIZA⁉️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deanglazeruc @UCnursing @UCHealthNews @AACNPolicy @UUHEALTH P.s. love you tweet!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EverythingGrich @grounder761 @vinman905 @slinki21 @TheRyanSupreme @Puckywuckums @AmyInJetsLand @davidtabrown… https://t.co/GaSTTjByMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global Odyssey Morocco 100 - It was my day (finally)  https://t.co/nkOzp4IqYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My treat to myself in 22 days. I took them with my energy bracelet because this little incentive is energy to me. I… https://t.co/FcRcK3sD5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkpolaroidgrl Hahaha !! I know it . He and the guitar are so beautiful and the fact that we hear his voice throu… https://t.co/woJlQFMiUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This’ll be insanely great. @sxsw, #barry, #sxsw, #FonzAsHamlet.  https://t.co/wiJWW0376X]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Will the new Bond film be called Shatterhand? It's not quite that simple”  https://t.co/POiin5qdxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dream #podcast: @rockcandypod on @thecountdownpc with dueling best musicals lists]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remembering the Republican primary, Trump had ‘only’ 13% support in a huge Repub field. But he had largest block vo… https://t.co/su0zjmjocq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlwesterfield @Annendil 'Beets' lockdown....you may as well put those on the sandwich too 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok last one but imagine being so petty trying to be a smartass by making a common saying so literal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missymom15 @dmurff5 @peter_schlifke Thanks for stopping by! We love having guests and sharing our math brains!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proposed changes to Endangered Species Act. Write your MPP by March 4. “This is yet another in a long line of examp… https://t.co/DpOVAVAyRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapsindepthabc Yuck. He’s not charismatic or charming. Smarmy comes to mind though. Just my opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett Shame on you. You truly aren't aware how much damage you have done to so many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CantUntil I rebuke that cold pizza in the name of Jesus! https://t.co/Zqs0Vhlimx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating with GarageBand! @DigitalGISD @GMES_Hawks #DLDay https://t.co/A7AeBeSlJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for the leadership and service of our @prsadallas chapter VP, @malizy! #PRSADallas #BlackHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ian gon lie the DJ need to be on it ( Kivo usually good ) &amp; we need to not be holding up the wall all day .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt Or life with someone with narsistic personality disorder.  Flashbacks to a mentally abusive relationship constantly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i... i would be in jail. fuck an investigation. i’m beating their asses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh why do all of my neighbors play the bongos? Yeah, bongos are lit but they only play them from 11pm-2am]]></document><document><![CDATA[if this is @mpeg_angelo why mans want everyone to know he part jewish SOO bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mydayinla My knees are hurting tonight but i forgot to take my #ldn last night so Ive been sicky all day.  I think… https://t.co/TdR3pHcmgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Serena Williams introduces A Star is Born because she is a star herself and Queen Latifah introduces The Favouri… https://t.co/0ZqPnr7K6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some more channeled messages from this 5D reality. https://t.co/wGId63zeTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, the guy in front of me for the past two blocks as I walk to my car is vaping the whole way and I’ve finally d… https://t.co/zTCIR0hZIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great 54-42 win over VIewmont on Tuesday, Leopards! Keep up the good work! (Leopard fans, you should probably skip… https://t.co/60sDhxemPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostgirl11 @NGDAverk @darker_dearie @tweetNorvena @hjhollis93 @AlliCamAllison @VillainPeterPan @Danielle21A… https://t.co/ClWPqCRVaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow  this is how much people like @AshleyMcBryde we retweet everything! LOL  book her!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanemNow @morten @realDonaldTrump Climate change is a hoax- check out https://t.co/NGFeOuhuqm for the facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyaBaker2 @Blueequus775 @sharon_elle @CeciliaCmaida @EkbMary @Joni_Looking @MustangRehab @CyntWhite… https://t.co/W1tAWIkUsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see @RealGDT and @alfonsocuaron hugging as #Roma wins the #Oscar for best #director = me crying. 👏❤️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had an older lady try to get into my car bc she thought I was Uber or Lyft...that was a weird feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9021hoee Not at all. They’re probably just as bad but they don’t center their conversations around that in front o… https://t.co/iuv9NxCXEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAvisW @the_clark405 @SelmaSchools Now, this pic is one that MUST be framed and placed on your desk 4ever!!!! Love these smiles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, If Paul Manafort was poor and black he would have never been targeted by the Mueller Witchunt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amara, the General &amp; Bella🐱♥️ #caturdayvibes #caturday #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #blackcats… https://t.co/gTzeGTZKK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much needed date night with this handsome face😘❤️ https://t.co/7stfMPiYrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenGartside Seems like a surprising editorial choice until you find out the kid in question is at Oxford and then it alllll makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper and Jackson are so cute! Welcome to the @OCFireRescue team to these good boys 🐶💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let it rain ‘cause you and I remain the same” #thebones #girl @MarenMorris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColsToTheWall His 2017 interview on @nprfreshair is one of the most delightful things imaginable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Any help for boys lost in NC mountains. Requesting helicopters and any help we can get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes It was so hard to watch him keep asking about those boxes. The GOP members looked so bad today. More i… https://t.co/Iq0CqcwJQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 The thought of those ancient, sagging balls, bouncing.... https://t.co/paHhJvF8Sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#almosttime #lessthan3weeks #mmw2019 #wmc2019 #musicdays #sunnydays #daytimetechno #denondj #denonprimeseries… https://t.co/1dz6J6kbTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to smile a bit. Most of these are incredibly dumb, sappy, oversimplifying, grammatically horrible, and most de… https://t.co/i224UXlIX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special guest at TPC Myrtle Beach today for the Grand opening of the @DJGolfSchool #MyrtleBeachGolf @DJohnsonPGA https://t.co/TpFWDuuwvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stewpotfan @dinogcole Good morning.  It's snowing.  The good news is it's going to warm up in a couple days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPLC president says Alabama does a poor job tracking hate crimes https://t.co/jjGDgEH3TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[😢 Mother Nature doesn’t know its race day at @amsupdates ☔️. @JClements51 will be rolling off from the 17th startin… https://t.co/mCwSUzPzqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel on @nbcbrooklyn99 ??  My son and I are watching and he is laughing his @$$ off!  My favorite actor his favorite show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing better than driving on the wonderful michigan roads at 2am!!!  gotta love the pure michigan difference!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 'o the mornin' to ya! Time change 🕖 and a 5K🏃‍♀️...I got this! 6th Annual Shamrock 5K on this chilly, wet Sunda… https://t.co/kb0LdAdB5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to tell my yoga teacher that I was leaving early because I was expecting a delivery. She paused and was like “o… https://t.co/I5pO9TCETX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little girls is one years old today. Happy Birthday to my baby girl Daenerys!!! #dogstagram #dogslife… https://t.co/rFubzwnEoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl in the library is so focused on flirting with the guy she is with that she nearly let her quiz time expire wit… https://t.co/g3KXDSUCuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Actions speak louder than words. Put down the kool aid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebindley @TwoBitWhackJob Thursday my wife said outloud the words “Imperfect Produce”, a company that deliverer… https://t.co/qHEuc3yvVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascinated by @cnn’s story of #Opportunity the rover that was meant to last 90 days and instead has been sharing im… https://t.co/r4QJR8GUff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keith_Hosman @PascoSheriff So bad that I think that would be hilarious!😳😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[These Rolex commercials are the new #Amex celebrity commercials. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight Northeast INT’L PinUp Doll Tara Emory Live...TS Goddess Ling Hosts ...Dancers Plus @ RBar460 west 34 st https://t.co/hGVsHdGBkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌇Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🏙Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🏙This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/fN5e1qyKCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[New friends made at #CBFlive2019 @ Hyatt Regency DFW https://t.co/RTNfXos2YI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finished in about 2:03... time to eat! #HalfMarathon #dchalfmarathon https://t.co/ShVX06f4Ox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittanyJBurnam To say yes is thought to be militant/radical and to say no is disrespectful to what we are fighting for. So yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come make some noise with us tomorrow night for #InternationalWomensDay  https://t.co/U9nLOzRtqg https://t.co/pqt2DXn34i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help! I am trapped in an abusive relationship with the President of the United States. #FBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @elknight20 Maybe shit like this is WHY they want someone more progressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 It's like there is a contest who do or say something stupider or uglier every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fitting for a “super moon” night. “He was her super moon. He liked giving her an entire galaxy, but one star at a t… https://t.co/Q71Ij51L8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashUpStanleyT @MorningMashUp @SiriusXMHits1 Christy Mauller, Gas City, IN and my birthday is Monday! 🎂 love liste… https://t.co/ymoE3XgdHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJohnson1097 “Amanda. I’m scared. All men same size all women sized skyscrapers”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn172510 @HippieVol @jamesonandbeers @The_Fool_Monty @8MillionML Bless her. I can imagine how upset she was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewmercer Seriously 44 more days and you have enough for the whole VM campaign https://t.co/s05PxcrgG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaAnglin I said 99.9% because I wasn't sure if Marie Kondo's show on Netflix is considered reality TV. I'm onl… https://t.co/7mlNUdCZnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nv_zde Es lo que quieren hacer. Pero no podrán. Los militares son parte de la población y si los civiles están 90%… https://t.co/YkN9Zuu13Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told the preschoolers and kindergarteners the story of Ananias and Saphira this morning because they were telling… https://t.co/kBmNI7mPo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr DOESN'T LIKE THE PEOPLE OR DEMOCRACY LIKE #HeilTrump @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m sorry y’all i know you’ve seen those pics everywhere, but they’re just too cute to not show 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtwife @HuffPost I don’t understand why people are messaging this better. This is a problem. They are letting them… https://t.co/PHQEs7pIrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Georgia_McBride @Month9Books @TantorAudio Thank you, @Georgia_McBride @Month9Books @lizaroyceagency for making thi… https://t.co/sCZBq23iR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_Haumont @MikeMorrisPE @ncties @TheOfficialCvHS https://t.co/3BtF0RSBbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 2 things that make me rage when I drive   1.) People who drive slow in the left lane 2.) People who block the intersection]]></document><document><![CDATA[ECRs: now is your chance to sign up for Personalized Career Conversations with leading scientists at #AACR19. Deadl… https://t.co/J1qMVu8q6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day #graphicrecording  at riceuniversity for #bestboards #ricecontinuingstudies  episcopal_health_foundation… https://t.co/B0dc9eqkBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmd51375 Yep and it’s unfortunate that he’s still on the street. I hate Michael Avenatti, however prosecuting Kell… https://t.co/lt7emBgshO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that was a play!!! With 20 seconds left?! 😱 go #flyers!!! #StadiumSeries @NHLFlyers https://t.co/5U3ziXk7Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#selfietime @ The Office Bar &amp; Grill, Holland, MI https://t.co/WzMUdf3APo]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York, Lower Manhattan  Stefan Hirsch  The Philips collection   Taft Museum of Art Cincinnati  March 2, 2019… https://t.co/UZmqjKTVRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFrustrated @WhiteHouse @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Time for gun registration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning Reps Jordan and Meadows looked like the corrupt Republicans they are. The Republicans were guilty o… https://t.co/Zwz3ajdZZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowing still at my house..... oh my!!! Where’s spring?? #snowinmarch #snowinginclarkton @ Clarkton, North Carolina https://t.co/Zdqw9GnyGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blacklilmermaid I’m honestly not a morning person... I’m only okay with interacting w/ one person before 10/11 am😂]]></document></documents></author>