<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash @brianstelter does a disservice to the American people every time he opens he’s mouth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i call my mom and she sends me straight to voicemail...oh you bet your ass i kept calling until she finally resp… https://t.co/tKquorjOwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikWemple @jmartNYT Those complaining about Fox derangement should understand that a real news organization would… https://t.co/jm2MBhNGLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexthetvterrier Like Salt and Pepper says, “Express yourself, you gotta be you and only you, babe...”. I like to k… https://t.co/8jp3UzEHDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imDREADserious @osoyoutink @Bucky2x your talking shit to a girl? IM DEAD 😂 boy put ya big pants on and act like a… https://t.co/GFWZyB0Upv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saqibishaq07 @freeCodeCamp Yes, I did not want my heat map saying I didn’t do anything while I’m working on projects.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Friday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Lawnton, Pennsylvan… https://t.co/9GbkU8lKBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i want is a #1 from whataburger and to watch how to get away with murder... but obligations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmclucks I haven't watched this week yet. I'll catch up and let you know. I'm not sure if he likes the vageene enough though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, @SouthwestAir Had such a bad experience w you yesterday. Beyond frustrated (see friend @Jen_Betts tweets!) Ine… https://t.co/9oM9Od7Qon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatiePorter @CFPBDirector I suspect there's a lot more she can't do beside figure APR--She clearly doesn't have… https://t.co/cunyyv0xDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’ll give Rizzo and the Lerners credit they kind of told us multiple times this offseason that he wasn’t coming… https://t.co/3myOao56vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ,I'm serious you little tubbyshaped, malignant sow. You wanna run your mouth about @JussieSmollett… https://t.co/O0nEXk5CKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonikaZiehl Please accept my most sincere condolences on your heartbreaking loss 💔 I am so desperately sorry ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[for breakfast i put more everything but the bagel seasoning on my everything bagel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgdendekker @RossBarkan @Gothamist @AOC As a white, Jew who has lived in JH since 1954, I pledge to vote only for… https://t.co/5AnC20za8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I am going to stay focused on training, I have a lot of races coming up. 💪🏊🚴🍎 Also me: I wonder how many of the… https://t.co/SWLfz4CkuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your PSA for the day.  "I HAD NO WARNING" is now obsolete.   h/t: National Weather Service Wichita, KS @ United Sta… https://t.co/8oGEpna8dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[That first career homer  . . . . crash2800 #michaelamditis canesbaseball miamihurricanes #miamihurricanesbaseball… https://t.co/RL3QFfs6zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of us MAGA hat and Trump supporters believe in the 2nd amendment, and yes it would be horrible to defend yours… https://t.co/cR0Kg3U016]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce @IngrahamAngle “All petitions 4 sanctuary MUST be made outside of USA” @DevinNunes 👍World z at War… https://t.co/xNEIXW25y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travel_MSW I live in Tucson, AZ.  Sounds like  going home is a good idea;  enjoy your trip and rest well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefffdeee @Frackalicious @TG_isthe_Best @ccmfcruise @JillScott113 @Amandas0223 @ShawnKrulik @bkstgurl… https://t.co/JaODz0Dg4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @KathyStricker2 @NRA Dear Dana.      Why don’t you ask Heather Hyer’s mother how she feels about Tru… https://t.co/bbBqyidlNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the thing: I don’t care about Bernie Sanders’ platform. I don’t care what he has to say. I don’t care if eve… https://t.co/1wnpDdT4gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking someone raw is a privilege and if you ever get to do it with anybody you should feel special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew I needed to create a plan that would involve me building my own credit, finding independent sources of incom… https://t.co/MNS0HErbP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Valentine’s Day, Jesus Luzardo planned one last workout at his high school before heading to AZ the next day f… https://t.co/O5LzCWAPwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Sara’s chihuahua went after the cross country team and it literally gets funnier everytime we talk about it 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignore previous (deleted) tweet. When you’re hungry, for latenight.. anything is possible 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2getherinServiceandLove  K is for Kindness in Kindergarten. When we are together, it  is always a little easier. L… https://t.co/QnciYTnnUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man this is so true. Why DO they ask for your resume AND make you write in all that shit still anyway?! I need answ… https://t.co/VzNqpsyeJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Conservative Cpac conference, you might think Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is the president of the United States… https://t.co/NPgTnSwed2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out n turn up wit me #youngdellz 3.28.2019 🗣🎙🔥💯 https://t.co/7KTO5CsUJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I love living in Hollywood. #Chewbacca #Superman #HollywoodBlvd #BestFriends #TotallyCasual https://t.co/Gaojlt2yFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna nap so bad but I have reservations at a steakhouse in an hour...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I say vote DEM. Period. I love Bernie a million times, however, VOTE DEM. PERIOD. I STILL say #startacommune I'm ov… https://t.co/3fb01PgwK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@segura_ps @bonzaiblog @Kowa97 @GypsyHart73 @RealJamesWoods I like the way you think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wittelstephanie @MeghanMcCain Are you feel about gun control in this country? Or are you like the rest of the Repu… https://t.co/qUleTpj30k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @andersoncooper @donlemon @ChrisCuomo Why doesn't it make the news that Ilhan Omar married her brother?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oscarmayer @Wienermobile When will you be in Virginia or the DC metro area??]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad to say goodbye (for now!) to our friends today but we did it up right at one of our favorite places and topp… https://t.co/wknqqE97EO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro tip sis - do the job you’re paid to do and act like the “manager” you’re supposed to be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very impressed @sendbellemare during our meeting #CLCLobby2019 #pharmacare #saveourpensions  w/ colleagues… https://t.co/ntUZuM1Qls]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that randomly check up on you and ask you how your day was; you are appreciated and deserve nothing but happiness in life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu_support any idea when the issue with shows I've already watched showing up as new? The new format has been aw… https://t.co/oGio3oYGOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pastor mentioned today “if you and your friends prayed for each other, imagine what things could be” and i needed just that]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright tonight was a week straight drinking, i think I should not drink for a while now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a meticulous rabbit builds a large, elaborate house, he inadvertently attracts a gaggle of displaced storybook… https://t.co/C45qKFER3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing more precious than the man you love sleeping so peacefully beside you 🥺 like wake up and make me a mother 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO 🎥  Talk To Me Baby 😉  Sexy Cute Tease Behind The Scenes At My Latest Photoshoot 💕 https://t.co/xt37eJPlj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sinfoniarx #snow in @Downtown_Tucson @ Pioneer Hotel https://t.co/no61pID7Ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted a salmon piccata from work but I also didn't want my manager to think I have time to spare to wait for food.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week has been a rollercoaster. We received news that our sweet Kate will be placed in palliative care. We don’… https://t.co/b1Bab4s9CL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you don't wanna be Spiritual....  Sometimes you want someone to burn in hell. ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends are the family we get to choose.  ❤️ @ Newwayvapors https://t.co/qaOUvu84pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DOG Crew! Dreamer #2579, Oban #2125 and Georgie #2267 having a blast in the snow!  #winter #ontario… https://t.co/uLI5uwp8n2]]></document><document><![CDATA[See ya later Sandy-Eggo #stewardesslife #comeflywithme @ San Diego, California https://t.co/DKOXr3LguC]]></document><document><![CDATA[she’s still the cutest little dog eva  @Bai_Bai34 https://t.co/OdmqVuV2AO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity, #NO #NO #NO #NO I will never again say I love you. It’s your turn to prove it to Me. What The Living… https://t.co/AQafBv82d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Modern historians say this brought the Indian economy almost to the verge of collapse, with West Bengal being burde… https://t.co/Q2Zx10AGdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep at 4 and just woke up... I was suppose to go to dinner hours ago. 🙃😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IHOP I tried placing an order and they wouldn’t answer the phone. So no pancakes for me. 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro #Cassie is so untrustworthy! All the girls saying someone wasn’t ready, they were true. #SHESALIAR #Thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yeah, those of us who watch MSNBC and talk to each other here on the hashtags are reinforcing our own opinions… https://t.co/jFPsQGQbDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so this is happening... myself, Rebekah and Telicia are going to be doing the Star Wars 2019 Virtual Half Mara… https://t.co/1aQWoUvio7]]></document><document><![CDATA[is there like a tinder for people who just want their hand held and hugs or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks I do love Rotel dip, just never heard it called Arkansas dip lol. Thanks for answering. https://t.co/pARY0Z5Ear]]></document><document><![CDATA[As my indicator. I switched my cable provider. My first question.  Do you carry @MSNBC #MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adehodges Well that really explains why I didn't vote. I wash my mass. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last yr at #Detwilers on University + Lockwood Ridge Rd in Sarasota FL. My Aunt Elizabeth High and Tanya Cutajar wo… https://t.co/sZ6fnaGYda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump In a few hours you will be more screwed than ever 😂😂😂 #MichaelCohenTestimony #MichaelCohenDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago, a shooter killed 17 at #Parkland Florida's #StonemanDouglas High School.  2,000 miles away, a @UofA g… https://t.co/01aXwPCTQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my jersey signed today. Thanks, #92! I appreciate you taking the time to do this. @GabeLandeskog92 @Avalanche https://t.co/38b0W9TO3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnaEaston03 @marypearson  Eighth graders have questions. Skyping with the author. #prosper4ward https://t.co/F2k6jWwhII]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @ArlanWasHere just told us she asked @IAMQUEENLATIFAH to play her in her future biopic and I bow down to her epi… https://t.co/bsKR3DNxBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Legalator @mkaz9800 @CathyPe78176224 @musser_benson @WaywordKnight @ForeclosureOz @Traci36362909 @JDGarfield2… https://t.co/M52oE90mSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenPKiernan @BostonGlobe Loved his family, God, country and the Red Sox. Not always in that order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissyWeigand @DavidKoechner @FortyThrive @DavidKoechner where are they???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaWorldCaresCA Will never stop saying it. Thanks for helping animals in the wild, when they need it. #isupportSeaWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TR401 I’m liking because your tweet made me laugh — not because I agree 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Dr. told me no more greasy food and spicy food until my surgery...  Sooo basically you want me to starve a… https://t.co/lrxhbTez7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump God bless you, President Trump!!! Ignore the haters!!! Real Americans love and appreciate what you… https://t.co/fGVALI7Csg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisonatkin @archaeocore @Sarah_May1 Exactly. It’s not hard to be like ”oh and this is a museum or a well known cr… https://t.co/9Pi3bJB4XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[my anxiety is gonna fuck up an opportunity to see someone I miss goddamnit]]></document><document><![CDATA[sad to see my husband has a girlfriend now?? it’s okay boo, one day @Mtrubisky10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichGoldman7371 @Coralspringsfla @CoralSpringsFL @RosemaryOHara14 thank you for noticing my story, but ... seems l… https://t.co/ky7dM1nTSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: 6A Southeast Regional Final @HGHSGirlsBBall 46 @leehighhsv 34! The Trojans heading back to the State Semi-Fi… https://t.co/xEOwZaAsT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEVELOPING on a Beacon in #AndersonTownship : Sheriff deputies located 2 victims which were transported to the hosp… https://t.co/46NeHoivv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[experienced the hardest thing I have ever had to see in my entire life today]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love working with my colleagues because we are a TEAM and a FAMILY ❤️ #teamminter #mediamonday]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BrandieMullen #GoddessGang #GoddessLightEmpowerment #GoddessLight #PsychicMedium  #IntuitiveReading  #TarotReader… https://t.co/OVPiA7gXFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPat2022 @SenToomey Toomey was behind the tax cuts for the rich.  He has remained silent on everything this presid… https://t.co/ogVkVsaAKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So close - and yet..... so very different - Marvin can’t stop complaining- he who used to drive with the window dow… https://t.co/jI7acCaSWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valac666 @SharonG40210896 @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @BeardedBuddhist… https://t.co/ByrzExdcgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chee_Burger15 once i cut back on my shopping habits in college saving money became a lot easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGDAverk @tweetNorvena @SourceRobert @AlliCamAllison @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @frostgirl11 @hjhollis93… https://t.co/GAi9WUKjaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Apparently waiting on paperwork. This is part of the administrative problems @AlaskaAir has been having… https://t.co/31lotnzlSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaJaegerTV Don't worry our tree is in our finished basement. Still decorated and waiting for Christmas 2019. J… https://t.co/qtCGZRraDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2nd year of this competition from @WEForg &amp; @WaterResearch through our #LIFT program]]></document></documents></author>