<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/dLKyBSxoKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a novice, but I’ll get this eventually. Just gotta change shoes. Jordan’s are not meant for climbing. @ Ninja Q… https://t.co/nOpFlCi4OL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up at 4:10 on @NBCSWashington, watch @RealSmokinAl and myself talk #caps #trades and much more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is he saying using *just* GPS? Because really all the GPS needs is to get the aircraft in line with the runway. App… https://t.co/wTjxCpis0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be a penalty for Schalke, not sure what they thinking about? #SCHMCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why has it taken about (50) years for Democrats to pick up on the Republican dream of flipping democracy on its fac… https://t.co/4zwn63WF95]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this last 2 minute back court rule is actually legit 😂 and it happened against the Spurs IN THE PAST TOO! It's l… https://t.co/IkgJusgbHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress Never heard a lot of teams knocking down the door to get AB. Once he quit on team in wk 17 just wan… https://t.co/I2qc4boH6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[DID YOU KNOW . . .  National Brand Cleaners have been 'Linked' to Lung Damage? Clean you home 'Once per Week' with… https://t.co/a04Ow31i8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta make sure your hoes come over to your place cause if you go to their place that means you're their bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeldobson07 @MrNormalDraws @blumspew @RealTomKenny @BillyBobThomps You and Blum are my favs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Briteeye777 @Razorsmack1 @Conservative218 @1ConservaDog @BAM4AU @donchatham @mikedavis_88 @debit_mullins @PJA1791… https://t.co/idRUDdiDkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out a new tapas bar. Happy Saturday! @ Bulla Gastrobar https://t.co/IpX7xx5Y99]]></document><document><![CDATA[O how they love to cheat, since they don't have enough sense to do anything right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Great8 #History #Natural @ovi8 @Jeremy_Roenick @NHL @gSchroedes16 @redwingdgr @Panger40 @Darren_Eliot… https://t.co/bjbQXdqJav]]></document><document><![CDATA[For LBJ to become 4th all time in scoring over mj but play in over 100 more games than mj... lol no words stats say it all#mjthegoat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunnerJingo @JamesMartinSJ @eloiseblondiau Only if they are non-functional at the end. Fertility is not the issue.… https://t.co/u3EgqQxplq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuttsForTomball Ohhh...I see how it is...😂.  I’ll get started right away.  The first book that I truly was inspire… https://t.co/tRclW566y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If ALL are not brought to trial for treason then this government has NO RIGHT to prosecute anyone. Citizens will ha… https://t.co/nvVw1Vei5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRoyHolbrook That was a thing of beauty. Then to finish it off with a goal was the icing on the cake lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taken right after I purchased our new car yesterday. Kudos to Michael Knippenberg and the staff at QCM for treating… https://t.co/sy4lz6ePbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#anniversary weekend in the #poconos. Diner and cocktails @pubinthepines #poconolake #lakecrescent @ Pub in the Pin… https://t.co/bEx3dkR6Ua]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for the first #BlackDiamond  #tipsdown @breckenridgemtn https://t.co/YbYmMVAG7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si el presidente no sabía del atropello que se le hiso a la magistrada Mirian Germán,debiera destruir al procurador!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexqgb @mims But it’s a very good point—there’s no doubt Pence’s legislation hurt the business community in Indiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time @ Disneyland and California Adventure yesterday in Anaheim 🎡🎢 https://t.co/roj7bzpvy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChefBetter him giving no effort on d is why you say that? when he wants to play d it’s not terrible it’s been dece… https://t.co/bypyaIai5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Captain Marvel. Movie was somewhat awesome and at the same time, it was less funny than most marvel movies. Rea… https://t.co/rXRZYqvz6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davefrom_ct @mcnicollme @kyle_tunis @BernieSanders You’re a fucking idiot....a system where it costs $12,000 to ha… https://t.co/zITGEMd64v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganTheBayer @JamesMooneyGC Omg it’s so easy just follow all my playlists and enjoy your life]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Alex. God's speed to the entire Borgmann family. You're in our prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes They are losing racists. Might as well put them all in one party, don’t you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSearcaigh It’s Romeo and Juliet for adults. Sorta.     No duels, no bumbling priests, no blood.      Lots of grea… https://t.co/yKAJ9ayzN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatMWilliamz Honestly I have no idea? Ahaha they fixed it at intermission tho so that’s why I have a double mic now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rashidfentyy @gigi__moreno @kailah_casillas Ahh, it is like a club now, well we were on the same team because of D… https://t.co/dsaSccBuZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNLV’s 8-5 conference record includes a sweep over the worst team in college basketball and a split with one of the… https://t.co/SuN13QllAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo compro o que cabreas @stephany052127  Para ir todos juntos ya q no puedo pagar los de la varonil 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can offer no proof beyond common sense but it seems to me that, here in 21st Century America, where lynching is a… https://t.co/L5zamqmbrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@896f2b8111464e8 @Whexit @WilDonnelly @thedailybeast What color is the sky on your planet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my sixth 1st place finish. This was a good one. Got 6 KOs in the final 10. https://t.co/7CVN5uvy1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaxonwhite13  with the @Younger2Connor step back from Friday night https://t.co/BkmtJJ651g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgtgary Got it thanks, I looked at the radar and couldn’t see anything in the same location so I wasn’t sure. 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Comité Central del Partido Comunista de #Cuba (o sea, Raúl Castro) está muy preocupado. Ha hecho publicar en Gra… https://t.co/yNCkTE0bzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyMayton Good chance he will be. I think he and Ozzie are part of the reason the Braves aren't going on a spend… https://t.co/BXGSYmAyAw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misspunk63 @nancylee2016 @CaptainShaedrax @thorshammer021 @annettesn011 @realDavidBrink @Sequencer16… https://t.co/9ButpqbUxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuthRogul This is such a Trvial Hypocritical issue...   I have never been so entertained with @Canada #cdnpoli in… https://t.co/cBWRkXWieP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You are an obtuse moron. You this your Doctor picture makes you look smart. It makes you… https://t.co/XIwZrlpjBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what, you were a true Pro. Alot of Respect from Steeler Nation. Thanks for all you gave here in the Burgh… https://t.co/knK8H19n6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could relate when I didn’t have someone perfect and treating me well, but before I’d do it... the idea is CANCELLED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantalStrand @WildwoodEyewear @Rod_Brown Oh, nice! That's really cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devildad12 @si_ncaabb Huh, You are upset because the news is drawing attention to a possible rape by a duke basket… https://t.co/GBeVf1YPhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulesJordan_N would be so lucky to get @janewildexxx for your first DP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another awards show down, where I watched absolutely none of it.  Mission Accomplished.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to give Northland Communications wifi a big thank you for not bailing out on me during my videoconfere… https://t.co/XJhwyVbkfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@108Charger @ConstanceM2015 @ArmorocCA @Jenny2Hugs @BrentCushman @arek_janula @ryan_dauphinee @BakicJelena @AnonLadyCop You too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night Andrew wasnt picking up my calls so i started sending him snaps of my asshole. He hasnt opened them yet.… https://t.co/fYgZ5RX4di]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are way too fuckin sensitive these days.  If u was joe I wouldn't apologize to none of yall #joebuddenpodcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know everybody life, direction, potential, and favorite socks to wear... but unaware of how to properly assess o… https://t.co/64IjuJb1Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating at @blufftonbbq was best decision I’ve made in a month! I met the owner, we talked politics, work ethic and… https://t.co/RkeEOdFg1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely, my number hasn't changed at all aven though I get lots of new followers. Screw the Dems and screw Twitt… https://t.co/TfxR4NQst7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFetterman Can we get a state health program on the discussion table, since we could use the tax funds towards… https://t.co/AigGvNUpyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why everyone is just now seeing the serial killer vibes that Rami gives Lolol does no one watch Mr Robot? He’s… https://t.co/f4yjdDou70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExpEconomia CUANDO ANDRÉS MANUEL DECÍA EN LOS DEBATES, CUANTO DINERO SE AHORRARÍA EL PAÍS, CON SOLO PERSEGUIR LA C… https://t.co/cjG5biHVok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eli was busy photographing his sister this morning! Does pretty good for a 3 year old. (Now to delete some of the 3… https://t.co/Go8ZPBKhzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NardieInJapan Lmfao Forreal meanwhile the seats are filling and in antsy as shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MasterWilliam Im watchin this, just sayin to myself, this can't be real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien @MalcolmNance She’s always been on the defense. All those years of fighting off daddy’s inappropriate grabasses!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highest allocation is PSEG’s 18.86% (jumped up from .42% in the original solution-based DFAX method), but that’… https://t.co/5cGm8mBqto]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRAVE Winterfest bound 2019! Thank you citylife family for investing into our students 😊 #citylifetampa… https://t.co/stampNqbqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulstolk Hola Raúl, igualito al intergalactico Chaves mesmo. Que ojalá se esté quemando en la quinta paila del infierno.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Harbor Freight Tools? We're hiring in #Gadsden, AL! Click the link in our bio for details on this j… https://t.co/wbNVzQqfup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan you’re a huge steaming pile of shit. As a conservative I’m embarrassed of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SorryIOverslept @Shaquemgriffin dude I just saw this on ig not 30 mins ago, fucking nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summalummadumb @GovMikeHuckabee Huckabee's hilariously self-serving, inane distortions are a weekly fun fest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard If I had this data base in 1977 my college degree would be very throughly excellent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @WayneCabot ... that bus that ran up on the shoulder near the LT ... to quote one Mr. Saggy: Wasn’t me. https://t.co/i2cpDzTMMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Tried 2 Be Romantic Offer A Date A Room A Trip All Paid By Me Aint Ask For A Penny]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a scum bag! Even if he gets away with this crime we should make him the face of Hollywood so no one wil… https://t.co/ev71j8kkhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean to tell me his numbers aren’t as good when he has Landry Jones throwing him the ball?   No shit.... What a… https://t.co/EDkTBi2IZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevhorn @codymon1980 @CIFState You’re not getting it.  That school is LOW enrollment moving up.  Foothill is HIGH enrollment moving down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratitude to @WSMA_update and @peacehealthsw for testimony at vaccine hearings in Olympia. Reps bravely provided a… https://t.co/CfJG4mqPAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaGrad So eating cholesterol doesn’t raise cholesterol? #NSNG https://t.co/y8aahUCNdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tokufxug @michaelhazani @magicleap @magicleapdevs I don't see any creator email from them either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pushdowns s.s. BB Curls w/ 5 sec negatives 4 x 10-15 ■ Close Grip Bench Press s.s. Reverse Curls 4 x 6-12 ■ Rev Pus… https://t.co/LU6ktIcB5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is a freakin legend!! Hopefully the weather up there is on his side 🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, Padres got a steal, Machado for only 300 million is a great value]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportzzTweetzz @Padres @LuisUrias03 @tatis_jr @TheRealHos305 Mejia-Hosmer-Urias-Tatis-Machado-Myers-Margot-Renfroe is a major league lineup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattspire The money you saved will be lost in time spent in stall incarceration. Hope your phone is charged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blowing snow here.  We got it lucky compared to further north.  I think the luggage tags are from as far away as th… https://t.co/uOiK9w8t8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vu la qualité du Wi-Fi, je pense que je vais tweeter en morse. https://t.co/Rm1Yl3e5ZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrinatingTree The Nets ought to offer that guy tickets to troll Dolan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingIsWar @Phoenixnjpw @AndyNemmity Same... just add breads and my crippling Diet Dr Pepper addiction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1. Student driven decisions can be based off of authentic data! #moedchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnKennedy I think any fair minded person has to wonder  if all the gop senators are puppets to @POTUS  except @lisamurkowski ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanting to be someone else is a waste of the person you are. -- #KurtCobain who should have been turning 52 tomor… https://t.co/0z5ohHRU1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 TONIGHT it’s the weekly SunDrais party with a LIVE performance by @tydollasign as he headlines @draislv Nightcl… https://t.co/YKfdYFJtPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Thanks for following! #WRITEON #TermAgeLimitsforPoliticians #KarmaRollsOn #420 #TaxReligion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never want to look back on my life and regret not doing more, traveling more, studying more, partying more. I can… https://t.co/Tea4w3eplY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandoval_isaac @Fvangioni11 Maxi en el lado de Pabón y Pizarro MCO Y así tienes a piri y gallardo en donde van  Así todos en sus posiciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baconflavoring @Outback Get this cat free steak.....FO LIFE! https://t.co/zYeSLoc0eU]]></document></documents></author>