<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian I also have been wanting to take my daughter! She’s 9! I think it will be fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how people don’t work out. Today was first day off from the gym in 9 days and I feel like a whale 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @FoxNews = Trump news = stste-run propaganda. The people who watch it are dumber than peo… https://t.co/LlSgZfUCMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Orleans Mardi Gras recap! Another weekend of fun with the homies ⚜️ #mardigras #nola #nolamardigras… https://t.co/wqf2vfSFf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats ladies!! @JClaireBatson @burnsELA6 and Martha! So deserving ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work in Wilmington today... popped into @bespokecoffeenc (so cool!) and spotted the #secondstreetmural across the s… https://t.co/RWYd7xnTqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLueCrew Make it stop! I think they pay ET or TMZ to air their dirty laundry. It just seems like they have way t… https://t.co/NOaEOEEmRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie has been fighting for  us for more  than 50yrs! The Party is not what I vote for, it's the ISSUES !  #ACA… https://t.co/NwwYIys5f0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really slick out there this morning! Drive and walk safely, Cougs ❄️☃️ #stillsnowing]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is farcical. #funniness #lol #smirk #amusing https://t.co/ecJThUVNst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan And Kraft was so holier then thou about kneeling. Karma’s a big old Bitch Kraft! A big old ugly Bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFreehams i’d have to take it to the vet to get spayed and whatnot. but honestly not looking to replace my dead ca… https://t.co/jRBoapkdju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I hope the Sara Lee that we keep hearing about is the Sara Lee from the sandwiches. (Are only #southern peopl… https://t.co/0Tb2wFn0f0]]></document><document><![CDATA[LADIES!!! Is anyone paying attention to what is happening in Congress today??!!? They are going after our healthcar… https://t.co/laulqU4GRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Hillary Clinton Should We Believe? The One Who Tells Us To Reject Trump’s Attempts To Divide Us With Fear, Or… https://t.co/qyjaeXx5g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athletics It was great to see you in Phoenix.  #LookingGood⚾️💚💛 @ Sloan Park https://t.co/ILZknx7YQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local Parks Now! #parkequitynow #redtogreen @advancementproject @preventioninst @CBECal @tpl_org @PromesaBH… https://t.co/ZP6B0clu7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC YOUR FRIENDS in the MS-13 gang are MURDERING AMERICAN CHILDREN! Keep talking Alex YOU are going to be in so ma… https://t.co/aMQWSi5l8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBCSaysRepent There are plenty of spots reserved (and waiting) for your ‘group’ in Hell.. until then.. I pray for… https://t.co/OHWzr9nSsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonswaine If anyone deserves to be put in jail forever, it's Roger Stone. He has had a disproportionate influence… https://t.co/DhRFTtyyxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a second there I thought he wa gonna make the Asian eye symbol. If he did I’m sure some people would defend thi… https://t.co/AFUBtD1q20]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what age should a #man stop wearing an earring in his ear? As I get the older this is so unappealing. I would be… https://t.co/94RiG4pFFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popehat @gtconway3d He heard it from John Miller. Or, maybe he heard it from John Barron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re literally the biggest dumbass/asshole if you do this and you’re definitely not worth shitttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends who slay together stay together. 👯‍♀️👯‍♀️ #Squad #Solid #SolidGold #SistersForever • • • •… https://t.co/S1y1h5PkML]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever send a risky text and u so scared u start doin chores https://t.co/175f8BsCaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USEmbassyAbuja @EUinNigeria @UNHumanRights @mbachelet @AmnestyNigeria  BUHARIS THUGS ARE DESTROYING PDP VOTES AND… https://t.co/oqvJeKFEVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cmm09672 @Stephanie851574 @MaxKennerly @AJA_Cortes That's great to hear, and your daughter will be proud to call you mom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Wonder if she was as mean and sarcastic with that interview like she is with reporters. Bet she showed her ugly side to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m catching his ass with oil and flour to the face when he first walks through the door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’ll be looking down, swear I’m gonna make you proud I’ll be living one life for the two of us...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonRice4 I mean nobody in particular but if the shoe fits lace that bitch up and wear it 🤗👟]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bf admitted that he’s been using my $50 purple shampoo and he’s a ginger like are u kidding]]></document><document><![CDATA[The safe tea cups ride vs riding the tea cups with @BLUEJACKSON Blue..... eating the corn dog and churro before tha… https://t.co/YMYfHs26KL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, so much, Eve!  God Bless you all as we remember and celebrate all women are and have done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Twitter,  I am going on vacation for two weeks. I will be trying my darnedest not to check this site during th… https://t.co/5P0HxCfOUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quaseinedita AIN -abraça-  eu fico muito mas muito feliz quando alguém comenta pq meu cabelo natural era motivo de… https://t.co/dQhULdVdsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonElkins24 Hard work and determination! 🏀🧡🖤🐾 https://t.co/TyFl61OEPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there places in the country where it is not a traffic violation to neglect to use your turn signal? Because on… https://t.co/bN5E8N7z9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other news... cleaned out my bikini drawer today lol Got rid of 2 tops that don't quite fit anymore. Also i'm ve… https://t.co/bmhbmw7hN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CNNTownHall Tulsi rocked the town hall by not getting deer in headlights look, or being tripped up by fractious questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you ever want to tell someone how you feel but you have a feeling like they are already annoyed of you so you just let it hurt you? Bc same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche Pretty sure the people who live do not think Vietnam is Utopia. Oh ya communism....that's all they know. E… https://t.co/1L8VqaUHPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VZWSupport Is there a way to pay a cell phone bill in advance? I don’t see such an option on the app, but I may be… https://t.co/aGHoUFB3Hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taybaby_x @melanie_kondor These are some golden memories from that English class]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone thinks the worst part about pregnancy is morning sickness but for me, its actually how bad my skin has bro… https://t.co/T3NJ9KL57a]]></document><document><![CDATA[people really be out here getting on the flight as the pilot is getting ready to leave? what the fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelalucard666 @Michael53991477 @PDunn99 @Alyssa_Milano My background and work with Human Behavior says different… https://t.co/9GzV2IInvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life won’t give you purpose, you give you give purpose to your life.   -me, as far as I know, could be someone else before me 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up craving eggs. I wonder if that is a protein deficiency, or just me remembering how much I love a poached egg 🍳 🥚 .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything in your life is a #reflection of a choice you have made. If you want a different result, make a differen… https://t.co/E2eZyuVOR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup. This plus Bernie’s don’t look at race, gender, etc! Check yo privilege people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSSmithII @CIAspygirl @TheWitcheryEdin @TowerEdinburgh Unfortunately no (canned only)! Have you had haggis a… https://t.co/Xm1jeeshfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sandmann Sues Jeff Bezos for Amount He Paid to Purchase Washington Post https://t.co/fft3aWSAVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyliemacy2021 @ImpactGoldLang Most definitely Kypes!!! I'm still exhausted. Lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope that doesn’t come across as mean lmao i just rlly don’t check for the islanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a new favorite pitcher. I can't imagine losing a game with this last name. I'm rooting for this guy. https://t.co/GUPiK4ogVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritstiles also ask her how many students in the already strained school systems who are CURRENTLY getting suppor… https://t.co/IcPDBCRrjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beragon #Maddow Cohen explained how it worked doting the hearing! There are actually two parts to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryZ07 @GayWeHo Wtf is wrong with anyone who would watch this stupid shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilDonnelly @MichelleWinsta4 Make that interpretation of *legislative history* to discern intent, which may includ… https://t.co/kVLJyB1bhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve self-published sf before … have a short story coming out on the first, in fact … but this is my first romance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dylan_RobertsCO challenging @RMGunOwners Brown assertion that other states w/red flag laws violate due process. Sa… https://t.co/QzstvYVIPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James3940 @McAllisterDen Sure thought Dr. Carson was Black! What' the matter with you Demos?]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND YET NOTHING IS DONE TO ATTEMPT TO USE CONSTITUTIONL AMENDMNT THAT BEGAN ADDRESSNG ADVENT OF AN UNFIT POTUS, WHC… https://t.co/jRkXlTCct2]]></document><document><![CDATA[my blonde days only last two weeks and i hardly took pics so enjoy these https://t.co/RzpeT1KHXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian @CharlieWilson Hey Kim @kanyewest rolled into a union town and went non-union riggers sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cried putting Sasha in the bathroom this morning and told her two months would fly by.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time singing Shallow anywhere besides my house or car. 😂 So glad my fox 🦊 twin 👯‍♀️ socks 🧦 twin 👯‍♀️… https://t.co/hRsUSvHrUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine having the worlds smallest car and still parking like a jackass.. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaidUruguay Ange eres una niña muy tranquila y te desapareciste mucho 😅💕 Siempre nos apoyas y en todo, todo por el… https://t.co/jBP4qHx6rz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally paid $200+ to have some type of motivation to learn java by myself 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Don’t get excited about Medicare Mitch. It just means you people won’t be getting your pockets lined… https://t.co/IYx4xli9OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Done with the gym #OTFPortland before sunrise...on a Friday! #Priceless Bring on the weekend with the family coming… https://t.co/cUH1CD7uba]]></document><document><![CDATA[1975 Italy broadens abortion law  1977 George Harrison releases "True Love"  1978 1st Iron Man Triathlon (swim, bik… https://t.co/FWtARUez6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamHendrick I could go on and on about why I’m a big allie! So I’ll just say , YES! 🏁48🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oceansidewebtv @tylermeredith @janephilpott @fsorbara @TOAdamVaughan @cathmckenna @JonathanWNV @jyduclos… https://t.co/iyNA3PVx7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will attack other people for doing nothing, just because they’re unsatisfied with their own life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt posted a pic of me for #InternationalWomensDay and said I deserve a trophy so I’m pretty sure there is nobody… https://t.co/mcLtITYaAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 4th #dool #days  Wed Mar 6th  Rex confronts a man with a  gun , who appears to be stalking Chloe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m balls deep in vegan mayo rn eating a blt but without bacon so it’s an alt bc avocado and La loves a vegan food… https://t.co/0aiZ6Q4rj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought Wilson- Raybould told her story last week. Do you think it would have changed between then and now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[been feeling this way since before my first cycle. like what do I have that you cannot have? 😳🤔😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fashiongranny1 @julie_kelly2 @DineshDSouza Congress is made up of Representatives plus Senators.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ian Ziering sat behind us at a Van Halen(?) concert. Eh. If only it could have been Luke Perry💕. He would have left… https://t.co/ZqBExGXmOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenRMarks @AeroEvan949 @Auggiie69 @Pameladj13 @MKMcQueen Congratulations! Awesome partners 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why does college have to be 4 years? Why not 3 years? Why can’t students focus more immediately on their discipline?” GREAT question! #FSTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happened when @BrandtSullivan and @KyleHardin8 set kbs driveway on fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of work I got done &gt;  The amount of work I have to do &lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FroganMeeman i’m so used to it that honest to god it’s just funny now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teylor_smirl I live in CA so we don’t really need booties but my babies do get a little chilly during winter https://t.co/lo92LdWVlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelsonLisa @JeffreyGuterman Because if one ends his or her own life he or she goes to hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Silky Nutmeg Ganache is my new role model. My queen #DragRace11   @RuPaulsDragRace @GanacheSilky https://t.co/ARbdEw5k3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans Looks like that bottle of tequila is helping him out greatly 😂😂😂😂😂 I wonder if he would share with you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like my weekend is going to suck.   Anyone have any pics, GIFs, etc. for a preventative mood booster?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing in Vegas!! Go Knights Go! @Lcasimiri #toques @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/Y3g5UPWobI]]></document><document><![CDATA[See How To Make Over Your Everyday Meals With Tips And Recipes From @Cdn_Turkey! @OttawaMommyClub #MakeItWithTurkey… https://t.co/vO1IW0XsCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm revising 2 books and making a new picture book dummy this month. I laugh in your face Mercury retrograde! #kidlit #amwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzanneLively @NancyLeeGrahn It’s all just opinion, both sides. I don’t do mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color coded all of my apps so I inevitably changed my lay out. Let’s see how long until I lose it. I’m betting 13 hours.]]></document></documents></author>