<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@lopezobrador_ @emoctezumab @CiroGmezLeyva1 Tweet # 557;Día 102. Buen día Presidente, Secretario. Ruego a ustedes i… https://t.co/tI6ZTyKF0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is hands down my favorite event held in KY every year. The Next Up Recruits Unsigned Senior event gives senior… https://t.co/agJ0x5rlpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of the highlights of @ethaneckerr (2022) when Roy played Bountiful and his his cousin(Devin 2021) this past w… https://t.co/nIIvyhdq8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is sad but there are a whole lot of lefties living in these tents who voted their politicians in cause they wa… https://t.co/TgtCpQoGog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeProtich @jakeperry820 That's quite the vocal machination. I always heard the Chris Cornell element.  The first… https://t.co/5oif4ZorUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to get a box tattooed on my arm solely because of the 1975 song Give Yourself a Try]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron passing Kobe as a laker will be one of the best moments in NBA history lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3rdBaseBlonde @miamiuniversity Nice! When did you graduate? '06 for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Happy104th #ColonelPaulWarfieldTibbetsJr #EnolaGay #LittleBoy #Hiroshima #Japan 🇯🇵🍄 #GodBlessAmerica… https://t.co/VuZUV76hkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayDobenskyWx @NWSLosAngeles @Wxetctv Wow! That looks like a lot of rain! Do you think mudslides will be a problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and I was going to take today off lol  . . . . . . #fitdad #fitnessmotivation #weightlossjourney #feelgood… https://t.co/DjYFaYAel8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this not obstruction of justice? Does anyone think the President has the power to do this based on his office?… https://t.co/eJWMWfomKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Tack24 @NASCAR Oh, I get RaceView on my desktop and my phone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make fun of Rubio a lot because frankly he deserves it, but he’s been right and lead on Venezuela and deserves cr… https://t.co/7rFROv4f1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just fell all the way down on the way to class. Now I have dirt all over me and I have a presentation in 30 minutes. Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pumped to witness the nephew's first baseball game! #BlazeOn @coachesche14 https://t.co/KU8oI6teKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love doing these adventures with you hallesantinihamilton let’s keep at it!  #runningthroughthedesert #sandfordays… https://t.co/xPXcLTRxxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec What the hell are you on and does your doctor know you’re abusing it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bealeader #beachampion #striveforsuccess #aspire https://t.co/gFxPMPDi5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jd_burge @ofofilms But then again, the moon landings aren’t real so technically it doesn’t 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hhaving a great day at the Teen Bookfest by the Sea in Corpua Christi. Aquasaurus selling fast! https://t.co/oSIK4Eezzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The art and science of #leadership have more to do with being open to new ideas and change; #listening to all the d… https://t.co/Fq61FKipRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When socialism is law of the land, we’ll all get to follow our dreams as podcasters or writers. Pot will be free an… https://t.co/zS1ezbHwHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulogia0 @puertoricofilmC @ovjocm Good, or given the impact to the discussion isn’t relevant because it’s a disti… https://t.co/oxexbyI9Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps the answer lies before our very eyes!  7 congratulatory photos/ 29 men (some may appear more than once/Zero… https://t.co/d7fcrOWejf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @SenFeinstein I call total #Bullshit https://t.co/szdv9Zftp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder  Wednesday from 6- 8 will be our first practice/workout at the middle school for the Runnin Elks AAU team.… https://t.co/btA2pPDw65]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how much money and research went into this? I also hope the technology used helped develop something impor… https://t.co/nKD0L0xP25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaSherr @nealrider98 @themaxburns @AOC @RFKHumanRights Some are. Many are not. It’s the MANY who don’t follow… https://t.co/XgBwCR4OrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaymitch This was the biggest trend at the time #sombre giving sophisticated dimension and movement to the hair.… https://t.co/Q6It1AlbEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eb lanes closed til 6 am for construction in #DowntownRaleigh on Peace St EB at Capital Blvd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveweigel I’ll give you that point. Bernie has been very consistent with his “it’s ok to not vote for someone sol… https://t.co/PmHxFX2D1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today do what you know is right, dont concern yourself with what "THEY" say.  #letsgooooooooooo  ##allforward @ Aub… https://t.co/TzlI4XnMhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did the Cavs get rid of Joe Harris... Every professional sports player that leaves Cleveland gets better... mus… https://t.co/bPAOPV2LRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope every time my ex buys a new shirt there's a loose thread and she pulls it and keeps pulling it until it unra… https://t.co/q7OvwmR9fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell Apparently she doesn't know the rules you're not allowed to pick up the balls stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayJayLuv EXACTLY! it's so annoying, like stfu and get out of my face with all that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎈OPEN HOUSE | 2/24 | 1-3PM  - 4 🛏 2.5 🛁🚽 2 🚗 - ✅Move-In-Ready ✅Sweet Kitchen with Enormous Island ✅Awesome Master S… https://t.co/yuiNElLYyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I can see it, then I can do it If I just believe it, there's nothing to it! #youaremyeverything  #bestwife… https://t.co/NSE4iZcNZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multi-layer structures do give "hierarchacal wrinkles" with small-wavelength ones on top of longer ones, but only i… https://t.co/HVWhVm4rUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@komonews @barbara08100912 Barbara is fine with that. We just need to credit her like we did on the evening newscasts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncwrestlfactory @CPyles8 @ncaawrestling A hands to the face call sent it in to OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A la larga, es mejor que nadie nos conozca, que nadie sepa demasiado de nosotros. Basta con que uno se conozca bien.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT!!!!! R.I.P. Brody Stevens. Why do the people who make us laugh the hardest suffer so much? #depression]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomannn @matttywill51 Thomann, Duke still has 3 guys projected to go first round. They'll have at least an 80% ex… https://t.co/ZhBaA1SsVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all so stuck on the Kardashian’s but forget that flint Michigan still has no clean water]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Django_Kitty @NBCNews @maddow trump tonight............ https://t.co/xWJLdhHaEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I had to explain to a table of people who Charli XCX was after I said she was my celebrity crush and honest… https://t.co/tM62o252CS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rule of law did not win today. And don’t be surprised if the president pardons Manafort. Calling it right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWIPE right ➡️➡️➡️ for some B Roll footage on our biggest project to date! . This project was a nightmare, but noth… https://t.co/Un2eNrwJpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter the homie destroyed the keyboard in Haverhill two nights ago straight up best live performance I’ve ev… https://t.co/qlmEgTKVRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought my mom tickets to Paul McCartney at Dodger Stadium this Summer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic win by the #LadyMantas @LBHSsoftball @Kpinkham12 !!  Come out Thursday &amp; cheer them on as they host… https://t.co/m6MqUDt59J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanrosso @kellyrossoMD Collect your own night soil, and either sow the millet field with it or throw it at a Lollard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz  Hmm...looks just like the mouthpiece who is also tampering with and threatening Cohen, doesn’t it? You’… https://t.co/QJRiC7ctc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier @AnnCoulter And she's proud of that, probably got some silly ass degree which is useless to boot]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't stand for the #Constitution you can hardly claim to stand for anything at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 February 2019  Music gsguitar  📷 video @Spirit_Bombs  #artists #music #guitarist  #performingarts #live… https://t.co/5TGXkg9Ckk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codybright20 No charge cuz, ill bring it over today. When you gonna be home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to drive down backroads and listen to “Whiskey Lullaby” with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an over 3hr delay on #united we finally get to the gate at EWR and no one is here to deboard the aircraft. Ev… https://t.co/uvmV7eVgEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’ll take a while for her to get better but at least now we know for sure and that she’s getting help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pizzahut Yes first time getting these. But wish it came in a pan as an option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwgrooms @GriffinTSmith @MariiahGarzza @rogerpatmyers @BamaRightField Thank you, it’s my favorite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_gauthier1 @cnnbrk, @shaunking, @MichelleHunter, @BuzzFeed:  So, this is what we’re doing in New Orleans for Mardi Gras?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just here working on a Sunday. Happy Oscars everyone! And thank you mercedesbenz and @abcnetwork @ Four Seasons Hot… https://t.co/1MIMkfx6iT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parked for the night (@ Cowan Systems in Burlington, NJ) https://t.co/DeFzYiSmXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been watching Limmy's Show lately but it's hard I haven't got a fucking clue on what he's saying half the time https://t.co/Dtt6yxclGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erik_niel @PackYrPixieDust Thanks for the tip shopEmilyG has some great designs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whacky dream sequence. I was sitting in a balcony with @elonmusk watching the St Patrick's day parade. Maybe it's a… https://t.co/Yp1kHXNGRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scene of the crime, 25 years ago tonight. #FirstDates It took me about three months to ask her out but now we look… https://t.co/OyYQ2Rg1fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ross_minor Ross, you're the man! Talking with you made me excited about racing again! Stoked to be on the #RoadToTokio with you!]]></document><document><![CDATA['Merica!! @anthemgame #AnthemGame #anthemranger https://t.co/OGxTSTMtad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraMar111 @sxdoc God what is wrong with him yuck poor girls, peice of crap parents is right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLBruins Let’s go Bruins Let’s do this Let’s go get loud Let’s go Let’s goo goo Let’s goo]]></document><document><![CDATA[📣📣📣**BIG SILZ will be hosting the 6-10pm show on Monday Night in #Boston on @WEEI ...#1 TOPIC...#BobKraft...What wi… https://t.co/7fTZGtg7AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s hard to believe, but I swear, one time I successfully rewound to my desired scene while streaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XorjeO Wow! It looks like they know how to improve your mood. That’s awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the final regular season home game for the #Badgers women’s puck team. A WCHA title is on the line for Wiscons… https://t.co/7EpaT9rSOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send this guy to the border @ My Command Center https://t.co/VT2odewFSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone else kinda get nervous peeing at school, cause you think everyone is judging your pee stream?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlitosR_11 @misslaaurraa @ARXO96 Si guey pero es mejor no tenet ni una de las dos, como yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rose's are red Vilots are blue  Your side girl is pregnant  Jokes on you 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My (accurate) love diagnosis is ‘Commitment Addict’ what’s yours? @mullenlowegroup #LoveDoctopus… https://t.co/W6Kz8Tycqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated Mazel’s birthday at school, we brought the class Yogurtland and it was a hit #mazelturnsfive… https://t.co/4ntJstftKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MonDAAAYYY!!!  #SpringBreak2019 for @ProfHankLewis...  @KPRC2Andy   @KPRC2Haley  @KPRC2Eric  @JenniferReynaTX… https://t.co/LPzPzPCeqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro Dile a los narco de Raúl Castro y sus cómplices van todos para el infierno]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grab you green and get down to the @hollywoodimprov March 12, 7:30 for some pre day Irish shenanigans The line up i… https://t.co/svohreM1st]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve be able to meet @sambassartist a few times. Always was a nice humble guy. Rest easy Sam! #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch @justicedems @MarkWarner @SpeakerPelosi @SenFeinstein Blimey! Are you on Westminster time, or just don't sleep, like me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elephant in the Dark based on a poem by Rumi retold by Mina Javaherbin pictures by Eugene Yelchin #bookoftheday https://t.co/Ri5huH19Dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayleeSmerbeck @cybenning @g0nz4l0g0nz4l31 @marcorubio My location does not make me more nor less Venezuelan. You idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibepacheco Buenos días Ibeyise, yo perdí toda comunicación con mi familia en Maracaibo.... saludos desde Orlando FL...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarragan @SecNielsen Keep up your good work. Hold @SecNielsen and this administration accountable to their acti… https://t.co/jSEfgAJGbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you forgive, you cannot change the past, but you can ensure the future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasticDad2 @CalebJHull I think this is correct- they're responding to his "massive amounts" claim- but there's… https://t.co/HVCvaumxmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @GOP SHE’S. NOT. PRESIDENT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @YouTube Richard I have a rule it's a life rule. Do not engage ignorance. And Carson Tucker or Tucker Carls… https://t.co/EIbn7HkrrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recommend this podcast treat from @alanalda for fans of the all time TV classic, M*A*S*H: a show that made viewers… https://t.co/3TbksY9DaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachC_Collins Of Georgia State I have a top prospect Caine Savage stopping by your school this weekend with his 7… https://t.co/P1E7ShYboa]]></document></documents></author>