<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[DM for BUSINESS📲 TRAVEL STYLIST ~ WE BRING GLAMOUR TO YOU • • We specialize in Eyelash Extensions, Makeup, Sew In I… https://t.co/pp4eMZttZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[REALLY looking forward to seeing all of the different ways Wiggins finds to put up bricks during tonight’s game.  A… https://t.co/gGbWP9nDYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCWildfireToday @Rubiconski @PRAIBeauty @CathyKangas2 @AdoptFire @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13… https://t.co/0I5JcShXxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get $20 when you use my referral link to join MoneyLion Plus and start investing! Learn more in the MoneyLion app:  https://t.co/DNtLApnZWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been punched in the vagina but I assume it’s a similar feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaboyblue357 Where the FUCK are you, I'll throw some energy your way... I'm in far nor Cal...I assume you're east… https://t.co/RWZob8AQKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking Biz News is now available on app form. Here's how do download on your phone: https://t.co/XcRLPJ27xk https://t.co/oM2NANJiC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people whisper “he a drug dealer” I know they are snitches! That’s nobody’s business 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandomAndyLyon @ksvenu247 @backt0nature @NammaBengaluroo Sarah Sanders would have bitten him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sinahiwnl Wednesday is lan tournament, org jersey not even shipped yet MonkaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thirst4dodgers Even though I had two lunches today I am legit jelly that you got to go to DQ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars can kiss my butt leaving out Carol Channing in the memorial when she was a Oscar nominated actress @TheAcademy sucks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found Rickie Fowler’s Doug Baldwin tribute to be very, um, moving... https://t.co/VODj3c8vX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leosangal @LeonKrauze @Debora19650415 No, no es correcto lo que le hicieron, pero si hay diferencia en la nacional… https://t.co/ng8en1D28e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jose____89 @SophiaBush So am I since when do celebrities actually give a rats ass about the military when they hav… https://t.co/aVTJfkA18S]]></document><document><![CDATA[. Going into the studio, getting ready to cook up somethin real nice! 😎 With the artist ygk_gkotti . . Stay tuned f… https://t.co/KVfNwhnbQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @DrumrofTedworth March madness. https://t.co/Kg1qapCZGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghostly_ennui @PhilOutsider I worked at what was then St. Edmond’s Federal Savings Bank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTokes @DebHiers1 @realDonaldTrump What the hell is goin on in Texas ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry The dem house has to impeach him. They promised their base and they have to - probably for the bimbo pay… https://t.co/aeHvmAz3rM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeromanAT @MilitaryMaps @DocPakistan @watanisy @lummideast @CivilWarMap @ejmalrai @Navsteva @EHSANI22 @comcen76… https://t.co/IDYWnlu70n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thus is the most lazy and disgusting human. Lived of his mom ti@he was 49 when he was elected now lives off tax pay… https://t.co/lqwPn1pNLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Interior Department has given offshore oil drillers nearly 1,700 exemptions to Obama-era safety rules put in pl… https://t.co/3CANBBE1ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Suite Life of Nuni &amp; Mack ✨ @ Harold's Chicken N IceBar https://t.co/4UjH2DKm8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️Not slowing me down today!🌨 #Focus2020 be on the look out!      ▪️SW Oklahoma       ▪️Panhandle TX      ▪️Wichita… https://t.co/Vq2Kv8NUwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post Malone is going to look like that sad alien from Star Trek that had to kill him self when he gets old. https://t.co/4uSUALH3Gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oddslotcom @Ferozkhanhamid @The_Mainlander @MoonzSmile @behindtheledger @XRPTrump 2/2 Since then we have seen more… https://t.co/4z3P33Uwgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSugarLily @1RealLori @Bmw2163Heart @tillmantweets @busylizzie48 @ukwildcatfan191 @HarrellRyan1 @SpaceForce1prh… https://t.co/mlX0JNUwHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have said Twin Peaks, but that third season was just an amazing surprise that gave me everything I wanted.… https://t.co/BMza28km6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IVPvideos Dude I’m there. Hope they shoot the canons at some point too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are we picking up?🍾🥂 . . . . . #disneyweddings #disney #tampa #orlando #Kissimmee  #florida #orlandoweddings… https://t.co/D8ue9xyjsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Porter shoots 10-12 from three-point range for a career best 30 points. The 10 triples is a school record. A… https://t.co/7gxVyZHuS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler Do you include the likes of Speaker Pelosi who has repeatedly said she doesn't see grounds for impeac… https://t.co/qX8RcAFwCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[MRN-finity  #tour #mirrorselfie @ House of Independents https://t.co/lSKkowEddV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchMossRadio Lon live now viggo here from hometown here in Watertown ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood @realDonaldTrump only hire the best people. #fakebillionaire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kakapolitico @MikaSpencer @emrazz While I know that’s a horrible thing that happens all too often, it says a lot t… https://t.co/RRGiWHJafH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karaoke at #BedrockTavern tonight! I can’t wait to bring @kaciannem here. I wish mom was here too, singing one for… https://t.co/tJv28ShhZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Switches to English. She starts off with a normal conversation and we talk about her family. She tells me she has t… https://t.co/YQSKZwg4ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most intense moments in TV history is when Hank figures out that Walt is Heisenberg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys There's Allways an Easier Way! Let Someonelse Do it! lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DENAirport @denbizjournal Hopefully includes bathroom stalls that don’t have a 1 inch gap between the door and the… https://t.co/JcjtZKgtZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson is a dingbat. Watch him get vivisection. By a legit professional. He then starts swearing like a sai… https://t.co/8PvXtSRLVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: Landon Spicer won the 3 point contest.  At one point hitting 7 straight. On his final three he went btl sid… https://t.co/eOeebOfYlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did it! I pulled off the Catalina Wine Mixer!!!!! https://t.co/oWbvmb8om6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear @NHLTVSupport is blacked out more than I get to watch. So stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenBullet3 @FUNimation @ToeiAnimation Except for Usopp. He’s tragic from end to end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the reality for teachers and kids in too many charters in America. I’ve seen it first hand too from the ver… https://t.co/ZIh6KcicRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanger4norris @TheEmoToaster Everyone has said faggot once in their life, it was a popular insult in middle school growing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Spurs are about to lose their 6th game out of their last 8. They'll be tied in the L column with LAC and SAC in… https://t.co/NzAJrabocT]]></document><document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: ALL girls no matter what height are great bc we literally have no control over it :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put a blend into this cup and it explodes. #singleorigin #coffee https://t.co/FlqBvcxodx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USANana1 @ANTIQUE4UNIQUE @CharlieDaniels Right, I forget that basically we’re dealing with a mafia like organizati… https://t.co/2tV95JV01x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children's Church on wheels! Cool stuff! #focus19 @ Knoxville, Tennessee https://t.co/PmgwR55KgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I don't go on many trips, and I fly even less frequently. That being said, I'm convinced that my next… https://t.co/5c46r4VKv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Tell Mexico that Democrats and liberals are crossing the border into Mexico. I bet Mexi… https://t.co/ff07ZBU5gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrayAJ @Sean_Hertel That’s St. Clair Avenue, and the streetcar loop is right underneath. But it’s a lousy street t… https://t.co/nfVmLUQTjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeG_0710 @TmobileMike @Travjustice12 @TravisRubenhold @ljeangib @CristinaJust1ce @MW_einstein @TrevorCarskadon… https://t.co/FmDJflRSFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLoulouC @50F10ULE @50F10ULE je te souhaite une ptite friteuse   ok j'ai triché]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenaisapeach @Babes @RealDera Not only tht, but the taste of the juices  is addictive like 🐝 to 🍯.]]></document><document><![CDATA[His only crime was loving the wrong chocolate ninja samurai frog. #dollartree #chocolate #frog #chocolatefrogs… https://t.co/OuikNIWZeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In search of awe and wonder:   I looked at Antarctica  on Google Earth and there is another small white dot in the… https://t.co/Q3JIOOVPOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZA_Campbell Exactly right, as much as I wanna chew on people for stupid comments, I’ve realized it’s not even worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexajanine123 @plurmaid22 This is the type of shit I’m here for 😭😭😭 I love this 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffBezos / Bozo = hypocrite, he puts out lies via @washingtonpost but cries 😭 when truth he doesn’t like comes ou… https://t.co/gNPThhajbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelleePeterson @Lena38Baker @MysticJosephine @bendercock @DanPeacock12 @SarahConnor2001 @MrSammyblish… https://t.co/fQrJO1yWtk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justin24hr attached dual screen case is pretty genius. Too bad not available in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Hurst at Podium offering Amendment requiring each County Commission and City Council to have recorded vote supp… https://t.co/LzjqMLoLVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavvBaby_ vs herself in #dreamselfbikiniboxingmatch👙🥊 #dingding🔔 #fight👊 #knockurselfout #youwin xoxo #wceveryyear💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@centsible @3rdViv @USMCLiberal @thewebbix @msuamie @VegasMel @abbeludwig @KristyLyn11 @ShelbyKStewart… https://t.co/pYfmB9B3KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManInTheHoody @AnitaNelson Tokyo  put up a strong bid but I'm going with Los Angeles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s crazy is I don’t care who touches you or anything but what really gets me going is someone else chilling with my dog and shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylansprouse @allwisemeadery #dylansprouse #allwisemeadery #ValentinesDay #Valentines #Valentines… https://t.co/7NfiBFryki]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current situation, trying to sweat this sickness out. #ballislife🏀 #ballislife #notfeelingwell #floridacity @ Fl… https://t.co/8iwJLvWIg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hbowman1H @Rubiconski @MsLynneMiller @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/uleDWC02G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little Saturday morning enjoyment for you: The best version of the best guitar solo ever. (Notice there were no… https://t.co/zru4cAJYP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have revived my love for heavy metal today and idk how to feel about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamMegl This is really a crazy recovery on the weekly. I mean it can definitely go higher, but I am willing to… https://t.co/tQLRUInYr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidgaliel @SPHFLA @HerringLiz @UNCtarheelsx6 @petersagal @gehrig38 No, the CDC shows that is not the case at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrapSandviche @adamclanton Typically not how you start a conversation with a lady, Crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever been friends or went to class or worked with a toxic ass mfer? Like to the point it’s a nightmare to work… https://t.co/tvDEXymPdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmallSandi @Jim_Jordan @mattgaetz It is amazing that those gop congressmen didn't even care to ask if they ur potu… https://t.co/SvIn0UXoPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen @Doodisgirl I agree but have to ask.....With such a platform.....why are the Republicans not cleanin… https://t.co/95Iy2hZpbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill It isn't taxing the rich, it is just taking what isn't proper. Let's see if the Dems include themselves i… https://t.co/62TKrwI0JI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agreenphotog @In_The_Slot There is nothing like walking up out from the tunnel and seeing the Green Monster. There… https://t.co/BbS8YdPdbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 Named “Year of the Nurse” Endorsed By W.H.O https://t.co/kE2tf5jNsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off the week, rocking this killer shirt from ugliegram. This Hill House design by meganmushi is so badass… https://t.co/a3vU2WqvHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecasiokid @joecs1220 @skyessong @thatJakeSenesac @jewleesi @AndyNemmity @Phoenixnjpw @Marlie520 @daTRUTHallstar5… https://t.co/1HljaZa1RM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@androidgenius Tourist talk about BBQ more in one week than the average Texas does in a year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SenateDems @realDonaldTrump Look what's playing! 👀 I think I'll choose Panic in DC first and then FISA… https://t.co/NaIBBTrbhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@countdown2march @ShaneGoldmacher And he didn’t even have the balls to stand up for himself when the DNC rigged a P… https://t.co/nS55vzdAa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny joke of these two idiots getting sent to a gay bar instead of a party, but were they really not gonna let the… https://t.co/HaId2fwsQu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willsommer @Z_Everson What is the point of your nonsense? Don't you have,something productive to do with your time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[what is crazy about the metro division this season is that 6 of the 8 times are still in the hunt in march for a pl… https://t.co/jl9VOYaFaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I am glad someone finally recalls the pics of Groping Joe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CORYorBUSTxNPC Yea me too. At one point Kron said he hoped for a fighter better than Caceras.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sethrogen @mattlieb This has to be the best shit I've ever seen and it's literally only the movie trailer lol...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett He's just a kid, chief, he will learn or he won't]]></document><document><![CDATA[my good german “straight” friend sent me a video via whatsapp saying/showing that he shaved his beard for me — too cute 🥰😍🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dat damn #SocialMedia don’t waste no damn time to get u. We all know Leonard ain’t no comedian 🤷🏾‍♂️😫🤦🏾‍♂️🤣KMSL....… https://t.co/1xticUavLx]]></document></documents></author>