<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GaymerChat But they *were* happy, their relationship was stable...and like any other couple in ST, they face adver… https://t.co/MdbVgDSZS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamon51 @Dynamic_Joe @Twitter See? Simple. I always double check my posts before sending. Spellcheck, all of that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakaylinEfird Well why you ain’t just say that 🤣😂 https://t.co/DMWaPL2Jdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Operation Lashes (countdown 4 weeks, 1 day) is going poorly. Can confirm it's not the type of lashes I buy, it's me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think Stone's explanation of the crosshairs symbol used on Judge Amy Berman Jackson's picture as "Celti… https://t.co/2RgjCCXi6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her smile lights up a room and we are so fortunate that she is on #TeamFACE! #ProudCoordinator]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to hug @YalitzaAparicio she deserves all the happiness right now. #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom loves @michaelb4jordan, yesterday she saw him on tv and says omg he is so handsome, and now she posted this… https://t.co/RVmMPakmyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ang intense nung 800 MB for an Ateneo vs UE pre-game. Kalerks. Hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[kristen has never watched an episode of survivor but she watched it with me so i wouldnt be lonely. i want to thank… https://t.co/nYWZWloLF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[1/2 Tonight I am extra thankful for my amazing husband.  He stayed up super late last night making sure the last of… https://t.co/X6H6I4CkzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC and Maxine belong in the same mental hospital, neither one is all there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrillManny__02 I’m taking this tweet when I turn to ashes   Me: (the tweet is in the suit case) *walking into heav… https://t.co/Vyu8Yd9FEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtyMoMedia @NBCSN @DaleJr @TonyStewart @MikeDavis88 @MatthewDillner @lmvaughn @NASCARonNBC Got my DVR set!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This episode of #sayyestothedress with the transgender bride has me crying my eyes out! It’s beautiful and her moth… https://t.co/aqAoyCBuG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The instruction dyslexic students need can benefit all students. Why shouldn’t all students get it? Especially in t… https://t.co/0L6ABmBLzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkartalias @TheRealCamilleG I agree. I love Camille. I’m team LVP on this one fershur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you been to Huiskamer Coffee House yet? If not... You're missing out. Coffee date anyone? ☕️ https://t.co/GUi3xPDQOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te preparas desde hace 3 años por si es uno o una 🙊 https://t.co/ICmURlcGam]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUNK SHOW  MARCH 5, 6-9 NOT TO BE MISSED! SPREAD THE WORD @ Gisele Tune Clothing Store https://t.co/Pu2n4vnlvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#زعيم_تويتر_بيدعم_الجميع  اليوم الاحد ..الصبح هون. الساعة ٩ و ٤٠  دقيقة ...نهار مبلش بالثلج   #صباح_الخير  .… https://t.co/JDh54kF1wR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling Holy Scan Remains on My Head/Mind-Await Ceremony w/Trump.You can Hear U.S. Govs Speak on Satellite as… https://t.co/5d0J1E5Zqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this made me think of @theedpodcast this morning: Kid Plays “Smells Like Teen Spirit” On Ukulele… https://t.co/YaSkGaArfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever get into character...and can’t get back out? #actorslife https://t.co/nP9U31FdhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelKeith @russellhantz @survivorcbs Ummmm I highly disagree with that statement. Examples: @BostonRob… https://t.co/3p83ubjeyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[what kind of psychopath wakes me up at 6 in the morning and asks if i want to link up. excuuuuuuse me]]></document><document><![CDATA[All love songs can be about chocolate if you believe, right @Hersheys? #HappyValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdFans @LivePdBlueLine @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation hey guys can we help out an officer from the early days o… https://t.co/T48Kzf0Ew8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently minimalists are going furniture-free   If owning a couch makes me wrong, I don’t want to be right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is possible to one who has faith. Mark 9:23 #wordstoliveby @ Syracuse, New York https://t.co/XTw5xtaAca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Channing_Frye Wow I want to be selfish and don’t want you to leave us but thank you for all you’ve done and wish y… https://t.co/0gaP5FXybE]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 has been the best year so far, and I’m traveling through Europe in the summer, then graduating in December so… https://t.co/UrzX3eypRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoArquette I miss having a President who cares about Constitutional law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahR77 How different it would be if she supported American values, American Allies,  POTUS!  It would be wonderfu… https://t.co/emjVjVLT5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some asshole decided to back into my car and left a fat dent without leaving a note, some humans just suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to think that all creatures in Magic the Gathering were in fact very real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Anyone supporting this Green New Deal, is an absolute idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahHughes37 @VerizonSupport Have you tried switching to @ATT they have never let me down❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever cry when you think about how much love you have in your heart for your sweet little ball of fur because… https://t.co/9HEC8atwuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @NancyLeeGrahn @WilliamdeVry1 chemistry off the charts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertLuke8 @kathygriffin 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂  Hello bot  I know because you have no idea what a good lawyer is or does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well tell NY this.  The next thing the will be doing is killing old folks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 64 : #huskiesrn 1 @voltigeurs_dru 2 08/03/19  #rouyn #drummondville #gohuskiesgo #lhjmq à Centre Marcel Dionne https://t.co/vWqi89pqlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are the truth that feeds us all- Jacques-Bénigne Bossuet #Catholic #pray #JESUSIsLord]]></document><document><![CDATA[When micron pens are on sale you get excited. Ecstatic enough to make a video! Lol 🖤🖊  #penandink #artist #micron… https://t.co/NiTTts6Yjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is crying for AMERICA!! My heart breaks for my Country right now, and the devastation one person is reigning on… https://t.co/iaG2VZ5HEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelle_furlow @Coutorocks10 @DRyan4006 Thank you!  I never have had a need for simultaneous translation when tea… https://t.co/dbB7nxBI2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motivation Monday- this girl pushes herself to be better @laureniosue 5:30am workout. Interview ready..and btw kill… https://t.co/wwEdEZi1aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deja tu, la biblio deberia tener 5 pisos y estar tan mamalona como la del tec, lo merecemos Y necesitamos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #snowday has started here at @B101Philly...roads still wet rn but it’s already sticking to cars and grass.… https://t.co/848I3xzvQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I schedule PT at 7am at Gillette Stadium ? Fuck is wrong with me 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the fuck shows up to work with their 6yr old and they both have the flu. Oh that’s right my office manager... I… https://t.co/dhvzlmItkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaa_KIERA @ShawnQuinn93 Are you guys together and tweeting each other? Asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[who have facebook the right to make all of my targeted ads about studies for clinical depression?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to our coach, but most importantly to our friend! You have brought so much learning and joy to the B… https://t.co/sfM5PuAzvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday, Feb. 19 Business associations request Calvey's release Five business associations appealed to the head of… https://t.co/cKE8UustDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LDCs4CLDs And there were a lot of compliments to go around among the three of you!! So proud of how everyone is em… https://t.co/UohhzJVauM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cc .@People4Bernie @TulsiGabbard Payless ShoeSource will begin liquidating its US stores on Sunday  https://t.co/MpRpyqo0lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evanchill And they have that right to make that political decision to revoke it in the interest of We The People a… https://t.co/DpYjA74PMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi @AOC @IlhanMN @JahanaHayesCT @RollingStone Not one of you support my values. You ARE NOT the face of women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost knocked on my neighbor’s door today so I could visit with his dog. They’ve been out of town and I really only missed one of them 🐶]]></document><document><![CDATA[So hard to believe it’s been two years since I had to say goodbye to my best friend, I miss you so much ❣️ https://t.co/ax6rarzOTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all know how nice it is to be able to just shoot my bestie a text when I need someone to talk to AFTER NOT BEING ABLE TO TALK FOR 10 WEEKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You be the match, I will be a fuse..💥💣 #kindfestival @ Desert Hot Springs, California https://t.co/tRmueEjTiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManteyDS @LifeResets @YoungDemsBCS @ORTXCentralTX @BCS_Indivisible @IndivisibleTX17 @MFOL_BCS_TX @AggieDems I am n… https://t.co/jYPFTmKjN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to Chilis Brownsville to pick up stuff and caught Victor Hernandez with my Dr.Seus stuff!!!!!#ChilisLove https://t.co/OFV1tPDtgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast at Daytona Supercross 👊👊 #DaytonaBikeWeek https://t.co/C6kwU8lH33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeanne_eliades So sorry to hear that your mom is dying. May she have comfort and peace in her last days. May you t… https://t.co/QPOfnOeXKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanRGallagher You and Shawn are literally like the voice of a generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/NqkXhmBKO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet, you refuse to support employers who insist on a legal workforce.  @SecretaryAcosta - do you stand behind the D… https://t.co/5eLXuLP0QL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter what day it is, I miss him the same everyday but just the old memories of the phone calls and the… https://t.co/b70IVqEZZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Most women don’t mind a man kissing them .   What’s the deal?  A kiss!   Really !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joel Osteen Frustrated As His Pulpit's 'Check Theology' Light Comes On Again https://t.co/ObAXtoG4V0 via @TheBabylonBee]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Help Teens Weather Their Emotional Storms https://t.co/SpzEFJeWUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Saturday. #mattnathanson #aarontap @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/yO5uW2OCMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cognitive processes- the map of the how our brain processes reading. #Read5373 #mindmaps #readingrocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if the same situation were against a black man in court or even Barack Obama - I don’t think you’d believe anyo… https://t.co/75ph6yeliy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Brandon/Brenden challenge was a real treat for me! @bigstuffparker @WBHUAlum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlonaDanger @Cheesecake haha I’m with the fam PATRICIAAAA WHERE U AATT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SophiaLamar1 They're silent. Waiting for the pastors and televangelists that support/enable him and other Black male abusers to do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing Iike getting a dm containing a dick pick from a guy that has Deadpool as his profile pic 😷🤢 you pervs gross me the fuck out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: 😞  😍💜😍💜😍💜😍💜 😍Jonas Brothers💜                                😍💜😍💜😍💜😍💜  Me: 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Teddy might be a better source than Limbaugh on this....@realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really let my time be wasted by the same dude...... twice https://t.co/sxF6gkdZxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natalie came home and said “we had springs pictures and I dressed like a pig”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNotOwned @jackjluke @maggieNYT Among many other things that it was important for the kids to hear - and she list… https://t.co/0NRC1x9k6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AboutLastNight Got to see my girl @Basheerah_Ahmad dancing on stage at the Ron Isley concert. The dancers were ama… https://t.co/UuHCZjTmvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀Wranglers fall in the Region 5 Championship @OdessaMBB 71 @SPCTexanMBB 73 https://t.co/WECCB8Q7YK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry .....they put him through hell even sent someone to my house to say what was going to happen to him if he wen… https://t.co/Xcqd24S4Qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else think it’s weird that the POTUS tweets quotes from an @FoxNews host and we all accept it and move… https://t.co/DSEkiyLnAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccblueyes70 @IndiaEaton I can get behind that!!!!!!!! her promo on Monday sucked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their moral values would have by and large been influenced by the Christian values that they were brought up with b… https://t.co/4FNnUywm7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 hours of sleep &amp; a 14 hour day ahead of me, letttttts geaux #mightdie #maybenot #needcaffineIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beyonce Enough with the niceties and packaged up link. Your kid ripped me off and were a tear away fro me having e… https://t.co/Gcj85LS5yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[just an fyi: if someone is asleep, maybe don’t try and make a move on them? ever?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is Antoni Porowski, Pete Davidson’s friend? https://t.co/HZD1lkYMoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I scheduled to work at 6am tomorrow with my store manager.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marshawright It makes me sad that he became an anti-vax fool. Jenny couldn't have been THAT hot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truth #facts #thisisme #random #randompost #saturday #saturdaymorning @ Anaheim, California https://t.co/772h1zVne1]]></document></documents></author>