<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[🎶 Your pussy basura. My pussy horchata 🎶 - CardiB  #CardiB #PleaseMe #PleaseMeStreamingParty #PLEASEMECARDIXBRUNO… https://t.co/435L6HWnWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you dude you and the rest of the band have helped me with a lot 🖤💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlieBrandt Way to smack the azz out of that ball Carlie!!  Go Gophers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabihalameddine Somehow haven't ever seen this painting... thx for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Some people are concerned about the effects of this technology on health.  We probably shouldn't r… https://t.co/HqUyXCNAKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irishprincess32 We never even had our 20. People voted for have it this Spring in a Park w kids instead of adults only in a bar 🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[me going for walks at 1am in new york alone while crying my eyes out is so funny the streets of new york are probab… https://t.co/BFNT0o2wCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually Germany seems to be a great place now. I hear their food quality is much better than the crap our food ind… https://t.co/aN9TwES82R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesuthozil10 Omg I’ve had problems with this guy too, he’s a bloody dickhead. What was the tweet? Looks like it’s been suspended!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say it louder for the bitches in the back. Ain’t nobody worried about u sis😂👋🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAVE time. #MARVELousWOMEN #WomensRetreat isaspear @ Rough Acres Ranch https://t.co/WpbVAo1yr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s a good nap when you wake up thinking it’s already morning time but it’s only 7 pm 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchell_greg35 IFHY FOR QUOTING THIS TWEET AND BRINGING IT TO MY TL 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irregulargawd I’m really happy for you though. ❤️😂 Let me know if you need anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was ready to be drinking from a coconut and shaking my ass on a Caribbean island but instead almost missed it: a thread]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been up for almost 2 hours now. Thankfully I have a four day weekend ahead of me. 😊it’s almost puppy time!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I’m so glad I can seriously go to work in whatever I want and no makeup and not have to worry about people se… https://t.co/AFUZa4ftNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer We the People call on you, Schumer, @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems to start protecting U.S.… https://t.co/HLH8vg1pUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christineschu48 @mae4499 @JimmieJohnson @JeffGordonWeb @AllWaltrip I Agree!  🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, while we're on the topic of expanding the Cabinet, where's our Secretary of Culture?   (Pssst... I nominate Quincy Jones.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelshel7781 @JasonOttom @23Mkc @jlgreen212 @crutcherlisa45 @IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump I feel completely vindi… https://t.co/a65cqt12o7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter❣️ #happiness #home #snow #winter #winterwonderland #wonderland #sopretty #beauty #beautiful #snowday… https://t.co/9UEjTd6MkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Oprah similar to your @SuperSoulSunday with Tolle (which I’m obsessed with) I’d like to suggest the same format b… https://t.co/tkw5BdpTmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 27th anniversary to my husband, my love, my best friend. I have loved you for 28 years and  will love you mor… https://t.co/4odt6hJUP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @kae_stoddard Yes they are ok with the gun policies that killed your daughter. It wasn’t their dau… https://t.co/wMM4oZG9Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@formoftherapy Was it at least cheaper? cuz 6am sucks no matter what.  *sitting in my job at 5:30am*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_PJAnadio Rollin’ In Hoodies And Sweats All Weekend. My Kindof Weather 🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT - Standing on guard for thee. #ridley #armycadets @ Ridley College Alumni https://t.co/u56VsRp8ZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Sick Shit Right here! I call on Congress to Stop the B.S. You Represent! PERIOD! https://t.co/zhazlHOB1n @JudicialWatch @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/aE7VfGa4ZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side streets appear to be pretty bad. We’re going to cancel class this morning.  Stay safe! @ Kansas City, Missouri https://t.co/ci6PlwP6bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Apologizes for Engagement ‘Issue’ Spotted by Conservatives https://t.co/sneolUQNDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Y_Vs_A Who were the adults with you from the Sunrise Movement? Why were they with you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Ed Sheeran Memes - Best Ed Sheeran Photos - Seventeen https://t.co/eIssWofu7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm officially not allowed to buy the friend group movie tickets anymore.  Because I accidentally got the 4D tickets for #CaptainMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teresa’s hating not being the center of attention this reunion AND I LOVE IT  #RHONJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[An excellent scripture to keep deep in our heart and confess daily during trials..  But Thanks Be to God, Which Giv… https://t.co/8PddbwvWxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be a woman-of-a-certain-age (yesterday's video), but that tarp held through the rest of the wind and is sti… https://t.co/5hUQYKvDpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I hate doing night shift but I absolutely love going home to a glass of wine and sleep at 7am when the re… https://t.co/6e2GhH8guz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTrumplican @anna_sorget @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump But not broke. Not rich but not broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Senate Judiciary and Oversight need to pull her ass in and question her Soros backed ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class B: Waverly has extended its lead to 13-3 over Northwest with 3:12 left in the first. #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Qué emoción! De nuestro aula observamos a Tower Girl varias veces cada semana. / How exciting! We observe Tower Gi… https://t.co/2vP4aRbLTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bolo de cenoura, compartilha. Carrot cake, curte. 😂 https://t.co/pVfhpeyUu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever get so into the habit of bad eating that the thought of consuming something healthy is utterly repulsive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok @KitKat_US ...I reached out to you about using a very sexually explicit song to market your bar, and you didn't… https://t.co/2svhIcDAks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to OITNB for being the first series EVER that i truly binge watched😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is this the type of thriving you want for Americans underyoure over ruling?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the last @nasponline convention I was able to attend. I am SO excited to be leaving for this year's conven… https://t.co/Mo6OzbZ4Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackshawMD @DavidJMathison @DespiteTheTimes @UVA_PICU @cjsmith3md Congrats!! It’s a great feeling, isn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnRosembert @ActionNewsJax First starters, it’s Colombia not Columbia. It’s clear you have no clue what you’re s… https://t.co/3VenBEiv6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN NOW! Come say hi and grab a girl scout cookie at 5716 Mammoth Ave in a desirable part of Valley Glen. I'll be… https://t.co/wOAlbAUhA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman year I couldn’t eat a whole Pad See Ew from Madam Mam’s in one sitting, and now I can definitely eat two.… https://t.co/uWQwFCVlgY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't have a child unless you consider my dog as one 🤣 @IMDb https://t.co/dj4PJN9rnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve paid for festivals for me and another person. Paid rent for another person and I. Paid to go to another state… https://t.co/ri18Vj1zLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cohen's testimony was excellent he did a wonderful job. He seems very well educated unlike Donald… https://t.co/TF7pboVxT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when your presale ticket purchase went smoothly @TheStruts #ticketangels https://t.co/ATXL80Hl84]]></document><document><![CDATA[He WAITS 4U!   Calling you home!  Ride with HIM on the wings of the WIND! https://t.co/oTKrI1zijQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav! 🤪🥳 @ Rose &amp; Crown Pub &amp; Dining Room https://t.co/xj6vU5EEGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Why not #JamieFoxx hang out with #MeghanMarkle? 😉. They deserve each other. https://t.co/bvMyEa4wmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #BedtimeCrew is waiting for me to come to bed. 😂😂 #LuckyDanyAndDusty #2JulyLabs #LuckyLucRobitailleSwartz… https://t.co/Z5bqRUYfif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is World Thinking Day let's make sure everyday is Thinking Day for our students by allowing them to explore,… https://t.co/3VCaSx6s60]]></document><document><![CDATA[We talk to students about where they are going and look at what their college/university expectations are. As an SA… https://t.co/c8eqZmlD36]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a blast on the Climbing Above Conflict field trip!! #hpsdtigers https://t.co/VFYUhssHM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FallonTix Please help me I desperately need two tickets for March 12 please please please please thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your story came out cause you sent me out there. Can’t wait to testify to the senate with the real story]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome @AUG_Nursing Dev Day w/ @AUG_CollegeofEd researcher, ESPN announcer, &amp; ⁦@GamecockSoftbll⁩ legend, ⁦… https://t.co/ZfDltpD87f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elise and I had to give up our tickets because of softball, but these 2 look like they are having fun! @ Columbus B… https://t.co/67jtxHAFs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brinaa22 Girl, you’re an old soul😉. But for real, I’ve always worn them to bed and then schlep em off in the middl… https://t.co/dCgW9dDLqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best team name for an #Oscar trivia tournament? These folks seem to think so. 😁 . . #oscars #oscartrivia… https://t.co/Nrxe210DR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everyone gets the same version of me. One person might tell you I’m an amazing beautiful soul. Another will tel… https://t.co/xy8Mc0BAts]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a beautiful wedding! So happy to celebrate with you Kate and Andy! 👰🏼🤵🏼💗🥂 #metztobe @ Bakers Ranch https://t.co/kTfLsaQXRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much overdue! 💆 (@ New Day Bodyworks, LLC - @ndbw_massage in Rockaway, NJ) https://t.co/rcif8jP3yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never watched this because of how scary it looked and the kids who did watch this have issues now 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zadidoll I'm confused about the shingles vaccine,  I'm 50, had chickenpox as a child and have had 1 shingles outbreak about 12 years ago...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited for all the trips I’ll be making this year, 2019 is full of good vibes &amp; traveling w. the people I love 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Federal judge issues a new order against Trump administration's 'zero tolerance' immigration policy… https://t.co/Yy2khHPztF]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the lesbian couple that just walked past me in target (in HILLAND MICHIGAN): I wasn’t staring to be rude, I was… https://t.co/q1x40rAgQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa, I just dreamt about someone from like middle school??? I was like wait who is this person I know their name but who are they?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gop go away. every attack you make is also against DT for hiring #Cohen, also ask fucking questions, not just blam… https://t.co/RFZLHwbAjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanigarcia33 @sanmaski1 @Qualityman156 @darkvi9 De acuerdo! Desayunás tranquila y salis a caminar, que es la mejor forma de conocer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylerVaughnn @MovieManny I met her at O’hare abd she begged me not take a picture with her since she was getting over swine flu haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all.....   This finale did NOT have to go as hard as it did. It was incredible!!! It was so satisfying thematical… https://t.co/eKAmUZTS94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@searchlibrarian I need to meet this kid - I think she needs to come to conference 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕#WonderfulWeek @GStarkeyBooks @Micheal_Rivers @AMBazzi @GlenGreenPro @snaphappyshan @ceebee308 @Dearharts @Melissa_Foster @SueColetta1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmatwood @DrJenGunter Same here, I get out of alignment really easily and end up in spasm. My chiro is gentle and… https://t.co/sNxgbE4B17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTonyKemper @HerdWBB See you on that plane! Time to turn Frisco into Herd country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes No it's SAVING the lives of wild life and keeping CA clean DUMB ASS.  How PATHETIC is a grown man can't… https://t.co/yhoUtmL7fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who say some sports movie is the most inspirational film they have seen, has clearly never watched Legally Blond]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so happy I found an outlet for my emotions in music and writing Im so grateful I can put my thoughts on paper an… https://t.co/QXBmdzZv4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay wow not only is she beautiful but i’m getting so many @NikitaDragun vibes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adding a time limit to social media has been the best thing I’ve done 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my bae at the Valentine’s Day Lounge #MountVDay #OATM https://t.co/rXDSw8wipK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why? #DirtyDersh trying to keep it quiet.  Alan Dershowitz suggests curbing press access to hearing on Jeffrey Epst… https://t.co/KVsTQKMeCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian But why are you sueing @Missguided when it should be @FashionNova ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por lo menos espere a que seamos libres para dar opiniones que ahora no vienen al caso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I leave to class or Dalt leaves for practice, Kirk immediately jumps in our spot to cuddle the other person 😭 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KingBooks_ I started a shot glass travel collection when I went to Europe 2 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud Alum and Mom of one, soon to be two‼️ #proudtobearocket #rocketnation #husbandisalumtoo #rocketfamily]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harry Potter star Tom Felton takes the coolest picture of Emma Watson https://t.co/KwfWPTspqR via @MetroUK]]></document></documents></author>