<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@edgarwright Did she look at the painting and confirm that you were correct?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how you tweeted this 24 minutes ago and nobody retweeted you yet like this ain’t the truth or something 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiderBaseball LET’S GO!!!  for the love of all that is sacred let’s play some Baseball!!!  #rollspides #espnplusstreaming]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuquesneLight gonna replace what spoiled in my fridge? I was real excited for the burgers from Omaha steak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejanecek @bumpypitch @JimmyConrad missed partnership opportunity: Helles Verona Lager 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erhsathletics @EastRowanHS @mikelondonpost3 @CarolinaVarsity @allenjd4life @pepmancv @NCPiedmontSport @nc_hsfb… https://t.co/fGbgoIbA1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapitolComments @CNN It’ll be the exact opposite of what you say. They’ll go down in history as conspirators is wh… https://t.co/IixpjTjjRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingSimmonsPC More taxes on working people to fill holes in roads caused by Republican inattention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nomnomnom #yuengling @ Hallandale Beach, Florida https://t.co/DmGcnlADh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lips are my specialty. #lips #poutylips @DrJayHRoss https://t.co/EwZnKqSswz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blondenorsky Valjean doesn't finish parole, which is why Javert now hunts him. In a new identity, he's mayor of sm… https://t.co/SbBy4VIaoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I look at my social media. I honestly don’t know how a single person could not love me. Which makes me so conf… https://t.co/2JmvXpUDB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mech2112 @chesterbells1 @BeverlyWarrren @RushFamTourneys @titletownusa73 @donaldabaker66 @MiSugrue @vivien2112… https://t.co/rQ7jP4KV1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolemartintv @CHCHNews Haha... well done Nicole! Next hill to tackle: lowville!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerrysaltz Hedge funds went into schemes instead of deals for car building labor. I'll look into it. How many peop… https://t.co/PKKLD5b2R5]]></document><document><![CDATA[John 5:30 and Galatians 1:10 has me meditating on who am I trying to please: God or people...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never understood SF where space-faring beings carried swords. #MeTVBuckRogers]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family watches an awful lot of cooking shows for a family that never cooks anything...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BanditLites Those look ridiculous. Do they at least do something cool?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerdydirtyplay Just honest 😁 you’re beautiful, adorable and just seem so cool all at once 👍 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos, los espero a todos en @campodefuego después #ElClasico, mi compañero Felipe Monforte estará desde el estadi… https://t.co/PXhkA6lMcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stelmo Saturday Night @BurgerStudy Today  The carnivore in me is more than satisfied  #LifeIsGood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddieonfox @benmaller _Five Bucks isn’t much for Ben as a kid, Edge! He was most likely two hundred and sixty poun… https://t.co/cwvVDWZICd]]></document><document><![CDATA[he HAS to lie about wall construction to keep his idiot supporters happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nieceandnehpews (@ Hyatt Regency Cambridge - @hyattcambma in Cambridge, MA) https://t.co/Orpcv6KeW7 https://t.co/sMBuLt9HtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimMarieCoxCoo1 No question it will be blockchain; truth based. Only thing people will accept. Decentralized a req… https://t.co/yxz3FAZIpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamnacho1 Just conversation brotha and being that father figure.  Reminding him who said this and who said that......and to be a MF Killa💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @Indie_Originals thing be blowing up! https://t.co/Pq8Rv1USvf https://t.co/DA7Ggp36vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol this is the background of the “historian” guy from the Carlson incident... “more thought leader than historian”… https://t.co/VI7FRK1BX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pirates of the Caribbean #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #werehome #magickingdom @ Pirates of the Caribbean https://t.co/agalvkqVOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ThomasBvl @CozyBoyMeech It’s true though 🤷🏻‍♂️not saying he sucks or anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcortes64 @durb1220 @AlanSteinJr I’m talking high school and college basketball for the most I put youth sports in… https://t.co/jC9FbqijGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanitaSurman @pitbuII_real @sunrisemvmt @SenFeinstein Under the Green New Deal, the Poles will not be allowed to… https://t.co/mYV9Ollt8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this year I promised myself to keep experimenting with new styles, never settling, and expanding my art. Here’s… https://t.co/pZXG0mtk49]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom : idk why you waste your money on this shit cause by the smell of it you can’t be getting high 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarvelStudios @Marvel @brielarson @SamuelLJackson @clarkgregg @LashanaLynch Which #GlengarryGlenRoss role would yo… https://t.co/YrWStDiVMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexxxiLondonXXX Bartering system can never go wrong.  Doing music videos yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessBravato tRUMPS personal knob polisher. https://t.co/sjFpiAr5Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#squineros43🍓🍓🍓🍓🍓🍓 #pollito43🍍🍍🍍🍍🍍 #lospollitosdisenpiopoi🙄🙄🙄 #megustatuchocolate🍫🍫🍫 #teamoyeresmivida21🍉🍉🍉… https://t.co/EBIR6dt1Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Suggesting Cohen Lie Is a Crime, According to Kavanaugh https://t.co/xjcMq3ScQ5 via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mars asked me to choose music that wasn’t hard and it was the hardest thing I’ve had to do all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ap English was hard AF, English 101 I barley showed up and got an A. Hes right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this. If it’s anything close to Senna, it’s gonna be amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After he was appointed, Robert Mueller sent word to U.S. attorneys’ offices across the country that he needed help.… https://t.co/GakrmCdcxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @realDonaldTrump LOL - nothing has been "debunked" and the collusion is staring at us in plain sight.  Wh… https://t.co/FBuVwjDYPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @realDailyWire This woman is a traitor to the US. If State Dept allows her entry to US, she should b… https://t.co/z8R1WAq0ST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine my frustration developing a narrative arc regarding gun culture that doesnt intrinsically connect it to cri… https://t.co/fCFMMjOc88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mica4Life @cbschicago Phone records and the brothers' own testimony are all the evidence the state needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @KarenDoe50 It's the parents job to raise the kids, not the government's.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgraceful.   Nazis hunted and killed people. Wow  @RepMGS needs to apologize immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zzzulukato Los españoles y canadienses turistean mucho en #cuba con minúscula!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The historic Hotel Settles in Big Spring. I definitely recommend getting a room here. Hotel featured in 1969 films… https://t.co/ds6Db7mPhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spike11117 @Richard4m @RealOmarNavarro @realDonaldTrump @sabine_durden @agnes_gibboney 😫😫😫😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is madness. There’s good research on the genetics of pointing dogs and you could spend all day reading it, or… https://t.co/4IsdkG0Tgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Clementi crossed 10. Time 01:40:28, pace 09:59 min/mile, est. finish 10:53 am https://t.co/LhFe6nporh #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPSbiedermann @mccreah10 @SSpickard @MichaelFullan1 @MichelleAllenMI @AllysonApsey @Syndee_Sue @PWPrincipal… https://t.co/ePV2zildsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like @jamescharles is watching me do my makeup today and sisters crying or laughing.I’m not sure which.  #SisterS #makeup #mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay fun with the hubby. #love #loveislove #gay #married #marriedtoamogul #bruanenterpises #season1 @ Mad… https://t.co/XLD97ptWSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The irony of taking a dab right before settling in to transcribe a 45 min anti-marijuana group discussion 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadpool kinda night, with a Wolverine kinda morning after. #happyvalentinesday #aviationgin #laughingmancoffee @ F… https://t.co/eQrFNQgGmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. It is real. It's also incredibly treatable by a number of methods starting with talking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @angryorchard blocking Disabled Parking spots is not cool! Not to mention illegal! @bvuepd This was at Kelsey C… https://t.co/rP0nIKxNtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlorgRunner @billmeltzer @nufced An annual tradition for last 43+ years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son's class and my nephew's class cupcakes are all homemade and you made and ready to go for tomorrow strawberry… https://t.co/qQ3kLSPibW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting to think my nephew has been going into my room and stealing my shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...socialism advances under the banner of progress but in the end, it delivers only [MORE] corruption, exploitatio… https://t.co/gNuRQ5NoQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crimsonfate88 @alistairpge @POTUS You people all need hobbies. I suggest Kosher Origami.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PurposeForPain @ScottStapp I can not tell you how freaking pumped I am brother! 👊🏻🎤🎸🎼😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was hella funny while I was in line to get in the venue to see Travis at Toyota there was a group of 4 be… https://t.co/btV5UkmCar]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the research and the seat counts, here is the list of the  new top 10 largest Indiana high school gyms: 1.… https://t.co/Lke1r356fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@will_fitzhugh A reasonable expectation of your ability to detect bugs if your only process is manual UAT is "oh, y… https://t.co/UiuYRPXDdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son un verdadero desastre los intelectuales del antiguo régimen. Lo más curioso es que de verdad creen que lo que d… https://t.co/1GabigeNu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asRico1 I’ll be more than happy to take you there whenever you’re in the Phoenix area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels Be the best You can be and forget the rest honey. You go girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom said don’t wait too long to have kids but she had me when gas was $1.10 per gallons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper In the #80’s I could afford #brunomagli #shoes I liked shopping for #menshoes then. Now that I’m #💯 y… https://t.co/JLT1Dnft0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ho hum, getting up, yes I can do  This  ,well it's 4 with 8 below wind chill,  back to my nest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great new lunch spot in Elbridge. And it's on the National Register of Historic Places. (@ Bailiwick Mark… https://t.co/3OsceyBFpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the info @FitYourStyle is sharing with us this morning! 🤩 #EtalkRedCarpet #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recorded myself doing deadlifts today at the gym to check up on my form...and it definitely needs to be refined..… https://t.co/zqJRzmF2JO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash AOC is the Republicans best weapon against the democrats. You go girl!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟 #DrNo Sean Connery 🌟 #FromRussiaWithLove Sean Connery 🌟 #Goldfinger Sean Connery 🌟 #Thunderball Sean Connery 🌟… https://t.co/1ZM9zsXp6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CjHollidayWWG @charliekirk11 Well, since for the most part they were routed in less than 2 years, given they rose… https://t.co/quKBYLQcq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonharper70bd @thezenteacher @DavidGeurin @SteeleThoughts @D4Griffin3 @KJDellAntonia @DrMaryHoward @drjoy77… https://t.co/wQeM6t9xzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stenhouse causes a wreck at Daytona THAT NEVER HAPPENS says no one ever #Daytona500 #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, I was trying to be subtle, but the Bulls had to go there, like something in a china shop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the morn', #SoundDowners! What are you doing for St Patrick's Day next Saturday 3/16? We think you should co… https://t.co/9C9yyjpoV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FletcherJohnson Haha, it’s apparently in Lafayette, Louisiana. The country’s only Popeyes buffet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul @realDonaldTrump The ruling political class hates Trump and us.. It seems as though we have no choice but to back Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- why the 2 together? C- technology has got us to here good or bad.  I see all of the pieces now it seems.  How do… https://t.co/U6ka6NUDDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahCharmander @RE_Games Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/fMj8VUOyFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moment: “It only takes a moment,” Has been the theme that keeps following me around. A moment can change everything… https://t.co/6QzQT3IqNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Could it have been what POTUS told him to do when they had the infamous meeting? I'm just sayin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been to yoga in ages (@ Sterling YMCA in Beverly, MA) https://t.co/iGQEThOK8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA2K_MyTEAM @KingJames Yeah “we all win if lebron scores 13” my ass...ruby demar derozan that I will literally never use]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patg85 I don't believe they can relocate.  Team signed a long-term contract with the City.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen captain marvel twice and I have minor issues with it but it’s good and you should watch it bc it’s worth… https://t.co/aLOo6leQfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[All else equal, what job experience would you prefer in a presidential candidate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlwayzInTrouble This made me check the extended forecast.  It looks like winter the next 10 days in Detroit.  Please avoid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lgbtqfc I mean...... can’t I be free to watch what I want to watch? Has nothing to do with Male/Female. I watch gi… https://t.co/V9g9mYv6iL]]></document></documents></author>