<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ElizLanders @SpeakerPelosi @VP You hypocritical lefty loons really crack me up. Karma children.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dial6Dial @Matthew669691 @GaryEll85341441 @patrizesyra1 @Aaron_C5 @mjmgop @LBengtzen @ron_ron31822845… https://t.co/H3NXek1wP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back40feet although still explosion! It should be a crime to cause panic like that. Maybe it is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except I did go to community college and I have the exact same major and I’m still going to be 108K in debt at a pu… https://t.co/6O25vprWOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/GPRxRZs3gr this is how you treat our Angel Moms you low life… https://t.co/kiS76U3HCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[i spent like almost $150 on skincare today who am i https://t.co/zha3CaStla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltd_To_Two @ka_birane @LaShandaWest @CameronFarmer8 Yes while all along keeping in mind the fact: TIME WAITS FOR NO ONE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandalambert I guess that’s what happens when you toss a 🥗!! Couldn’t help it!!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy bday bestie @TheWaltonn I love you and miss u even when you’re showering  hope u got the most drunk today and… https://t.co/1cTF3sijh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Front-row seat for learning - connecting with The changing consumer @NatProdExpo https://t.co/vfhbVC7gPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a shoot for new headshots tomorrow. And I’m dying. Cold/sinus infection BE GONE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, fun show! Thanks for showing me the ropes, @KBTXMax 😊 I'll be back later for News 3 at Noon on @KBTXNews (poss… https://t.co/kTNNglboFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Supply Chain Supervisor- Electrical Team"? What did you like most about that job? #SupplyChain #Melbourne, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I'm up for the day I decided its time to reach my next life milestone and bought myself a Kirby vacuum. I am adult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed breakfast with a special #BangBear this morning! Green eggs and ham was on the menu in honor of Dr. Seuss’s… https://t.co/R05iAEfJsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[im still mad i never got to see the jonas brothers live. my mom never wanted to take me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried the abracadabra nitro sour from Blood Brothers today. So creamy and delicious. @ Blood Brothers Brewing https://t.co/jV1WVKO6Up]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love hanging out with people who always hype me up. It's much appreciated 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[She writes..."The show stopper here is the controversial sculpture by Gian Lorenzo Bernini titled Beata Ludovica in Ecstasy."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo fun at Rocking Taco Rumble- thanks downtownphoenix 🥂 🌮 @ Unexpected https://t.co/kfrO5x7M7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emshadyforlife @Eminem_Pro When u back in the USA. I’m truly in a critical state of an Eminem dose. Enjoy down und… https://t.co/H7C3hmozTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy( around 8) at the theater sees my MM phone case  Boy: wow that’s a cool case  Me: Thanks 😀  Boy:  And you have… https://t.co/vBS0DINlrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ughhh cant wait to move and redownload tinder so I can meet newer hotter better guys that don’t suck🙄🙄 #sorrytally]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all deserve people who will at least try to reciprocate the same energy we give them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd have forgotten my everything ... To be that close , I wouldn't be able to function.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesssss I need this causeeee I hateee havinggg tooo let my phone ring 🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[American technological advances decline as # of #INDIA visas increase.  Outer space advances with #INDIA tech leade… https://t.co/QUreGBdWWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KissMy_Fashion She's ashamed and in hiding .... she can't hide forever ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain With women  and fans crawl  around  u case people  are noticing  that's what ur searching  for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inna @kellieraymond_3 I make one each month and share it with our staff. I changed the settings, so you should be… https://t.co/bDnXcacwlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuppinthemcakes @kadeejra @drea_sarai Me getting rid of it again in my dream https://t.co/aZ4TOQ2k3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same people exploiting Malia Obama’s private life are the same people who are ignoring actual national emergenc… https://t.co/kQC9DpbjzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm choosing Sobble to join me on my adventure through the Galar region in #PokemonSwordShield!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUBMIT SUBMERGE SURRENDER 4 those that were on the fence! The most powerful prayer you can say right now is.... Lor… https://t.co/Gbi0tDITth]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the airport over the intercom someone just said “If you lost your wedding ring at the security check point on Va… https://t.co/5uDZm2CWxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidjohnsonpdx @MeghanMcCain What was the question? 😂 You know she cries when she gets cornered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirtyblxnde Girl same. I want to know what it’s like to have a top lip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary #wow https://t.co/hykL7sLzt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLukeNYC Good morning from Hanford Calif! We're at 54 degrees and expect to reach 68 today. A beautiful Cali day! 🏌️‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleAbel7 @1madwoman1962 @MelindaYoe @TpsNelson @CathyBawden844 @wang_xiaolu @LordJesus111 @craig_novy… https://t.co/0EFIqDbYGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[She Walked the Talk: Farewell to Water Warrior Grandmother Josephine Mandamin https://t.co/kdfBQtqMkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book a Hair Appointment  Mess it up on Feb 14th It’s okay we got you cover!😘❤️ Coupon must be purchased online. Hur… https://t.co/w4rylk4HqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ttinnnaaa Thank you so much Tina 😭💕 I love and miss you so much too!! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[if your boyfriend constantly likes other girls pictures break up with him!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiannabradley @InsurgentDesire @AdamWagner1 Antisemitism is vile. And so is defending this antisemitic mural.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA https://t.co/obdq61CCsp https://t.co/PVz6ztHv5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay me! I’m a year older! 🎂🍹🍹Now what’s for dinner... I’m thinking chicken Alfredo 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been working on a new project and having conversations about the way people feel about cooking. How do you… https://t.co/bdaFNOv5We]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaSimpson24 @mbtmom2000 @mascott04 @CrimsonKristy @CrushingOnSaban You should get it again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We don’t have enough housing, period, for people relocated because of the Camp fire,” said a city councilwoman.… https://t.co/tRVSEpKzes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers @nickjonas @joejonas @kevinjonas I did it I did a cover of sucker haha ❤️👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼🌹🌹🌹🌹 https://t.co/Q9FvQ57nGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Morrison has excellent tips and techniques which will help you to become famous and rich at the same time.… https://t.co/ZCRXg3pCwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[i got $500 for anyone from NY with a working cash app, uber/lyft and venmo account. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annaanbg Beautiful Anna An. Have a wonderful Sunday. May you have peace and happiness 🤗💐🌹🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_iraprice u mad bro? https://t.co/LL6KoMBU7Z You would have been great on this debate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrexitStand @tlsg99 I’m an American, so I can’t vote. I hope there will be someone who will restore your country,… https://t.co/nD5QZGdehD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want to feel the Bern again. I was Berned a couple of years ago and I'm still recovering. #bernieNO #goaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy fourteen months 🤒💙 it’s been a trip with you, but i wouldn’t do it with anyone else. i love you most than mos… https://t.co/Z6K4fGjnMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt MERCY saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea Now MERCY is fostered in Florida➡️… https://t.co/tp4DXvzz85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigEzzle I’m going to a matinee alone today bc I’m off work. I can’t freaking wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring break is in a month, which means I will be on a plane to LA in a month 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commendable Senator ... but where were you when Obama did it several times after you were elected to the Senate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The next fucking client I have that shoves their religion down my throat may make me lose my job 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[What home project are you working on? #jessicafinchrealtor #CABRE01813490 #sundiegorealtygroup #realestateagency… https://t.co/6eUU9U5J8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Scott at Howard and Beale @Starbucks for going the extra mile today. He crushes mobile orders.… https://t.co/woMy7nONaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[he really did just say what we were all thinking..   dima is braver than any US Marine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wide brushes cover actual facts. Sources please. Anonymous claims are blather.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcast My internet service failed again. Now I have to decide whether to spend the next two hours on the phone wi… https://t.co/83spNG0GWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewNadeau0 Yay! Congrats Andrew! Could not happen to a funnier and more worthy person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time i believe things in my life are going good, some shit always happens]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is something in New York air that makes sleep useless ⚡#NYC @ Union Square, Manhattan https://t.co/N0YaLl2oGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[In three days I’m gonna be in Texas and let me tell ya I’m ready to leave this town for a week. I need a break but… https://t.co/2fvwHa8moC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’ve been saying that you would believe the US was leaving Syria when it actually happened...  “Two months a… https://t.co/bi8ERxlClo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hopefully people will view it the same way most do NOW...ABSOLUTELY INSANE. Freaks will always be freaks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one more old lady stops me on the street to tell me my kid’s hands are cold (under a weather cover, in the strol… https://t.co/du5EQMLSqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nickelback US Congress gets into a debate about ‘Nickelback’, and congressman shows Nickelback as number 1 on his playlist- ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to it just to do it on #BlountTuesdays 🔥  We get #StraightToDaPoint kickin some of the hottest #Dancehall… https://t.co/KNda17CLRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephrose272 I've checked ebay several times and it's always been at least $200 😭 the only time I looked on abe it… https://t.co/QuL3ELpUTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperWinterGirl @SnyderSpartan @PelleCreepy @WeirdNPissdOff We need more Ellen ripleys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAES PE Kids Heart Challenge!  Cardio Fitness- Speed Jumping Service Learning in Action #heartheroes #givingback… https://t.co/FyKGblTSTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have my hands on everything even stuff people might never know about 😊💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE YOU DAD🙏 SO BROKEN RIGHT NOW❤ I LOVE YOU NO MATTER WHAT IT IS. HE  CAN WORK ALL OF IT OUT. LAY DOWN YOUR BURDE… https://t.co/gDSj2pFKPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferweiner So the acknowledgments will be a nicer version of this? https://t.co/lkREW7dYZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_hallsworth Of course! It’s obviously centered on Canadian policy but I’m sure there are parallels!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yogaDGAF @selina3sticks @Rutho_ @ladyheatherlee Yeah, I’m here for this. https://t.co/sns37lU1pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the difference between modeling lingerie and stripping for a living? 🤔🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PepperoniRollz @politico Well good for you. What about the illegal alien who shot a man’s Daughter right in front… https://t.co/NN3xWrVDdv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakeupsIay @makeupjadebunny Following and thank you for this opportunity!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah well, they thought the 2017 women's marches we're big...just wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudeee. It’s real dusty in here. I couldn’t do it without @nhsportspage and @Justin_McIsaac who have called these g… https://t.co/gu98WjlQYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must do better at the community level—w/in communities, neighborhoods, schools to support #veterans… https://t.co/UttiKUTDCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkamarketinginc @brushmechanic_ @ItsMeCathi Oh my.  Raised by an abusive narcissist, I spent much of my life expla… https://t.co/uYUhf2pd0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Abilene Cowgirls are undefeated league champs and the #1 seed in the 4A west region. How ‘bout them apples?… https://t.co/000XWBMJ8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump noun: #Communism The word who's definition U keep using instead of #Socialism  a political th… https://t.co/PNiLLvuXCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in a restaurant with the 6 year old I babysit and playing I Spy he tells me he spies something gray- fast f… https://t.co/pDDHs85Ptc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t even explain how badly seasonal depression has been hitting my this year. Fuck, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillySportsSrc @JoeHeim @Phillies Boo!  #teamJoeHeim.  He’s absolutely right on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnchaffetz give it a rest, nobody wants to hear what you have to say! https://t.co/di8kRy7Kgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrASMcManus @CastletonWhky Thank you! Game starts at 3, and, yes I believe you can purchase tickets at the stadium… https://t.co/zc23m4d4AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[trying to concentrate on this workout while listening to the new @callherdaddy podcast 😂]]></document></documents></author>