<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My My my, Kamala I live in your district and I would not vote for you as county dog catcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the worst Oscar fashions since the 70s and most of these looks will not age well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradfo I almost don't care who plays out free agency as long as this man is our manager. Seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jump around! @ Aerosports Trampoline Park Oakville https://t.co/AeAGsiTPAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song and a fat blunt while looking at the stars👌🏼 https://t.co/KHRrnt2HDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jean D. Woods-Powell is the outstanding Principal of Info Tech High School in #LIC. Jean has dedicated her life to… https://t.co/mNjGTVjlIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: anti-vaccinators should lose the privilege of having a child if the child contracts one of these… https://t.co/9ylkasjyVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgerkramer @LGrundmeier It is a nice Saturday. You should both be drinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't judge me for having @brielarson on my couch. #captainmarvel #warmersoftercuddlier #marvel @ Juanita, Washingt… https://t.co/tfNdILY4jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonorToTheKing @seanmdav I’m very aware this is old news🤷🏼‍♂️ You can stop listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening night... #captainmarvel #marvel #mcu #amctheaters #dc #dmv @ AMC Lowes https://t.co/s0SFjn9qRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united flight 2246 IAH-&gt;ORD aboard a Boeing 737, boarded for an on-time 527AM departure, greetings from 21 F #WheelsUp #fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud Proud Proud of what my brother @petecho and his wife have built at @HanOakPDX the past 3 years.   Their cultu… https://t.co/d5zcLTdb6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radio silence from the media in this🌋😱😱😱😱😱😱😱🔥Chicago police believe Jussie Smollett PAID two brothers to ATTACK him… https://t.co/fGCAetCXlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshevilleFM @womensmarch @YouthOutright @hollis_duty @annajanejoyner @BernieSanders @DalaiLama @RuralHome… https://t.co/MHo4lXlFiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chicago O'Hare International Airport in Chicago, IL https://t.co/IdWINqsUVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m wearing my brand striped button up rather than my kroger shirt today and @Aberrant_artist was like “wow, you ar… https://t.co/PyHNhOAkUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[el Espíritu de Dios Sr esta moviendo en Edta horacen todo lugar, y viene para que le seaa entregando tus cargas, tu… https://t.co/m2mAsgQZa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black ice. If it looks like it's wet you can count on it to be a dangerous patch of black ice https://t.co/HF7Nr7nnNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off a BIG day with a little @NHL early action and some @NASCAR #NXS  5 #NHL lineups led by Varlamov/Barrie… https://t.co/hVWTfwxqDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“dearly beloved” Congrats to the Big Bro on getting hitched❣️ https://t.co/fM1fOVCJmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s SUPER EARLY, and I almost hesitate to show support for a single candidate given how early it is. But to me, th… https://t.co/ZJFEnGA84x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a clip of @zoe_worship leading last night at @jesusculture i was amazed at how many young people was there,G… https://t.co/WGdTYP58gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the POS Runs. Then we’ll see who America wants running our country. He and his boss were total embarrassment… https://t.co/p9GTsHW1aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @emrazz There it is again! It’s that new kind of stupid!  I want to be loved.   If one’s loved, seems t… https://t.co/6KysRU3UaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[SE LLEVA ACABO AUDIENCIA INICIAL Y QUEDAN EN PRISION PREVENTIVA, LOS TRES DIRECTAMENTE IMPUTADOS EN AGRESIÓN A PERI… https://t.co/eYWQl6FG9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn’t planning on masturbating, but now that I’m thinking about it fuck man i gotta do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donwinslow - well past the halfway mark in The Border / its like riding a bullet train - and so timely with tonigh… https://t.co/ulpN9Hxh7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonegan_matthew In most cases, I totally agree with that. When I’m commish I make little changes without asking. B… https://t.co/g1e6s0iOhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbwhite @printtemps @jodirren @FordGoBike Ok thx for enlightening me. It didn’t occur to me people would take it t… https://t.co/MRIoyDG75s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loyalty is an empowering thing. Glad to have supported the PMs Chequers strategy from the day it was announced. She… https://t.co/gZFMIDUA4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 19 - The Washington Post Opinions:    I’m willing to testify in public. Justin Fairfax should, too… https://t.co/fMXmTh1XLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle I belong to the most disorganized party on Earth, I'm a Democrat,  Everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoggyBee @laura_shantz Google is your friend if you need to.  They taught that in teacher's college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Girly_Mags @TiffaniThiessen It is important that @blink155pod hears my intro and important that @LanaGay listens u… https://t.co/TXjeUFi2JJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for @BlessThisMessTV! Will love to see the interpretations of #Nebraska]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pants are fucking ugly but I love my iron ranger so much. https://t.co/V4CjfrtZMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ribz95 @aaronmcbride21 @JamesBarden_45 @trvisXX I saw that and i felt awful and now I know how you feel 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best moments was when we were smoking at the top of a roof during a sudden rainstorm and lightning struc… https://t.co/1YeVxqizzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeallenn the dream scenario - truly  - the DREAM  I would give the Bucks pick or the Suns 2019 SRP for Jrue]]></document><document><![CDATA[WBB: Bethany Stucky with the and-one! Cardinal Stritch leads Sterling, 62-58 with 30.2 seconds left in the 3rd. #swordsup #kcacscores]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday February 16 - The Weekend Reader:    The most indispensable politics stories from New York and beyond …… https://t.co/eebmnqu0yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure talk some baseball with the one and only, @Steve_Perrault. Great interview that everyone should go… https://t.co/xwSHF7u06m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guitarist Scott Spivey facing the crowd at Sonoma's   Ready Set Go at Sonoma's 2/8/2019  spivey_scott #singer… https://t.co/I4jUCjyx7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamamalus var 'Arnold Promise'. This shrub is 8 yrs old...every other year is blooms especially nice. Great Winter… https://t.co/AvTVbYEfzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldBandit43 @pkwwilliams @KByrd_71 @prodicalson1971 @Man_I_Fish @HakaiPass @randibarry @DarynDalton @OlHossVike… https://t.co/55endqJo2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameSpot The legendary electric snail and one-eyed Christmas tree pokemon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way Trump’s numbers should be that high. We’ve got work to do folks, let’s get to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNTucson @JustinESports @TristanCalhoun @DiamondCasinos Abe 6-4 (7 footer with his hat); Obama (you need an actu… https://t.co/ZAwzypHsgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hutzie @TeeOhEmm @Tims_Burner @bcline760 When it comes to NHL hockey, I'm Switzerland. I don't really have a team.… https://t.co/sGEiqAg9br]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know therefore that the Lord your God is God; he is the faithful God, keeping his covenant of love to a thousand ge… https://t.co/cEObwJXxZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apileoskulls "They're fake LA residents, they're just transplants!" Yeah like you, you're from Riverside lol. That… https://t.co/NgsdieavIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostbuckCoffee BETCHA—it works! What a way to start a great day!  HAGD GHOSTBUCK THURSDAY ☕️👍❤️👊💪☝️🤟🤙🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Martha Stewart is teaming up with the world's largest cannabis company” by @tictoc  https://t.co/susegWGdmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[And while @IowaWBB is taking care if business in Bloomington, I find myself rooting for...Minnesota?!?  If they cou… https://t.co/lIAIbrx4rW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kolak_jason @Plazmyk You are an emotional wreck 24-7.  I’m not seeing a difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain Rain Go Away! #whowillstoptherain #imisssummer #stopraining #raypublishing @ Winston-Salem, North Carolina https://t.co/x50q4UU5ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried a new variety of roses last week “Silverplate”.  The color is reminiscent of Sterling Silver or Karl Lagerfel… https://t.co/EotDZUdfIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[💉💉💉by Trey ad1unique  WE HAVE OPENINGS! Open 12-10PM CALL ☎️ (504)533-9000  or just stop by 📍61 Holmes Blvd. (New O… https://t.co/GMZGJlgWpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw #HappyDeathDay2U this morning - loved the first, enjoyed this one. The sci-fi aspect didn’t always work and it… https://t.co/p8iHYHPHrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I am one of your many bosses, our tax dollars pay your salary, so you are NOT the boss😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookhoops @bhsredzone They better...the West Aurora (and Waubonsie) fans showed up. Looked like a packed house on the livestream]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always have to stop myself from doing my introduction as "America's next Top Science."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinchandScrimp @CBSThisMorning Absolutely! Imagine a corrupt police state trying to overturn a Presidential election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanlucas2000 True. Could go for anyone who picks a time without ties to a country or city]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers play the pelicans again &amp; I swear if they lose again I’m gonna be beyond pissed 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[A clip from cowboykillers studio session superxranch in Pioneertown, CA 5/5/2018  --- FOLLOW THESE MOTHERFUCKERS NO… https://t.co/KT8gJa0zff]]></document><document><![CDATA[وعلى فكرة الناس العزاز عملت أصداء بس بمصر مش بكل الدول العربية وال ١٠ مليون كتيره عالاغنية]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop 🛑 the ilegal invasion, stop taxpayers money 💰 for all country don’t respect USA 🇺🇸 laws and order, send our mi… https://t.co/slmVcl3BEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WideRtNattyLt @HammerAndRails Played for us and then transferred to Mississippi State and yes I am sorry about the… https://t.co/IpTsuqroDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning to be satisfied with where you are today is important. Not worrying about the yesterdays or tomorrows, but… https://t.co/6ZxYiXBsdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always fun to visit the mementos and artifacts of @SJSUAthletics history in the Athletics Department at @sjsu!… https://t.co/16ujiIIzf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry religious or not,,,,nobody's,,,is most to stick he's dick,,,, in another mans ass,,,,,, dipping for s*** but that's real wet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Except Eric Chavez did it 2001-2006. But hey no big deal...🤷🏻‍♂️  @Athletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy before pic 🤣🤣🤣👍🏾💯 @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/SrWApftT5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billbarnwell You’re running a team that is building around a young quarterback. Given zero other information — inc… https://t.co/CuEXvtZozn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@r0bbier0berts0n 🎵”we may break the rules, but we don’t break the law..”🎵👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @LiftOurVote Sweetie cups. . .HAVE YOU SEEN THE DATA FROM PENNSYLVANIA??, CALIFORNIA, AND OTHER STA… https://t.co/iolI5W0ecf]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 degrees is soooooo cold for a early stroll through Minneapolis! Put some Smifn Wessun in the ears and walked str… https://t.co/99YyEURgWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You complaining about being single when I’ve seen you curve niggas over and over. Please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @Ja39194961 @RL9631 @AlohaHa59067534 @ImabitcSumtimes @grgbkr37 @CandysOpinions @GodFirstGina… https://t.co/JeLzPxe2Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[White dudes with dreads legally should have less rights than everyone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJthaFiasc0 We saved you a seat up in the press box with us @LJthaFiasc0 ! @GeneralWasp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsJustPr1me I’ve pretty much hated Shero since July 1 because he didn’t sign JVR.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsonchris82 @WhatsOnStage @ThatKevinSmith @TheNotoriousMMA can help with that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and shine baby! I hope to challenge everybody this weekend to do one thing that you've been wanting to do but… https://t.co/UH7H1lLRQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amaltea_A @rogerwaters Marxista, antireligión o ateo, sin fronteras, Obvio q los Beatles se adelataron a los q viv… https://t.co/EcNxE3yTBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjsacco @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/PSMK7QPwNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beyond The sunset oh blissful morning I know our savior will soon be here.. https://t.co/XeQIu7CTtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jet ski date night on Ana's birthday #happybirthday #mylove #grateful @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/n8DiBAdkww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to cry but don’t really have a reason to/physically cannot https://t.co/n9MvtFXsfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeviDamien 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣, WOOOOOOWWWWW could u FUCKEN IMAGINE.!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpearlman I would be happy to see that fire on the sidelines in Westwood from the next @UCLAMBB coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ty_TrueReview @Marvel Ty,  This movie deserves a higher rating than a 7.6. Seems a little harsh! 8.4 minimum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning ☕️ ... rain.. Rain... &amp; MORE RAIN 🌧  But it’s still going to be a good weekend 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m saddened to hear of @HalBlaine's passing. I’m still discovering things he played on all the time.  https://t.co/lcMfoSNV6H  #halblaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott98rock @JSS98Rock  why make @MikeAnderson979 get rid of the old stuff? they had everything piled up already..… https://t.co/nEGwyE3wvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Colleges Opening Doors To People With Developmental Disabilities via @forbes https://t.co/g6eEZF2dBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WhatSexEdDidntTeachMe How to find the energy to make conversation afterwards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylviaplanth The last time I was there I was trying to think of a self derogatory tweet about how I’m leaving with… https://t.co/uO6ekfrMAE]]></document></documents></author>