<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RachaelPerrell @sethmeyers Hey there, my fellow Heliumtopic meditation participant, you absolutely crushed it, job hilariously well done 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Plutarian_Vibes @blackqueenofTU @her I would’ve but I don’t have it don’t know it it ain’t that deep lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roxy52fun @FrecklesXX20 @Joscha_doxie @DelilahTheDoxie @JakeandJack1 @prettyred52 @Daschund8969 @goobie2014… https://t.co/tqaDazS4eB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple fatalities as tornadoes hit Alabama and Georgia  https://t.co/oH4P3refiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My (spoiler free) thoughts on Captain Marvel: (1 of 3) Over-all a very good movie. Not the best Marvel movie, but I… https://t.co/lKWmTWRc2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends who visit from out of state (AZ, TX) almost always comment on how much trash is strewn everywhere here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russian Doll is hilarious and Natasha Lyonne is amazing (2 eps in so far).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M2Madness He should head a second counsel on these corrupt politicians]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God made man in his own image, and man, being a gentlemen, returned the favor”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterTHistory @HerdezBrand Great brand. Like their regular roasted salsa. Just tried a Julios salsa that they kee… https://t.co/uMuzAmKWaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/Zb2L0U4euv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I think of my grandpa I smile and my eyes fill with tears.... this has been such a tough time for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently literally everyone on Twitter is watching the Oscars to get pissed off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@be_katz @RobMills91 @johnwintertweet Shouldn't have to, if he can get paid over there but not in his own country t… https://t.co/rzvYHPECuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael_house9 @Jimbo679 @Puglaas He was trying to reorder his thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yes, we think it’s a good deal. Let’s get it (#USMCA) finished,” say American corn, soybean wheat and sorghum lead… https://t.co/mUTyisyp5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best deals and coupons for   eBags https://t.co/oGpUAjqjaM via @yazingllc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop CPAC. 👉CONSERVATIVE POLITICAL ACTION CONFERENCE Conservative Political Action Conference (CPAC) https://t.co/kES2y2bMC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solutions all major cities: Protected bike lanes, helmets for every rental bike/scooter, and a tax credit if you wo… https://t.co/QCN8eIvSDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure I’d go with “LOLZ you’re not gonna beat me up, wrestling is fake” as the angle to sell the Wrestlemania main event]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTweetOfGod @TimothyS Promises, promises.  Anyone should know better than to believe your promises.  Isn't your… https://t.co/3MuqDDMY1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a cool place to shop for vintage clothing. Prices are great and the employees are hella cool. @TBJClothes @ Th… https://t.co/YK9xwrg5JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pithynotpithy @MuslimIQ @slpng_giants Somehow liberals try to defend anti-Jewish rhetoric because the person that… https://t.co/K2Hty9XgAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASPCA There should be public policy or legislation that allows fines or citations related to animal cruelty be app… https://t.co/gb4r173xDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#homosassa #florida #bridge #construction @ Homosassa, Florida https://t.co/6IHbFAYqaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikethemiz when did they downgrade your status in the @WWEUniverse and make you a tag team with @shanemcmahon ? Yo… https://t.co/KkWhiRYk0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say I have a million dollar smile. After paying for today's dental appointment, we're that much closer to it… https://t.co/WmxgRatURT]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for humor . . .  Moms are the only people who know the true meaning of 24/7.  Yay for our...… https://t.co/2UqJ2ege4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Remember the widow’s mite. She gave the least amount, yet it counted for more because she gave all she had.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You what's sexiest is my taxes are being audited because I'm a father claiming his daughter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Michael Blair, the world is yours my friend...🙏🏾 @ Chicago's Home of Chicken &amp; Waffles https://t.co/1nkrQM0zTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I supposed to believe anything @FoxNews puts out? I hope their are no illegalities going on with @AOC. My guess… https://t.co/ZBtrmFWKCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissyGoodman Tonight we were good enough to beat any team that dared to come to Rupp.  That team I saw tonight was… https://t.co/XLTDZDh6Mu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to duel! https://t.co/PgpXsJ7rZo #yugioh #duellinks https://t.co/tJVGkwSDGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool #coffee shop here in Charlotte. Best signs of the week here for #nbaallstar. https://t.co/RVFl807h6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWPundit @Evelynjame9 JUST WONDER IF THE CLINTONS ARE SAD ABOUT THAT??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jKingHaiti I’m bored I only been here and Orlando for the most part I’m ready to dip at this point 👉🏽 ftLauderdale possibly]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GSOTD (#Gym Song of the Day): "Crawl Back - #VeilOfMaya  https://t.co/MDP8SKaSz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianlionheart @AboveavgJoe1 @UnitedYVCanada @ThatsMrNeil @gofundme I hate to repeat myself but I truly couldn't… https://t.co/WLtaVNyRSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay que saber la definición correcta de ser fuerte....💪💪💪💪 en Lawrence, Massachusetts https://t.co/VLjGkeETWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[waiting for my Techno Queen @NicoleMoudaber to get this party started. love you mi techno reina.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olallo_Rubio Me quede a la mitad del primer #TristeTurno en @convoynetwork y se me a hecho tarde para escuchar al… https://t.co/fQmcADUWym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay you have to slow down. I swear you just ordered your cart like 1 month ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder… If I’ve ever bought milk from the same cow twice… @TonyBrunoShow @ForzaCorrado @LuigiCurto22… https://t.co/lVU1YauG47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabe_prewitt Exactly, reviewed last week again. Had plenty of trot down the lane, plus post relief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #fundamentals class this morning.  Some new faces and some old ones #cpmma #joshjistu #evolutionfightteam… https://t.co/mBvz2i2AZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sport_simon I suspect no one from Leeds will be commenting on spygate until the EFL make a decision. Lawyers will… https://t.co/iaF7kc6sbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 2 days and I can’t get over this guy. @GOP is afraid of @AOC? This dude should scare the snot out of your… https://t.co/r7glwVOdUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 5 The Prodigy songs 🕺🤘🏼  1. Smack My Bitch Up 2. Breathe 3. Voodoo People 4. Out of Space  5. Narayan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our awesome ops team @cafexapp scored 💯 with the health inspector today at One Bush 👨‍🍳 https://t.co/41ZvawPkNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/uz1R5Osrsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cliffednotes @WPXIFinalWord @albyox @steelers Dollar dollar bills y'all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoneSoBlind @LazyMeatball @YouTube Not only am I against Planned Parenthood killing babies but taking my tax money… https://t.co/UCVDiinHfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun #SIGCSE2019 blog from David Largent #mediaComputation https://t.co/VHVjfABpPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant wait until someone cute the stupid bullshit organs out of my body so i can be okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronVancoillie @QB_precision We are fired up about you. But we don’t GIVE you scholarships. We GET you scholarships.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Historia nuevas, vivirlas y después olvidarlas. Todo progresivo en Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/fEzZ9sS5P5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your Sidney Throwers shirts before March 15th!  @Sidney_Raiders   https://t.co/Lb4KcD4FMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fernandito000 @minteri @nayibbukele Viejo cabron junio 1 .te buscaremos y te vas directo a MARIONA INN SUITE 9 con… https://t.co/nafPhGbj0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burnham_Jay I would bet Machado generates more revenue than Judge Judy. Unless she has an apparel store I’m not aware of...haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czardasgirl @gypsyjenn @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music… https://t.co/uhcafs3MY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, while I am putting this energy into the universe, I still want an Enfys Nest tie-in novel]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a public announcement that I will be leaving Lily effective immediately. Great relationship, but no one put… https://t.co/laC0p7Xikh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKronader @Alyssa_Milano Left wing nuts? Ask me what I believe in tell me what you believe in . Bet you were not t… https://t.co/abFtUFkKpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully more games like this ahead for TJ. Our picks have to pan out with lack of FA's willing to slum it in Indy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCurle @Space_Station @NCState @NCSSM @Astro_Christina @NCSUTechnician This officially qualifies you as an out… https://t.co/apdWx50Vys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Half-Stack IPA by @SingleCutBeer @ Section 201 — https://t.co/tLrNpxNLiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win @utahjazz ! Tough test against nugs after beating the clips last night. Stellar play by @rudygobert27 @KyleKorver @dfavors14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is the #ActualEmergency. Sign the petition to tell Congress to revoke his emergency declaration:… https://t.co/asONiwCAw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin Aid from Brazil, also blocked by Maduro. Maduro has missiles pointed at Brazil in Santa Elena de Uairen… https://t.co/AVMi8teMnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget this day. @lylebphillips taking me through a basketball training session! It was intense! Love ya… https://t.co/ftITBxFzw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattiekaye7  Somebody broke out the hitting sticks! Scoring runs  in bucket lists...keep it coming girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNCaddie love stricker but considering how the 2018 Ryder cup finished. Might not have made furyk the first vice captain. Just saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little man at 53sec with the jab crossover step back combo had me shook little man is a baller at heart not to ment… https://t.co/qh8RXiY5Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #DMV homies @ChrisPaulComedy and @HuggyLowdownDC are in town TONIGHT @PBImprov ! Welcome to town guys ! Don’t MI… https://t.co/MweJjssHK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pokesnap #dtsp #fl #stpetersburgflorida #pokemongo #pokemon #raids #snap #snapshot #pokemonart #dance #dancing… https://t.co/Tn6SeqT17k]]></document><document><![CDATA[4) Upon finally leaving, she demands a hug. I try to tell her that my hands were dirty and I was busy. My coworker… https://t.co/J2BBPe9b1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnellyAL Have you ever heard Ambassador Soemadi sing? Talk to him if you’re sincere in your quest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tstyles77 Got a Taco myself. Loved mine too but as soon as I had an issue with it they tried to screw me even thou… https://t.co/JCsfAxhqOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Northeast is going to be extra cranky over the next week as their busiest stretch of winter arrives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo AB just said “bro I haven’t ate since the last time I ate.” Guy ignorant af b I’m done 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay   @MercedesBenz tells the tale of how Bertha Benz took the first long-distance journey in a… https://t.co/NdWTKWH49d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I was religious so I could have a god I could thank for giving us 2 chainz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jacksonville State radio network has lost power. Crew frantically trying to get back on the air.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember dark skies, torrential rains and very muddy streets. I definitely remember passing Quonset huts, the por… https://t.co/0KA3YrkgGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teresa says “In fairness, I had my dress picked out last week.”   You what!!? Last week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna see a haunted house movie where the second the ghosts start their bullshit the dad just gets pissed and sta… https://t.co/DHiVGvXx11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownMarubozu I will check next week and come back.  $SIL.V is getting big market cap wise &gt;$400 M.  Not sure about liquidity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @lyralawxxx @KarlaKush420 @xoJillianJanson @TheRebelLynn @SyrenDeMerXXX @AshHollywood @lolamarieukxxx… https://t.co/Aj2jPSXlR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith:  Firm belief and trust in something for which there is no proof.  https://t.co/H34xr0GesY | Mobile Number: (… https://t.co/VmVsQhMrfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @lexcr14 @Jbriggsy_14 @DannyLeBlanc24 @Nascar_Girl1990 @CupCakeLady1313 @emt4godgranmma1… https://t.co/CdTZVilcDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a night in NYC. Not over it anytime soon. Max Kerman of Arkells. Irving Plaza, Manhattan NY, February 26, 2019… https://t.co/HXHWUlDyLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ian_walsh11 @derekflorko I told someone I wanted to throw Jav after I tore my UCL (obviously can’t do that without… https://t.co/wdqy2tkoQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teslarati @elonmusk Can I sneak on there Musk??  No one will ever know untill it's to late, and it would totally b… https://t.co/tJkcBuK5Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JB_UnivEx "Taking the rap." Your friend Felix can give you a refresher course in American slang.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been busy turning myself into a #meme with Sometimes Chad. Check us out tonight at Las Rosas in Miami https://t.co/BvbDAp5JRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Paprocki He's had knee issues for a while. It's not inhibiting his movement, but his left rear leg is shakey… https://t.co/dr2bdYY6qY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting so annoyed with everyone only wanting drops from the stream.  Like, do y’all even care for the game its… https://t.co/Z88osMDAmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melania Trump 'mistook former female Australia FM for partner'  https://t.co/PVxTcyhRZk via @Yahoo]]></document></documents></author>