<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BillClinton @JoseMuFi @jguaido #we need help Mr Clinton not too mouth bla bla  Venezuelan people it’s dying every… https://t.co/phanP00OH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hearing @JSerravallo at #RFLOI2019 and talk about #completecomprehension @PearsonK12… https://t.co/Re67jHCngV]]></document><document><![CDATA[put focus “back on customer service,” Kelly said.  Olson agreed. “The IRS still views itself as an enforcement agen… https://t.co/n5xSyt7nso]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO. In the final installment of “Kristen turns 25” I will be having cake and ice cream at my place in Provo toni… https://t.co/qbnbDytMni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachergoals @MsSafi_hse I would give myself a 50/50 shot of passing then!]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 like and I’ll go walk outside in shorts, a tank top, and barefoot until I get hypothermia and die]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first day as a #bearista with chilosogummybear at molcajetedominguerosf was so fun!! Huge thank you to my amiga… https://t.co/sJt1qbT7x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol it’s 5:20am.  I can’t remember the last time I was up this late...early...? I’m so confused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verse of the day. Hope everyone has a great blessed day!😊https://t.co/wi4JrUba5v https://t.co/oFcOUaC6HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegalMoonshiner It's so sad for so many people I know. Our grandson's girlfriend from Orlando interned at Beaurega… https://t.co/JhQPWZ59LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 week since I got my new ACL.. a few months + a lot of hard work and I’ll be back stronger than ever 🙏🏼 #aclstrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to remember that on issues of the 2nd Amendment, there's the danger of asking a person why the Admini… https://t.co/z0KtFkH0KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vevans1 @TheLeaderinMe Yes!  My son attends Kensler and I love all the @TheLeaderinMe  program they are doing too!… https://t.co/drANQlFeFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bonjour @Souriswingette  #ShakespeareSunday  "“But, soft! what light through yonder window breaks?" 17 days until… https://t.co/gASgP3zWkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggie_limbeck Now. Go back to the department. (I'm kidding, but only barely.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early word has Bryce Harper, Joe Flacco, and Kevin Durant to @BlueJacketsNHL for future considerations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch @Rambobiggs The funniest part is at the end when they said if Bernie wins he will get his testicles back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some shots from the orchid show at #missouribotanicalgarden #orchidshow  #art #photographer #photographerlife… https://t.co/Q5aItSFQzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was today years old when I discovered that Davis has a competitive gymnastics team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Funday   #sundayFunday #mimosa #poinsettia #champagne #myGirl @ Old 27 Grill https://t.co/y7D82PUoOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[pretty cool shaking and having heart palpitations when im not anxious about anything and in a generally good mood?? thanks brain!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii A completely crafted speech by the Democrats. This is a monologue for the Democrats 2020 Election camp… https://t.co/iKi6cQfu8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ders808 I had Chipotle once... i got food poisoning mid-burrito. Never-ever again 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then She Going Text  Me &amp; Say I Didn't  Wanna Kiss Her 🙄. IF I Didn't  Wanna Kiss You Trust Me I Wouldn't  Have Kissed back Lol❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunkyPumpkin Oh ok... now I get the tad joke from the comment section under the fs fan art Shay posted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALENTINES AY - for those not getting any V or  D today 🤣... give yourself a smoocherooni 💋 😘 ⁣ ⁣ what’s your status… https://t.co/ftg7g1lFQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we first got to NY we were too scared to go in the boys room now we’re sneaking out to go time square at midnight like😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting at the gate and Whitesnake starts playing. 🤘#hereigoagain #Kurkas2SanDiego]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimisanauthor37 I'm following this hashtag and I've enjoyed your answers the most. What is one thing that you wish… https://t.co/YwhQJmYh99]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dying to get away right now. Even a quick weekend trip. Something ANYTHING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 45 degrees in Nebraska, which means it's time to grab your swimsuits so you can go through Lake Potholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father - daughter soccer. Spring is upon us!   Love this pic!   He is her soccer coach. #greatparenting… https://t.co/7fiOr8EI1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@80sreference @80sreference - A wise man who recently reminded the fans, “this is 7th grade basketball, everyone.” 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omgggg #uglydogs!!! Bler did so good!!!! And Pepe and Jenga!!!! AND TIMMY SO BIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just found out I won't be seeing my favorite artist due to educational reasons and I am shOOOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trudyhp @naeemaothman4 @RealHughJackman ~ so eloquent &amp; grateful &amp; heartfelt ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please let me know if you’d be interested in buying one or more raffle tickets to help Gannon and his travel team.… https://t.co/JWRCKVLiTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy por subir nuevo vídeo en mi canal. Es de sólida típica de un país centroamericano 😄♥️🐖.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm -$250 in my bank account but everything's okay because @Weezer dropped the black album on my broke ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things @DrakeBell and @JohnStamos have in common: 1) Orange County natives 2) Elvis and Beach Boys fans  2) Massive… https://t.co/FkLJYzssqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ledrew @marshahorn66 @FelixNater @MinisterBarry @MotherRose1 @Ccangelsing @sharonePack @AHeartofVirtue… https://t.co/qNXUfkfViW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Houston weather so fucking bipolar fuck I can’t wait till it’s OFFICIALLY warm again]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is my brother not wifed up already? 🙄😂 @SwoleyMammoth https://t.co/do81qhiEIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have one and only one favorite person that I want to speak to right now and she ain’t answering my FaceTime 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YellowMustard19 @KrisAndersonTV @7News @AmakaUbakaTV @clamberton7 @KaitlinMcCulley @CW56 @RealCapnCrunch… https://t.co/jR0s3q1i1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally Getting some eats after a long walk in the parade! (@ Chino's Rotisserie in New York, NY) https://t.co/We8wBknXSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[After High School, I never thought I’d wear a purple and white cheer uniform or even do musicals again, nevertheles… https://t.co/FRenxpOC9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__brianne I've cried while editing and told my author I hoped everyone cried when they read the passage. It felt w… https://t.co/TXCYZV7u5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[jonas brothers was really a gateway emo band. look at all you fucking emos (me) crying now that they're back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Job Opportunity - Vocational Rehabilitation Caseload Assistant - Canton https://t.co/KGyETdB9fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[New 3am mood: Acting as weird as possible so a guy doesn’t ask me to come home with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to giggle it off. One of the funniest cat memes ever. #funniness #laugh #smile #funny https://t.co/VMcN5enoyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ltvcq0q4Qq 11:40 I wonder if this will work on cabinets too]]></document><document><![CDATA[and THIS just happened to be the first song that pops up on Spotify :,) https://t.co/xKwSUxpEDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyliehoelcher I mean that sucks...but so does unconsensual touching. Spray paint can be removed, years of misogyny can’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyraeweber @lexvespa @WildMonstersTM I just gotta say that this is pretty shitty.. I get that the dudes texted… https://t.co/kPibPDMNMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we confess our sins, he is faithful and just to forgive us our sins and to cleanse us from all unrighteousness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylawyoung Some are already up under their committees, and I’ll send out everything as normal night for… https://t.co/icodGpdZvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lifeline X Baptiste -- I SHIP IT!!! 💊  #ApexLegends #Overwatch #CombatMedic #PowerCouple]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time at a movie theatre in the US!  And I’m fiiiiinally watching A Star Is Born! I didn’t realize it was such… https://t.co/tcdTSsZ4kO]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd annual ski trip was a success! Especially when it includes an indoor waterpark 🤪 so blessed ❤️ thank you to Amy… https://t.co/dTNZV4btFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrPoynter That's great! Now what would be cool is to hop into a 7th gr ELA class when they discuss the differences… https://t.co/KzXOSCMMfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bratty little flirt! I wouldn’t have #JIMIN @BTS_twt  any other way 💘  https://t.co/ptvbqnl8nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s happened to #Amazon customer service? Is there no shipping guarantee any longer? The agents I talk to act li… https://t.co/44bPK7cvkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me virtually a lifetime to find the courage to live my life despite my internal struggle. No one knows what… https://t.co/GiPbJvtVnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HibaIssa Many local fans would happily bring our furballs for the sake of those coming from far away 😸(although th… https://t.co/h1619omRj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round one • you earned this babe • you have worked so hard • for this trip and  • we finally made it • to the land… https://t.co/n4wwwRon78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher We love art at #magnoliaemporium can you tell? 😁😂😘🤩 https://t.co/cC0kOvhpZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class List for Friday, February 15, 2019: 5:00 am Wildcard Workout: STRONG by Zumba with Cheryl E. Wood… https://t.co/osaI5J1sFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How are our soybean farmers doing?  https://t.co/CWCaqDnTe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the day @ Beyond The Papers: Kingdom Entrepreneurs Pioneer Summit!  “Lord you multiply” @AkiaHardnett… https://t.co/pJn3KiYAfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up again before the birds... I wake up way to early! 🤫 #earlybird #sleepy #annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun morning listening to legendary Jeannie Seely and Tim Atwood. https://t.co/aPez2HK2jq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are getting ready!! 10-4 come out to Turkey Thicket Rec Center for National Girls and Women in Sports Day! @ Tur… https://t.co/bXW3vBEp2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2AdamW @JackYatesHoops @tguilloryHISD @HISDAthletics @KPRC2 @Esther188rod  YOU GO GENTLEMAN  PLAYER'S FROM YAT… https://t.co/frALoYswNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamSimlishQueen First of all I’m so sorry you went through that. I know what hearing that from mother is like. And… https://t.co/g3OFU8FiFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching him break up with Hanna B. #TheBachelor https://t.co/UKLLveVODP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WoahItsChelseaa The character isn't even Michael Jackson himself? Leon just claims he is for part of it. Wtf? (I g… https://t.co/vdt5wW7Igd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when a gown has pockets because evening bags are always too small and asking someone to hold your phone and… https://t.co/BLGgKMhQil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harvestmoon940 Love you dude! #bestiesforever #thankyouforbeingmyfriend ❤️😘🥰😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[What?!?!? I ran into a celebrity at True Talk Friday night! Music artist, radio show host and so much more - Rene’e… https://t.co/udtdJxkT24]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworkers are always like “you don’t talk much”...or “you’re so quiet”. I’m like no I do talk just not to ya’ll smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy is good for the soul. Funny Pictures – 58 Pics https://t.co/PZRcj9AsPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chandra0816 @TMZ @TooFab You do know they swore under oath when they were grown that he didn't touch them? #LiarsLie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @realDonaldTrump please help keep our future safe, our children, by not allowing states to have mandatory vacci… https://t.co/1PWkyC9DMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Yeah...just another self-important meanie exposed...bye bye Presidency]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s a stay inside, pj’s all day type of day here in montana ❄️. obsessed with this loungewear set i’m wearing and… https://t.co/PSBNFZZGcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thirsty Thursday means new beer, kinda! This week: Tequila Barrel-Aged 99 Limes Sour re-release. This batch has mor… https://t.co/qNxebuQ3HC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, celebrating #InternationalWomensDay with the two amazing young women that made me a mom! ❤️❤️ https://t.co/YWNvIiySCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of birthday weekend in #NYC! #MOMA #Vangogh #Matisse #Picasso #Dali #Wyeth #StPats #Rockfeller sellmoresteel… https://t.co/Pdgxxujb9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melnickjeffrey1 See also the regional publics attempting to shore up finances by pushing for online graduate degre… https://t.co/3Jwh5Ierlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone keep saying it’s not the same person he looks exactly the same in the face. Look at his brows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@commiefairy @namratx Lol I did that. I was like ok let me listen to this Jonas brother song first and then give all my time to Solange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent this evening @crashspaceLA - a very cool #hackerspace in Los Angeles. They had a „coding social“ meeting. It… https://t.co/6M5dSaH8Qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleJamal4 thank you so much for the past four years. We love you and wish nothing but the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen  Having a problem with your "Alternative Facts" this morning?  A cage is a CAGE no matter how you screw… https://t.co/O1tC9di0sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noelcarbs @MyFavMurder @emtothea @MelanieScrofano @cdemrys @chocolateyshell @BridgetOnTV @PunkyStarshine @njnic23… https://t.co/ugA3Tdb7kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all talk down on each other hustles too much. Niggas don’t even be sayin none til women sub tweet dey boyfriend b… https://t.co/4iOrZUmopf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto I'm Totally Heartbroken! That, a... Intelligent, Talented, Successful, and popular Young Black gay M… https://t.co/QHVa3K0Gny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to share the news - I’m Mrs. Columbus United States 🇺🇸 I look forward to representing one of the best citie… https://t.co/OTfbysSiSw]]></document></documents></author>