<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Alex just drove to McDonald’s to get me a shake and cookies while I study. https://t.co/X9LOGGvLGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I am a hippie, but it seems to me that objecting to war with Iran on grounds that it usurps Congress’s auth… https://t.co/94CgrZ88My]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sstange111 @santaanitapark Yes, ,@carterevans got that badly wrong. https://t.co/At15sJJ0xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Keep doing what you do, the American people know what is really going on, thanks for the sacrifice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyOnEd I teach in a school, keep them away from me and our students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember Dinesh, this happened in deep Democrat Chicago...not likely to happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickDGarner @RepAdamSchiff @MeetThePress Never say never - when a dude or a lady shows up with a wispy mustache an… https://t.co/czPBDIkKQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayrosen_nyu @thedavidcrosby Not that I’m on their side, but would you like a link? They explained it fully. Don’t… https://t.co/PADDvg69Yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idontfold Sorry, I had a long day at work. Came home and was set to go out to dinner with my wife and got called o… https://t.co/vt2tPkbOmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very thankful for all the women in my life.  Without them, none of us would be alive.  #InternatinalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSea1964 @LadyRedWave Do you think people would be doing this, attacking #Trump supporters if not for… https://t.co/BYJWVdWVC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary Wow. Guess Twitter bday for me? I don't been r… https://t.co/i7sCLYaHIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, the Cambridge City council cancelled it's meeting for a DC junket! LoL... Cambridge Does Better!! #jefferyforcambridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salt Lake City, UT Colton, CA West Valley City, UT South Jordan, UT Juiz de Fora, Brazil  Rio de Janeiro, Brazil  S… https://t.co/YXYmFP8LcP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecoachvogt @slade248 @CoachMartin99 @CoachShiffman @rdsmith86 @chowan6464 @dacoachmohuddle @bensonbuilt9… https://t.co/r485fWcQqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liverpool I'm sure would have loved to have #var but I know they can handle their own.  #football #sports #futbol… https://t.co/EN78NilEmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Durham.   And it is definitely a charge; the bridge’s feet were set.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/fZ9NgvLCw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreselopeze @DrRobertoLopez2 @c_larreategui Farsantes ahora están en contra después de permitir que destruyan la… https://t.co/0WGQ4KyyXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing that did remind me of 2008 winter was seeing some of the side streets in Iowa City even before this lates… https://t.co/BHMxqFpYu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be heading down to Lakeland soon and will have coverage of Class 1A final between Trenton and Holmes County at 2 pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why would we care about #NaziPropaganda ??? We live in a Democracy! We shun and obliterate aggress… https://t.co/VjWAntRPCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackie Robinson is the GOAT. A true American hero. It would be an honor to have this movie in my collection.… https://t.co/13OTLNruY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I can't believe that CNN would report this obviously racist arrest by a black police chief of a black man for… https://t.co/IAXvRiJuzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @danpfeiffer Is this a parody account? Have you seen your parties President?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlashgitzAnims @NoahBero @TweezCake43 @skaionhati9044 @jimmysnye *Jimmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FJasmineG @ProfessorEA Not sure whether this is good or sad.  Great that’s it’s highly racked.  Sad he and other A… https://t.co/O7OQvl9ctX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC why don’t you and Mika physically go to work and show up with guests ? Do you want to continue your show? L… https://t.co/y4h4IewNQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[See, thats what a hotel stay should be, @HiltonHotels Just had an amazing stay at the #HamptonInn Denver Airport-Gateway Park]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewaraven @aimeeterese @martymacmarty Sounds more like a bro-country song to me....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VonWolf9 I don't really no was kind of stamina it would take to climb that wall. If anyone wins they automatically win a free green card.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Yeah, we tried that by voting libertarian and ended up with Drumph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisNeiweem @antjuansea Good Morning! Great job on @FoxFriendsFirst w/ @SchmittNYC Keep up the good work on… https://t.co/h8sb64XaUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Stone has been very effective so far. Bishop robbed him from getting on the board #VegasBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Just found https://t.co/TIDVsI5a2q  Makes using the Touch Bar much better when hitting the ESC key because I c… https://t.co/Mje2awWTHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, that’s not a crisis! Tens of thousands a month attacking the integrity of our country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodneyMute @GoodmanHoops Just messing with you man! Lol https://t.co/vkk1JxMzps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanCarabeoCBS3 Hi Jan!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Maybe Jam can be your nickname?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[We draw at #ILOVEARTBRO   #wip #spirallegion #armageddonit #pride #geneticenhancementtemplate @ Cellar Door https://t.co/tXLgIzeoV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh why was sir mix a lot at the auburn Red Robin tonight like deadass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachD_AU @coachdeesmith @Thebigirish73 @MashElite @JasonSpray @SouthTXCoach @coachfeld @austinwwomack… https://t.co/MpwBxpBScM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marques Bolden’s face screams “now that just aint right” https://t.co/uWWCr02cmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prediction that Bradley would have the greatest second half in basketball history was only slightly off the mark… https://t.co/w4HUYAIiHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s loot! Really good deals.  -Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles #3 (rare) -SpyMan (2nd Jim Steranko) -ASM poster (s… https://t.co/PZJYr45jjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 days to go!!!!! Are you ready???? @whillsathletics https://t.co/jsvVzsnjTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Target caught you again! Price is advertised lower on the app, then you go into the store and expect to PAY Higher… https://t.co/7ASAIluctg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manifort is convicted of Tax Evasion,Bank Fraud, I believe Money Laundering and Now lieing to the SP,,he gave Polli… https://t.co/KTIQiUKArH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking. Tommie, the dog who was intentionally set on fire at Abner Clay Park in Richmond on Sunday, has died… https://t.co/0P2GRjDP1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ben, can you ask unhappy bank robber guy if he likes beastiality like Angry Bill does?? Maybe it’s a prison / b… https://t.co/ZKZYPDJIS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savannahfiish I just saved this so now you get to be my first victim. Congrats! https://t.co/1zZm60I2wG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tydeshaaaa Not the yams 😩Whatchu gon mix the Mac and cheese with now?🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone else has love, but I have pizza, so who’s the real winner here? #valentinesday @ Lighthouse Pizza https://t.co/aZs2gu6sFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaPagina Me da un gran gusto ver que si quieren el cambio, se nota que Uds hacían lo q los de arriba 👆🏾 les ordena… https://t.co/szootkXtOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pathetic and disgusting ://christiannews.net/2019/02/18/former-prison-nurse-who-identifies-as-male-awarded-120k-in-… https://t.co/MuvwSCRAkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whogivesashirt @NoahPaulLeGies You still seem to be operating under the delusion that I don't know anything about… https://t.co/LyOIfX0J5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkingImpact Well you let ne@know because I don’t really have time to watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaithRubPol @petaluma @GovMikeHuckabee @realDonaldTrump That sentence is levied. I read somewhere else that Muelle… https://t.co/QTBo81wGLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[O Captain! My Captain! . . #portland #fuji #x100t @ Portland International Airport https://t.co/WCvHT0W1Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job Pens! 🐧 - Drinking a Glove Dropper by @slyfoxbeer/@rivertownebeer at @LuckyLouies814  — https://t.co/ABz6j3wWHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChickenMarsala #Chicken #Mushrooms #Marsala #NomNom #NowCookThjs @ Camarillo, California https://t.co/au5Jy20xxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeAnnaTLorraine Because then they would have to admit everything they stand for is bullshit. You've got a better c… https://t.co/9rmhl9swyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:53, Q2 — Ellington 31, Classical 24. Knights are playing some fantastic defense #ctbb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends let friends eat at Kelley's Deli @ Kelleys Deli https://t.co/fEwVtzFMMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theBurlyChef @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You being Canadian - do us a favour and take back Mark Steyn?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bit of Scandanavian #DoomMetal from 2015 #MammothStorm #Fornjot #NowSpinning #vinyl https://t.co/2r8Cfwql37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @KE0PBR. Lots of calls, but CAS4B telemetry uber alles. Heard K2AL. 10deg over the Wasatch. No bueno.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaTourEiffel When will April tickets be available? (Only available through April 4th currently)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say there’s still time to change, remind them that no there’s not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for women like Hillary. There are many women that are following her foot steps. It's a great country to make… https://t.co/mTaCcUtypy]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to social media, every person I know in Juneau went to the ice caves today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Kroschel @SilverthorneCO @SummitDailyNews @karenleightv @jimbcbs4 @NationalSheriff @NatPoliceAssoc… https://t.co/M65DSWRlvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada persona tiene que descubrir cuáles son sus detonadores para poder vivir, pues la combustión que se produce al… https://t.co/QdLyLyFSrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s right‼️ It’s #sunday again, probably my favorite day to hit the gym because it is so empty in the morning.… https://t.co/66CNftUwdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniversityFour @NOAAClimate Fun to note that FDR tax rates are why power is so damn cheap in the northwest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @WhiteHouse @IvankaTrump Good Afternoon! Great job working with @HouseDemocrats @HouseGOP @SenateDems… https://t.co/ifQ1HZW7jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel bad for people who don’t love America first. Is any party affiliation true love? #LegalizeFreedom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mabde33 This team still needs to make it's mark on the season. #sjubb  have talent to win the Big East tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darylblas @ERICBEL60765524 @CricketGirlMN @LeeHenHen @richard2380 Yes it is ... !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mischiefthecat1 @gobigorgohome71 @PaulKuharskyNFL https://t.co/G2icCTu43F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey What about the people who listen to your music instead of seek therapy and professional help for childhood trauma , ahem me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[just now found out i bought an astringent instead of toner,, feeling: stupid as fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi No it’s not for the people! It’s Democrats Free Speech Suppression! #DemocratsAreCorrupt… https://t.co/MTbO85n51z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to South my guy @JoshflyhighHawk big time player and person excited to have him aboard as a cougar! 🔋🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman Krugman taking the Harry Reid path of choosing to lie to his audience. But he’s a liberal, so it’s expected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lasagna With Meat Sauce &amp; Kraft Parmesan Cheese ! #ItalianFood #Dinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the Allen archery team tomorrow at the 3-D state championship! @OutdoorAllen @AllenArchery @LFCEagles… https://t.co/g60bkJRW2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AletheiaAtheos @malkabethwendy I agree, I was just wondering whose idea it was to do that if anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More fuel to the fire for #NERevs fans.   The club slots in at No. 23 in the preseason @MLS power rankings. The onl… https://t.co/dRpIhuSFSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reneritchie @PrivacyCoachPro That’s the thing, 2FA using the phone is inherently less secure. We’ve been over this… https://t.co/ddng0OJzSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 when your mental twisted You gets traded for a mid round pick, remember, @AmariCooper9 was traded for a First… https://t.co/A25oWTLYIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[yowza cole hauser (star of the film)(??) just got tom hollander killed by police]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EatonKrone @ChrisGault My feelings exactly.  Thought i was alone.  Might be best book of all time.  No weak spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport I bought this when you released them three weeks ago. When do you think I’m going to actually get t… https://t.co/nUtJ45tJ7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost This is not analysis. This is a puff propaganda piece. You didn’t learn anything about Harris.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite saying he didn’t know his attackers previously, now it appears in fact did know at least one of them - and… https://t.co/pdXg4v1ZlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an interior designers opinion on shelves. I wanna decorate my room]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbyoliver03  Abby I always wanted to ask you. After I watched  you play at the sen high school all star game. Wit… https://t.co/FBuNedjWZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also a wrap on the season. And should be a wrap on the coach. #FireHousely #Sabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice clear day today at #jfk @ John F. Kennedy International Airport https://t.co/UKz0FdSnRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing on Lake michigan &amp; day trip💜  #lakemichigan #chicago #lake #frozen @ Lakeshore - Lake Michigan https://t.co/IJBpa9mwem]]></document></documents></author>