<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@marie18081 Muy buenos días para ti también María Elena y feliz Lunes y inicio semana cuídate mucho saludos cordiales 💋💋💋💋,!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckBell4 The sad part is that we cannot say “slushy”, “messy”, “winter blast” , “winter wonderland” and all thos… https://t.co/1lhcqUvoGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDI_CHILE @INTERPOL_TIGC @INTERPOL_HQ 07-.07 or I7.I7- John 'safI Then Thru ThI TruT ThI yord Is TruT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golf - It's apparently what "leaders" do during national emergencies... Man, even Ann Coulter called this one right… https://t.co/aVjza3410x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really hope this gets and anime adaptation soon I have high hopes for it tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my2k @TheMadMadCat Oh please be the sequel to jalopy I desperately need]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad respect for the guy at the end and defending that man. Now that’s a U.S. citizen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Headquarters Barber Styling https://t.co/i9Jx26c4eM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BazzB70 @uncuttool8 @aussietrbl @Unsucchiacazzi @jockboy1113 @Pixel_622 @Hockeyguy13 @BobHail @StantonGreame… https://t.co/lrHuVU1t4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Caution_Cole If you don’t think racism exists I don’t know what to tell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craigcalcaterra This might be an option, my wife and I love this https://t.co/zYy7cKVXob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_donahue9 @BostonGlobe I do... Every business should have the right to discriminate for any reason it chooses.… https://t.co/jFtIzlAMAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentsDayProtests #Presidential #Trump #OcasioCortez https://t.co/3mtSj8nPNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAWKS GOAL!! 🚨🚨  🐯 gets his second of the night, on the powerplay, to tie things up with just over 3 minutes to go!… https://t.co/UZ8GWVK3Bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wisconsin Gov. Tony Evers (D) has announced a proposal that would legalize medical marijuana and decriminalize poss… https://t.co/cKqf6nh0lD]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had to convince her that since our mayor — himself no mean song-and-dance man — and his spouse, who had played A… https://t.co/mliQQR4jct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCOutOfParadise @Bigmama25296029 @AndrewPollackFL @realDonaldTrump Plenty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get 6" PVC pipe and caps. Cut to needed length. Seal one end, put you guns in the pipe, put the cap on the end. Bur… https://t.co/Uov7Fxj541]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gemmapeacocke The Cantus was in Latin and the other parts in French, with hints throughout of hidden Masonic formu… https://t.co/FbnCvk5tR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost done ✅ #art #artist #artwork #nailart #instaart #streetart #arte #artofvisuals #digitalart #contemporaryart… https://t.co/LY6u9fFmnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What could have been.........   Biggie and Tupac.  Rest peacefully GOATS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happynationalmeatballday - this is a food holiday I can buy into. Having the opportunity to head up marketing at… https://t.co/TalNxANknc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEP I think that answer varies by age. Goals and perspective change dramatically through the years. However, the t… https://t.co/4G0Hwg41Kl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #2: Balboa Park, La Jolla Cove, Little Italy, Coronado #sandiego #bff #gooftroop @ San Diego, California https://t.co/GH6RzN89CA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since @BernieSanders announced his run for President, today, here’s a pic I snapped of him when he spoke in #LFK Ma… https://t.co/VUtz2kiMRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esmith2c Gotta say it was a good day. Picked mine up on launch at 5am or something with Madden. Ended up going bac… https://t.co/oRO4GHeYOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeuceThomas @Tunde_Tifase @Chimweeeeezy @TheGreatKenny_A @NBAonTNT @Candace_Parker 1)James harden  2) gannis  3) P… https://t.co/QX0TWI1k1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are calling for the investigation into a.o.c. and her lover ! I don’t use caps for her initials , I TOALLY lost… https://t.co/Y3IP3J31HS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting some blokes during the #bombcyclone #wind @ Scott's Computer Repair https://t.co/d7KnSxaP1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAPuritans @TheRickWilson If there was any justice Roger Stone would be Satans footstool right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaboiTCfresh @StLouligans @BernieShow @SillyTailgate @SaintLouisFC @msmallmon @miklasz @Frank_Cusumano… https://t.co/MuPQv5yr0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: This is the best six-stick of the entire building boom and will be seen as an icon if it survive… https://t.co/U9bRZpV7lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homie was knocked out before he got hit with the second punch.  All i remember is everyone ran everywhere 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frecklednattie1 I've done that a few times! And I hear pro athletes do it along because of being on the road so often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curt Davis #hysterics #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #losangeles #marvista @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/XSrK3qIRrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los amigos son la familia que uno escoge 🙌🏼 en Saltillo, Mexico https://t.co/kt36mhCw8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh, Oh! Guess what day it is? Huh? Anybody? Lol! 🐪🐫 Currently,  it's 16° under Cloudy skies.  Sunrise: 6:49am, Suns… https://t.co/MJCcql3vD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Aspen Park/Conifer. Happy #FlyoverFriday @KOANewsRadio https://t.co/FBONobYm0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghouliesp @candyjo08 @therealkarlholt Once again Lilly, what your mom says and what is reality are different thing… https://t.co/Icul1XlYAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The concert was amazing. It’s colder than bones out there. (@ The Bloomgrens in Scottsdale, AZ) https://t.co/o1fJOtU5id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaithlenn Well I would say ice it when you can and let it rest. If it doesn’t heal naturally within a few days, yo… https://t.co/A31hTwI60L]]></document><document><![CDATA[does the name Prococo ring a bell one of your brother close friend heading for jail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcherTyrell @Szladesyn @LeoGarcia_1990 @PhilSzostak The shame he feels for his actions, and thoughts call back to… https://t.co/L8gmHl7zgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShepherd2013 So if we can pull coal from air and diamonds come from coal, will that mean we can pull diamonds from the air? #IWannaBeRich]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is legit. Been down that patriotic slide a few times already. https://t.co/6Lg1pM90V0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeFortenbaugh Damn I glad I don’t listen to that Niners station you called @957thegame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid ass street take over idiots driving in circles like morons! How stupid are people and who raised them. If I… https://t.co/Lu6CMfO4xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’ve learned the last couple weeks.  Do NOT date or make babies with Basketball players]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have noooo idea who the fuck I just played with in Apex but holy fuck man, guy just wrecked whoever came in his path.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1990, a great year for the @GeorgiaTech #YellowJackets. Not only the first major university to establish a college… https://t.co/MGfHyCEVME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a #TonyTheTiger #FunkoPop? Click here for your chance: https://t.co/VXeWg6MtOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithBKyle In the top two primary, a DSA candidate made it out of the primary against Adam Smith. This is a distri… https://t.co/FdiPpnaT8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClifAndNydia #WeddingBellsLife #MiamiLife #MiAeyO @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/ZZMmRW2CQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a wonderful morning @bradfordville. Today in SS we look at 1 John 2:12-18. “You Can’t Take it Wi… https://t.co/3F0VwUdzuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[People with courage and character always seem sinister to those who have neither #politicians #BernieSanders2020 Fuck Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamHendrick @chaseelliott @WilliamByron @JimmieJohnson @AlexBowman88 That's sweet jimmy and them]]></document><document><![CDATA[any reports that Zion Williamson sneaker could have been something else? How is it possible that a sneaker could do… https://t.co/mSuEfLPC75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC Democrats have their own political agenda, so truth doesn't matter to them. Also, more illegal aliens… https://t.co/LDF7ZzU1H9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a cruel man, Jordi Baró (either that or you work for Barcelona Tourism).  We’re predicted to drop to 16 F to… https://t.co/4mSSbzT9XE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the AFC north dissipate while Knowing My Browns are on the Uptick 😏😎😎😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uncle_Jimbo @LoveCovfefe2020 @JerryNadler @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Hope this kind of thing never happens t… https://t.co/s35bYpEOaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; clear sky temperature down 48°F -&gt; 31°F humidity up 49% -&gt; 67% wind 11mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[No man, this is the onion or something. Cyah tell me say dem publish this inna MR. Stewart new paper]]></document><document><![CDATA[8♥️9❣️⚠️ #bellagio #poker #lasvegas #texasholdem #gamble #chipstack #allin https://t.co/V12SV43cdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMLeo @JordanUhl Wow. There’s just, room for everybody. Let’s just say that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may induce some vigorous discussion. Pim and I take 4 long-familiar ideas on changing fitness and try to clari… https://t.co/sbNd9BGtPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huawei’s folding phone uses their own processor, modem, and I think screen. Are they beating Apple at the vertical… https://t.co/CCsiWIZmd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible product, even cooler opportunity. Thanks for the unique experience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It don't have to be honkytonks, boots, and wrangler jeans It ain't the banjo or the fiddle, no It's the words and w… https://t.co/aizkGM2Zfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you stay up all night playing super smash bros with your bro 🎮 https://t.co/UtoIpQog4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usedarkroom Wow! Can’t believe it’s been 4 years! Congratulations on creating such an amazing app that has gotten… https://t.co/9FfRFoh5Vk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alcaldeledezma @amable020201 @NicolasMaduro ya te debe quedar mucho menos tiempo y el dinero que tienes no te va alcanzar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @REVMusicNY It’s not going to come down to bernie so fucking stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UweBollocks they're on tour with jimmy eat world right now and ra ra riot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smitmartijn Safe travels and thanks again for your efforts w/ the @vExpert program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bird on the head . . .  #farragut #greysunday @ Farragut Square https://t.co/SZ3CMjidoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBaileyWFNZ It’s probably just me, my ADHD just can’t understand how people watch baseball due to the lack of a… https://t.co/JMdUtw2Obc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hardball That was the Problem Republicans did criticize trump but in Private most all the time-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samsung Launch Event.  Thank You Samsung! #S10Launch #Samsung #ATT #Topgolf @endlesscrowd  @SamsungUS  @Krivs14… https://t.co/4YGUi8OLoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weetuscren That’s what happens when we don’t let them have a popular film category.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's our way of helping our #LeeCounty neighbors affected by the #AlabamaTornadoes. FREE admission to our hilarious… https://t.co/H6Yj06Iwn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvillacastin @CarinaHardy4 Es una via septal y probablemente PH. He visto ya dos casos de pre-excitacion “asintoma… https://t.co/vx5PdfWSpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theycallme_Cp3 @ESPNNBA @jryansmith29 You forgot the cc @theycallme_Cp3   Cc: @jryansmith29]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dono how I've watched this entire race and missed every single trivia question.... Didn't even know it was a Twit… https://t.co/wj2nQPcYxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Lawrence makes a compelling case that @MarkMeadows is a racist. It’s undeniable that he’s an embarrassment to his constituents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camped out in front of the TV. Big time college basketball rivalries happening tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow-up: Here’s a better headline regarding #SB349. #ARleg #ARnews https://t.co/mdLeomT027]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE READYYYYY. WE READYYYYY. WE READDYYYYYYYY FORR YALLLLLLLLLL #UniteAndConquer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraSanborn What’s the merit in clearing it now? Won’t it just drift over?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to learn from my brother across the river, @KeithEricBenson at #EthnoForum19 @PennGSE @EthnoForumGSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonscott49 From white sandy beaches, to white snowy ones... You’re living the dream!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadalynSpitzer She wanted to be snuggled. I woke up from a 2hr nap and that's how she looked! All melted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty nice looking presentation from our friends @harthrestaurant 🙌🙌🙌 https://t.co/LLPchAPlcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[💪🏼🔥This is the platinum age of Mexican/American cinema. #AcademyAwards2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LevineJonathan We are seeing the last performance of Jessie Smollet.  Everyone, please a round of applause!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfa And paying wages!  I’ve wondered exactly what period MAGA’s are pining for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Naval Support Activity Millington in Millington, TN https://t.co/Fdj1y5G0H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi luce la casa de los Hornets. Afinando todo rumbo al 2019 NBA All Star Game. Aquí en Charlotte @ Charlotte, Nort… https://t.co/YreSUlQGOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you think I love @AndersonPaak so much that I’d schedule a trip home in April just to listen to the new album wi… https://t.co/XjX6dac9NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the guy remodeling the condo next to me....relax with the drill and hammer. It’s 2:41 am.]]></document></documents></author>