<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ElGordoyLaFlaca @LorenzoMendezz @Chiquis626 No tienen nada más que aser que hablar de esta que no artista es ya ve… https://t.co/68TH30kwP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Can you run for office from #Gitmo? https://t.co/sN6HPS3Ve7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zoodlemouse13 He has a long time girlfriend who he has a 2 year old daughter with. But seriously, he and Gaga have… https://t.co/X65P1XCKpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashback week! This week I am going to remind you all about my first book, Vivir el Dream, which has won 5 awards!… https://t.co/HauvcB0CxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The media is dishonest and only reports stories that support their agenda and ideology.  The loath… https://t.co/ogJDREmsog]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT IS THIS NONSENSE?!?? This show is amazing and wonderful and lovely and beloved and perfect and GIVE IT BACK! G… https://t.co/UN5NKRzTgE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evilpirate @MPCFitlanders @Sheugs @sarahjaswim @barbaramills1 @LaurelSchuett @GHJNancy @RunTheEdge… https://t.co/wkktmUKfFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrianambl Doesn’t want to give me any attention. Lol. Seriously, tell the truth and the lefty lying liberals will… https://t.co/5LjZceXsbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[ion gotta fight, i got hitta’s ready to kill💯🤞🏽 https://t.co/T2JpL4a5FU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#delusionaltrump excuse me? So you’re saying “God Bless...” but let me get this right ... as long as the Venezuela… https://t.co/4ExCp345Sv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m finna cry Momma Denson looked so good at her 50th last night. ❤️😭 https://t.co/xV2KU9RDKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaveyDaniel Can you open my dm. There’s a surprise waiting for you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuleymagomez36 You would say that! 😭 No, I already started looking at Airbnb’s. Going on a trip for my bday will now be tradition!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how much I just absolutely love watching Sherlock. https://t.co/4P6tbBBUvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never felt more disrespected than when someone takes my picture without the flash on]]></document><document><![CDATA[MPP @LauraMaeLindo literally does not quit. She’s a single mom to three kids and wakes up every morning to make… https://t.co/LtVYrxWB83]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @MCPS_Elementary #STEAMshowcase is underway! These projects look AMAZING! #WeAreMCPS https://t.co/Es9iVwxXFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Drinking water, working out, having a positive attitude, and getting lots of sleep will  strengthen your immune sy… https://t.co/XGULnZ0apb]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my fav influencers n stuff r going to Mexico the same time I’ll be there what is this 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[LISTAN LISTOS Y LISTAS PARA CANTAR " Do i ever cross your mind" 123456 VECES ? YA ESTA RUIN NKJCBDNJVBFN  #ShawnMendesTheTourAmsterdam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tortellini in Brodo! Swipe for some of my favorite inventive dishes from avery_sf’s tasting menu - don’t miss the 🐒… https://t.co/e1MMRPem41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFW22b @FauxRealityM @anitabreak7 Well let’s wait and see. They’re getting older, and being that I’m about to fina… https://t.co/UwYd6P0ITe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andres @PennyRed Wow I’m really sorry to hear that you both were faced with such a terrible choice due to our brok… https://t.co/6Cs6at9xx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[thx coconut milk &amp; guanabana..🥥🍹🌿📷📦 #spikeddrink #spikedhair https://t.co/HeYn8dPDEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeroLux1 Insecuries first then the art...caterpillar then the butterfly 🦋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy President's Day 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 YES America @realDonaldTrump is YOUR President!! https://t.co/LGJQrTvdrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radicalpoet_ I know it’s surprising but I definitely recommend popping into any place like Sephora that sells them… https://t.co/dfKvjtWTC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenCohan @scottkfoley @WhiskeyCav  Nooooooooooo she didn't 😂😂😂😂😂😂DIED😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 there is no emoji for that kind… https://t.co/nUpD2BaoMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#parents #recherche #cannabis❓ @rclalq @FRAPRU #polmtl #logement @francoislegault  @CarmantLionel  @SJB_CAQ… https://t.co/cu0hMrgyfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking around the sa riverwalk thinking about scorch: stranded wow I do miss cheer sometimes /:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out here to say @_rtrush is the realest lady I know and I can’t believe this woman is my best friend!!! Wtf!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the ladybugs have won. they took over my room. i am now a loser on the couch]]></document><document><![CDATA[buena noche..que dios vele sus sueños.fue dia del amor. #familyfirst repostit_app en Heroica Guaymas, Sonora, Mexico https://t.co/jD6I8J16gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it 2019 and people still shame sexual health? Yeast infections, STDs/STIs, menstruation, and the like should… https://t.co/33qQHDRf6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHLBaseballNsdr Very much so... but it’ll all end happy when I remember that Ralph Cox wasn’t the last player cut from the team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_holmesjr I am beyond sad my builder now Holmes approved builder we are out 150k legal/engineer over $200k+rep… https://t.co/KnVjN4aKlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[PODCAST: Tune in on 2.26.19 to hear Dr. @AllisonMilner2 talk about #workplace &amp; #suicideprevention.… https://t.co/SPuAh0jD26]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shut the absolute f-up about book deals and quit it with  false moral outrage @GOP  #MichaelCohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelK12319637 @KamVTV @realDonaldTrump Ditto, me too!!! But I'm stocked up on the popcorn, butter and a brand new… https://t.co/xjQ9FzI5Nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños @ThisIsRobThomas have a great day - see you on the road 🎉🎁🎤🎼🎹❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unexpected moving perk = Girl Scout Cookies over a month early #wealreadyatethemall #thisisoursecondorder… https://t.co/OIBdtD9C2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JolaBurnett @TamaraMcCleary @TechWorldsHalf @digitalcloudgal @laurenmaille @LornaGarey @TechnyGal @khalihenderson… https://t.co/jOxm99ZRxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[All your leaders have fled. They surrendered without resistance. The people tried to slip away, but they were captu… https://t.co/F3hVfNEIhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeKOIN @JoeJHoyt @KATUNews Little Red Wagon I barely knew you... 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of calories in a bar of chocolate is 2x what i burn in a typical workout sesh lol life ain’t fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAmbitious12 Lmao oh my I can imagine! Sadly, people can’t handle the truth even when they ask for it 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the morning and before a full complement of coffee, everyone sounds like they’re yelling. That is all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to hit the ground running @pizitzmiddle with @SAThomasTeach this week as we transform geography instruct… https://t.co/lB68SmnIGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[These girls are Distracted Driving expert! #WeAreDE Exhibition @Durand_Eastman https://t.co/OiMVLKrATg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes my version of trying on shirts includes “how does this look when I do finger guns?” https://t.co/acBtJxOyoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsbak_ She is just now waking back up! 😊 normally in my bed she would be waking up around 2ish. She did good lol I’m a proud mama]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican men belittle AOC because they’re absolutely terrified of a fearless woman of color unapologetically disr… https://t.co/pptUZr4SRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nran75 @DLoesch @tangytangier I've worked in two,none of that's happening on my watch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Native plants in bioswales are not only slowing the flow, but are providing habitat. #cblp #gonative @ChesapeakeCLC… https://t.co/6UWj5q8oOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@najeeqwilson that girl ain’t missing she ran away and is STILL in windsor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shea_Buttah He can’t. But let us pray for him obviously a disturbed young man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctanner3 @KHutchinson440 @TrumpFan80 @CaliRN619 @4x_Clubchamp @ImabitcSumtimes @louisa_ip @briantopping66… https://t.co/S6aexPfHE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCVB @TheView has fans? She is a hateful, bitter, angry woman. Her immune system is suffering for it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remaining in servitude to God has allowed me to trust and allow him to use me as he wishes and because of that, my… https://t.co/sY5EFRLzU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WCHS_Librarian @getnicced I actually think I may be sick now. It’s like my body just let me survive the last 3 day… https://t.co/pfoqOrZ3tV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the send off @gojhstitans ❤️❤️ headed to STATE https://t.co/tVOqR0QgGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing everyone filling these beautiful #EmptyBowls on Wednesday evening in support of… https://t.co/oSFMPraf1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have some big decisions coming up and I just wish I had someone to tell me which path to take.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @EdKrassen #Kohl I texted him on Twitter to learn more before he writes. 21 is young for some!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngridTwinkie   Hi Ingrid. Can you please follow me back?  I would really appreciate it. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mheatherly3 @tucsondelsol @charliekirk11 &amp; how about we check into HOW they got so wealthy "serving the public."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words to live by from @staceyabrams   “Don’t let anger undermine you, let it galvanize you”  #speakerlife… https://t.co/YifYKo9ljx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like the Arabian nights music  .. But it does remind me of the #Nutcracker a bit ...hmm🙇🏻‍♀️. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Superviso… https://t.co/QL0qKJTuJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campbellsl Is she holding a laptop in her other arm? (Seeing a new version of Lady Liberty. Lamp and tablet became sword and typewriter.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantCardone It’s never for America - in politics. Only us patriots are for America. Bring politics in and it ruins everything...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t often see good, healthy marriage advice out there. This is really sound, meaty advice!  Going on 30 years w… https://t.co/3mDADJHeT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[All collegiate athletes have talent. W/out it they wouldn’t be a college athlete. Right?  I’m a firm believer the w… https://t.co/eKZrPnHVhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one of those things you hope to only experience once if at all during your lifetime: Had to call a person w… https://t.co/GMHxTjp9N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to have been part of this amazing panel to celebrate #internationalwomensday at caterpillarinc. Just go do… https://t.co/PaZEMIYbh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re telling me that @mulaney watches #TheBachelor then I am telling you I have never been more here for anyth… https://t.co/V2xRX2Q1dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to be adding another nephew to my family! #teamboy💙 @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/FioVa1qhCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeineckeLibrary @YCAL_JWJ So many interesting activities! I wish I was closer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SoBe Love 💕 • • • #itsAnnastesia #SoBe #BeachLife #SoloTravel #Miami #SouthBeach #305 #BlackTravel #Blogger… https://t.co/rdXpIm2VzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t worn make up in 6 years but after watching every @JeffreeStar makeup video, I want to do my makeup everyday… https://t.co/c42Q6YvRcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angel_lovaticxo @BadBloodSeries @KimFCoates @netflix @markmontefiore @MichaelKonyves Yesssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly don’t tell me bad news till it’s something serious bc deadass I will haunt myself with bad outcomes for the rest of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beware if you go to cosmetology school they’ll make you stay with a 100 degree fever. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was great seeing you today @ScheleenTX And I love this bold color by @Hello_Lipslut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraGiura1 @dbongino @realDonaldTrump I've been a Dem all my life. Seems to me that the Republicans have moved a… https://t.co/kAXxPka6tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC Go Ken! Suddenly temperament doesn’t matter? #HypocriteMuch She needs to stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a horrific scenario and a real national emergency. #buildgatewaynow @MayorsRvl @build_gateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so HYPER to teach you all about HyperDocs this year at #Teach4Gr8ness!!! Come join our session to hype up yo… https://t.co/2iSFQedQ4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept the challenge from @fourmonkeypress to post covers of seven books I love; no exceptions, no reviews- just… https://t.co/XChdjFF9o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[just had to wake up my mom bc my nephews father said my nephew had a temperature of 105.... (we checked and it was… https://t.co/r3lbE6XxzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@12bLAxx Maybe that is it... such a pity. Now I have 4 packages left that I will not be eating. Guess I could leave… https://t.co/j0lAnhmkFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E1r0yy_ My mans fucking drooled all over my head top. Like sleep with your mouth closed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimBridenstine - sustainable return to the moon. #Moon2Mars @NASASocial]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole situation is so messed up. I hope this doesn’t call actual hate crimes in the future as “something that… https://t.co/LJNeuSVCqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfrutando lo que me encanta🌎 y tu estas en lo que te gusta hacer o porqué no tienes otra opción  "Viva una vida q… https://t.co/lctP4aBqoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one talk to me today because @QueenHattieJean and I are going to see @MarinaDiamandis in September and IM SO FRE… https://t.co/zyRq9fo698]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so intensely uncomfy by modern AUs that remove a layer of separation to reality by giving fictional characters… https://t.co/jTKehXs5Mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @BachelorInterns where can a girl shop these group date bench pillows? #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[A million % YES 9n about 50 crime since running for office and a 100 before then. He has cheated hundreds out of mi… https://t.co/9xq7HCxxYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell do the reputed Mitt Romney for?? He doesn’t even realize he’s a Republican.... flip-flop loser!]]></document></documents></author>