<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ready for one of the coldest nights of my life! #cold #Motorcycle #BikeLife #Travel #Grapevine #LosAngeles @ Grapev… https://t.co/v98inM1g4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAndrad10869585 @oleomorato @jairbolsonaro Os maiores estudiosos do mundo, nunca foram p uma universidade. Por iss… https://t.co/lQklgZ57sU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mweeden11 @JussieSmollett You people wtf I never said he wasn’t wrong and iam not placing the blame on anyone but… https://t.co/88nPBbOXee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just love AOC. She compares the Berlin Wall ( which was built to keep people in ) to the border wall ( me… https://t.co/UcdgbOkJ0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Everyone!!!  Here's today's bonus word... :)  -- -- Follow my other media…and be kind and patient beca… https://t.co/aFQ89G4pty]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a bag that's in good shape besides the zipper. Where can I get that replaced?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newsobserver This was such a weird episode of The Andy Griffith Show 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBarnsy Com'on...what's  the big deal? It's only 9 zeroes. https://t.co/7OJyriWhhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duck getting cut off at the beer garden. #goducks #oregon @ Matthew Knight Arena https://t.co/6GHCuJKWkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I solely started listening to @KaceyMusgraves bc of the Selena cover and this shit slaps   https://t.co/vKpkS5WPHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[C'est une chose effrayante de tomber entre les mains du Dieu vivant.      -Saint Paul https://t.co/pjHtWjDiAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sgtstumpy @StuartNHousePA @Independent Doesnt matter. She was secretary of state and ran for president and was never held accountable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmon1112 @Cernovich @SpeakerPelosi And Nancy said "Happy Halloween,"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Co-worker gave me some cold-fighting daytime Alka-Seltzer deal and now my left eye is twitching and I'm having a re… https://t.co/SfvJgQjxQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowWhite7IAM @EsotericExposal May our ears be opened to hear.  May our eyes be opened to see. May our minds be fr… https://t.co/l3KR6EZ0tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many won't remember this and many don't even know this, but MJ once wore number 12 in a 1990 game against the Orlan… https://t.co/EklL7pxfwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cecilejanssens The beauty of this for 23andMe is that if one is flagged as high risk as a child, you probably woul… https://t.co/j9WWfmLcMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeeamfam @WendydarlingT @brightfutureguy @Shamusroan13 @gentlemanvet67 @WarrenWattles @Mr_Spikey_Head @fu_dad… https://t.co/CJhFqWjhdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler How about we take a look at Barry’s college records and probably Communist writings?]]></document><document><![CDATA[if we go to an art gallery together all I’ll be looking at is you because.. ur baby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan just named to DeepDish Football Class of 2022 players to watch in Illinois. Make it happen, Ryan!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope he can parlay this to head of EPA, but that's his absolute best case]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southernfriedJ @dbongino @DonaldJTrumpJr I have to laugh at how the GOP always thinks they are more patriotic than… https://t.co/jxDUjzy3vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit I just watched dumplin on Netflix. Not good. It’s a movie where the main character is awful and everyone… https://t.co/RB7ujoV5Hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents who want the best for their kids it's important to understand the the difference between talent 🏀identifier… https://t.co/Optrw7s3Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerogan Hey buddy. Thank you for the extra long session with Alex. You've really made my work day fun good sir.… https://t.co/1I3AHjyj2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@third_husband Right now there is not a ton of credible evidence against her. The stuff that has come out has been… https://t.co/CpnVFPSGOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nate_Hale @Futureof55 @TravisAustinWV Nearly all evidence shows that, overall, charter schools are not only ineffe… https://t.co/tPW3dmuSDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas Was it pushed back? My code wont work for DC. Come on Rob]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Africans are not children in need of Western enlightenment when it comes to the church's sexual ethics, the Re… https://t.co/xJvVc89AXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greatkubuki @THR Marvel fans gonna go no matter what.  Let’s see the final numbers in a few weeks. I’ll never see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizcontreras24 One of my friends LOOOOVES short guys.....we always joke each other.......it's cool....... whatever..ya know...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VezoVezir She played the melody .. he's playing the guitar parts .. both, amazing :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday son! Very proud of you! 3 days! Raider up! https://t.co/4X8LLfBhqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy and Daddy first night out-out! 🙏🏽 thank you to the best titi and tio out there for holding the fort down toni… https://t.co/tWLH7A7vHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) “It sounds like one of the more blatantly unethical acts I’ve seen recently. That’s just ridiculous,” Wood said.… https://t.co/QouWKCFeeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm watching The Blacklist and earning great rewards from #viggle #TheBlacklist @NBCBlacklist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to know @NC_Governor is diligently working hard for the people of NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTopGrant I think I started the manager mode when he was having that rough run. His stats made no sense to me, s… https://t.co/bThJ4X9R4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartTesla @jchen5588 If I was the business owner i definitely wouldn’t appreciate this behavior. Especially in a… https://t.co/068i1hAuHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minnesota going hard after #iubb handoffs and have gotten IU called for 2 offensive fouls because of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyGeorge36 @MMAFighting I had to look again, but it seems like Ben still has the W. Let me know when they change it to .5 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur As always, the older one gets, the wiser. Except for journalists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I moved to the west coast to take chances and fully pursue my passions. And that's exactly what I plan on doing. Ha… https://t.co/LaCz8TcjiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Accuses Clinton of Deliberately Losing Election So He Could Be Impeached https://t.co/2d9kSEFg9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreatestBrand No, for the fueler doing more than just fueling the car.  Taping and repairing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many POS systems out there which don't support Apple Pay. I wonder how many support contactless credit… https://t.co/GC7cEt9TV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all the MHS teachers for taking the time to engage with parents tonight.  We appreciate all that you do f… https://t.co/FWX8EhOCVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMSupdates @KyleBusch No he can root for him self , he might not do that https://t.co/hhQOJBHNR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to phillypridebasketball G Jamir Reed on passing the 1000 career point milestone! He finished the game wit… https://t.co/yyjtBGY4Vg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear scam phone calls. You're likely to achieve more success if you don't call your victims at 3 in the morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. It’s day 16 of the General Assembly’s 2019 session #kyga19. Here is the daily legislative calendar:… https://t.co/ySGaRSHfY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[People I know, but I’m not close to, are not friendly to me on the streets. I almost felt like it was somehow my fa… https://t.co/NHBI5UUAMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 7 Arcs unknown, but will almost certainly include the planned final arc, The Siege of Mandalore in which Ahs… https://t.co/0eRSFq09Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honduran and Nepalese migrants sue Trump administration for ending protected status program: Immigrant rights advoc… https://t.co/Vbk3fiIysl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progress not perfection.  It is about growth.  You did your job and deserve a pat on the back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuckin sickening, Gaga’s iconic wearing something so iconic. It werks. Nothing compares to her diamond heart though… https://t.co/BWMG441zMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adambellringer1 @Zander9899 @Nigel_Farage Bye then, and be sure to take your family with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the day here in beautiful Florida. It’s nice now but the rain is on it’s way. @ 5 Flags Speedway https://t.co/arvK4S2dpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key Biscayne Families in Paradise. Coldwell Banker Pet Adoption Booth was a huge success. Finding homes for pets an… https://t.co/DAODzoWZso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsPerkinsLib Christine thanks for attending. Hope you had a blast. #FDSInnovates #MWGSprizepatrol #MWGS @fdesignschool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it. Technically my local high school in the southwest part of Durham]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spokes_Murphy @Jeff_Sharon Major League Baseball better make sure Harper return to DC is broadcasted by ESPN or Fo… https://t.co/4urhecmLuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When in the U.P. - one must have a pasty! @ Dobber's Pasties https://t.co/MOFvW4lMmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VAGirlsmom @JaiNoelle01 @troyaccola That's awesome Katherine congratulations way belated]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great 2019 Planes of Fame Hanger Dance.  #planesoffame #hangerdanceplanesoffame #hangerdance #bigband #satindollz… https://t.co/RoWOSRWfZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrettclark @kerrizor Sure, it’ll cost more than a reserved instance, but spinning up one on-demand should be a q… https://t.co/M7SWxfjcon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to the week @NCC_Chamber for a talk by @SignCurve on National Security Implications of Cryptocurrencies… https://t.co/lzVBEcOTXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sumfatkid @yelmelnobrainer damn it i still need to play Forum Trajanum. it mocks me from my shelf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paige loves #Reading #MercyWatson @ArroyoMustangs @ RHR II https://t.co/3T4TkBSYu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.  Love it. - Drinking a Strange Stars by @OGgravity at @OGgravity  — https://t.co/gsEKmoB2mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you gave me $15 I’m 💯 buying a rice bowl at Moes. My Moes is no game. @Moes_HQ @BarstoolCuse #Cuse https://t.co/KE93e0J019]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is more interesting and more important. #RIP #RedWings #RealNews https://t.co/km3XiIRS92]]></document><document><![CDATA[#obamalegacyisajoke          Our astronauts are in RUSSIA to hitch a ride to the space station, because Obama shutd… https://t.co/UIbCV9Awl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile @MistyStrohl borders always been open, Americans are drug addicts, dirty american doctor sinthatic… https://t.co/EkknKDlyEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndresCubano_ If you know me, you know this isn’t true 😂 @AndresCubano_  reaching now]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, Hays [Ellis Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 5.00 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Plaskett finally getting to unleash all that energy behind her facial expressions! #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supmurph @jdevilb @jalenramsey Yeah Fournette appears to be super motivated. Got a tough schedule this year but I… https://t.co/uc5505o7lI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totalcurtis @BeesonOnBeer Sorry, Dudes...I take full responsibility for how dumb this thread has become. Goodnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets go on Sale this week || Special Guest will be announced this week #NSU #HamptonU #HU #ODU #MEAC… https://t.co/J0KZfiLdso]]></document><document><![CDATA[The saddest people care the most. Look around and see who really ask if your okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraketoU Jajajaja no mames ¿jugó bien? Esperate ahí en la 9 para ir a verguearte]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an absolutely fantastic and innovative story by @rachelleingang and worth your time.  I don’t hide my @ASU… https://t.co/HRkrglojzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arthurabland @mockingbirdbway @BillClinton @HillaryClinton They were conservative only in the sense that they want… https://t.co/ds9Zj31Voh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrewUnga @RunTheJules It’s unreal. After he announced the Knicks would be sold for 5 billion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu I’m shocked, absolutely shocked, that Erik Prince would’ve lied to the Congressional committee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fine! I guess I’m going to have to pay for @Showtime so I can watch this Bronx awesomeness...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trcfwtt It is a counter intelligence investigation so I think legally Rosenstein can lie when he says Trump is not… https://t.co/KAZcg5uscX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shaun12361257 @_dopedaneille @crazyjane125 @ZeffToke @migoodridge1 @kubagardener @SweetlySmiles @JoeVito12… https://t.co/iyhTNnVDz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just tryn My BEDT Self and look it too 🤷🏾‍♂️ #GM #HappyFriday #TGIF #DoYourBEST #BeYourBEST #WhateverItTakes… https://t.co/X89x97rpHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein I paid the money to the lawyer I waited the time For all the approvals Did everything right  we left… https://t.co/jDJhmKYpsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews Harvey Levin is a liar! Can’t remember the obscure website that they got their tip from..that’s bullshit!… https://t.co/bM5eS8amFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FIFAPlayerDJ Werner definitely getting boosted. Sancho won’t be boosted enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDBM @stephlam02 @SergeLvesque @envirosci_alex @wildforbees Thanks for capturing everything and the great tweets. Cheers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨🚨Spend $75 or more and receive 108 pcs golden desert charcoal and a coco flame burner coupon code (flame) @… https://t.co/E9Aw0dDbh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz Funny thing is it works both ways. We can see where mom is too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 5.30 km in 32m:56s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/cT90RT6k6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb 24th my first born was born. #FactsFromJay #ABlackManAndAFather https://t.co/ALlmzPA233]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lap 14/110 - EJ in for his first stop, also switching to blacks. He was running 8th. #FirestoneGP https://t.co/Z13dXKK6Ky]]></document></documents></author>