<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[That's right! That's why NYC went for @HillaryClinton by a landslide! @gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney… https://t.co/4lSEWL81jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ay personas que son medicina, que sanan, que iluminan, y les juro que él es una de ellas ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call me old fashioned, but I didn’t know it was cool to collect babies. Especially from broken families]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Hope you get censured in the house, a congressman that acts like this should be eliminated from government]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Love #tulips #SanAnselmo @ M.H. Bread and Butter https://t.co/IjPQQemtkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkelly Welp. I suggest you start rehearsing Feeling on Yo Booty because rumor has it rapists don’t do well in jail… https://t.co/lmXImDisc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy me preguntaron si era la mamá de Mira y Sarah.. mm las amo but thank u, next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fjaviersilvag @arielortegaj1 @yeidckol @CiroGomezL @Radio_Formula @lopezobrador_ No.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @lizzieohreally @jaketapper Were you crushed to learn that the Earth doesn’t revolve around your ego?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a dollar for every time someone said that Ohio is terrible while I’m in the room, I would be rich. In fact… https://t.co/3AspPz0PBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agamanimukherj1 Hi Diya I'm good getting. A lil tired it's 3am here in the US but I just can't seem to log out of Twitter 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I have a bet with my son that he will do time and my son says he wont there is no justice in this world unless… https://t.co/4btYAI5wd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You will NEVER be criticized by someone who is doing more than you. You will only be criticized by someone doing less.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not even 730 am and I’ve already been called “m’lady” twice. I need to go back to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only hope that we never lose sight of one thing — that it was all started by a mouse. - #waltdisney ✨🌎 @ The El C… https://t.co/yX3QuIQPe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to YouTube link below, then go sign petition! Millions already have! Let’s strip Congress of their power and set… https://t.co/L95XT8G5AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is called murder. You’re saying women take home their babies and murder them?  Is this a Russian Bot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Maria CA Tue Feb 26th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Rain Lo 50 WEDNESDAY Rain Hi 56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, nope, niet, negative, never that. That looks like the fucking ride from spy kids that juggles the kids or some… https://t.co/NuHEwJxKLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum oh sure - with the money Trump has already stolen from the fund for that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mvukovcan @MarkMaddenX But did media know everything back then or is it being leaked now by Steelers personnel/pla… https://t.co/M0HYgHC8gA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrebsProfessor @corybarlog I was raised on: The Bible, Star Wars and Pasta 📖 💫 🍝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marischeidegger @raaafa_u eu tbm, to mt decepcionada pq to firme e forte nos exercícios, e fiquei nessa de comer u… https://t.co/8IP3ofxqUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so excited to reveal this year's University of Akron Press #poetrylives button design! Stop by our table at… https://t.co/6jRGAl1wy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t believe anything IQ45 says, period.  He lies even when the truth serves his best interests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #nationalmargaritaday! 🤷🏽‍♀️ @ Hard Rock Cafe Atlantic City https://t.co/UfL6gnwL5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my friend and fellow @PLSprogram Scholar, Lucy, for her hard work on behalf of #CriminalJusticeReform]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooooooo!  @metmuseum manuscript leaf with Initial O, from an antiphonary (15thc) #medievaltwitter https://t.co/7N6du5oZhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRock @nbc @nbctitangames @8pm What up with that Gray I know it doesn't matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heat in my car is currently not working so that makes this -12°F commute a lot more interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[After some persuation, my good buddy and badass #Synthwave #Producer @destryur is now on twitter. So you better fol… https://t.co/Bej0w3gabZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[More good @ExhibitCityNews ink for Cobo Center’s #susty and #CSR: https://t.co/lRzhtSy7SU #venues #sustainability… https://t.co/IVoRSOkFUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why I’m out here traveling like I got money like that. SOS these student loans have offically kicked in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya’ll see that bright beautiful sun?! I feel things are on the come up and I can already feel a difference in my mood 😌☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...he provided an individual in the DTO with CBP sensor locations, the locations of unpatrolled roads at or near t… https://t.co/U2AXRsipAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackishWriters @SecretaryCarson @kilmeade #BlackHistoryEpisode 2/26/19 ScriptBIASag/Dr.BenCarson! He'sMoreThanBra… https://t.co/Tq4yfUSjCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just thinking Avon💟*https://t.co/s88lSmxaKS Orders in Tuesday March 5th Shop by *eStore 24 hours Call for brochure(… https://t.co/OTbXbBAXm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomas_today @PeteReweetsDogs @HoneyRamblings @gucci @FancyPenguinP @abonniebon I thought paul was the one tweeting… https://t.co/dbw7FxdLW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the best, I'm living my life! I'm speak my mind but I'm good. Everything I just cooperate in my stories]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my HerbaSisters last night at #BGRfest was sooo much fun but your girl is feeling it 😆😜😜. To stop the… https://t.co/Kh8FsXPlQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt da melhor montanha russa de todas! 🐶🤟 . . . #florida #orlando #disney #disneysprings  #waltdisney… https://t.co/uMximJGZfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Mom: Claire, never touch a cactus, they’re very pokey.   My Dad: Claire, be careful around cacti, you can’t touc… https://t.co/VFZqEMpRpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Billbrowder @DenbrotS Tulsi Gabbard is a Republican posing as a Democrat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC You are wrong, wrong, wrong. You are bad for our country. Sit down and shut up. Asylum seekers are… https://t.co/a0PuEhnrsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @iamRuthECarter @theblackpanther Love her and such an inspiring speech!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think Devin Booker maybe a bit overrated? If so, then why? Asking because someone in the gym feels he is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instructedby @RealSaavedra @DonaldJTrumpJr He did disavow Duke.  I don't know where you guys come up with this non… https://t.co/TQYL7iwzV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another value high-end diy project! 👌☺  *floating shelves: from amazon 3 for 12.99 *articles on the shelves 1.00 do… https://t.co/hi0fXhaXJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out one of my love poems here:   #love #poetry #relationships #truelove #heart #hearts #lover #poem #poems… https://t.co/jjq4l2p2x7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen  Harder buildin' trust from a distance  I think we should rule out commitment for now  'Cause we’re fallin' apart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@walterbatler Women are the most possibility packed people! You’re fired ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poor_lux_life our mission is to not end up like the kid in the grey shirt lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. and China said to appear close to deal to roll back tariffs https://t.co/AR3VjC7oiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving this #blacklight number! I am adding this to my rounds! Where would you like to see @torahiman next? Comment… https://t.co/cYRezYqyQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulu can you pls put season 17 of Hell’s Kitchen on Hulu so I can watch more of @ChefChristinaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[And everyone who calls on the name of the Lord will be saved. Acts 2:21]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert covered with snow❄️❄️❄️so pretty😀 heading to work by Rainbow and oquendo #VegasSnow https://t.co/AGwEhTr1Hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeman1313 @niksnook57 @ProudResister @realDonaldTrump These people don't even care how this looks to the public. It's baffling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our normally quite little creek😳 #abc7eyewitness https://t.co/7rP5rEaNVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KittyBhagat @Communista2 @QuietManc @bunkybun @Dennis_Lintz @haloefekti @lilith2u @BlakandBlack @deeshanger… https://t.co/wc2Y3x92ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune into @ProShopGolfShow on @ESPNDallas today from 9-10 am. Special guest @TotheMan Tournament Dir. from the Char… https://t.co/WAgqHPre8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to personally thank @Windstream for making me super late to work because apparently every single one of th… https://t.co/JgcR8V4FLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the best banquet last night celebrating the amazing accomplishments of our swimmers and divers for the 2018-… https://t.co/rkVhpe6Awi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so The Lonely Island are going on tour again but so far they’ve only announced dates for east coast and midwes… https://t.co/1LaustQEp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TulsiGabbard IS LYING.  She was standing right alongside her father when he supported conversion therapy.  to say… https://t.co/yjl0IWW7nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[what goes thru somebody head when they do heroin for the first time lmfaoo  “i’ll just try one small hit pls” 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey did I tell y’all I fucked @AllanaMaePromo while I was in Vegas? Well I did 😍  A hot sexy sex scene coming out s… https://t.co/UKqgVf0QYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks when your favorite boys are in your town and you know exactly where they are working.(which never happens)… https://t.co/xzFkJ9pGKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not Catholic, or religious for that matter, but I always give up something for lent &amp; I always regret it 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Galentines Day tell me what these songs all have in common https://t.co/xoQrJ32yiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsHackCA @DominicSeifert @AstrosKyle @07reddevilz @TH3_GOAT_ https://t.co/6JPmOoXEkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seuls_ensemble the fender ppl seeing ahj give away two guitars in one night https://t.co/iVx4Y4jv1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppSame @realDonaldTrump But, what about those guys with the tiki torchs, polo shirt, and khaki pants?  Talking ab… https://t.co/HK19Hemm8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brokebackstan Wow can’t believe maya liked one of your tweets you’re an icon!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2472snowyowl @NLL @TomSchreiber26 @TorontoRockLax @Top_ched83 @SealsLax Wow that says a lot coming from a Bandits… https://t.co/n1xTgP0IoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The source magazine has so much old content up as their featured stories... everything okay over there @TheSource?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Umbralwalker @theYJfiles @OneShotNetwork @EncounterRP @TheRpgAcademy @DMs_Block @DontSplitThePod @CreationCast… https://t.co/OS553wQCG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[On International Women’s Day, learn how to say your female identifying co-worker’s name correctly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck yes. Let’s get that fucker @realDonaldTrump outta office. He’s a racist. A cheat and a conman!!! He’s doesn’t… https://t.co/XbEa5bLV4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioYeg Just an update. I will be interviewed today at 11:35am live on @AM900CHML to discuss my daughters story o… https://t.co/DdcWQffo4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris What an ungrateful "B" UR https://t.co/6bNwIYYU7D @DonaldJTrumpJr @invanka_trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I love about my husband is that he is always listening to EPCOT entrance/park music and/or music on the Disney Parks channel. ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW55 @NASCARONFOX @FS1 @JimmieJohnson @adam1alexander @KevinHarvick THAT WAS FANTASTIC  BOOM CONFETTI JOHNSON  IS A NATURAL  😎☝️👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remember to add the #Alcor_RYS19 every time you tweet though. Let it become a habit #Alcor_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where do these people come from that want to be rid of all Confederate statues and history,  if that's what you wan… https://t.co/zpLN773Wjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tacobell really needs to bring back the Zesty Chicken Border Bowl or I’m gonna have to keep making orders that loo… https://t.co/C8CFuDllJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[John 1:1-3    In the beginning was the Word, and the Word was with God, and the... https://t.co/pQ0Rr6bS5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Xunta de Galicia: No al sacrificio de los jabalíes de Lugo - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/7aaIjrenjp via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly why I post my messy sketchbook drawings. 🤷‍♀️Great discussion in the comments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catsrgreen Nah, I'm used to it. She can pet all the animals she wants as long as she always comes home to me and Livy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important new work from my @sju_english @stjohnsartssci @StJohnsU colleague @ShanteParadigm]]></document><document><![CDATA[earlier i really was about to start crying on the subway over these ticket sales and then emily said hang on, that’… https://t.co/xwaRO1sVJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s -40 at the top of the mountain , I take back what I said. I’m not riding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poohnash Oh Miss Pooh...way to work with it!! Does it make you hungry though?! My issue with it in the past is the munchies!!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[TV addict. #BuffyD is into sitcoms, comedy, and of course smash, while Faith is more into adventure and dramas.… https://t.co/EySAKd7wlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michell84761434  Good morning beautiful I thank God for you it was a devine appointment to meet the way we did have a blessed day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going to be an amazing couple of days.  Learning about what's best for gifted kids from experts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re telling me that it is 15 degrees outside and it didn’t even snow????🤬 https://t.co/NiS9k4AvlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilkins_siobhan @BachelorABC @colton Back when PageantGate was happening.. producers teased that “one is fake and… https://t.co/DYbegRhtHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy siendo discriminada y a la vez beneficiada por ser mujer. No like !]]></document></documents></author>