<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Also #ThrowbackThursday to that one time a friend and I went to @sweetdazetx while I was on hiatus. You can’t stop… https://t.co/L8n1TJbc5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milliemangoes That's not a good comment.  If someone tryed it they tryed it. It doesn't make them that for the rest of their life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m still wanting to know if she had work done because .... idk why but she looks different ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS Mia is an evil, jealous bad A$$!Cannot trust her! Today she pulls off the biggest lie to save her butt!… https://t.co/j74jUdZ4tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 Time for a woman. The last one was cheated out of her rightfully elected seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATA in the House - studying the draw with tips from Coach Norm! #ataresults https://t.co/iZMaUbNhrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen. Y’all know I love Spielberg, but to say that he doesn’t want Netflix films to be eligible for the oscars ju… https://t.co/m2Qw4H4EPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Controlling every movement the teachers do in their classroom shows the lack of trust on the teachers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep cracking myself up like fuck why’d I have to be the funniest person I know, conflict of interest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulaneAthletics seems odd that when you go to the site that the item shows up as “preorder “ but yet is sold out a… https://t.co/mLsqIVHe4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Weird_Dana I hate it when I do that!  Hopefully you will be able to snooze a little bit on the plane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what a good day looks like . . . #younglivingessentialoils #younglivingdeliveryday #oilsfordays @ Kirksvill… https://t.co/YIMPhCTfdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have been in bed for 24 hours and havent seen the sun in a week . worried abt my wellbeing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there really people like this in the world? Like... real life? There’s no way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta wait for this bowel movement to pass so imma be up another hour probably]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NebraskaAlumni Happy Wednesday! Did you see that Life and Nothing More is screening in Lincoln this weekend at the… https://t.co/agTB5pjR6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu Aww, what’s a little white lie, or the biggest pile of crap ever.  All the same to me and the cult.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Thank god for the people in my life they make sure I’m good everyday ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenbookmovie was just phenomal😔 I hope I never make any colored friend's blue white purple etc feel that way..… https://t.co/ONdyscvmID]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 2 assignments and 2 papers standing between me and Panama City. I may just get them all done tonight, stay tuned]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY She’s great. There’s a terrific British police drama on Netflix she’s in - Broadchurch. Just wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irina Shayk should win an award for her role for having to sit between Bradley and Gaga #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all my fellow New Yorkers...Don’t forget to vote tomorrow! https://t.co/haJXCHRZlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great W 💪💪 @HartfordWBB @CoachKimUHart  - on to the next! #HawksUp #CapitalCityTeam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIAnderson3 @AardFourFour @AkishaGarcia2 @alexmontejano52 @allen_realtalk @AllisonWhiteLee @american2084… https://t.co/EYlkMYnTEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethan (10): “There is a 99.96% chance that you will get married.” Laurel (7): “No.  I will say no to boys.” Ethan:… https://t.co/3UlddwTMmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing - and I mean nothing - on this planet is as cute as a baby wearing a fluffy bear onesie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissy40697285 @thehill Everyone has biases. To think that only impartial and unbiased people work in the judicia… https://t.co/gLPIi2HgoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋💋💋 #pepper #peppersinger #brooklyn #newyork #kiss #vibes #woman @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/foBPt6QEev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LosDez @Complex They are made by a different baker. The savanna smiles are this bakers lemon cookie. Each council… https://t.co/SHywzltkgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgiving can be such a hard thing to do but we have to keep in mind that if we don’t forgive those who hurt us or… https://t.co/g9dwGgcR3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half of the coffee drinkers in coffee-loving Seattle wouldn’t know what that kind of coffee tastes like.  In fact,… https://t.co/1etqhvg73N]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. I’ve got her. Her dads got her. She is loved here and even though she’s gotta grow up so fast, she is capable of… https://t.co/elareYOjx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting excited!! The webinar! @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/TZvBJNQKnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we know why Donald Trump is such an expert in lurid details of sex trafficking (especially duct tape).  Turns o… https://t.co/fuspKvghDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live finished product!  "As long as she leaves refreshed." @ Hera Salon https://t.co/qnMllJ1FhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish the vending machine at my job had chocolate milk :( i really want chocolate milk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePurpleHand @mjs03093641 @ZandEDad @ScorpioNan71 @peggyzab @greyeyed87 @maxi_fabulous @pippasykes154… https://t.co/3cDiUdVhUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[First @ColoradoRapids game Definitely worth braving the elements! #Rapids96 #SnowClasico3 https://t.co/U8dSJrmlma]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of our friends are married with kids and our running guest list is currently 252 people https://t.co/OWHtrieOUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[ETGs Very Own kevyloso - Recipe #etg #everythingtogain #recipe @ Bridgeport, Connecticut https://t.co/cpEY47mmJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men say shit like this but if a man drugged them and raped them they’d have a huge problem with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️NYC. Here my print, “Walking Through Times Square” where I attempt to capture the feel of walking through the m… https://t.co/79iIo8rEnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity She left. She should stay with her new “family.”  I suppose she took them “ for better or worse,”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Transportation &amp; Ticket Center (TTC) - @waltdisneyworld in Bay Lake, FL https://t.co/rUQv2lpARI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand80760480 @Cantero9Vega @angsala67 @szalacain1 @mainzina @LilianaSnchez9 @jobragag Linda tarde Fer y amigos… https://t.co/jrrGdNyraI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling a lil too chunky for emo nite to already be tomorrow again ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world and happy hump day.  Don't forget to share a smile and always be kind to one another.  😇 https://t.co/QcV3q1uGEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weartv @nwfdailynews REMEMBERING PARKLAND - Today marks the one-year anniversary of the shooting at Marjory Stonem… https://t.co/mSi17Q2fx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanShieldm @James_rwnat @_88MilesPerHr You are an obnoxious woman who hides behind an avatar and some sort of… https://t.co/GG9sCZ5GCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_freeayo You HATED Eeyore!?? I had a stuffed animal of him that always got to sleep on top of the bed so he wouldn… https://t.co/GKlSswSQ79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who got Venmo and PayPal so I can send you money on the Venmo and you send it back to me on paypal I lost my Venmo… https://t.co/gXBplraAqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RikkiHernandez5 @blakeshelton @NBCTheVoice @nbctitangames @TheRock me too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmm!!! nothingbundtcakesaustin provided this #delicious alternative to traditional #weddingcake - very tasty!… https://t.co/PwfyxGuuJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna reserve comment on this right now....and btw, I communicate better when you don't talk trashy.  Just sayi… https://t.co/mI9gi23Ksp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rarb221 @washingtonpost Stop pretending that this behavior, sexual assault, is about a relationship. It is about p… https://t.co/HT7ew79leg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @Tomprorok1 @realDonaldTrump @nbcsnl Fox News pundits should actually read the Constitution and read it to… https://t.co/OkO4dtv4r5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen Joel Love ❤️ you . I love that you have wisdom from God to talk about . I know you read the Bible, I am… https://t.co/DsVf6TJbFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Date with this handsome boy #boymom @ Chick-fil-A The Ridge https://t.co/aM0tpuMipa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopping on the new BO4 update with @deannaonfire_ who needs 9 followers to reach that 50 for affiliate!  Pop in and… https://t.co/v5G0wj5lWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CecilyTynan Wow! It seems like March has been our snowiest month the last few years. I remember when I was little,… https://t.co/acqjd3EY6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePTraffic Did you hear your wife saw my parents the other night? Well, according to my dad’s text they saw “Mik… https://t.co/y8c3Ka6aW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy for you anezka!! You deserve this more than anyone knows. I love you💕 I knew you were gonna make it !!… https://t.co/q2Et21WBz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[IHOP: Please Flip Us Some Vegan Pancakes for National Pancake Day! https://t.co/bgw13xcyfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femmeliberacion Ya know... So they can make mommy creme brulee 4 dessert]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should’ve pulled an #allstars4 and had a tie for best actress because Glenn Close was ROBBED!  #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Dutch Treat Restaurant in Spartansburg, PA https://t.co/PQr3afX5AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird It is unbelievable how long it takes Trump supporters to wake up to the scams being putting on this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itskaitbabe @gabriellaleef @AdrianH018 @hippyjohnnykat Okay so do you believe that man was being homophobic and discriming them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream I went shoe shopping with @garyvee in Detroit, he was giving me advice. Unfortunately I don’t remember it. 🙈Happy Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @jamesonandbeers @The_Fool_Monty @8MillionML SMH you people are crazy. I kind of like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow.  Nothing like shutting down free speech!  But is it free soeach when you are in his building??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueinRockville @TeamPelosi @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @GOP #DitchMitch #DitchMitch #DitchMitch #DitchMitch #DitchMitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KSeattleWeather @NWSSeattle A few flakes hitting Kent East Hill. Just a few. You could walk quickly and not have a flake land on you. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WattersWorld @RepMattGaetz @JesseBWatters Hey Jesse,  U guys know what all this means? Or do u take a pass bc it's… https://t.co/sRt6pPffb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to share this fabulous art chair with you! 👊🏻🙋🏼‍♀️ love it #interiordesign #chair #art @ Folsom, California https://t.co/kaKwYFJIlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop fuckin playin like I’m one of these regular lil dumb bitches you used to tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @MalcolmNance #MSNBC OMG Common sense has come to Congress! What will the do-nothings do now? BTW Tha… https://t.co/NRu88sD0B6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too controversial?  Have they actually heard of our heroes, such as Harriet Tubman, Malcolm X, Rosa Parks?  The con… https://t.co/gbY75zf9ex]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate is getting dick downed rn... must be nice https://t.co/UtizzY89so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edvonbev @KellyannePolls Ur bigotry lens is so thick that u cannot see anything else. If u've watched the entire v… https://t.co/2CewWzSYLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[live recording of me singing the song of my people https://t.co/JruAjQZV9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Hotel California Radio on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/WSMWlagQ9h https://t.co/dKnQrH0dp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uneasy because when I called to make a reservation today my iPhone did the thing before they picked up and I heard… https://t.co/eOO5YFwpQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Yoda afraid of seven?  Because six seven eight.  😂 (Cinema teacher humor)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classroom Kleenex are going fast. This flu, runny noses, allergies are waging a serious battle in room 237.  Come o… https://t.co/2mKhK2CS5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes people won’t say the good things about you publicly but they will tell you privately and that made me hap… https://t.co/FUViWqpQvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigNasty14SHR @CopaCavanna @FrankVelat @TonyStewart @alexb__19 @ClaireBLang @JerryJordan_KTT Oh that’s right! And… https://t.co/zIpsiAicai]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad. Sharpstown Mall was THE place to go after school and Saturdays.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when u lay down for a quick 20 min power nap but remember the 8 page paper, lab, blog posts, 4 responses and a grou… https://t.co/DbAtFa78C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalesoftheCork @winetraveleats @GrnLakeGirl @Fiery01Red @SteveKubota @suziday123 @magee333 @always5star… https://t.co/XZCCOOVK6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[going to try burrito boyz for the first time..... thinking about @brendan905]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich: Pelosi’s grip slips as Ocasio-Cortez and friends throw a party, leave the grandparents at home  https://t.co/rmpf5mrbhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many people are whining hahha not me I’m grinding the pavement , I’m hustlin and making things happen. I’m very… https://t.co/CS7gYXU3TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! Have a great day! @ Nurillo, Texas https://t.co/UkH9hLd9Th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary to ME!!! #AmericanAirlines #LoveMyJob https://t.co/C5j5ORFUNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don’t tell me they shooting out here...already having a hard time going to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilovethandoh @Bibo_George @nkosincobela @SyahShandu I saw this video a week ago. Ngithi mina usashona😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesjawa @halfmoth @ek_johnston @MystGalaxyBooks Aw, shucks! https://t.co/jqmlzmTOx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never in my life did I even consider I'd see this in live action...life is complete now...I'm good...bury me right… https://t.co/jFDZJCeMaY]]></document></documents></author>