<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HotavioH Great match... figured it would end in a draw. Live streamed it on my Instagram for a few people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Security Clearance Process Is About to Get Its Biggest Overhaul in 50 Years https://t.co/UawNEijJhq via @Nextgov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VargasJrJockey you remember when you were making fun of me because Celtics got beat against Bulls ? .... What happ… https://t.co/nX5XG3c92T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewSiteRadio @WWMRSportsRadio @bshields0244 @DJournalPreps It was Northside/East Webster boys and East Webster won… https://t.co/evNPCypWzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @OneMileataTime, what should @andrewvarda do about this lunacy? Best way to be compensated by @AmericanAir?? An… https://t.co/FitSIFxarZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[be the #robe of #Christ https://t.co/fEEVjaYosM #Jesus #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/qzOttF3fjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchovden1785 @cbrangel I hope so, I wish Charlie was there to throw the taxes in his face, but I’ll take this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our mission is to provide the most helpful, friendly, unbiased wireless solutions to every visitor, at every touch… https://t.co/eeJfFfOqww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halobreakerrr That's how it works when your President, if I was him I would not want my wife hurt either, but the… https://t.co/AzRsR7lbeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at BioReference Laboratories, Inc. in Elmwood Park, NJ https://t.co/wxKerNmITK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandarees9 Voyager “Non Sequitur”, TNG “Family”, DS9 “Homefront” and “Paradise Lost”, TOS “The Conscience of the King”]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you try to help yourself I'll help you, but I ain't never liked a bum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like the first day of spring training and I already really miss Joe Kelly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But as I was saying... if I worshipped me--which I don't-- I would just ... what??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AiG The first responsibility of a parent or a grandparent is to tell their children the truth. If at some future t… https://t.co/fW2yGHb0cS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luis Miguel is my second favorite singing voice. That voice is beautiful as a mother fucker!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entregando una  de mis obras el Lic. Roberto Rosas en Toma de Compromiso al  Lic. @GilbertoFimbres @CoparmexTijuana… https://t.co/34YWg0IQkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those bounty hunters. The product of a third grade education. #Catitstu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Golgari story is even worse, @GLHFMagic - the kraul actually won, but the lich named two winners (which was nev… https://t.co/BABeyoGZt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I didn’t really like the movie, I kind of want a Spectre ring🐙 https://t.co/FGMDTneqfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped pin Near 5948-5924 W 3rd St, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/oz6ibWyxNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Money was continuously publishing papers about the experiment and labeling it a complete success, which… https://t.co/H81ODiSI0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martibatres @donainesdsuarez Señor. Le deceo que sigua trabajando para un mexico mejor algun dia bolbere. Alpueblo… https://t.co/YZdtBfjemK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Broome @charmcitylwy I think they believe (thought?) Americans would be harsher on their own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov and Mayor mad. Tech people mad. Real estate developers mad. 🤣 #nycisnotseattle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brody got his mounts today and was super excited can’t say thanks enough to Triple Drop Outfitters @HecCanales… https://t.co/dBcQ7Vo9o6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff #AdamSchiff you have to be the most out of touch disingenuous politicians ever! congratulations 😳. E… https://t.co/i1EEeMnr6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @other98 with get_repost @ New York, New York https://t.co/25bqzAvZlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t say this very often but FUCK YOU MOTHER NATURE YOU FUCKING FUCK!!! I ALWAYS STICK UP FOR YOU AGAINST ALL TH… https://t.co/LUmVdt2HTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton "TRYING TO INCLUDE MORE STATEMENTS &amp; STATEMENTS TO EXPAND THE "CRIMINALITIES OF DJT &amp; ADMIN." ANDY STOP THE BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKalebMorris Bills was rumors. They shut it down the same night they leaked. Still crazy what the raiders got him for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hot_shoe_pics All acts of love, kindness is a start in the right direction. Well said @hot_shoe_pics we all need t… https://t.co/15iTP88Ko3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what the @PTECHNETWORK is all about. Rock on @jayulia_   #BeEqual]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Verona982 @Saturnation8 @sonya_lala_ @ryanstruyk @AOC Trumps a con man and ur a dolt https://t.co/m0OvEJrEft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump ...to walk free from their known criminal activities that continue to plague our U.S. Constitutional society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@this_is_biggs @cecpetes @mkf @NBA You guys must not be researching, I win at least a few games almost every day, probably 5 times a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuriVanKenobi @ElMariachiNinja lamentablemente tienes razón, pero se escucha mejor "la banda es procrastinadora"]]></document><document><![CDATA[He playin w all of philly🤦🏻‍♂️ but i could only imagine if he came to the birds]]></document><document><![CDATA[first twitter~ one day I'll be in one of them!! https://t.co/hiMPCCgd1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is in a matrix system so achieve the necessities to be content and live your life to the fullest. #Simple]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is me coming off of anesthesia after my surgery I had! Enjoy it and make it go viral guys! 😂😂😂 https://t.co/cNNtYN3woz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradMossEsq @superlorna69 Ummm yeah. What was he doing signing a trump org check?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentonTemple That’s what I’ve been saying since I was 10. Guess better late than never for the rest of you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TProphet Are you getting injections? Or the oral version? Where are you going?  I just got my second Hep A/B shot… https://t.co/ovRSQs7z98]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuotedNevermore It works if you are trying to summon fire though.  Or firefighters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lavendrblonde @luvandstrife I love it for you that you love mike for loving someone else ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosedixontx @Airbornex82nd @AOC @terryatthebeach https://t.co/f2LdSMxdSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveofGod, “And this same God who takes care of me will supply all your needs from his glorious riches, which have… https://t.co/CPpPtJ1Kg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heat #35mmfilm #35mm #dirty35mm #nyc #nyctaxi #taxi @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/6NAjW7FdoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callowGuru I'm just making a inference based on how the community is split rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#twinpeaks fan girling ⛰🦉 #myloghassomethingtotellyou   #damngood #☕️ #🎰 #youllhavetospeakup 🕵️‍♂️ #doublerdiner #🥧… https://t.co/tjtikLDbJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! 10 whole damn years wtfff! Anyways it’s been fkn amazing so that’s t… https://t.co/ND7XKUX4OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliasvaughn It’s not witness tampering if they simply talked to a witness. There is no property in witnesses. Remember Perry Mason?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you everyday Lisa.. Find me somehow be in my life Lisa you're so special to me.. I really do love you Lisa I… https://t.co/AhIreFlAiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sak_shoes @rdickey249 I now rotate my burgers with blue cheese, Brie and smoked Gouda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks out from my first powerlifting competition.. cutting weight to 181 and doing my best to maintain strength… https://t.co/q6HPBzPsoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyTesla4Life @Model3Owners @teslaownersSV 1800 collect, it was a thing of beauty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to support alumnus Gustavo Camargos from our Summer 2018 Cohort speaking today @ @samaschoolorg conference in… https://t.co/twp5CPx1BJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown got exactly what he deserved and it’s funny as hell, good kick it Buffalo 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuzinskiGreg Awesome idea. I'm doing that this season. You'll get tired of seeing me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Sen Graham is right. He should use the televised interview tape prior to the hearing and have the transcri… https://t.co/4DMKEPLVBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlesadler @Puglaas Get real. There is no scandal. The new law passed last year allows the Attorney-General to o… https://t.co/Y4Bxv8Bq1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Herring1967 Can you comment on the theory that popular Canadian sport Curling in which stones are slid across ice… https://t.co/J2KhGesyh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mukhtar_Dotun So sad!!!  How did we as a people get here?  Every life is so precious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyyschiff @SamRobert78 @BernieSanders I just like trolling and providing no value https://t.co/eRhvhE7hW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn Jim got some troll in him 🍻🍻🍻, we know isn’t on that plane and that’s one Manny Machado #phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check it out! First song I’ve uploaded since like 2016 lol. https://t.co/ub7nvqxbHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaUniTracker Alabama’s Coach Jerry Zulli dons the Tide’s uniform combo for today’s DH opener against South Alaba… https://t.co/QrAqTwh4DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tider_Todd87 I spy a Shaw at Legion Field. Where I played many a Dental Clinic games for McAdory. 😂 https://t.co/xmS17jjX4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serrano5159 @chitofernando6 @ParkerMcCollum , get the man a iPhone and some air pods]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since the AS break Trae Young has lowkey been playing unbelievably well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denton, TX 4.5/5 stars! ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️✨ A friend told me about bubblewell in Denton and I hadn’t heard of it! 😱 I got a r… https://t.co/jalXkoLMi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcocuevas2001 @Reporte_Indigo @lopezobrador_ Si seguramente los 57 millones restantes son los que marcharon en c… https://t.co/Tb5JbQd5c0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianOlveraVA @tomqe @CapcomUSA_ @DevilMayCry @VoiceOfOBrien @johnnyyongbosch @ReubenLangdon @brihanford… https://t.co/ZHLXSOGmxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock #69/395 #hatwheres68  #lol @ West Town, Chicago https://t.co/4TpeIwFFop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleman_rhodie I’m dreaming right now that they will be public. That would really restore faith in our democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The longest it’s ever been #beardlife #beard #beardgang @ Springfield, Illinois https://t.co/mjXKWLNKVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savemejebus0 @KamalaHarris Showing you bias and hatred for anything different.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These pics at a rest stop in Arizona came out pretty decent so figured I'd post them 😁 https://t.co/rDRLRrtoXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s times I have great pride for the sunny beaches, luxurious lifestyle, and diverse culture Miami has]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched the True Detective finale instead of the Oscars and I have absolutely no regrets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me licking the peanut butter off the knife when I’m making a pb&amp;j https://t.co/WE2KsZ1ioq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you find this funny you have a quality sense of humor don’t listen to anyone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about women and engagement by our very own @__Winsome #WomenEngaged #HappyInternationalWomensDay #UAlbany https://t.co/Les3YY9U7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johniadarola @thedailybeast He should be prosecuted for earlier crimes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing out All-Star with TNT.... @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/9eihuoY6em]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are your Valentines Day Plans?  Do you celebrate it in a special way or just an ordinary day for y’all?… https://t.co/XCqem5QRR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s going to be wind chills of -20 tomorrow and i ain’t ready for this https://t.co/wcFncfu8UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @RepSeanMaloney @RepAngieCraig @RepKatieHill Sorry but it's time to really start to think about impe… https://t.co/uYdChU6zNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runawayjimjump @BarstoolNewsN @barstoolsports @BernieSanders Killer pump fake and absolutely automatic from 5 feet!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/em1KobH9ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlenromero_o @jorgitomijito Me if they ask someone if they want to go on stage https://t.co/2pOiOdCosj]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 October 2018.  Flexin' hard in Key West. 👑  24 karat magic in the aaaaaair, Head to toe, so player. Uh, look out!… https://t.co/TuZ7IAkzlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackblack met you at your Palladium show in Dec. Here’s my band’s new single. We’re playing Lucky Strike on Highla… https://t.co/g5X7Z1PQ35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EileenMKane @shaviro @imaginationASU Remember there is no Wakanda but there is imagination and there was the Tropo… https://t.co/8WHVtwtlzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patches_monahan @mjwags23 That’s the one! Never wanted to see him go, best pure hitter they have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Then put your boy Schiff on a leash.  He’s making a fool out of you as much as AOC is. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKurtAngle watching highlights of your matches in TNA with Desmond Wolfe and forgot how great they were. What was he like to work with?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Verizon leads wireless companies across the globe by developing the ecosystem to deliver #5G to b… https://t.co/Z3cQJ5nm4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Of course it is! It always has been, and always will be!😠😠😠😠😠😠😠]]></document></documents></author>