<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Everything truly is supposed to happen the way they’re supposed to. Trust the process!! 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok - only first round in the Manafort conspiracy against USA story. 🤡 47 months is just the pre-game sentence! Now… https://t.co/Bhquo6ohoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerGoodrich Repeatedly kept saying there is no evidence of harm from seed oils. Aside from mechanisms and Epi I… https://t.co/nrTe4CdS2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollywoodInToto Holy crap this is sad. Could not happen to a more deserving guy, but still ... ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein Looking forward to learning what leverage is being used on him.  Really hope it’s not just a craven desire for power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azsweetheart013 @realDonaldTrump Good Lord. He thought he'd get a "Sitting O(vation)"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Year 4 of Family Valentines Day #AllStarSpecial @WaffleHouse https://t.co/ahkVaM7SkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ngnoriel @zoom95fm @GALLONEGRO777 @DesertZION @Panchonteabraza Awebis https://t.co/2v47pd9epu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrencemcd @ReenaSibayan Are you saying that you *don't* keep millions in a gold briefcase near the TV?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertdos @LDFitnessCoach Anthropometrics generally dictate. That’s the beauty of the trap bar. You can squat your… https://t.co/jcl67g91gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexpiersonAMP @JustinTrudeau Why doesn't he just come out and say the truth. "Couldn't let SNC Lavalin fail. They… https://t.co/kfyExmpJOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at a restaurant visiting a friend in the Dallas, TX area, our waiter was from Vietnam. He really liked me a… https://t.co/x7rtZPaNLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s still hard to believe that I played on one of the best high school soccer teams in the state]]></document><document><![CDATA[We really do have boundless potential as individuals. Just have to believe in yourself and not give up right away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as I predicted from the start! #Trump will 100% pull a Wag-The-Dog to try distracting us from the impending… https://t.co/UVrWiVx1yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every morning I wake up and go to twitter to see if @Bharper3407 has signed with the @Phillies yet. Nope 😞 #MaybeTomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloWrestling WOAH WOAH WOAH HE PRESSED ON HIS BACK AFTER HE GOT THE TECH!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evansilva @flefster @PFF_College Correct. Of his 75 receptions this season 64 of them were considered “open” which… https://t.co/laFrz5UmEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzannebuzz @yashar @maggieNYT Will GOP make up their minds?  Are we evil Jews for or against them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haslametrics @wolverinestudio #Haslametrics  #buildyourdynasty  #ididit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtskls00 I love how people act like we are just going to drop dead because of climate change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andidee15 It’s actually a really chill place and one of my favourites to hang at in the city. Plus it’s only one b… https://t.co/eE48fGACDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back 🎶 Welcome back 🎶 , Welcome Jacccccccpot. @DeSeanJackson11 https://t.co/I8nykG43z5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RN_4Vols I saw this and thought of you and all those in your field! Save my life and I’ll love you forever!! https://t.co/LJD0kp69Z7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiking Anthony's Nose in the snow with my favorite hiking companion. Snow hiking is cool! @ Anthony's Nose https://t.co/rL8sEADIeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Ney_sha @IWriteAllDay_ Make a slogan out of it too! “Groupon Peen is basic peen, you deserve the best!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JONATHAN0305 @DannyWest1 He won’t play this season and as I stated, I’d rather take my chances with a rental QB TH… https://t.co/1LoOow5U7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barthalomu Enough has been said. I would’ve reported you if I was him 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eres un valiente Luis @luisgonzaloprz te admiro mucho tu impecable trabajo periodístico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickVasos is not only an anchor and reporter for @fox4kc,but he also moonlights as a dancer during @KCComets games… https://t.co/93yhtPZQdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The girls are getting ready!!  You still have about 40 minutes to get here! https://t.co/acCl0rvzYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dagger!!!! Great job by the Wild PK late and then Greenway puts it away with emphasis!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpTicHitch Eventually you will be old wondering why you never lived in LA.  Make it happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to work and boss said next Sunday morning you Stoner... lmao now I get a few hours rest before I work Lil Rob at El rey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 weeks and already took his first plane ride. And did so good! Already my little jet setter #StoryJohnson #Nola… https://t.co/wMQO4kHRyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else experiencing problems with Casting to Google devices? @madebygoogle #googlehome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APoley1 @CoachColeJr @StevenGrysko10 Mayo and Mustard? What kind of animal does that]]></document><document><![CDATA[・・・ 🤗 Lazy Saturday Goals? Tag one person you’d want to chill in this hammock with 👌🏼. . Your home is your space to… https://t.co/QkEnijYavo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ken78020841 Very Alarming: Boss of the Swamp says "Something ain't right" If you’re not concerned you should be.… https://t.co/OyV5LGIVpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget what my iPhone looks like under the case and it makes me want to have it without it... but then I r… https://t.co/d3EKgFE6KD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT Saturday will… https://t.co/HP7ya6L0R9]]></document><document><![CDATA[As enormous a talent Carey Price is as a hockey goalie, he's an even better human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening! I'm here at the UT School of Journalism's first Innovation Lecture, Discussing audio storytelling wit… https://t.co/grpWTr9tml]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make....work....fun! 🤠 "Even our tumbleweeds are OTC branded." #OnlyInTexas #Houston   🎥 #OTC50 🌊  @OTCHouston… https://t.co/yrjNsuIg95]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our demagogue in chief has his Republican rabble attacking Michael Cohen for speaking the truth about their pagan godhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrew_schmitt @RetroWDW @GoAwayGreen @lbvhistory Yes on the posters. https://t.co/sN4um329mk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priscilla_74 This was his low key expression too https://t.co/wA9ariyhL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfTripExperts Hidden River Golf and Casting in Nothern MI, a trio in SE MI would be The Orchards, Shepherd’s Hol… https://t.co/s7QgfgM7J4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaD1301 are you fed up Donna do you feel like @RandPaul is just a spoiler for his own party so let’s see if we… https://t.co/EaTNn2p8M1]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 3 months until the ⁦@chucknorris⁩ 5K comes to Aggieland. Quite a bit of work left to do. #running #nikerunning https://t.co/67mPdGtxZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for my musical artist followers:    If you knew where one of your favorite artists were staying for the ni… https://t.co/mGRqTjSmDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to With You by Mariah Carey #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/rggbtDUYn8   #MARIAHWITHYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way Houston’s mayor is handing out days for these undeserving celebrities is crazy....We gave K.Michelle her own day. HUHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity so what happens now the democrats fucked up whats their plan if the summit fails and the nukes fly bec… https://t.co/DdYCr3R5FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyscatering8 @DallasEatz Just shared this info on my Instagram that connected to FB account. #SpreadTheLove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawnANjax, @RacheltheQueen8 @Bronzed_Glow @AndreaIsomTV I'm stepping into Hump Day like .... https://t.co/LtjkBMhY7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mañana jugaremos a las sillitas con señores de la comunidad, se aceptan recomendaciones de rolas]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-0-1-9...Jordan 14 “Indiglo” (1999 Release) Feels crazy to have on 20 year old sneakers. @ComplexSneakers… https://t.co/M6swgDOada]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCastele @jeffsleasman @HannahLebovits @MyFriendCamilo “Abstinence from eating meat or another food according t… https://t.co/ymMA8jGDoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoebox Float day at school.  I - I mean, Jack - created a @RaginCajunsFB float. #GeauxCajuns https://t.co/hrWLcnMCYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy busy over at Lansing!!! Couldn't find a spot in the parking lot https://t.co/j23Szvo4xI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Let’s talk about everyday, thousands of illegals cross our borders, taxpayers have to pay for their care, and… https://t.co/v2Dij6kUJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFanos @kpolantz @jj_fedigan @PaulManafort isn’t scared of his #Collusion brother, @realDonaldTrump… But he is ter… https://t.co/gagGGYXqQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big win last night for the Cocoa Tigers! #DistrictChamps #CocoaFast #MultiSportAthletes https://t.co/JQM4Jv4gqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look out @joerogan . A stand-up comic is born 😁 https://t.co/IzEB2mBEOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tariffs don't work We'll there working now An made in China or (Guaranteed to fail) Is going to be replaced by M… https://t.co/ebSiZAYWUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stylin ole Beario !!!!! @ Goldsboro, North Carolina https://t.co/emtRq3B7OE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodeHelixGaming @FlashPointGG @SmitePro @Kespainie @Sibi_Smite @FusifySmite @Dzoni___ @FaraKrik I have not. What kind of game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the hell is the point of video review if they still get it wrong???!! @PhilaUnion @MLS @AlexiLalas #PHIvsTOR #MLSisHere @Kevin_Kinkead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody I respect asked me to do something- and I will oblige and end my communication]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jredding 4/4 What's "new" is that most VM-based cloud computing services (e.g. EC2) haven't involved or allowed cu… https://t.co/clr9EdPYCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @LanceSEdwards1 @AOC Keeping silent huh? It's a mystery isn't it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike can’t tell you how many pairs of your expensive sneakers I have blown through until finally moving to @adidas… https://t.co/M3URHxWFZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom I bought another Costco blanket, and she had the audacity to say, did I really need another blanket.… https://t.co/ExVhtJoxAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMcGovern @realDonaldTrump Got a good point but you either cling to strictly that and shut down the rest of your… https://t.co/IpUftL768F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin had 3 shots on goal in a 1-0 victory against a tough cwscsoccer team that out boys lost twice in a tournamen… https://t.co/ZzhpnJHvaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frpaul1 @FBorgal I was actually thinking they were saying “let’s give March 31st as the handover date and no one w… https://t.co/8120YcT89S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Patterns Triple IPA by @anchoragebrew @ Stouthouse — https://t.co/GV4JT9XoCy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a player. Look at the movement in slow motion to lose the defender.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump He is winning the supporter of naive Trump followers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @Chris_09765 Made some Democrats realize they shouldn’t “sit this one out” anymore. #trumpsterfire]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate the Leafs, yet hope Tavares scores a HUNDRED goals tonight. #thechosenone #pajamaboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesFinch Congratulations!! I know, old hat and all, but still thrilling...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeAsman Well since the team got $200 million from taxpayers for the stadium, it’s the least they can do. https://t.co/HkS34HZL1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying out the @bobbibrown 20th anniversary lip palette! This color is Berry Punch and maybe I should have put chap… https://t.co/SfvEGg5Ttl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Enterprise native has been one the of most prolific players for the @TroyTrojansFB program in recent memory. If… https://t.co/117WvmmM36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamden mix-up sparks call for statewide elections audit https://t.co/VaRhTcX8ma via @ConnPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now fight with the Night King! I just entered for a chance to attend the #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How do you p… https://t.co/DsurJK8gAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ANC2A's agenda for our next meeting is out! This week, we'll be voting on:  📖 Overcrowding at @WallsAtFrancis 🏘 D… https://t.co/L1TdTXCYdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magdra @alltoruin @AIPAC That’s a baseless accusation and a flat out lie. Show your evidence. Israel demonstrates… https://t.co/YQ4SUMR3cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s feels. Sometimes, even if progress is seemingly made, we’re not always using the best tools to tackle the p… https://t.co/SNyMRtIjoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:30AM spin class on a Monday sounded great until you realize at the end that you still need to find enough energy… https://t.co/1ZJ2vGnQiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watters really falling on his sword to take the embarrassment off Trump calling Tim Cook "Tim Apple"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oddly enough ...  three best beers where @CigarCityBeer two being old... @ Key West, Florida https://t.co/Ni6FormkaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NadeGrinds @PEUFRAZIER Beating his ass, just cause someone is big doesn’t mean they know how to throw hands 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChukkaBennett @ChuckitUK @Crufts @ArchieLakeland @dandy_wire Congratulations! Great job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucasdirt @WoOLateModels stick those sticks in garbage, let the drivers race. #RetireTheSticks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday’s are normally the days I do laundry, organize the apartment, and go grocery shopping. But I’m fucken sore,… https://t.co/pHfutZMhB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @KingJames for passing MJ is the scoring list of all time.. This season is just not ours.. #LakerNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alhamduillah!!! #AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad #PBUH #Quran… https://t.co/yzArc1xiLQ]]></document></documents></author>