<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek To protect them from pending criminal charges is my best guess?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ronniegblevins VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥https://t.co/vaAT1XmggR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cmon now Rich Homie &amp; Thugger was unreal bro Rich Gang need to run it back!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA w/ @eliasbiz https://t.co/uCmwwg5Ylq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating being a strong, independent woman by hanging out solo at the best heavy metal bar in America. Come at m… https://t.co/FOHm2B4dPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your #daughter says she wants to try the soy sauce! 😅😅😅  Hey #dads!  What is your kids favorite food?… https://t.co/GuuVOefxiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch probably expecting to get her ass kicked since she’s talking so much shit 🤷🏽‍♀️smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poptivist i cant even tell you how much I love my new icon. It makes me smile every time.i see it. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not go to college for 4 years and bust my ass to graduate on time to hear 10 million lectures on correlation versus causation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you ask your friends to help you pick a small project to work on first and they all pick something different.… https://t.co/fVcUJ2bYAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran a baby guided run tonight using Nike run club for the first time and WOW that was inspirational af. Made me *… https://t.co/LgpaN7CFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better yet, pay your employees living wages.  You won’t have so much profit to tax and so much left for executive p… https://t.co/mkjCq1oduB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona being last place in p12 truly is the phattest glitch in the simulation no cap 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[So since jordyn moved out and all I’m trying to apply to be Kylie’s new roommate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHPSWFL Appreciate the work of all our state troopers every single day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I would have given to have been able to attend just one of these 😍 Some of Chanel’s most awe-inspiring show sp… https://t.co/hdS2B9tyZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaSGrey @CTG_CEOGEH Nine children will show you  six won’t be bad. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨Fleetwood Mac with the Christine to my Stevie. ✨ @ Bridgestone Arena https://t.co/pdZGqS0VlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelHitchens They’re estheticians and they 10/10 know what they’re talking about 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Po Trump, nunca te pedi nada.. libera aí um green card pra mim, namoral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daynbayn If He can’t do it for you, it may not be for you. What is ordained and meant for you will come to pass. J… https://t.co/QvVMIdoUJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Good. We could care less. The less we see &amp; hear of you the better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a Now Hiring sign outside my local Starbucks, but then i pushed on the exit door clearly marked “pull” so I d… https://t.co/umqvwxcrbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEWWWW! Held on and got that W!!! We’re coming for you OKC and Portland!!! @HoustonRockets]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been really thinking about going for my masters. Like what’s another 2 years? Right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 Good Morning Eva! It's 19-c at our 5 AM reading; windy; Enjoy another Springy day 😘🌞💐👍😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevTKel @NDConnie1953 @TalbertSwan @JerryFalwellJr @AOC He is upset cus he he doesn’t know who his mother is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know who’s in the Sully The Seal costume?? I swear it’s Queeny Cheney]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a weird competition w myself to see how long I can go w/o tying my sneakers. Removing them while still tied.… https://t.co/P6IDFnW0Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you received a Valentines GIF from me this morning you mean something to me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Howard Frankland is backed up all the way up into St. Pete this afternoon. 😬😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keenanhailey27 Happy birthday keenan😸😸😸 I hope it was amazing♥️♥️♥️ https://t.co/5Z2ZtA3cnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turning a blind eye to the real threats and creating our own is a way people have been able to create political inj… https://t.co/kLy0Rw3Oem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Scary So Glad he was caught!!! #sociopath #compulsiveliar #HoaxAttack #jussesmollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all Begging for a nigga to invest in y’all .... why you can’t invest in yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as much as you nggas want it the bitches want it too! She is purrin prrrrr 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscar2019 #OscarNoms who should win? They’re all so convincing? @realDonaldTrump @sidrosenberg @bernardmcguirk3 https://t.co/edlqRw4jF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[sorry if you’ve had a bad experience but AP classes got me out of 20+ credits in college lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. So is ignorance a step up from just ignoring the suffering of others and calling it #FakeNews? @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P33Tee36 @Cirah_TV @Hollyoaks Okay true. But still Breda deserves to die after what she did to Louis and Russ though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrentonSaucedo @barstooltweetss @barstoolsports @SamTheMan1442 @ UK tho 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZabrenaXO @thataylaa @AndreaMatillano @jambeauty89 They just set it up today. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkumathurman Life goes by quick....I remember when the McDonald's in Woodlawn said over a million served]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren @latelateshow @JKCorden @CBS Oh goody.  Another money saver for the taxpayer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabyvil happy birthday 🎈🎁🎉🎂🎊 my lovely hooligan 💋 https://t.co/yZPnNIOOq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods It’s more possible your a traitor and don’t really have morals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldenmv_ How can you look in her parents face or even to her daughter and say, oh she’s not alive now because I d… https://t.co/GYNL5AEhoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkPit73640953 @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump ^^^bot. https://t.co/1HP4sqxpUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in a parade and allI took was like 2 photos of friends #kreweboheme #kreweofgoddesses glorybeaming @ Lost Lov… https://t.co/5uDd1mMva6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#godsword #hope #peace #faith @ Willmore Total Fitness 24/7 - Guntersville https://t.co/ael3UT6xEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suevee85 @Yo_TheOrangedog @Copy_Beethoven @JalenReeves_10 @sloopydeb @natti_p07 @RunningtoResist @Runn4UrLives… https://t.co/VawPgUeRc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CenturyLink, there’s been a slow down for the past two days (85730) in my area. Is there an issue around here or is it just my house? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I bring my own marijuana to RP with me or no? I ain’t trying to smoke no shitty ass weed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtsiBella Thanks, court! I’ve never been - gotta check it out next time I’m up that way. Will travel for good pizza 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that he's a Top 5 player in the NBA, YOU REALIZE THAT RIGHT???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former NFL Star Martellus Bennett Publishes Book that Encourages Black Boys to Dream Beyond the Stereotypes https://t.co/krhyr2UYS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duckhandyman @PhilDuck5 You're dreaming. First off, she said she would hold the position for 4 years. It has nothi… https://t.co/gNPN1Bvo1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sweet girl texted the Kids Care Kits flier to just about the entire 7th grade. She got her first donation on the… https://t.co/zy47O2j4aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 hours for my first tat session today. 12 more hours next week for my full sleeve🙏🙏🙏🙏😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[my girls and I met/hung out with loud luxury tonight so i guess you can say we made it in life !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccatmpt @GailBenzler @suziday123 @jflorez @SteveKubota @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @simplysallyh… https://t.co/2Vy4hxdF1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's tense at the Smith County GOP's headquarters as people shuffle in to a meeting that could start the process of… https://t.co/RdZ9V3VnYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Netflix has its own dating show..... this is either going to be really good or really bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two awesome guest readers this past week! One former student who is now writing his own books to read! And an older… https://t.co/aNRx20kvoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a commercial saying Juul is a good replacement for smoking cigarettes 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting cultured! #ilovenyc❤️ #viennaphilharmonicorchestra @ Carnegie Hall https://t.co/msjAA4X1m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Your brothers are ready to stand by your side.” @GeorgeLatimerCE #InternationalWomansDay #WOWconversations https://t.co/PSI3qQV7zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buShroom @FamiliarAlien @harrysiegel So true! It’s a really elegant piece of commentary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISeeYouMotel6 @HalmMary You are correct! I take those addicted into Drug/Alcohol Treatment. They have filled me in… https://t.co/YIUcdhzYej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr The Democratics are such an embarrassment can’t believe how low they have become]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe it has been 6 months already... #PowderPuff2018 #JakesHustleForMuscle  Shoutout to Connor McGrew for… https://t.co/pvimOYxTHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Kalanchoe blooms showing off in this morning’s sun. #sanfrancisco #succulents #urbangarden hiddenvisvalley… https://t.co/3adZW5UIUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder who is here. The poster.  #ReconstructionAtDuke https://t.co/6oPNHGaLQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW!👏🏻You actually used your brain!? NOW I for sure know you DO use another profile to stalk mine. You’re such a CR… https://t.co/6HWQg7bEx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagobulls @NBAAllStar @NBA Well we know #RKelly won’t be doing the half time show ☕️🐸 https://t.co/4oR9f5PxdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumi❣️ #instapup #socute #puppy #teddybeardog #teddybear #cutest #littledog #winterwalk #dogwalk #iceroad… https://t.co/BqWV987auj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burstinglion @BlastingSharks I'm going to say the middle one. Let's talk tomorrow about reasoning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baltimore 4/10-14th Kourtneycakesmanagement@gmail.com 🚫 Dm  #bbwlovers #bookings #beautywithabooty #bigbootycutie… https://t.co/HZ4FPU7XHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincengi @FaceTheNation Has that worked yet? Build the wall get rid of that third, then the money you save on taki… https://t.co/g28C3PHY7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only have two episodes remaining of the Sopranos and I need to talk to someone about my feelings.. if you have wa… https://t.co/fvXZrni7en]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to all my lovely ladies out there!! We as women are literally the fabric of our wor… https://t.co/CohjV0beMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good night cuties I love all of you so much. Ty for making my days bright]]></document><document><![CDATA[This fake field reporter sends my news station fake fam good vibes today! Have fun! I love our #LiveMovie crew! 🎬 .… https://t.co/U9dDuZw09T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grocery shopping with 210 of my closest friends. #ReadyForIt @MSD_DECA @mralbertmsd @MrsCutler https://t.co/8tWAkYtppE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a world of pure imagination 💜 • • • • #epcotinternationalfestivalofthearts #epcotfestivalofthearts #artfulepcot… https://t.co/2xjJUNNqyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house for “A Conversation on Becoming” with Dean @verna_williams! Dean Williams highlighted how there is “A lo… https://t.co/DT6j3UDLyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Margarita Day! casaamigosrest Great food &amp; service! Thanks David! #stluciecounty #portstlucie… https://t.co/i14s4pn35x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Name a better duo… I’ll wait. #MIDECA #SCDC2019 #BLTDM @MichiganDECA @DECAInc https://t.co/Txb0xnqtiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @Jim_Jordan is just a mouthpiece for @realDonaldTrump .  Someone buy him a jacket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkCalc @AmericanAir Not to mention having our luggage soaked from setting out in the rain. But! The seats were g… https://t.co/ovVUzm6ZNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twinkleblinc @JohnNizich @StormIsUponUs They need to check her fingerprints. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just asked Huxley to please grab Weslynn’s blanket, and he did. Piper says “oh, he’s so sweet” Huxley says “NEVER… https://t.co/mL8zGnzzIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog We know not enough prison time for the crimes will be lady justice ruling for Manafort because of the f… https://t.co/rOg1Uq3Eju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is too important to be in a hurry, my darlings! 😁  It’s going to be a great day. Enjoy it!! https://t.co/BddTA7VUmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AWP #AUTUMNWINDPIRATES  #AUTUMNWINDPIRATESDEFNATION  #AUTUMNWINDPIRATESINLANDEMPIRE #RAIDERNATION… https://t.co/9o7HLJDqxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going LIVE for the parade on @mynbc15 Facebook as soon as it comes my way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertJohnDavi Yes Yes Yes do it! Oh by the way you are are a great actor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know there’s a new generation of actors but UgGh😑 i REALLY love the original X-Men cast😩 https://t.co/HlnUSJV0qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebindley @herrmanndigital @kmosier42 Thank you. I want to delete anything that isn't a vinyl record, a cat, or cereal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when we were younger and were having bad days my gpa would take us to get slurpees after school. I tried… https://t.co/m1OZbeOHbC]]></document></documents></author>