<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RKLance @DRFLivingston Why???? Id never sell a TC trophy no matter how much I need the money. You cant put a price on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patricia Chappuis, Northwest Academy co- owner and wife of Marcel Chappuis, appears via video call #8NN https://t.co/3FqB4npA6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corriendo a través de la niebla 🌫🏃🏻‍♀️🌫  5 brumosas millas para finalizar mi ciclo de entrenamiento @TWMarathon 🌲🌲🌲… https://t.co/JzTqUepUqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelMBandy @Gay_News_Now @JerryBeller1 @ballotpedia @Interior @CoryBooker Just fyi @Gay_News_Now was hacked and… https://t.co/IQL2O5jXvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost jenineinf with get_repost ・・・ SWEET ROXY NEEDS to get OUTTA this SHELTER and into a LOVING FOREVER HOME ...… https://t.co/B5DNlgi2Yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 That way he can screw more people with one stone, destruction derby at it’s best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dealing with tenants can be difficult, but property management companies are aware of issues that may arise and the… https://t.co/25aoCTxPde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @Acosta Better to be a journalist clown than a TRAITOR like your daddy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathygoldade1 It often went undetected. It’s now clear to us that my 63yo sister in law has always been on the spe… https://t.co/8Apzqwd9EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the wall money he wants..oh, and don’t forget we’re in a  phoney National Emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been more people out here doing the Lamiphi! Do they even know the origin?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjmillard @PollenMidwest I pumped in a closet (with no lock)with both of my boys. This made me teary. Such a thoug… https://t.co/vB8WXrlSM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have had 3 people randomly ask me who my boyfriend was.   If this is a sign or symptom, I want to treat it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To all the nerdy girls behind their sketchbook, don’t be afraid to share your story.” - best animated short winner Bao #Oscars #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffCrosby2 Haha, thanks, Jeff! Running errands with toddlers feels like a workout sometimes! 😥But yes, I did enjoy that candy bar. 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[n honestly the explanation she gave as to why the pizzas are cut like that still makes no sense to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disability Awareness Conference - thank you @TheAryaFoundati  #ssdlearns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Conradi_Peter I don't know.   I'm sure that both sides of the negotiation probably prefer it be kept confidential.… https://t.co/17LqLsejPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prindigo @YerboutiSheik @harry_bolls @CoolCzech1 @bayareahausfrau @mowoodier @EmersenLee @PubliclyPrivat1… https://t.co/u8AQaMSyar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDBrunn @mrsteacher77 Haha--oh @PDBrunn you are the very very very best:) Thank you ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am currently still at work, running off of 3 hours of sleep, &amp; an iced coffee. i leave for Disneyland in 4 hours 🙃 send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJuanVargas @realDonaldTrump @JoaquinCastrotx @HouseDemocrats Or this one...https://t.co/06dy3DJhuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Viviana__MD__ @Pink The X series has a bigger screen than all previous iPhones but still is a smaller phone and th… https://t.co/eoylPDH9ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[22. I believe life exists outside our planet in the form of bacteria and the like, but little green men? Nah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysticnamja I expected a table full of delicious food like in animes! But no T_T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ellenarlenemich @AngelaF08695845 @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump ???? Who?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterjukes @zelo_street yeah..I dealt with the Mercer /Thiel goon squad for actual decades now...god how time flie… https://t.co/gBFZt2yFW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@People4Bernie @realDonaldTrump Until you ask how it will be paid for and if they want their taxes raised to suppor… https://t.co/bTKm8PuYLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my hot twin @t_parmer wouldn’t want to look like anyone else 😉💙 hope you have a great day beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My finger nail broke and I think imma have a freakin melt down b4 I can get it fixed tmw 🤯🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[oof, never felt so backstabbed in my life. walls are thin ppl!!!!!! lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yLlYO6qy41 lots new up on my issuu page , go check it out! https://t.co/W2liii3zBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungHov_Absol Lmao nah nigga nigga 🤣😭 the nerve https://t.co/z6VMX0OEWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud to reside in Waukesha County. I am impressed with how our county government focuses on improvement. Th… https://t.co/igYRlR55bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I would hope she would be. She’s as much of a liar as he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The White House serving @ChickfilA &amp; @McDonalds to the @NDSUfootball team today in the State Dining Room. https://t.co/tUWYldVCAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisC25265543 Oh yeah, man. Between my browser history from my Cracked days and the hours of screaming that make… https://t.co/6D1XCuk36Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's Go 🐺 ... Come out and cheer on your Hamilton Huskies today @ 4:30pm at Chedoke Twin Pad. @ Chedoke Twin Pad A… https://t.co/t4bIhR1K7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keto ultra diet shark tank Eventually, forwards and backwards movement raise regarding has displayed that it can re… https://t.co/31SWqioBZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww sweet little Duke is turning into an... adolescent. #BetterThingsFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[THREE days since this message where I have sent my medical documentation MULTIPLE times and NO ONE has contacted me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_carrasco2 @NISDMurnin @mrskbconrad Love it!! What a great week!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱 at first I thought it was just another no seasoning straigh to the skillet video ....but… https://t.co/TbUMN5Y3QJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WILL WIN THE LOTTERY!  I WILL WIN THE LOTTERY! I WILL WIN THE LOTTERY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not as much as I would have liked, but I’ll take it!  Great, first skate yesterday. I live out of the city 90 minut… https://t.co/WuV5RdbmWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I smell fear in trump.  The odor emanates from every orange pore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@interfluidity @MattBruenig Yes, lots of complexity. In general I think this policy would give a lot of freedom to… https://t.co/YUMql0JPbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now that the White House is denying supplying requested documents from the House, I hope that the House follows… https://t.co/GH71XnSmvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love you love you, little bestfriend!❣️ @ South Lake Tahoe, California https://t.co/8hWsZKWiQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Rosenberg still employed?  Does Mueller not understand this whole thing?  So they rigged Hilary not getting… https://t.co/O7RnJHVdca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one talk to me, I’m saving myself for a goofy hippie dude that took my heart with him to Arizona.]]></document><document><![CDATA[JDJGKWKFLWLGNWLGKWKGKDKVLDKGKEKFKEBFKDLHGKWKFKFKFKFG LOVEEEEEEE DLGKDLKGFKGKD https://t.co/hKTFezBAiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kironcmukherjee @ROMtoronto I have my old photo ID cards from when I was a programs assistant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1madwoman1962 @karenslinn43 @mann_reelmann @MelindaYoe @Shirley82829043 @merabethjames @11syoung @JackConnie… https://t.co/Qrd5YeMhJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HushamHamad @YasserEljuboori ترامب هو رئيس دولة عظمى و عندما يعبق على موضوع نشر في الديلي بيست يعني انها ليست مغمو… https://t.co/6vCvjLTGyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, I'm going to Twitter jail but fuck them! They can't even figure out how to let us edit our tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics These will be the lowest rated debates in history. Big mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoxArcana4 @katedelcastillo Dos mujeres: La Maestra Elva Esther y Kate del Castillo.  Además, éstos hechos me hace… https://t.co/biscVlQ3dw]]></document><document><![CDATA[how nice that the “thank you” cupcakes my team received were personalized just for me https://t.co/nRdscsZQQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright nct haven’t even announced tour stops but nctzen moots, when are we planning our road trip to ncity ?😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alphacat do you write your own scripts? You cracked me up! Couldn’t concentrate on game!! Lol nice shirt, I was ou… https://t.co/IMgXrgCYsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s freedom of speech oh that’s right there’s only one side, the left????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcorippo @TechMikeBUSD @TosaChat @mhebern @EdTechEddie @EdTechAri @kmartintahoe @KarlyMoura @Jyoung1219… https://t.co/UvglWPjgz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I let you borrow money and you don’t pay it back it’s cool . Just Better hope you don’t need me no more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahMcGrathRD Hence I support @EthosChocolate 100% for being education-forward. A breakaway mainstream brand could… https://t.co/SXkWufrtUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to have Fred Armisen as my accent coach, please and thank you :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are not meant to be in this world just to work and pay bills.  There is more to life than just paying bills and working 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake Thank you all this pointing of finger will be the thing that destroys out world!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it slightly humorous when my Fitbit tells me I have 250 steps left to get for the hour..... after I've run 9… https://t.co/Q0sQvNPhDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_xoxosabrina I was gonna tag you in that too 😂😂 those were NOT the days lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting Bible school soon and will be blogging &amp; podcasting monthly instead of weekly! #BibleStudy https://t.co/HmWO7Po08j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignOfApril Oh please. Who didn't do something, anything while with friends that one wasn't supposed to do? The B… https://t.co/KZefpqIQYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PjVMop93Gi  Goodmorning perverts call me while I'm taking a break from driving @NiteFlirt https://t.co/XI88xmNz6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola Twitter @jorgegestoso Comunista parisino Uruguayo que actualmente, y lamentablemente vive en mi hermosa ciudad… https://t.co/2iYhdmQNIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merci à #PaulineMarois en cette journée #Journeeinternationaledesdroitsdelafemme #aqcpe #plafonddeverre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come buy your Girl Scout cookies!!! We’re here until 2pm!!! https://t.co/dZTdOhuy48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact me for all your Real Estate Needs. Buy-Sell-Leasing-Contact Stephanie Passler 561-436-8296 Real Estate Brok… https://t.co/Ix5Q2DQ1tZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw someone refer to their ex as their “wasband” and I can’t stop cackling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Which article upset you? Was it this one?  https://t.co/lr0IcHcaEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MForman5 @leeniefrancis @KaniacFever @NHLCanes Ok thx. How about on line orders. ETA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@W7VOA @realDonaldTrump @PressSec You over Melania! Cmon dream some more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone was appropriately awestruck for their first movie theater date with daddy and mommy! 📽… https://t.co/C6K8yMSKkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retomando nuestra amistad... Aunq lo q es real jamás se pierde.. Te quiero amiguita.. 💋💋 en Sohoo Sushi Bar https://t.co/SZ27eoDX8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amharawit @BTA____ @NileAyu It's hard to believe why?  Is it worth it? He was loved by many I wonder what is next?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just bought 2 more jpn pcs I was missing and I placed bids on a bunch of other stuff fjsjdnfnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AoDespair Are they counting every time someone says blow me in relation to this admin as a "job"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello pweas follow me on Instagram bc im so close to 1,000 n I post very sexy free photos on there all da time and… https://t.co/699jmZ8vz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of a fight in high school where everyone was throwing milk cartons &amp; fruit 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish more of my friends woke up in time so we could get breakfast but no these bitches wake up in time for dinner 😔☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrustFellows @iamwesmoore @NYCommTrust @BaruchCollege It was a great conversation! I'm so grateful for the alumni fellows community.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to help the sharks make sure you check out the Shark Trust ❤️.                  Gordon Ramsey: Shark Ba… https://t.co/nfHHsgm3nG]]></document><document><![CDATA[grateful for opportunities to support the arts and people who leave extra paper in the printer in Johnson hall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa Do you think Jesse would sit down with Robin for a follow-up interview?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me listening to @solangeknowles Binz from her new album at work like https://t.co/gygFtqrFaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MechelleV @CoachCloseUCLA @UCLAWBB @OregonWBB @pac12 That's why she's the best! She's all in! #GoBruins #Grit #EverybodyAlways @bobgoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@northbird_ellen @BirdNoteRadio They are the finest Accipiters. You’ve seen BBC slow-mo, I expect.... https://t.co/R2XmgNIlT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KT3378 I'll fight to the death to protect the accomplishments of Sansa. She's the definition of character development.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1011WNOE @LukeBryanOnline thanks for playing ❤️❤️❤️❤️ What Makes You Country by Luke Bryan ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/0Eci7HW9qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Condemning these posts is a great first step, @wrdsb. Now let’s set a new, higher standard in #ONTEd on how to trul… https://t.co/YIk0S0EtAu]]></document></documents></author>