<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the same fanagers who celebrate when certain boxers make great deals for themselves, are now upset with Tyson Fury… https://t.co/CrckjO6GjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylecarlson Another (less theological) way of putting it: we need to get down to the root of how we're really thin… https://t.co/VvXuNZA3pI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Q: how can you, in your life and in your sphere of influence, bring about positive change TODAY that will bring equality to all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta day DK Metcalfs performance is one of the best I’ve seen. 4.33 in the 40 and 27 reps on bench Godamn!💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRIVE SAFELY this morning! There's statistically a higher than normal accident rate today, after everyone losing an… https://t.co/iNJSdugd1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneyjeann_ That sucks. She’s always been so awesome and offered great service. Also I am comveniently tweeting… https://t.co/zG96ioyQ3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cathiemccorkle5 @ACCHockey @NCStateHockey @WahooHockey @WSFairgrounds Thanks Cathie, for everything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ate at @BrothersbbqCO at the airport.   Did the survey, and it only asked me to rell about the good things...… https://t.co/Yx8ymgEKbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam Miller, co-chair of Cleveland’s Forest City Enterprises and philanthropist, is dead at 97… https://t.co/o8QwdivLy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fucktruuump @questar1959_ron @PalmerReport Nanananah Nanananah  Hey Hey   Good bye   - dedicated to Roger Stone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelMarks4 @JerryFalwellJr @AOC @CPAC Hate is in the Bible and there are things that God hates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lollardfish @CNNOpinion From which alternative universe did you pen his missive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexievigne "Thick" 🤣🤣🤣🤣 bitch please. Shes about as thick as a drop of water]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleRempel Perfect speech showing the absolute uselessness of their  GVT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful 4 choice servants of God and there faithfulness throughout many years to our Lord. Humbling to get to b… https://t.co/OyadoeivQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fathertorey @erinjeanwarde @RevGrey @kmaustinyoung @brokechurchman Hey, I saw those fezzes in your office! The leo… https://t.co/JYmrFwiOIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @SpaceX @Space_Station So to have a day-time launch with the syncing to ISS, you would have had to wait anoth… https://t.co/are5Gx5cOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @MeghanMcCain She’s gone bananas for sure. Her thoughts make no sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I have accepted a challenge from @SiegelCC to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews - j… https://t.co/fI9bNyUn4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS. IS. NOT. STUNNING. IT. IS. OBVIOUS. AND. SHOULD. BE. EXPECTED. REALITY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No kids there anymore when we get here! 😥😥😥 (@ Ladybird Academy in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/NB7ttNNsTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning My Beautiful America And Wonderful President Trump, May God Walk with you all , he loves you, so do I… https://t.co/PLmGUpqteN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasTechMBB @stakingtheplain @vivathematadors Now that’s a spicy meatball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennyERJ Goodnight Kenny! Have fun watching Idris Elba do his thing tonight on SNL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky to see several@of 95’ hogs at dinner. Al Fillard came over intro. And was very kind. Think he could still go… https://t.co/F8t2x3VJtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[something *fun and interesting* about me is that the right animal-centric video set to the right music WILL make me… https://t.co/bvXbOcGVMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg my girl gets so excited when she’s able to connect the correct pieces of the puzzles together 😩❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yungskrrt @auden500 At 180 no u shouldn’t and shiny is in but this is the watered down fast fashion version so it… https://t.co/UFTxe12lP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gdubya1 My local hangout.  Pretty much every rural Iowa restaurant will have a big ole pork tenderloin on the menu.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want you in my life more than anything Lisa.. you're so special to me Lisa I really do love you... https://t.co/qZb24gDlp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If even one program accepts, please be nothing but thankful.   If all programs reject, you can seek further study/e… https://t.co/L527Rho2IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[J.S. Ondara - “Torch Song” (Official Video) https://t.co/eML8tABVQW via @YouTube What a Great Album.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes It is an excuse. But I had fun too. #silentservice #lifelongago https://t.co/7eVmVUzc1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has been my pleasure working with @SAISDGATE  The community is amazing and the G/T Team does an outstanding job… https://t.co/vnZUti8U8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt is so selfish with this time now, probably just stinking up his house with curry and making slapper music he’s… https://t.co/sNWHszxBYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reeves_Aden Jackson Feldman....wish he would have stuck it out. He was really, really good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryCallahan @MutCallahan what bothers me to no end is @EvanDrellich would like Elizabeth to speculate when she r… https://t.co/2z0NNM9QJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ATRL20 This Day In History (02.26.1999):  - Bill Clinton (D) was President of the US. - Jean Chrétien (L) was PM o… https://t.co/X27clOynrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh good news they're not going to harm the animal. They don't want to repeat harambe I assume]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FIAFormulaE This looks like it's gonna be fun let's go @leylahassanxo 😛😣😉 the plane tickets are gonna run me a couple Grand alone 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CCF P Building (Surgery Center) - @clevelandclinic in Cleveland, OH https://t.co/u9eH0FirtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvonnaCadaver @BigBitingPig @YoutooAmerica I have enjoyed @BigBitingPig movies on Amazon videos...highly recommend!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reptoy4 There are dumb decisions being made by kids in every district. Spain Park will remain a multi blue ribbon… https://t.co/cZGbBUTd4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amvetsupport #@realDonaldTrump is an immoral, incompetent, corrupt, draft-dodging coward &amp; lying asshole!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 #SanDiego / #LosAngles #Chargers from 1965 on. https://t.co/Mha9ILiCKH … … … … … … https://t.co/e67StVxeM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone who didn’t bet the chalk honestly believe this was fixed? Genuinely curious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leonardo_Padron el problema es ese carecen de cerebros y allí si estamos jodidos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncaawrestling please do something about all these "medical" forfeits!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianJo32095311 @AMartinez_13 @DoninNorthbrook @NBCSChicago @SportsTalkCHI 🌴😎☮️ #Nagy didn’t commit to the Run unt… https://t.co/0mW8Y4c1Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenorG #badgechat. I have not seen it though some micro credentials for classes teeter on being one task only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In his lengthy @jacobinmag missive on Modern Monetary Theory @DougHenwood never really lays out the theory or criti… https://t.co/0mcZLUYg9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @IlhanMN They took down the towers, killed almost 3000 great Americans and now we have them in congress... who counted the votes?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruisedNBroken Come snuggle with me I'll wrap you in my arms and hold you tight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morininfo @ChantalMarquis3 Ceci est un tweet erroné ou de mauvaise foi! Blanchette, du #BQ veut protéger SNC Laval… https://t.co/4NiuMKDSht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Friday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍 https://t.co/ZNZZWN0B4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Arellano produces a run-scoring hit to pull @TMWARRIORBSBL within a run of @TMWARRIORBSBL at 4-3. We’ve played 2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NzhhhhhzbAnnjjhhhhhjsjjsdJjdjjxnxnnxjxjxkmxjxkkxjxnxnkmddklkxkfkkxkxkkcjXjnjjndnndbnbjchhjxhhncncncncnncncnnnnndjzj… https://t.co/I1R9Ek3eZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue and yellow just shuffled on by the used and the hair on my arms just shot up with goosebumps...what a powerful band.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clrforthewin Some of both - we do have moisture wrapping around the back side of storm that is well to our north b… https://t.co/U0FJ5gdCG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[robynkonichiwa @thepalladium 2/23/19 A true queen!! #robyn #hangwithme #latergram @ The Hollywood Palladium https://t.co/3xRPcu9193]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddBrommelkamp Not attacking anyone. Just get disheartened and sad sometimes about what we have all created....I’… https://t.co/9TZLbR2Wxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comments happen in every stadium. Westbrook has been yapping at fans all night. One side: If you say something vulg… https://t.co/x7HpGOhBPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Picard_Resists @theJagmeetSingh Reminds me of the last election, when Mulcair‘s policy was very close to the #CPC line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renfamous They should have just gone with "actor." Much easier to spell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[General Joseph Votel breaks rank with Trump over Syria https://t.co/BLpTb199cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it bad that my first thought was "he's only 5'2" and then put my phone back in my pocket? https://t.co/kUpDvbnlV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[All #Houston #Astros team 1965-2017, position players.  https://t.co/HR0S0ETAq4 … https://t.co/jfVNbm7aX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh oh, someone doesn’t understand how population growth works. When the percentage doesn’t work for you, go with ab… https://t.co/4TJoy2UySS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever shotgunned a 12% imperial stout? #acheron #martinhouse #tbt @ Martin House Brewing Company https://t.co/pZOaimjzUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the stronger voices here just disappear.  Who is Twitter working for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boomereng I’d say in many ways Aragon assumed his leadership role, while Legolas demonstrably earned his.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still love this song and it’s a part of a really good compilation album. No weak tracks! https://t.co/0HMqAZqLMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[machine learning days with @ZlatanDzinic at @AWSstartups @AWSloft #MachineLearning #nyc https://t.co/Sswpphxecg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosieWoodsTV @WLOS_13 Florida follower But love the North Carolina reports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musdurken @JosephSteinberg @noobfatherof1 @Fritz588_ @AOC Yes, so either way no property taxes but now no jobs eit… https://t.co/ugMGwkcQ7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to start a B1G day in Indy.   Four games — beginning at noon ET — that we’ll bring you on @BigTenNetwork… https://t.co/vxJTTwL2i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time @FWBVikings CONQUEST event!  Thank you @Lindaboriedugan for allowing me to shadow you!  @spolskij… https://t.co/ksLm99pY4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to set your clocks ahead one hour! #DaylightSavingsTime https://t.co/JWQPeh5emu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Unofficial Tinder Meetup Party @ PB Shore House https://t.co/GHr65q6SiC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MovemberIreland @TheRock My mom @HISHEIRESSANDCO @empirelivingc probably knows more than anybody about this she st… https://t.co/TdvWJYxl7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gonzalez___Benz Let’s go man fuck it, but 1 way tickets and we can decided if we want to come back]]></document><document><![CDATA[C- I save some, I use what I buy, and I get rid of things.  I have seen the mess and piles of some people.  I live… https://t.co/rGTwleabfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow It is just amazing that you will continue this diatribe when you are party of Steve Knight]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMFG THE MOST ROCK AND ROLL NEW YORK OBSCURE BAND  MAN WENT ON HOLY SHIP Smh I’m soo stoked to read this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Logic301 used keanu reeves in one of my basketball edits, what u think 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrtucci “I never would’ve spoken to you” BITCH ARE YOU BLIND https://t.co/rojEVmOVUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in they're making a live action family guy movie with joaquin phoenix as peter]]></document><document><![CDATA[That camera was sick. Definitely need to get a couple of those @DJIGlobal Osmo Pockets in our Social Studio. 😎… https://t.co/kr6ZajF6JF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been changed since You came into my heart, from Your word I am wise.  Life is absolutely exciting and amazin… https://t.co/Mb4j5ru6Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsmith_NYC @tonster009 @warriorsworld 12 POINT 4TH QUARTER! FOH BAY AREA LAKERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[reckon let your speech always be with kindness, seasoned with salt, that you may know how you ought to answer each… https://t.co/TgKNaiD6x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost got caught up in the Kamala Harris/Cory Booker beef last week. I’m not gonna fall into the trap of the 202… https://t.co/nwCTYIa1Cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[People seem to be forgetting that even if the Mueller report were to exonerate Trump on conspiracy or obstruction c… https://t.co/OrgR8YAU5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marriott recently stayed at a Marriott in Cedar Rapids, IA.  Bathroom was absolutely filthy.  Called to have somet… https://t.co/oe2gKULY2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @steph93065 The voters of Minnesota have us this person...after they gave us @keithellison, partner abuser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is official, @shenrichsen32 will be playing with @PaxBaseball this spring. I love baseball...but not as much as… https://t.co/eqFPyPPQdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s make the MAGA movement the strongest in USA history. The founding fathers waged a war against abusive taxes.… https://t.co/84IG6YZkIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I second this emotion, @drvox - we’re doing A LOT of big things on #waleg this year.   It’s a dizzying array of cli… https://t.co/xP7lzKzDQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop spending my leisure time at work looking at flights 😅 I be too tempted to just book some sporadic trip somewhere.]]></document></documents></author>