<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Wow the first time hearing Knuck if you buck without someone strolling😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisagemeni @Hercrabbiness Also, no offense to anyone, Nathan won the Free Skate so 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#oquirrh #oquirrhmountains Heading down the mountain from #snowbirdresort @ Utah https://t.co/d9d1NRdyUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVE 💕LOVE you are so beautiful inside and out. I love @Undisclosedpod @45thPod @rabiasquared @WajahatAli… https://t.co/GMtgSIRMTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alytadpollo Lo haré ,cuando cumplió 15 años le encontraron hipertiroides y medicado con hormonas sintéticas todos… https://t.co/6o9tEKsOIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Bella!! 😍😍 It’s #internationalwomensday, so support girls and women wherever you can. Bella’s mama brought m… https://t.co/MruZSFx4zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Problem is not the system ..it is the implementation. No consistency, fidelity, or appropriate follow through.… https://t.co/SFAAvKocef]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISSA PEACOCK 🦚 💛.                              #makeup #pictureoftheday #makeupaddict #melanin… https://t.co/yK3RhfGKPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out that another great MAGA thing is wanting to abolish the TSA?!?! there’s actual humans that think w… https://t.co/9NOHtVKxu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is ​the MLB about to get itself a brand new super-team on the West Coast? Ooohhh man. Now I'll definitely be on T… https://t.co/SzmOlVPCLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmckinnon @SHO_TheCircus Cheerful trailer. Good thing I love this show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the KOA Behind the Sign Giveaway and you could win the Grand Prize of a Keystone Passport 175BH, a $500 KOA g… https://t.co/4H1sTVBmGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a time it has been. . .Goodbye Mayor @BobBuckhorn https://t.co/5x6Yecg0QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you need us love ❤️. But a Spa Day spalogicdc dupont_circle_main_streets Now and Then doesn’t hurt and it still… https://t.co/UUmVDi1DuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vap1337 #Chicharrón ?? 😳😜  Where's @Stu_Mundel and @Sky5Tim  This could be a first for them too, Danny!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Adam Schiff, we will send all the illegals to your house and to Nancy's house and Schumer's,there mi… https://t.co/hY0IzOqIkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once upon a time a scrawny bucktoothed young girl was taunted and teased for being tall and weird looking. Her moth… https://t.co/YqJRtQn1Su]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aric_Almirola @ISMRaceway @SmithfieldBrand @FordPerformance @StewartHaasRcng You done good. A win is in the horizo… https://t.co/SSsH8FU0u4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harpy_diem YEAHHH! I'm just like... ugh they're gonna make her straight but like.... please kiss your best friend… https://t.co/vkdLqFkqqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok guys, tell me the truth, does my new banner pic look ok or no?? I’m undecided if I should keep it or no?? 🙄🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaughtySassyHez @binestom @mandra40 @KellirjA @kerrykushner @Lothiriel_1 @wcugrad_09 @WynterSoldier00 @S_Absolem… https://t.co/a7i80rQtP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day Double date with Pop and Bunches!  We had the most romantic table. @ The Hook https://t.co/4FF33Xw0cF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudleyGlove @oggasbagss @HakimsArtNStuff @YogiSplit @xZelusx thank you!! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your behavior is illegal and unacceptable @mattgaetz #MattGaetzIsAThug https://t.co/I9rESpIloi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbo8898 @NBCNews Thank you I’m not an idiot and I’m for every little thing that helps. You are entitled to your op… https://t.co/mG0ri6gBAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving Goodbye messages on our Spiritual Home.  #unitymoves #onourway #spiritualfam #soblessed… https://t.co/7vzKhFQSr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneEUrai @meganinlisbon @sepalmerNeuro @synapticlee @EugeChapadur Really happy to see the awesome efforts of cosy… https://t.co/mzQAiG3vPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every 1 knows Wall Street is full of more "Russian" money than any country!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being at peace with myself basically means I’m at war with everyone else.. Surrendering myself means something only to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fat_Male_Virgin And you're not shareing with me? WTF? I thought we were friends??!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're here and awake and ready for #GenghisConCO!! Come say hi!  #savageworlds #rpg #wildcardsrpg #savingthrow… https://t.co/x833pp6Pj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just want everyone to know that i made @ThePollyAmory wait over an hour to meet remy and emile but we both know it was 100% worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy (belated) Valentine’s Day! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ Honestly, though, the 15th is the best day because that’s when the ca… https://t.co/qe30ZlZ6nb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why but I always procrastinate sleeping whenever I have a big day ahead of me 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[White lightning on Ameki Wajew #ontheland #anishinabe #relational @ Fort William First Nation https://t.co/jApVBcmjwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaInxs2 @cannsd51 @Klein2Eric @Lexa_Merica @MagzillaGorilla @RL9631 @sappermartin @SealeyGerald… https://t.co/eQU6TlsyqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swiftlycourtney @taylorswift13 @taylornation13 @Nicole_Fritz96 Thank you for the retweet Courtney!  Let me know if… https://t.co/uC6d1Lp6yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Harrow. #hangingwiththeharrow #theharrowvikings #broat #minff @ Michigan Nordic Fire Festival https://t.co/qixbJMtCJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CriticalRole @DnDBeyond @TwitchDev Ooooh, schnazzy! ✨🗒️✨ Can't wait to try it in action!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei If you don’t stop it, I’m going to turn Air Force One around right now and go back over there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sector_KL @_U_R_I_c Привозят из Юж Америки,  потом они им надоедают,  вот и вывозят в Everglades]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UntilRevelation @childofpromise3 @GKCdaily Also, do you believe they had the authority from God to do this? After… https://t.co/QX8YD982Dl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The proof that the Jonas Brothers fans are all adults nows is that my little cousin knows their songs because his p… https://t.co/73TtbNr6jV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScoopB I think kyrie was talking abt brooklyn having 2 max spots. Everybody knows the knicks has 2 max spots im sure KD knew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great show on the books! It took this guy 7yrs to win another singles title (his 39th) and only 7 days to w… https://t.co/jiFtVTbvM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Compassion/jealousy, success/failure, overjoyed/heartbroken? The do-si-do’s of a lifetime, providing us the ultimat… https://t.co/N3Ka8DOzR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Conley @KIRO7Seattle King county is known for not prosecuting cases and allowing liberal judges to sweep… https://t.co/JsOy56IzcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg I love this video even my hubby does too❤️ #BoysInTheBand @ADUB791 #VeryCatchy #JustMakesYouWannaDance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisPeitzman @juliareinstein @MSNBC @STOConnor I saw it, too, and thought maybe you used your mother's name in honor. Nice guy.🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear man I be so cold at night I need some socks that come up like pants 😩 like all the way to my waist.   Or my… https://t.co/xRCdeUYKfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you’re so bothered, PLEASE keep me blocked, don’t don’t lurk my stuff! thank you! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHellwich @cjberanek90 @UrbanAchievr @JonahNRO There's nothing wrong with a private citizen wanting to expand h… https://t.co/xGMGWRcsAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joanwalsh Whitewater? A “bridge” too far? If so, Dems get WMDs, Iran Contra, Watergate. They win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when someone blocks you and they feel you don’t have spys and 20 accounts to stalk them 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing Again was just that. Thank you wheel...and @aarontap (cause if you have to take the blame, you should also… https://t.co/Iwc6rm8OR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you dear @daliahanna @mbountrogianni @ChangSchool for this very kind recognition 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lexa_Merica Trump2020  Follow all MAGA PATRIOTS RT/fb https://t.co/6CGCeTTYnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved hearing 3 different messages today from 3 different men and they all ended with Jesus is the answer! 🙌🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple Ideas That Are Borderline Genius – 28 Pics these are cool. None of these are... #laughter #snicker #smirk… https://t.co/3xFXvMcNMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that what I thought my almost 3 hour nap earlier, was actually 5.5 hours and no wonder why I’m so awake rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[hopped on the celery juice daily. &amp; honestly my skin has never looked better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a real lady. I will sit by my phone for hours refusing to text him first. Cause I’m woman enough to let you man… https://t.co/lGoEHO793d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright all of you AWESOME people. I am going to try my hardest to stream today. But at this point I'm unsure. I ha… https://t.co/Zjsxahtarx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although Trump plans to meet with North Korea he seems he forgets to discuss human rights or brushed through human… https://t.co/qFpZd8HMIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusicIsMedicin1 @CrazyXxYall So you think Miranda and her personal life wasn’t covered by the media until her ex h… https://t.co/AwDPaRezEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m about to say something VERY controversial, and 2012 Miriam who got this twitter for the sole purpose of followi… https://t.co/YeBqvKHkwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes #younglifeclub needs to get off-site! Reliving my high school days with a trip to #friendlys 🤣 As… https://t.co/eyRKSXCvKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[L'amour ça se dit, le reste est à la portée des gnous". Bertrand Perrier @cavousf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just from this I know Jane’s dumbass is going to pick Michael/ Make amazing ass Rafael hurt in some way. Hope I’m w… https://t.co/bNfp66C2iP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Republican lies. You are covering for the criminal president just like you covered up the sexual assault you witnessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Realtor makes a big difference whether your offer gets accepted or not. Good luck competing against cash. Call… https://t.co/qURK8aBr78]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be doing schoolwork but instead I’m watching Michael Cohen’s testimony because I’m #woke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matadoreltiempo La verdad no me interesa mucho el atuendo de las personas, pero a estos niveles, con los recursos.… https://t.co/EidJYDU9Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does my kid's school website not have any information about before care or after care on it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of @MeridithMaskara, Troop Leader Giselle and @JimmyVanBramer for their support of #troop6000 Great shoutout… https://t.co/BsUSQXXX8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great way to start a Thursday! Your daily dose of @michaeldamian1 . #RockOn @YandR_CBS #YoureWelcome #hot 🔥❤️ https://t.co/sOjmcr6nIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatRobHyl @GlisanMelissa @GovRonDeSantis @realDonaldTrump @NASAKennedy 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's ridiculous. That cop has been incredibly professional to have the conversation away from the children and she… https://t.co/X7jLLhe2iO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@instagram 😞😞 did I like too many posts? #blocked #nomorelikes #instagram https://t.co/nmK4LDh2j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So be careful how you live. Don’t live like fools, but like those who are wise. Make the most o…… https://t.co/TcJU7vtpnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so indecisive when it comes to nails colors but I think I have one picked out.....I think 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check the link below to see how your AP course connects to college majors and careers. @NISDHarlan @2020Harlan… https://t.co/d8dFUa4G3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just a comfort to this woman in Lizard’s Thicket that was upset they were out of collard greens. Columbia is… https://t.co/1loKP1OJRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday before spring break fun! @ThorntonCFISD @ReginalMitchell https://t.co/UmbivBBWz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really worried about the baby, but why would you waste cheese like that???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rebekka024 @Emmetcahill I'm telling you if he ever has a daughter, she will be the apple of daddy's eye!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@failedmanman This pizza thread prob isn’t helping with the hunger thing. https://t.co/FXdj8zsb5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmartinharp Hi Gloria, Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swithou… https://t.co/scB5xrev3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want signed, personalized copies of the #fenwayandhattie books? My local bookseller, @henrybearspark, will take you… https://t.co/F4JoGZ2nxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Democrats have lost their minds and are going into full-tilt destruction mode. Will this be a winning strategy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The secret to living and longer is: eat half, walk double, laugh triple and love without measure.” #livelonger… https://t.co/IfN6qCNGKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of scorers on Senior Night tonight for your Crusaders!  3 in double figs! And every healthy senior scored! Har… https://t.co/AO8GRXD7Ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@screwthechew God told you to wait!  Glad you’re ok.  How’s the guy in the car to your left?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve literally been TESTED these last 12 months and I’m still thriving. Resilience is key.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And away we go!! 🤩 Welcome to it! #cheercommandments2019 #thoushallnot #nca https://t.co/tVsntdyV4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patrickcaelan Not that nightmare before Christmas painting looks sooo nice 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[stolen tweets are the equivalent to telling a joke and getting ignored and then someone saying it right after and everyone laughs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnbalancedMemes Wow I’m so glad she fanned her child after blowing smoke on his head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Miss Ruble, I have a brilliant idea. Let’s start practicing TODAY for our next play!” 😳🤩😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Citizenship Question of the Day  What is an amendment?  Listen to the question and answer here:… https://t.co/xeekerhiA3]]></document></documents></author>