<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JWEngelhardt @crerrity @Twitter I mostly agree, but he should know at this point that posting this stuff makes peo… https://t.co/hwr29oBf1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSmithCFB 0-5-CHOKE at the Doak .......guess Doak is the loudest of the loud.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katcatbee @realDonaldTrump Guarantee you that trump could not break 100 without mulligans, his swing is horrible, betting he slices a lot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BENTWOOKlE @Ange_lala_La @ashholesimmons This is toeing the line of whataburger slander. I’ll let you off with a written warning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the new exaggeration and it’s dangerous. Spreading this falsehood on such a volatile subject is going to ge… https://t.co/Yr5tlKq8Kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛫 ORD. Finally. (@ United Airlines Flight UA 2368 in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/L7wGXMgXig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye Douglas, see you soon👋🏿👋🏿👋🏿 (@ Douglas, MI in MI w/ @golfskirun) https://t.co/t7euDEXH0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are both illegal and treasonous. Biggest crook to ever hit the Bigtime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMonimbo USA Senator: Marco Rubio, said that Venezuelan dictator Nicolas Maduro government is on decadence. In add… https://t.co/gtLKW10AC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @HoustonRockets romp past the #76er for their 7th straight win @Jonathan_Feigen #RunAsOne #houstonrockets… https://t.co/HYuj1bxC5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 mins late...I’d be nowhere without these and so many other women!!! 💛💛💛 @ Finding My Way https://t.co/6RQk8NmaD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I know it's sound effects but @Zelina_VegaWWE slap sounded alot more convincing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe not a Reichstag fire so much as checking to see if the Reichstag sprinkler system is disabled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨🏻‍🏫 Raise your hand if you had “woman behind prostitution ring sells Chinese execs access to the President” on the… https://t.co/VhG7RJ3TnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[NM Rep. Deb Haaland @Deb4CongressNM, one of the first Native American women elected to Congress (she’s one of two w… https://t.co/oWJwo3g3tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promise you’ll be more successful and happy if you stop acting how you think you’re supposed to act and start act… https://t.co/2VIXmC26Dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the guy you keep awkwardly bumping into at the hotel breakfast bar is meant to be your next bro for life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman this off-season and spring training has lacked Starbucks and Arby’s observations. Are you OK? Are you on a diet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IP4PI @sarahkliff Consumer 1st Digital Health Network is designed to solve this https://t.co/TVRzLqSXSj https://t.co/X5SjvgCWaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers fans: "I don't give a fuck about beating the Clippers. They ain't shit anyway."  Clippers fans: "I don't giv… https://t.co/5JokUHmYUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, 1 point will be awarded to the driver who achieves the fastest lap in a race, provided that driver is also clas… https://t.co/V4uv6dnUZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidberdbag That doesn’t sound like the actions of a man who laughed all he possibly could.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Let's see. 25,000 jobs, people paying taxes, doing business, buying homes....*bad*.  In exchange for tax break… https://t.co/3aLTTBZi3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CJTS7006 @WalshFreedom This is another example of how divided racists our country is! Jussie lied, deal w/ consequ… https://t.co/lnyRaZrqcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricAllen619 @21Allen619 @CoachWhiteEra @GregBiggins @SJSUSpartanFB Not surprised it’s the 4th; I must have missed… https://t.co/FTLJV16ZwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grannieof10kids @ALLCAPSTWEETX Don’t be too critical about not having a lot of followers. Roger stone dissed me fo… https://t.co/DosIH5YIPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlitaBattleAngel was pretty dang good. Well-paced and incredible visuals. Pay attention to the details.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKornacki Ben is wrong.  My community doesn’t receive the Senator.  Ben is wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shantelstyles You know I'll go to the BX any day, any time for you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tories put Brexit to a referendum, had party members lie about the benefits, triggered article 50, haven’t mana… https://t.co/txA4s87rh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoArabic Hi, If you have any plans to hire a resource from an agency to work on your project remotely, we would be… https://t.co/c7ADcwqipQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes @CalvinKlein Shawn my friend @kropp_top wants you to *puts glasses on* choke her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random thought 💭 during this chat. When we find a way to address issues such as these, then we are really working t… https://t.co/M7BVGGFpJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great night to be a Duck! Men finish season strong w/win streak while ruining perfect home court season for… https://t.co/MuhXqp6gox]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU CAN'T SAY I'M JUST A SPERM DONOR, WHEN YOU WON'T EVEN GIVE ME A CHANCE TO BE IN MY DAUGHTER'S LIFE.... what in… https://t.co/QaBA1zRL9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently Tuesday is Kid’s Night here at Sweet Tomatoes. Young guy is going table to table, entertaining people. H… https://t.co/tTpGaudnz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world of Guild Wars 2 always feels so alive and full of new things to do and new places to explore. The only MM… https://t.co/p9zzXU3Wmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[To travel to an event that might only have 10 entrants but at the end of day, is an event with 10 people not enjoya… https://t.co/YeCCQLDyLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgirvine1989 @Scott11885446 @MisterTrashcan @MetroVideoGame Maybe a bug bro? I playing on rhc and yes they are op… https://t.co/4lZXYviKbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I'd titled a chapter of my book "Liquid Analytics". Went with Croce-esque "Time in a Bottle" instead. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hispanic voters, they too, don’t want socialism in this country, they want Bernie Sanders to be the presidentia… https://t.co/GUlLdhvnWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just sadly reminded in the form of video that alani has some gorilla ass toes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michydoe27_ The one where she said me too she’s agreeing with the black guy who said something about the video]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day ♥️ • • • • • • • #robavalyan #robavalian #robavaliancollection #boys #usa #singer #armenia… https://t.co/zRjfCDiIB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see him play this spring, his 100% effort all the time is greatly appreciated and rare in professiona… https://t.co/Ym6DbtmWol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @EMluvsPibbles @AnimalFarmFndtn @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/FOjclrQlfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Want the Bible to be Wrong !! Because i Wanna god to be a Happy God !! Sincerely yours me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since she cones from a different culture, why in the hell did Minnesotans elect her to represent their values (Amer… https://t.co/lz3rkWr3wW]]></document><document><![CDATA[the towers of the el dorado cast a shadow over @centralparknyc @ El Dorado https://t.co/RQvqoPNA9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[The "business edge" has evolved beyond the regional office or retail branch. So too must the capabilities of "busin… https://t.co/cFmAt9pxoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only thing about working nights , It be  quiet af here’s and they dim the lights on my floor  . I’m so glad I got t… https://t.co/OgnWxSNHfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of all the fucking games I decide to skip its the one we not only win but win dramatically]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Pretty Fly (for a white guy) comes on a pop punk playlist and you’re trying figure out how the hell Rock of Ag… https://t.co/AfkrxFWphN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Juice13_ Snoop top ten ... like 9/10 tho .. drake can rap but top ten rapper all time ? No. Far off my guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[[2/6] #SXSWMusic X #internationalwomensday: @alba_farelo at @sxsw 3/13/18. 📸 by @methodman13 for @BlurredCulture. .… https://t.co/qdwnlOh4b9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Atkinson with fourth shorty of the season!!! 37th of the year!!! 2-0 Jackets!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great weekend with great friends. Now for the long drive back home...]]></document><document><![CDATA[David clearly representing philatelists today... #SupermarketSweep @BUZZRtv https://t.co/gCpkPUmyyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump You're not too bright are you? An inability to synthesis a large fact pattern while stres… https://t.co/QGD4E4ioft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolderStephen Could you see the @colts putting a package together for @obj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Urvaksh @Automotive_News https://t.co/7Msy3pRveJ     https://t.co/feqBq63zTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drone pics of the week...  Looks much warmer that it was... #havedronewilltravel #dronephotography #drone #mavicpro… https://t.co/JD42lsQ5V3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robpetsch I imagine kids are gonna pick this up and glock their friend with it lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[...how many times? ?......until American voters love democracy and their country more than cheap partisan politics.… https://t.co/Zdi1P0zzaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pirates! (@ Swim in Pinellas, FL) https://t.co/9oCiI5JLKr https://t.co/66qiQysY2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge win for @MizzouWBB tonight at No. 5 Miss State.  Beat a  team 22-1 and hasn’t lost at home in 2 years. #MIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellenNordling @RussoHockey I think fans want more from the trades. As in draft picks. I’m not surprised by the tr… https://t.co/CPFxxCFOvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soldierscrystal Just the fact that #Suspiria was nominated and won an award]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re ever feeling down just remember today is Friday and also the Packers have never beaten the Vikings at US Bank Stadium]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakeDanesh @Becca_L_M @okyeahthatworks @JohnTsui12 @Cariteacher @Alyssa_Milano @Arthur_M_author Nah, I get the fac… https://t.co/E05Mbyn7yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyrannosaurCarr Can anyone help me to know if my fossil is indeed a edmontosaurus mummy head I compared it to a sk… https://t.co/Z7CuLOPu51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, @united after a flawless trip last time, two delayed flights (so far) this time. Trust... Eroding... #united… https://t.co/WEGoZ3QWkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenlawrencejr @MontcopaDems @LMNPADems @VAArk @JasonSalus @MayorJeanne @SeanKilkennyPA @NoahMarlier… https://t.co/TqPrQDvakw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on a radio power supply box for my brother today.  I'd do a few things differently if it was for me.  But I… https://t.co/rHjCfE4teA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robando en despoblado y dando dádivas en la campaña continúa a los 30 millones de votantes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEDavidMoulton good sign for Fly. Doing work at FGCU. 8am 2 players working on shooting. No coaches around]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HailstormDavid You: “this is depressing” Also you: “hey, @dbaez2, you should watch this” WHY YOU TRYING TO MAKE ME DEPRESSED 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenn_abbyy I thank god everyday that he blessed me with the prettiest girl and most amazing person on this earth… https://t.co/d3ZcPJw60B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for everything @TheMalikJackson, especially this moment. #DTWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jevnaker92 Will keep that in mind and tag the memes in the future, thanks for letting me know it was something that made you uncomfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my music nerd kicks in...the @startrekcbs #Discovery soundtrack used a phrase from the hymn tune #Nicea during a pivotal scene tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guys @MonmouthBBall are keeping this train going. No time like now to be hot fellas. Leggo #HawkEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toca Madera 8450 W 3rd St, Los Angeles, CA 90048 (323) 852-9400 https://t.co/ryYevgWCsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg Journalists are currently their own worst enemies, they don’t need help from anyone else.  Go back… https://t.co/W1jCqnm5ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovelyMonster97 agreed, I absolutely still get my life to them every time I listen to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divaquise @bearlyjeremiah You guys make a fantastic couple! I hope one day I will be as blessed. 🙏👨‍❤️‍👨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Anywhere and everywhere that Democrats are in charge the economy tanks and the rights and privilages… https://t.co/cJNvgiAlL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pantherzfan4lif @queensfirm @BoAStadium How bout Jack's Militia and leave it 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish @KatyTurNBC will let guests finish their thoughts. When she interrupts, it implies they’re wrong, or she’s s… https://t.co/t5EDRGjSz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geekmystic @aisghair That's what I thought I remembered, but then I decided I was too tired to figure it out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec I know exactly what each one of those democrat anti Americans are thinking 🤔, they thinking why can i… https://t.co/GdpAvx4BOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT - Reflections on Two Years Since @50States100Days, LIVE from Huntington Station, NY ...… https://t.co/Q7bw63tmg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RingFalcon @JustJeremyHeyYo @MichaelFloydHa2 @smarktodeath @DoItWithFlareon @DaGreekOlive24 @Krystina_Death… https://t.co/jj0WtDSI5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyPrinceton @AG_Conservative Because true MAGA hats would have gotten themselves attacked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelisDave Happy caturday to you, my good friend Dave, from your pal Snoopy. https://t.co/AJXUWB3ZpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a great weekend in Miami with the @miamicityballet performing (among other things) the Martinu Piano Conc… https://t.co/kdP9JKqHnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good people can't do what Trump did to those children. And still sleep at night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen with the RECEIPTS.  This won’t turn out well. #CohenTestimony https://t.co/dHjjM8kzn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost abcworldnewstonight with get_repost ・・・ TURPINS PLEAD GUILTY: David and Louise Turpin, a California couple… https://t.co/oI17nlZdc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donald_Driver80 @DrinkBODYARMOR It’s a toss up between Tropical and Strawberry Banana for this guy]]></document></documents></author>