<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is such a wonderful activity! Making a positive difference...one child at a time! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Tharp crossed 10K. Time 00:57:36, pace 09:13 min/mile, est. finish 9:14 am https://t.co/gbutb6woeD #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASA @NASAaero This is, well, ground breaking, (not at all like air braking!) Exciting technology. Congratulations… https://t.co/Z5iHcHsz6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher Who’s going to create the AirPod holder that doubles as one of those pop things on the back of the phone case?]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS PISCES SEASON BITCHESSSSS AND IVE ALREADY CRIED 3 TIMES TODAY!! let’s get this bday month bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[I temporarily reactivated my Facebook.. I haven’t been on since 2010. Is there a way to erase my whole profile and… https://t.co/NBsE2JyLox]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ox knoweth his owner, and the ass his master's crib: but Israel doth not know, my people doth not consider. https://t.co/qgX6b2S6mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[tried to sleep with a sleep mask last night but my subconscious mind must’ve said fuck that because I woke up two times to it gone 🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Give it up!  So tired of this old song and dance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The action is the chart I just sent you. @SecretaryAcosta : please meet with @GovernorTomWolf and Mike to discuss p… https://t.co/eavNkqbFe7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d do it all over again seriously the most beautiful experience ever♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 5:15am and none of the airport restaurants are open and I’m tired.   Note to future Gillian: stop doing this. Just stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother ordered insomnia cookies for me and all my roomies for valentine’s day... who needs a boyfriend anyway???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Valley CA Sun Mar 10th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 42 MONDAY Chance Of Showers Hi 61]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then some of y’all actually bump these girls but front on social media cause y’all scared on what the next mf gon day 😭 BE YOURSELF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannygonzalez Fuck lasso. Fuck umg. we reviewing legal options all of 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@respiewak @cricketcrocker @_Astro_Nerd_ I never heard of this until you retweeted the thread, and I've been to sev… https://t.co/LsvlQFce6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you still alive?Would love to hear from you once in awhile Assure me you're ok@km_rust]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldKerry Well after some digging and family answering why his DNA didn't match his brothers or sisters...suddenly.… https://t.co/sWlNeGeKMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shrushhhka That’s really interesting! What sign is your 4th house in and do you have any planets there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a memorable #ValentinesDay2019 ! #NotoPipelines @GreenpeaceCA @GreenpeaceCA #canpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[You just can’t get a better sunset #californiasunset https://t.co/AiYx5vwp6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanDreyerNBC The Sneetches (90% from memory) is our go-to in our family. In this day and age it's more relevant… https://t.co/Z9mBoVj2eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howiemandel. We are trolling Instagram..Twitter and YouTube looking for @CourtneyHadwin. Singing with @TheStruts .… https://t.co/VCB8AaS42w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KianLawley Post pics of the women that inspire you. I will start. Johnetta Elzie, Ferguson activist. https://t.co/tVBORIlgIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little winter white for all the snow ❄️ outside- new post is up on the blog: https://t.co/WXLWvGD2MO 📸:… https://t.co/ziaa9HZHjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OntarioMasters Invest in marketing activity developed by an experienced  company or resource who understands your… https://t.co/i26r5940eM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always remember the day you kissed my lips Light as a feather And it went just like this https://t.co/hl2VWAq6fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @girlscouts @penguinkids @RaiseYourHand5 @Oprah Alice- you an amazing young women with such a bright future👏👏👏👏👏🎉🖐🖐🖐🖐]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know how strong you are until being strong is the only choice you have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anticipation season. Two of fourteen trees. #mangoes #bloom #Irwin #Beverly #Miami https://t.co/qqAKGBo6HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad I have my winter coat in Tennessee. #makingsongs @ La Vergne, Tennessee https://t.co/uBJVovUfb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Italian aunt drinks wine with EVERYTHING.... last night, she poured us both a glass of wine and we drank it with… https://t.co/XgFZLWr92j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momofbunnies We've received the official 'All Clear' by now. You should be safe to return to class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonCouture Assuming you meant the Chris Gray goal against Vermont lacrosse today? https://t.co/EPYKUpLytw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Erie, PA? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/itAzHQlo6l #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuclearAnthro Yep. “With bells on” in the slang sense would not be a bad translation.  And using «ехали» rather th… https://t.co/bvETPESCGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Really we are haters because we want a president that isn’t a lying, cheating con artist. This jus… https://t.co/ZKYsWCLS0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate those dreams that are so real that you wake up gripped by the emotions of the them. I woke up this morning w… https://t.co/n2TDs2dQPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter would be so much more entertaining if users had a basic understanding of fallacies 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to boys basketball in Norwell I stopped at my favorite teacher supply store “Teachers Rule” only to hear… https://t.co/ILS7W2ehsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiktok_us Get your dang livestreaming situated!! It still won't work on most android phones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dstluke @imcorinnemec I have no idea, I was just looking for a hell yeah gif playing guitar lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a minute to explore the updated Cavalier after the Circle of Excellence luncheon and decided I'm moving in! 😂… https://t.co/XogGZ31K6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinScampi @LinglingDemocat In Lingling's case it was a rescue. My cat Classy had disappeared- she had been gone… https://t.co/RFo4FcXAUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfehr2 @ElieNYC @amjoyshow @realDonaldTrump same! best line of the day 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume His evidence is his wish, worthless. His sexual exploits do not seem to be what he investigates. SHIFTY SCHIFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThongThursday Repost from chelseabeaudin He bought sand to the beach cause his bitch is better 🌞💦 @ New York, New… https://t.co/G92nTXVGmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricAllwardt No it came out right. That’s for sure a good boy I would snuggle with. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annefrances This was the best scene laughed my ass off. I love Alexis https://t.co/aAyPZvcIrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I‘ve always been team @duffgoldman. Aside from generally preferring @Charm_CityCakes’ style and the fact I feel the… https://t.co/VWOldpVyYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I’ve learned about umami has been from @shokugeki_anime https://t.co/k39UYqAs3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[HotNewHipHop: Instagram Gallery: Alexis Skyy's Sexiest Pics. https://t.co/s3HEVVTaNa  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to utilize all the tools in the toolbox to help solve the opioid epidemic ... that will include full legali… https://t.co/r5umyBf0qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeltWitch @Fact_Check_Er @pollsofpolitics @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Now you're attacking my CITY? Wow.  That;s very… https://t.co/NyBcjL0bdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[also mandy moore brought up one of the most glossed over points with abusive men: "his controlling behavior essenti… https://t.co/YKj1H76I7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AvAccc_slp @funder @realDonaldTrump They say insecure people like to constantly brag about themselves and put others down]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2 I’m a Parent Ambassador and I love visiting schools and posting the great things happening in our classrooms. I… https://t.co/ppwEkig7X8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a whirlwind couple of days.  Regret, and lack of, rule on partner thrones.  Such is life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irisastraea i’d love a reading from you 😭 how much are you asking love? i think it could really help with my peace of mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to a man whose apparently had the sauce since ‘88 ❤️ can’t wait to smash a 🍕with you to celeb… https://t.co/UtiNAg8DDk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recieved an Email from the Detective re: my Niece Killer still on the streets.He stated its not a "Cold Case" Im… https://t.co/GnMdOx85aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie about to drop him like it’s hot #TheBachelor https://t.co/3Tkqq91vZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[sound...i’m starting to love the sound of my feet walking away from things not meant for me. 🍃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our students continue to shine!! @WestburySup @DragonPride @theparkavenues2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remove @IlhanMN from @HouseForeign Committee.  Listen to the song and Retweet it.  No double standards for anti-Sem… https://t.co/TDHmm8E8Wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dj_RTistic Yeah dude..its a new version of 90s r&amp;b + Studio [schoolboy q] + cardi's flow =..it will be played all year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@995KFUN thanks for the opportunity to win the KFUN in the sun trip! I look forward to giving my acceptance speech this Friday 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle has said it also, so both Obama and Michelle have said that he was not born in the United States!🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PineyElem our awesome @EcoSchoolsUSA #MonarchHeroes + our fantastic #ArtsPartner @DaCameraHouston = extraordinary… https://t.co/r2MSZmIgSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Mainly, as we all know, including you, your wall will be ineffective against border secu… https://t.co/EdGg1xVuqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latestarterfire Yep, Adelaide has some good ones! Austin, along with Christchurch (NZ), Himeji (Japan) and Georgetown (Penang, Malaysia).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlight of my day: somebody walking into my dorm room and making it all the way into the hallway of bedrooms befo… https://t.co/JUS68SOsHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hoopfest meets #HammyDays. Headed on stage to dance in Ham on Regal with my Hoopfest team’s coach and the team’s h… https://t.co/9cq8Xb4BPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paublancoynegro Lo más estúpido y biased que he leído hoy. 😂 y no soy feminista mi soy lesbiana diga @jocelyne4394]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hadip @60Minutes @codeorg @ayahbdeir I want to make sure that is crystal clear because sometimes our personalities… https://t.co/eiKKFiv69P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 Isn’t it interesting, you are being judged by criminals.  Don’t you think the world should know of… https://t.co/MM5VLbmOWD]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the first time, i’ve experience this must of changes of times...i should be almost to florida right now but… https://t.co/dHKeEdykN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: UCLA moves on to the semifinals with a 73-69 win over ASU. They will play the winner of Arizona vs Oregon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changing clocks still...I bought this in Delft Netherlands a few years ago when visiting my online Dutch friends. (… https://t.co/bW9vuc3SaQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleylayneee Ugh. Serious withdrawals....need a concert now. 😩@bretteldredge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PorterTWC The traditions and folklore handed down is always the best reference point for any location!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregpmiller Sad part everything McCabe has written is true I am sorry he had to deal with these two disgusting nas… https://t.co/SeIYOoKlSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sister is on her way to Charlotte for a dance competition... she’s clever ain’t she? https://t.co/scon3wpV1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[When i genuinely stop caring, and i mean REALLLLY stop caring, you won’t hear a peep outta me. See, silence is the… https://t.co/zquNEkqvAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for RJ Barrett for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/85bVVSKMqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you say to comfort a grammar teacher? "They're, there, their!  😜😜😂😂 My students have the best grammar teach… https://t.co/HDTpwFsx8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[He just wrecked Harvick and Larson that’s gonna make him super popular...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCWard7teacher @rmc031 @jonbecker @DrPrestonGreen @dcpublicschools 🙋🏾‍♀️ 2yrs after a reconstitution where I was f… https://t.co/4gDP9uG62Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IntuitTurbo My dream is to be debt free going into retirement! #RealMoneyTalk  #Sweepstakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[i sat down and charted for the first time today and this funky ass nurse gon ask me to do vitals on 2 of my patient… https://t.co/vvGVAObLAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lithuanian Ceburekai (aka beef pockets) 😛😛😛 #InternationalCooking #Ceburekai #Lithuania #GoLemont https://t.co/h2KPdDFK0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedThreadFarms @BootscootinGMaw @AGofTheWorld Be careful what you wait for 😜🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickeyDollens Where are we at with the changing table bill?? This wobbly thing is severely lacking 😑🤦🏻‍♀️🙈 https://t.co/nVAcLb0VOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new reclining seats are in at the Slaughter Drafthouse! @ Alamo Drafthouse Slaughter Lane https://t.co/JvEqDgna6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregolear People I shared these stories with two years ago told me I was crazy. Nope...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @spacetimeltd You think they are the same? Go tell that to the families of the lost souls of… https://t.co/0XVew1legU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MzKatieCassidy Laurel Lance always trying to save the world. Even Earth 2 Laurel is going through some really good changes! #Arrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomboyD Oh right!! I forgot about the FEC filings! And the discrepancies in the ones they DID file. Wasn’t there… https://t.co/ktZAYnBze3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready for @OfficialLivePD here in Texas but my Nikko is just ready for bed 😂 @PascoSheriff #9PMRoutine #LivePd https://t.co/2VRoZTL5tK]]></document></documents></author>