<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Dlbstyle @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump @OANN Still crying over your lose  your Psychiatrist probably has something s… https://t.co/poeriC3aIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eileen_Ellis @ReaganBattalion @BernieSanders Not sure if he can but they will leave nothing to chance and attack all that try]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaymitch : "you'll get there too one day bitch"  @bretmanrock :"jokes on you, i plan on dying soon."   I really felt that 😬🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skye_Carrington It just keeps getting worse. 🙈 but I still look forward to every new episode 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to some of our favorites: Betty’s Luncheon, Josie’s New York Deli, Giacomo’s, George’s Pizzeria...… https://t.co/86ASd8vcbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOSullivan36 @Mysteri759 @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton She wouldn’t have met with that slimy murderer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m explaining twitter to my mom &amp; how she belongs to 30+ twitter... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to go shopping for anything including groceries with Awkwafina. #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YandR_CBS The Rosales Show getting old people, want the real #YR back people. FF this BS all Rosales can go away for good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That thing when you finish a workout and then you don’t want to move ever again (but you gotta)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I like it better when Sarah doesn't do press briefings. She is so hateful to reporters and democrats that i… https://t.co/teXdE0xue4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg I love you 😘 Thank you for being so awesome 😎 #loveeternal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cindymccain @michellemalkin @SenJohnMcCain He was a republican sometimes. A democrat others. But he has cost me $3… https://t.co/rlzk3IPYKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of remedyaca for winning 1st in our ICCA Quarterfinal!! 💕 (swipe to see the sweat dripping down my face) @… https://t.co/T1GY82nXkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryPask @ericboettger56 @high5assfuck @maydaymindy9 Barry, maurice and robin! I would say Andy and Barry got… https://t.co/WyF2vy5NDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timhays22 @criZzy_p My dad said God took some IQ points from us when he forgot the rest of the pigment for our hai… https://t.co/WtQ9peujdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great end to @thielcollege Tomcat Accepted Student Day. #commit https://t.co/ihDH0y44XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathiametz @angel_travels2 @Caygrl3 @myrealitytea @Andy Are you sure? Thought it was the other way round sister slept with Jackie husband.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahAmador3 @DowneyPatriot @DowneyASB @DowneyHigh @downeylinkcrew As an alumni I will be there 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OLCoachHam All because of you sir! Wouldn’t have this opportunity at all! Much Love coach!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClariceFox4 I like Mark but not sure politics is his forte or better said that "Washington" politics is not. I'm o… https://t.co/1iAgfpvZs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faut connaître la scène au complet pour émettre une opinion éclairée. Je te suggère de Googler ça 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The American people elected Clinton. The electoral college elected you. Why should we recognize yo… https://t.co/zvrwk8ROvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bliews_com You don't! But we can vote that mf out of office. He's bringing pain to whites now so maybe they'll get… https://t.co/mXMYuN7FVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you think Alec Baldwin will play you in Cohen’s movie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[so i got that toews goal on video and then my snapchat didn’t save it.... I AM SOOOO MAD!!!! i loved that video 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another happy customer!!! Love this stuff!!! @ Vancouver, Washington https://t.co/habDXUCyzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeanetteh83 @CortesSteve Not the same. That was another time taken out of context, referring to O.J. Simpson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You spineless twat! Your adoration of despots like KJU rather than condemnation of his brutality t… https://t.co/pbz2SIi3v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ideas for dining area.  What do you think? A little mid century modern, a little coastal, a little bohemian, and a… https://t.co/56PnSJeTEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would absolutely love to drink rosé with malia obama while we hate on tr*mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop with the pics / servers to further promote dumbing down of America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loureynolds1940 @dcexaminer @DWStweets @realDonaldTrump me toooo!  so aggravating to have that horrible talking po… https://t.co/TmGmIjA8XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, you are spot on about #45, he’s something.  Oh, you want a bit of insight to him? Read Stormy Daniels’ book Fu… https://t.co/kk7I9umSnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aromatherapy candles. Another great gem! Created by the talented taylorwinslow 🌷 #shoplocal #supportlocalbusiness… https://t.co/d0yXOsPE6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForumNissen @posoem @KathrynMaga @GeorgePapa19 @senjudiciary @SethAbramson @LouiseMensch @CNN @Acosta @maddow… https://t.co/ivHrS4aC9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany If you believe the political world started with Bill Clinton in 1993 you will have no sense of the… https://t.co/ITqxHT6k4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veganbrieana @jordanshrinks @ZachAttacksFat Good call 😂 The discounted shipping for 5-12 pkgs is less than USPS fl… https://t.co/sGo8IhfZu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching The Golden Girls “72 Hours”! This shit was so ahead of its time! Do y’all know how important enough for a… https://t.co/gEgHhOY3tZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Read your timeline old man. Your tweets only serve as a landfill for decent ppl to… https://t.co/kqveQvu3JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lfgg536 No ni hombre ni nujer y nibguna cualidad debe de ser presumida.. Te hace ver ostentoso y arrogante.. Ni la… https://t.co/f1ju6cxjYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@busbee_deborah @elder_jodi @koolkaryn @LadyInHats @simplyemc @Idclair @ladyred1956 @heckyessica @FishFunSun @AOC… https://t.co/WROwVjFQhT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have Three eyes. Two to look and One to see! #LoveNote @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/muW7xRnpPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why was I crying so much during Leonards date?! #DatingAroundNetflix so much cuteness]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the BEST time with @brianandtera learning about different birds and their adaptations! Thank you so much for… https://t.co/GgLKD2GN97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ik y’all know this but this is my favorite song &amp; I’ll share it weekly on this app until i tire of it ✨  https://t.co/L9TWRGh9sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leafs3434 I only have 20 lbs or less on her — she may be the closest in weight that I’ve met, other than @UrsaFierce!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A message from the unknowable Universe. @ Fremont, California https://t.co/eGYgMjPK03]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you should throw them some paper towels. What ever happened to Puerto Rico?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our next Intro to Stretch Therapy workshop is just a few weeks away! Register now for this two day dive into how st… https://t.co/hh3PbVPrLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone’s down to cashapp me $20 so I can buy myself a gram I’d love you 5 evaaa 🆘🆘]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Starbucks California Gift Set at @Poppysweeps - you can too https://t.co/3dLTaITEGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpcunningham8 @DanCrenshawTX The president of the board of trustees unilaterally decided to banish the Pledge. She… https://t.co/k4KY9Cghoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolaMControl You ok sis? ❤️ love you. Text me if u need to talk 💕 always]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhhHumanity @MoreWastedYears @amyklobuchar You respect someone that WASTED millions of taxpayer dollars for nothing????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeC1163 See, now you’re liberal and I don’t upset you. Why is that?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinaaaxo @havana_ariana @rock_chick @JustTrace9 @devii_dess @Queenshoard @OfficerMooken I understand why they are… https://t.co/7Ht5Qq5A9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oksnastark12 @seanflanery @Robinson7Rick @smoking_reedus @StephanieMatne1 @Cheryl_W61 @snegurkaV @BlackCherry8692… https://t.co/dZ0R33fGVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went from 'Secreto' w/ Anuel AA on repeat to 'Soy Peor' cause fuck people in relationships rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBlkshrt He will only get my vote if he turns out to be the nominee. I find it hard to believe that he could win over the majority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así se van uniendo para hacer otra masa, con características increíbles de progreso.  Tenemos tanto trabajo como re… https://t.co/qMA8XVTMqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried getting back into bed quietly so I wouldn’t wake up chandler but I didn’t completely sit on the bed and fel… https://t.co/tZZyeNG3VD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming soon! 👶🏽✌🏽👶🏽#BigBrotherMak #2under2 #MakJames #MarryMeMak @ Old Fourth Ward https://t.co/YrF0bc9byn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 can you please DM me. I really want to talk to you. I've been trying to get your attention for awhile. 💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Who are you, Senator Sanders, to tell people what they can buy? Such a scary question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so tired of white privilege BS! Let’s do a short list of white man inventions: Printing press, telegraph, steam… https://t.co/1LQwQ5u2xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahrileylong @GameOfThrones I have a feeling it’s going to be a bittersweet ending... 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t have friends that hype you up when you feel like you’re drowning, you need new friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Lent, my church is studying “busy”, but I’m going to be studying ashes, fire and Phoenixes. Something glorious, I suspect, will arise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[True Love Always!!! #mom #daughter #granddaughter #angel  #myvalentines #missmyboys @ Grantsville, Utah https://t.co/X1SzYDPX6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke at 5:45 am and thought “at least I slept thru the night.” Next thought: “This is what Monday morning will feel… https://t.co/PMGuoB0Idm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just dropped my Econ class because it doesn’t spark joy in me! Thanks Marie Kondo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chaosfeminist @CMichaelGibson I never said a thing @ diagnosing. I said support 2 patient &amp; family during the video conference 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vaccine reactions suck but I’d rather my baby have a slight reaction that makes her clingy and just a little grouch… https://t.co/zARpChI0C7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningCommute (1 of 4 parts)  My usual riding partner, Tony, has the day off. So his seat next to me is empty. I… https://t.co/Zi7NMFX2Ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double the love for these doodles. #labradoodle  #goodtobehome  #doodles #dogsofinstagram  #puppylove @ Parkland, F… https://t.co/wcHew7jKJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoNotBother8 @AirCanada Thank you so much, I saw how beautiful the earth looked and had to take it. 📸😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Of course you should put them in east and west coast cities that are oversaturated with options! It would… https://t.co/pUxfCtD4tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PinkPinkpetunia @CarlWorsham @MarkDice @CHueyBurns @MaeveReston @KamalaHarris She did!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow just used my hair mask and instead of leaving it in for 5 minutes I left it in for 30 and I feel like I could b… https://t.co/46lxwy6QBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really interesting (entertaining) reporting about how Trump's schools chose to deal with his school records, especi… https://t.co/sTUZryp7xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My car was snowed in for 5 days. Move to the east coast they said, it’ll be fun they said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betholmert I literally cried when Randy's dad showed me this....so sad. I can't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlobalWoman @WineTasmania @paigelovesbooks I’m going to be at @Dark_Mofo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @miss9afi @Imamofpeace What is going on? Does Twitter respond to requests from Pakistan? Who filed… https://t.co/MQQDk17X7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Grateful Hearts,❤️ Good morning Heavenly Father,🙏🏽 Thank You for waking me up.🙋🏽‍♀️ Thank You for anot… https://t.co/S73kIy8cMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to catch an international flight this year idk where but I know I’m going somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does everyone remember this  ? I think reality of what she said is coming true. Who is the half involved with her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pokemonswordshield   Está bien referenciado y vinculado con la región en la que están basándose que en este caso e… https://t.co/hAGLwxiOUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[FarmLink is a program that connects Canadians who WANT to farm with those lands that NEED farmers, or have part of… https://t.co/RvFWyA7JnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just how did Democrats block a debate? This is beyond stupid...even from Dipshit Donny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsDomK Need not to explain. We all have been there. Your family is hear for you 😘😘🙏🏽💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priya_breezy We gone do like it's about to be the end of the world and they depending on us to make earth shaken a… https://t.co/Zx8ik4KWzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU HAVE BEEN GOOD         For By Your Hand We Have Been Fed, And By Your Spirit We Have Been Led.- Twila Paris]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 409 has THREE teams playing for State Championships tomorrow! #409Sports #txhshoops @HJladyhawks #Woodville… https://t.co/0IpqLIAuGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ultimatecircuit #studiofitness  #crunch #dailyfitpost #fitchick #fitchicksofig  #coretraining  #core #workout… https://t.co/BNHVCv7iwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cprwarner @thericandback @adukakis Erica, why pile it on the poor piano though?! 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stooop with the cute stuff @lecreuset! 🍀💚: Clover Cocotte https://t.co/wIi7kzyefF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBillinglsey Can’t wait to see where you go. You will do great whatever you do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Saabrina_Marie Of course not you, yoouuu doo everything you say as far as I know so you solid in my book 🤞🏽]]></document></documents></author>