<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Picked up some yummy pastries at #butterbaker 🥐🍞🥧🍰🍪🎂 ❣️ @ Butter Baker https://t.co/k4PhlEAhkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch @ChelseaFC all matches Live for free Via our website  Link🌐&gt; https://t.co/tHBIJhAGHG  Link⚽️&gt;… https://t.co/CAcNoq7AWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giadamatelli2 @KTVU I’m not related to @VickyNguyenTV. Nguyen is a common (and #Nguyening) Vietnamese last name. S… https://t.co/NOm6qCGiv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This niche tweet is brought to you for people who are both fans of Riverdale and have knowledge of Al editions of D&amp;D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking my green juice, and just witnessed a regular dude use a telephone booth to piss real quick. Real New York… https://t.co/mfqkIkpNet]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myfirstbook #tellyourstory #sharetoshine #yourstiryispowerful #contentcreatorchallenge @ Erie, Pennsylvania https://t.co/or9vd6ociI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheeto377 No patience for these people! It’s not the 1950s any longer 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veto if needed, I'm hoping the Senate doesn't let America down! #BuildTheDamnWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to note, I continued to use the word “it” instead of them when describing a child. I did this to quote… https://t.co/DqNjp5Rb9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruinsDaily @tdgarden Thank you @BruinsDaily It was a day of #fraternity #family &amp; great #hockey for a great cause @ResponderHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henryrodgersdc @DailyCaller @TheDemocrats believe in power, not democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurdOnTheHill you are NOT a Republican/Conservative nor a true Texan- You are a Rino !  Intelligent and HONEST ppl… https://t.co/kWbeAeekQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunny @JoyVBehar @MeghanMcCain @HuntsmanAbby Re #kraft prostitution legal issues. I'm beginning to think that the… https://t.co/w09rlCmAmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven't been to #leelee you don't know what you've been missing!!!  A little slice of heaven... @ Lee Lee's… https://t.co/1QaFdaA45O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyWilliams of all the times for you to be gone. This Jussie #JussieSmollettHoax  has us in a code RED. Gurl- ta… https://t.co/lb9MYjChOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted  My Mammas Too But I Really Dont Have Time Or Eneg6 Anymore For People  .Shit Hurts Odee But I'm done 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma have to hit the block if I want to go to this concert. Prices are ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone’s traveling to another country soon and wants to bring a friend I can fit in a suitcase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emptywheel ok a toss up as to who to post on,, methinks the one who believes me the least because this is about to… https://t.co/6e1gwriq4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers are FAMILY We are here and We stay! @SYFY @IDWPublishing Put our cast and crew back to work!… https://t.co/TSjaueZxdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMikeHuckabee @DVSanders1 It also has forever damaged the Committee and the Democrats. No matter how you put it,… https://t.co/Q6TJb4ad3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This collection! Thank you, Natalie, for your wholehearted support of students!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickyleepotts Refusing technology I guess? Actually became a running joke at the club as I had never even seen it… https://t.co/Mlq0ECAdf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomGibson5705 @RealKyleMorris @MAGAPILL I feel like it's more... "dont care what you have to say because we have our own shitty New Deal"]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future is bright, but not as bright as my highlight 😂 @jeffreestar   #makeuptutorial #loveyourself #influencer… https://t.co/p2YCKb7yEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's my girl! 💕  #Repost kesifelton with get_repost ・・・ Better to Speak: The Book Drive is back! In honor of Nati… https://t.co/rrcWU6jahW]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day, 5 years ago, I committed to moving to NYC for the dream job at NYU &amp; my life changed forever 💜 https://t.co/8GTnS2gEAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[For what is the hope of the hypocrite, though he hath gained, when God taketh away his soul? https://t.co/xQA74zlQPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Who could be worse than this? Democrats don't need to redeem you for this when you had 16 normal people but needed entertainment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most relaxing blast game  Down Link :  https://t.co/jptAixxK96 https://t.co/MJvo36VfKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This very Christian man who speaks like he is still fighting the civil war, has been married 4 times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@openargs In re the most recent TTTBE, why is C an obviously nonsense answer? Is it because res ipsa loquitor clear… https://t.co/PqcxeQlBnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Did they ask him just how young the girl Spanky was with was (like maybe, 13)? Oh sorry, I meant he girls E… https://t.co/ckcbENjppu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men don’t matter, so next time let me know next time when I get super espresso depresso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we stop fighting about Bernie for awhile? He stands a very small chance of winning the dem nomination. Let’s qu… https://t.co/OoNO4efjAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDianaW @VisionTV @MarthaMoonWater @hallmarkchannel @HallmarkDrama @RealCrystalLowe @kristintbooth… https://t.co/5BVj5dp0ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog The best. Fabulous. She cracks me up every night. Love ya, Rachel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatieLy78 So proud of this young lady. Smart, strong and funny all in one cute package.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live Life as if  EVERYTHING  is Rigged in your 🔥FAVOR 🔥  On Sale  NOW   👇💎👇💎👇💎👇💎👇💎👇 https://t.co/kVHXUWVmCR  • • •… https://t.co/EMp6vGkTnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talgemain @MAarenau "(...)if someone accused that Jews was collaborating with the Nazis(...)" So who were these Je… https://t.co/xKPgQZWK5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@07Malouin07 @patmartin91 @lazurit_plus @EfiMakri7 @EKirkopoulou @juliecole196012 @ShireenWiel @AngelHealingArt… https://t.co/GxIeE6T83z]]></document><document><![CDATA[all black? what’s new @ Embassy Suites by Hilton Indianapolis Downtown https://t.co/e3BfWIKl9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desclowe i only got one episode left it’s def worth the watch the plot line is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LeavingNeverland What if someone accused you of sexually molesting a child and it wasn’t true. Who would believe y… https://t.co/tMWWH6fJlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago today, my sweet boyfriend walked into my life for the first time ❤️ I won’t bore you with the long sto… https://t.co/sXU9jRLWkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best looking booth,  by far! @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/OVUi6KelO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jrbacon50 You’re right. It will not create competition. It will gut public schools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClandestineRos1 @BrAiNfReEzE69 The Dems are blind &amp; very stupid! In 2020 vote ALL Dems out of office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[lauren daigle’s music just brightens my day. like I love worship music but hers is just on a different level sometimes 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Stick you’re head up Nancy Pelosi’s ASS and see if you can find her BRAIN ! Both of you LIE ,CHEAT and… https://t.co/d7qt2oUcQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hate people; they’re such assholes. Theft in all forms raises costs for everyone else. Selfish pricks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWorldWatch @__TheScript__ @JerylBier It's in the video. He said it right before "his lack of sensibility"]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #BridalShow day! Getting signs and samples ready for the show here in #Indy today 💍 #calligraphy #weddinginspo https://t.co/jGkxa11Cy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to change &amp; my mom bought me some Nutella...it be ya own people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanmburke I was at the game last night but luckily i set my DVR. you did an outstanding job!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenscomtrust Such a splendid snippet. Proving____ how important the DOS is (locally, globally) for that "needle"… https://t.co/8gAYelOu90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithppereira @AbdominalCase @TirathPatelMD @DrSoGu @DrIanWeissman @AKrishnarajMD @DaniaDaye @ARRS_Radiology… https://t.co/RkPHxITAmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tolmanbrett @BillOReilly @NoSpinNews The ACCUSATIONS have been PUBLIC, the findings should be too! It’s called TRANSPARENCY!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @MarieKondo gets invited to the #oscars, you know things are changing. #minimalism #givesyoujoy #livewithpurpose #tidyingup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eric says the next person on the moon should take a statue of Alice Kramden and leave it there. #thehoneymooners @… https://t.co/zzDDtXZzww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you San Francisco. From the bottom of my belly. From the tip of my feet and up. Love love love. https://t.co/2HzFgvf8sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You’re never alone.”  . What an experience! . “Small Mouth Sounds”  Thank you A Public Fit Theatre!! .… https://t.co/1ghReNtV6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my boyfriend hits a pothole while driving my car, and I’m waiting for him to realize]]></document><document><![CDATA[Line ‘em up!  One change from last week’s #NERevs lineup with @Mance888 in today against @ColumbusCrewSC for the ho… https://t.co/ZY6F6rrrRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VernBB 0, Elms 0 Mid 1  Blankebiller works around a two-out double aided by a great diving play by Briner at 1st.   #d3baseball #d3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobjoyce27 Never fear, already done!!! It’s pretty sweet if if I say so myself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caesar anyone?! . . #lempin #caesar #clamatojuice @ Cactus Club Cafe https://t.co/V7JrGqQnYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quickest decision ever. Got 2 @dennislloyd_ VIP MEET AND GREET TICKETS IN SF ❤️❤️ SEE YOUUUUUU😭 https://t.co/oGL4Z39tKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FairContractNow #CTUACTSstrike #CICSGreed #WhereIsShaw #CICSSchools #KindaBigDeal #AreWeCICS. CICS DOUBLED ADMIN S… https://t.co/taxejEBBlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 I'll Find You (Feat. @torikelly ) by @lecrae on @PandoraMusic ❤️❤️ https://t.co/djgUfMJwes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow just hit an epic hunting rifle snipe and that was probably the peak of my gaming career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Quoting @RealCandaceO, “time out for puritanical conservatism.” Those days went sideways in 2016.… https://t.co/BQUEhtam9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamzinblake @raganwald I feel like Pokémon names also provide a simple argument against deadnaming. Like you’d nev… https://t.co/6AI3cM0VYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MasterTyson1993 @Pornhub Oh hush. One leap at a time 😂 I have 10 other platforms 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harpdesignco Coming down this weekend to celebrate my B’day !  I need a charcuterie Board in my life 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanah_13 Where are your seats? Did you splurge and get DNA? I’m coming with @Goofy322Tracey. We have seats in th… https://t.co/uWbQF1AUX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s break this down:Khloe stole Tristan when he was with pregnant Jordyn (different1)Kylie stole Trav when he was… https://t.co/6ZKvTLg8Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best FU...is to level up every time to the most potential you have.… https://t.co/nfasE4m31o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutsidersHouse Might have jumped the gun on booking my flight...looks like I might just miss it by a hair...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraLisaVogl @DFinsterwalder @Wallon_ @_LucasRizzotto I’m in! I’ll DM you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liberalism owns the Dems.Liberalism is now Socialism. Take away piece by piece the Constitution and what's LEFT, bu… https://t.co/w41iNIgybl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody want a 200 year old MacBook. I’ll pay YOU to get it out of my sight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bits and pieces streamed together. Bob Seger concert at the forum.  Thank you Mike Parker for bringing me along.… https://t.co/jRxD6BlV5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[New way of thinking about things. @ Santa Rosa, California https://t.co/ujTE9gihi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaleeAdams @RealJamesWoods Everybody ends up doing less. Lose self drive to do better. ...  I read about restaur… https://t.co/Ng3wuqimM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I really be out here dead. People do not look like their pictures 😂😭 AT ALL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coryfarleymusic  Saw you in nashville last night. #GreatMusic #GirlsWeekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snake_adia Ive asked myself the same question a plethora of times and never have an answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A one minute journey through wine country. #life #adventure #journey #winecountry #california #napavalley #vinyards… https://t.co/QPTZlaczk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews We had Slave Day when I was in HS. Back then it was a fund raiser and all in good fun, I was bought tw… https://t.co/Z3J26fIGB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @PressSec Or is it because you are a shameful, disgraced excuse for an American who should reexamin… https://t.co/hhthRX6gqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA Dems are trying to fix gerrymandering. Why don't you put your money where your mouth is and join Pres Obama… https://t.co/HrjZkU2E7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Support the Smithfield High School unified sports teams and make a donation to my plunge page! I’ll be plunging Mar… https://t.co/TJTS22TMIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is only with the heart that we can truly see...  #mayalllovesurroundyou… https://t.co/FHIMqMSzEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy I got the job and will probably work the same shift as my bestfriend 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I’m doing the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge! I’m posting the covers of the books I love: no reasons, no reviews… https://t.co/oX5dZTWfjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best shot of the night. Of course @StephenCurry30 was involved.  #NBAAllStar #NBATwitter #Curry]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t blame lady Gaga. When I saw Bradley Cooper, I was memorized by his beautiful eyes. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always good to see BIG tonyditcharo #morninggrind  #gymtime cjgranda and I got our #miles in for @runrgrrun… https://t.co/G9gPhDZhc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students studying about activism have seen the problem a neighbor school is experiencing and is working to do somet… https://t.co/ihtqn1LCKu]]></document></documents></author>