<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LukeRankinSC please join us for the 6th annual Spring to Life Gala.  Coastline Women’s Center at Hilton Myrtle Bea… https://t.co/4JhPrqN4M0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historiteacher Not sure this will hlp but over time I have come 2 realize there R mean spirited ppl who live here,… https://t.co/ao0o6NWldx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessings come in all shapes &amp; forms... @ North Bergen, New Jersey https://t.co/FcVTUQM1zi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Medical Data:  Don't Leave Home Without It | Psychology Today https://t.co/42nxVSTyfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyVanBramer Obstructionist. You and @AOC just wrote your epitaphs “Dumb &amp; Dumber”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Mariah Carey this past Saturday!  What a show! Listening to her new album #caution right now! Love me some Mari… https://t.co/tC0tAF3ttL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Issues right now: -Too early  -need coffee -need food -still raining  -needing to sneeze but can’t because I don’t… https://t.co/yZEriZEeq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scheer demande la démission de Trudeau. Je seconde cette demande. Justin Trudeau tel son père, se pense au dessus d… https://t.co/oVnOLPkChC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matside seats for the finals! #pac12wrestlingchampionships @ Wells Fargo Arena https://t.co/RITOMZmrIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe all Black people should work together.  As a Haitian.  I stand with ADOS. First of all, it should not be… https://t.co/0lRLnDEHZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katienotopoulos Let's take this opportunity to nag @robleathern to make good on their intentions and ship an ads a… https://t.co/dteXk5xZTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 42 year old coworker hasn’t had sex with her husband in 3 years. Why even be married?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's become a numbers game @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/EUIvRg75Jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me parece LAMENTABLE lo de Álvaro Benito. El Madrid se ha convertido en el Barça 2.0. El Barça echaba gente que hab… https://t.co/e9kX6vDvm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @Google can activate secret microphones in @nest products I think they can integrate into #HomeKit. Stop being petty 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY FREAKING 21st BOMAR🎉🎉 I hope you partying it up in heaven and living life in Paradise bud 💙 love and miss you… https://t.co/1CkndYBZ5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress Everything about republicans has become sheep. What spineless, immoral, creepy enablers they’ve become.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can drink for 20 hours straight but the moment I sit down and relax I feel like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodenough_fu @mez_merrill @CAT1PRO @ViktorMochalin @BobKillman1 @johnnyrockhill @frances_van @a_nowtime… https://t.co/ZVZjRks93u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaradoSheny Muchas gracias e igualmente para ti Sheny abrazos de regreso ,!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Journeys_Film @SassyMamainLA @Carlos_Film @TheCurvyCritic @claudiapuig @jozjozjoz @gilrobertson fair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Turgeon Just a few years ago the 6th seed made it to the championship.  Make that happen ... or better👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2014FloridaTOY We say that, but teachers’ expectations are almost always aligned with a test score because let’s b… https://t.co/Gl6QfMahBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prosperbwealth @babanihitesh Honestly, if you ask employees how well this feedback sandwich works they’ll tell you… https://t.co/6VL5y2txBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took Snoop to the vet for a regular exam and she said like 4x "wow he's so muscular and athletic" so now I'm basi… https://t.co/9f7IQt37cK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, so lets put this deranged guys exact plan out there 4 all to 📖. That's real 🔆.  Who said TNYT is stupid, they k… https://t.co/9qKuYh11BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmluciani @tacobell Will you be trying the @CheetosCanada &amp; @tacobell partnership? https://t.co/ch41FuZw10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lauren_Daigle makes me love people from Louisiana so much!! She’s just a bundle of joy! She made me realize, we ha… https://t.co/WD0upsq1IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren got so much publicity from that Facebook decision to delete her ads that it was almost counterintu… https://t.co/BNC78ivJu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraFARC @AlbanFarc @MujerFariana @PartidoFARC @Carlozada_FARC @PCatatumbo_FARC @IvanCepedaCast @AlirioUribeMuoz Mamerta.!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anyone in the Clearwater area that wants to do raids for Pokemon go https://t.co/pGvgz5seTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajoneswilkins @lord_balls @wser I think 2010 and 2011, given the course was adjusted both times (I think). But the… https://t.co/dCHfGe5DFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our country’s next great hiking trail gets a welcome boost from Congress and advocacy by @amyklobuchar #getoutside… https://t.co/BL8nPwm2qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSosnaNBC 5 Pm. The snow is starting to stick to the hard surfaces. I’ll keep u posted throughout the evening✌🏻 https://t.co/GA3Xl2tZmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on @arlowhite “plus change” I know your audience is based over here but jeez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I have to Adult today? 😴  I do have a to do list of 2 pages.... Oh yeah! It’s also National Dentist Day 🦷 @ Brow… https://t.co/Dp1bmqcQnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 9... Me Still... #EmbracingBeauty ...2 Things @ Fair Heights, Tulsa, Oklahoma https://t.co/cBVMhKBBd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyvaily @samisadancer @CBoom909 @dutchgymnerd Yes - join us! https://t.co/QS6DC4UKkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Temptations- Ain't to Proud to Beg lyrics https://t.co/EWyFPDLlMK via @YouTube a little Motown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 Either sign with the Phillies or tell us otherwise. We are tired of all the reports telling us 20 diff… https://t.co/aqhtiQ71mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to Spend An Evening With @sfosternyc on my 20th birthday tomorrow!!😍 This is a dream come true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of blind anti-corporate attitude is not only stupid, it’s hurting our economy. While I feel bad for the r… https://t.co/y2Yq2w4YWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because you guys only like east coast shit. I love all hip hop. Fat boys , run Dmc. Fat boys. My first time epmd. Y… https://t.co/AaQmg8szja]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥2-14-19  Car Meet//: 124streets  Owner(s)//: N/A (tag) Tags//: #dmvmeets #nissan nissangtr #nissanskyline… https://t.co/lObSky992A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWAthletics @UW_WBB do you guys have team store that can do phone orders on jerseys??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bansky I used to ball with smooth veterans Denver Andre Miller and LAC Caron Butler in the early 2010’s and it use… https://t.co/FBlchvjrzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who have kids that want to improve their hitting with @ReggieSmithAth and @thepureswingsd this coming wee… https://t.co/6X53uc5mpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody cared about the overtime rules until the AFC Championship ended...nobody. Maybe dont blow 4th quarter leads… https://t.co/f6yRWPLhI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great day on the water! A bit slower than usual, but still a great day! Slammed by 8:30, but slowed down ar… https://t.co/cLtSkxV5Nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think I tweet too much, sorry. I’ve tweeted about 500 times today lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here Are 72 Reported Hate Crimes We’ve Documented During The Trump Era That Turned Out To Be Fake https://t.co/DhZYpvt67I via @TurtleboyNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very popular piece.  #Lions top 5 free agent targets (via @BaxFootballGuru) https://t.co/OsXpwvudDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carecanada great turn out for Walk in her shose! #carecanada #walkinhershose #ottawawalks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choreographing a fight scene.... I don’t usually get this detailed at the thumbnail stage but I was in the zone...… https://t.co/Lfjwqn4ufK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawsonlawgroup #survivor #love #warrior #mentalhealth #life #cancer #recovery #instagood #health #abuse #fighter… https://t.co/jK9IcrMR21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmrivera02 just wondering when you were going to issue an apology for what you said during this Jussie Smollett th… https://t.co/icV68ZUFn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Noah_Guy30 @staash13 Really :/ I saw blue in state basketball and assumed CP... I’m outta the loop now. Disregard me being dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickKayal Receiver talent matters precious little to me. If he’s smart and he can help the young ones learn how to… https://t.co/bGFGwWAjjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Hey Matt does your constituents know about all your arrests?? DUI?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The three stages of realizing you should have told Spencer to listen to your podcast last week. Cc: @jonlovett and… https://t.co/FnlCCMoEaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this flat Earth thing really a thing?  I kinda thought it was just a joke but I've seen things lately that make… https://t.co/rYxlPry1pF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonInga @AmerMedicalAssn @CDCDirector @HHS_ASH @NIHDirector @TheJusticeDept @RobertDRoseJr1 have you seen this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Camila Morrone wearing Martin Katz Jewels at the Vanity Fair Oscar Party. #camilamorrone #martinkatzjewels https://t.co/JZS331VHeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been tempted to get another tattoo the only thing holding me back is that I don’t wanna message my artist lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma stop tellin ppl imma pull up early in the day cuz then I’ll feel obligated to do it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Prophetspeaks_ @emilysears @SincereFire Sorry is this in reference to the 18th century?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @PhiladelphiaGov's phone systems are experiencing difficulties. If you need immediate assistance, please call o… https://t.co/HhcCcZFqL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneSweeney4 she's young. the lib examples are them doing exactly the same thing. it's arrogance. debbie hanlon d… https://t.co/VDpL7S9l9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know what RHA is asserting about a Brown Act violation other than being scared about an emergency just caus… https://t.co/xRWgnyl0ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gus Kenworthy is here with about 50 muscle gays so yeah I’m at #OlympicDreams #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trick will be putting a the eight pieces together for Rob's junior and senior years. Those are the years that c… https://t.co/ULmGx2xsNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh the irony of accusing people of #McCarthyism while simultaneously stoking fears of socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First order of business to be conducted at nascar is getting a corn dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever since i drove all the way to new york and back two years ago 30 minutes feels like 5 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump will never measure up to these presidents or any president for that matter. https://t.co/7nHCsJ3hT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of Ah-Ha moments Thursday and Friday. Strangulation and Trauma training. Baton Rouge, LA #TIVI #Trauma… https://t.co/XLja2FTzxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“High Achievement always takes place within the framework of high expectation."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on the doctor. These high table/beds make me feel like a kid. 🤒 @ M.D. Express Urgent Care https://t.co/wms9y0CCbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m case you missed this in my stories.... here’s some shots of the finished up Dream Cubby....  next up... little… https://t.co/Fsy0OdcpyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump That's buIl! You  need check your facts! Under Obama all unemployment went up, as the e… https://t.co/waeGD8uyW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea, the same Military men and women that your party sticks it too if they're fortunate enough to make it home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #BYU basketball game must have fans hoping more than ever those WOW rumors floating around are true. https://t.co/iJhXY9PyHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knew it was coming but the cancellation of #ThePunisher and #JessicaJones still stings. Here's hoping some of the N… https://t.co/lRG08n955i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fgcottam Values have improved? In some areas, like racial and sexual equality, surely they have. But watching They… https://t.co/eaQ3qxq9md]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never woulda ever coulda thought i could come off the baseline and jump over 7 footers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SXMTheHighway @stormewarren @MCSiriusXM @TommySiriusXM @Jason_Aldean As I hail from the Rushmore State, these are… https://t.co/vBd7bD4Jyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz The @POTUS you so ardently defend is a known serial liar. You condemn one man who has confessed to his p… https://t.co/S7tJZg4Wvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusRequenes ¡Vengan a ver!  El poder de la unidad, mientras otros quieren ridiculizar desde su sofá. https://t.co/IouuaEyJkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people in my social media feeds losing it over a freshman congresswoman is hilarious... and revealing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @FarmingtonWres alumni Victor Gliva on his All-American 5th Place Finish at the D3 National Tournament!… https://t.co/bGDIjd2v7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majogm @NicolasLucca Un artículo ejemplar, para ponerle un marco. Todo mi respeto para Trejo, un trabajador honest… https://t.co/tu0qEjoF8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both seniors go back to back for 3s. I love Grady, I love Cline, I love Mackey, and I love Purdue #BoilerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been eating stroopwaffels for 2 days.  Subconsciously, I think it’s because I’m meeting up with a friend from… https://t.co/15I4dE1HNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's great knowing that when I go to bed tonight, I won't be losing an hour of sleep. Good luck, everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dru Hill heavy these past two days. The original 4 are one of the best R&amp;B groups to ever do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting it in FIRST, when you get back home for biz... stops the craving!  🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥 @ Gates Bar-B-Q https://t.co/odBIFOmwWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slightlycrunchy @he_islove @Fitzee67 @HuffPostEnt @benshapiro No doubt lies are told but anytime lately a victim c… https://t.co/cRXa3XwBiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post-storm sun and temps near 40 will lead to some decent melting Monday. After that we deep freeze Tue-Thur. Not b… https://t.co/alRY4YlbFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dumbass got what he wanted. Now they need to throw billions at a wall #BuzzVideo https://t.co/532e4xWdm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerksOfTheHub @HIGHMOONMovie 🤗🤠🤗 thx so much! https://t.co/qAQCL7wqqz for more info!]]></document></documents></author>