<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The next Ninja Warrior Jr!!!!! ... This little girl right here is a little beast... She wont give up until she acco… https://t.co/ur1LMY8f9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[👧🏾 me when I got my period for the first time at age 13:  “YES! FINALLY! I AM A WOMAN!”  👩🏾‍🦱 me at age 25 getting… https://t.co/ABl2SHxDul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redshadowpr te pregunto,si eso hubiese pasado en PR con un artista extranjero,estuviésemos defendiendole como lo h… https://t.co/iIJJWojhXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The pain of getting an IUD inserted into your uterus is extremely painful and I am not looking forward to going bac… https://t.co/Ue5v8ScvEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul I’m not numb. I feel embattled and war-weary. But numb...never.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You democratic hypocrites! You will murder newborn babies, so stop talking children at the border!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bf knew i was sad &amp; made me a playlist with all our favorite songs to sing and dance to 😭💕 i’m SO loved https://t.co/34fv4Eku4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is so full of shit! And so are all those Republicans standing by his side! What a bunch of shitholes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spreading love from City to City❤💯 My skills are 🍌's No one can take that away by God God gives you skills please u… https://t.co/0RefcJWRnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aubernutter @ElizaLucinda That sums up your tongue beans ❤️❤️@ElizaLucinda]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost paws_give_me_purpose with get_repost ・・・ Today’s Featured Dog Friday paws_give_me_purpose is beautiful Sall… https://t.co/6FDlpDhzKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night #wine #wines #winesofinstagram #wineoclock🍷 #wineoclock #wineonwineonwine #wineoftheday #instawine… https://t.co/HFr5CwHdi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The word is former she should take a seat she has no right to say anything she's no longer in that job]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catz are taking over… or at least their fur is. #snuggler (@ The Catz Den in Deerfield, NY) https://t.co/PWRKxTURcL https://t.co/O3FdvmiAeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Trump either has no idea what is in the Emoluments Clause or is purposely ignoring i… https://t.co/TwFErcvKJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy if my man ever acts like this I’m taking applications for a new baby daddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Iwanker got her security clearance the same way she has always gotten everything else in… https://t.co/i6VNbBBK9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[NUMTOT is having a hell of a time deciding which side of this story is the Obviously Ideologically Correct one to b… https://t.co/fJCvueDsSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I try a new pre workout, I always do a half scoop just to test it... people say “oh this one is strong!” A… https://t.co/oYpUHdLy5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukecombs Will there be any more tickets added to the Evansville show?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Terrence, thank you for giving us an up date in person, I am from PUERTO Rico, I come from a family ful… https://t.co/z0CuCV7KyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Continuous Improvement Specialist (Lean)" at Thermo Fisher Scientific? Apply even… https://t.co/oJsrrLe8mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget Daylight Savings Time change tomorrow morning! ~ Pastor Smith https://t.co/rq16DAHdcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelm1976 @CmjBrittney Hahaha I plan too! I’m quite excited. GET YOUR RAIN COATS EVERYONE! ☔️ https://t.co/VJAE9EaFeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frecklesnlove @J0Y2theworld Absolutely! Jumped in way after poont got made. Clearly people who are not parents sho… https://t.co/aEvCTL4QYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥🔥🔥 NEW MUSIC AERT!! Dropping 2/22 @ 10pm Shan Donn - Go Get It. Don’t miss it🔥🔥🔥 @ Cheverly, Maryland https://t.co/viToxiuLWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrimsonKristy Yep — It’s sad — and what’s even more frustrating is that they continue on like they’ve done nothing wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrived safe and sound in Charlotte thanks to @jakegmclean1 and @SouthwestAir! https://t.co/BGmup9Cefm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom said “el ano pasado te compraron flores y mañana no te compran nada” lmao why she do my feelings like that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9fN0Ji585Y  One of my “go-to” songs by ANY artist.  RIP #MarkHollis #TalkTalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuckNTickles I used to feel guilty but now I feel like as I get older I dont want to waste time finishing a book that sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of one of @jiujitsuluvr massages... any chance you want to fly out here to give me one and visit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGrahamCTV @BellCentre @TheEllenShow @CTVMontreal Go Lori! Go! Your the best!  Show them what you’ve got!👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninavarelas Congrats on the new book! Pls bring tiny adorable dog with you on book tour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What a great childhood I had in CT - blissful, superb public schools, (30 kids in a class no probl… https://t.co/mRB7ohYmGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS IDIOT INCARNATION  LIAR IN CHIEF  YOU TRUMF AND FAMILY COLUDED WITH RUSSIA! IF THERE'S A NA… https://t.co/8TiwJQT64o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends @FoxNews Nothing would surprise me when it comes to Schiff or Cohen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blancaa___ @magioneofkind Aye i want attention from a certain person that’s ALSO different lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaeeebabyyy Bitch pleaseeeeee i give you til Wednesday. https://t.co/2eGv2eToyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Just a blow hard did nothing when republicans had both houses.  Now not supporting the People’s President… https://t.co/PGRA128KLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PublicHealthHaiku Health can thrive in peace - All beings, planet prosper - Imagine a world...… https://t.co/QWb78QaBRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows As someone from NC who is neither Democrat nor Republican found you theater disgusting. You may be… https://t.co/a9V40KiZ4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyFuel @StBaldricks @IndianaFarmers @bobarbers @NAMIC @theTylerTrent @Kat9798]]></document><document><![CDATA[allergies are literally the worst and i’ll i want to do is blow my nose and cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soulja is so damn skinny 😂😂😂 Nia's thickums self should have been left him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaywonk @AOC The new deal means "Do as I say, not as I do". I can fly in planes but I must not! I can travel by ca… https://t.co/1uUPkdHSDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Of course they did, please everyone knew this shortly after it happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimejoshi @MyFavMurder The fact that you’re a #murderino shouldn’t surprise me since the same inappropriate thing… https://t.co/mVOWhqb5Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love pasta. I could eat pounds of it! The moment I discovered shirataki noodles via @miraclenoodle I thought I wa… https://t.co/LN6vurMWzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business 🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄🙄 we always eat mortadella but now that hipster cooks know about oooooh biiig f’in deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSpacepig Now the stigma against gay men is very much less than it was in the 90s. For most of the 90s gay and AID… https://t.co/QSGfeeSjx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finished Suits and y’all I haven’t been this sad since I finished Friends :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 1:30 in the morning and I can’t do my homework because all I can think about is how much I miss Eric😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[You snooze you lose. Sold out! @Watermansdisti1 #ApalachinNY https://t.co/30JWSDZXmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Thank you someone with some common sense.  I say learn from your history DO NOT KEEP LIVING IT.  bett… https://t.co/PJwG3xmm39]]></document><document><![CDATA[WARNING FOR YOU PHONE SAFETY! Place it in a cool place asap. Trump is boarding AF1, he is about to burn Twitter down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kincaid_rabb my composer husband @kurterickson7 suggests using a box above the staff accompanied w/instruction “to… https://t.co/VYGUowkMTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now water. Soothe my vocal chords. Quench my thirst. @ Cornish Pasty Co. https://t.co/4o74TMAcJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@syntaxjunkie It’s certainly the same band but I think this and Marauder are really well done. It’s for sure using that as a foundation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlwaysBCarryin @TheMafiaMachine @sam_vinograd @BradMossEsq @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @UN @VOANews Still doesn’t disc… https://t.co/MbR310Erbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s hard to admit but we as adults can be competitive.  The collection of badges for the sake of collecting is rea… https://t.co/j8MhRSFott]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our student assistants play an important role in identifying, explaining, and resolving technical problems.  Thank… https://t.co/tvmgargR54]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Travel Physical Therapist - Acute and Outpatient" in #KingsMountain, NC. Go on in… https://t.co/F6jCztvHMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with this. @MattFinnFNC is one of my favs @FoxNews . Time for a promotion for this fine young man]]></document><document><![CDATA[These republicans are hard hitting.  “Liar liar pants on fire.” #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Nope nope and nope and your still a traitor #IllegitimatePresident #TrumpResignNow… https://t.co/7oJD1mxF7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS is getting me through this week  #PETRILTOSQUIL #SPIRALSQUAD #BAMBOOZLED #THROWSOMEDSONTHATBITCH… https://t.co/kVwXI52IaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gorgeous (only mildly impressed with my photo op) lunch date! Missed you, friend. Cheers to many more skywalk lu… https://t.co/ufWSNrmce8]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one:   me: i’m graduating in august! did you know i’ll have my bachelor’s degree in august? i’m going to be a college graduate at 19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impactmontreal @GeorgesStPierre @maurobiello Quand GSP est venu donner le Pep Talk. Les souvenirs. Top Gars!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delpotrojuan Espero que el tratamiento sea efectivo! ¡Te extrañamos!   Te vemos pronto❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamblackbear 1 sided love &amp; a 24 bears song. This is everything !!!! #1sidedlove #24bears #beartrapsound ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How often does a 9yo make the @BloodHorse cover?! Very cool! #respectourelders 🐎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t need any introduction... I’m Starr! Annnd I am amazing! #houston #texas #starrempire https://t.co/ZLXKWdhG1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProbsYoongi I'm so sad that I'll never get to see him perform this live! So happy we have these fan cams. 🤗😍💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickmercer kicking off this evening’s @Disrupt_Mining event #DisruptMining #PDAC2019 looking forward to hearing th… https://t.co/mCnJeq5PAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's tee-hee a bit. lol ;) big curvy plus size women are beautiful! Curves quote real women body consciousness acc… https://t.co/ZEqZBSxRQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_MartinezRed @30_britez @SimpleGain @Stallion_Team @lIMGWVIl @tinatwitte482 @Caroola11 @am102358 @Zigiar @MarEthr… https://t.co/tGc9tS2RoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I have a panic attack every time I check out at the grocery store]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @IlhanMN @FoxNews @Ilhan Right! We have to know if you denounce Sharia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to spring forward an hour this Sunday! https://t.co/qc1lPHVn03]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said “yeah but that was 3 weeks ago. I wasn’t going to tell you about the assignment 3 weeks ago. It’s up to you… https://t.co/nRyC4hq39U]]></document><document><![CDATA[But they can't believe that large amounts of drugs are coming through large amounts of unsecure parts of the border]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some bts shots from today's photo shoot with on_point_photos2018. #texas #texasmodel #model #sanantoniomodel… https://t.co/zi45G24jQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙GOOD MORNING💙 . .. . .. . For inquiries please email me at glambyveronica1@gmail.com  #glambyveronica #glambyvero… https://t.co/5d09Kqoyso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEUMBasketball swept it!  Do you need an extra suitcase to get all those awards back to ATX @CoachAndreCook ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pdubsRN Watched @Kestdaddy yesterday, he also, has a BEAUTIFUL swing 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; imma say only good things to my friends when I speak about you Cause I ain't gotta reason not to]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one:  clear polish:                          ✧･ﾟ: *✧･ﾟ:*              .｡*ﾟ+.*.｡(❁´◡`❁)｡.｡:+*… https://t.co/z1UVOEUrWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost beahappyamy with repostsaveapp   · · ·   Days 1 and Day 2 #LetsPlayAYogaGame  . I love working with… https://t.co/WSWmxP8QOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así van mis cejas, ya están casi set, está semana vamos para el retoque y quedamos de show... Gracias a Key de brow… https://t.co/u6AUSMJjwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaclark1313 @law_champagne @am_Dino_rawr My friend from law school fosters catahoula rescues!!!! What great dogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also hungry! We have no idea what some have been thru before coming to school! 😢💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potato_Chip Yay! I just wish it were easier to get Sanrio stickers in North America! I can never find them where I live 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindfulness class?!?!?  Who’s in?  I’d be SO willing to get trained and teach it! @jjmac78 @kelseyemiller… https://t.co/Pebtndjfmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great weekend in #venicebeach 👌🏼☀️✌🏼 So sad to be leaving this sunshine! #Cali #SundayFunday #sunshine… https://t.co/iYK9yeys7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not complaining but I’ve had a Spotify daily mix filled with heavy heavy low low and duck duck goose for months now and I’m not sure why]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that Monday will be my last @TexasTechMBB game. I’m going to cry some ugly tears. I’ve seen this pr… https://t.co/hOm0nnveFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl sat in my unassigned seat in class 😑 doesn’t she know the unwritten rule of college]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuarezViry She’s a young queen laying her edges with that toothbrush tho lol]]></document></documents></author>