<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blind Pig IPA by Russian River Brewing Company @ McMenamin's — https://t.co/tHfCu3koL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lokmow They are free range squirrels and they are drawn to our place because of the peanuts I leave completely unguarded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hale_razor @dcrspn @PepperoniPurist @ralphster_jk @brianstelter They just continue to expose their own hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, you aren’t the “all time favorite President” even among members of your own family.  But you’re right, the W… https://t.co/mkXkTPaMYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine this jail cell at the fed penthouse:  Madoff (you stole money from Cancer non-profits you’re a true piece o… https://t.co/iEGgPdUdjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh from the groomer😎🐶 #spoiledbulldog .... this boy is happy because there’s no more rain☺️ #roccothebulldog… https://t.co/ZXyNzJMvN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black ice.  . . . . #blackice #winter #nightphotography #newburyport #newburyportma #massachusetts #newengland @ Ne… https://t.co/I5uP5AEhkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is one takeaway from #Oscar2019 season it is this- screw what other people, especially critics, have to sa… https://t.co/YLmsmJbFa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @Me_Miss_C update for the ones that love her. https://t.co/P2nBvGr950]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marcus Thornton of the @grdrive got the silent treatment after 11 triples Wed night and he knew something was up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zhaoqili @eclien @mvh_lab Hey I know the guy on the right! He's awesome! (I'm sure the guy on the left too!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, Wesleyan world — who knows where to go to stream #GC2019 natively on an TV (ie, no AirPlay from my phone!)?  D… https://t.co/leyKsqis4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottmgower I think they give out these contracts with the hope that they’ll get 8 good years out of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sulliview @brianstelter Is it sexist to point out that Harris and warren are liars?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catfantastic1 @ByJenSmith You joke, but Joe Lunardi used to teach a non-degree seeking course in bracketology for… https://t.co/YWeV1IZZCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Woods &amp; Waters by @mainebeerco @ Small City Taphouse — https://t.co/l86WJtDfqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Disappointed to see how #DonaldTrump signs an order to begin creating the Space Force. He may have NO… https://t.co/KGzNiZM5ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally i look forward to seeing Skylar everyday after work cause it’s just so relaxing to come home and be with… https://t.co/ucVez6DbqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeyhemLauren Well what did you expect!? My Man to stay creative- sober! Ptsshhht! Ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s going to be a great day when you get cheese grits &amp; Conecuh sausage at #IronMan small group!… https://t.co/kd7XeyprM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deb: defend the ending of kill the moon...EVERY YEAR GUYS LET IT GO #Gally1 @VerityPodcast https://t.co/mA5xhdkqlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ChristianYelich goes 2-for-2 with a run today. He is now batting .450 (9-for-20) with 5 runs, 2 HR and 3 RBI in 8 games this spring. #MVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Slim &amp; Husky's - @slimandhuskys in Antioch, TN https://t.co/b96kSHpsiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp You missed the racist traitor Jeff Sessions. He lied during his hearings but was sworn in anyway because… https://t.co/dfHvJPAqGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop thinking ISH is sweet @ North Philadelphia https://t.co/7J827d7CfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Fury had his left eye scratched out by a cat, I had my left eye scratched out by a cat (true story), so now my… https://t.co/cx2JpmxzMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The night before one of the biggest servants of my pastoral career… I chipped my front bottom tooth. #Great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knielsen18 @tfullervcs Crazy, it really does seem like yesterday. I need to lose some weight. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ogglethorpe @RepPressley You're literally advocating for one path for the wealthy and another for everyone else. N… https://t.co/zgcQ7lAUJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[heads up to my new owl followers that i’m also parttime kpoppie and homestuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarieStLucie1 @capricornmathlv @Newsweek Absolutely blue states create almost 70% of the gdp we pay more to the fe… https://t.co/x7FLcjQWOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodreads Starting with Christine by Stephen King.. After that, who knows!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the reminder, my driver sent this to me, be aware of kids out there they are off.  Be slow, be safe and… https://t.co/ytp1EmBURW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn look at the block. #nitenite @ Gwinnett County, Georgia https://t.co/AOasImg2Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was the fourth story in my submission reel. @FOX46News uncovered @USPS first class mail that was in their own… https://t.co/0CCHxOEdk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zerpin @j0shimitsu I'm sad I didnt get to make it out to this, but just things to add ro the next trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Dershowitz said even suggesting it is criminal in and of itself by those at the top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SQLProApp @squeakytoy @marcoarment Swift became source stable with Swift 4, so no, there won't be Swift 5 and Swif… https://t.co/JYgWxtdCzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venue for today’s interview in Worthington, Minnesota. A bit chilly but a wonderful location https://t.co/tLFSx881XL]]></document><document><![CDATA[While renovating our new house we have made quite a few trips to the dump. It’s amazing how many people have left n… https://t.co/Ox4yxsGfhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austintheory1 You have to be the most looked forward to wrestler coming to @WWE @WWENXT in the country! Hopefully… https://t.co/T12mKNHtvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[the "creativity" and "originality" of some PNW influencers these days....  my photos on the left. https://t.co/3C35YSHEeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything.” George Bernard Shaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be reading new poetry along with new original music at The Argo Bookstore Open Mic on Thursday April 4th, 2019… https://t.co/tuB9Yl1Lnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have things we would do differently... things we wish we hadn’t said/had said. Sometimes you just gotta hope… https://t.co/FtqKdIQGRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will take the passenger seat for the Lord to lead my life. #Jesustakethewheel #faith #blessed https://t.co/Aa66McEUfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[That part!!!🎯💯✊🏿💪🏿 #FoodForThought #OneToGrowOn #Inspirational #Motivational #Positive #Powerful #Affirmations… https://t.co/rWSQUGPcrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you too. In to this mans chest!! What the fuck is wrong with me. I need a dab haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us this Thursday at @austinfilm for Lee Chang-Dong's POETRY, winner of Best Screenplay at the 2010 Cannes Film… https://t.co/AqMRIXBOUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhfrank A common problem I’ve had with these anonymous query sites has always been the startup. But once you get a… https://t.co/5uA3dYnRit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaHuseman I covered a walkout protest at my old high school a few years ago. I was walking down the line of p… https://t.co/MKj8vTbnJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike!  It’s a great Wednesday. https://t.co/bxcL2fJOrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stvzbnk @KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff Not sure felons are eligible to run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Logistics of People – A Mobility Forum for Businesses. Find out what’s available in transit for your employees, whe… https://t.co/f4d2I8RtNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually... this is a repair to existing fence that Obama ordered while in office. #keeplyingDonnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[6% chance for the lakers to make the playoffs? Lol @FirstTake. Not only will they make it. They’ll beat the Nuggets… https://t.co/rRPTOOhe9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2019 Sunday Supper @DanielNY featured a great line up of Chefs for the 22rd Annual City Meal on Wheels. Another… https://t.co/VQOjAB9W1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an American Pale Ale by @pabstblueribbon @ Milladelphia — https://t.co/9KYnI5iYmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Blues up 3-0  on the #Wild (2nd) .. on their way to win #10 in a row .. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews @CarlBanksGIII @crackdown @MSStudiosBlog You are Blending 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL of Twitter. Then the person be layered in makeup when you finally see them in person. 🌚🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World Is a Business, Mr. Beale https://t.co/4ar9ZV6h9Z via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Dems will@stop@at nothing to bring down all the positive that you have down for OUR country .🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday’s South Jersey roundup: Seneca boys’ basketball upsets second-seeded Ocean City in South Group 3 quarterfi… https://t.co/GlDaSWye0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough as nails❗️ Go to war with this kid any day, a pleasure to coach him @KolekTyler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Mulroney Excellent. Thank you for your kind words. Have a nice weekend.😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice beat. #NowPlaying Lovers Again by EXILE. #jpop #dancepop https://t.co/4oDpdEtpiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whereas once the fathoms of my coffee mug seemed endless, this is proven entirely untrue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @NaughtyAllie is still making porn videos for her website, or is still in the swinger lifestyle. She's… https://t.co/zNNA8V74X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the moment of the game tonight.  The big game awaits. Talk to you Thursday. 🎙📻🏀 https://t.co/0RCioJD3hE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlyssesUnion @F1RETHECANNON I totally agree. Torts words were blown out of proportion, too. Then another GM decide… https://t.co/opRk2wwfGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @Mimirocah1 My 215 lb. English Mastiff attacked the TV set with teeth bristling when Jim Jordon at… https://t.co/Q0roWigZ6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a life style... #Seizemeals #Farmerdankziel https://t.co/H5Ka1Rnc5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankfully an uneventful drive to Blacksburg. #UVA #Hokies (@ Cassell Coliseum - @vtnews for Virginia Cavaliers vs… https://t.co/kPCSy40YYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Meanwhile your RACIST buddy Congressman Mark Meadows had is racist balls handed to him on the Hous… https://t.co/VE6n7vE3pN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenCarmichaelWV Go lay down somewhere.  West Virginia has seen enough of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow yesterday morning in Michigan, sunshine and palm trees 🌴 today in Miami. Life is good🙏🏻 https://t.co/QtcjyhiY6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Duh! He wasn’t the great negotiator as he claims to be. Kim has been dealing with other leaders longer than… https://t.co/2K3F4QQvzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pushing my luck! 🏀🏀🏀😏 (@ Saint Ignatius Loyola Academy in Baltimore, MD) https://t.co/Cdr7DAQ64b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else likes watching these guy at this time of morning every Monday at 5am now at 5 am?? https://t.co/XnGEugJeTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Retribution”  “Should he looked into”  The President of the United States, attacking free, political speech.  I’m… https://t.co/rbu4cOAslD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pipeorgan #closeup @ St. John's Episcopal Church (Dubuque, Iowa) https://t.co/MWx60cqmyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @EPiersma Problem is, we don't have capitalism, we have corporatism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @elonmusk when we getting a battery powered pick up truck? We on the South want to jump into the future, but st… https://t.co/ceQcGAcuce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V4Revenga @renepereirajr Porque sera que esta gente habla en el tono de "meter miedo"? Si el capitalismo nos ha ll… https://t.co/qLnL6e0qJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday ❤️ check out the @ShockleyFields song “Diversity” • link in bio @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/LzI05UeDfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elvisduran @TatesBakeShop Elvis I'm also on low carb and sugar. 1 cheat cookie is happening with my martini! https://t.co/0PLLV5yzob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do yourself a favor and catch one of these shows. Take the time. Make the effort. You wont be disappointed.… https://t.co/WLDNnIuXWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethTweets Might have to take a pay cut to be on a good team. Not being on the Phillies has to be worth a few mil a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neontaster Truth. I just good food from a fish and I'm enjoying my buzz and fish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Ramblings – Spiritual Saturday – Living a Life of Victimhood https://t.co/gP06jlTij8 https://t.co/La2hDdEUWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aviatordiamond9 @SycamoreAthlet1 @Baseball_Aves @AvesAthletics @rhcftb @zoso58 I expect to see you two dudes signed up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morgxn2001 Wow! Almost as foul as the movie now circulating by that liberal studio who graced us with, "A Star is Born"!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeliDraws @naturalsciences Baby dinosaurs were basically Mesozoic snack food. Can’t blame ‘em for being a bit tense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the Miami Lakes community Bike 🚲 Ride-February 50 riders today! #iheartmiamilakes #marioesierra… https://t.co/TZS2tCrpdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @joanne48640679 @BertJ4411 @GhostOfTick @Hybrid1979 @jan_hemeoncRN @r0xie_f0x @FREETOMMY8… https://t.co/yn3qISQSDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Hmmmm, how many and how long were those Benghazi investigations??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacred Heart near top of state for childbirth complications, hospital argues high risk patients drive stats https://t.co/DidO9Dxv8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sincerely hoping that Momo comes and gets my ass if I don't pass this Math Class i'm taking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media is in collusion with the Deep state 2 perform a bloodless coup and get rid of trump. That's treason]]></document></documents></author>