<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[i’ve had 24 ounces of cold brew, 24 of drip coffee, and 24 of diet coke is it time for bed yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeesMom It’s an unpopular opinion, but I found the whole thing over the top. Two processions that shut down the hi… https://t.co/Ibfvnnmecv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandersMichi Humble Beginnings! #PreemieStrong https://t.co/34xWGjS46Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendar: This is a Missy Elliott one-time exclusive! Playhouse Party returns March 14th celebrating the… https://t.co/sZauk06KZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else got their #NiallHoran #RteOrchestra #Flickeralbum ?!? Yaaaaa me!!!! And I also got my #Travelbottle… https://t.co/5J2I0HUEe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@INDIVIDUALONE19 @CarlosM61269234 And how those around him accommodate his ignorance is also astounding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romancane 🤔Gimmie the Greatest return man EVER and one of the most dominant offensive lineman in NCAA history! #4… https://t.co/b5kbxgoebS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elle elephant can't wait for spring.  . . #illustrator #cartoon #cute #photo #photooftheday #photoshop… https://t.co/6QdnbqD3cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DjokerNole wonderful to see you both "on the court"! Congrats on your win tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneCu58149333 @thehill Art of the deal  😂😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/sfVWD50MPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltitudeTV @LGRed See you on National TV somewhere I'm sure. Smart, Beautiful Woman who knows sports. Remember Colorado as you move on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Infusing #Indigenous content in math through games; resources abound; check out https://t.co/Cufp2EoFV0 for math/ph… https://t.co/gM51DLYFJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesssAlexisss a lotion that literally doesn’t smell like anything but yea go off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being successful isn’t always what makes you a success. #perspective 🏠 💰 ❤️ #selflove  #Financial… https://t.co/LxViyL5PoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lock screen makes me smile whenever I look at it...... https://t.co/oMVZXbscbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #gsuite #oetc19 folks, be aware that AIR testing sites are not working with chrome v72. Make sure to pin your v… https://t.co/1DEtHfODYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealdakkery I'm just doing the TESOL doctoral forum and then heading home!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambientabbot Yesterday we had a rare warm up in temps and the birds were loving it.  So wonderful to listen to them sing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you truly want someone you should take them for their good and bad. If you’re not willing to see past or work th… https://t.co/8rhLcFRoTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuminousLIGHT1 @MarlaMondora @littlebluespal You are on🔥these recommended book titles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMichaelGibson @PartsUnknownCNN Understood. It’s really well done. Bourdain is my favorite. Keep me in mind if dec… https://t.co/3NUIhvdgAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man really out here smoking an entire blunt with his baby with BREATHING TUBES]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MotivationMonday : Work for it more than you talk about it and have GOALS so BIG even you get scared ...… https://t.co/xEAaaxK2th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya know, it always hurts more when the trades players started down here. Gunna miss Monty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank god I have a notebook to write all my thoughts in because no telling what would’ve came out of my mouth by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[love this pic of me from when i saw one direction https://t.co/NBNt4aEt9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a blast today with @chooseATL and the #ChooseATLRetreat!! Made a stop by Google’s #Atlanta office and had a… https://t.co/cFQg7gYQEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVER AND I MEAN NEVER DISCOURAGE ANYONE FOR THERE EFFORTS TIOADVOCATE  EVEN IF YOU DISAGREE WITH THE WAY THEY DO I… https://t.co/p4Xxaw74WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics Michael Cohen could not have a better attorney. Laney Davis is a good man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[after a night of going out do you ever wake up with your significant other and don’t speak but just “hmmm” ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fltweet11 Be careful. They might start using standardized testing in lower grades just so your point is obsolete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoniqueCoyle @JKingsbury201 @JHerrod15 Oooh. One of my favorites too. And I was just about to post for my book of the day! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dumbass had to do a double take bc it looked like she chained herself up lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamarSoftball @PurdueSoftball @SAUSoftball @TNUsoftball @BelmontSoftball @KUSoftball @coachstacpickme @CycloneSB… https://t.co/NKZRDNRvHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darn proud to serve at #NASA under @BarackObama to help shape the space policy of today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We https://t.co/qTlMwrfsRL Arizona4BeingInfested WithCaliforniaPpl .TheyRHere2 Escape InnumerableCompounded Taxes,U… https://t.co/e2gVchSvRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘ZOMBIE DEER DISEASE' starts by infecting the brain and is passed through contact with contaminated body fluids and… https://t.co/T68joObSEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[President trump bring back MC CARRAN act 1952 forbidding muslims from holding office!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newtgingrich didn't get enough @seanhannity air time, had to sell his soul to highest bidder, #INDIA cartel. Old N… https://t.co/MjzZxDsyaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is always one morning radio host that sounds like he’s stuck in a well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barndinner May 11-25. Call today. 336-292-2211 #patsycline #countrymusic #Opry #livemusic #buckowens #music #genre… https://t.co/6LBK3VnwVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hale_razor @whpresscorps Why TF is conservative media losing their collective minds over this?? Media outlets repo… https://t.co/pezyzZNwl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry this happened to you. It breaks my heart to know that what my mother (white) and my father (biracial) mig… https://t.co/9DCXQ3dbBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 20TH BIRTHDAY SYDNEY!!!!! Eat lots of cake🍰 and cupcakes🧁! 🎂🎂🎂🎂🎂🎈🎈🎈🎈🎈 https://t.co/YS5ENNXyzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IdGeek confession- I’m so excited about this and I like the flipping noise it makes as you turn the pages. #HIV… https://t.co/6ZyJg1FKXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Niffmar @hoover_melissa @brithume Vote Not for any DEMOCRATS AND NO TO AOC she is  ignorant !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all.   @GayleKing interviewed #RKelly for his first TV interview since last charges against him.   Airs tomorrow… https://t.co/gJIGK7jSps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoNoNotNormal #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass #MarALardass  #MarALardass #MarALardass… https://t.co/x7Vo94i4jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet @2Much2TakeDaily @BarackObama Oh I miss him so much. 😢 https://t.co/wByAmGqpMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all...I was showering and the neighbors next door started blaring Choppa Style...I’m never leaving NOLA #WhoDat @Saints]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I take it this means you’re canceling your next video of going to get your ears re pierced there, huh?… https://t.co/otwo7ELTKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoczijTDSB @CityNatasha @MicrobioGen @NehaKapi @googlecanada @westhumberci @Perimeter Thanks so much for having us!  It was so much fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student: Ms. Loman, if you were a Greek goddess, which one would you be? Me: I don't know. Maybe Athena? Student: I… https://t.co/V6U3gTEyp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God, you were hot” -@IAmPatrickB #HappyInternationalWomansDay #me #were]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is a BEAST! note that this gator barely has his eyes open #russojourneys #onmywalk #inthewild #hugegator… https://t.co/B2ZcAqdgdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly surprised to hear abba's "take a chance on me" NOT followed by @MBMBaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would I do without my best friends and my amazing co-workers??!! How can I be blessed anymore??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Specneedsmom4 @veterans_i @OleVetUSAF @brinstar9 @TerriPlaysHere @Hell_HasCome @anti_Chump @ZombieAlertZulu… https://t.co/12Wbx842bP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Wilson is talking about “2+1 road” pilot project in Northern Ontario on Highway 11. 2+1 roads are not only bui… https://t.co/sQ4LufSeyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande You’re a dream to me!! Can’t wait to see you in St Louis this summer! Just bought my tickets. 💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Collab and tell what #leavinghome is like. Thank  #YourQuoteAndMine Collaborating with YourQuote Baba #yqspecial… https://t.co/SJBMo6VmD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill And why do her insults toward anyone matter? Guess she forgot, if you have nothing nice to say, then don’t speak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want clear skin, get in shape, healthy living and my hair to flourish some more. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can give young people the gift of a peaceful and healthy planet by putting your voice on the Marine Arctic Peac… https://t.co/sQwXJCOiq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s able to do exceedingly and abundantly above ALL we could ask or think!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic bucket list moment for me yesterday when I approached the stage and Sting @OfficialSting during the final… https://t.co/hrQnz4odlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met the most amazing lady that recently moved to Glendora and she said that she’d come back Wendys everyday just… https://t.co/hIIcjEMmZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[All she wants to do is trash talk Hillary. So obvious and mean. #meghan the view]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than 10 dead, many injured, in apparent large tornado in Alabama, officials say; fatalities could rise  https://t.co/8ZjYOqLo5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaning toward Grookey but I gotta see the evolutions before my final choice because they can be a game changer 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gary56907481 @WhiteHouse let’s build the wall, the people will get it back and it will save a lot of lives]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a loss and such a legacy. Visionaries are hard to come by. @lilsingher @HealthPolicyHub Godspeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to say this @MarcAnthonyHC ultra-hydrating conditioning treatment is DA BOMB! Saved me from having to t… https://t.co/ssyAM1Cvbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDavePeters @wino911 @RealCandaceO Did you get to the part where the servant and serf women and children weren’t included?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs of spring.  💞 @ Biltmore Gardens &amp; Conservatory https://t.co/KhhqjPim62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing Thanks for providing me with an awesome new profile pic! ✊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrift shop treasure.. you never know what you gonna find!@ymblueoriginals @ Bedford–Stuyvesant, Brooklyn https://t.co/88PL4KnIla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLeonardKim Wow. Twitter was more supportive. 🤷🏽‍♀️ But truly you will get through this just fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat 2 faced, crooks are robbing the taxpayers https://t.co/nWHVH55WOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JKeithnosweat Thank you so much. Man. If you haven’t been along all my shenanigans. 🤣🤣 idk how I would’ve made it 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little unbalanced in the analysis IMHO, but still a really interesting read - especially for folks who study/prac… https://t.co/2xMpdE8tix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaEarlene1 @veganempanada @SRWells3 @imjustasteph @WolfeLing @IlhanMN Yes, it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like late night packing to get you amped for the next journey!  #Atlanta #Here #I #Come]]></document><document><![CDATA[America is equipped with The World’s finest Plumbers! Who’da thunk “Plumber’s Crack” could be so dern sexy🤷🏻‍♀️😉💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normally I’m all over social media gathering info on SXSW events and what I can get into. This year, I just don’t c… https://t.co/tS8cCqTkvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING We have a crew on scene this morning. Updates right here on #CBS5 @CNYcentral]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many things unsettled in life but now is NOT the time to cave!  #TrustGod #TrustTheProcess #YourTimeIsComing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen57036680 @T_FLgal @BellaInxs2 @my3monkees @karmasenz @RodHillis1 @misspunk63 @GinnyGinny_1 @KamyMAGA… https://t.co/QB35CZOLux]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a video that exists of me scream singing Shallow with wine stained lips and tears running down my face. Yo… https://t.co/FzIoKbZrwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Didja see that?  That's exactly what Letterman said was gonna happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine #SheSmokesCrack  no matter how many times they play the race card there is -0- evidence.  #NeverAHarris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aprildouglass_ I get what y’all saying about the females part. I was just explaining what she said 🤷🏾‍♀️ never said i agreed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Outpatien… https://t.co/Qa7cMGjhaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LimJo last time I ate fufu was in Ghana and it’s been three years 😭.. just not a fav of mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissLizz “I think my punishment for bailing was waking up with KT Tunstall stuck in my head so know that I’m suffering”]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you’re editing, and create a cursed image... https://t.co/Y7zXp4Zfko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night @ColinKane we couldn't stop laughing all night! Thank you! Hit me up sometime! Xoxo #comedians… https://t.co/fi21uh5jlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephForrer Try to carve out  time to make it to the restaurant at Hotel Cap Estel if you can.The grounds alone ar… https://t.co/dHtvpFFxaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman You know cheating on your wife and being honest with the American people when they're supposed to be… https://t.co/hsScR5oVHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got over a fear and climbed the rock wall for the first time today and didn’t do too bad 💪🏼🧗🏻‍♀️]]></document></documents></author>