<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I love to ghost hunt. Or, ghost converse. Mostly because I love to have conversations with the disembodied humans,… https://t.co/dtYluybbie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got exposed by the birthday boy yesterday, wish I could show the video 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtsolomonwriter That sounds an awful lot like “mud season” here. That’s our equivalent of spring where we trade ou… https://t.co/Yy1CXLQIfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FNMExposure @voxdotcom The tl;dr of your tweet: A “news site” with 14 followers leaves a hot take in a thread abou… https://t.co/VynFQ4Kr0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benensonj @jashsf Yeah, who's Schultz's greedy-I-don't-wanna pay-taxes friend at @CNN ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing about being in restaurants 14 times a week is that when you show up to the party, you always end up smell… https://t.co/iYzKeQMR5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahkedra @AndrewScheer @fordnation Yep, thanks for pointing it out - honestly :)   https://t.co/lYbiiBUz57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_lossfor I like books best. I am on my devices too much already to actually read there too. BTW: I just followed… https://t.co/IDRSKFnxJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now that I’ve tweeted my opinions on Israel and bisexuality, I shall sign off for the evening and expect no one… https://t.co/bmVvnw2EU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeknoGeisha nothingness but also if you don’t put anything in them they kinda taste like dirt? or like. corn?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halle_shea @martinn_matthew The daycare episode turned me off from the whole series for FIVE YEARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lookin up from a pisser in Portland.. Ok ok.. Slow down get to know me than spit that.. Geez https://t.co/aMAAJJH2ss]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman and her Father live on a different mental planet. @PressSec @GovMikeHuckabee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechelleshock @theresakhuu @vaishnavi @bonappetweet Btw let us add a snack component - samosa, vada and pav bhaji for 3pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it once and I’ll say it one million more times. ALL 👏🏼 TOO 👏🏼 WELL 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic &amp; informative  interview with @AliciaMenendez for #AmanpourAndCo    You can watch it here:… https://t.co/rsKDN357Jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr  over 65M voters support nuclear option for @realDonaldTrump ‘s NED to secure our borders.  Obama dec… https://t.co/WJN5Ne6bUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AzharUom @ZEYNAZERDA @heroldbarton @Cathhewat123 @Alexa17101614 @dahut07 @maype7 @LOYALFAN1 @ollivier_yves… https://t.co/zQZaPjFMJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jiminquas_ @markbear_08 why is it you feel the need to shame someone? if they allow you or not. that’s not cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 46: Yikes, busy day! Yesterday I was grateful for a long drive where I could belt out my driving playlist. On m… https://t.co/ddTwRQhNtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[One guy in front of me is listening to Christmas music.  A lady behind me is listening to what I think is a form of… https://t.co/SJd3XtuN7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I never catch episodes of @truTVjokers I haven’t seen before but right now there’s an episode on I have… https://t.co/cIyvwr4MN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRichardBlack @SenWarren @SenSanders @SpeakerPelosi @Consortiumnews @joekennedy @johnpilger @cynthiamckinney  Sa… https://t.co/35SsF17STc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets show @SenatorCollins that we want her to vote NO on Kavanaugh. Pledge to this campaign. If she votes for… https://t.co/hRh3Z8Glw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world is full of monsters with friendly faces and angels full of scars.🔮🖤 @ Cleveland, Ohio https://t.co/SXvvmNaUzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NO1GifQueen @SdOceanSea @dchinn2005 I mean if she had some sort of issue, it should of come to me. But FYI I’m not as nice as Nikki.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who think that being light skinned is a personality trait are stuck in the year 1893. Give it a rest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The shame of having your name on this list will forever be with every death of every baby !  Shameful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knows a pre-teen/teen/young adult who is trying to get their skin in under control? Acne, oil, confidence? Who… https://t.co/xRdIZSoizL]]></document><document><![CDATA[An evening of opera at Bartschland Follies with the incomparable @operagaga &amp; @shiqueeta @Amanda_Lepore… https://t.co/NVpHB2exUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that 🚶 is starting to pay off I'll have the perfect body b4 I go to the next chapter!!! https://t.co/sTs4z48zLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWolking I never say this but in this instance I'll make an exception: WTH?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland It wasn't Russians Purging me in Texas.  It was Republicans Purging me in Texas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it now! Sometimes “later” becomes “never” #🤙🏻 #soccer⚽️ @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/ja7CM8I5kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[what an amazing year! I'm so proud of all of you!! Play hard/work hard and 2020 will be the year! 🏀❤️💙 @lildelberta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Girl0nFire84 Oh I know!! I finally JUST NOW, got a response that I will be starting back for sure on Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smart of Tennis Canada to have Felix do the bulk of his training on clay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usminority @CarpeDonktum And @TheDemocrats he rode in on #MichaelCohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[A whole damn PROM TRAIN 🕺🏻 @ LYTE Nutrition &amp; Fitness https://t.co/hnu1AYxANp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m working for half the pay I was offered by a marketing company. I love what I do but sometimes it’s discouraging… https://t.co/rTwPobcZc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if it's possible to have a love affair that lasts forever" -Andy Warhol #artfullymine #art #artist… https://t.co/3w3HJA0ETY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow...it hasn’t even been a weeks once Peyton left and idk what life is without @_notpey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kerryowen1 @freedom2marry @cmclymer @AOC @CraigSBPA I am sorry for your loss. 😞♥️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be nice if the celebrities attending the Oscars gave their swag bags to @LittleMissFlint so she could do a… https://t.co/zYjFUXw64p]]></document><document><![CDATA[My crush intimidates the shit outta me so I go with the “avoid &amp; ignore at all costs” flirting strategy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guard your time fiercely. Be generous with it but be intentional about it! ❤️ . . This beautiful and light weight w… https://t.co/9tpNQAyBnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aquí donde me ven pondré @netflix , porque lluvia + domingo = maratón de #PabloEscobarElPatrónDelMal 🍿Todo esto es… https://t.co/0mdiheaOtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Well, Donnie ... you just admittedly watched it. Fake President railing against the “Fake News” is… https://t.co/YQmt1o1byS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe Raji’s about to start training for a 5K 😳🏃🏾‍♀️ #GOTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnesotaDFL @mnhouseDFL @ERAMinnesota FYI, Americans: We need just one more state to reach 3/4 of 50 required (a… https://t.co/dFylDI2D6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsDickinson @BeulahMiners The fact that I said ‘here’s’ is killing me, but I also don’t want to go through the… https://t.co/Km8Z1kZAz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin @DonaldJTrumpJr @TuckerCarlson We don’t have sharia in America !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carlos_Film Pooh SMAP!!!.I agreed that was not the film but MA and VM are very good actors it was too forced and c… https://t.co/tBjnW6fX9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotANoctor I have seen “life and limb” lost in patients being cared for by.... gasp.... doctors, nurse and teams o… https://t.co/XSYCZuUw44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brownsfan0328 I’ve had too much shit happen to even remember where it all began.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AJs #day1 #mcfrs building his future. Time to think about tomorrow. 2 more years to go. @ Montgomery County Public… https://t.co/Ta4vrxr69F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sanaya23 @GoogleForEdu @DCIU @delcoSTEM @zimmermath383 @somegoodideas Does this mean some IU training offerings to… https://t.co/jrLzwCMIQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@it_meirl_bot @WadeWilsonXD I just had to giggle on the area 51.. thankyou..]]></document><document><![CDATA[B7 | Holden Bernhardt in to pitch the 7th for the Broncos.  McCarville goes 6 IP, 4 H, 1BB, 5 K and most importantl… https://t.co/c3TiQGIwZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaPoStormborn Yeah, the trouble is that we just moved and have lots of little projects, so there really are a lot… https://t.co/2cwJrnWYZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Midgespeaks Because God directed me to. Then I learned of the prophecy rec'd by @lancewallnau that same day that T… https://t.co/CxpjCmYL86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@survivorcbs Yes except no bc it feels like Lauren will give her her idol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the minute everything is going great is the minute it all falls apart again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily fluff. Every morning mom makes me food. She "drops" some on the floor for me to find. I like this game. My ot… https://t.co/nrvkI8j4Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve gladly accepted a challenge from @jcoreyatzeck to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no reviews—j… https://t.co/OQME5VRM0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heysally Back to spread the good word of Tsurumaru https://t.co/K9VUjOxyzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr So why did she rush to judgement before she knew all the facts in the beginning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting your head scratched by your girl gotta be one of the BEST things u don’t understand]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLRo777 @DearAuntCrabby @realDonaldTrump He’s trying. Anything to deflect from Cohen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoomerFanClub Thanks for following me. I pray that everyone will follow you too.  We are grateful for your strengt… https://t.co/NBsYjmbZ5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logannm_ Well this is awkward because I was just about to tell you the same thing....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to start blocking ppl why are you calling me at 530 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen showed what it was to be a man today. For all his wrongs he withstood the wrath of the Rep. that don’… https://t.co/ebB19zCz3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los Parras are 20 minutes away from me 😭 when will I see them?!?!? I really need to go get my license man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes he is. He was also a leader with Honor Society while at Gadsden. Continuing to do great things! Love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion NOTHING more boring than monochromatic cultural cohesion...it's like having nothing but doughy white bread, yuck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women comprise almost half of today's college grads, but only 30% graduate with STEM degrees.  Women make up almost… https://t.co/EuaJrppUI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conspiracy or truth? #twins #riponindians @RiponHigh @MrMayfieldRHS @Adamgiedd https://t.co/WZ56decAt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy @iammrssamuels @Andy I watch all shows on Bravo. I mean everything. I cannot get on board with Bravo home. Th… https://t.co/1JByVQ0xOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have we still not learned that barriers at the zoo are, you know, there on purpose???!   Keep it, I feel 0% bad for… https://t.co/VaT1pJ5eLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 inmates died in a span of 8 days at Georgia prisons - https://t.co/us5GJvDi9v https://t.co/nAGwf4kWqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win the Valentine's Day Giveaway! from @theramblingjen #giveaway https://t.co/ceKwGogGdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is Goebbels Shitl....ers henchman  #trumptreason #TrumpCrimeSyndicate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PollyPapaya @Steelerschic85 @kathrynresister @CindyinMemphis2 @pam_brundige @Kovie1961 @nicole_bertrand… https://t.co/ZPf6qdHx5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a pain to acknowledge that swamp dwellers' salaries are funded by middle class hard working Americans! What a… https://t.co/m97Csdq8OW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact me for all your Disney travel needs! It’s FREE!!! https://t.co/qQ0uG8qEYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesse from @dmfaini and @GlenwoodGRT  class presented his passion project today.  His passion is coding and he used… https://t.co/fptNbY2soK]]></document><document><![CDATA[5AM Zazaam Slam Session! 💁🏾💪🏾💪🏾💜💜 @ Sculpt Fitness LLC https://t.co/O4ZwzdY8Wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I get one more phone call that begins with “we’ve been trying to reach you about your car’s extended warranty” I… https://t.co/MOtUAFRRU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally any of Cher’s outfits from Clueless, the yellow dress from How To Lose a Guy In 10 Days and all of the rh… https://t.co/22FJgEDzWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a great evening celebrating education and the arts at Parker ES and Jeans Hines Caldwell ES.  Our students a… https://t.co/iST0m2ou9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are your bestfriends really your bestfriends if they don’t trade shoes with you when your feet are on fiyaaaa in he… https://t.co/Jovn0afr6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for #KanardThomas! #TheVoice https://t.co/IiLqSUCl3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@contrarian11 But Nancy Pelosi wishes that more than anyone else. Think about it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEB wants to make sure we are all safe and lubricated! 😂 #HEB #Lube #Condoms https://t.co/vrywJbpTUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawdustbear my rose gold snakes. I have one in my ear and one in my nose and it's only been a year but the thought… https://t.co/Au5dFHBctw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supernovia @DanaSchwartzzz Me, too!  Damn that Wizard of Oz movie!  Still can’t watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Perkins worked very hard to abolish child labor, institute the 40-hour work week, launch the Social Security pr… https://t.co/VDY7gLOz7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkilahObviously Mona Lisas and Mad Hatters Goodbye Yellow Brick Road Tiny Dancer Rocket Man Someone Save My Life T… https://t.co/ULVsap1n77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader Just when you thought the Democrats couldn't get any lower they surprise you and get lower.]]></document></documents></author>