<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FreedomsRingUSA @womenwithgifts Followed your FB pls check me out @  https://t.co/UaZMHFwdFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accurate depiction of how I try to live this little life of mine.  #work #benice #workingmusician #indieartist Snea… https://t.co/DH4U9dBWIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No I didn’t!  Yes the libraries and others are digitizing -slowly- all sorts of historical docs]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #BayCity, MI #SocialSciences job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: BOARD CERTIFIED… https://t.co/KM7ElZQ3iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet, gentle Puck is waiting for you to pick him up from Charter School 🧡 Visit Puck and our other Charter student… https://t.co/Q9ADPhpPJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mood When ya homegirl is #lit because its her birthday pinktigress_ #everyoneistappingbottles #virginia @ Virginia… https://t.co/DpIeoYP1zA]]></document><document><![CDATA[deadass just spent half an hour doing my eyebrows so that I could sleep in and not have to worry about them in the morning 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a habit of trusting people who should not be trusted, assume goodness in them when they have never shown it,… https://t.co/1kxk48LF5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends, you've got to check out @imjustincharles' new single, #TheSweetest 🍯. Unbelievable talent from this NY nat… https://t.co/dGgDgxA4dQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome to hang with some local D.C. area #pubarch archaeologists at #AAAS2019 #FamSciDays yesterday and help out a… https://t.co/Hj0JETtXk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@walterowensgrpa @AOC AOC should lose her job! She’s an incompetent IDIOT🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think happiness just comes to you, or is it something you have to work towards?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahnGarrison @og_dbl_lo_g @noah_nonsense @tuckettweets @Richard_Stands @BeaglesResist @nhojhpesoj @LisaM3732… https://t.co/EurvtBBlWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaclark1313 Now we plan to take him a couple times a week for the play and socialization.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fab weekend in DC!! Had an awesome time eating all my favorite things and seeing some of my favorite people… https://t.co/9yP1jaGr69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielUlibarri @JoshMooreXXX @JoshMooreCF But yet you had nothing but good things to say about him when you posted… https://t.co/F2JnUmKa9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a twin size bed and some how my 20 pound dog takes up the whole fucking bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silentdeplorble @ToddXena @establishmentno @hockeygrandma23 @hungryturkey007 @ADeSenze @nightOwlbookLvr… https://t.co/UMANvyCAiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it only my friends that make a different group chat so we can talk about some other tea??]]></document><document><![CDATA[what (and i cannot stress this enough) the fuck https://t.co/LZseAhgzYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMPaulWilliams hi Paul, did I send you my sons song? Oh my husband made an album for me too, it’s pretty great https://t.co/PwaUWFZV59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @NBCNews It just NEVER happened!! PERIOD!! https://t.co/NtkZz5dhsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great Valentine’s Day x @ New York, New York https://t.co/sVNHlU256O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very thankful for today. Thank you for liking, following, and sharing! Have a great start to your week!  Sunday was… https://t.co/NsQ4eqrmW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Admin Cynically Weaponizes LGBTQ Rights https://t.co/nG6MBluWGG via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBISD_CTE @Mr_KingDHSHST #braingames #netflix #medterm cool facts on paradox choices https://t.co/UHoX0JJUof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave your assumptions about me below to be included in the nect vlog :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[hearing my tenth emergency flood warning today can’t wait for my 30 minute drive home 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smily0815_ 😍 If you think about it too long you'll start to scare yourself and doubt everything. I don't want to l… https://t.co/uI7wa2ZILl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody home??  #acorn #hole #home #house #nature #greatoutdoors #macro #macrophotography #photography… https://t.co/PFlGYlTxZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ljoobbie @SenRonJohnson @GovEvers Yes and it’s great. @GovEvers Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myraysalina Kay kinsa naman sad ng bouquet hgiuslan nimo mommy shark? HAHAHAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it shall be, that whosoever shall call on the name of the Lord shall be saved. Acts 2:21 ASV… https://t.co/obAUXCCjal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept a bit too long this morning, but woke up to the sun peeking through the blinds, birds chirping outside, my do… https://t.co/oFLV5c5nL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffposter1211 @marwilliamson So your saying everyone family  convicted of a crime should make restitution to ever… https://t.co/hCi56iTgNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nikki29752620 Lmfaoooooo it’s happened to me so many times. Welcome to the club girl lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinaltrap42 @drunkhistory You were sweet ladies and gentlemen and, Dr. Drew, helped to drive this odd and sad sto… https://t.co/PZmCAOALLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro @guypbenson This reminds me of when someone did something bad in school or work, and the principal/boss… https://t.co/QYEIBAlOJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badwlf910 He &amp; Abby were sperm donor babies of Victor &amp; Jack #yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I am absolutely outraged by this. Taxpayer money is not for her little pet projects to play with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @bengin1003 Because he has been compensated or compromised, take your pick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennChallenger @HoustonDynamo @MDAndersonNews Again no photo credit? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSDesertDolphin So total count matters? This is a bs point. If it’s abuse of power for one, it’s abuse of power fo… https://t.co/ZlNZaJysaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lafell_ It is pretty common outside of the casino and casinos In general, I took an organized crime class that loo… https://t.co/aboiUgDJnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe envelops got mixed up again and these are the categories that were supposed to stay in... #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/28 7:30pm Jazz in the Neighborhood host The Destiny Muhammad Trio W/ Emerging Artist Sean Huong Piedmont Center f… https://t.co/BBZdnpKMl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @sound_reasoning I dumped FB after 2016. Never looked back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberflier @GStuedler She has no problem locking up kids, she only has a problem because we know about it. She has… https://t.co/NmZdWXoGA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmfg_9 I KNOW! I was so devistated when he sent her home. I’m feeling the connection between Tashia and him, even… https://t.co/N3dTHVW3C6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeriopMedUCL NCEPOD and @RCoANews We need to better coordinate care for folks with Diabetes having surgery- a Peri… https://t.co/7mkcRyYgca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdlang this is a funny, Simply tell Siri "I Confess" and tada🙇‍♀️🎸🎶 k.d. lang plays! Why couldn't Cinderella play… https://t.co/ML9wJmtQFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% in! I’ve done the research. I follow the money. I know who walks the talk, who REALLY looks out for all of us!… https://t.co/H9h1dVKt2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Does My Cat Sleep With Me? - 5 Reasons You’ll Love to Know https://t.co/D1NMgTwq4J via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Lost by @ChrisYoungMusic on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Ys7HMdJjO6 💕💗🥰💃💃💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hazelebaby my sis said she saw u at the Houston rodeo but by the time she came and told me u were gone. Hope u had fun. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayer Heavenly Father, help me always to honor the people You have placed in authority over me. I thank You that Y… https://t.co/tRbVxGoIHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jan 11, CDF found McCarrick  guilty of "solicitation in the sacrament of confession." Feb 15, PF told him he was di… https://t.co/cjG2WKYbID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Because we all have to have 2-3 jobs to survive, it’s not more people,it’s the same people having… https://t.co/7UgmWtyQ6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Criticism of Israeli policy is not anti-Semitism https://t.co/IGTEV8SxpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I showed my ID to the bouncer and he looked at me, looked at the ID, looked at me, looked at the ID, looked at me,… https://t.co/fZntiJ5C4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoodgodabove Well, I mean, you've doomed us before. I've read the Bible stories. But somehow, we keep coming ba… https://t.co/12QHHMO6fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[U disgusting short ballless torture monkey 🐒 u leave me alone u godless pig  u don’t care who u Hurt forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if they still make the grade school use that awful fluoride/mouthwash crap once a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squalloogal @sr_donnas @DanaTriasMarion @EffieKammenou @NoitesFPodcast @FunnyLaughter1 @Florseriespcast… https://t.co/X3TvJFIWfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Machajewski completed the 10K! Time 01:01:23 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/Zdq4ExPkEr #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the Texas Legislature reforms school finance, don't forget gifted and talented students https://t.co/A5Ba1TObwI #whyGT #nisdgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this! #preachsister! #EngagedParents #ParentsAsPartners #teamFACE @BcsdFace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Infection control procedures in hospitals are based on studies that occurred a century ago. #APLHealth is studying… https://t.co/qB1XitpvHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Resistance is futile...just because you’re a monopoly, w/ a stroke of a pen that can change in CA. Get out of the… https://t.co/tJdzC4Fxel]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss: Hey, Would you like to come in early today?   Me: *needs money* Yes, Of course! What time would be early e… https://t.co/K1yhKWJfu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I share all of my Uber rides with @lizfraz. And she texts me every time I get home. Everyone needs a Liz. 🥰 https://t.co/NcZX92P5j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @wonderfullone Ego in size second only to Trump @seanhannity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bahidkofone @_davishel_ Praying for you Alex!!! I sure hope you beat it!  My dad did not!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoxNewsCEO @SafiMaasai Anew type of “Ponzi scheme”. This time lawyers needing their own lawyers! O what a tangled… https://t.co/n1BRyL97kY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pwSOAR @GreenJournal What I did learn is that there’s a lack of cultural competence in our medical education. Ther… https://t.co/UiyAMclWNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveForHell @YouTube I just realised this is peter coffin... &gt;_&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.  I don’t consider any of the movies I love to be bad. So I’ll choose a film that was universally panned but hold… https://t.co/vEu8qk9jTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila @CharlesM_NV What is wrong with these people! This is insane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would like to apologize to secaucus, nj for all the shit i talk about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is niggas working on things with 2 different people? 🤣🙄 super silly]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this day in 2011 someone stole 725,000 condoms in Malaysia. I hope they used it for the good of the people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuddleBarker I've only read the Dark Tower series... I have friends who love it. I'm not impressed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allllanaa It’s so stupid this year. I fell asleep during the girls tell all I was so bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nucleus1409 Right but i thought lying to special counsel also  a crime. Maybe she was not put under oath?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've had enough of myself ,I've been up this whole time perfectly fine and now that I'm starting my homework sudden… https://t.co/FKc3Mig1hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KitatPawz @RHOGossip @LisaVanderpump @TeddiMellencamp Can you link the Articles to me? I'd like to read them myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibbsMshairgrl Except @gwenstefani  needs @blakeshelton  on her arm instead of that other guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philshapiro Yeah, you don't want them to have lower self-esteem because they're robots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#et #casa #callhome #xayita #loveet en Quetzal Residencial https://t.co/JklygTq4HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago I was finishing grad school, at my most unhealthy weight to date, and not practicing any sort of self ca… https://t.co/B8ybIVZFX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like a good time to mention that “genus” &amp; “species” have actual meanings...  #whyareyoustilltalking… https://t.co/Q3eWTwTfyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexmahoney Ha! I wondered if you were there, given the time and venue! I'd love a recording, thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Nope on Bernie. I thought we were trying to avoid a replay of 2016. #NotBernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs embraces a 'flexible dress code'  https://t.co/uPItPLv83s https://t.co/WgYRAw87fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone should be a doll and get me the James Charles palette @jamescharles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch Date w/Kennedy!❤️😋 @ Sakura Sushi &amp; Grill Maryville https://t.co/kJVfbui1AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my brother, my friend, my constant from day one @Mr_Crooks12 !!! Love you so much! I hope today i… https://t.co/FlyQDbtDzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve honestly done so much with my life for only being 19 years old. But we aren’t stopping here. Not just yet. Bii… https://t.co/72jR3VJDy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I DID look cute. Thanks 57 bus @MBTA 🙄 @ Brighton Music Hall https://t.co/jz8At1du0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miami up 13-6 early as GT not shooting well but getting baskets on dunks.]]></document></documents></author>