<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[my mom is seeing Hamilton tonight and she’s not taking me so i am now taking applications for a new mom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance They want blood.  I am inclined to believe Cohen was indeed just smitten with Trump, admits to mis… https://t.co/C1VV9xzplq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never really understood the need to lie when someone’s been caught with their pants down 🤷🏽‍♀️ might as well be honest🤥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should’ve gone with the bachelor tonight instead. Less depressing. #mnwild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS #DefendSNL #NoWall #FakeNationalEmergency https://t.co/Qkxob3u4WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittnaynayy I can’t wait to see you! 😭 I really need a night with the girls]]></document><document><![CDATA[The episode of @parksandrecnbc when Leslie has the flu is absolutely one of my favs https://t.co/EJfeHc2OIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s it keep patting yourself on the back .  It is so unappealing!!! People think you’re a puff… https://t.co/eDQ3C3fieN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolframJoy Thanks for the hands-on lab experience in and for extending your reach to students of color. I can’t wa… https://t.co/r9XpTu1Dsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mhambi_M @mommamia1217 You stupid fucktard. Dumber than a box of rocks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Because he does not know how to properly govern. He was not qualified for this job. It is about mo… https://t.co/2AHXCIMbMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Marco! The pancake breakfast helping Get Behind the Vest Initiative happens this morning at 8!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power is out.  I’m trying to put on makeup by candlelight... but it feels like a seance is about to go down in… https://t.co/mK1EcGB9El]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis Never too soon for Peyton, but especially not after all the class shown in Oxford tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[A7: I think it is all the extra things that teach the kids way beyond the classroom! I give them opportunities to u… https://t.co/udz5AEWyuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComicContext You’re mine forever, you blond beauty! MUAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!! *Cough*]]></document><document><![CDATA[i HATE that my mind said “OOH YAY” for the split fucking second that it did @Sotero130 @Melenaj14 https://t.co/4YbnEHmrUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parlin81 is 5’7” for reference.  This record setting February snow is getting ridiculous.  We are currently under… https://t.co/EvUlViAjwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀 Proud of Newman Smith Boys BB, played an incredible game vs McKinney North. Came up short in OT but closing shot… https://t.co/ukRN37HCqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[kristen doesnt want to get matching formal dresses im not taking her anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tylenol is red And sometimes blue, If you are pregnant It's not for you.  https://t.co/1jFmBRV2z1… https://t.co/yN63NWZbx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megan_lynch @thegoodoommen @maysoonzayid @Malala @HillaryClinton Needed addition: @megan_lynch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I accidentally ate candy with strawberries in it and like broke out in hives and tonight I had a mental… https://t.co/EKAyV62vkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredButcosk Yep I heard that yesterday too! Said he’s the one that found Hamlin and gave him his start in NASCAR!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Great news! You take care of yourself. I am still praying for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hdzmirandaa “I’m gonna be studying, I’m gonna focus and memorize everything” https://t.co/GDAv9jp0RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have wanted to give up so many times this school year bc this transition to proficiency-based teaching is exhaust… https://t.co/DsdnoyEOgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@happywritingco 2 I struggle with Goodreads! I have such a hard time navigating, communicating, getting in touch wi… https://t.co/Wv4axGXlm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babe 😍🥰💋🥳💓Love u little hopevictoriaxo @ Gamma Phi Beta - Beta Xi Chapter https://t.co/X92PcSZKka]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about this song is that he really wasn’t playing when he said that the best women are in Africa cuz h… https://t.co/cJl3OGPz0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MobilizeLanka.                                       Have we solved all possible issue that we now need to hire ha… https://t.co/x8OYZKm2wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 11:28    Whoever trusts in his riches will fall, but the righteous wil... https://t.co/iwnaNopQTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any recommendations for ankles that feel like they want to fall off from running? I have to do 9 miles tomorrow 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is finally coming together for me. I have a job where I feel appreciated 99% of the time, a man that treats me… https://t.co/v02P2qZ9Bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and join me in @Minecraft while I built a home and defend it against pillagers and if it thaws visit the villa… https://t.co/niqJoH9T03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dannicus523 @Paul_Cornell Oh my goodness!!  Congratulations to you &amp; @HibaIssa ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always remember that the “EVIL 1%” worldwide is you, the American, who earns more than $32,400   So the Green New D… https://t.co/RP7EXRIYWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inappropriateKM After awhile time just kind of mashes together. My gran asked me when I started listening to kpop… https://t.co/oZQ4EHIOMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamLOwen @MichaelAvenatti He started this ball rolling to take Trump down.  We should not forget what an outstanding job he did!  #hero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teaghanthomas_ You are strong! You won’t let it!! Remember I’m here for you 24/7 text/call anytime.❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga is the hero all girls need. So confident. This #Oscars performance was to die for.#Oscars19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldgat @davidhogg111 @TomiLahren Ooops. Shoulda laid low hon. Reported and blocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect sentiment. May God keep and bless your family until you are reunited. Stay strong @YunaLeeTV… https://t.co/A86lObNAdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[College is for: •being awake for over 20 hours:)) •midterm week is upon us •t-minus 1 day till spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally so jealous of everyone who has had their babies in the last couple months😩 I'm just so excited for my lit… https://t.co/d07dCKMNNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianneM65725926 @bcamshepherd Agreed.  I like their original name... Conservative Reform..,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[This breaks my heart! 💔 U of Iowa students launch digital campaign around minority issues on campus https://t.co/Hh8iVK2cG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_M @OrangeChuck Everywhere! They benefit the Rescue Mission. There’s one in the plaza at Old Liverpool Road a… https://t.co/BmwRHPyveR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we just talk about this GORGEOUS engagement ring from @diajewelergs !?!  #perfection @ Gulf Shores, Alabama https://t.co/2Vs3TBy98P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whose going to lil baby and blue face next month in Houston ?🤔😂 That show finna be litt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomensHistoryMonth Meet Jackie Cochran aka Speed Queen, aviator, 1st woman to make a blind instrument landing, bre… https://t.co/tabiQqFi9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumbs up for solar! There is no better place for solar than California. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #HomeSolar$]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Simon? We're hiring in Indianapolis, IN! Click for details: https://t.co/t0HmYk8mtK #Simon #FacilitiesMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok done being a sad bitch. i've got this and everything is going to work out amazing in the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artceledelrey I can even really explain it but they kinda feel like visions]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The power of music”/ In honor of Read Across America Day, which aims to motivate all kids to read every day of the… https://t.co/LtBVb6SFtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[there's an adorable baby in my terminal gate wearing an IT pennywise onesie that says 'you'll float too' on it. i'd… https://t.co/RfYEfrjIfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am doing this with my future dog lmaooo   This just made my whole day 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[why the fuck have I just been sitting on this plane for over two hours and it hasn’t taken off I WANT TO GO HOME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brains_brawn_MD @ICU_Recovery @InSPIREICU @innovaHICU @tammyeaton17 Excited to meet you in person! ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[officially starting my day by throwing away apology letters from my ex.  💖 happy valentine’s day 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did my best Scarlet Takes a Tumnble impression in the middle of a downtown mall. Cured my misanthropy for the day w… https://t.co/Pnchzm6wIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmc031 @AOC We should all encourage this philosophy. The government should NOT make laws requiring it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition We absolutely have to take this country back by winning the Senate in 2020.  These people don't wo… https://t.co/j2Py6QjZBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker @NHYoungDems Your arrogance precedes you, Spartacus!  No one cares what you are your high school does!!! Dude, give it up!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can be anti Israel dictating American policy and not be anti Jewish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We’re so glad you’re home, mama!” @ Altadena, California https://t.co/dz5vBhbY4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this construction analogy for literacy instruction. We scaffold for strivers and then gradually remove the sca… https://t.co/vRIOVNI7Hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yes, I am very interested in what he did for @seanhannity , his other client.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @Verizon for being recognized as top company for exec women - and to exec @TamiErwinVZ for being such a… https://t.co/pvhZ58Et9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Nursing job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Nurse Aide /Healthcar… https://t.co/zWosJrgJrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never gets old watching a team hoist the Cup! Congrats @SCSUHUSKIES_MH &amp; @BrettLarson18 #PenroseCup #NCHCHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beckiina My thoughts exactly 🤦🏽‍♀️. People take the term “Self-Made” and take OFF! Everybody can’t be, will not be… https://t.co/i67DrJVGFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeeLuv2bme1 Details about the breeder haven’t been released yet. Nassau was focused on getting the dogs to safety]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up on the pool deck #wscruise #wscruise2019 #walkerstalkercruise @ Norwegian Pearl https://t.co/Ba3yKZNZgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it or yourself. Do it for him ❤️🐷❤️#HappyValentinesDay #Challenge22 https://t.co/TNb2rLhUTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicktangorra can’t wait until #TangorraTakeover tonight cuz i can’t wait to call you !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff You ARE  the Outrageous EVIL SCUM LITTLESCHITT AMERICA KNOWS. ABOUT YOU👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stalking myself on the internet...one of my hobbies...😂...I found some of my shirt designs. https://t.co/vKFksj1UNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariana_rojas09 @yackie_p Deja conseguir su número pa aplicarme jajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say hello to your newest Cameron Mitchell server 👋🏼🍔🍻🥂 So excited and happy to start this new journey 😊 (Not excite… https://t.co/EJgssM9dSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[One gun violence death traumatizes 20 other people on average per @ChrisMurphyCT I will tell you for my mom it was… https://t.co/ieIKiA6UQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisvirtel @marcjordancohen Very similar to my feelings about camping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s annoying ? Patrick. Patrick our cat is fucking annoying. Meowing at the door like her dying or some shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[19/ As explained in this article, to de-program people who’ve been fooled by disinformation, it’s “important that t… https://t.co/lSaBLrzJZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLBriscoe @AkronWineGuru @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007 @CaththeWineLady @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @joneill55… https://t.co/10Rh6W2C8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great networking and learning opportunities at #TABSE2019 @mariolayne @IL_Texas https://t.co/1CD5St0FBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a very long list of closings and delays today. Make sure you check it out before you leave the house.  https://t.co/vWwr7YF9OA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will vote for the Democrat that wins the nomination. It’s just that easy. Full stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt What? It lasts 6 months and you throw it away? I thot you just change the bulb!!! I did not know!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad only mega rich can invest meaningfully in stock market.  Try again @realdonaldtrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laracrystal4 @El_OsoBarbon @Chinohoven Still wondering how they look chafa.... somebody always gotta put their 2 c… https://t.co/zrMD6vFf8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATT I’ve been losing service all day(on WiFi and not on WiFi), my text messages aren’t going through. What gives?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are some good shows to binge watch during my recovery stage (2 1/2 weeks)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RosaryMysteries @DavidHarris707 @JudyMcAferty @aryservant @judysix6 @OfficiantR @ITGeekCT @disciple96 @myrnabob1… https://t.co/gkq1u8wr7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, two years and $50,000,000  of taxpayer money that the Dems caused and they have the unmitigated gall to want t… https://t.co/3z85TnCn8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I'm really really really good looking....and I have the black lung....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFoxxandFlora @Milly1776 @dan_sauceda_ This wasn't in reference to speech pathology specifically, it was in general.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly... #Supernatural aside. The new coat rack behind the door will probably always make me flinch when the liv… https://t.co/cB4VwCCW23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow “Mandy” by Barry Manilow. It’s sorrowful, memorable, everyone mocks it and many still know the tune/words.🎶]]></document></documents></author>