<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Ranger vibes. Missing my @Hyper_RPG and @PowerRangers family rn https://t.co/ltj2EjISQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecAFOfficial I haven’t been paid for 10 years. No limo. No plane. I drive myself. I won elections with Trump. I a… https://t.co/y9BPKrg3rR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy I’m just trying to study for my midterm and your crusty toes are stinking my nose up 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saintlennybruce @dominickevans Take it from this disenfranchised Black Woman #Unions are not all they are talked u… https://t.co/wEpXdTAzfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone! Happy Friday! Final day here....😞 https://t.co/OvVTNS21RJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottkfoley @WhiskeyCav Rocking the 80’s loving it.  Great show, looking forward to the rest of the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually got to sleep most of the night last night and don’t feel like total shit😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itspetergabriel PETER!!! THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR PARTICIPATING AT THE CONCERT FOR VENEZUELA THIS MONTH!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me if anyone asks me to help them with their homework this semester [I’m taking 15 credit hours this semester]: https://t.co/qXOVdd9UK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I Should probably be asleep by now but I’m way too excited for my first day of work, and also the fact that my… https://t.co/8FZihLIDSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[And do we really need the FELONY warning at the top of every sheet?  Because threatening people with a FELONY reall… https://t.co/dhdcmpWPlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@counsel4ubaby @NewsBreaking @POTUS That’s ridiculous! The way they get away with this crap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Misty Danielle Copeland is an American ballet dancer for American Ballet Theatre, one of the three leading classi… https://t.co/GOcZJDA6wF]]></document><document><![CDATA[lookin for a woman who will love me enough to tell me when i look like a badger....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalirebeccaaa SAME 😂😂😂 I always feel like I’m going to accidently chunk it across the gym and have to walk away 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[i stayed up too late and now i’m hungry again. great. thanks haley. bitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you never fight that means there are things you don’t say to each other and keep to yourself. The less you say,… https://t.co/4ETl73epKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pinky81949548 @jesusjugs2 I was just going to say that the apple  doesn't fall far from the tree]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming For You Herk And @Coach_PJAnadio 🥎 FL ✈️ NY https://t.co/hMgYoIhBHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you think your minions don’t know what “apprehended” means?  You have to define it for them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momo_sandiego @OhanaGrilleDenv @visitdenver @Colorado @winetraveleats @Jessicasquared9 @gigirules7 @suziday123… https://t.co/59ssUj9yQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have a one track mind your stupid wall. I hope they stop construction on it. Do you really think this is ever g… https://t.co/zAKuO0SREe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaudiaCastle3 @mikesonn @Jim_Jordan Beat me to it! https://t.co/w97efwJ651]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le acabo de regalar unos gases pimienta a mi hermana y a mi mamá porque más vale que estemos prevenidas y armadas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow does not stop @designcoredet - #DetroitMonthofDesign info session kicking off now at @CCS_Detroit Taubman Cent… https://t.co/FioyANmyKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started off #IWD2019⁠ ⁠ by dropping off 200 lbs of food 🍏 donated by amazing @TD_Canada women &amp; allies to the… https://t.co/ZzMllYN1m4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I felt bad for Brie @BellaTwins when I saw her hurt   @YaOnlyLivvOnce. But now that I see her reactions i… https://t.co/qRPfSILRxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard_Stands @kyleruggles @Azillion @KimBrker @woKEnancy @IsaacRockwell @CindisPLace @kodiak149 @CajunBlueAZ1… https://t.co/SopkGSbvuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BSmith’s Husband Finds New Love Amid Wife’s Battle With Alzheimer’s  https://t.co/NCrYTwRfL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tokenbrotha wow! First y’all don’t invite me out then this? Following me 4 months later? #Lameeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a while since we had a wholesome Saturday night💗 https://t.co/8j2jah5odd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youtubemusic @SusanTFor @blakeshelton @carrieunderwood @ShawnMendes @PostMalone @dariusrucker @ElvisPresley Favorite part of the show]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final thought for the day: I'm so very blessed to be where I am, do what I do, and have all of you.  Thank you for… https://t.co/GF1xJx7Qph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CortneyGurr Omg bitch I make like .0003 cents per stream to work my literal ass off u already know I’m writing all… https://t.co/C7r5jU78zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech skills are important but just as important is to be good at problem solving, organization, communication, and… https://t.co/2kGqH0w12G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live shot of the Trump presidency. #TrumpKimSummit https://t.co/h8lVt4GKdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why y’all spendin money on coke when a diet of Sudafed and wine do the same thing?  #frugal #TheWalgreensDiet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMilley3 @HonAhmedHussen @JustinTrudeau @blackvotecanada Well done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Malazan72 @dmartosko @DailyMail @AOC Retirement totally not the point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t regret a lot of things, but this, this is going to be one of those things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lifesabeach Not TOO much today but should be rain free! Enjoy your walk!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RED PILL OVERDOSE: What has @FoxNews been HIDING from #MAGA? Cover-up EX... https://t.co/2Etc5cD9iI via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe I went to Nashville last weekend 🤠 https://t.co/ec3eZELaMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to watch the #Hokies take on Clemson in the @accwbb tournament round ✌🏼 #ACCWBB https://t.co/5V60YBXwWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr I hope he starts by firing those with 25th Amendment on their lips and treason in their hearts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never realized how many asshole drivers there is — until I started taking E driving. #rude https://t.co/QD07428SoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This goes out to my dear friend Tony who was found dead in his home this morning. They think he died Friday. Tony w… https://t.co/V8tJfazZfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there was any doubt Amelia was my mini me, veggietales, Elvis, and Post Malone seems to be her favorite music.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyElves I complained to my lawmakers back in the 80's &amp; 90's that I didn't want my tax money funding abortions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HaPpy, HaPpy, HaPpy 39th + ?? Birthday, Joanie Ponie!!! As sisters we drive each other crazy, but the love is alway… https://t.co/byNQIaALfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh fuck this love shit I just to go back drinking and haveing fun and been with friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skcopeland @skcopeland let me help you......There is no line at Betty Rae's, so we are getting ice cream. #FixedIt #IceCream365]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya pasó navidad y mi cumpleaños pero ahora si tengo una lista de regalos que me gustarían 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[brown suga  secured in  soft velvet 🦋 @ Marietta, Georgia https://t.co/15cLE25uWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey daniel when I wore my sweater half off it was a bet. just thought I’d let you know that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having some Valentine fun in K8 this morning! ❤️🥰 https://t.co/dJQ2hiv9SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neighborhoods are the heart of our city and we must see that no neighborhood is ignored. #WorthTheWork]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually don’t care for intros to albums but Monsta X’s “INTRO: WE ARE HERE” is my fave. I’d love if a full length version came out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great resouces here: https://t.co/Hu09w7V2L1, The US National Center for Women and Information Technology in Boulder, Colorado]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a random ass flashback from when we went to Trinidad James concert in SC. And everyone was sauced af. And someh… https://t.co/T45fPlkGJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessperate Just got to page 391 in the handbook and figured out how to export process videos! Here's what's goin o… https://t.co/HerS7Rwdbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemme get this straight. On one hand, you lament that self producing artists are underrated. You then try to drag B… https://t.co/s1FYYtA2ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimssamjang ok but tell us abt your version of sound mixing/music producing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi How many chances does Omar get before she is run out of DC on a camel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[he comes inside and starts yelling at me and calling me a bitch because i could have taken two seconds to do him a… https://t.co/iTvVMGyq12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanarbabi @DoughneyJ That’s why I am a proponent of standards based grading.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @khloekardashian and @KevinHart4real care to weigh in or retract your comments promoting #JessieSmollett and h… https://t.co/jNSIHLE8QL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt great working on the prko line tonight! Feels nice to feel like u belong and accepted in a way! For the first… https://t.co/7aZ6npt5iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will @POTUS ever take responsibility for anything that's under his control? A failed deal with Kim Jong Hu is the D… https://t.co/5q88nIFfW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched Bohemian Rhapsody for the third time; SPEECHLESS. Still in awe that I get to see @QueenWillRock in 174 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Built in storage seat. When you want to hide the mechanicals of your steam shower AND sit while your bath fills...… https://t.co/cit4YoknkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Hog80 I think he's just holding off cos he know I lost all my $$$ playing ....poker ... oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have come a long long ways. From living a life of a victim mentality to overcomer.  I spent years using the victi… https://t.co/1dNi1wbSWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠⚠ THIS FRIDAY ⚠⚠ GRAND OPENING OF #FLOWFRIDAYS 🎥🔥 flowlounge_ri 📍 Sounds By: djmegajay X ltg_entertainment 🌋🌋 Birt… https://t.co/F4JwJB5vBn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars #BlackHistoyMonth Today I honor Hattie McDaniel, the first African American to win an @TheAcademy Award in 1939.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlynnowen #FBRParty #BlueWave2020 #IndictTrump #TrumpResign #TrumpFakeEmergency #25thAmendmentNow #ImpeachTrump… https://t.co/63qg030m7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoiceBlinds I think Dexter is the front runner on your team so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our President Trump is innocent. The dirty ones want to get him out because he has the dirt on them and hopefully t… https://t.co/SfD14VLnLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of our goalie options are total trash. The last 2 years have told me this. Watch any and all highlights. We scr… https://t.co/gLbn6zcK0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so this Monday wasnt bad.... got a 2 dollar raise, workout done, the sun is shining and its 34 degrees. This calls for an iced coffee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the thing that annoys me the most about this khloe jordyn thing is her bringing her kid into the tweet and saying h… https://t.co/nSvSGcpjp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN  Go bad to Africa !!! America is a Christian Nation your Muslim Crap isn’t wanted here. Get out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Target you only have 1!!! plus size bathing suit in your Washington DC store. This is unacceptable. 1 bathing suit… https://t.co/6QlFgQNeAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahNelson11 They had already made an outline of what could have developed into an essay, and they recorded on Fl… https://t.co/Eb9jeXMHhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Now boarding to make great memories. #iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our very own Exercise Science rockstar, Rachel Brown! @PittEducation #h2p #hpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I took your advice and started watching it and all I can say is IM OBSESSED. BINGE WATCHING IT AT THE MOMENT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the reasons that I LOVE my job!    #destinationderrynh    https://t.co/1ZFeTC8yqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyRxMan If I lived near you I would give you my cell and you could call me for a taco run any time you wanted. My treat.🌮🌮🌮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt And what do you want to bet they “don’t believe” in health insurance either so the public, directly… https://t.co/R8PNJUcS75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek That can be little doubt that this is a cyber attack by US-aligned individuals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Jill Stein and Bernie always demean Democrats. They are russian assholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister: one day you’re gonna get famous off the jokes on your tweets I gave you   Most tweetable person I know 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune In at 10pm  Nightly on @MDHRelationship 💜   Sign Up Free:  https://t.co/UZDo2hJFq7 https://t.co/0meT6eWTWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIAnderson3 @Vickivbreezy @AussieDebBell @Sarahwaugh20 @ninampls @lc1_summit @jhgurf @minhtngo @MrsblksantaX… https://t.co/7kmzRHO9Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/u12bijz2Jw  #bethechange #PositiveMentalAttitude #WillieIsTheBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hem_demj @TheBreakdown167 It’s funny (to me) because she was a local news person here in CT. And her name recognit… https://t.co/34hR4Tvhm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really is too bad we couldn’t do something like that. As many times as I sign my name, I feel like I should be c… https://t.co/uaLhdbLoPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting out HOOPS on... Channeling our @BenDavisBasket1 GIANTS here in TN #wearewayne @22_kenken_ https://t.co/THEdeELgTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBollard BIG facts. Soon as I get home I’m hittin my bed hard. Idk if I’ll even change my clothes. 🤷🏼‍♀️😂]]></document></documents></author>