<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Roseline et le @SUBWAY !!!! #Smile @SUBWAYCanada https://t.co/6KvGliLfLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suffering horrible seizures today. Gangstalkers channeling themselves through me. Being violent. Running me down ve… https://t.co/uEVkQXxZpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graywolf442 @aggierican @AlaskanCourtney @Pomquat @NucMM1retired @skreletron From a dating profile of mine. On tha… https://t.co/ouNkdkK4Xj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let love be genuine. Abhor what is evil; hold fast to what is good. -Romans 12:9 Lord God- I pray we will love what… https://t.co/YgCSZb1oLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been YEARS since I’ve had a nightmare where I woke up screaming...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te espero hoy de 4-6pm en el Gwinnett place mall con el universoulcircus y tú @LaMegaAtl estación, ven con toda la… https://t.co/cSnFqJs5d6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawayneMcIntosh @KMeyering @CCMSJags @tlmstornados @FranklintonMS #BETTER https://t.co/8LCcQSGHXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#imwithkaepernick✊🏾 #facts💯 @ New York, New York https://t.co/vIiCFiqmdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martinxsky Should I get the chord back and drum pack separate or the chord and drum pack 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonmfournier @CurtisDesroches @Sethrogen Close personal friend...he just doesn’t know it yet....I plan on workin… https://t.co/OFGGjVg2bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rather large Eminem on stage at the Pink concert tonight. https://t.co/bUW40dgAMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[TWO BANNERS FOR BRAEMAR.  Wow @hockeylogic.  Just.  Wow.  Congrats to you, Kristie, and those amazing kids]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope I raise the kind of kids that would never think to post a response to an Amazon product question with “I don’t know.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting true love In motion #trueloveinmotion @ ESPN Club https://t.co/Ssj9RPpFWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IssaDoll 🤳🏽   #MyLife 💁🏽‍♂️   #ThePrettyBoi 👌🏽 https://t.co/m5rexsdh2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterLodde Seasons are longer in GOT'S world. They can last years. And it only was coming for 6, it arrives in sea… https://t.co/ewBNhUpYPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[humor for me today. HAHAHAHAHAHA "and then there's this cunt."  LOLOLOLOLOLOL #mirth #chuckle #grin #amusing https://t.co/iUd8IytKtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@importcarguy @letsv4real @VMware @MyVMUG @VMworld It would be my pleasure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early risers. It’s my weekly visit tomorrow morning with @JimTothSports @TroyWestwood @TSN1290Radio 630amPT/830amMT… https://t.co/7gIsIOY3g2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un says he believes Trumps claim, that he is unaware of child abuse on our southern border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CmdrJonty Possibly...but that, in itself, won’t cause German car prices to rise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alvie_barr @JNJInnovation @JLABS @winterlightlabs @Analytics4Life @CloudDX @AFMesquire @BoWang87 Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's not forget that 'Tarzan' has easily one of the greatest soundtracks of all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[The steady, much-needed late winter rain continues in Santa Barbara, California... . . . . . #California… https://t.co/pZQZTclVIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @FoxHonors information session happening now at the #Temple #ETD2019. https://t.co/swXA2Z0eo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This Porg contains chemicals known to the State of California to cause cancer and birth defects or other reproduct… https://t.co/1UFLuiyQoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! Faith is a rest and takes you above pressure. Believe God’s Word more than you believe the pressure today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burgessev @guypbenson Hey boys get a stem cell infusion and grow a spine. Time to fix the issues that have had lit… https://t.co/QdnWAZ5XHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterjhasson Isn't that the same guy that snuck the photo in Northam's yearbook?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_hanke @RealSaavedra Just more #Propaganda to promote #US takeover of #Venezuela's oil reserves.… https://t.co/eWftKHVj87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palita_40 Muy buenos días pAlita y feliz Lunes y inicio de semana saludos internacionales y cuídate mucho,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learn from the lessons and experiences encountered in life, become stronger and smarter as a result.]]></document><document><![CDATA[: Four seasons | One Bag | the most versatile all-purpose carrier | still a couple of #Lemuel totes available in th… https://t.co/ued3H9vlBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evan and Centennial High School Indoor Percussion at BHS #centennialhighschool #indoorpercussion #ppaacc @ Bakersfi… https://t.co/o8S0QWeKka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kat4Obama @sharynski Very bad strategy for a politician. Dubious but very edgy (potentially viable for some while?… https://t.co/fA11AiEHip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewlwheaton @TremontHSBBB @MasseyBball @CoachTwaddle @CoachJayHatch @ChargersAD @ehughs32 @streaksbball No, but if they made them ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karinabarbosa lo único que necesitamos es que las fuerzas armadas pidan la renuncia de Nicolás Maduro para evitar un baño de sangre ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now we have a very close score, #KawhiLeonard 19pts, 9 in this quarter #NBAAllStar #NBAenTN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elimination Chamber overall was more good than bad. The women's chamber match was awesome. SD Tag Title match ended… https://t.co/vxun77D2S7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresJuanObama One day, those things are a money pit man, you gotta have yo check RIGHT right to really fuck wit it. I got some work to do 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missnemmanuel @GameOfThrones I didn't think your character was interested in the throne 🤔 #forthethrone #missandei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CinematicBanter Right?! And I know he spoils it in the interview, but it’s like dude, you just robbed me of whatev… https://t.co/cCrPzVB5B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toucan_x i’m too lazy to search songs. so that’s why I love apple music also! I have offline playlist. music video… https://t.co/4M1cJo2Aye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SantaPatriot @beer_parade @HudMagy @johnspanyers @highhopesUSA @McbroomRobbie @MJ33929126 @truthseekerd… https://t.co/dIEE9E8sSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sol Agave by @lostcoastbrewer @ Sol Agave — https://t.co/Xt4J0xfAPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lumiere87024120 Well, since you like blue and I like red, both colors make purple…🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[After All Children’s deaths, proposal aims to catch heart surgery problems via @TampaTimes by @kmcgrory https://t.co/NiEPDEw0iB]]></document><document><![CDATA[my research proposal is keeping me up all night but it’ll be worth it when i’m in JAMAICA doing what i LOVE w peopl… https://t.co/2KTBi7vgjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t sleep. Woke up at 3, got some coffee going, &amp; watching Kitchen Nightmares. God damn I love @GordonRamsay]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m gone , I hope y’all feel it 🙏🏽 cause while I’m here , y’all don’t feel me at all 💯✍🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeForeman Hey Champ. Thinking of you and your family during this difficult time. Sincerest condolences to you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not need eyes to believe . .  No necesito ojos para creer. . #kcphotonetwork #kccreatives #kcphotographers… https://t.co/0B2pZ1admK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures from the 2019 Women's March in Portland, OR Sunday (2/03/2019)! @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/a7oaDO84dm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have asking this for ages, what happened to the fight for Mumias  sugarcane farmers that @KBonimtetezi was leadin… https://t.co/HMVMlOsDuO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleedColtsBlue @_Dawg_Pound @Browns @Colts You're trying to tell Browns fans that our team was garbage?   WE KNOW.… https://t.co/UeaVQHTbF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just can’t stop watchine #adiscoveryofwitchestv! Perfectly perfect sceneries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In memory of a great woman Margiann Mello, I am so glad to have had her in my life, if only for a few minutes on Su… https://t.co/rwIdlAYaVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph N. Barometer 29.924 in, Falling. Temperature 26.7 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 92%]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left has lost the mind. The declaration of the governor of NY and VA are terrifying. These guys have to be craz… https://t.co/bhv6AwoWVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog His highness doesn’t know what the word truth means cause he lives in an alternative Trump land with surreal facts and “truths”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social Studies is in the people building business.  The health of our democracy depends on a solid base of active e… https://t.co/a7V2Gp9tQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MingNa Just finished watching all the episodes again. Looking forward to seeing what happens next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeNationalEmergency #FakeNationalEmergency #FakeNationalEmergency #FakeNationalEmergency #FakeNationalEmergency… https://t.co/h5tBfZnfy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porque está escrito: Por minha vida, diz o Senhor, diante de mim se dobrará todo joelho, e toda língua louvará a Deus. Romanos 14:11]]></document><document><![CDATA[craft beer festival at the fairgrounds!! @ Orange County Fair Speedway https://t.co/WNkd0nptwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch lied about gettin raped now she lyin bout me beatin her ass.. what a joke of a female take the ass whoopin an… https://t.co/pz8j5QHuqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notallbhas Right so rich people should stop donating to the poor altogether... makes sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGATOUR @McIlroyRory Way to go @McIlroyRory. Thank you for being great to these kids and showing them what kindnes… https://t.co/9VEIepgybb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsaBadTake @MrBrianKenny JD was also coming off a 45 homer year and Harper has only topped 30 homers in a seaso… https://t.co/rmLgGIhD5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's brisk baby! Taking in the wisdom and fashion advice of a good friend and @folkalliance veteran @ian_sherwood… https://t.co/KMjuPh6KjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just sitting back, watching Buffalo sports Twitter eat itself. https://t.co/7LCSQk0wx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Malone is about to get fired at halftime the way that this game is going #LeBronEffect #NotHisCoach #NBAAllstar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my apps instantly synced up on #CarPlay from @HessertChevy  🚘📲🔄🔊🙌🏼 https://t.co/WQNlc3azBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kipwinger LIVE at the @BuffaloRoseCO  - the finest concert venue ever! @5280Magazine #80s #80srock #wyckoff… https://t.co/pybeH4F7k6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LakasBack!! #SomeoneIsHappy!! @ Oakland, California https://t.co/wiBVdAYbqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight: “Merrily We Roll Along” @ Roundabout Theatre Company https://t.co/FknEgHSZZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one team they beat must really stink.  Goes back and checks schedule  Logs out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EjmEj @nytimes @Noahpinion @conorsen @mattyglesias Many on the populist right are suggesting the same thing. Tucke… https://t.co/aTwSTssOlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT @MUTGuru @EA_KRAELO @Jstein2469 @Schautz47 @Sgibs7 @MaddenBible and can we please get combine power ups this Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Milenio @IvonneOP @fdelcollado @TragaluzenTV No devuelvan las paridas con las preñada decían en el rancho; el PRI… https://t.co/Mh2i8YLI29]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #favorite quote by @CaseyNeistat  and my #inspiration behind @Juxt_App.  “If you want to be a #writer, you need… https://t.co/0WxnO1C22A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PeteSmith_ I say no. Just because they have Njoku and Landry filling those TE and H-back roles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NCAAsoftball No @kkatlyn111 ? Inconceivable... https://t.co/wpRDoaIz04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @zuriwilliams_  for making ECC second team!! https://t.co/EV5pF8kBdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you gonna trash talk when you look like a lollipop that fell behind the couch and got covered in hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should have added: “if we can unionize sex workers, that’s more union dues coming our way”]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤 🎼Quiero ser 🎸Todo en 🎵tu Vida todo 🎸esta en que tu 🎵me quieras en 🎶que te desidaaaaaas 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also thank you to redtimsmit and kathy_smit for the cover. Good start to the birthday which is still a couple weeks… https://t.co/4WP3yPbjjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all my people for coming out with me to celebrate 👌👌 @ Garden City, Michigan https://t.co/CJBdBfoK7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @KristySwansonXO @RealJamesWoods @LindseyGrahamSC   America  belie… https://t.co/W8dRXHEQtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBlanchard1978 @BuschLattes So say I’m 113. Imma need 135 G protein. What does that look like?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After pinning the second ranked wrestler in his class and defending national champion, Daniel Lewis earned MAC Wres… https://t.co/WHQHauwLhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Process Control Engineer - https://t.co/15oQGT1hpK #Engineering #CityOfAngels]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many critical bad calls in ALL sports.  Refs are not getting worse, replays and HD video is getting better expo… https://t.co/lZ0JglW8d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A trip to donut man for their seasonal strawberry donuts after an 11 hour shift sounds fantastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews "The Old Sage"- While reading one conservative report, quote "the UNITED States as an apathetic nation. WE… https://t.co/IKPWMi7hbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagaGoldHat @luvnewinfo @TexaLonestar @BlueSea1964 @Jali_Cat @CajunChick25 @HLAurora63 @harjo111 @Maggieb1B… https://t.co/DFiwYF9GWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@groupekeolis @KeolisBoston @MBTA_CR I guess it’s too early to sale or shovel?? I wonder how many lawsuits today fo… https://t.co/lLfGtIWdOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow will you wish me a Happy Birthday?  Feeling blue and missing my hubby of 23 years.  But JB has now got me! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m late with this @KellyHrudey but great shout out to your friend Mr. Bob Ridley for being the voice and the bus d… https://t.co/9RsPNvDV0l]]></document></documents></author>