<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GeeRubbs Woah I didn’t even know fire on the mountain offered pizza? 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19 #Paine_RYS19… https://t.co/o1sjANxZzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Solo: wow.  A fascinating look at a person who has the most insane laser focus on a goal that I have ever seen… https://t.co/yWmml63BAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve been raking my final tonight &amp; working on my case-notes for work tomorrow evening]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord I pray u reveal all the snakes that’s trynna poison me and only send me people that’s gone watch &amp; help me grow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are all my fave stores turning into nightmares or straight up bankrupted. I’m not always going to be forever 21 I need options damn it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que bello detalle de mi compañero de lab, Jacob. Hoy por el día de San Valentín, Jimmy!!! https://t.co/hRu4iREaOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[my 5 year old just told me he hates me...  cuz i didn’t trade pokémon with him. now i feel like an asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow in Bethesda! @capitalweather @MCPSsnow heading out now before the icy stuff comes https://t.co/Wu9z7NC7rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@296_cool @loveujustinjb5 @BhanuRajput33 @kulsgrace @Monika_Kapoor19 @curly_bug @Bizzlex8 @justinsplanet42… https://t.co/LTf9LCjIFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My liver is NOT ready for this weekend with @britt_waterbury but we are gonna do this shit anyways 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some stuff I added into my room and a pic I found https://t.co/lkQiXY2VLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night. Post Harry Potter pub crawl. We survived. We are the Sisters Who Lived. #harrypotter #norman… https://t.co/ayB0u1I5rS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abby’s 21st is less than a month away and I’m more excited about it than my own birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up on GMV: 🌹The Bachelor is trending. Why Colton jumped the fence ✔️An unlikely national pharmacy is in trou… https://t.co/iJJrLlzcwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caribbean people so annoying with this 🙄 all hip gyrating/ass shaking is lit. Y’all be trying to say this to shade… https://t.co/sPAyvrC152]]></document><document><![CDATA[and give the biggest headaches and heartaches uwu fuck y’all anime niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USA_Aquanaut @CNN I guess you better make sure only Repub teachers have guns!]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘I think women are foolish to pretend they are equal to men, they are far superior and always have been.’ - William… https://t.co/UBuWRR0FAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a racist you are. That’s the only word you know and you put your ignorance on display. An embarrassment like b… https://t.co/MftQelpCSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RunStreak day 315. 20 miles. Pushed the entire world out of my head and focused on training as hard as possible. F… https://t.co/OP6Unw0cMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsBETTER I ain't getting rid of my mattress and pillows. They're still good to sleep on.🛏]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAG.  How low must #WeThePeople go before it's time to push back, redeem our civilized, ethical + moral principles… https://t.co/k0ubrhuGcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[every day is valentines day with my guy. So happy and lucky to go to sleep every night and wake up every morning wi… https://t.co/LncrXceRFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sug_knight At 77 years old I am still curious of things in the world.  Welcoming new faces.  And taking time to smell the roses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See everyone at 10am for LEI interviews and MBA Speaker Series class at 4pm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CL_Cook_ It's supernatural drama. Nine chapters in, hoping I can make it ten in the next thirty minutes. 🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your hubby takes you to The Wizard's Tower.  #nerd #gamer #unicorns #omgunicorn #pusheen @ Wizard's Tower https://t.co/LRrNX94Gil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to my world. I was born with a pre-existing condition almost 70 years ago The most amount of money I’ve see… https://t.co/BZg8EkBzNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shrubwalker @nkertzner A block up from Baghdad and half. Block from Portland Cider in Hawthorne. No idea about Screen Door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time in 2 weeks I’ll be waking up in Barcelona.   Catching flights all 2019, just watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna know what I'm doing for Valentine's Day!?  Washing my hair cuz I care more about my hair than I care about you niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolifesounds @NiGHTS_official @CampCandleMusic @SuzanneSheer @dstntstrr @imyeek @tylerpursel Appreciate fam. 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maranathakurios @benjamindcrosby @KaitlynSchiess I believe church that cares for kids as its children rather than… https://t.co/9NOXVLKiWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharon_cantley @VitCza @deborah26449389 @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @SassyCassyCat… https://t.co/StTFS4GExU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mokeefe315 The last one could’ve been more sophisticated with a between the legs or something. He did enough to wi… https://t.co/C0nLU194ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom really did well with the birthday gift 🎁 🎉 🧠 https://t.co/CqFjjDXohq]]></document><document><![CDATA[.... because all 3 will die for what they love and that’s toxic as well b/c there’s no returning from that damage]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PropertyManagement is busy today addressing properties affected by the high winds in #CentralPA!… https://t.co/7OZMgmSqo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[About Last Sunday at Slide Thru Sundays with TTE Twin Towers Entertainment!!! With Big James &amp; G. Turner!!  You… https://t.co/WIz1HhXLcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i forgot about this time change...seeing it turn 3 really confused the fuck outta me for a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Vietnamese food but I feel like using chopsticks might be a little soon for the second date]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir @reply Omgawd how I need a sunny vacation soooo badly. @AlaskaAir @reply  ...Hawaii, pretty please.  #Hawaii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarpeoDesiree I did not know of the existence of this Institute. I'm going to find out more about it. Are you fami… https://t.co/oAPVXERi35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllyDemmith yes i got it yesterday , if you don’t like strong coffee i would add extra caramel]]></document><document><![CDATA[tim sweetie, u really snapped in as long as you're happy, i get chills every time ✨ @cubsportmusic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jellies!!!! #mysticaquarium #jellies #jellylove @ Mystic Aquarium https://t.co/mESMkIY6Aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Seminole way....#gritty and #hardcore! #whateveritakes #OURtradition #NoleBlooded  #nothingnewunderthesun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoyosgirl0824 I would happily volunteer to get those for you my fingers hurt do you mind if I use my tongue 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are hurting women by spreading lies that have no basis in real world medical practice. They assault the dignit… https://t.co/I8oJXUEY42]]></document><document><![CDATA[a mía original #apprentice 🧚🏽‍♀️🙇🏻‍♀️🍀⛰🏚🍞🌹🌈☔️🥬 #sundayfunday #sundaycomingdown #candyred is life a #stage or… https://t.co/dp2s5AfszK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women in urology just don’t treat women says @DlambJ. @SWIUorg provides this practice profile. #AUASummit19 https://t.co/TeyG4bVHZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mary_mulvenna9 Haha thanks @mary_mulvenna9 ! I’m on other side of court #vipsection 😉... hopefully IT takes long so you can keep watching 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierrazellmer_ One time i told my mom i partially only wanted to get married for tax purposes and she cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5awritersclub deep deep in #editing this weekend. Send provisions(and by that I mean chocolate!!!) #writinglife… https://t.co/YdGWL10PQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ew ew pls stop acting like u bout it bc we all know what ur like in real life 😖😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do most yinzers know #ManWithAPlan is set in #Pittsburgh?!  I didn’t, but am instantly intrigued by inside burgh jo… https://t.co/e0mcwhOf2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCSDMLKJr @RCSDcommschools @lellegay @streemode @RCSDNYS And we love them! https://t.co/w4ZIGHKiuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 NO! And I don't feel weird about; I feel strangely normal. How about that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HasidPuentes @BlackshearKISD @KleinISD One of my favorite days in Kinderland 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA Thanks Sarah. Obsessed with trees (they surround our cottage) and the moon💙 https://t.co/QDaLLB4a9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to celebrate International Women's Day! Accountability inspo call with my growth friend summerscolaro ,… https://t.co/CNttegzv8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[“you are so much sunshine in every square inch ☀️“ walt whitman @ Ellicott City, Maryland https://t.co/lscfkjxczR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest Agreed! I was super happy when Mark Wills was inducted this year. He's such a great country artist.… https://t.co/wWwKPBW9pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 Would wish a poor dog had to be in Trump’s phony presence. That is akin to cruelty....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal here we come again. #abouttime #universalstudios #freeweekend @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/VeHmtVA4JM]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my latest @HerCampusUFL article, I discuss the false pretenses of journalism and the first amendment.  “Journali… https://t.co/VxZFg0caGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @ImDexterRoberts! #TheVoice https://t.co/nsvbR2JhHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in the nursery organizing boxes of clothes too small for Lucy and catching up on #GreatBritishBakeoff on… https://t.co/ff1FWmF46Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brigitte St-Pierre Leader #Tupperware à #Sherbrooke 🦋 ☎️ 819-238-5138  https://t.co/ctd3R49eMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[One big take away for me from A Star is Born☄☄☄ https://t.co/KZyEMtgHin]]></document><document><![CDATA[It also helps that I worked from home and always get far more done there. Less distractions and people interaction… https://t.co/OdXAKkhTwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckster_1977 @jessicalbuxton @xhipee @ChrisolytheN @Orpheus631 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump The problem is the drs… https://t.co/YX5EwZycPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbvena @JulieMarie5 @realDonaldTrump That’s your opinion and that’s ok.  Your as entitled to it as I am. Two sides… https://t.co/ZdWyOE9xaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuuTakeNotice with the basket!! @raptors905 @ Raptors905 https://t.co/eeeIQqJO2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BP_America Hey remember when you guys had that oil spill in the ocean and it just gushed and gushed and did tremen… https://t.co/cVbxJIU6Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We keep this love in a photograph we made these memories for ourselves where our eyes are never closing and the hea… https://t.co/5Ti1cOQEqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Margari_Aziza @MuslimahMontage You can call whenever, but I don't extend those privileges to e'rybody 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EcoSexuality It falls right in line with everything else tied to our president.... Just lock him up already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ig being the same as everybody else is the “new in thing.” Im cool bruh I’ll just stay to myself 🗣🙇🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The closer we get to the tour starting the more curious I get about that ‘old song medley’ 👀 #SuspendingGravityTour @mtrench]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anne_theriault She thinks Molly was undervalued; that Ginny and Luna rule; is on the fence about Harry; and has a… https://t.co/6sXKWkD5XH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are neat Pupusas are good And I like to eat   Roses are red Violets are in my cart I’m Asian… https://t.co/EiQ5bDIlqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[God of all, God of hope, We pray for women and girls today. That they will be all they can be. Give us courage to s… https://t.co/tZMnu9cv6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would any parent entrust their 5,7,10, or 12 year old child to any grown man? For money or some sense of fame?… https://t.co/gxmDirIW3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[2000’s country mashup monday...  asking for a friend, is the @keithurban lyric “take your cat” or “cap” ?? •team 🐈… https://t.co/6bx9pNjxbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought the coolest vapormax, too bad no one told me how uncomfortable they were. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pusherbmx @JeffBezos @realDonaldTrump I’m scared to do my taxes. Everyone I knows paying for the first time ever a… https://t.co/mhdA9V9Nyb]]></document><document><![CDATA['Moment of reckoning': US cities burn recyclables after China bans imports https://t.co/MPa7QsTBFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primer día de paseo con mi primita Jenny ♥️🌬️❄️ @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/cKK8q3J77e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mohamed36836678 @drassagheer وماذا عنك أين وطنك وأين دينك وشرفك وكرامتك وإحساسك . هذا إذا عندك إحساس . البلتاجي مص… https://t.co/BLDyQ0Hjzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6_7_96 Naw, joking here and there was the norm but everyone was always joking on Africans and now everyone wana va… https://t.co/nMhEzR7XWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Because the road to truth Justice and the American way is HARD! Most men/women are too cowardly or weak t… https://t.co/E6NExAIM12]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walmart farms out same-day grocery deliveries to low-cost co drivers https://t.co/JOUCshOox6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congestion and traffic-wise, Pembroke Pines has turned into Miami Jr and I’m not here for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rowenachan161 @LuisaBarrantes5 @dimash_official #TWBDimash , #WorldsBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyTstout @SotehPR @steven_seibel @KenCageRepo @coyoteweather10 @HappyAndFreex13 @PhilliesMike @jonmorosi… https://t.co/Y07NCKvs51]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Georgia On My Mind by Ray Charles, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics ® https://t.co/iBlRzw9pBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! I’m thinking a summer trip to Vegas is in my future!! #MetamorphosisVegas #ilovejanetjackson]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a crazy week and a crazy day today. We didn't have plans since our son had a birthday party but my hubby… https://t.co/h77YHSV11c]]></document></documents></author>