<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BlakeMurphyODC Prob didn’t sign cause of lack of guaranteed playing time I assume? OKC doesn’t have much front court depth if at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice play by @johntrous11 gets the inning’s first out, but scores a run to give Ball State their first lead of the weekend.  1-0 BSU T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratuations Stephen Harper @stephenharper for the trap you laid for Skippy McFuckhead He fell for it big time SO now what trudeau????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo creo que todo el sonido está conectado a un solo cable y a cada rato lo pisan y se desconecta esa vaina.  #VenezuelaAidLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #UGA commit, 4-star WR Justin Robinson (@jay_robi22) of @ELCAFootball likes what the #Dawgs are building in Ath… https://t.co/AFCn1pZyvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pull the trigger @aafexpress.  The answer to our problems just became a free agent @JManziel2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this were to actually become law this is step 1.  Step 2 is gun registration so they can enforce the law.  Makin… https://t.co/QMpFE52zBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[overcast clouds -&gt; broken clouds temperature up 20°F -&gt; 23°F humidity down 62% -&gt; 58% wind 9mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guttipistilli @juniorportillo2 Me vas a decir que lo de pachi era para Segunda tarjeta?  Ni le tocó.  Además de es… https://t.co/IQBGMFANNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoDucks @OregonWBB I believe the holy spirit is with this team. God is using you to do amazing things always keep him first in your lives]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pro tip from @PressSec: if you can’t or won’t answer a question, just say something about ripping babies from wombs… https://t.co/6IshJuhGX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #KnightTime! #Vegas plays with energy and urgency and sends the #Preds back to Nashville with their tails betw… https://t.co/cEPYKSlLka]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the massage parlor down the street from the strip club they give happy endings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Astros_Jenn @breakingtco That’s why I @ them so they could offer you the first subscription and best deal.  Hint hint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow marks my first day as a pescatarian. My last meat meal will be pizza and wings! #pescatarian #SundayThoughts #timeforchange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mommy loves you. @OneMinuteBriefs @dalger2001 #CUSTARD https://t.co/GT4WNLrx4e  #creative #advertising RT https://t.co/ObORBO6Rua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitweeting Self-absorbed A-holes.....and, the sad truth is, they don't realize that they are this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These “What if Obama had ... “ thought games don’t work. First, we don’t believe Obama world ever behave as selfish… https://t.co/uNgirr2JZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorBaldwin Quick one for ya.  What caused 5 billion years worth of climate change before there were humans and… https://t.co/JMiIgWALXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afternoon snack with Dr. Springer #madisonsocial #tallahassee #florida #fsu @ Madison Social https://t.co/uGRJPHwPyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey i'm running late today because i'm terrible at waking up on time for work.-me giving the real reason why i'm late to my boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[A father is a man who expects his son to be as good a man as he meant to be. Frank A. Clark I push him to be better… https://t.co/Ts5htUeNl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runcandice Two nearly perfect gifs. I couldn't decide on just one. https://t.co/B2aZGrHBmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConsumerReports But actually I wouldn't count on it,unless the Administration makes changes,tell your company you… https://t.co/FBV3jXfOfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Breanna_clark01 Strongly Urge you to take a look at a True Self-Helper I wrote.  This is All We Can Do For Ourselves... No Doubts...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IForgive_ILove Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy… https://t.co/DboBlU3YQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your name in my phone is something other than your actual name, you have made an impact on my life and I thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2014FloridaTOY I don’t blame teachers who sell their lessons online ... or is the epitome of capitalism ... if som… https://t.co/7byzkwzJuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy comienza una nueva etapa en mi vida y ministerio con el inicio de lo que será revivalchurchpr esta noche tendre… https://t.co/5orJJSSPeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of our early deadlines Chad only had time to do a short. A longer story and video of the game winning shot… https://t.co/Wveqs9VPBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most influential men in my life is about to have the first surgery in his 73 year long life to try to re… https://t.co/NMnDfKaGx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s one expungement, Michael. What could it cost? $500?” @GovMattBevin thinks $500 isn’t too much for an expungem… https://t.co/gkZ88ICv7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[My column today on Matt Carpenter (anti-shift), Mike Shildt (pro-shift) and some commentary. To quote… https://t.co/esxHH6WQIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews The film is NOT "up for 10 nominations. Who writes this stuff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beercatphd I was involved in a submission to @BMJ_Open. They seem to be very receptive to publishing protocols for clinical trials.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it now 4 straight 200-games during my weekly All-day long practice Bowling session at Main Event today with a… https://t.co/W2wa20GYLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muluneh237 @royaleleamour @immunetovibes @xPukkie_ @donbarry_ @chih_somh @KweenPhotos @Blackdotmandy @4eeevverrrrnaan And me? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier today.  Lori and myself having a goodbye lunch.  Lori is moving away from the Puget Sound area soon but sti… https://t.co/ZaU8R6iqoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barmore27 @JulieReichwein1 AMEN..THANK YOU PATRIOTS.  TEXAS. THIS WRIGHT HERE GIVES ME HOPE.. I LOVE SEEING OUR SI… https://t.co/aSZBAq0Hse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind Allie Ball's 256 and Payton Watson's 216, the girls rolled a 1,035 in game three and now sit in second place… https://t.co/C5R5GqoHex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles PLZ sign with Jacksonville, my future somewhat second home. I'll go to your 1st game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of the nearly 141,000 students who compete in Speech and Debate nationally, less than 1% are recognized each year a… https://t.co/42Km5cRyPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh well if it isn’t the annual Sean Payton “I love this QB!” just to make everyone think he’s going to try to draf… https://t.co/aPbBSojPHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new spot a new venture hiking at Temescal Canyon Park. The view reminded me of my hike in Cape Town . #hike… https://t.co/0IolY065Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kobe should of stayed with adidas for their better quality footwear but that’s none of my biz https://t.co/rorb3LBw7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael_Nania I think they can start talking on the 11th then sign the 13th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Solange_Sonnier @RonniLaurie @LAintheOC @40calsolution @livin_2point0 @62WalterP @keanothedog @gheetar @heartofmel… https://t.co/Yqd165OuTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna start to look for a valentine now so maybe I can have one by February]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralWasp @MrAndersonJared @rivercitycards @LouisvilleBSB @TheGilpatrick Thanks again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cernovich As a born again Christian and 62 year old architect with a masters degree and my own very successful bus… https://t.co/LfxHjT1nxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something I didn’t know was medically possible 24 hours ago is now by biggest fear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MADestlife @tolle55319974 @LPCO @BernieSanders Yeah, he’s kinda got ya by the balls here, Max. Uh, rhetorically speaking of course!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This documentary about Alabama HS wrestlers looks awesome https://t.co/UP3SkMulJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter what you’ve done or how bad you think you’ve messed up, God loves you. Go find him today, in natu… https://t.co/M8GkJyAK1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine's day???????? @ Utica Hotel Procore Core Service Group https://t.co/q4JEk3bxXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌ I hope it was all that you wanted it to be. Good night. Until tomorrow. Peace out everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunesCartagena @NSanabria7 @presidencia_sv @nayibbukele @LaPagina @fulloa51 @NuevasIdeasSV @GANAOFICIAL @elblog… https://t.co/3oq2SLzzy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yR3uqzjaFf Our certified professionals offer ATT customer service 1-855-436-9666 #attcustomerservice… https://t.co/VSjfRwXi5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great sessions on #technology in politics happening all day in this lovely room full of Texas Democrats. Thanks to… https://t.co/5LHork1U1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain't nothing gay about pegging. If you're girl wants to stick a dildo in you, go for it my boys 👿 BE PROUD OF THAT… https://t.co/fwfpkUZvdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Protip: To help adjust your body to any change in sleep schedule, eat as soon as possible upon waking. Metabolism i… https://t.co/liu72nINuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[in my CIRCLE meeting as one of my colleagues presents on leukemia and says “we see this in women who drink high lev… https://t.co/koIyzSKK3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omfg you guys I'm panicking theres rlly almost one month left in the quarter and I need to get my shit together...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my #ValentinesDay Greetings from Team Snapchat 👻 Thanks @Snapchat 💛 https://t.co/4YH7HzCdII]]></document><document><![CDATA[At some point you have to trade value for best available arm on the board and employ quantity approach because it i… https://t.co/A6TY3JwQyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KantsImperative Wait David vs Goliath is about David cheating? I had no idea that perception was out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just waiting to see if these simple minded fucks will have the mental capacity to understand the MCU’s most pow… https://t.co/GPgCcUJ8mm]]></document><document><![CDATA[3D printing, laser printing, inkjet printing be damned. I say let’s go back to old fashion woodblock printing.… https://t.co/Y5avwZTSqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleriveraa Conocí muy bien a la Hna Panchita amiga de mi Doña Mercedes de Gamez mi madre la acompañaba al cereso aquí en Hermosillo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonRFloyd Hey There Delilah(Plain White T’s) and I might need Security(Chance).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine @TheLeeGreenwood Oh I get it, you can’t be objective he lets the help hangout .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carmens_feeder I know, I don't know what happened. I guess Twitter slowly became obsolete to Facebook, Snapchat et… https://t.co/O8tHBxXYZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he started arguing that the resurrection will restore everyone to their earthly “eternal genitals” so transiti… https://t.co/s319TV5oyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @ACJJustice Sounds like what happened in FL with the Trump U investigation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PCnowisthetime @Allenwrestling @uiltexas Congratulations 🎈🎉🎊 @AllenEaglesTDC   10 consecutive Texas State Championships!  #awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Afternoon walk just now at the beach just beside LAX.. #tuesday #beach #dockweilerbeach #losangeles #lax #cali… https://t.co/u0D5yzzihV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's amazing how little of the sky we can see with our naked eye. And this is still only a fraction of what is actu… https://t.co/Zd75wg6nos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching THERE WILL BE BLOOD and remembering the guy who got this Daniel Plainview tattoo. https://t.co/FiqNWNisr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @camilitocamilon talk about the history of the Nueva Canción movement in this new @pandoramusic Stories epis… https://t.co/2RKTCIfC9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRStoetzer @kp3a @w4acutie Practice makes perfect! You are right though. It requires constant tuning to keep up with yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Mitch McConnell is just saying he has no underlying principles,  he is just a party line hack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I’m doubling down 😱 Sprout Fig Dubbel 7.6% @brewerybhavana Caramelized Chocolate Churro Baltic Porter 7.0%… https://t.co/hzpyb31QXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I can’t believe @iamcardib broke the Houston rodeo record of people 😍👏🏼 #cardib https://t.co/G3eAoWOnyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Natural #selection please. #dumbanddumber #dumbass #dumbingdownamerica #stupidity #stupidpeoplesuck #firehot🔥 @ Al… https://t.co/BefSlljFFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onemoresir @meetthebreeder I want to know mom’s reaction when she does the laundry, to be honest.  There can’t be… https://t.co/RbhHwHCK1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBAKSMAK @OpTicHitch MW2 was about as advanced and complex as I would want and it was perfect. Besides MW remaster… https://t.co/Pxru0AJ80v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras is the only time ppl from New Orleans can act as their true self dirty bums 😁🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the only reason I have an Instagram still is solely to see what Skip Bayless posts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking someone “are you a man or are you a MAGA?” is the only example of toxic masculinity that I wish we could keep around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday February 19 - 3 O'clock Stir:     Mud-smearing Jefferson County deputy was taking 'security countermeasures… https://t.co/X6rUDq4tTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cizzorz  your deathrun is making my blood pressure go through the roof]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @jack @twitter could you please add an edit button?  #AskingForAFriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Oatmeal Milkshake Stout by @Rochmillsbeerco @ Charter Township of Chesterfield — https://t.co/Ir92B0FG4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacramento Locals Feb Week 3 Divine Shine #3 Results 1. Spark  2. GalenTheWise 3. The Trashman 4. Mooninite 5th. Ja… https://t.co/SPZeiXWmSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#creativejuicesflowing A great morning with Matt Guastaferro @Hugocreative and Rico Labbe | Exciting times ahead fo… https://t.co/OHdvj89iO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cphillips_17 @panerabread Well you see, when they sell all the bread they made, that’s how they run out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaryMoyer @BlazersBoone @Logan_DB @WyoFootball @maxhurleman @Berkselite @RobFlowers5 @stevenoneil77 @KickItJZ… https://t.co/nzuupACDaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are the @Senators either a new owner or @MelnykEugene Considering throwing an offer sheet of $12mill AAV for… https://t.co/IW2w2UPKAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanhollister7 A little history: queer BYU students have been at the forefront of honor code changes twice in the… https://t.co/bmMCC9vLCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEChrisMack As I just said, he screwed up. He’s acknowledged it and trying to work out of it. These deals haven’t… https://t.co/RrsibLkxUR]]></document></documents></author>