<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[why is she more ready for this picture than i am @ New Jersey https://t.co/VDypTzWPMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve almost quit my job like 8 times tonight. I usually have a ton of patience but one of my patients has gotten on… https://t.co/jZgTvTELZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No 🥶 #75onFriday @ Orangetheory Fitness Four Points https://t.co/Py1YtLbA42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You do realize calling people names and using extreme language is not going to win you more backer… https://t.co/wcFfxGmZOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crying your eyes out on video chat with your best friend over a guy real that's true friendship right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boss gave me and my mans tickets to see the GSW and that shit was lit 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[First job in operations for startup - miserable. #MattEversmann @hellowestmich]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got told I’m losing my titties with this weightloss 😂 and i am. We were looking at my loose ass cups and I s… https://t.co/2N3V35iW12]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY MONDAY, EVERYONE! It's an hour earlier for us in the US, so it's going to be a rough start. I feel a little o… https://t.co/1dK5TzFUEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[These all were amazing but fetch with ruff ruffman has a special place in my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vita_Labels have you heard of Dritz Sewing! John Dritz and sons? The San Aruther was my Great Uncle. He also designed many board games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauren_orefice Congratulations!! I’m working on submitting me and Emily’s paper now haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engaged. Enlightened. In love with books! #guidedreading #daily5 #3rdchat #litchat #DES https://t.co/JkZJ1aJIBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A perfect sky as a backdrop at the wedding of @ananavarro and Al Cardenas. Que viva el amor 💗 @ Indian Creek Countr… https://t.co/5fmhZdBsia]]></document><document><![CDATA[This episode on President's Day was so powerful. I'm with you. Let's keep the hope alive for change ♥️… https://t.co/Zf33VJpKsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@utsdoc @kevinwatson @thekrak3n @SpiritTruthLife @HolySpiritPod https://t.co/o182oyvxhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outfit Of The Day! 🌸🥂☀️Rosé And Shine☀️🥂🌸  https://t.co/weOo5w7kII  ✨February 23, 2019✨ https://t.co/jD9fH6uIbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keatingthomas thinks I’m funny so I’m out guys, bye. Life goals accomplished. #winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got 2 sold out TMZ tours this morning 👏🏼 I’m looking for the #RHOBH cast today, season 9 just premiered this week..… https://t.co/zWGdnn91Es]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emrazz I will never forget when a boy said to me “what did the five fingers say to the face?” And slapped me hard.… https://t.co/lmXx0x1CK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time has come for me to watch the first season of Real Housewives of Potomac and 20 minutes in I’m asking why did I wait so long!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you are giving free tickets to people in Chicago today, but you have dedicated fans in Northwest Indiana tha… https://t.co/mqhqAJyxZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing surprises me anymore but....this means she is calling the 2 brothers who CONFESSED, liars.  Yet, THEY had a… https://t.co/zKYDxU8NRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bachelorette 👰🏻🇲🇽👰🏻🇲🇽#MichisLastRideBeforeShesABride @ Ensenada, Baja, Mexico https://t.co/UbDq4BDibr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonRobertC @NateComf5 Nope. It was just he consensus and then of course looked good and fancy so got my attentio… https://t.co/a2S0HiTxzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDGrossman One of the nurses called me “honey” and then drove me home when I had an abortion at 19. #abortionishealthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarDamnDarcie Actually, come to think of it, was Ole Miss running flex?? BC IT WORKED LIKE A CHARM AT SECOND #29 EVERY TIME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boyanb1 @ArmondRizzoXXX @adamrussoxxx Love how you make Porn look classy, Mi Mr. BEAUTIFUL! 🤗❤️🍑💦🍆👍🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanBryanLopez This is the third tweet I’ve seen about dreams today. Did everyone have some weird ass dream last night? 😂🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[He broke the law. I say he be stripped of all committees he sits on, along with resigning and charged.   Congress s… https://t.co/rGHuuuom3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plantain &amp; egg as appetizer.... and my crush in a sexy lingerie as meal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have them Liv mg on top of me in the home that I brought at 622 Fern St., in Yeadon PA 19050 trying to take my bo… https://t.co/sxwW6yeJ1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 #bigdogsunday JD and Goldie taking a break from their walk!!! https://t.co/NLQbRTe9qE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @kelmshae to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challenge so… https://t.co/A8tKlWnClQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Manny Machado will bomb as a Yankee, you heard it here first.”   - my coworker, who is a diehard Yankees fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when you wake up and realize your phone was never charging 🤦🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDudeInSF @keithboykin It’s almost like they don’t want illegal aliens to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wah really a Gwaan yahso ..  🤣🤣🤦🏽‍♂️ a who let her out @ Bramalea, Ontario https://t.co/pXeOkGl8ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow okay paddleton on netflix is absolutely depressing i want a refund on my existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn another Sudanese aunty got her pu$$y exposed on fb??? I’m sick 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we plan our inclusion training it is essential to include the A4 inclusion, assessment and  UDL documents… https://t.co/Mc9vI8fE0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielgilman I wonder the economic status of the affected. Also convinced the customer will pay for this overtime,… https://t.co/65zz1KADtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_seeairuhhh @leahstheword Same shit to me too back in 2016 I think. I thought it was way sketch and declined. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lt_gray @SheriffChody @PascoSheriff  A little Tuesday humor.....They had to taser her again https://t.co/FgwwhBGoXk via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 5:03 in the morning and can't sleep soo... #ColdInLa @SeaveyDaniel @JonahMarais @corbynbesson @jackaverymusic… https://t.co/2nxNzCcrMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJDexMKE @PrinceOfTheMiL @RayZamora17 @dj_Soppa @cassylutts_ @t_michael08 @BrandonV87 @trinabaranowski @allidmke Y… https://t.co/2WjKiM6HWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be proudly speaking on this incredibly huge gap at many key market events this week with @monaghiami in #GTA… https://t.co/syo0247XuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SafeHaven is just that, trust that your baby will be placed in a loving home, with a family who will take great ca… https://t.co/c4L5Glnuk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of bbq from some parking lot somewhere in Central Florida where I discovered I’m not a fan of collard gr… https://t.co/wliIdCfUXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I guess you will be live hate tweeting @60Minutes you are so predictable 🖕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melissa McCarthy heat | The Heat Release Date June 28, 2013 - The Heat Trailer https://t.co/013Lb2oqJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burd71 The silver lining to my divorce, if there is one, is that my kids realize the importance of working and get… https://t.co/ySL8vCj8pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1023WBAB Rockin' to WBAB on the Rock (Shelter island) https://t.co/FmwWh87Ywr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthernWaid @kimbalina3 @NissaMai Thank you so much. I appreciate it. I will miss you. Much love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryMartinV @keanothedog @IsraelM59713490 @clairermassey @ThaddeusArjuna @ommatid @62WalterP @a_patriciann… https://t.co/OeC0Njuwb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikoCrystalBall @red2007 @OneDayAtATime @ODAATwriters @JustinaMachado @toddgrinnell Gloria Calderon the shows creator liked my tweet 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matejka5thgrade class wrote notes to their teacher to tell them the things they love about her today on Valentine’… https://t.co/bKqvBqIOHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CooperLeeB You are a joy! These complex questions were the kind that elevate any answer. Thank you. Great writer. Good man. Love you. X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, S 70th Street northbound is still a problem today. Two cars just north of Van Dorn are stuck because they cou… https://t.co/qWMb9JX0mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. No wonder this country is going down the drain. You’re discussing coffee when the world is crumbling? You have… https://t.co/F7wiaxRGla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarlettgavinue Omgggggg. I forgot about ftsk 💀💀💀 are they still a band wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday funday with my Dad! #thankful #blessed #❤️mydaddy @ Coalgate, Oklahoma https://t.co/O5jFPwXn8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how the conversation around #womenintech has changed in only 3 years. So many more people in the room, so m… https://t.co/e4sd2qfm5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccheshirecatt my favorite line from white people: “well i don’t think ANYONE should say it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCU_Baseball Go Jared!!! 41 has just begun!!!Frogs are better with you in the pond!!! ⚾️🐸💜Love our Frogs!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redtowel4 @mrsdave2 They tore his jacket off too! Hope he learns a lesson. Repent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eutierrialife @kayleighmcenany Obviously Trump got lucky and found a good attorney who did what he wanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy decidí quedarme en cama a descansar y parece que a Edu le agradó la idea. Ha estado muy tranquilo todo el día 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took the book #valeriescateyescream to the exhibit at the #brandlibrary I love that this is so close to our house.… https://t.co/rkfovENVfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto Perhaps it would have taken less than 800 pages to list the people he did not lie to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your classic mink lashes are going 4 weeks strong thanks to i_fabulash  Yasssss🔥🔥🔥🔥… https://t.co/kfnlMvKMpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioStatePA I’m here! These bad boys are heavy! #NFMS2019 #NFMS19 https://t.co/tZuLRSYIjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can read this, you’ve helped me reach 10 followers. Thank you.. POTUS  supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawyerLadyNYC And still not one newspaper in the entire country has called for Trump's resignation. Why is that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol cats.exactly what my cat thinks daily when i come home haha #mirth #tee-hee #grin #clever https://t.co/1HqNRibwPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast - I also find it unbelievable that Smollett just happened to encounter-in a blizzard, at 20 below zero, at… https://t.co/cXXxljtpmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyn_taylor @erinstrout Ditto with colt headed to mammoth. His stroller set of the swab thingy alarm. Closed doo… https://t.co/WBYS9W7KOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[These children are at risk of being forgotten casualties of the war.  https://t.co/QIvdHwNtyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most people of African descent from actual socialist countries will tell you otherwise. That’s why they’re here. So… https://t.co/lIxNQBI5Xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth @chuckwoolery Oh Lord- Al Franken, Al Sharpton, Jesse Jackson- the racist ranters just keep on keep… https://t.co/k4m7bqzJNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏦"FBI, Cleveland police search for suspect in PNC Bank robbery https://t.co/rPiacTtVx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heathereirene @ALT_uscis @MigrantFreedom Is there someplace to download the data?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with my amazing son ❤️ @ Panini Kabob Grill https://t.co/3PVD6C9jsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydneywiseman28 happy birthday syd! hope you had an amazing day :) can’t wait for saturday🤪❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulionHairris if nothing else, at least you’re a good example of men how men can’t take hints 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else got issues with the 'Sweet but Psycho' lyrics? Makes me mad every time I hear this damn song.]]></document><document><![CDATA['Scared. Ashamed. Crippled.': How One #Lawyer Overcame Living With Depression in Big Law https://t.co/InRgor5KTc vi… https://t.co/AdgFgMzOm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin is trying to go Paragliding in Switzerland. I can’t even watch the video without sweating! @JessChristensen]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the girl that was screaming across the street to her friend about not getting invited to “Maddie’s” birthday par… https://t.co/pih2PtMmLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels like forever since I last slept in. I just woke up and already planning another nap lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kacavide @DMoone78 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Sit back relax ENJOY life. And watch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniaaabee ahem. sorry. the last thing i remember was laughing then i was DONE. 😩😩😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathymelkins Thanks Kat, just when things seem to calm down. Blip...knocks ya hard enough to hit the floor.  😘😘😘 I sure miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raising our eyes to Christ, who was born and died and rose again for his people, let us cry out: Save those you hav… https://t.co/xGl5AZsgvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Gutiérrez NeuroCoach-Terapeuta-Conferencista Internacional. Teléf. +1 337-570-0617. Hasta Donde Puedas Ver S… https://t.co/iG8rDzPlvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikeanewton Sounds like a fine day. It’s called “adulting.” I’m proud!]]></document><document><![CDATA[America  wants me to b a president biohazard off limits orange pad bags 🌈🍫😷😴🕷️🤞🎂😒🛍️🎹☃️✝️🤞🌈🏰📱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLJeffLewis @TheDr_Donna @RadioAndySXM .... OOPS I was listening and forgot to tell you HEY, girl, Hey💖🙏🏻‼️ 💜💜💜Lis… https://t.co/Va60ddw5ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did the most fraudulent, sleazy, lying, criminal I know convince an entire party that he’s the guy to Drain The Swamp? #Maddow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@island_cynic @theBreakerNews More accurately, an opportunist supporting opportunists. #cdnpoli #bcpoli]]></document></documents></author>