<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@paigie_wagie @Jamoney8874 I mean. You going after leake county now? Keep searching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auhoopspodcast Maybe if more players had been in the rotation? Starters wouldn't have been exhausted in the closin… https://t.co/kObaqadgch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyBrickley This day 2011 in Fort Myers. Your baseball brother spent an hour talking to my boy @calberman35 and h… https://t.co/4Y0ph8u4P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only family planning going on at Planned Parenthood is killing babies. Get it right. It isn't health care, woma… https://t.co/UxasueEHIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunny West Palm Beach Trip 1 - Part 1 #sunnydays #streetfair #culturalcenter #lovetoexplore @ West Palm Beach, Flor… https://t.co/NheC55Pxgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mideberry My dad was born (to American parents, my grandfather was a petroleum engineer for Gulf) and grew up ther… https://t.co/xcGwliTR2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @calebpressleyxo @_rone what a back door cover by Miami Ohio! #StormChasers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t tell if it’s because I’m lazy or old but I can’t stand having to go downstairs to pee https://t.co/UOzIjhqyoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody sitting courtside touching players at a basketball game should be removed immediately  Westbrook handled it like a champ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that @RealJeffCobb guy is a pretty cool dude P.S. Tino = @AstroKrunk https://t.co/TPZeKKHJVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for having us. For some reason we seem perfectly comfortable with microphones in front of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great performance last night. Can't wait to hear whats next !!@maelynmusic #TheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hale_razor It’s only the second national emergency to include military force.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crawf33 @tweetlauf i already had my jeep paid off before i moved otherwise i would’ve absolutely ditched it bc i r… https://t.co/DzIzoPNNkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vincent59370244 @robertbbrown007 @BernieSanders How stupid.  Are you that dumb?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grow the fuck up...fuck outta here witchur “we’ll talk soon” then blocking me three weeks later all while acting li… https://t.co/Uc4ua5e1j5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets are already running pretty low. I’m almost out of $50 tickets. Hit me up ASAP so I can put them aside for y… https://t.co/3j50oeyNtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows are you going to ask any questions about Trump? it is documented that Trump has lied over 7,000 plus times???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnesky88 @realGolfchat Yes, The Masters. In my mind, the first day of spring! #GolfChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rodrigo1993 Do mayors get police details? Maybe in big cities like NY or Chicago but small towns? I don’t know. I… https://t.co/E28lSnAX1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA Belmont Street &amp; Woodleigh Road inbound. Scheduled for 10:03. Arrived 10:13. Driver driving aggressively to catch up for time lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliarceo @Tribuna_I @tdn_twit Ni tanto ya que FIFA quiere aumentar el número de participantes después de Qatar,… https://t.co/yPrupNekCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieHearn @PhilCrawley87 @StephenEspinoza @ono5985 @ededward16 @mpeticca @MikeCoppinger @Tyson_Fury @loudibella N… https://t.co/ew3V69WGyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_Welter Holy crap 1131 days ago I had a different opinion on Xavier I’m fired...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Trump is a liar and a traitor, and if he could he'd change the name from America to Trumpistan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have finally ascended to the top. @LILBTHEBASEDGOD retweeted me about a Roblox tweet. I'll try to remember all of… https://t.co/Cd5mRl6EED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PHWillington @dave_doomy I'm not going to do that because a) it's a teaser trailer,  b) still in post production,… https://t.co/8kgb9zF06H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Dirk has been unstoppable the last 16 games or so, I’m very nervous about that matchup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com Shouldn’t she be in jail. If anybody else did what she has done they would be under the jail but she still is free . Why ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady handing out samples at @Costco: what is new word for “cool”?  Me: Lit 🔥  Her: Alright. These samples are lit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCharlotteWWE  You are Smoking Hot in this power jumper !! https://t.co/cMdapwkfBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichieYemie @JamieSchmidt14 @THRmovies #HigherFurtherFaster https://t.co/4JfXIpRbuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a feeling this was the way they were gonna go, neither woman had to get pinned or made to tap. #WWEFastlane #WWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it interesting that AOC has an answer (excuse) for eating meat, riding in a gas guzzler etc.  Welcome to the… https://t.co/nDUbMpQRuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really looking forward to the 2022 think pieces about Joe Rogan, Clay Travis, Dave Rubin and Bari Weiss who are… https://t.co/K1hYRqRwPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricof85 Fantastic!! I’m so torn because they both seem beautiful but the fact that Cartagena is on the coast 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CassadeePope You did an Amazing Job Cassadee!!! Way to go!!! #nascar #nascaronfox #LasVegasMotorSpeedway… https://t.co/HXNRjLgjK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris: “I woke up with my hair stuck to my pillow from so much hairspray]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is going to give you what you put into it.  Put your whole heart in everything you do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I and most Americans are not accepting  this  as normal !  But the only ones who can do something about it are the… https://t.co/Mg8iPG6Bp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighMems @DEN4life88_58 Sometimes they’re the cuts two years later]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling anymore.  #music #life #road #trip #forever #love en Bay Ridge, Maryland https://t.co/vAdHPew4Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HogsHaven I’d say we give a 2nd and a contingency 4th next year if he starts 10 games in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QBsMVP With Murray rumored to go to Arizona, that will be two athletic QB’s in our division(Russell Wilson). Does… https://t.co/wu1kcx0BHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephDiazJr Trying to get a good payday!! @leosantacruz2 will eat you bro! #1273punches #boom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @erichards24 #She wins the Primary she gets my vote . Trump will never get it ! USMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[whatever drake says, goes. ☺️👶🏼 #drizzysays @ Grantham, North Carolina https://t.co/04jb9nASvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnPrineMusic @Spotify @davecobb7 @thesecretsister @JasonIsbell @KaceyMusgraves @Bonnaroo Please bless us with Clay Pigeons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry Bonds was the greatest hitter of all time and should have been a first ballot HOFer and people who say otherw… https://t.co/SVaKgFCOFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerbusJames @hugh_bothwell @alastairjallen1 @doctorbuttons @NotATro04866731 @Watsdecraicjmac @def732dan… https://t.co/wwVY8QhGsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[black mirror #kreativly #dark #light interior @ Zablozki's https://t.co/tlPIilLW6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tessa_25 @MTURIZOMUSIC @MauYRicky @fuegomusicfest @AbrahamMateo yo trataré 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenhorRaposa @decunningham2 It's one election--definitive claims like this are extremely dangerous in political prognosticating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @VP Your An  Treasonous Idiot, The late John McCain is rolling in his grave. Your Just A Crazy Cra… https://t.co/buoLKbBHdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shittttttt 😯"Mass panic at Hamilton show after shooting scare in San Francisco"  https://t.co/KAfM96G3jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a girl with:   Bad tattoos and piercings Child she had @ 16 named Kaiden Died hair (dark) Works out and is a… https://t.co/PIzpeCBcEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randomly watched 3 @BarbaraHershey8 movies this month and they were so great that I am going to spend the rest of M… https://t.co/Svyihr4wSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karinsoil @madisonlilly @NightwatchRutl1 @onebigheart1958 @JoyOverturf @Vegasclimber @nightwatchniki Now I'm mad .… https://t.co/SL7DBYacIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[-Traded D’Angelo (now an all star) -Traded Nance (great fundamental player) + Clarkson=zero return (isiah)  -Moved… https://t.co/Y3J3TALty8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the YouTube community could raise money for a two hour debate once a week with guys like dom 2k rb the break… https://t.co/oXCI6p8kph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a pleasure to be with friends at Georgetown COG and hear Pastor Steve bring a great on the olive tree… https://t.co/3zvRTrGAQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowdeshellBen Ahh the good ol’ days when I could toss some babies around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Be nice if our President would be our President and not worry about what somebody said at the Oscars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EEUU Elliott Abrams, negó que las sanciones de su país a Venezuela hayan causado el apagón en Venezuela. Las causas… https://t.co/Lg22reUsZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_J_Fishing @cauzin_trouble @8pointCityHick @EasyKasting @66horseshoe4u @DennisBigelow6 @_Darcizzle_ @Bassin_Away… https://t.co/Cz9RdNoYjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, I found this stash where you can easily redeem $20 ! Ending soon, act fast! https://t.co/pvdlSjXWKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandroJPC @YesiSLP @GiuseppeNoc @realDonaldTrump @jguaido @ricardopuentesm @Soniatalero_ @_Gabbyta_ @jmlara02… https://t.co/51kRaSKL3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you put yourself in that situation you kinda deserve to be kidnapped 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNTLA No se puede tener todo. A Yalitza por el simple hecho de estar entre las nominadas y formar parte de la mejo… https://t.co/fSlf1D34KY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Stephen didn’t he want to do this look at the fit he was getting ready for a night out damn you lakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I added a sensor to the door that sends a notification to all of us whenever someone knocks.  Phase two involves la… https://t.co/0TFZ5DSGBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BigCountryPreps has arrived at the AlamoDome for today's Class 1A boys state title game between Jayton and Slidell… https://t.co/dZZEXIUbL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisDouglas515 @Murph_Andy Fran will be in Des Moines watching Patrick bring home a State Championship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller You are Russell Westbrook smells fart face #WhoAmIGame #MallerMilitia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redskinstoday_ Pete King is a blow hard. Just likes hearing himself talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Bukowski You have a good point, but we saw Burks play. He didn't change life the way LVE, Smith or the Devin… https://t.co/nbiNNNFKYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCoveBaseball @CovNewsSports @R_Spikes13 @Vol_Baseball @ChrisBurney15 @jahughes21 @Alcovy_Sports… https://t.co/tryeyGBTqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilteachu @washingtonpost I meant to reply to person's comment above you. I apologize]]></document><document><![CDATA[None these last two years have shown what it looks like when grownups through a fit. They are vindictive and will n… https://t.co/fzCGgOsOJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The anti corruption community has lost a great leader-Michael Pedersen-May he Rest In Peace and May his legacy carry on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short term sacrifices for long term gratification. Fuck what anybody has to say there’s no right or wrong when chas… https://t.co/JxnwFIjzHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdracing got my shirt for #DAYTONA500 tomorrow. Look for me in April @BMSupdates for the #FoodCity500al Go 95!!! https://t.co/nc3jpqdmAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Hillary Clinton puts to rest lingering speculation about a White House bid but says she’ll keep sp… https://t.co/UgFN81V2TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeylyz @CMEGroup Also you're private so I don't think they could see that if they wanted to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find our schedule and menu on @goodfynd! 📅 Mon, Feb 25 🕚 11a - 2p 📍 Patriot plaza 🍽 https://t.co/tupvUSbn0c… https://t.co/IlpIlQNFS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dmartini24 @demonrock @derek_mafs @robbysoave Most European countries have choice. Including Sweden and they also… https://t.co/OzXSFU9IWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niagara Falls GOP chair rules out Democrat Restaino for mayoral endorsement Good!! https://t.co/PrhiKHNxXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact 2 of the 3 player shown are Duke players should be as a reminder no Duke fan should use Zion not playing a… https://t.co/o8UjTxQvBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shadow is home from her vet visit whet she got got her girl bits snipped. She seems to have forgiven us.… https://t.co/KSteCmQQ5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelixLoperena Y el 747 se sigue construyendo, según yo. Boeing se la metió doblada a Airbus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylF19665664 @Jim_Jordan Says the person thinking Trump’s decision to not collect his $400K annual salary means… https://t.co/L5BjreBGzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces tienes que jugártela, hay que dar el salto aunque pierdas... en Monclova, Mexico https://t.co/24eBtzCNXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny that Sullivan starts the period talking to the officials (probably telling them that no call on simmonds… https://t.co/JwMrkIKexr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightningDuck @marklevinshow But I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA HISTORY 3/5/1770 Boston ma… https://t.co/IS1FjCwXWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jholtham @parabasis Nah it’s chill I just know to mute “Federer” a couple times a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love wines from Tariha!  @ChalyBalanza  first introduced me to these wines back in 2006 during a day long BBQ -… https://t.co/6Dgha3mZQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work buddy is all set up in his new @buybigjoe bean bag! #brokenarm #presidentsday #noschool @ Fayetteville Wood… https://t.co/HeMKGEA7ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimChandler1075 guess I don’t have to have a cold squishy butt on Broadways tonight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: National Director Business Development - https://t.co/1tKTt6q3jG #Simon #BusinessMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must. Watch Commercials! @ Independence, Missouri https://t.co/loj17BQOYn]]></document></documents></author>