<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is like the time my bf asked me to go see Cold Pursuit lmaoaoao 😑💕 https://t.co/WHqhBE0lD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[at #NYC🗽 during #NYFW 📷 taken by @8and2  #YuFujiwara —————————————————————————— #FashionWeek #documentary… https://t.co/fGhlwa0ILl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gellybenz hahaha ito yung ata napala ko sa pag-aaral ko nung college 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son produced and voiced this video at Bloomberg🤔I have wanted to know more about this phone company so thanks He… https://t.co/mFl8crgUSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of celebrating V-day I’m at school getting an education 😭perks of the adult life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskReidMath @MsAshleyDubois @MsMathnik @SueM_MHS @sueabes1 @MHSBromley @mikemcraith @sylviafagin @TomSaboVT… https://t.co/exz1x6q8Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Pence is the most disgusting Trump sycophant.  It's disgusting to see him spew all the nonsense about how Trum… https://t.co/3eGsr5o9PG]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing turnout! @cpedvcoalition #OrangeDay 🧡#Orange4Love #PreventionAcrossCA #PreventionWorks https://t.co/p3YhLU4Yxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vakeraj @DanDarkPill @DanielKrawisz @_Kevin_Pham You have to include all costs, darling ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jptrib1 @AWorldOutOfMind You know how Trump yacks about how Putin called him "bright" (Trump later changed to "gen… https://t.co/XpiIG7oKer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m siting here waiting on @KylieJenner to unfollow @jordynwoods ... but Jordan already beat her to it!💀 THE SHADE https://t.co/ch7hgvDfUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[if we drunk together and I tell you .. “I can’t see” .. bitch..  just know that  I am DRUUUNK lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joneill55 @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @Cbp8Cindy @SLBriscoe @FionaMorgan79 @cowineco @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari… https://t.co/S6nlO7dUZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @Tvargon_rams hope your day is great! (Ps sorry for taking your girl)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCBachelorThe @chrisbharrison  My daddy just passed in the nursing home of congestive heart failure. His all time… https://t.co/fgLrj6ON1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow. I'm raising money for We need to go home. Click to Donate:  https://t.co/8PLdNcapfS via @gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to walk in the dark on a busy street IN THE STREET pls pls pls wear a safety vest. Almost took out… https://t.co/cAReiwdZJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not crazy , nigga you just bothered because I’m not stupid . My stupid days over with 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 Nick can’t whistle and Joe can’t walk.   Kevin’s hair! 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 #LateLateJonas #jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirecrackerKatt @mjs03093641 Too much stuff! 😄 https://t.co/EeK8DPPrvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @AinsleighMit23!! hope your day is the baddest!! Enjoy the nasty 19! love you!!! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of control birth control. Spin it all you want. It's murder. You know it and I know it. Speak out. #babymurders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amansnivis @RVAwonk And we’re damn good. We also get very tired of being told we look like we are in high school w… https://t.co/aHoakW5frn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emily_eckart I just read your haunting, beautiful piece @NatureFutures ! Wow! You are a wonderful writer! Congrats and best wishes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealdakotah &amp; there is literally nothing that we can do about it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @HillaryClinton @BillClinton The people on the right are afraid of her and will constantly bash her until the end of time. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scedmonds @lorimcneeartist @muz4now @paulatooths @JohnLusher @CarlRamallo @ShiCooks @socialbuzzlab @terrinakamura… https://t.co/Yat7j0lNzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you trust a puzzle company to make sure every puzzle piece is in the box to complete the puzzle than why can't y… https://t.co/XcmrP0XXxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catchin more flights not feelings ✌🏼 @ Greater Rochester International Airport (ROC) https://t.co/g5gP8ULopV]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy how people switch up on you. nobody has your back other than your own damn self.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my best friends, gladys_dm11 and her husband, joemangyan87, whom I call bro, invited me to attend one of the… https://t.co/vpY2HyxDb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Cumpleaños Paquita! 🎂🎉🎈🎊🥂💕 #2019 #february15th #allyouneedislapancha #sapoverdetuyu #birthdaygirl… https://t.co/pHPjpOEtw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what though I love the Isles. I love to play them now. I used to HAAATE them. Idk what happened!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvissyy Even if you’re not in a relationship, some people are just better off left in the past 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toby got mail yesterday!  It had toys for his cats in the box, too. 😻😻 What a lucky dog!!! His foster mama is a spe… https://t.co/Hm6Y94R6jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have so much more respect for @colton asking the dads for their blessing!  #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aplicacion de extensiones de 22" con microring.  No te arriesgues y ven con las profesionales   Salon TRY NOW  Te i… https://t.co/GHys9t2AuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooting on top of #ElCerroDeLaSilla #Mountain with 📸: @aldeezy04  Thank you @ktherealill for the #bts pics yall St… https://t.co/zMdNYpq5L5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces me pregunto como los aviones vuelan sin aletear. Obvio sé que hay una ciencia detrás de eso pero solo me pregunto🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto The day I hear you’ve given up scrapple I’ll know that something stranger than usual is afoot in this land]]></document><document><![CDATA[Garrett has a second chance but is still looking for his fur-ever home and family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethany_Petty Some of my fav #formativeassessment tools are  @Socrative @nearpod @Flipgrid @kahoot, just to name a few! #IlluminateED]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Ted talks as I lay on top of all of my clean laundry that I organized on my bed giving me the illusion of productivity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martica123 @TheRealCamilleG Awful. I met the wife of someone with similar experience at my Onc a few months ago. M… https://t.co/s6m8zkRxYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesFloyd I think you should focus on how you have five cats. Tbh that is an accomplishment and you should be proud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[終於到了今天唯一的一餐🍣🍱🍤🥗🍺晚餐 dinner time #japanesefood #sushi #yammy #delicious @ Oakland Gardens, Queens https://t.co/4bS5nveuf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its soooo frustrating when you don’t wanna leave but you don’t wanna stay either 😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinkedInExpert We did the best we could given the big T - but I want to meet you when I'm down next for sure. I was gutted to miss you]]></document><document><![CDATA[so the dogs i'm housesitting for wouldn't me sleep last night !!! and now i gotta work a 12.5 hour shift, i'm so RE… https://t.co/YA2HWWphoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I miss California humor!! Spotted by my sister in SoCal!!#humor #realtyexecutives #workingcoasttocoast https://t.co/nEGTxUTYse]]></document><document><![CDATA[mahirap din naman mag spill ng drama sa media, kasi kapag malungkot mga salita mo, iisipin agad ‘aY bReAK Na siGuRO… https://t.co/vUMC5W8tWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile I’m sorry but all you make me want to do in the text commercial is watch #Grease lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to @MeganEllyia today, who's running for President of the Board of Alderman in St. Louis 🌹❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Your Party is the DEMOCRATIC PARTY MOB THUGS of HATE n RACIST ! You Should Know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vakerohuevudo @mileniotv @VicenteFoxQue @EPN @FelipeCalderon Porque durante el juicio uno de los jueces comentó qu… https://t.co/V873IxSIeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appreciation for the the opportunity creates a significantly higher level of employee engagement. Which in turn cre… https://t.co/sQQy38my8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day the shop is open I will be showcasing an artisan. Every one is unique in their creativity and I am honore… https://t.co/maUDo2i87X]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's about the same. I believe, that there waiting for her to wake up.  He said, thanks for all the prayers. God's… https://t.co/Z0SHANy9gN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know who this woman was until now but this was the best! Loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoustonTexans @JJWatt He might not of been a Texan when he arrived....but we have adopted him.... He is now!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She never liked to be negative and always saw the good in every situation.... She wanted to become a doctor..." My… https://t.co/LnqRhVBRVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made some fun 5th grade field trip memories liberationescaperooms and cicis_pizza! They planned, they conquered, an… https://t.co/zWdPZRJZKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up on #RHNJ and there’s a lot going on but omg @JGSchneid’s mama at the salon is just so pure I can’t 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all don’t understand how far and amazing these throws actually are and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarapaoMs Hi Abby, your search ends here. Can we connect and discuss your app idea here - https://t.co/9FCwcjAIYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the things you do are a labor of love, my mom and I made my twin granddaughters champagne velvet dresses… https://t.co/KitZEwcZ6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a Pinot Noir lover, a must-do when travelling through Sonoma is the @waltwines Root 101 tasting! Enjoy pi… https://t.co/uKozj4ZXP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here watching Twilight and I’m being thoroughly reminded why I couldn’t STAND Bella.. 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFRICA ISRAEL INVESTMENTS https://t.co/P4x3xhyKvh Africa Israel Investments is an international holdings and invest… https://t.co/B90X54hiR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️ m o n d a y ☕️☕️☕️  #monday #mondaymood #mondaymotivation #mondaymorning #startoftheday #startoftheweek… https://t.co/ZiMCJ3q1OW]]></document><document><![CDATA[never let the illusion of something or someone’s intent distract you from the reality of something or someone’s intent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRowland9 @karen_erotoo1 What has happened to common decency.  #LETCHILDRENBECHILDREN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseanneTellez @fox32news @RaferWeigel Our loss. Their gain!  You've been my co-worker for all but a smidge of 23… https://t.co/7LDMId0SwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraCandler @mrsEViterbo this looks interesting  @MrsKimGr4 @MsDestephanis @MingHuang_OCT @MsScalia_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieOntheRadio I have a surburban. I even stand on the side to get the top clean. I refuse to be that idiot that… https://t.co/5fIRbn3mzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptJPrudhomme @alex_savoie @SgtMisner @DentonCountyDA Patrol car 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartOTXHeartMD I assisted in events because they occurred near me and I saw it or my husband elbowed me and said,… https://t.co/s8k80VQsMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp It IS sad. What’s saddest to me is that it hit all the right buttons for media confirmation bias and you fo… https://t.co/AtkY0fCHUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katg03 As long as you don’t fall into pyramid scheme then I think you’re good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko @AkerKathi Delay of gratification is an excellent skill to posess. I feel sorry for this generatio… https://t.co/qHCfSIfmv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the EBP advisory group for teaching our leaders about evidence based practice and how to review research.… https://t.co/bEPYaety5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's the thing I just started this video but if number one isn't coming back against the cleveland after being do… https://t.co/wpAfGAnva0]]></document><document><![CDATA[After that, as William Shakespeare in Macbeth said, “And then is heard no more.”Why do we work so hard, make so muc… https://t.co/ps0B1WNq6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[this song is hitting a little different tonight ladies https://t.co/c3z3ZuTMeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[High contrast dog. High contrast day. #blueheelersofinstagram #australiancattledog #dogsofinstagram @ Beaumont-Wils… https://t.co/7iIDwQKXTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my favorite people on this earth!!!! I love ya kobs!!! 🧡 @kobimoore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Drinkin' Too Much (8pm) by @SamHuntMusic on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/x6Llc3qRj6 https://t.co/u7FyZmrNAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot drink the cup of the Lord and the cup of demons too; you cannot have a part in both the Lord's table and… https://t.co/d2O9AxDbAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyWithAK7 Good Morning Dear Friend Kathy Have a great Sunday 🌼🌻💛🌼🌻💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEVIN!! She is amazing @ Disney's Animal Kingdom https://t.co/tzq2FqzmCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5punkins @realDonaldTrump Yes, the Piwer Four!  The Four Horsemen of the Acropolis!  The Four Mouseketeers. The In… https://t.co/2pEIJ3QTCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abigail_Hope_ @jennylewis Not suggesting that in the slightest. Just real tired of women coming out in defense of… https://t.co/21Jo0ayy9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to share my workouts with you on YouTube!  A lot of you have been asking for this for quite sometime… https://t.co/Ia466hBTES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Philly🇺🇸  #philadelphia #philly #cityhall #jimssteaks #cheesesteak #david #traderjoes #philadelphiamuseumofart… https://t.co/iYXmVR3tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanboy You're just working that out? If you really have juice and can pull from showrooms for FULL front row loo… https://t.co/7Q3m7DJkQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude disembarking from his @Tesla in a Tesla jacket with a Tesla cap: way to commit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want her free stuff! It’s not worth the cost. I don’t want the federal government in my personal business.… https://t.co/Mj7gkxiBGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear diary,  I didn’t make it. I came to Buffalo to buy duty free alcohol. Checkpoint is  flooded with Americans. C… https://t.co/aaS4GPWCbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AKinkhabwala @Girlsurgeon Not anymore.  His interviews are so disrespectful. I don’t see ABand Ben ever talking ag… https://t.co/famJGfYUk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i put my work passcode into my phone like 3 times before i realize it’s my own phone]]></document></documents></author>