<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MrsHCox @MicrosoftEDU @gamify_i and @NiaBTeaching ....what say thee???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarriottBonvoy consider this a big report. Happy to DM my rewards number.   Shows me as lifetime platinum when I’m… https://t.co/GsCqKYe5sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edward_thefirst @LanceBriggs @mrileygroup You know what a run and tug is right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Claypool Lennon Delirium - Blood and Rockets: Movement I, Saga of Jack Parsons https://t.co/S7V9xvEoXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i follow you &amp; you dont retweet my tweet @ 2pm, im unfollowing, idc anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Msmariablack @Cptnrwrpnts @mason4922 I’m off to bed :) have a great meal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowballs that don’t require jackets and scarves are the best kind.  In the best city in the world with my favorite… https://t.co/vCWRWPVvrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a GO! @mammothmountain @nbcsports @usskiteam  @btoddrichards @mstinadixon #toyotausgrandprix… https://t.co/acEb8S7c8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiroGomezL @diegosinhue @lopezobrador_ “Dos gobernadores panistas, uno No se presentó” Ciro ( Amlover)  😉✍️🏻🇲🇽]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is always that one friend in the text thread when everyone is joking back and forth and they take it too far… https://t.co/Sw76vN6amH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx @_ElizabethWyman 4 gr8 @MastodonMBB coverage! Thx 4 gr8 pieces on 2 Srs this yr! We’re fired up t’ment 2morrow!… https://t.co/7u6F035A9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickRuffini To a certain extent, everyone has her as a third or fourth choice but nobody as a first choice.  Al… https://t.co/KJqOxBthsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cdngirlsluv98 @98official Its actually supposed to snow again tonight. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MRBIGBANKUCHIES Im watching the second time through rn and it’s crazy how much other stuff I’m seeing. Show has so… https://t.co/S6T2IiV5Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinasCall  Crazy winds already in Wilton / Elk Grove / Sloughhouse area! Sounds like train rolling thru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MairavZ @SenSanders Agree he could definitely do more. Have any of the other Democratic presidential candidates done anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikip221 @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump As if you have a clue! Just look at all the people who don’t really care wha… https://t.co/ySN1x8Gz6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luckyswing5 @yana54lv @BloodlineGolf It’s the R1-J Blade 2018 https://t.co/V6uD5Tp9Mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a blast spending a few hours in the city last night. LB got to do @serendipity3nyc and a horse ride in Centr… https://t.co/ad5LgvEClN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancesWangTV @Disney That's me this year with Dumbo, Aladdin, and the Lion King.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem the generic is made by Glaxo and not covered by pbm cause they don’t get a rebate. @SecAzar let’s discu… https://t.co/9O3ZSWgykW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petet Yon Jou avan Nou Mouri na Konn Rezon Ki koz Edh pa janm Ka bay Kouran]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone loves Landon for different reasons: amazing teachers, athletics and art achievements, or the opportunity t… https://t.co/PLe3gkBmPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no one in this world more confident than a 21 y/o at a house party that just got busted lmfaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Those shirts are going to sell out by noon tomorrow (Presidents’ Day fittingly...or maybe not)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle Why won’t you just go away go walk in the woods with your husband and maybe get Lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are the great destroyer of jobs in New York.  Please keep your socialist ideas there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lejeune wrestler Stephen Mainz at 106 pounds will wrestle today for third place   📷 Jim Gardiner https://t.co/I7wkHhouyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremendous response on social media (nearly 20K impressions) to our modest proposal ... that @acgme should require… https://t.co/WkyTeirmB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've learned the hard way that Trader Joe's Green Dragon Hot Sauce is only tasty the first 3 times, and then a drag… https://t.co/LHQxsFguX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 61st birthday to the legendary Ice T @FINALLEVEL https://t.co/Wxbt6YQNaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[If one more person tries to speak Spanish at me I am going to scream.   Listen, I know I’m brown but that DOES NOT… https://t.co/S55bkHpqRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ashland, Oregon  #cattleranch #ashlandoregon #ashlandor #landscape #rightnow #oregon #ashlandphotographer… https://t.co/FV9pIuYXMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro at what point do the left and pro choice people call it murder? 2 years, 15 years ? should Andria Yates… https://t.co/oyZ11LSe7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CONTUNDENTEE @Moritavc @AuntJemimaBlack De bola que sí!! Comienzen a traer las bolsas plásticas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez attacks ICE as a 'dangerous agency'  https://t.co/M4jkLjDZ3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm jealous of the drummer's mohawk. @ Key West, Florida https://t.co/SScdLjp2yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@contrarian11 @RealJamesWoods Progressives will see him as a martyr for the cause.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebJHull This is ridiculous. First question after watching video. Is that you? His response yes then end. This i… https://t.co/EzbM7G1mEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Maybe not in 2020, however I'd like to see @HillaryClinton run for #POTUS in either 2028 or 2032.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamarlowe85 What a game! Great article again. Keep up the good writing..of course you have outstanding subject matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for me to read myself to sleep. I'm off tomorrow, but no alarm is being set. (Though I'm reasonably sure I wak… https://t.co/c2GBnvccRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hankschulman Thank you Hank!   Now can you please come say this to Dodgers Fans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Stroudsburg (D-II – PA): Jimmy Terwilliger, who served as the program’s interim head coach since the retiremen… https://t.co/Sg5xTnZiE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill that would charge drug dealers with murder for overdose deaths passes House &amp; Senate https://t.co/YLyXBqRPA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencer_young5 @Starting9 @Jon_DelValle15 330 mil and this dude doesn’t even know what city he’s in damn 😂@Phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring training, beautiful weather #springtraining #springtraining2019 #mlb #baseball #mariners #az #az365… https://t.co/iINnlHU23F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scott_Stiller I'll even get my wife scouting for us if need be, hope it helped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in the studio doing the #makeup for the beautiful actress @yayaizfilmin and photographer mariethomas505.… https://t.co/C9aFDE3Hi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rector 52, Marmaduke 38. Final. Rector advances to the 2A-3 District Tournament Finals tomorrow night at 8:30. #GBB… https://t.co/am6NsUQx59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Que vergüenza, tremenda revolución... Como les gusta el imperio a estos mamarrachos vestidos de ve… https://t.co/SgzYUDspVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personal training starts tomorrow after work kind of excited and nervous at the same time. My trainer does not play around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hottaketuesday Steve Nash was a much better point guard then Stockton ever was and Nash is a top 5 pg ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerthecreator are you going to do a documentary on “scum fuck flower boy”? 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me siento mal por lo que hice simplemente sentía la necesidad de hacerlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all, happy VD and to all a good night. #hallmarkholidays #valentinesday #doyoubooboo @ Costa Mesa, California https://t.co/D8TbB8eRwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I became a “Fulbrighter.” I’m off to India in August for 9 months to research the British treatment of the i… https://t.co/wJS3gqtaaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #WebDesign job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Full Stack Develope… https://t.co/HucK6rmodQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Flashback to pure bliss at Nora En Pure exactly 2 years ago today! ⁣⠀ .⁣⠀ .⁣⠀ .⁣⠀ [Photo taken March 11, 2017 at… https://t.co/MY9nEfrQJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanHagey Yes, I taught in the PT program at Rockhurst University @RockUPT from 2005-2010.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are innocent until proven guilty. Just like all other people. You have the right and will exercise that right r… https://t.co/dMyxQtNMlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3WinstonSalem 14 Pax tested their manliness with a @oneenrg beatdown at #purgatory. https://t.co/TuDVMuqqUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottfawcett Because Brad Faxon thinks it “looks” silly? That is his main problem, right? He mentions other things… https://t.co/wTCiMqSrLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyred1956 @grasshoppr93 @cherokeesher2 @girlsreallyrule @sunrainsunrain @andrerucker51 @Rosie @CraigCo62… https://t.co/m4N2C607DD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two great things today:   Bike ride with my son on his first derailleur bike.  Watching my daughter sing in the Eastman children's choir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nacho Ambríz &gt;&gt;&gt; Marioni, Patiño, y todos los puñetas del ADN Puma]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're working with two trees from one end to the other from the beginning to the end there's nothing but in b… https://t.co/o4zlBgrTFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke Not one repub said the Pres isn’t a liar. Your party is a joke!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philsy81 @MattG1314 @DepressedDarth @LPFootball12 @jjpearson4 @CoachDFrank That's a really good edit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktbonesthomas @FrEdwardBeck Oh I thought maybe it was his 5-10 125lb frame]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the reasons I moved to Portland. Resting heart rate is down 8 bpm in just a week or so of hiking these hills… https://t.co/aFk3dD7TGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help my Dad out if you can and Retweet. He’s a vent-dependent quadriplegic...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beat got no melody. This beat got no keys. My bitch with the shit : Angelina Jolie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 6 days until @SouthWestAir takes me to San Fran, Denver, Phoenix &amp; Sedona, Vegas and then Los Angeles for… https://t.co/yU5yGrKZPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be the kid in the corner who's phone only got a notification from teamsnapchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puedo expresarlo mejor, y tienes razón al 100% amigo, es de las cosas que no pagas con nada y a su vez no tienen… https://t.co/nuuBv27qTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have six fish from this gene. #SuperRedMonkey https://t.co/ODvcG2728j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLDouglass and I talk a LOT of players and schools this wk.  Many kids mentioned. Thanks Dr Kramer and @janasko fo… https://t.co/cGAoqHexnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @JermaineDolly •  •  •  •  • HOW CHURCH PPL LISTEN TO SECULAR MUSIC IN THE CAR!!! Part 32 ...… https://t.co/3cxbzxLUio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jduffyrice @jbarro Getting into the weeds of who qualifies and for what is simply thrashing strawmen without meani… https://t.co/rD9hkZRjKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseBWatters The goal is to keep you spinning in an endless cycle of disgust and impotent anger. It’s the ultimat… https://t.co/2LIx1rfuEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rosatti's Chicago Pizza in Bloomingdale, IL https://t.co/9i8LdoMe90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @POTUS Maybe there is an opening for you in Venezuela especially since you care for poor people and your great empathy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissyRoseUp @1TechnoBuddy @SandalsAnew @JMaccabbee Yes, I wasn’t meaning it as a judgement. I just didn’t want to sound preachy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beachbumm_97 Eye watering, heartburn inducing, panic attack causing farts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Most of the words you speak are lies. #TrumpIsTheMostLyingPresidentEVER @MSNBC @foxnewspolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNightengale Bob how come they had it at dodger Stadium? Did Frank live in Southern California at the end?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a new favorite k9.. #k9BOLO..  @SheriffChody @lt_gray #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let this crack headed looking bitch get caught lurking around my house at night she getting hit with a 10 piece McN… https://t.co/XpX26nSM0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_palazzolo @JVER1 I took that oath as well. I still honor that oath.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever our souls are made of, his and mine are the same. -- Emily Brontë @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/nppDmE6Ib6]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @fleabag somehow manages to be totally different, yet completely amazing in the second series! #fleabag PS—If any… https://t.co/w4MxoLEE59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica But that bird was really the Holy Spirit. https://t.co/JagVyd7lKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad observation as I review hundreds of portfolios this week:   The % of intelligent, creative minds that are being… https://t.co/xqqBYXrSnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CEOTechnician I’ll take the trade opposite you and Akbar. Good luck to us all, though I suppose we all can’t win https://t.co/XLN50bxllI]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a month of record breaking rain, this is a welcome sight #clearskiesasightforsoreeyes @ Franklin, Tennessee https://t.co/uwyf83TPgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonah’s synopsis of Mulan:  “She dresses up like a man cause she doesn’t wanna be a pretty little woman anymore. An… https://t.co/5GqKV4AIJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTfue Fortnite just needs to restart from scratch, 2 years of a game and it's never not had a bug. But thank God t… https://t.co/qFNldSzFlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maldita_ciencia Corrijan, por favor. No hay ningún *indicio* de que cause autismo.  Evidencia, por supuesto que no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the next episode of Saturday Night Live: John Mulaney gets more specific]]></document></documents></author>