<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I had a creepy dream about Voldemort and arson except Magenta from Rocky Horror was his sidekick instead of Bellatr… https://t.co/jrQKa55duN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes falling can be a new beginning too. @ Destin, Florida https://t.co/QRlpasuxmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weekend is not complete unless me &amp; Sam wear the same outfit @ Carmine's Italian Restaurant https://t.co/C5PzjTh5ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I up at 7 in the morning on a break, I don’t even get up this early to go to class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKELLY; ROMANS 11:32; FOR GOD HATH CONCLUDED THEM ALL IN UNBELIEF, THAT HE MIGHT HAVE MERCY UPON ALL:]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you looking at him sleep and you just like.. I should slap this nigga😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really sad how people could carry hate in their heart.. oh well that’s not me tho, ima forgive and let go even… https://t.co/5FUDdgkU32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AyshliWaleska06 why is this some dumb shit that I could see us doing and crying for hours after 😂😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjroche70 @MrDane1982 True. I have been told that I am blunt and even militant. Really? I figure, why play games.… https://t.co/xX8UiIYslD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Reunitedanditfeelssogood #theressomethingaboutmary #comiccon2019 @ Greenville Convention Center https://t.co/99rtWjuyV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPsyBuffy No, because #Republicans don’t actually care about oppresssion. They simply use these issues to go afte… https://t.co/TiiALpWomt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smokey look with this @urbandecay #nakedreloaded palette! Enter to win this palette in my blog post linked in my bi… https://t.co/xIgzP8iOzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do when you feel like your whole world is crashing down around you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EspyMiles @JaxFryburger Thanks Miles! I just commented on a commercial and he brought you into it. Either way. Have a good night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeBDR Lol you’re literally the only person encouraging my nonsense right now and I love it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you sad and in your feelings about guys you listen to @juliamichaels sorry I don’t make the rules https://t.co/JayWA7GAdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACECMN lives its strategic plan by supporting the #business of #design as well as the #profession of #Engineering.… https://t.co/V5A7erjECH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent my manager @Schmittastic’s calendar blocking video so he would stop complaining to me about not getting stuf… https://t.co/WNzrp3sEVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is not about reading ability. It is about reading behaviors.” @Stephharvey49 This gets to the ❤️of my philosoph… https://t.co/V84vSlNdjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillCassidy I hope you are at the top of the Lake Charles bridge when it crumbles to the ground.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite pastime has become the phone calls, texts, visits, e-mails and letters I get to share with our graduate… https://t.co/sE1qDZyh2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a second I thought, 😳💭  “I might have to perform CPR on this #Alpaca”. 🦙🤣💕  #AlpacaFarm #Chelsea #HesOK… https://t.co/I8KwIbPPjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day to all womxn, women of color, trans womxn, and femmes out there - you are beautiful… https://t.co/GyllqGKb5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joined the new crunchselectcameronvillage a few weeks ago and I'm loving it! 🏋️🏼‍♀️🧘🏼‍♀️🚴🏼‍♀️🏃‍♀️// I'm especially… https://t.co/glICNAuIAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love of vintage cabi❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ Whats your favorite vintage cabiclothing pieces? @ North Carolina Museum… https://t.co/zkB1ZT2gvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cresskill open house this Sunday, March 3. Just Listed!  238 Phelps Ave. $719,000. You’ll be impressed from the mom… https://t.co/6a5qadBLzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focus on yourself and making yourself better. You’re really all you have!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to meet @ZERTZ_86 of @eagles last night @thuzio thuziophilly benefiting @ErtzFoundation… https://t.co/sMvNixdo09]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me, or would it be really cool to see online media platforms like @voxdotcom put out a bimonthly newspap… https://t.co/JLMT3kCwrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sad thing is, that’s normal in the day of the life of being Black in amerkka😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, a mom, finding out I’m getting even less sleep cause this weekend is spring forward #HappyInternationalWomensDay https://t.co/LZm99BkFBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookelynreigel I think we need to have a rewatch party...it’s been too long. We can finally get all the jokes tha… https://t.co/7s5kR9V66E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait: #BenedictCumberbatch to Play Satan in #Amazon series of @neilhimself ‘Good Omens’ https://t.co/xgRYinipwU via @variety]]></document><document><![CDATA[should i wear a hawaiian shirt to chicago in the dead of winter would that be funny would peOPLE LIKE THAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spin class with  my hubby and I kicked his butt #vegancople 🌱💚🌱 @ SoulCycle Westlake https://t.co/zn2Kp3YYwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wtCrowell It’s true though. I cringed through a ton of them and then just watched hers again because she was a bloody utter delight. 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @WSUDiversityEd for the MLK programming, Art for Social Change. It’s a life work that we all must continu… https://t.co/iADACwy5o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your mind is on vacation but your mouth is working overtime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun game tonight, + David Thompson! Thanks to the Davis Moore team for the opportunity! #gopack @ PNC Arena https://t.co/cJitjpUtWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard It plays well to their base, not so much to fly over country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCMayor @NYCSchools Mr. Mayor, I have been doing "meatLESS life since I  was 20, I  am 73 now. Meatless Monday, y… https://t.co/pxDlTETKIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[my experience tells me that about 55 minutes is appropriate. however teachers have to know how to use active learni… https://t.co/X5eBuW1Cwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #FacilitiesMgmt job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Accelerate to… https://t.co/VFkEnGm24H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still staring at a giraffe. Baby today maybe? #AprilTheGiraffe  #giraffewatch2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHall00 @MichaelPoyma @DavidGr78574965 @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump 5. https://t.co/iAGqIUsd6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ideas for lent?   My mom thinks I should give up alcohol or swearing and neither of those are happening lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganReports Ugh....I do not drive well in snow! I feel like a wuss when I call in and say I am working from home.… https://t.co/KrLBMrJNLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karellyxo @kaycole02 @NatalieeZamoraa @RobertA13628420 did I hear a yes !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ***are*** torturing us. What do you mean “very hopeful.” IS THERE A POSSIBILITY THIS WAS IT? We will NEVER SLEE… https://t.co/mWxAfDZz09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hstevens33 @kyleparkwalton @OU_Volleyball @livvykat I’m impressed you know that Hunter!  Just for the record, she’… https://t.co/06wUKiVW0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 @Tammylynnmiddl1 That's exactly it.......all the Democratic governed states over run with illegals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[psa I am very happy, healthy, and loving life. Accidentally tweeted an annoyed emoji earlier so sorry to concern an… https://t.co/RTYK5SVLnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MENAsymbolism @BL_MadeDigital @BLQatar @For_the_Wynn @FantasticalScr1 @ethiopic @EndangeredAlpha @RobinDelMar1 I d… https://t.co/m3YletJVBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#safarilive Hi Safarians! Ready for our afternoon drive and crossing fingers to see a spotted kitty! Hope that the… https://t.co/yH55YNeiKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hunters Point, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/2rGQvjRJgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJMORTON @iamjojo @MortonRecords @dominicscxtt I'm just crazy about this track. Keep going higher PJ!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InMyFamilyCircus We like to keep the air conditioning low. https://t.co/k0lnQtu8To]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was freezing in my apartment and my dogs wanted to go for a walk. So I bundled up. I’m talking two sweatshirts… https://t.co/qsqWBKN2EC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/dafePYZHDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 2201 S ONG ST S #Amarillo #TX  #realestate https://t.co/zBEql0qbuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheinelleJones is that dress from Loft? It’s been written up in Allure]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @GoogleAds Prices depends on the keywords you use, and they change from moment to moment - the price is seldom th… https://t.co/hsTyCiUqmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[History Club decolonized the ecological reserve today! Pulled the invasive European grasses and planted native sage… https://t.co/U03kELtoxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next project.  A skull cap for Doug. I've never made a #skullcap before, so we'll see how it turns out!… https://t.co/hqRDNarvve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes things seem like they’re chill but they’re really notttttttt chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna rip it off. Fuckin oweeeeee....... @ Des Moines, Iowa https://t.co/xG5Ytbs9jL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A8: Wr are working on passion projects!  Trying to get ss to find what they love to make the world a better place! #scitlap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week I puked in the parking lot of casa. This week I puked in the parking lot of Applebee’s. This baby does no… https://t.co/BDKnQJAB4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[My account is $400 overdrawn. I’m in debt. Work volume is too high for the amount I get paid. I feel fat and can’t… https://t.co/4SCmO1Op93]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t mind the lil’ yellow leaf when you walk up and see this at my community...my new baby survived the freezes to… https://t.co/p52Y1c4gF4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexnmcguire This is so freaking hilarious! I laugh out loud everytime I read it  It makes me think of how… https://t.co/DVxWsHmhjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how good of friends we are, I will never remember your birthday unless you tell me like a week before. Every year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you and your one of a kind eye, Emery Becker (cheese7224) This time of year I can feel you more near. I will… https://t.co/k425U1jAfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao my bro in law Stevie really be having females all up on him causing they bf to get mad at him]]></document><document><![CDATA[This look is reminding me when a friend told me I was looking like - what I heard was - Idina - thinking I miraculo… https://t.co/lrZtlsRSUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddyCoSheriff @UTChargerTom His is pretty mischievous.. https://t.co/PipVWwwlbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best waterline buddies. #makeup #cosmetics #scandaleyes #rimmel #style #ownyourlook ##sephora #tartecosmetics… https://t.co/jzNiCmhXID]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna take off in my modeling career and travel the world already 🙇🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless you are a regular coffee drinker you will never understand how amazing the first sip of coffee is]]></document><document><![CDATA[being on #honeymoonisland today reminded me again of why in want to #live in this area the #beach at the #statepark… https://t.co/ebbDwYUsX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg this salad just gave me explosive diarrhea , I can still see the leafy greens 🥬 as I flush the toilet #veaganproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow @angiecthomas A very genuine, sweet, and inspiring interview. Thanks Angie and Noah ❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have also discovered that Valentines Day is now my LEAST favorite holiday :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Especially outer suburbs” busting the myth that millennials are moving to cities in droves.  @JedKolko  #Jobs… https://t.co/Lr5l18NBRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrissy_NC @joncoopertweets @aloha_alaska @mattgaetz Now I understand.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double tap if you’re happy it’s Friday like me🎉 What was the first color you noticed in this pic? 🌈❤️💛💚💙. . . Let m… https://t.co/KnitaQRGz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkjohal64 @jimmyfallon @FallonTonight I’m so excited to see tonight’s show. It’ll be fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsvn If this is true then all the man hours paid to look into this he should have to cover and should be charged f… https://t.co/9CXRSfOMcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para sa isang case ng eggs mambibwisit sila. Jusq. Lutuan pa kita ng scrambled. Vaklang toooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be welcoming iconic photographer @RichardYoung110 for his talks to celebrate @hotelshangrila , an arc… https://t.co/MmXb9hiByD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annika_Kraft Mama Kraft I need a little of your spice in my life I’m absolutely a mess with you in Chatty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Opticheart @dynah233 @khloekardashian @jadapsmith is call BREAKING A TRUST &amp; DISLOYALTY!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad I had to miss time with the amazing group of educators! Great work, @WstaSci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non edible objects my dog has consumed that I really don’t understand how she physically can: tinfoil, a plastic sp… https://t.co/Ds0i1j5jk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurdsIVue hhhhhhhiiiiii I tried to tweet you yesterday from the Kohl’s I was in but I couldn’t. I know you are tak… https://t.co/wIrFpKITQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[VR Math fluency! @QuercusPrinus trying out @joelwehr &amp; @JustAskJared recent innovation! #equity #ptnmath… https://t.co/xPzZsbLTek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essayareayaitch @ChelseyKelsey Always direct. It’s so much less exhausting. When are you going? I have a couple trips planned this year...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepWilson @RepCheri @StaceyPlaskett I thought of you last Sunday when @60Minutes did the story on the girls. Was h… https://t.co/KJkSZKLW4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/i5I708dUBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you only like two of the beers enough to finish the tasters you go back to what you know... @ Vanish Brewery https://t.co/GsIe0IvE3k]]></document></documents></author>