<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Take her away!PR Disaster for AOC as Authorities Receive Complaint of Illegal Dealings with Boyfriend https://t.co/ou9D0lzNd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Patient Care Technician - PCT"? What did you like most about that job? #PatientCare #Lancaster, OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheToiley Instead of Twilight...it can be Toi-let.  Instead of The Room, it can be The Bath Room.  Instead of Gone… https://t.co/mvj581ZteD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great seeing my man @ciscoreyes @Neko_Sparks happy birthday @davebrownusa #celebratelife #rodneydamoncollins… https://t.co/4IJXv34lhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@llmhhg It’s also rewarding watching them progress through life, Coach. #wlmbbproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear children, let us not love with words or speech but with actions and in truth. https://t.co/gOqqrbDj1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mister817 @USDirectExpress Ive had them for 10 years with my SS, and I got lied at all over the place last month w… https://t.co/wfHjEjSDww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaroldAbend @cifccs @Prep2PrepSports @coachnatesmith Salesian will also be in the house to match the energy 🔥👿 Gonna be a crazy one 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you look at time.. my @mvmt watch is telling me it’s almost time for another apex stream on @WatchMixer in 10… https://t.co/XErvqc2yqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesbionicamazon @rickklein @mtracey @MeghanMcCain @TheView A winner? Is that serious? She ran against an absent co… https://t.co/DEwJ6FXNtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh the indignation of Meadows ugh ugh it’s so hard to be called a racist ugh ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Enes_Kanter work on mending the relationship with your country bro we would have crushed them with you #nexttime ✊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNNFL This man is ready to lay it all on the line for you. Jason’s gone, HE LEFT YOU! He had his fun and just ki… https://t.co/BFlFJ3H80E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just hate when you know someone for 10 years and thought you were friends and all of a sudden they delete… https://t.co/tULpfiKFvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninjahulahoop @CatsClassnSass I guess he should have thought twice before entering the kitchen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bold predictions for @nascar 2019 @BubbaWallace and @mattdracing will win a race this year. My teams of drivers thi… https://t.co/OF3J2jlhwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dirty (baker’s) Dozen 2-23 #forksup # @ASU_Baseball https://t.co/ENLUkdcOwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EclecticRadical @TrueDetective It's kind of ballsy that they reference Bill Clinton as being potentially involved in the crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its that time of the year @natspooner5 @BradDalgarno @nursey16 @DougGilmour93 @BrandonPrust8 @SamiJoSmall @Kostka85… https://t.co/JHGRtClksH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuh if you find a spicy chiccen delux from chikfila spicy you a weak ass niggah / female 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Impactful Ways to Combat Sexual Harassment in the Workplace https://t.co/9k4vjofLKu via @hireonlinkedin]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my friend Ms Carolyn Wells of KCBS (founder) at the natlturkeyfed #turkeysmoke 1st ever all Turkey cookoff… https://t.co/mHWp8rjiLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellievan65 Agree. I had 3 Westie clowns. On my darkest days, all I had to do was sit on t couch. Pets break your h… https://t.co/1lQ8Ve9jgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelfish74 @SpartanJessica @AsianJoeEvans @brainreceptive @foodandwine @omaha_hawkeye Throw me into the "love Cinnamon Life" category]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fund the wall Save us Americans Taxpayers Billions. Stop spending money on illegals. Maybe you should do the math.… https://t.co/MW1hbQ1Mu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FriedrichHayek @EconTalker It’s ok, what’s wrong with Popper’s “Realism and the Aim of Science.” Aka falsification?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attend a church that has a #pulpit and an #altar, #not one with just a #stage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allstarweekend #Turnup #celebrities  #shows #Artist #events #charlottenc #charlotte  #northcarolina… https://t.co/pBb22T1CB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night sunset special 📸 @komonews @Walter_Kelley @KING5Seattle @KIRO7Seattle @Q13Tim @Q13FOX @ShannonODKOMO… https://t.co/4EEMiP2l5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's only Wednesday but the week got you wanting to nap hard 🐶💤 @ Downtown Orlando https://t.co/Xlu3apvYFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Another uneducated, Pavlovian t-Rump dog, eating piles of steaming  💩💩💩 served up to the gullible 'tards… https://t.co/OBrGVzdNcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows It looks like @POTUS lies every single day to the citizens of the USA. While you are bu… https://t.co/wzppzwTvcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most difficult Twitter poll of all time. But viewing the Gifs in the replies made it amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PitusaGO @SCJN ¿Segura que es progreso de los derechos humanos?  No toda tendencia puede llamarse derecho humano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I began in the investment business in 1976 and the dissatisfaction with the stock market was pervasive. Today I gri… https://t.co/SIiXuLrrK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGpenn This tweet shows I'm (we're?) getting old. Pretty sure I was at their grand opening weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏🏿💯  Stay positive and continue to work for it. @duskopoppington @1996Biggs @rocnation metroboomin @londonondatrack… https://t.co/cD1wxKDiYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coderrob I’ve pretty much abandoned Camtasia. The FPS limit on 1080p video is a travesty. Would love to compare no… https://t.co/TUsbQSAQDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So doctors so possibly in 4 weeks I’ll beable to start walking again .. 🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan So, what will his last tweet read like??  _______ Ohh sh*t!!!! ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Westside_Twone @fthemilenials @yanksjets322 @bostonbetterson @BleacherReport Oh yeah? https://t.co/8LQHsv3Mkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats also to Craig Zies on continuing his career @MuskingumFB! The muskies just got one of the best all around… https://t.co/RqsuXJSKew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Lipi Pali O Theos by Giorgos Mazonakis on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/OWqUoLs43W https://t.co/aM30uBebok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy to think that six years ago today I was shaking in my shoes awaiting my high school tryout as a freshman. Hus… https://t.co/71cd8QRKHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day. #fearless #fearlessgirl #bull #chargingbull #landmark #attraction #monument… https://t.co/j1GuhGvws9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You sound like a commercial for state run TV!]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 ALS 500 Push Up Challenge Full video up on IGTV, Facebook, and YouTube  ALS does not discriminate against age,… https://t.co/VdU7VAnj9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Love that 28min in on @GhostAdventures they already have so much evidence and they haven't even started the main… https://t.co/rcY8uwYyks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayonaboat do you use the Samsung phone due to the removal of SD cards for transfer video? Could you use a phone t… https://t.co/bPjYPoDtPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mecca Johnson speaking at the CDEA Conference. #ignitethe passion2019 @ First Baptist Church of Orange Park - First… https://t.co/DmKtejN3hR]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO IS SAYRNA VOICE ACTOR!?!?!?!? That voice rings so many bells !!! @anthemgame  #anthemgame #AnthemColossus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stop cooking lol 12:20am and I’m hungry for strawberry pecan pancakes 🤣🤣🤣 (Hint) cook ya strawberries in mapl… https://t.co/p9xb8G6B3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always forget the hashtags. #indiegames #indiedev etc. etc. We'll do it better on the next tweet 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewEnglandPatr #kraft going to a massage parlor falls under the category of #whofuckingcares]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote Sen @jvejercito back to the Senate to be able to continue what He has started in uplifting and improving the q… https://t.co/jAwDV14MvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMEN and God bless WORLD have a great day don't forget to SMILE @DennisJBolt 🔱⚡BOLTIBOLTZ CAN'T STOP WON'T STOP Be… https://t.co/5r2ucTvdun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Murray should definitely play Mark Sargent in a bio pic #beyondthecurve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EwdatsGROSS You’re the only person ever to actually take the time and do everyone’s! #DEDICATED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoolaHoopsMcGee Yes that would have been tragic. I bet people will miss appointments all over the country tomorrow… https://t.co/BokioZkriu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRafLemaitre Unless they're at least BLS licensed they're just going to be in the way. If they want to try a dif… https://t.co/3Qj0KsdkvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a lot of shit going on but I couldn’t help myself and now going to Get Lucky SLC 🍀 i can’t wait to see the primos 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brick Red Ale by @KegCreekBrewing at @gatewaymarket — https://t.co/FLpqObttBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shauntuzzy @WWEUniverse @WWE @WWE_MandyRose @SonyaDevilleWWE She trying to dress like Alexa bliss Corey probably liking it]]></document><document><![CDATA[6/ my previous research has been conducted on failure modes of Tri-structural Isotropic(TRISO) fuels. Also worked o… https://t.co/xJjbtmjQMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[First game at CCP ever. PIGS vs the Gwinnett Braves. https://t.co/5Rii7qfmN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone posting today and giving their odes to the “Grand Canyon” understand that you’re celebrating stolen land f… https://t.co/MYm3kAn6SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@optimum Tv &amp; Internet &amp; Phone Support Home Apt 105 - C  @ThomasChieffo Myers Corner Road 🌟 https://t.co/HrplCN7gRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can think of ones better than Batman Begins and Dark Knight Rises but I think Dark Knight will always be my favor… https://t.co/iHzj8j5ifK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a St. Charles Porter by @blackstonebrew at @legends_smyrna — https://t.co/xxN5MeGi58]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna go “out on a limb” here....#DebasingOfAmerica #NRAisGRU #Mueller #SDNY #TrumpTower]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I sitting alone in an ornate chair, sipping tea, watching ‘Call Me By Your Name’ for the second time this year?… https://t.co/PRAE65ZStc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBakerSF @markets Subtracting approximate annual fuel expenses, the price drops considerably.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new lil guy: Pippin #kitty #furryfamily #lotr @ North York https://t.co/BI6FqHsxOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then there’s me who waits to ask for extra sauce after I’ve already paid so they might not charge me for it   https://t.co/7drTjzHU6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcballz @Timcast Horseshit. Build something cool that people want, people flock to it. Sucks to be on the losing e… https://t.co/zrkuUsoHvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Packed house is ready to go for tonight’s division 3, region 20, regional final hockey matchup between East Grand R… https://t.co/U5n5X3PLTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp Like the president going around the congress for the fever dream “invasion” at the border?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gardiner played a season-low 16:30 against the #Sabres on Monday.   Igor Ozhiganov will dress in his place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshroz Does she realize that she will disappear??? Where’s Jimmy Hoffa???? Dumb ass woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SanCadilla Pero es rayado, no se cuando se vino para acá 🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/LFWnUtmRAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thursday @AndrewCrowl! I may have an opportunity for us to collaborate! I'm working with a client that is a Z… https://t.co/RYE08H3hsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS is true journalism ... kudos to @NickStevensHSOT and @highschoolot for their hard work on this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_white_sails @wbz Fake Indians maybe?  Had em 1773. https://t.co/8GyFZAoEh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulwama attacker was a local kashmiri from #Pulwama, the person who supplied explosives was arrested from bihar 🇮🇳… https://t.co/Ry9dNBZvUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress At the exact same time that kid sues @washingtonpost for $250 million.    Another sellout.  It’s sad… https://t.co/s4xHCTQlmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top reason Millenials are fired- they can’t collaborate! CTE courses focus on these “soft skills” that are so criti… https://t.co/u3i8aEdpuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Declassify declassify declassify all Fisa documents. Prosecute the offenders Rod, Comey struck Page… https://t.co/iIQxgPS2Bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdellag I don’t fly well either. I feel your pain. I’ve never been to Europe because if it. Bums me out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the same version that @RepGerryPollet and @PramilaJayapal and I introduced three years ago, but the fact that t… https://t.co/9tNkPOGLKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jholliday83 @ODGCSA @EricSnelsire @turffeller @BayerGolf They wouldn’t let you in the picture, would they?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that is caused by?  Seems the left should start a voluntary program to give back to the government what they ha… https://t.co/cHkLQlgJRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to rawbeccs for help with the camera today! &lt;3 @ Tall Cypress Natural Area https://t.co/fjnKzgfPxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall Use Twitter to take notes. Make short summaries of things you find useful and interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't have to agree with Joe Biden on everything that comes out of his mouth. I have disagreed with every preside… https://t.co/NBN25JjZBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time — high time — to take Fox News’s destructive role in America seriously https://t.co/2dNGy4qH9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@berner415 The opposite of layed back,&amp; stress free!! Fuckin'c Stressinators "! https://t.co/bkAycXmbdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronjmagnan A3: During the work day I focus on my students and they need more care / attention than I do...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StalkandBeans @StalkandBeans Thank you. We are all focused on providing #veterans alternatives to what they are cu… https://t.co/VlUezDv1Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean @RepAdamSchiff didn’t leave the hearing room to twit to #FakeNews MSM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Atlanta #Georgia @ Omni Atlanta Hotel at CNN Center https://t.co/VX4IcqtnOj]]></document></documents></author>