<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Bigkountry #bignfat2buffnfit #canthurtme effort must supersede our excuses #getrdid @ Blue Springs Fieldhouse https://t.co/4stsat94oP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ariam124521 Muy buenas noches 🌙😘💤😴 para ti también Amiga y que descanses cuídate mucho y hasta mañana,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social media. Because I see less and less benefit in having this account. And music is everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurelPfahler @jeffrueter I would love it if they sent matcha tasting notes. I’ve whiffed on my last two amazon orders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stanchion injuries don’t seem that common, but they’re some of the more memorable ones because they’re incredibly b… https://t.co/DoMWyMSf1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorsmack1 @CoyHamp @Briteeye777 @hlee39hlee @TG2TruthSeeker @reinamarie768 @pepegazebo @cujo1000 @donttrustgovt… https://t.co/Ra4YIxlj5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilymakenna02 @_sammy7754 Ask someone to get ur shift and then go eat dessert🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseDocMaker Liken it to the Grammys. Where old rich white people put themselves in charge of what other old rich… https://t.co/bHkfcHuJbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bootsy17 @wshsterriers @BrownieSports Should have been a couple more @BrownieSports Emily’s on that list in my opinion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsraelUSAforevr People this age have traditionally never been heavily politicized. Whoever has inflicted/taught th… https://t.co/fxbOCbNlhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElJodario No te parece el camino correcto. Ante tanto constructor falso. Las pólizas no son garantía, pero si van por el camino correcto!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day to @alicemarchx 💖💖💖💖💖❤❤❤❤❤ #ValentinesDay #porn #porno #pornhub #sexy #alicemarch… https://t.co/er2WcytXfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful organization that is capable of changing the world  #ChangeTheWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatsSupport @AidanElt Is your program integrated or segregated skills?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely outstanding game! The mood in this gym was unbelievable. Greeley brought their faithful and at times had… https://t.co/gYl5UjdSUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything about life is so freaky and wild if you really think about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus was mostly focused on gun rights and the importance of a low marginal tax rate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#diamondband #pastpresentfuture #3stonering #february #loveyou #monthoflove #bemine #diamonds #ladieswear… https://t.co/ls9b4xXaCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidChitwoodd @jaesofamous @Rocketfan2503 Most articles on the old interweb list the last year of the millennial… https://t.co/5JAetJphkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[On steel guitarist Noel Boggs:  “His advanced tonal thinking put him on the harmonic cutting edge and kept his soun… https://t.co/6PXpff7unG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nl19 #hgraeromissio #hgrtour2019 I have seen your drive shanegoldn you can't drive there! @ San Diego Internationa… https://t.co/mz4fetOzKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nikola Jokic, on top of being better than Embiid anyways, is going to be a staple of the all star game (or at least… https://t.co/NGWIcenKj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenGolliver @WorldWideWob @SpectrumSN It's crazy that this bunch has done what a few sordid Cavs rosters full of h… https://t.co/2GlSvdRR4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are excited to announce Drake (@Drake) will be returning to @XSLasVegas on Saturday, May 4th and Saturday, May 1… https://t.co/KNfbxZV5Lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just need to know why parents feel the need to attack hardworking teachers and faculty, to create issues when the… https://t.co/zcuWUIAydH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Everyone, here’s My Greatest #Legacy. Enjoy!   1) Encourage People to #LiveHoweverTheyWant with NO Fear of What… https://t.co/5pCdLNLpO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @aj_emrick7 @KLong1724 we have plenty of time to get working on our choreography. I’ll take the bum… https://t.co/VVUZihfOE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I waited for a furnace to be repaired at home so I pointed the #sony70300g at the #backyardbirds @ Falling Cr… https://t.co/LaWSSfmV1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasSowell Asinine Statement not because it lacks truth, but because it is misleading, irresponsible and incompl… https://t.co/MJECu1MnxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[That?s some mirth right there. Funny Confession Ecard: I farted myself awake again. https://t.co/X6fVCIlV9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyddyer @TubaRemus You have to take into account which events these athletes are competing in. While the roster… https://t.co/yQo1kZjPf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Story Behind the Giants’ New $10 Million Scoreboard - @frntofficesport -  https://t.co/dpnzYzGlJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better make it about 10 million more because 3 million more didn't do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm single life harder talked say Quits no more dating and marriage they girls speak don't like me nothing did help… https://t.co/bU8fjOE5tS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vaultwest @pvandewille @jayrosen_nyu @jonfavs Thanks for calling him out right wing media hosts are household name… https://t.co/kFsYUEH79I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpStudents @MrHinNH Is anybody else not getting videos to play off Twitter's site?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordancole23 @BC3Plus3 If he showed up for every natty, he’d never have a free moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MConsuella @JW4Hillary @rubycramer @BernieSanders He makes it virtually impossible for someone to run against him]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BlueJacketsNHL are really going all in this year.  Love the agression.  #NHLTradeDeadline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lightsaber duelling registered as official sport in France https://t.co/jlxAITTkZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well surely if it’s one coach who can get Foles to duplicate his MVP ways, it’s Saint Doug 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL You are disrespecting 🤡  everywhere.  At least some 🤡 are funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @zbyronwolf I have to ask , was this information only available to her ?  Who was supposed to be following thi… https://t.co/CigK8xRJdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Another enormous waste of taxpayer money on a joyride. #whoiswatching #thesebums]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelForDallas It’s @NelsonTheDoodle he use to be a constituent of #D2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveRamsey Cool. So be born into a wealthy family should be on the top of my to-do list.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing a show on Saturday is really going to affect the important stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindseyyok @caudill_410 I mean she has a job writing about football. Fuckin a id love to do that so yeah I’d take her somewhat serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamDextersLab on @TyltEnt—'Dexter's Laboratory' is my favorite boy genius show of all time https://t.co/0jNsCPKsNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessBirken @JEGrant3 @MadaanLaw @inspiredcat @mikewhelanjr @ZaviehLaw @hellodivorce @mymodernlaw @samglover… https://t.co/et5C26LdxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “I’m not really invested in celebrity gossip.”  Also me: “what the fuck was Tristan thinking?! And Jordyn?! 👋🏼.… https://t.co/2hpeWYWKuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you really want to talk about failed projects? Dude- you somehow managed to lose money on a casino...]]></document><document><![CDATA[True #SorryNotSorry moment... I legit just went and read, also liked every dog pick on @barstoolcarl’s feed.  🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st graders learning a cuss word and saying it all the time = Oberlin Jazz bros who take one politics class and hear the word “neoliberal”]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a self serving take from a white, straight male approaching 80 years old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBLightning has no chill. Y'all are like 20+ points ahead of the guy in second. Calm down 😂 #mybet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayy_cookie literally!! and they charge more for people that are paying for housing that doesn’t make any sense!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurauNathan @ericprydz Openers are on until 2:20, prydz until 430 is what I keep hearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Respirar... Golazo de Benzema!! #ChampionsLeague  #CHAMPIONSxESPN  #RealMadrid]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫4. Finale(Allegro assai by Various Artists, from #SoundHound https://t.co/1ej2mA3b1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a My Bloody Valentine by @AleSmithBrewing @ Josh's Almighty Castle — https://t.co/6GOgahoJMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanNumbers @NBAcouchside @BillMonty_ @bbstats I don't want to bind Bernie to this messaging, but if that's th… https://t.co/oKaK9V33dP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rt @editoreruggeri il crollo delle vendite degli iPhone cinesi e' un buon indizio :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more days till the anniversary of my Earthly day of birth. What a long, strange trip it's been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djoretiree @wdunlap @senatemajldr I'm sorry which party does that traitor running new york run as again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing a Happy Birthday to @carrieunderwood who proves that "Love Wins," along with extraordinary talent, a tremen… https://t.co/65CVyg7kVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrTedros Meet one of my favorite people in the Syracuse, NY area! https://t.co/rhyePiM7zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want me to talk a bit about video games, now is your opportunity. https://t.co/1wsomp9fkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for tonight game vs Miami. #LetsGoDuke #FirstRealDunk @ Durham, North Carolina https://t.co/V06JZffX0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @horusrage @Cern_lXXl @PCribbett @BlancoIndian @CingetoOfBelgae @zapher134 @selgowiros @PolyRhuagh… https://t.co/paONcJsvVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survivor Bias at its best.  Now try that routine as a single parent. THEN maybe I’ll consider buying your snake oil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VXchad @QDM_85 From what I recall you were the birdie king (although my memory is poor) - we'll get you back on the links soon!!  🌴⛳️🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBoxDave So JUSSIE'S a Russian troll? Because he's been working overtime dividing Americans by staging a fake h… https://t.co/GtoEMIn5dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that if we understood that more, be honest bout what we want, go where we’re celebrated and not tolerated,… https://t.co/MzYpzmWaWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ChrisCuomo Let’s see. One type of plane has been involved in different crashes over the last few years. Someh… https://t.co/C7rhdgrPiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renae131 @FaithNaff @WhiteGuysTV @Twitter The book took me over ten years to write. It took seconds to find and re… https://t.co/uxwkkkMEd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinmooney72 @BlueAngels @BlueAngelsCC1 @BlueAngelsAssoc @TexasTNTrocks https://t.co/u1jp9LfE0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traumagasdoc Good points. I am astounded (after 25 plus years in practice) about how many times I can walk into a… https://t.co/6z9T85qJzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If J Cole and Kendrick don’t make a collab album this year IM GOING TO SCREAM!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen Rubio     You’ve Been reporting on Venezuela       How can U S and OTHER countries toooo.... Help Venezuela? wh… https://t.co/Di80fgZ3Z9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Testing the science of gravity and the lack of it with my phone.   #science #gaurdiansofthegalaxy #marvel @ Disney… https://t.co/F52yljuVx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, @jetboyds and I worked countless @VirginAmerica launches (he’s a security exec with Alaska now) and this was a… https://t.co/GEPrXXVI6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danovar @santosmercado El problema es que incrementaron el salario mínimo sin un estudio previo y consulta con la… https://t.co/Jskx8yrgBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deryk Engelland scored yes, but he and Nate Schmidt also shut down one of hockey’s best lines. All-around terrific game from #5 #VegasBorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously why can’t there be more Centurion lounges americanexpress ? @ The Centurion Lounge Las Vegas https://t.co/bxnfgtcRZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinteeKneez Of course!!  “Midwest” is too vague and not all midwesterners drink pop 😜 ... “northland” it is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so my new friend JAY was #1 on this topic that I frankly haven’t decided how to hashtag quite yet. If you have… https://t.co/a0xVWjC5re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Scott from @TwistedXBrewing for the free beer! This WHOA-MANGO IPA is delicious. Looking forward to getti… https://t.co/PgY9gsDHSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 “He tried to rip this country apart on lies”.  Yes, he apparently did.  But this coming from you of all people? Seriously?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurierBiology Plant taxonomists do not @ me. Your suffixes just ruin jokes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biting as a social experience? Don't hang with primates even if you are one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmstrongFcps First Graders have a special guest reader today for African-American Read-in @Keys_Gamarra @fcpsnews… https://t.co/QzHDKIC4PZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pammerhockey I see... still though that’s like a Dale Hunter style cheapshot. Expected more....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul So you quote to make excuses for your arrogance, stupidity and opposition to everything Trump. What a los… https://t.co/mBQo8H7iRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGloriousSons @buffalobills We heard the rumors of Ab coming to the #billsmafia 10 minutes before you guys went… https://t.co/32xzvGc0mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBuckeyeNut Only the beginning to him taking over the reigns as USC's head coach next year. Buckeye fans should… https://t.co/qawwHEeyXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terib3294 @benfluencer @sonny9636 @SenBlumenthal @nytimes @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems Trump should be gone because… https://t.co/McvYiAwYmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruthSalvo @davidaxelrod @Lawrence @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Brass ring? A job in the Trump Administration… https://t.co/XyucJKrIRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_C_ can we plz get all ur stuff on Apple Music  already ? Sorry I don’t do tidal 😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath As long as your profile picture continues to gravitate to look like one gender I cannot take you seriously]]></document></documents></author>