<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @POTUS This is gonna be good. Trump has to pay the Scottish government's legal fees in Tr… https://t.co/vQVqRJF8bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey I found this card on @MTGCardsmith, any idea what the art is from? https://t.co/6LBZIh4lj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok but like i wanna do a camping trip with my close friends like imagine how fun that’d be???]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you couldn’t stay up late to see the Blues blowout the Kings, no worries, we’ve got you covered this morning on… https://t.co/nlbVMB6SKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to show this to my daughter every day 💪🏾 Follow your crazy dreams baby girl...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarenJackson16 @Hinesite @OaklawnRacing @TVG You can’t blame the trainer.  He took advantage of the way the condit… https://t.co/zRcoLNfPeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvrybodysGotOne @RangeBrad @RealBenCarson @realDonaldTrump Can’t wait for Government to take all that private Texas land by eminent domain!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s one of the ugliest things I’ve ever seen. The jacket is a piece of 💩 too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why didn't Alice and angelo clary charge r kelly with statutory rape they said they  learned he had sex with her wh… https://t.co/zyHFc79Wmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLeeZeldin Attacking law enforcement (with a disclaimer that’s its just leadership) just like the president. Tha… https://t.co/SCL00Mb8Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[El @realmadrid necesitaba tanto a Cristiano como éste al Real Madrid...]]></document><document><![CDATA[There has already been precedent yet. A couple of dudes ran for president in Oklahoma and West Virginia on the D ba… https://t.co/HyrJvDsUIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@historBilia @MollyJongFast What about 2/24/17?  I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City o… https://t.co/okfPbNpoMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn right. I don’t care if she was impressionable or brainwashed. She made her bed; now she can lie in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders hey bernie, there is an article on education you need to read on https://t.co/JKMFvJdcaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strategic misfire! I don't know if other independent voters like myself would think that this is a "strategic mis… https://t.co/IZi7mtQVy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilBee67569241 @RealJamesWoods Oh schiit, I am wrong.  It just hit me,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenRickScott please speak up about all the wrong going on in DC, we need common sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chad Michael - The Aura (Official Video) https://t.co/r2S6h5N0f3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearstownSox35 I’ll be going to a few games this year, hope to see you again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arlboromight2 Yeah I mean maybe Sunday scaries have sunk in too far but are we really remembering them or saying “… https://t.co/XEdbtHlh2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonGowton @SportsRadioWIP And u sir will be receiving a stern warning from Comm Manfred]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up. Busy day ahead. (@ Wes’ Living, Broadcasting And Work Space in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/N4yN8OSRaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chet_Cannon We’re not. We don’t care. You do realize that for the “group identity says X, also says Y and that’s h… https://t.co/4dLdI9NOwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[10. IDK if it has anything to do with my Mom being an immigrant, but as a Black / Latinx millennial I've never had… https://t.co/togbdgwn2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[When all else fails, God's hope endures:  Hope that redeems.  Hope that restores.  Hope that heals.  Hope that prot… https://t.co/dV149vxgOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are the highlights from today's @LittleFlyersHky @EHL_Hockey game against @taseahawksehl. Recorded LIVE at… https://t.co/SnIg5RdjJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMtwo @BeginTry The metadata is no longer valid.   The metadata is dependent on the data type that contains the lo… https://t.co/q2dBzQnfs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just me and my #penis  watching #DrPhil  on a lazy #SundayMorning #nyc #losangeles #actor #comedian #directorsdream… https://t.co/9BRfXNOytJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @awonderland is talking to us in discord means the world. She can literally say one word and I’d flip out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEOMidgetAAA @RocklandNatsU18 @RocklandNatsJrA @HEOhockey Well done Shamy!! Great coach and a great program.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorizedMusin you could roll a pizza, too. Eat it like a burrito or wrap. I think you lose a lot more cheese tha… https://t.co/mTLNZgTH0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was unaware that a Supreme Court Justice had a roll ... left or right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golftecsully It’s like AOC saying people are too concerned with being factually correct than morally right.... Lik… https://t.co/nuopacu2Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me. Wishing I was in Orlando this week for the @APinv Admitted #PGATour super fan https://t.co/Zp4AQLc7Xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[As was to be expected, my Twitter Naija friends aligned differentially on the elections. Yet I believe ALL are reas… https://t.co/43DWhIaHzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics This man is very ill. But he still wants to "run" for reelection. He really wants his $185k yearly salary PLUS kick-backs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chinchillazllla @socialistdogmom legally speaking the ability to hold anything larger than a chopstick automatical… https://t.co/20OY1DZSzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a microcosm of insanity of relying on twitter for “news”  -verified account posts an unsourced “snippet” fr… https://t.co/Hu5TJgw8yX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Alright time to go to sleep  My brain: I wonder what the most miles covered while playing one song is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionelMedia To throw as many baseless accusations as possible and see how many can be exploited for air time on CNN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TD6030 @dbl610 @ThePlumLineGS @Samlice3 Good LORD, you're using SNOPES? That explains it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonDarlingJr I’m getting nuts just hearing about this. Can’t deviate from a plan causes too much stress. Maybe you… https://t.co/1qmml8hNCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samir is an amazing person doing great work.  Glad to call him a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nitro Cold Brew with the Sweet Creams.   #Starbucks https://t.co/A5towlNRWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremont waters doesn’t play and Naz Reid scores 1 point and we take down Tennessee. I love this team. What a win]]></document><document><![CDATA[HER IMPACT! Both Chapters are Available on @MangaDex  Chapter 1 Part 2 coming soon this year.… https://t.co/6I1VTbxATz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we honest 9/10 times the woman will be like “i really appreciate the honesty I do but that’s just not what im… https://t.co/OSl5jxaxcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rod really left the justice department a long time ago but stayed in his office]]></document><document><![CDATA[We saw so much so much so much today. Now to hit up the Meet and Greet Reception for the #iiesummit2019 Say hello i… https://t.co/yU35DEiE9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its always nice to have light reading when doing a showing #realtor @ Westfield, Indiana https://t.co/SC71M8eJ4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going Fritos, BBQ, Cheese Doritos, Lays, Ranch Doritos, Cheetos. Y’all gotta get to the Fritos first cause ther… https://t.co/ok9aiLeo0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dwelling on injustices that you have not power to change can make you soul sick! Focus on what you CAN Do! Let go of the rest! #Slamism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSBoston @tomecurran What an Idiot statement last night,,, concerns with the trafficking part,, dumb ass stateme… https://t.co/LK2aSMbLsR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheVegasTake Funny. I’m an alumnus and former employee from UNLV. It’s not the media’s job to help the school or c… https://t.co/mFPvJD2rfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kate_Amara @aarostew @WanderNWoodsman @bonaevolentatis @images_mc @udarnik @texbrodave1 @nailbomb3 @marymjoneil… https://t.co/ljtoKNa98w]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hometown of #Sebastopol is flooded and my dad is going off the rails with dad-joke water puns. CC:… https://t.co/B5Jhf1i2m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @matthewamiller @JenGRodgers no process with trump - it`s what ever his massive overweight gut tell`s h… https://t.co/OT302yuP0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t recall an apology to the 500 people or institutions he terrorized with threats. If I missed that, okay.  Th… https://t.co/8Y8FxUgrgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parfait Maxime faudrait tu dire qu’il joue du bon hockey??@CanadiensMTL @919sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippeReines @Oregonemom Out on the West Coast, we smell targets.  Remember, this is the INITIAL list, today's list, for documents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is heartbreaking💔 May God keep their souls...🙏🏿flew this route countless times in 2017/18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenEyedTwin Your to funny for being so serious beside for an Irish lass you are way pretty ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylankendall12 @HaagoMyEggo Time to pull the plug. https://t.co/V3H12pGb3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobTheYankee No disrespect but take those two jokes out the equation this is about Zuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PenaltyTalk The ratings aren’t the problem...TV and the Rays are a good thing.   More money coming in the next TV… https://t.co/7hamQQ8xv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish there was a version of @WaPoExpress back home, nothing beats a hard copy to start da day]]></document><document><![CDATA[By Lindsey’s “logic”, you can’t *consider* invoking this Constitutional provision unless you end up deciding in the… https://t.co/2IZyX80G6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teslaownersSV I’m hoping when I do finally get a Tesla, the glass roof will allow me to eventually regrow my hair back 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleigh40466485 @JonasAfrend @alllibertynews @OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1… https://t.co/mqQrzsi8Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKuhnerReport SORRY. . .JEFFYKINS. . .sweetie  cups. . .SHE IS A LOUD MOUTH. . .B. . . .Trump is doing ALL HE CAN!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI, District 10 Boys, Girls Basketball Playoff Brackets Updated (2-24-19)  https://t.co/6RthfMWmNc  (Via YourErie 2Go)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eleven_els @Delgadosaurus Correct. Just dinosaurs and other prehistoric creatures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipoff time here in Auburn Arena. Auburn WBB is taking in Missouri. https://t.co/ADf2yO1GWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ericslosingit Man did Eli Cain strap your lunch money in kindergarten and you still bitter about it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHC_UNC say hi to our @ECUPublicHealth students attending today. Thanks to chair @JDonChaney we were able to send… https://t.co/zMur2Uyftx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC...you're a young beautiful intelligent woman! Democratize the Enterprire! - Richard Wolff https://t.co/6FD7hX2QLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewperloff the guard asked me if you could help me I said can I go in and take some pictures he said it can't h… https://t.co/N7gregMr3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyloverico_ Man niggas pressed cus yo gurl lying and shit. U know me nigga u know I wouldn’t hit no female . So… https://t.co/aWieLl6WsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trev_orDie24 Can’t argue that🤷🏻‍♂️ &amp; the fact that Baskett is using it is hella funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadNinjaTurtle @missmindylouwho @DannyDoesCode @NatalieWebber10 @thegoodgodabove Doesn't the bible say that God is… https://t.co/S7HVqotgAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @SpikeLee on your #Oscar Well deserved!  #SpikeLee #1986   #AnthonyBarbozaPhotography… https://t.co/v2W6A23AHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still not good at “exercise” or “fitness” or “being skinny” but I’ll be damned if I can’t make a bumpin playlis… https://t.co/6NaYVRnoYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like how when minorities are in a place where there’s not many of that group they automatically gravitate toward… https://t.co/w0CjhDbr2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[‼️Why I started socialxevents_ ‼️ . . On Thanksgiving night, I sat down to do a reflection exercise called “The Fiv… https://t.co/wDmKuCOFJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bestcruiseprices #Disneyland #Vacations #cruise #sandals #disneyworld Thinking of #Sandles #Carnival Cruise Line o… https://t.co/UnuksauDaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyMikeCheck don’t treat @EricHasseltine like that. He had a pretty decent beard during the 2011 playoff run.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:52 left, Webster Thomas breaks up @SkanHockey shutout. 7 seconds later Titans score again, cuts margin to 4-2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burns23 @JemarTisby I guess my question is whether or not the pursuit of ME (and trans cultural) churches is a gos… https://t.co/d3O1VjqWPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC19691 @tribelaw @SethAbramson Man are all of you from California our killer fans ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew! Seek the truth, tell the truth. One💚 ! ☯️☮️👹 Trichome Thursday! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E… https://t.co/4V2UITLL8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on get your brakes done @ Miami Gardens, Florida https://t.co/iAyWXgDKQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody need a Simpsons donut maker? Think im proly guuud. 😉 #thriftstorefinds https://t.co/KNWjfLev0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my “balloon day” tomorrow!!! Ugh. Getting old-er! Good night and sweet dreams everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[appetizers the chicken good the mozzarella sticks was not fresh at all @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/wfsey1Goor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maroonknight14 You know who lives in Montana, right? Or the FBI mentioned the Ant farm,who's from there? I feel Mu… https://t.co/2NsiVi7DjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been awhile since I worked in an office setting, so I forgot you get paid to watch sewing machine restoration… https://t.co/I5J296OlJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 13 year-old daughter spending her babysitting money on gifts for her best friend’s family whose cat died is the… https://t.co/OFTCXtzj1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sukanya I think @JennLahmers could be Kelly from the Breakin &amp; Breakin 2 Movies from back in the Day ! 🤷🏻‍♂️😂😂… https://t.co/z2AyOwMh1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special prayers for the folks in Konawa tonight. These kinds of things are never easy]]></document></documents></author>