<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[knowing im having hibachi for dinner got me liiiiike https://t.co/ogppVMKwfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I am going crazy with all the crap that these libs are doing....]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a class ends with chocolate covered strawberries you know it was great! #cooking #chocolatecoveredstrawberries… https://t.co/6MhmGfaYAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummmmm ... WE SOLD OUT! It’s a good thing that I’ll be out of town so that some lucky person could take my seat! I’… https://t.co/O6FWb0ll45]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you realize that your black puffy jacket is the unofficial PDX uniform, and your chances of findin… https://t.co/2O1kFH70tV]]></document><document><![CDATA[First car🤓 College Throwback😇 ...Workout wit me Saturday 9am corejamfitness 💥R U Ready! $16 single class! FREE for… https://t.co/wjpoJcW35e]]></document><document><![CDATA[affixed a screen protector to an iPhone, 100% aligned with zero bubbles, anyway think I'll hang my honorary doctora… https://t.co/mmw2OeTX3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao a little old man came up to me while I was working out and says “are you a trainer? No? You’ve been on that m… https://t.co/dB7wSagCxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This why I can’t get nothing nice, Of course a dumbass has to crash into me today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the #btwellnessday sessions lead by our fantastic teacher facilitators! We have so many talented staff memb… https://t.co/RZtl7szRkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve not had coffee yet / gone anywhere at all yet today and I just tried to swipe into the subway with my YMCA key… https://t.co/dNK4QrYLls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kateandmrt Yeah.  It’s raining over there.  I was just looking forward to some trail time.... spring will come, an… https://t.co/cOXPdZigN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squarestates @charliekirk11 And as for peace; OBAMA STARTED WARS IN CAMEROON, YEMEN, IRAQ, AFGHANISTAN, LIBYA, SYR… https://t.co/voXKUDT1YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ommarwah This is why storytelling and diversity are so important. They foster cultural empathy before you've perso… https://t.co/pogz9amatT]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEEP and he just continues to Keep on walking. HE WALKED OUT THE FIRE EXIT🤦‍♀️. So me and my cousin ran through the… https://t.co/Lu0Co2otmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StmmNC Love having @StmmNC students look forward to Physics!  Gibbons students are so creative!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBuschi @thejustinfisher @DDrummond88 @donkoharski @StanFischler @NYIslanders A 7 year honeymoon 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing off a great week of Women in Leadership events both professionally and personally.  Remember to give a hand… https://t.co/uwl2EvJ2nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[But really someone come get their hair done this week I’ve gone crazy not doing hair and I need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am Available for the next 6 Hours on https://t.co/GwVVOpLwzG @TS4Rent #TSEscorts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher its so irronic that your bullshit is going to be held accountable.  I understand your the next one to be… https://t.co/uE0a5NJseb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanshrinks I don’t like it. It looks like cultural appropriation of Indian wedding clothes whitewashed to me. W… https://t.co/o8fKdyksnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow PLOT TWIST on episode 2 of S6 of chef’s table - he is a BUTCHER but longingly recalls wanting to be a VETERINARIAN!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chocolotto12 @Amwamil22 3/the more ya pay. Vice Vera. Eliminate tax returns. Have it taken out paycheck just like… https://t.co/z8vvDWJEjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been this excited to watch anything in a while  I’ve been patiently waiting 😩🙌🏾 #DESUSandMERO #SHOWTIME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthlesswench @Cha51brolll19 @Ginger_Lyn_66 @readnallthetime @L_ei8ht @BicesterBrit @MelissaFunGurl @Prince3eb… https://t.co/syHRJXKu1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m prolly the most goodie goodie bitch I know... 😂 I have been public about why I left Ferris on Facebook and Inst… https://t.co/qRGt1iQ7Ep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dokta_foth @Hazel_River12 @jeannefisher17 @MissesBun @cinbashaw @akach5 @ecclesias @FredFriendly7 @elias_julie… https://t.co/w2JqO7vKon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BattleshipGarcy I feel that in reading her sometime, but then fanfic Lucy is generally not slithering snake Lucy w… https://t.co/oHCNqct8h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyHouth Okayyyy lmao. I was so high last night eating a clementine and a ice cream sandwich 😫😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marymacTV Excellent article! You lay out, in a nutshell, the problem with 24 hour news cycles and their relationsh… https://t.co/OIF851rFfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsengteach I would say that collegial relationships are important, but we became teachers to help students, not be… https://t.co/tFuR6BvaRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday pretty girl 🤩🤩 @mne__  hope ya had a great dayyy ❤️ https://t.co/or7JR0X4hX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desayunando deli (@ Restaurant "La Herradura" in Coahuila) https://t.co/1ocmvFMaCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[lady gaga’s birth chart : sun in aries, moon in scorpio, and gemini rising.... is she doing all right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck what he did them crackers better not give him 70 yrs His wife Andrea with him for years an neve… https://t.co/N07CjLCgKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@67jewelCDH #LOCKHIMUP #LOCKHIMUP  #LOCKHIMUP #LOCKHIMUP  #LOCKHIMUP #LOCKHIMUP  #LOCKHIMUP #LOCKHIMUP  #LOCKHIMUP… https://t.co/kW0OoVGIFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A priest and a couple of therapists have started following me on Instagram. I'm thinking, they either have a great… https://t.co/h2uVVqhXui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahhollowell Sometimes when I have a hard thing to talk to my therapist about I write it down and read it to him… https://t.co/XYd7fWEVrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s see what the fuss is all about. Had to be convinced to try a 🍔. First time here. https://t.co/Qf6HQKff3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[As you are crazy comment on a border yet never bin thear kaveghna yet it never happened Russia yet never happened w… https://t.co/SH61DidN1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you @BigHitEnt  and I sure as hell stan you!  And if someone doesn’t like that I give 0 f*c*s because you ar… https://t.co/6B4O6Ko7ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[21 years later and I am surrounded by the most amazing people. Feeling so loved and so thankful for all the birthda… https://t.co/mQY7NQLHxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched the Studio 54 documentary on Netflix and it made me want to both get wasted + go dancing AND do my taxes. https://t.co/Gvy0nIYhld]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna share my opinion on something really because I can (a thread) . But y’all know racism is never going to e… https://t.co/xqtFXFZLNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been challenged by @dizwire to post the cover of a book that I love with no reviews or explanations - every da… https://t.co/wrRwA7goce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! How terrifying in the sky! Wait until you see the video 😳✈️  I just stepped away from my phone and came back t… https://t.co/2z7EXuXbUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder WHY some economists insisted on making models of things like supply and demand, something super… https://t.co/jDHQLNWHPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very proud to support the launch of the @CybersmileHQ assistant! https://t.co/7PAz0jliah]]></document><document><![CDATA[we bc stronger, better and more grateful for God and for all the people who come to our assistance. We are not cast… https://t.co/QMFZbLpIYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmfaooo dude he was definitely listening hard to the questionable conversation at the end 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no friends and any social interaction I have is with my roommates i have actual anxiety talking to strangers… https://t.co/Z0xW3jglpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoNameGirl8686 @Tha__Problem @egyptiansteven What a epic throwback https://t.co/JP2HTbaSH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[IVE ALWAYS TRIED TO REMEMBER THIS WND IM SORRY. IF YOU SEE ME STRUGGLING PARALLEL PARKING PLS HELP ME BC I SUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[405. Northbound after midnight. #waterlogue #imnotdriving @ Seal Beach, California https://t.co/SumFm78pKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple.......The Democrat wins! Another election 🗳 where Republicans cheated to try to win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hat hangs above my collection of winter coats and scarves, to remind me that #WarmerDays and #HorseRacing are… https://t.co/jztFIutC1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #WomansDay @iam_ari1 I want to be you when I grow up♥️ Natalia says I’m half-way there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca más voy a soltar tu mano, se que Dios me mandó mi regalo, pa' que se me cure too lo malo, mandó tus besos de… https://t.co/BRA6bBNVhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some book recommendations. I devoured The Golden Notebook and The Good Terrorist by Doris Lessing and I woul… https://t.co/FYetbzZn9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @AOC If people want to leave this country, no one will stop them. Look how many people were going to… https://t.co/KYBW1lwwKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have trust issues but .. I don’t trust anyone lol. It makes sense to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerito_ Wey, nunca más. Hace muchísimo daño, o sea.. me encanta pero ño.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are looking for editors. Get at me. Info@ten000hours.com https://t.co/RgWspv5iJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TseaTaughtMe LMAO you cannot tell me when you laying in bed watching tv you ain’t going to start kissing or someth… https://t.co/9iZHKxKWaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich Unfortunately the cabinet and Vice President that he have do not have the same love of country and persona… https://t.co/Yet87QQYVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobForbesDJ @__SG17 @henrywinter @UEFA For CL intent doesn't enter into it. See previous response]]></document><document><![CDATA[AS USUAL YOU GO GIRLS!!! MAKING A SPECIAL BUT FACILE NIGHT MEAN SOMETHING!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛸🐋⛓#darkbeats #darkbeat  #instrumental #producerlife #untaggedbeats #losangelestrap #losangeleshiphop… https://t.co/hSrmbeyNL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t stop thinking about my patient who, while i was caring for him, made it very clear to me that “nurses do none… https://t.co/XZqAOrtmtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait. ahahaqhahhahhahahahahahahahahahahahahahaqhaqhhahaahahahahahhahaahhahaahahahahahhahahhahaahahhahaahhahahahahah… https://t.co/OjCgWu5ddb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started our Mar10 day celebrations with some Eezee-Kart, of course. #peezeeandjeezee #Mar10day #marioday… https://t.co/hvOiLfVKpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Style’ N Grace 11411 S Michigan Ave 773-468-0473 Tuesday-Saturday From 11:00AM To 7:00PM Skirts Available In S M L… https://t.co/vec2GVbfxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRA @GReschenthaler @AWRHawkins FU NRA. Happy Death Day #ParklandShooting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meli_melusine @spaceprole @MillieM80921509 @natashalennard Wikileaks / citizen bloggers are protected by the 1st a… https://t.co/opUN71WR79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris The only emergency we have is a crooked president and his administration. Remove the president and ou… https://t.co/HS8UhiQhIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I'm glad to see everybody wanna get physically  fit. Now I need everybody get there spirit fit too 3 John 1:2 KJ… https://t.co/CDwQV9LzIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Não te trago flores porque elas secam e caem ao chão, te trago os meus versos... simples, mas que fiz de coração ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Love4PoliceDogs thank you 😊 I just need a job for me please thank you 😊 if you have an suggestion please let me kn… https://t.co/qJPkoQhC2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one under contract!!! Chrissy Goheen REALTOR® RE/MAX Best Choice 573.518.4178-573.431.2210… https://t.co/y5iiLp9477]]></document><document><![CDATA[It Was A Great Day!!! Gaining good friends  is always a blessing!!! #greatful #goodvibes #goodfriends #blessed… https://t.co/5sAQGEUTOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les élèves de 1re année de la classe de Mme Nathalie mesurent des objets de leur classe à l’aide des beebots, après… https://t.co/D1UZ2QpaIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @TQLBeerSeries for their great social media coverage for the first #runflyingpig race of 2019! #Bockfest5K #BockStars #BockOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you close to me and someone steps to you, I’m always going to ride out no matter who the mf is period. That defi… https://t.co/b0SsdXBbsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bosstrainers @DonaldLawrence @kanyewest @Charlima I’m called as.a watchman. Why must the church watch and correct… https://t.co/vFsmeuf4Tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kittehs #chicagoBound #aww #furbabies @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/6UU30MMlfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ god was having a good day when he made Alaska, that’s for sure” - job Ross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @PucciaPatrizia @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @zetakaty @janaplauen @TereOrt51687394… https://t.co/eW9YCsgWaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already did this six day book challenge on Facebook @jnoellek and @5crazyfelines. Here were my picks then — and n… https://t.co/akn8imlObs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Autism_Dad Is it just the way the shirt feels or what is on the shirt?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did not send my son to school today uh fuck them because clearly they been out all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had this wonderful @starbucks new drink yesterday as I’m always trying their new drinks! Now I’m over here fully dr… https://t.co/Zqb7y3KDRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Russia has $$ to fund USA gun rights but do not give Russians the right to bear arms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so my last softball season starts tomorrow, my back is still killing me from my stupid ruptured disc and I don’t wa… https://t.co/9QEb01ksUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@democracynow Amazon pays 0 Fed. Taxes. How much would it cost to stop Amazon deforestation?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least Trump is sitting down with the North Korean leader I need scene out of a democrat to do anything like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyyahlong I love that! “Don’t waste your potential” that’s law right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErickaLuddy @cher She’s not preaching hatred. Once again everyone has an opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@emirates chances you’ll have the bachelor finale on my flight tonight? 🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you name me, you negate me. By giving me a name, a label, you negate all the other things I could possibly be. ~… https://t.co/ypgV86b2y1]]></document></documents></author>