<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[For most of my adult life I didn’t believe in God or heaven or hell. I didn’t really have any thoughts about what c… https://t.co/W3fOUTNd3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s a documentary on Netflix about flat earthers called behind the curve and I got about 23 mins in before damn… https://t.co/ripnicJXaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN WHY NOT THE SAME PRISON SENTENCE FOR BILL GATES? Indian doctors sue Bill Gates for harming children with deadl… https://t.co/Xu3l4mK40w]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far, just shy of 7 inches of #snow has fallen in Worcester, MA as #WinterStormScott blasts souther New England w… https://t.co/lYJQgOipYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mickyserge @AlanHydeStudio @psq43 @OfficialBTCT @BTCC @BTCCDanWelch @LouGoodmanMedia @addison1972 @timharvey7… https://t.co/l7Dzxkpgmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djphob Hypothermia is relatively quick and involves a state of euphoria before you die.    Insomnia you just lay h… https://t.co/0HIaP2FUOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 piece chicken dinner. And we dropped hot so it was extra spicy. Half the team died early so it was more like duo… https://t.co/kav2audKzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so sick of fake everything like news space NASA Fictional movies and books globe earth #FE yes it is true !!!… https://t.co/zLXpHYyCzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sure I’ll sleep tonight. McDonell’s “Mack” kinda freaks me out... @McDonellBasket1 https://t.co/bqjpF1vkPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was down n ain’t have nobody u was da only one I wanted by my side]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in case you think all I eat are rib steaks, I do not! Here is what I eat most other times!!! dm for more info… https://t.co/KQNE92xImU]]></document><document><![CDATA[They cross country ski on top of the mountain here! 🤪 @ Sundance Nordic Center https://t.co/dMjSQqwJaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kioscomayor @SoledadDurazo @sylvia_duarte @roviedoc @LinaBuenoLopez @DraCamachoSosa @teresalizarraga… https://t.co/jvSSSXzjkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rumpfshaker Carlson doesn't need to be singled out, there's a whole news culture over at Fox which needs to be uni… https://t.co/FU3IvQQ9ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISPIndianapolis @CarlosWTHR @BenHill_WTHR @WTHRcom Agree.  A good donut should be enjoyed no matter what time of day it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck did I sleep 8 hours last night🤯🤯🤯 shit now that I've stopped smoking lowkey sleeping is becoming easier again… https://t.co/PBwfPtp6lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodbye Pensacola,  until the next time! @ Pensacola Beach, Florida https://t.co/XL8P5L20Up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielhsimmons My sign is a man horse with a bow and arrow 🏹 idk I think I could destroy u, u stupid ass cow]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday to one of the times I advocated for increased state funding for my alma mater, the University of C… https://t.co/zHwHTtTD4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren Your suggested plan of breaking up the best and most profitable American companies is outrageous! I have… https://t.co/35XzZmLpd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBarnsley30 @CFL @calstampeders @sskroughriders @MTLAlouettes @Wpg_BlueBombers @RandyAmbrosie If ads on the fi… https://t.co/6wRAY6jD2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the answer is a simple one, as long as it motivates us to change our approach because trying to get those… https://t.co/GpuCV05kGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 But if he tries to tell us he’s 239 lbs, all bets are off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nokia @NokiaMobile basically there's low crotch all around the outside of the strings but and since it says it's g… https://t.co/NoccirdnJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[HD Who? https://t.co/JKjzIaqYYm via @YouTube watch and subscribe, need the clout 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adoro a quienes escriben poemas y se los comen, como si fueran la chica traga espada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VibeHi @freshfacesuk This is why every African American, really every American needs to check out the #Blexit and… https://t.co/ztjPNzQyh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 seed beats the 4 and then the 1. Championship game tomorrow. https://t.co/uLQEkYK2sK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, this is a great read! Major props to one of the best African-American sports journalists in the game… https://t.co/gTxApPCSVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it really the Academy Awards if Amy Adams doesn’t go home with an Oscar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebbrown32 @zelphontheshelf Believe in whatever fairytales you’d like to believe in your life not mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is pretty much coming down to "do people hate Ryan or Ben more?" scenario.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#roadshow #training #lgairsolutios en Mexicali, Baja California https://t.co/DgNGPWJmPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertBreer @theMMQB If this asshole can win then T O and Ochocinco should file a grievance as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yyj_housing Largest high performance housing building in #Saanich and #crd so far, 64 units built using passive house methodology]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyyyoooooo! My fiancé got me a new jersey! Hope your knee is ok, @MB3FIVE https://t.co/nxMxI2oxLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@photoJDL It's interesting the 734 had 2 over wing exit doors and the -700 only has 1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Inconvenient Truth About The Republican Party That You Need To Hear Now https://t.co/iK9X3XufTh via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I packed myself a fire ass lunch for today nd then forgot it. I officially hate myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachBIERRIA obviously you’re not even close to this fast but I’m sure you can relate !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just hear Pete Williams bring up Hillary Clinton's emails again? For God's sake, WTF MSM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[if people take you for granted, take yourself out the picture . . . C R E A T I V E C O N T R O L]]></document><document><![CDATA[California veterans home threatens to expel 84-year-old widow for leading Bible study group https://t.co/zdeutq5LrM #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeymourMarsha Not sure if you saw it last night, too.  It's predominantly set in 1995.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until my cousins start having kids so I can be an uncle and introduce them to cocaine lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman @spiritstar57 How about indicted on the threat? It doesn't matter how quickly he took it down. It's… https://t.co/bmei2HwQIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ReginaKing #BestSupportingActress   #ChrisEvans #bestsupportinggentleman    Chris Evans had a real-life Captain Am… https://t.co/7hlTHYSKWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We only slander y’all cause y’all the ones complaining about a job YALL chose 😭😭💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to get to a place where you understand your journey is your journey and know that other people do not have… https://t.co/HQXQCfDlhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Not good, we my need to vote to block them out at the earliest time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscars are finally here. These were the best (and worst) movies I saw in 2018. https://t.co/AaoU3dHh9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Your looking old and tired, thats what the continued lying for 2 years has gotten you and no respect. Aft… https://t.co/RnXqLgWajG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorfolkTweed It wasn’t a farmer. But you’re still correct. Take your rings off. It’s dangerous. Here’s the source… https://t.co/YKsqkdWFZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn't know Polar made Valentine's seltzer until I saw a few bottles this evening. This is the Lonely Hearts blackB… https://t.co/eoGtZ6DQ1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics This Democrat is a racist wow unbelievable disgustingshe belittled that woman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tristanspeak How about the rich relatives who mount the heads of their previous dogs, like trophies !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khoelmer11 Miss you too! We’ll try to make it up to grandmas sometime soon 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I’d be working at the @ColumbusCrewSC again. Thought for sure they were headed to Austin TX. But se… https://t.co/wpb2gMAGzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angie_mcmahon 🇦🇺 killed it in Knoxville tonight opening for The Pixies! Soooo good! Check them out! #futurestar… https://t.co/Eej2XusuW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis Buenos días Raúl estoy muy feliz por la eliminación del Ireal Madrid. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/rnPBdpQeKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfOttawa @Timcast @AOC (continued) I support democratic socialism which is totally compatible with capitalism. In… https://t.co/0lxsfNXpEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, 5 SE Copeland [Gray Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 2.00 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShowtimeTate He'd look great in Green and Gold https://t.co/wlUvVE23It]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BahraichSwasth @MinistryWCD @MoHFW_INDIA @icds_up @PiyushGoyal पीयूष जी खलीलाबाद बहराइच परियोजना से बहराइच के लो… https://t.co/QFPFaEsAKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm like 99% sure I just walked by Jon Benjamin (the voice of Bob Belcher and Archer). So.   That's fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes simple sunrises are every bit as beautiful as the lots of clouds ones.  Happy Friday friends from the EZ… https://t.co/KcKI8rnqML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Melrose Park, Pennsylvania https://t.co/CiUvJnj1gM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincestaples this is how we do em in south Florida #cookemup looking forward to you tearing it down tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went golfing 2 years ago today. It was 75 degrees. 8 inches of snow today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitneyhimes @DaveyCrockett9 @sskrzypczak3 @Han_Jolo #StopCyberBullying]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it from the source you cop from the kid my homie sold it too n remixed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookehazexoxo I still love ya, Brooke! #BonerInspiring #Goddess #Perfection #DreamCumTrue #DreamWoman #MyFantasy #MyFavoritePornstar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevJesKast To the privileged, equality always seems like persecution.  Speak loudly and often on women's empowerme… https://t.co/yF63eyUqY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing time spent with amazing family! #tylerperry #madea #farewelltour @ Arie Crown Theater https://t.co/41vUnOYnYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brett_A_little @rheem Would this type of water heater dehumidify the air around it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[snicker for some stress relief. Funny animal photos - these cheered me up NO end! https://t.co/FhneA8gsR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima shy mufucka so when I’m out my line be “ima shy nigga fuck wit me”  Listen it works   You’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitneyCummings Not sure what would be more terrifying, coming home to an empty house to find Kenny G or his older… https://t.co/O9hB9kwBsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressGop @DonaldJTrumpJr All of the California taxpayers money is going to the ILLEGALS! DUMB DEMOCRATS! The citiz… https://t.co/EFlSHgFRRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here to see our Lady Dawgs play! @ Texas A&amp;M University https://t.co/7ZXoGBKOvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goodness.. I lost brain cells looking at this. These people still don’t freaking get it. After all of these year… https://t.co/KhDBiJ9kaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL: Ohio loses on the road, 87-80, against Central Michigan. Bobcats drop their fifth straight, and now they’ll head to Buffalo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 3.17 km in 43m:13s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/bbFvioAsZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sir, if you didn't want me on the ice bar then you shouldn't have put it next to the hot tub. This is on you.   E… https://t.co/toiqy694XS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattxRed @mattgaetz I’m sure it’s better than the ethics investigation...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i repeat bluceface is so fucking wack...man like why is he getting features🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost best_newyork_photos with get_repost ・・・ Explore the most beautiful places in New York ▶️ best_newyork_photo… https://t.co/TBfQpjWVtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @Maga4Justice We love Abbott, does what is right and he knows tens of thousands of his citizens wou… https://t.co/npDwVPVOyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Japan’s Hayabusa 2 bags its first sample from the asteroid Ryugu https://t.co/fGrQb3PdyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK: Highlights from today's Div. III Wooster District Final between Chippewa and Loudonville. The Chipps pulled ou… https://t.co/pMEJTWwo2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiteTV when will the #FiteFest be available for Pre-Order as reported by @MikePWInsider? I only see a package for… https://t.co/BtKvtOdsEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nigeljhorton No one does it better than you. Since you were in Junior high you've been impacting lives for the good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsJayLee22 @15and9smom @SMaxwellStory @Megan78676870 @Shamusroan13 @hottsausage @Dangela2004 @305miami6924… https://t.co/HfHyXiULid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne Not in wv it isn't coal is nothing like it was and the trickle effect was too much lack of opportunity is killing this state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwAg_5 @Chris7959 @Daaaann72 @kosmoskpxx @ValenciaIvan32 Stop cyber bullying me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @RepAdamSchiff John J being god. They lied he gave in and committed suicide the ride has been disclosed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like while I was in San Diego, the liver of @uncletexgp  had a good rest, and seems to be processing bette… https://t.co/62bDNrC3hP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My one game this season at the Cross Arena is over, and I’m thankful to not be back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rdjotut @StopWithUrBS There's lots of old sayings. This one seems apropo for you. "There's a sucker born every minute".]]></document><document><![CDATA[An expert guide to taking a beautiful Sonoma Coast wine tour through Occidental and Freestone… https://t.co/zGZuVOPa1l]]></document></documents></author>