<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I want to support this in hopes that it really does make a difference. If we adopt solar faster it helps the econom… https://t.co/FQAShELJeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaWoo9 Yes! it can definitely work both ways. depends on the person , I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Rebecca - and police are still looking for the shooter. Just a horrible situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking at my 1099s and reading about self employment taxes and I still can’t believe my full time office job scamm… https://t.co/NYsOFWBTcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle  Are you smart enough to realize @SpeakerPelosi was joking about the $1.00?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna cuddle.. this is why I need a boo to come stay the night with me. 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DQualls01 @MetacarolineR Amen! My late husband was Navy, and so were two of my sons! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard Cory's for the green deal, those cow farts getting the whole Democratic party upset, right Cory! Your fresh… https://t.co/evUsiSAR1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmahMJ this makes me want to quit my job at the gym you just signed up at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesse_duplantis Hey tweet a Blessed Sunday evening to you and your family Love your post]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely Love these Photos... Looks So Much Like My Mom in Pic 2 #RIPBigRed #LittleRedEbie 🧡 @ West Hollywood, Ca… https://t.co/2ld1RMLACa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@authenticpaint @iamwandasykes @MMFlint Why r u living in the past? Or is Hillary running again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We look like trash but REUNITED WITH MY TWIN AND IT FEELS FUCKING GOOD https://t.co/qsVyxIYY2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare fucking citing of ALL my bros (including the step) and I in one room. All for the love we have for my mom. She’s the greatest ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrispratt23 My daughter wants to go but I she doesn’t want to go alone :( but really quick what’s your recommenda… https://t.co/XpGWLL9oX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResaCam @KWCosby And because of it native people have sovereign land and they are capitalizing on the weak who bel… https://t.co/9vMsiXoyAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work for a grocery store  that sounds like “hater hoe’s” We sell cheap flowers , tomorrow is going to suck ! Than… https://t.co/pblSC839Rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkingOutWithB Thank you so much my friend for sure I am going to enjoy every minute of it...we are blessed to wa… https://t.co/Fwhw3TZdc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Regency Health &amp; Rehabilitation Center https://t.co/xfhC4jhInr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what anyone says. I like the boarding process at @SouthwestAir better AND I ❤️that I’m not nickel and… https://t.co/6vl5VSh8DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Maybe if I hug this flag America will forget my entire presidency, particularly that I’ve defended dictators like… https://t.co/kybOnlZNb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @NBCThisisUs has @HamiltonMusical references @Lin_Manuel https://t.co/PCiba4pqKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the past month or so I‘ve seen like 3 of my tinder matches in person and I h8 it omfg. Sorry boys I don’t respond lol ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthMP20 @BlueBut28849088 @KatieKarter1 @realDonaldTrump Apparently some people are too dumb to know. Lol https://t.co/yzIicTzcMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chortletown Kennel cough - simple anti boitic. Most shelters treat this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary Great politics. A chair with one agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaNC9 She is precious and so sweet! ( I’m a kindergarten teacher at her school so I should know 😻)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bringing you with us from Philippines made our home complete, Cocoy. I wish you were still here with your playful,… https://t.co/wPme0qk1mM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelEMann Do tell? hahahhahaa.... Michael, you are best positioned to call truth to power on this particular is… https://t.co/LWugYOJfLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachspurcell @teachergoals @PrestonwoodPCA Prestonwood is the exception rather than the rule.  #greatschool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know I love @SouthwestAir but my Denver flight, was supposed to leave at 9:40pm, I’m still on the plane, they… https://t.co/43kuA7bcdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the truth will be found about your loyalties to Putin.  Fox and friends backing a traitor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special props to the kind, patient men at @jackprattsigns for helping my dumb ass figure out how to collapse my bac… https://t.co/zyvy0SKA9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in America should watch and listen.  Lord I pray he is the candidate for the DNC.  He and his socialist fr… https://t.co/WUBJZFHrTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyValentinesDay2019 everyone!! thank you to my love @nick_erbach for these beauuuutimous flowers😘 and for his l… https://t.co/IR4P6zZm2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys need a reality show, love it.@MeganteCalipari @TheErinCalipari]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stormy weather stole our #almondblossomseason   😢😍 #stillbeautiful #californiasnow #orchards #californiagrown… https://t.co/RmvzAbzP0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceHuff4ny @Erica4NY @Raphael4NY @StormTeam4NY @NCAdvertiser @WeatherNation morning sky and driveway ice. A bea… https://t.co/ZQk7yGLE3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wholesale Kids Hooded Bath Towels in USA, CA https://t.co/NY4EkjbRDo #wholesale #towel #manufacturers… https://t.co/bfO3C7BTxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[In three basic sizes; 60ml, 100ml and 120ml. Along with a choice to have with or without nicotine vape juice for al… https://t.co/16BEaMvW0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's kind for you to share your thoughts regarding a weapon that is NOT available to civilians.   In addition,  NO… https://t.co/L3CAvuI5Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[*looks at clock and sees it’s past midnight*  Dead tired of being dead tired, I said... gonna skip all the stuff I… https://t.co/bfLyrTKnkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHamernik Someone needs to have a talk with that groundhog. Or maybe @ILStatePolice  needs to arrest him. I'm s… https://t.co/u8D2N9J7pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updated my spring speaking schedule. Still keeping things light, but I'm excited to be heading to San Francisco, Pr… https://t.co/TgoXIdFqtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJeromeTrammel Trail blazer!  Love that one's fire! WTH can't we get more folks in Congress to be like her and totally call out this B.S?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever have a dream that you wake up from but try to go back to sleep to keep dreaming it? I just dreamt that Kirk Co… https://t.co/e6gyVKMQsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tessaraemiller @sm_ladypanthers @alxeldridge @boyd_emc @capps_emma @mattie_buck20 @keaton_freitag @annahhgoss… https://t.co/RMZMGNdeJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedLawCO @J_Dot_J Also we tease because we love, just in case you did not know that.  Sometimes my sarcasm comes o… https://t.co/ZC9q6XtZxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up too fast, ladies 💕  #mysunshines #babyrosenlundiscoming #family #sistersquad #💕 @ Cambridge, Ontario https://t.co/HACmSfhYoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pattyy_Ribeiro aí eu já acho errado, quer fazer festa, garanta sua segurança, o policial ter que ficar no meio da muvuca.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was indeed a tough day at work with a new job responsibility, but I did it, and that is a huge sense of accom… https://t.co/FHsPYV7vOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are some simple ways to make someone feel really special!  https://t.co/KMHgcRBwXL https://t.co/euz6zl54G8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even before having children of my own, I was smart enough to realize they would come with a lot of "baggage" (liter… https://t.co/R1wZM3qzvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contigo siento que puedo ser yo me siento sin miedos y sin complejos 😉 en Hollywood https://t.co/4SbNs5aKvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davewills34 Hi!!! 👋🏼 (in your general direction) https://t.co/mr6lsbjcbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to biromantic and panromantic people who aren't bisexual and pansexual but that's the only big/pan getting mentioned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Dude, you need to spend some quality time with your good friend, @RepCummings. You almost get it, but not quite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For an hour and a half we shared the same airspace, so by sheer proximity I’m funnier today than I was yesterday.… https://t.co/9be3bcnw8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonDrLJA @HiDesertPatriot Don’t forget she is descendent of slave holders. I truth that isn’t her fault. She… https://t.co/jrE6BPRmCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything@ gop accused obama of being and doing they actual voted for and  got in trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudepundit It’s a fucking disgrace. The entire chicken shit coward GOP are traitors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen Didn't Chi say he did the nomination at the request of 45's staff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to share how to transform coaching to transform learning through the Dynamic Learning Project with our awes… https://t.co/PecV6S1d7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranciscoCano @Newsweek @QEDAstoria I hope so!!! That would be awesome!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[- Fat shaming and skinny shaming is never okay.  - The “all or nothing” approach to veganism is wrong.  - Going to… https://t.co/8dDjHycd0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 i cant wait to get my hands on the riviera palette &amp; the dewy setting spray! 🌈🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPapajohn I think this was the prudent thing to do. Per @RossDellenger he lawyered up and refused to discuss… https://t.co/AO21HBaES0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to another episode of why #dogs are my favorite beings. They are the absolute best and we’re so lucky to ha… https://t.co/tKj0QEPQ5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliensanders13 @dmesticatedswag @FreshWithDepth @FOXNashville Underrated ^]]></document><document><![CDATA[coincidentally watching the episode where chandler and Monica get engaged ... on Valentine’s Day ... I am crying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnamacbabe @Boripa211 @dutchingmarkets @markogorman06 @jtmt2015 @AshAsran @majer_brendan @nferns16 Did you chang… https://t.co/Jf31hIp78s]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow she used her parents wealth to be more wealthy 🤩 yeah no one fucking cares, people out here homeless and starvi… https://t.co/twKfcilkDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@becca7598 @SophieT Love is love. That's what my daughter and sons have always been taught.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang @MaggieDeg4 Is that his tweet or a parody? He's admitting there is no emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealitySteve If Hannah B is the new bachelorette, I will not be watching. She is way too annoying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly thought this said be white people who make you laugh and I was like that's messed up lol https://t.co/N6W9n7blyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump While cutting health services and health research, and instead asking for daddy’s vanity wall. #TrumpCrimeFamilyMustGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[✔️unpack ✔️laundry ✔️clean(ish) house ✔️car washed ✔️fresh blooms. Still feeling a little under the weather, but se… https://t.co/ULVVafO3Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post-secondary students and recent grads sharing thirst experiences and stories with our youth. What wonderful ques… https://t.co/XrWZMSwU8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we stop pretending that wine-related workout merchandise is funny pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveJ1425 @Gil_Hoffman @netanyahu @gantzbe Often state/local elections in odd years]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to find Rice Krispies treats cereal,where I reside. I miss that cereal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad told me not to do anything unrealistic like skiiing off a mountain. He knows my spirit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda rude that I always say bless you to other people but when I sneeze I get “excuse me I’m just trying to get coffee” 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveBngDave @paulmitche11 @CleverTitleTK I'm in one but not the other what am iiiiiiii? I like #Xennial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelTaylor108 Honestly think puppies are my favorite thing on earth😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG HOW HORRIBLE,WHATS https://t.co/n7abH2VBHt MORE GOING BACK IN TIME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kbuhrmester38 @arociorl and 8 others Hello Kerstin Wishing you the same and very best.😘🌹🥀🌸🌺🍂🐝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga, Bradley Cooper - Shallow (From A Star Is Born/Live From The O... https://t.co/1jtyKV0qsP via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleinadSenoj @makeupismyshit @GiftedAsia Oh wow okay. That makes sense. Thanks for the info 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Healthcare and hospital jobs are fun and all till u get forced to stay and work a double 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just really feel like people like that are shitty, I get sometimes relationships don’t work out and things happen… https://t.co/8C86d6A7JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @MarcSerreMP for your continued support of research and community. #bravo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when my stomach starts cramping and there’s nothing I can do about it 😭😭🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone deserves to have at least one person that they can GENUINELY count on no matter what. No ifs, ands, or but… https://t.co/4YR0hzzUIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere I’m a longtime @TMobile customer but my office building in Fairfax is a dead spot. What can be done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely portrait sketch from last night by lorenzodraws :) @ Grand Central Atelier https://t.co/yQRdpKxuW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pathryn34 I rewound like did we just get a titty bounce.....yes yes we did]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s great to hear! We should talk. The little I’ve seen of it too - so many features and options.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold the Date! On October 31 we'll all give candy to children who come to our doors. Everyone will dress up. Men as… https://t.co/HGzkAsXBxG]]></document></documents></author>