<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FinnBalor When are we going to see a match between you &amp; @Jordan_Devlin1 again?  It would be nice to see his RAW debut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vote4robgill @crippledcommie I see you identify as a progressive activist. One of the challenges many  of us are h… https://t.co/On9RV7QtO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raemars Yes!!! That is definitely true. Just keep working and keep growing. But I am going to keep my fingers cros… https://t.co/mSPTdb3UNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You make everything worse. Why can’t you just go away....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeamMEupET237 @Stop_Trump20 @JohnalanJames2 You mean that special inbred kind of beauty?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone PLEASE bring me a shredded chicken burrito from Taco Bell,,I’ll give you my cinnamon twists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin And he says he isn’t running just to upset the Democratic Candidate? I disagree. That is the reason he thr… https://t.co/66xslb3wqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[IS there a Mueller? IS there a CONGRESS? IS there a SENATE?  Asking for a friend:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left my wallet at my boyfriends house so I just had to get $5 of gas in change to get home. Thank God I keep lots of change in my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseRodriguez @allinwithchris @chrislhayes Please address him as “Bernie Sandwiches” as Chris did that time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Mina gets older, I think about this a lot. I cannot imagine the pain of losing your child to this kind of sensel… https://t.co/qxOBAo8yv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con él si me trepo 😁 y ala moto tambien🙊🙈💙te amo @_CarlosRivera https://t.co/PhgrBUtA2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teamechavarre You never heard that?? It’s like, your year of destiny! 29 is Saturn return, 33 is destiny.   So sin… https://t.co/6jcsmNDg3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brownicity Celebrating women all over the world, whoever you are, whatever the color of your skin, your religion,… https://t.co/zBdVLzyWS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Achez22 This is exactly what this movies is saying to me https://t.co/4Rx06wwCQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMAGASteve @LisaSmith4680 it is crazy group  and looks like show, orchestrated by who knows whom?. Where were t… https://t.co/vCRAdAE9QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rose from my Tyler + a rose from my Jude. ~ We celebrated with Benjamin on Tuesday this week because we don’t hav… https://t.co/ZVgYcw944p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student choice this morning in the lab- we have a little of everything going on @storylineonline, @BoomLearning,… https://t.co/b0CjTLNkWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercadoPaulina @saleelsoltv @ImagenTVMex Ya regresando del gym con toda la actitud!! Gustazo verte!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenderFriends @weedandgrub You guys!! 🍗 Let’s all keep making things!! 🌱🐛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Keanu! Nice picture today. (And I like your hair appointment yesterday 😉😎👍). Everything I tweet you is very ac… https://t.co/saEQ8dm1gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preview look at the video coming. Yo Boi Brandon's new music release https://t.co/SFU2MyXCQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnxiousSelkie @Lily30340605 Not sure why this didn’t work. It’s perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into one of my fave celebrities at #DaiquiriDeck. Thanks for entertaining me amanda_marie_miller  #siestakey @… https://t.co/1ngHlZN8Fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LayciJ Only the Preds do TWO big moves within 10 minutes. My heart is done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDies_cmpsr @jhurstmusic This would have also prevented the entirety of Roger Quilter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mindset_x @francis_sielski @Gropher_Tump @TaylorRMarshall You really do have a hard time managing your own cogniti… https://t.co/sSqL8L8ced]]></document><document><![CDATA[2) Question: how did Cohen get bank statements? Did he have permission to share them? Was there a subpoena? Also PO… https://t.co/IM6kJI3dvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m more crying cause I’m glad this is all over #BryceHarperwatch2019 #phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netflix is taking The Vampire Diaries off March 1st and I have never been more heart broken.... like why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun celebrating with @thekellyford last night after the @desmondchild Killer Show!!!  Love U Kelly❤️🥰❤️… https://t.co/uXs1BKoaEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beccamaesay I hear you. We have a 3 am wake up call tomorrow. #Softball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcxd13 Ok i should’ve of said next next week :/ the 11th i come in and then i’m leaving the 12]]></document><document><![CDATA[your whole life can be completely flipped around in a blink of an eye....always remember to kiss your loved ones an… https://t.co/iTpxTOYaMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Palermo man is in critical condition and two others injured after state police said he went off the road, hit tre… https://t.co/fOu6lDsITB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao but fr why are people so dramatic about the whole Kardashian cheating thing . Acting like this shit don’t happen every day in real life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets Well we know that @LindseyGrahamSC @SteveScalise @MarkMeadows @Jim_Jordan are blowing… https://t.co/ntW0NVrYj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[La mejor terapia 🔥❤️ #empoderada #selfie #yo #lahuasteca #mtb #ciclismo #mty #cycling @ Parque Ecologico La Huasteca https://t.co/LL7HonhIKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RIRepublicans @NewportLost @TrussElise @RepublicanRI @SteveJazz @Blake_Filippi @MikeWChip @RIHouseGOP God remember… https://t.co/l0HdGRcusz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHMcWhorter Wow! You are making painstakingly honest observations about Black America! Phenomenal interview on… https://t.co/Q345sDLjmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKronader @ABC @GMA When it all boils down, it’s not about party affiliation, liberals, conservatives, left, or ri… https://t.co/JP1433aIdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up from dozing off while driving is some of the scariest shot ufrvever experienced]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evekendall76 @FactsFantasy Read the case then really think about it.  #amandaknox is a fool. A murderer.  Fake kil… https://t.co/o0PZxeTcmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The crowd at #CPAC2019 responds to President @realDonaldTrump repeating, “America will never be a #socialist countr… https://t.co/2WLsee6W7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope the Democrats in Kentucky are working to get @AmyMcGrathKY ready to spar with ole Mitch McConnell.  She coul… https://t.co/4W6WiEReZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @OldDominion #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries.… https://t.co/6OL2o5y6gO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be working toward another yoga certification from March 3-17. No Pura Vida Popup Yoga sessions during this t… https://t.co/ikHTPKeiVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You've come a long way since our basement movies with incredible tween written scripts, gentlemen.   So proud to kn… https://t.co/G1AJFxLRma]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am proving you can pomodoro your way to success from literally any freaking where.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve Y como sabes que estaban drogados? Sera que tu, la fosforito y Diosdasdo les dieron una dosis a cada uno??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clairistopheles I know you tweeted this 5 days ago but this is the most important video I’ve ever seen in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the saying “I believe in science” a thing? Science isn’t to be believed or disbelieved. It’s a fact and it’s… https://t.co/WT6hV7Azf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fyi if you don’t get 530+ point at the SAT math, they will take away your senior release . So now I’m damn pissed .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eliamarkopoulos Did you watch your stories, have some apricot brandy, then turn in? #seniorcitizen #poppous]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOS: if anyone knows what the cheerleaders say at the end of the TLU fight song please let me know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tlkr97 @dallasnews The House is promoting merit pay. I feel your pain. I’m a single mother. We work way too hard t… https://t.co/5x6xd9OTuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump ........  LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR LIAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chupamilto21 I think he tends to overthink sometimes, and get in his own head too much, but that’s normal for a ro… https://t.co/0NbT6ZhpUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[the single image that turned my love for tommy hilfiger into an obsession https://t.co/SiWFekQKia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump God bless you for stsnding up against all the evil hatred stacks against you....it truely is a swa… https://t.co/PVJQ3mMLB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE HAS SOMEONE BEND OVER AND ZIP HER BOOTS UP FOR HER! THESE PEOPLE ACTUALLY THINK WE ARE THAT STUPID ONE!https://t.co/ekZ814Gajp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlMomento_Qro Me encantaría que consideren a @RioRomamx por favor 🙏🙌😍😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Cathcart Towers Hotel in Surprise, AZ w/ @susanlowryaz https://t.co/CwUQ047blz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The horrible way Trump treats allies doesn't help when Trump asks them for support or favors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nurse, what time is it? 115pm. 155pm? It's 115pm. Nurse, what time is it? 140pm. 155pm?  #dementia #DaylightSavingsTime #changingtheclock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brunorafahell @ProencaBuen Caso Lula jamais foi juridico. Sempre e politico. Provas nao significa nada. O video da… https://t.co/Zko5vr6Ju9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @SteveScalise Knock it off about the socialism. Let’s talk about fascism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[awesome little event at unionmemberhouse today about overcoming anxiety. Grateful to learn more ways to manage it,… https://t.co/kokmziWZvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monsalfonso Dios les ilumine, buen viaje que vayas y regresen con bien🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran a half marathon in sleet and 30 mph wind gusts this morning. Well,  that was unpleasant! https://t.co/euERaZRU77]]></document><document><![CDATA[UniverSoul returns to Atlanta with big changes https://t.co/Vxosv8XGW7 https://t.co/5Hwet81z4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold your loved ones extra tight today ❤️ you never know how long you have with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breezing_in @mick12346 @AndrewScheer @CPC_HQ You took my pinned quote ... my motto ... I'm flattered!]]></document><document><![CDATA[opened up snapchat today to find that not only do i have entirely too many grey hairs for a 23 y/o but also, that c… https://t.co/LTQOYxR4NZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am quite literally the nicest person ever until you push the wrong button. People are so shook when the other sid… https://t.co/eB7ZWEjVR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a tattoo 4 days ago and already want another. I totally understand why people love them so much]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had an amazing weekend with some amazing people at @yogahouse1878! A yoga retreat is just what I needed and I am… https://t.co/eYVkmPbRdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you count yourself as for the rule of law? @RoyBlunt @HawleyMO @RepSamGraves @RepJasonSmith @RepAnnWagner… https://t.co/J7gG37So2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over the moon to have seen @petermurphyinfo tonight. In the Flat Field is my favorite Bauhaus album, and I coul… https://t.co/5coqbsAUOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[By who?  Name an instance where that has happened. I believe female voices are heard and not shushed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DitzMcGeee I don't know you, but I'm very proud of you! And by God you should be! I've tried so many times. I have… https://t.co/U12NZ7RCfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like theres a generation of children that will have no idea what this means and that makes me feel old... https://t.co/eLkDD66O5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tom_flaherty @AAALinks There was a camera there, but I'm not sure what happens with the recordings...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleLiveAction @Barbaradye921 😲That is a ridiculous notion - to mandate ANY party affiliation. 1st I would tell my… https://t.co/lo1rzsJFZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was I the only one who went to a school where they called these cheese zombies??? Drooling thinking about them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guessed this would make a change to all the pictures of tickets @ Central Park https://t.co/u3NMn6C5CH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityNews It’s NOT a Safe Injection Site, it’s a Supervised injection site]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t know who needs to hear this, but you do NOT have to depend on someone to be your sole source of happiness!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @IlhanMN Amazing what people will do when they are so desperate like the Dems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump tried to pressure DOJ to kill proposed merger to punish CNN: ‘I want that deal blocked!’ https://t.co/WiLa3nYgh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sashayed Ohhh my god tho I don’t think I can come, I’m STILL MOVING HOUSE. Can it be an annual tradition?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lonestarmomcom @GenGriebe Same. I like Kamala a lot, but I prefer Klobuchar's pragmatism. She isn't afraid to say… https://t.co/Z9n0GcXTre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @SebGorka Democrats won't allow babies to live.This would make me change party's.Democrats now party of killing children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A tranquil boat ride to Riverside, courtesy of the fact that you can’t get a bus directly from Disney Springs to a… https://t.co/2h6wBV9zqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DarrenCohen Here’s what you need to know about horses and “fumes” in NYC. (Bear in mind the NYPD horses mostly pa… https://t.co/HDFcNUzl3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strait to VEGAS! //1063cowboycountry.com/contests/sweeps/strait-to-vegas/ https://t.co/S4S9ieN6vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soundlyawake I'm a Sagittarius and that's why I don't want to be in the office tomorrow and will be back in the of… https://t.co/pD8D1P5siG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 14 year old me and the 41 year old me are both weeping today..He was the sexiest, coolest guy on tv and they gu… https://t.co/HxhTZikvhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows It wasn't OUR MONEY. we didn't FIND IT, we TOOK IT initially. Jesus if you are an elected official,… https://t.co/jBJ4KXUrP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be okay, I will be successful in every part of my life and be genuinely happy]]></document></documents></author>