<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@stackfprez His 5 year run was astronomical bro, But the generation that remembers how big Ja was dont ever bother… https://t.co/zz8gqmod1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should add as well that a lot of people came out today. I donated next to #AnneArundelCounty Executive Steuart Pi… https://t.co/9Is7ujXu38]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Keep it 100 I’d rather you trust me than to love me”  Literally all I want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok but the whole situation with Michael Jackson is getting on my nerve &amp; breaking my heart 💔 https://t.co/8MBsezEivI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bohemian Rhapsody is winning technical awards because the Academy wanted to honour the team who completed a film wi… https://t.co/Vmzqji6gOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️⚠️New video on IG using the new @TooFaced x @erikajayne collection! ⚠️⚠️ I also have the full video on YouTube. C… https://t.co/A0HLht7xyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you ask your child how their day was their response shouldn’t be a color. It should be filled with stories abo… https://t.co/I5lMZQk0k7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bossybigeyes @thederbyapex my partner tried doing this and was then was told by their team (that a few of us quit… https://t.co/oqIJ3soqlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐴Like our photos...Follow our IG🐎  🏇These photos were taken by me!🐴 🏇Photography by: Connie Wheeler 🐎@WheelerConnie… https://t.co/wQ0UkV3LP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DirtFarmerJeff @business Look at the trump EPA. Good water, good air, all bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rather than a Gap year young people leaving high school could consider a year of solving social problems with a Glo… https://t.co/X1Wq2mvZaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Me_Cennet @smoking_reedus @HeyMo517 @AntoniaSchmitt4 @leedusme1227 @Calisto82 @supportnormie @StephanieMatne1… https://t.co/37aytHkXhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[you get a roll of paper towel! you get a roll of paper towel! everyone gets a roll of paper towel!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you, President Trump, for all you do for our country!!!!❤️🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[What am I doing in NYC? Eating, of course... #eldaeats #eldaeatsnyc https://t.co/Bxo2xz6YCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthabayne @eirencaffall Take it from a klutz, juice glasses for everything. Do not mess around with your elegant hands!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN HOUSES SUNDAY, MARCH 10TH 2PM-4PM _____ NORTH NICHOLS HILLS 1505 Brighton Avenue OKC, OK 73120 2250 SF  /  3 B… https://t.co/OpkPfMCBXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllIn4DJT @SopanDeb @Fahrenthold @jdawsey1 Barry? Who the fuck you calling “Barry”? You mean President Barack Obam… https://t.co/r2WQ8oJV9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To Walk in Nature is to witness a thousand Miracles” #hiking #mountains #superbloom2019 #poppy #californiapoppies… https://t.co/2Qwc1xTd2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amarrealinzi @daisymarquez_ Ooooh girl, you better post some looks! That palette’s on my list. Stunning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the Love of History ♥️✊🏿  Bears, join our SGA Senior Class and Kenneth B Morris Jr., Founder and President of… https://t.co/LC3FgLBjwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Timothy Rogers Photography for this beautiful Tumwater in the snow shot! https://t.co/mEHktPqRdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust me this stuff really works.  Contact me for more information.  Email me @ biancaisfit@gmail.com… https://t.co/joPR5aQtZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamaica Estates Donald was too fucking snobby to ride the 7 train like everyone else in his neighborhood. He'd try… https://t.co/uN2jwEbyIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for anything! *I'm telling myself silently over and over* #FridayFeeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @dannyhoops @BrainbustersMPC and @_sharonku to post 7 covers of books I’ve read, no… https://t.co/qmiVun9jZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We could see a wintry mix into tomorrow morning and Meteorologist @J_Wheeler_WAVY has all of the details you need t… https://t.co/Ym00Ihhox4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robyn_rl @realDonaldTrump @WSJ 3/3 So seems we’re actually debating issue of hypocrisy among political leaders. My… https://t.co/kVmHw7wjMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day here at The Artist Project... here till 6 pm #windstormbedamned #artistprojectto #interiordesign… https://t.co/pxpm4ZYxqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve ordered so much make up recently and I’m just ready for it to get here already! Not that I can wear it anytime soon with the flu 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday motivation 👉 “A good #workout is a great way to clear your mind.” 🏋️‍♀️💪 🏃  #fridaymotivation #gym #fitness https://t.co/VkHZ2vjYgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers My self I love @SherrodBrown and would vote for him But then I am a Ohioan Brown cares about the workers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks kehlani for that scary ass moma shit I’m gonna have nightmares!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to have @AndrewPBrooks Sightlines back on our digital art screen at #NEOmcr   Made from over 50,000 still… https://t.co/KyUyxeFY6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidDa53577460 @TheDemocrats @GavinNewsom @NEA #inners In CA there are different school districts and each of the… https://t.co/UnWzJ4oFcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching visiting @UniWestminster students about BIDs on this snowy, blustery day in NYC. Happy to host you here… https://t.co/xbdnOm8mMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forcing myself to listen to albums besides Trench so I don’t get tired of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And lab meat - can you call it meat if it’s grown in a lab? Mixed feelings from the gang on the @ImpossibleFoods “Impossible Burger”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t understand how much my heart hurts. My dad is the only man I need in my life and he’s not even here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curiouskindie @ansonparkps This is a beautiful idea and I think everybody loves making a beautiful color. 🌸🐖🌷🌺🎟🎀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kentucky should be in OT right now fight me about it @ Lexington, Kentucky https://t.co/qe7IC9sU1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/GrsJ2mjSM6 https://t.co/OZ5d0Ghitg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Concord, NC? https://t.co/4DEhSuIOlo #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed Preview Day @ACUedu. College visits are always exciting. Babygirl is growing up. ACU is awesome! https://t.co/Fp5OcP7ZMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lovefilmz @louzival2011 @amerson6562 @sabinmarketing @ISignforYou1 @ingerickramire1 @datsyuklover @EndangeredBeans… https://t.co/t5rrRWeZyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys be mad cause other guys will be hitting up their girl but the boy will be hitting up other girls??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember Vinny Vella forever cc .@xtina @cafehabana sean remember?? https://t.co/saUVj5mguS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaosum @SarahEGeimer @tbemrose @mjgranger1 @IlhanMN Did anyone in this chain so far advocate Sharia Law? Must have missed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuttNation it is so cold and ugly outside but it sure is cute and warm inside! #MuttNationCollar #DeminAndLace… https://t.co/G0oikwuRrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! I am learning things.          #etiquette #thebachelor https://t.co/if0EoDrhIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ArianaGrande &amp; #TheBeatles have something in common. #iamup https://t.co/Ln1fosKPKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dayciajh I will be the first to say that I WILL go to jail for killing someone .]]></document><document><![CDATA[ria and i tryna be cute and play footsies but NOPE her feet are way too cold for that peace OUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[well now that my wedding dress arrived and is in my possession there is nothing stopping me from wearing it to all events and functions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAindex @MSill3 Please Lord and all the angels and saints be with all them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeritasLux2 @rbhowell2 @dbongino Exactly. Divided we fall. Who is promoting that narrative? That's what people nee… https://t.co/efaqRtgBvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[pretty coffee ☕️ and conversation with @thepreppypossum at @TheTableBakery! | #butfirstcoffee #thetablefarmbakery… https://t.co/bxAqO60jDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[hike day with my ladies and the poods 🐶💞👩‍👧‍👧 @ Runyon Canyon https://t.co/ecMBUvPfHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I struggle so much to go back to bed after at least 1feeding/pumping session a night. #momprobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @StercusAccidet and his beautiful bride Emily! #CheersToSears]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both dogs are cuddled close to me in bed right now. The only thing that would make this better is if @RickJLackey would come to bed too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He made me dig through the travel sized rejects like a damn peasant. He is a MONSTER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[POP DAT PUSSY!!! Pop it... pop it.. pop it...😂😂😂😂😂 @ Kew Gardens https://t.co/jWwyGGZrzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Independent The dumbing down of America has long been the goal  of the republicans! Control the masses with indoct… https://t.co/CX6z43Xl39]]></document><document><![CDATA[One touch of nature makes the whole world kin. William Shakespeare  #almostheaven #wvexplored #mywv @ Mingo, West V… https://t.co/QySWtJvIiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLKmakenup @realTylerZed @WoodysWife14 3 times ISIS bride should go to prison for a very long time. But if she com… https://t.co/HBuZK0QywV]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 Things to Do Before Baby Arrives: I'm beginning to really appreciate how close the girls... https://t.co/zP4xGmEPvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heck yeah! 😂 #gryffindorhouseforever  I got Professor McGonagall - Find out your Hogwarts teaching style! https://t.co/5a2sFaUXZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thevanisher (Or watch it all. I just LOVE his answer to her question.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I left work at 6 last night and returned to work at 4 this morning.   I feel like everything and nothing has changed all at the same time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 Been trying to figure that out myself. He has abandoned all Republican &amp; conservative ideals &amp; principles &amp; values.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna have a crush on someone so i can dramatically listen 2 goodnight moon by go radio every night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPTeamRafa @PPTeamItzel10 @polinesiosxlove @PPTeamCamila11 @PPTeamCataSk @PPTeamCarolina_ @PPTeamAlejand0r… https://t.co/Ca3MetAK6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#misrepresented I’m starting the series with the misrepresentation of female sexuality in art. To be clear, I’m spe… https://t.co/40lVh8d3CG]]></document><document><![CDATA[What. These wanna be socialist will take this country down  stupid stupid people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi my loves🥰 #TampaOutcall available 24/7🌇🌃 #TampaIncall only at certain times🤷🏻‍♀️ I travel all over Florida🤗 Hugs… https://t.co/8Jub7hWyZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BodaciousBeer @EgolfLeeann @KeenParts @keenparts2 @1844TomKeen Please Leeann.. NO duck lip pics!! Hahahaha right Bo??]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m actually lowkey worries bc ive had sudafed and nyquil and i’m still awake, still have a fever and still congested]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con lo eficientes que son... Esto va pa'rato. Cuantos muertos más necesitan?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmbc I would throw out the video games altogether and introduce this brat to some work]]></document><document><![CDATA[El que pega primero pega dos veces 😉  #ConferenciaDePrensa #EstadoAusente]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driftwood. #driftwood #driftwoodart #beach #oregon #oregoncoast #oregonexplored #taft #taftbeach #taftoregon… https://t.co/cZezZS5fDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just completed, “Day 49” of this incredible journey!! I’ve been embarking on a new adventure this year!!… https://t.co/ERZIhHkTGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChamberlainDr @Deb4Democracy @magi_jay @mkraju @GOPLeader True which also means you are just as subject to my opinion as I am yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mehdi_Khalaji Noone knows how others feel  and there is no one solution in this vast world,  one needs to take its own path to salvation]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a great conversation. If you haven’t listened to our podcast..why not ? I learn something new every time .… https://t.co/KRDpKnqRAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Southsi76833472 @RepKinzinger @RockfordPD What a woman decides is best for HER body is HER decision. Name one sing… https://t.co/TGqhRflKIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdFantasyLG @MikeMuscutt @CurleyWpd @lt_gray @FCSO_S6 @LivePDNation @JakeMorris186 @BradPeck14 @TJTavares3… https://t.co/ehpNa55OFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elevate your ring game with a gold cigar band. #solidgold #cigarband #diamond #sunstone⁣ @ Melissa Joy Manning Inc. https://t.co/H5CFM23YJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherkaj I’m going to Vegas on Tuesday will the weather be good driving 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Won 57-14!! So proud of my daughter and her team!! #proudmom #girlsbasketball https://t.co/YxclKpjUJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck, @APS_SarahSmith Great Debators! So excited for you all.  @carter_chiesa @SmithIntMedia @pointsbyPortee… https://t.co/OLjipstSNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverDov123 @KFearri @petergraigs @Bren_O1967 @MySwilly @ERKRadio2017 @TonyaRBlue1 @SunGodSevenBand Good Evening Veronica!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HartfordInsHub @buzzvaultHQ @upwardhartford Great to visit! Thank you for making us so welcome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got out of there with a bad reputation and mild ptsd, but better late than never]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly why is it so hard to find pants that fit me. I’m so over having short legs  THANKS RICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My very looong looong travel day through the snow and cancelled flights was all worth it 🥰 @ The Big Easy NC https://t.co/GoA1sKBWoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistamiller204 @MarciaMentor @joboaler @DavidENorman @Eric_McGuyer @jen_vanarsdale If anyone actually said that...… https://t.co/xajs07YW4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things keep changing with my dad’s health and I fucking hate it. We get good news one day, bad news the next, and t… https://t.co/9ohxW8Aji7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datsharpe @ajjordanphoto This person is so fake and such a kiss ass. Less than a year ago they were trying to suck… https://t.co/y4kRrq6Nwu]]></document></documents></author>