<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Here's my assessment of Kamala Harris comments to The Root about sex work https://t.co/RPGlFiti3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@langernutrition @HomegrownJoan @EatinAintCheat Finally, we see vocal critique of structural problems with a corp.… https://t.co/pAqUJnB3r7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaClackum @darreldrowland @BROADUS My mother worked at packard for 33 years and always bought GM.says she isn… https://t.co/ERcTTBb5uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain Interesting that you're spreading lies here by putting false words in the mouth of the Democratic party. And for shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markknoller @Cptnrwrpnts For absolutely NOTHING! The Silent Fart of the Deal. He failed 100%, here and abroad simu… https://t.co/K3XwXutQBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarinaDiamandis There is a middle ground between promoting a healthy lifestyle, fighting obesity and its dangers a… https://t.co/xNbX4oJVq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGHOMIESTONE Kazzy been saying this for like 2 years now smh everyone doing it might as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewLevine5 @FlaPanthers @Bokampers @racquelgoldy @ROARCorps WOW IM JEALOUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a long time that i’ve actually had a full 7 hours of sleep holy shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[and when you buy from SHE IN it takes up to 3 weeks to get it in the mail sometimes even wrong size and a lot of th… https://t.co/ifj9RIQB70]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if in spite of this you will not listen to me, then I will discipline you again sevenfold for your sins, https://t.co/DZ3951FVss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyCuse44 @OrangeFaithful @OttosArmy I go and root like crazy for the team.  Stand up.  Cheer.  Go nuts.   But if… https://t.co/rxlLCxuFQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mayydda @JoudiMallouhi https://t.co/B15qPB676V   Dont ask me why I just liked it so much and repeated it for 9 hours😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEOjobs @Routledge_MandC Pretty fond of this @routledgebooks title: https://t.co/7tL0RMgUUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop fucking with the stupid bitch that you’re fucking with cuz I’m bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOLLY.  guys.   it’s weird how often and expediently willful ignorance translates into racism and classism.   even… https://t.co/5Wskpui8pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a rainy or sunny, I love Disneyland!🏰 #NewProfilePic https://t.co/oWMIP9eHXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFergTurduson @Tgod_Oomg @guajirodejaronu @caitlinnowens I think someone else might need a visit from… https://t.co/xchC0eCQKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tara Hills CA Tue Mar 5th AM Forecast: TODAY Rain Hi 59 TONIGHT Chance Of T-Storm Lo 51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved working with @theyumyumfoodie and @kardeaskuisine on dinnertakesall !!! I can’t wait for you all to get to kn… https://t.co/PgZrz6G8H7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to complete the #MuellerInvestigation Join me in defending our democracy #ProtectTheInvestigation https://t.co/PXFXOOiFo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meghan_Trainor this video from your wedding is sooo beautiful. https://t.co/Av55FN68cn I love this song #MarryMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport so how is @realDonaldTrump morning starting off? Absolutely love your updates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCaroline21 I bought Tillamook Ice bars last night, I rarely get ice cream, but when I do, its typically in the winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis They are terrified of Christ. He sheds light on their wickedness. Evil hates the Light of Truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Zzz’s happening here at the Hendra Household with our new @HelixSleep mattress! Watch the entire vid on my YT… https://t.co/7dNTc4cjLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nawww I could just hear how your voice would sound to me based off of the punctuation you used and seeing your face… https://t.co/nvat7TAagv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amanda_Pleasexx Again not freaking out but especially if you have a fever you should think about seeing a doctor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is definitely something that deserves further unpacking. These assumptions directly impact African American Musl… https://t.co/eK4GOBoQLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing more satisfying then getting a flash of blood in your IV for a hard stick or after missing once 🙈🙌🏼 😬💉 #yay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlsinger @Bravewriting Absolutely agree with trump, but imagine the way a real female Bernie Sanders would be trea… https://t.co/z2RFZYSPek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @JoeBiden I've got friends and family all over the world and the general consensus is we have a MORON… https://t.co/TmvtlHdIst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day Break-up.  @QueensBarrios @DesisRisingUp https://t.co/cTIvgP8fRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the love of everything good and holy left in this world, think before you freaking speak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup I’m a bitch because I have standards and I love how everyone thinks I’m this huge whore because of what I post… https://t.co/qCCGEiRLoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistressOrochi Yuuuup. Luckily most of the people I have to get snippy with on Facebook aren’t people I know perso… https://t.co/ldR2gUPPW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marhearn @ZerlinaMaxwell I’ve been there. Rips your heart out but we found our ways to have a blast as well. I tre… https://t.co/XhtuwddePZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiulianaRancic A Star Is Born made me love @haibon_jared even more. I wanted to smoother him with love after seein… https://t.co/y0c5GoOAWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaltonFraizer @DemetriusHarmon Haha yes. You never hear song lyrics correctly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnkurMa15287277 I'm not frustrated. Your the one who started this argument.  It is not my culture that is at quest… https://t.co/1YPaPyTHxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Wrong Way” Yep, wrong way to plant trees. Guess what’s going to happen to these in a few years.  When tree-plantin… https://t.co/cPU60TOgU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@designskeleton @TheTwilightZone @JordanPeele @CBSAllAccess https://t.co/JjbMswQCd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you supposed to go back to work after an amazing vacation? How does that even work?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least your not superficial just afraid of death without reincarnating literally don’t need another life to repea… https://t.co/ndHN3vuUbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Audrey Kitch.. 🤘🏽🤭🖕 Justice has been served. Ppl! Always speak your truth no matter who the fuck tells you oth… https://t.co/tI5D0Rd0yG]]></document><document><![CDATA[As If! With @bridget_irish talking about Soviets, body politic, gaps and Olympia. What a great homecoming!!! sarali… https://t.co/pvGZJ0HNhl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Coachespoweringforward            For Autism #AutismhoopsShowusyourpin🧩💙🧩💙🧩💙🧩💙🧩🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mefeater Wow she’s absolutely stunning! I see why.... never mind 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday mal I can’t believe you are 20 but I love how close we have been over the years and hope we stay clo… https://t.co/Iet7oY3aQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Berger_INRI BOOM! VOILA! J’ai toujours dit que c’était un stratagème politique de maintenir les francophones unili… https://t.co/3tGyFM0ZOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[my irls deadass didn’t see how i said i’m bisexual they either had a feeling or they can’t read]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey all check out our bbq site! We have new products and right now through Monday we have a 10% off all across our… https://t.co/A2NQL5JaX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter. Happy Friday to you. Have an amazing day 🙂💜 https://t.co/RfzNwogloW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like that my #anxiousdog just responded to the thunderstorm noise with annoyance and not fear #progress #interruptedhernap]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is why the Lord says, “Turn to me now, while there is time. Give me your hearts. Come with fa…… https://t.co/2mxQ3yCwKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve already experienced hell. And it takes a hell of a lot more than someone like you to break me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valdezmj Puaj! Aca me alcanza y sobra con El olor en l ropa de la gente o el humo #weed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LostInEA My sister and I saw it tonight, first time for her, and she cries much easier than I do from movies. Exce… https://t.co/952Koc9LVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These ladies impressively up their A-game a little each year when it comes to prepping for their annual shoot with… https://t.co/bk18gAtZfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the expected snow storm Friday, cheer and dance teams will not be competing at the NCA contest in Grand Island.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a glorious snow day in DC! And the snowfall hasn't even peaked yet! (14&amp;U area) @capitalweather https://t.co/t9ci2sZYiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team WES #MCSDistheplace2B  #MCSDL3PD #TribeCalledWES ❤️ https://t.co/rQdR0dd4Zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[After that don't understand anything, please if you went to school I imagine know how to make a sentence that anybo… https://t.co/FQoRAO5xpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pritzker continues his pleas for bipartisanship as he moves his way through his speech, saying he has spent his fir… https://t.co/6tZ4Vz4HA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is making me crave #Disney! Looking forward to seeing Mickey and the Gang next week! @WaltDisneyWorld… https://t.co/YxA513UtsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter how hard I try I don’t think I’ll ever be as cute as my dog https://t.co/de3HwwAemd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkerSF I had a wonderful time! The marker is always a favorite. Thanks so much!🥂👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @GailBenzler @CaththeWineLady @ja2cook @DivaVinophile @TheSavvyChef1 @SteveKubota @cazj @Fiery01Red… https://t.co/gji3mqw9ZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a family Ocean STEM night you should be prepared for incredible fun! #problemsolvers #STEM… https://t.co/pLmiW47nVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DHHS blood testing program needs to be reopened to gather epidemiological data from people like @WendyENThomas… https://t.co/I6lRbNXKZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2711Mibeya @Tonia_kond @tj_hickey @SimySemsem @roberta_lanzoni @gabryluce @samahali70 @carolina_smal… https://t.co/cvQ0UaKR6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at FULTON COUNTY MEDICAL CENTER in McConnellsburg, PA https://t.co/K385fmtJox]]></document><document><![CDATA[#middlespoon #blackfret #mohawk #livemusic #austintexas #austin #livingeastatx @ Mohawk Austin https://t.co/GDb3Q3ZZ4c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choreo was abso-effinglutely 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥.. their passion in dancing ... their units keep getting better ...  #Jus2 🌴🌼… https://t.co/U4CmX6kuCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I told my boyfriend that his mad Windjammers skills is what attracted me to him. I’m so romantic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AIRPORT DRUG BUST! ANOTHER ONE!  Man busted trying to smuggle $200K worth of heroin into Atlanta airport -… https://t.co/VH1UmPl7qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Venezuela belongs to the people, not those who think they are powerful! #KeepFighting #KeepHoping #ThankYou to all… https://t.co/nHfTemLIHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump How much money and attention did you personally put towards women entrepreneurs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylezeppelin I meet people every day who aren’t traveling but  are picking up passengers, coming to ice skate, tak… https://t.co/DUxSPMVtjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaCAAlves Good morning Anna. Your words are so very true and wonderful! God bless you and all our friends. Have… https://t.co/GDhGFtl1Mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $50 Skype Gift Card Offer  Win $50 Skype Gift Card Offer By Your Email Id Submit,  Click Here:… https://t.co/oIoKhtuKFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can the president tell this brutal dictator he is a great leader? He is a murderer in his country of his own fa… https://t.co/6uilU9YGr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hates the after effects of a great day wine tasting, ugh why must I be wide awake at 4am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to realty this morning.  Vacation over and back on #ohio where it’s still #winter.  #iwanttogoback #beach… https://t.co/P8h0wPCguL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USEmbassyAddis I get a message that says the party I called is unavailable. Do you have a second telephone number? Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats K9 Eros. Hope you are getting stronger everyday and you are a true hero buddy. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE: I’m mad that if he would have waited for that car to pass, he would have had WAY more time to turn.  TWO: he i… https://t.co/O1b3RK5gJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are not all the episodes of #BeverlyHills90210 not on Hulu @hulu  I'm on season 2 and not all the episodes are there 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone has taken/understands Empirical Political Inquiry and would like to tutor me please lmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I survived what was probably the most stressful and fastest work day at ascend thus far - I need a celebratory drink #fuckmondays]]></document><document><![CDATA[so @ttripler21 just sent me a selfie of him Barzal and like all i can say is fuck bc Barzal has perfect brows and im STILL mad about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @GrantRyanxxx @LincolnTunnelXX @MMasonXXX @MarqDB @Pup_Amp @KristoferWeston @DJChiChiLaRue @mrPam… https://t.co/1B8E5BSbTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly I couldn’t contain my excitement meeting @christiantat2 @ Philadelphia Tattoo Arts Convention https://t.co/xQEncJgGm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[YFN Lucci (whatever the hell that means) is the perfect example of a grown ass man preying on an underaged girl. Isn’t Reginae like 19 ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT IS A DAY OF REST, IT’S NOT WEIRD OR GROSS FOR ME TO SLIGHTLY REPOSITION MYSELF SO I DONT LIE IN IT RATHER THAN J… https://t.co/lDeTDQo3e2]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my fave parts of #CapitanMarvel is hearing this song!! Yasss! @garbage por vida! ❤️ https://t.co/NzprxthIrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that #RussianDoll’s creators, writers and directors are ALL women is just the first reason you should watch it. It is incredible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Holiday Inn Express in Gettysburg...nice room! In town to visit long time friends...looking forward to some rela… https://t.co/owiHVbattF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj More Minimum Wage, Part Time Jobs than ever before in The American Work Force... That is not something to… https://t.co/J0BVvAxiHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok soo I took all my oro off last night and forgot to put it back on and I feel soo wierd without it]]></document></documents></author>