<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Getting up with Jon at 5:15, making his coffee and kissing him bye before work. Then going on the couch with a fuzz… https://t.co/oHGMZgNGjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[publix roasted chicken accompanied by a bunch of roasted vegs plus mashed cauliflower. Also prepped a frittata for… https://t.co/BLlkJKOiFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[the @jonasbrothers are spamming my instagram and twitter and I am living for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eyelash lace onesie from Amazon. #backinblack #iamcanadian #canadiangirlsrock #carriemoon @ Burlington, Ontario https://t.co/hJPVUUAnJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Century Park Place 20 And XD for Captain Marvel in Tucson, AZ https://t.co/udJpMeieBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and it just so happens to be kindness week! Way to go @JJWatt! All heroes don’t wear capes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Em pleno carnaval, eu em casa o dia todo sozinhaaaaa pq não posso sair lá fora por causa da neve 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you get mad at me cause YOUR nigga won’t leave ME alone lmfaoo wtf 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Just no words for the Republican party anymore.  #JohnCornynRESIGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentMcMillian @Folgers ...until your wife comes in and ruins it 😁🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_J_Rossi i am literally at a standstill with myself and i’m going insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darts (@ Cawley's Irish Pub in Upper Darby, PA) https://t.co/xFCzyIlESA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man straight up came into the office told us how he escaped from prison and he was on the news 3 years ago. NICE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still down and 2.5 hours to vote... Not thinking I can get a surge large enough for this victory sadly.  Who can he… https://t.co/uE9DVouuhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 Stanford University ~ AVID/Scholar Junior Trip 2019 🧡 @ScholarsOv @OV_AVID @OrangeVistaHS https://t.co/IMu6QkoGUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @andylassner @OhNoSheTwitnt @chrissyteigen @TheRickWilson @RadioFreeTom @JoyceWhiteVance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC The American people have a right to know if his personal finances conflict with his political position!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive faster. I have to pee. - #Ralphthepup #DogsofTwittter https://t.co/fxI0gmREko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day #Nashies @tessadebergh @SaraNesti84 @star_dreamer16 @Canadalovemusic @LoverMusic44… https://t.co/WQvLdvOVAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems like everyone accepts photography submissions until you start searching for a fit for a photography submission.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealChrisTweek @JennySoxgirl14 @grayeyesdontlie @GoPackGo2012 I don’t want to spend money haha I am saving for a new home. 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics @AP When your candidate has to win in order not to be charged with federal and state crimes you got so… https://t.co/8onL6ABaFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[St Edward Wins District Semi-Final 3/6/19  @sehsathletics @SEHS_BASKETBALL @CoachFlan @wearesteds @StEdBoosters… https://t.co/fUJHXEAeQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently eating my way through #Disneyland #Mickey90 celebration cake &amp; dinner at Naples. #Disneymagic… https://t.co/Eri4ngpu4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solodm_helper01 THANK YOU!! go follow them everyone❤️ https://t.co/luD0dnW1n3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelooooo Like it’s not going to defend itself when some random ass bitch jumps in its shit 😂 people kill me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janelle_2310 This is one of the best pictures of you. Ever. I appreciate you working it into the conversation as t… https://t.co/qjrYs8v3yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darlene0528 @MaryJo44966098 @Heevenlee @aluna721 @ItsADarcyThing @niterydr01 @KathyM1214 @lorriefencil… https://t.co/uQjdtBHwK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 years ago on this day I talked and saw my big sister for the last time 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right - no one wants to celebrate ANYONES SEX  or have a two year quandary where to go to the bathroom - just be wh… https://t.co/1G1nvQpGTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Supporting the declaration is supporting the jobs, health, safety and income of the American people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LoVe Makes the World Go around 💞#happyvalentinesday #enjoyyourday #spreadthelove @ EXIT Real Estate Solutions https://t.co/nQaKuqKkuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimfreethinker @DGPurser Spongebob is about all that’s happening here 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give you one guess who I am? #family #xmas #2011 #xmen https://t.co/3Nn1vnr4jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this #weather ☀️. It is a Cherry-Limeaide type of day!! #rockwall #texas sonicdrivein 💕 @ Rockwall, Texas https://t.co/Prkty9XDUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racial Literacy | A Small Group Session with Dr. Howard Stevenson. Thank you  Mutale Knonde for inviting me to this… https://t.co/E1Drxk0tKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethbauer75 I see this is from August  but love that color!!! Do you still have it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still not to a hotel, with less than helpful staff. Not sure I’d do that again #AmericanAirlines https://t.co/USYFPkSdw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#science #halideperovskites #LightBecomesElectricity #physics @WorldAndScience. @ScienceNews @sciencemagazine @NSF… https://t.co/mjgnFZWXVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jordyn could do that to kylie imagine what ur own “friends” would do behind your back lol.... it be ya own damn circle]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got called a country bumpkin tonight 😂😂 I don’t even know what that is lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This pops up after I tweet about TREX merch. I see you universe.  #meltedcheese 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey band... can I see this mystical picture of me playing basketball you got? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when this first came out me and my mom went to see it and afterwards she asked me “do you feel like Cora… https://t.co/EFwNWGZAMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how everybody was asleep on me a couple years ago and now everybody wanna fw Kisha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grinding, Growning and Glowing  #growning #glowing #grinding #realestate #realestateagent #exitcommunityrealty @ In… https://t.co/Kophxo0X1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my learn on at the Google Certified Trainer Bootcamp in Alabama with @edtechteam! If you can dream it, you… https://t.co/sJ8Fg5vMuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackInFullSwin1 Khloe had zero issue getting with him when he was another girlfriend, who was pregnant! How you ge… https://t.co/VHH4fWNuuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HauntedFairy13 @OhMyMithrandir Precisely. I mean no one seems to take a chance on Mexican Americans in entertainme… https://t.co/veqHkjUWY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke 6:37 - Judge not, and ye shall not be judged: condemn not, and ye shall not be condemned: forgive, and ye shal… https://t.co/i630hVKSpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and most super hero movies.  #AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kindercolts get ready for a great week!!!  See you Monday😊. @MiddleCreekES https://t.co/Kla64Kw5Qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Province of Alberta: Demand A Full Forensic Audit of Hillview Park Condo Disaster - Sign the Petition!… https://t.co/fJSgKSnPR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skepteis @TheCowboyCDN Anything outside the norm for people is “a strange place”, no?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxmackattack @ABC He ONLY gave up his phone after police subpoenaed him,5days after the attack...any phone eviden… https://t.co/ynmzHUyhUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[those of us in #California voted for this last Nov. but who knows when it will happen — so irritating and useless t… https://t.co/soGiz5G9xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are suppose to park behind a certain point at work so the customers can have the best parking but...fuck them customers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call us today and ask us how we save our clients money every month and help them #grow their #business by 2-4X with… https://t.co/Z2G4cE5CQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw the reports of severe weather all day but none said lee county til they mentioned 14 dead last night. I immed… https://t.co/fQf75u1Px8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s good to visualize yourself saying key phrases in public before your speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join me in  Letting CBP know Americans want  them to Demand A Boarder Security Wall..NOW..no more talks, no… https://t.co/WSforJmHSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnfieldPlug @red_devil_099 @SophRicho Hope it was filled with piss 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[#brrrrr bundle up #monday #inwx #4yourmorning @CBS4Indy https://t.co/l6aNQPoPGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @dpletka Sort of like they didn’t accept the 2016 election and had a meltdown like a bunch of toddlers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $40 Rush tickets for @HelloDollyBway starring Betty Buckley at @shnsf on @TodayTix! Tap to get them too:… https://t.co/MsUJ3CorT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week at RSA has been so busy that I haven’t even glanced at the program, but I just found out Tina Fey is keyn… https://t.co/F5QP5UCQCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many cute boys in the airport right now. Too bad I look like an actual potato 🥔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are the separating parents from their babies? Even given caregivers,which is at question,the seperation anxiety… https://t.co/kIhrgxzfJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Porch Swing Angel by @MuscadineBLine will always be a bop AND will forever hit me in a different way than any other song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to everyone wrestling in districts @ Rowan College at Gloucester County. Come ready to wrestle your VERY BEST!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gribbzley We definitely have red bull Italian sodas in Ellensburg. Lol - Barista in Ellensburg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did anyone really care about The Oscars last night? I didn't! Tired of all the BS!  Hollywood needs to get over themselves!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cute photo of AD and LeBron has whipped fans into a frenzy 😍  https://t.co/0c7ViCBhKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been listening to Green Day radio on Spotify constantly the past two days. 🤷‍♀️ CC: @AliMahowald]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephens made the decision to cancel @citizenjanefilm. But we won’t let it be forgotten. #IfNotForCJ, I wouldn’t ha… https://t.co/AEljO3l0Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Elway is getting dragged on Twitter for Joe Flacco trade https://t.co/wv7QfYBXSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman Really?  Because you know your team has children locked in cages, separated from their families… https://t.co/6z0nJc0hdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsCreekHS JV Girls Soccer up 1-0 over Chattahoochee! Way to go #JCHSGladiators @jcgladiators @JCHSVGS @LeadGladiator #DareToBeGreat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyBethCombs At this point, sadly she’s probably right. Impeachment wouldn’t necessarily remove him from office bu… https://t.co/6pgFcf8vxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried calling my dad and this is his busy message that sends and I just want to know why it’s so extra?? https://t.co/VVI276xJNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leopold_N14 Do you have a digital copy of the cartoon? I’m doing the strikes next Wednesday and would love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_doc_911 @jawbrea24031485 is Jacob Wohl's new profile. He's not taking the ban very seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She had 2 1/2 hour practice then 2 hours of open gym plus gymnastics on the beach for 2 hours... but she keeps work… https://t.co/J134HvAs2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorJohnHagee I'm so sorry but I need to inform you that there's someone pretending to be you on Instagram named… https://t.co/kqpBTedXVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[bout to start working 6 days a week and I just know imma be a old lady 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaBoy17thAve @daintyviolet no, you blame the person who cheated. if the guy cheats its his fault not the girl he c… https://t.co/uY1D3TZiJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/qxAkyzhomr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching GUHH and Eazy-E’s son Eric Jr. sounds so much like him and honestly, I’m turned on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelledemilt @ShefaniStan @NBCTheVoice Nice job, and such a handsome client!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorConnorP Oh dear, sending you all kinds of hugs - but if you don’t like hugs I won’t force them on you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s sayin n yep y’all made my corny ass famous too. So who is to blame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Jacket Symphony at the ASO: QUEEN Night at the Opera. 😄 @ Atlanta Symphony Hall LIVE https://t.co/tv99myQcbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heck yeah, Ive never seen @Daniel_SuarezG mad like that, but if someone grabbed my throat... Id throw punches too.… https://t.co/geUFMczCgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate it when you have to answer a question by over explaining it instead of just giving the simple two to three s… https://t.co/wID3IzRpkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Sometime soon Biden is going to get into the presidential race. And on the day he does, he will become… https://t.co/5u1A3pjdxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt I went and checked it out.  Left a 👍. It’s a good song with such a happy vibe. ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@histoftech Explain Everything (I’m most familiar with this on iPad but I believe you can use it on Mac) can do wha… https://t.co/nUOd0Pflk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is the only official comment i am prepared to make about the jonas brothers' comeback at this time https://t.co/kWyDp5n9pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garrett88dfs @KingJames Allowing the Zions of the world to go pro doesn’t change the fact that some players who do… https://t.co/W9OxZsDzNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigos twitteros me urge alguien que me quiera cambiar dos 6A por dos 5A 😭 no puedo permanecer tanto tiempo de pie, parfavaaar]]></document></documents></author>