<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I love hard... there is a lot of people that I still love but should’ve slapped the shit out of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Elsa. Or whatever her name is?!” @tomkeene @bsurveillance @BloombergRadio   @ptsweeney .. (and @Disney ) I ask, is… https://t.co/dQbic7oYC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Bernie don't waste your money.  Oh wait...not your money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raquel Welch - Bang Bang (My Baby Shot Me Down) https://t.co/BcdiIg04dT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[And who pays for it US THE TAXPAYERS there’s plenty of jobs out there tell them to go get one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Stop voting and appointing these white collar judges letting these people get away with defrauding the USA and… https://t.co/iUUMIVkiyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1027KIISFM @jonasbrothers dear lord please let me win these or i will cry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshtpm This is the type of guy responsible for putting the “wo”(e) in woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I bought a fish bowl for $70 and my coworker said “you can suck my ass for $70” and that’s literally all… https://t.co/csvvGNafyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWD2019 @compassion. I learn just how amazing through sponsorship and celebrate her every accomplishment. https://t.co/fIhVbMdioc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicious_Skulls @JamesCraigmyle @SOMissouri @oakley I have the Fila socks lol I don’t but my shoes here lol I actua… https://t.co/8Gf4XUPMH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise @SebGorka It is clear Nancy Pelosi cannot handle the responsibilities of Speaker of the House.  She i… https://t.co/0GcZQLa96l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Leavenworth Whistling Pig Hefeweizen by @FishBrewing @ The Woodlands Pizza — https://t.co/uPYysaAyie]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is just rude when someone else is speaking but don’t want anyone to interrupt her #theview]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why don’t you go build the wall yourself then bitch. You want it so damn much. All you do is sit and talk shit and… https://t.co/VZCTVQXWa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberpunkisdead We could honestly do it for p cheap. It would at least be interesting to try even if it’s just for… https://t.co/eqRbhdspNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow being around people that genuinely care about you and don’t have any fucked up ulterior motives or are just usi… https://t.co/PKQOi9NDLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckjason What should we expect as Reds fans with the Iglesias signing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very curious- @Pharrell  would it be normal for young boys to be recruited to have sleepovers at your house? Same q… https://t.co/lFYrvdzyh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@discountcompost And as you said I’m sure there are more creative applications of that system. I wanted to let you… https://t.co/frDdoGSIqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating "pitches" to share our passion topics and give us direction before starting research. @plumcreekelem… https://t.co/9STefAbnhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am by no means a twig so the fact that this Lubbock wind can move ME while I’m trying to walk on campus is honestly so rude]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to take a break!   Be safe, get rest, connect with nature, fill your soul, have fun - see you in a week, ALCDS… https://t.co/YudHuWowCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: #SnowMageddon2019 #PolarVortex2019 and applying for #ADE2019 gave me time and space to play and reflect within… https://t.co/XqGFKRLCwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women will always be pitted against each other.  What is disheartening about the DoS is she has been a member of th… https://t.co/kTNj5SNdzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I listen to I forgot you by @thisisphangs I feel like an astronaut stepping out of a spaceship onto the moon I… https://t.co/HNu8XF9Q1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s losing a fortune you asshole!   And where are you getting the roubles to keep it running? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will Michael Scott score an Oscar for writing the screenplay of Michael Scarn though #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently kicking myself for not sticking to my coconut oil after my sunburn...of COURSE it would be more hydating than anything else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonbonmonkey672 @LisaVS49 @Mistybucketlist @Brandyputerbau1 @DonnaLaCroix6 @rhondacrain4 @_____dclynch_… https://t.co/Xc37Bwx9OP]]></document><document><![CDATA[random but i love my man so much and i just can’t believe we’re goin on almost two years now :’) blessed to have so… https://t.co/FTqhOsBEqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jnana Mudra 👌🏻 Samadhi { Sam “united with” A “toward” Dhi “to hold” } 🌞🌕 In meditation when Samadhi is reached, the… https://t.co/s0FGHwVbuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ya_boi_spooky @chance_charming i knew u would see it either way and i deserve to speak out bc you almost got me killed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Countdown to @HeartOfTXCPSO @IDODI Award Ceremony! https://t.co/Xv0ANCiz20]]></document><document><![CDATA[A special on-stage opportunity for St. Mike’s students https://t.co/fxheu0KTEY @StMikesCSS @HPCDSB So inspiring! 💙💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my work and my life, you are my best support 😊😍🐶🐾   #LoveYourPetDay #dogs #BabyDuarte #dogslife #dogsarelove https://t.co/9u7rXf2Cad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I speak to people for free. That’s my choice though. Like, I am arranging that right now, for a group in the states… https://t.co/plbD4hExan]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MGEllis loves Ms. Mitchell. In the afternoons, you can find her using #LLI to help her students grow as readers.… https://t.co/tlXr4T38t0]]></document><document><![CDATA[People having sex in the bathroom at the bar and it’s not even 7 pm.. yep I’m back in baltimore 🤗 #charmcity #whybelesswhenyoucanBMORE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RasnawatiR @Ariatnachantal @Lunarteddy @Jonatha97947998 @AngelosOnassis @malucadua @mabel_carrera @AintitMarvelous… https://t.co/rlGXcL69Qa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selena - Como La Flor (Live From Astrodome) https://t.co/7kjBg8TqpJ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business explains why all Texas mid-rises look the same https://t.co/Ngcg95836W]]></document><document><![CDATA[These kids I just had on #musicalmusings were so good I am at a loss for words. It's hard to find millennials that… https://t.co/ukJxwMHflp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Behind the bar tonight for Happy Hour! 2-4-1 Drafts, Wells, and (house)Wines. Come celebrate… https://t.co/donhxzQjyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carribeanblue #bahamas 🏝 @ Paradise Island Bahamas https://t.co/toW5OTCRgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D57Mamie @ShirtJack Acknowledging you need help is the first step. I’m proud of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that everybody doesn’t know what I’m doing constantly. If you’re my family or a true friend then of course y… https://t.co/mARgFu43A1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tonykelly950 @CommonsCMS Precisely why @CommonsCMS is on point about Zuck's recent "Privacy" messaging [PR tactics… https://t.co/cHpbA9m1BF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was the worst day ever &amp; now I can’t sleeeeep😭 fuck my life😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @sarahkendzior @CNN I just don’t understand it. It’s not like there is a shortage of good talent or any… https://t.co/z1qN17IbuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt cute feat. my messy room and favorite pup. #selfie #mirrorselfie #ootd @ Minnesota https://t.co/xNRobm9ZOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FernandoPinna1 @opropriolavo @jairbolsonaro Pq não mostra sua cara? É mais um ilegal aqui? A Flórida foi sempre re… https://t.co/m71PIwNRYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Alison Ledbetter with Republic Title for lunch! And thanks to Tyler Street Christian Academy coming to sh… https://t.co/9tFW6RO773]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maximize vertical space in your pantry by double-stacking canned goods. Also, repurpose glass jars to hold staples… https://t.co/lRhZNq7QGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Houston plays Southwind tonight for the District 15 AAA Tournament Championship at Colliervile High School. I’m there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Planned Parenthood purging staffers linked to body parts scandal https://t.co/5rzQR9iHgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @IvankaTrump If people don’t know it by now, I’m going to wonder what rock they’ve been under! Just like daddy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any of my pup, cat, or horse friends can spare $5 or $10 to keep me from turning my beloved cat over to a shelte… https://t.co/0YrDGjivvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total BS. If Bernie believes that Carbon emissions are killing us he can fly on our public planes rather than his p… https://t.co/bjHkgcM7hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiCommieSoc @LambNathan @DeseretDagger @BasedFaith1776 @epicgeezr @McconneyMichael Telling the truth isn't harassment remember?]]></document><document><![CDATA[finally got my apple music back after not having it since november and now my heart is complete]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mallory Pugh has been seriously bad as of late. Wonder if it’s too much pressure. Horan or Press should be playing. #USAvENG #USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When you break up with him and literally get 3 can openers” what now bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BOWt_loc152 @iAintSh1t That’s when you get to slippin’ &amp; bust ya head wide open]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGSBookclub @EmersonBarrett Trust me room looks like mini tornado hit it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all  please don’t let this life pass you by without having something to show for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supportingbeamu We are supposed to be getting one but theres alot of drama going on with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pink shirt day with my youngest 2 kiddos 😀 #PinkShirtDay2019 https://t.co/X5ZxTRuXUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cuz I know theres nothing in life I cant get doesnt make me cocky. I was raised on knowing good work ethic mak… https://t.co/fmZtOzhXWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Randysummit1 @bigredwavenow We thank God for you cuz you are just as special to us as any one of us. Most all of u… https://t.co/GPxgFI92a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joseantoniokast @mbachelet Igualmente que la subsecretaria de prevencion del delito!.$122 mil millones asignados q… https://t.co/WMD4J93ixl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiliaultFrance @praecipice @elivalley @MeghanMcCain Please provide legit sources citing mass numbers of Israelis a… https://t.co/rKye6ZuCOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU are the true ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE. You are the disaster and your presidency is a blot on our hi… https://t.co/DfLg62p0WH]]></document><document><![CDATA[W5D4 and after stressing about this run all week, I totally knocked it out of the park. It was tough but felt SO da… https://t.co/mzCR9v7olF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franktisellano @dr_bitchface Oh Frank, thanks for confirming the lasting effects of the c18 novel 💕💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last call for the Jimmy Fund! Thank you to everyone who has helped me so far in supporting their life-saving missio… https://t.co/Nk634aXvPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSOPIO @NationalSheriff @GoodNewsCops @GoodCopStories @FLSheriffs @MelissaBujeda @BlueWalkPoconos @propacop… https://t.co/p5GanFuQQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Apartments cost more than our salary.  That’s a national emergency 🚨.  #livingwage https://t.co/V5oBhL1Ce3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueWolf2001 @StopBadDocs @headdock @LelenaPeacock @Katamac1967 @pleasure_ryland @shelley_bean60 @AuntTritsy… https://t.co/1GvN02Oybo]]></document><document><![CDATA[IranFM Zarif’s post on Insta, coincided with Mother’s Day in Iran. “I'm very grateful to the dear and honorable Ira… https://t.co/TJuUFYNFkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, 3-5 business days for a debit card??? What am I gonna eat for a week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people call you to say they've loved three of your articles and wanted to let you know you're doing a great jo… https://t.co/VWxcN4d8MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So josh has picked up my lingo and every time he uses it I just get so happy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockfordPD will host another press conference shortly. This comes after we learn McHenry Co. deputy Jake Keltner h… https://t.co/js0rjMH3cJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could they also please tell us what, if anything, is right with him?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fahrenheitpress Was it in BST? Just got home from the bar exam and was gonna order @JoPerryAuthor's… https://t.co/zvssKurBoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Winthrop Ramblers took it to Hall-Dale in a manner not many expected Saturday night. The victory advances Winth… https://t.co/TuWPyAMEIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepressbox_phs Absolutely unbelievable!! After winning their State Championship some of our @pilgrim_cheer drove… https://t.co/eyE8PIt0Jg]]></document><document><![CDATA[i miss waking up saturday mornings and being the first of my friends to hop on xbox. hear the bu-dunk noise and ins… https://t.co/u1tSwHJxMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving this presentation by @mfannie #WSMI I am so engaged!!! https://t.co/gAIeDn6x2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JassyCorreia was last seen at a Boston nightclub Saturday night. Police say 32-year-old Louis D. Coleman III of Pr… https://t.co/LZgcv3HS5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gum, energy bars, and almonds. Rain or shine or snow, I’m prepared with the snacks (and if not, I could live for da… https://t.co/wms04pKxom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawaiigoff for getting my start with writing. My Critics Academy girls @Maximinalist @devikagirgayi @tylrmntg… https://t.co/iWTMtJWQHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/gNNQ1MpNZA « On ne peut pas être contre la vertu, mais on voudrait que les innovations entrent dans le… https://t.co/pokc9tvHae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister And their parents their home life what’s going on there? I hope this video ruins their life for futu… https://t.co/w6XexCIEMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindness, understanding and acceptance are so important these days.  These kids get it... why can’t we?  A shepherd… https://t.co/6vD57Z1s6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennysDiner what’s the point of the special instructions section on your mobile ordering app if you aren’t going t… https://t.co/C7jJlUdYh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have a joke for this but the twee neolib luggage company that sponsors what feels like every single podcast… https://t.co/jBT76MpkWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DahlbergJeff @TheBrentSmith @verified @mshollyweird @MaryjoSpillane @SPMediaAZ @ZMyersOfficial And this one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is Abe Lincoln’s bday and one time in 8th grade I dressed up as him and thought y’all should know, so please… https://t.co/rGZeIs71SH]]></document></documents></author>