<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Did John Wayne say some unforgivably bad things in 1971? Of course  Is anyone really surprised based on what we've… https://t.co/y7Aq5VgiyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[35 weeks until worlds. You haven’t seen anything yet. https://t.co/rXrb6dXrKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Outrageous.  Do Something Congress!  Senate Intel Chief Covered for Trump While Russia Attacked 2016 Election… https://t.co/SX3gyNJteD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up @mcompton428 Trains a Dragon..stand and deliver... plus #free @Wendys breakfast and more! Tune in! #radio… https://t.co/UwtF5cqq6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is president for 1/3 country... when he says enemy of people, it’s his people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopeAjao Two hers facing each other in the mirror..who looks Better..ONE HERE THE OTHER THERE: Turn the other Glas… https://t.co/x0VkJ1uLmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanessabcalder That is a good point. There may be a threshold above which attracts disproportionate attention and… https://t.co/icCf0hfqB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful day meeting the Bishop of Youngstown ✝️🙏🏻 @ Saint Josephs Catholic Church https://t.co/DRpBrMXfVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before y’all automatically vote for Bernie, you might want to wait and see who his running mate is cause there is a… https://t.co/c9zfCr9w6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MikeSinde and the @GBSEngineering staff and students for welcoming me today. I am so impressed with your… https://t.co/VyvY8JTSq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine thinking everything in life is free just to get thrown in jail for breaking laws you think you’re above]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaitlin_Benz @rosegoldmarbles I’m like 99% sure unpaid internships Are illegal in nyc ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto Emergency was to   get him to the golf course and away from work! Now he will “putter’ around!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I jus remembered I saw Appleseed cast this year and it was good I dude really teared up for no reason lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickyDavilaH Esta es la guerra que continúa gracias a ya saben quien 🏴‍☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is ABJECT FRAUD.  The TOM trial has been proven as BUNK and yet the clinical community still pushes this trash… https://t.co/R42opUGlSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyGirlMTL @UnicornFor3some That place looks magical. https://t.co/yQxDQfPNsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEBBallRankings Just went through my video they ruled it a 2...made it 9-0 then 3 point play after that made it 12-0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont belive in Twitter polls. Specially cuz I be voting for anything I come across even if I dont know shit about the subject 😂.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skylxxxr i was so close to stabbing that fucker i for real saw a flash of red but then he let hot of car door and backed off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Well ... looks like someone got up early to start executive time. Rough night of tossing and turning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmycthatsme That’s what’s up, that’s what I’m watching tonight, I’ll get the popcorn ready now...wait no, I’ll w… https://t.co/IvHm5C1R6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGolfpro @FootJoy No golf ⛳️ up here in Norton MA, only snow covered ground and more coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miguelsolo611 @emirboscatto @_AntonioMiracle @Menatplaycom @CarterDaneNews @Pollas_lefa2 @HotMaleStuds @JRLCHARTS… https://t.co/BsOBDHJflm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatMoranTweets What about Chance Womack? He be a great addition to our interior. Be an immediate upgrade from Vlad and Miller]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronTanFB @49ersInsiders Well, doesn’t that take the cake?!  Bears: “You’re cut. GTFOH.”  Gould: (After bouncing… https://t.co/WaelpmqVxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Arrival Colorway @NewBalance Women’s 860v9 @OnTheRunShoes. #Me 👉🏽😂✌🏽🐦 @Sixp8ck - 📷📹 #ShreddedBeyondABSolute… https://t.co/KkBi8SHb6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well Spider-Man is the most famous and most profitable superhero so, yeah, he’s gonna always be around...   and peo… https://t.co/r82AiBgAzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[metric put on a killer show! Thrilled to share it with @fiercestories #lasvegas #idontwanttoleave @ The Chelsea https://t.co/Tum7Jxks6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes And how do you purpose we get the rest of the world on board with your national emergency?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you eat a worm to impress your crush? I voted No on Talking Dead. What's your vote? https://t.co/w9xQb7JTsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And those that can remember, how dismemberment works?.... @ Uptown - Carrollton, New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/QDREXF27Kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noelle of @PawsintheCity at our adoption event yesterday at @potterybarn! She is an Irish Terrier mix, 2 yrs old, 4… https://t.co/KcOwZpqLy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT So I trusted this guy with everything for a decade but he’s the most untrustworthy guy ever - that is the President’s logic...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F_Reyes415 My sister just went through this. Dang - get better. Warriors not doing too well right now either]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keepin’ the rubberside down (@ Harley-Davidson of Palm Beach in West Palm Beach, FL) https://t.co/q98ny3Qcrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played capture the ball in track today. Probably the best start to the weekend you can have]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM Authority: Cadillac Discounts For 2019 XT5 Insignificant In February 2019. https://t.co/NU9s9PvDAO  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nebo333 @SethAMandel 100% criticism of Israel (legitimate, fair and harsh) is on the table. But this is about a Co… https://t.co/Cnwv9HnGeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone remember having to pay for sports scores? like instead of the ESPN ticker at the bottom, it’d give you… https://t.co/goLBwDPdHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen in the crowd, a man who got  @StationCDRKelly and @ShuttleCDRKelly to sign his 2001 baseball today, the baseba… https://t.co/3qofYVlzRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its so interesting listening to presenters, who are teachers, reinforce the idea that coding does not replace curri… https://t.co/yctK8HFMNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got challenged by @boxcar_sarah on the "no explanation 7 books I love game" , here's book the first! I guess I’m go… https://t.co/PfKX8J17q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lizallison28 Such a wonderful and blessed family!!! Davey will always be shining down on you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefCovfefe @DirkSchwenk @thistallawkgirl @MollyJongFast @williamlegate @krassenstein   Tweet below is myself at… https://t.co/Qj6QvJhNmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GChlupsa @JudgeJeanine @robsmithonline “Judge” Jeanine should have her employment contract terminated, you’re right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialPDPNig is a party from hell and they will return to hell where they belong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Valentine gift ever gracias gandycvz en Santiago, Nuevo Leon https://t.co/oNNO62Glck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harrison Barnes lost all his strength on that nudge by Paul George. Weak offensive foul call by the refs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current Readings :  2/25/19, 17:23:01 PM Deg: 71.6°F R.H.: 49.6% H.I: 70.7°F D.P.: 51.8°F S.P.: 30.27inHg D.A.: 589ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffanywctv @WCTV I would try it, but I would like to find out if something is wrong with your items, who do you go to???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Shelby, NC? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/mXN8fR9Zhz #storemanager]]></document><document><![CDATA[HS Boys BB Tournament score after 1 quarter #MansfieldSenior 19 #Vermilion 17;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yarotrof @BuzzFeedBen Proof of life and proof of abuse all wrapped up in one video]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tombradyyisgoat They are aliens from an evil planet. Run. Run far.  That are relentless.  Evil Sucubi. https://t.co/2z3hN4PmeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manhattan from top of the rock 🗽🗺 #newyork #nyc #hudsonriver #travel #instagood #photooftheday #amazing… https://t.co/8ybfxzKVhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenHargis Luther is good. If wild is what your looking for try abducted in plain sight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#captainmarvel ❤ has triumphed at the box office, raking in $646 million globally in its first weekend. https://t.co/ruFGvVZSHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at Jimmy's Famous Seafood, live band karaoke featuring Space Taco with special guest drummer Justin Kruger… https://t.co/SCd25jyhq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoCoGovExec now testifies in support of a Prescription Drug Affordability Board. #mdga19 #MDpolitics @WashInformer https://t.co/ztN3QER0pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorainePoulain Pues si, siempre hay que tener apertura para muchos temas]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/C3mE0P2xRM where #networking is different. #smallbusiness #SanDiego #b2c #California #america… https://t.co/QDGXVdEBa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if Trump had paid out hush money with taxpayer money instead of campaign money.  Would that be a big deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFlashGordonMMA He might have some kind of neurological damage or something. WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally saw Catwalk and seeing Oh La La was life changing. https://t.co/STYBiKynwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[His emergency was that he is sick of playing "president," and needed time with "his people." He actually thinks the… https://t.co/iKvC5QfjDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dacornerman @chubbinatub I have no idea what you’re asking in this tweet, or is it more of a statement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus was a friend of sinners only the hypocrites tried to kill him not the sinners]]></document><document><![CDATA[The surgery was performed by Dr. Douglas Freedberg and involved a chondroplasty procedure to Herrmann’s central tro… https://t.co/g30TzKypIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frauleinaubrey You can do this! Just make sure you give yourself extra time to get through security and find your gate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giving new meaning to highlights inside our @IMGAudio offices today?  Dude looks familiar.  #HereComesDuke 🔵😈 https://t.co/xBtG7o1I3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took some off of the cad trade lock in some profit. https://t.co/xk3Kf2k2Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not know you.  I just know you came before.  Please eat less fiber.   Port-a-potty-haiku, Riverside, 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @mkzatx I’m surprised he could string that many words together. How is the weather in Utah?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAROLYNPECK  it made a good story during the Auburn game, but Kayla Wells was not the backup for Anriel Howard las… https://t.co/5y9x2kMuZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyTidwell @Slasher I’m not really apologizing for the opinion itself, just how a couple of my responses came o… https://t.co/65eMJR2LJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnotfacePromise @SVogt1229 @raudelwilson Haha oh if I get the chance to you already know I'll take a photo as I AL… https://t.co/4oAkrnseVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTfue I’m sorry u hope u feel better man I know how it feels to b depressed I suffer from depression myself if it… https://t.co/bvMUDmwVqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @perlmutations No worries @RepAdamSchiff words out that when @realdonaldtrump or one of his @GOP cro… https://t.co/rPWl3iW1xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @peterhook, looking forward to seeing you again when you play here in So Cal at the @wiltern theater… https://t.co/31xEsNfnkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA’s freedom dividend policy seems like a strong step in the right direction. Are any other 2020 candid… https://t.co/7yKlxfrwoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police in Canada are tracking people’s ‘negative’ behavior in a ‘risk’ database https://t.co/YbcHSRY12R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristapsThe3rd @ScottyV811 @TheRightMelissa @charliekirk11 Yeah, calling folks you disagree with a “virus” isn’t… https://t.co/qqhTI9QHvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have (1) ticket to THE LEHMAN TRILOGY at Park Avenue Armory that I need to sell. 3/26 at 7pm. Seat E-3. Asking what I paid - $82 OBO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMMOCOLLECTORR @ScottDocPinkham @trumpAngel45 @DLeighAlexander @shell0131 @my3monkees @Freedom2713 @susan_giannini… https://t.co/ddWGSTxvV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivilLost @tribelaw Um that's the dumbest question ever.   It's the foundation of our great country, puts checks a… https://t.co/mfEyczUbKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @michellemalkin @Ilhan @RashidaTlaib @SarahPalinUSA @realDonaldTrump They got rich off of us tax pay… https://t.co/XVNtilawGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC It's not as blind as the system you and your friends have used to prosecute innocent people without a trial. Y… https://t.co/kcSGjMgEEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MortalKombat #JohnnyCage with his own action figure! https://t.co/UxNWtgBrFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride on Chris! Thank you sir for your business!  #harleydavidson #kentucky #roadglide @ Man O' War Harley-davidson https://t.co/aawstH6ayW]]></document><document><![CDATA[People talking shit about Bernie running and how he won’t win, but his campaign earned over 1 million in less than… https://t.co/DngaC42J04]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Clinical Psychologist - https://t.co/QkEnRUMAr9 #Springfield, MA #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Oldham ability to get offensive rebounds and the fact South can’t stop turning the ball over is keeping North… https://t.co/4xHBATuNwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroyMauriello Huh? He abandoned their team. Left a very capable core without a big man. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what time it is! Take what’s yours Gorillas! @GorillasTrack #tradition #MBC #OAGAAG https://t.co/IlNCDwj3y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BASED_GOSH I'm not a cop but this is a friendly warning you're approaching your weekly allotment of allowable thirst traps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS UNTILL U PASS YOUR OWN BUDGET U CAN'T CUT FEDERAL MONIES FROM THE SANCTUARY STATES CITIES PLANNED PARENTHOOD ECT!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here it is!! My new 2019 #planbsupplyco Competition Mod Stacked 18650 kit!! I am very happy to finally have a stack… https://t.co/i31jLDUq06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gators get a 2-out walk, but nothing other than that. Still a goose-egg in that second column on the scoreboard.  M5 — USF 3 - UF 0]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s sweet but a little bit psycho, grab a cop gun kinda crazy 😜   #crazywhiteboy #sweetbutpsycho @ Kansas City, Mi… https://t.co/yNlOGYhxIR]]></document></documents></author>