<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[ᗷᗩE ᗩᖇEᗩ 🇨🇦 I Model Management, IM2 📷 Proda Photography #model #curvemodel #curves #photoshoot #imodelmanagement… https://t.co/ZR6FQprWo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mario__Bones ohhh forgot to respond to that! You shouldn't kick girls Josh 😁💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@hotwireglobal Laura Macdonald talking #genalpha at #In2SummitNA https://t.co/65FvibZ0IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@staceymeis @RealKyleMorris Yep! A patriot that is Saving America??? Yeppers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you meme I can’t tag Tabor College in this because they blocked me??? 😂😂😂 https://t.co/vGjNEuIoX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social protection is not a cost but an investment which is a fundamental part of the Decent Job Agenda and a precon… https://t.co/tvmhvr1uGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quaddogsquad My beagle loved to be under the covers. He would steal a blanket of you left it for a second. He owned them all eventually 🐶 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve hit the stage where instead of drunk texting exes, I drunk text my roommate to let her know how much I love her]]></document><document><![CDATA[saw/heard @brother_moses for the first time tonight and I’m hooked, boy am I HOOKeD 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein In Canada we call a complete jerk like Trump @fordnation .  Let's hope HERE at least he learns corrup… https://t.co/da7ssd3f8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ten30ninety4 girl that was the fse ever. i cannot believe you remember that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burkholderia Cepacia Complex https://t.co/EwnXIk5sWl via @cf_foundation #cureCF #cysticfibrosis 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeyjcox @TheVandals I feel like his arms are more limber than his lower half. But yes, agreed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopherGrace Nooo not the Cookies! They better replace it with an Insomnia Cookies!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisvanderveen @9NEWS There have been many sexual assaults in nursing homes. You can check on line by checking th… https://t.co/GyDPbbxUDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of the Queen of Hearts' garden. .. #AliceinWonderland #frankoz @ Salinas, California https://t.co/wFgwZUul1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dokta_foth @jeannefisher17 @DanielBRichard @Hazel_River12 @cinbashaw @akach5 @ecclesias @FredFriendly7… https://t.co/eQEmH7Cj8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do ya think there is another list of journalists that Trump considers dangerous that work in the White House now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[But also with the difference that these approaches, done right, actually also engage and empower the person. Many a… https://t.co/JnKBRUG0Pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauriceBenard Happy valentinesdsy Sony to you and your beautiful  wife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isabelgarcia_24 @BIGPETE_713 Aweee! But did your brother just whispered elote in your ear 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unapologetically always change the gym TV to Law and Order SVU. #sorrynotsorry #heinous @Mariska @FINALLEVEL @Chris_Meloni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to see this on Thursday night!!!!!  SO EXCITED for #CaptainMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas AGAIN another success!! Still got them little Rob Thomas moves that I love]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to personally thank my car, Lucy, for being able to drive 40 miles on gas light.   We made it to payday! ⛽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my mans valentines day suprise $: SHHHH NOBODY TELL HIM IM SUPER ROMANTIC &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg loving this! Ty to you and the rest of the New Kids for this! ❤ #BoysInTheBand  https://t.co/usoI15NFc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iNLuvWitMaryJ Good. Just moved downtown. And I have just way too much shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad Smelling the contents of that can PLUS the smell of the weed made me sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An entire book of poems about Don Draper, but more using him as, you know, a jumping-off point.  don draper checks… https://t.co/903XtlRv0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love how red lights are merely a suggestion during rush hour in downtown austin]]></document><document><![CDATA[mom, you're not supposed to think about it, your supposed to just do it  @mfannie #WSMI https://t.co/rB2yisNlEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these beautiful ladies 🥰 Had a blast this weekend with y’all ♥️ #BeforeTheTurnUp #FelixCulpa #truthandalibi… https://t.co/7NJCOMppK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[YO DISFRUTO BAILAR. Bailo. Una cumbia, una salsa, un meneito, un carrapicho, un tango, lo que sea... Cómo sea... pe… https://t.co/czRSvV2hf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, Kirpa went on to continue to be irrelevant so I’m still not sure how she made it as far as she did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been talking to my boyfriend for over a year now...  Just last week I finally sent him a friend request on FB.  Sti… https://t.co/Ml7SMOm1kZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday’s are for feeling like crap and not being able to get out of bed 😩🥵 https://t.co/FhXieOxNYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mine_pebble @LastWeekTonight @ArmyCorpsNAD @USACEHQ Bro, you do you. I’m just telling the truth, we obviously have… https://t.co/DTtTz0WWSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A thought provoking evening with Emily Bernard and @mychalsmith in #NYC https://t.co/yiRY6076kh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryBulat @SheriW10 @DogginTrump Never be optimistic about Pence. He’s as bad as trump but for different reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to our  @KStateMBB for winning the Big 12!  Just simply amazing what this team is doing! 👏🏽💜😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is the 7:03 train? We just got off the now disabled 6:33 train, which everyone assumed was the 7:03, onto the… https://t.co/xE8XMWYsGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yeah, I’m doing a mini comic of all of them, so that influences my decision as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golden Gate Bridge in all her glory. A rainy evening, but it highlights such a wonderful piece of architecture. I m… https://t.co/8WvkpGNTg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last September, @SpanglishKid (Ed Morales) speaks about @AOC and how she balanced between being two races, in a wor… https://t.co/vCDRYUbDrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that if someone I don’t like met my dogs... they would actually go lick them like they cool, I- https://t.co/U6rxJJYWQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there isn’t a scene that addresses his sex tape where Brooke Hogan was calling him mid-thrust and his ringtone w… https://t.co/rgqfG619vM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kobe's free throw line fade away and Tony Parker's  floater Shawn Marrion's jumper @LanceZierlein @DELv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My digital bag/Mon bagage numérique #noblackbagforme #pasdétuinoirepourmoi  #Idontcarryapurse… https://t.co/4WH3zFhz0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MountainDewMan_ Thanks! But unfortunately your birthday wish for me did not come true... on my way to my last meeting for the day right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kneeC Nah he’s not my cup of tea. And of course I like Megan. She cold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeedsOfLily We all sure had a lot of fun with where we could get a picture taken or where we took our signs.  😈😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud Where's the link? Thanks.  If he made a false report, he's getting fined, and possibly jail time. Ther… https://t.co/VYcLVjjGXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Youre the personification of a cartoon character. Liz: Hmm that pleases me]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t know who this man is, you’re not old enough and not a #nascar fan! #racing #legend #alabamagang… https://t.co/FDfgbDkAbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mann_pennt30 @Unite4Truth @POTUS @JudicialWatch I don't think you can include the president. The reason the dems a… https://t.co/Q0JbnVrC76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter You know how Roger lies. He could always sell one of his luxurious homes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandor285 @Felissa_Rose @BrookeLewisLA @WeWatchedAMovie @Elissadowling @therealjoebob @kreepazoidkelly… https://t.co/fdjN8HaV1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Man Cave is calling, and it’s your time to answer! Enter for a chance to win now. #DEVOUR #Sweepstakes https://t.co/oqgDrq8r0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aormaechea @PRISARadio @cadenaser @Los40 Esto significa que pronto pasaras por Miami. ☺️ Ahora en serio, me alegro… https://t.co/gmYPnLsYoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[White People making they kids MAGA at birth cause wit all this technology out here white kids starting to indulge i… https://t.co/ifUsjk8OR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @EdRollins @realDonaldTrump Everyone should watch the Rachel Maddow show tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[He not surprised because he’s one of them - the women accusing him should be heard]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just take a big rip off your dab pen and almost die from coughing? Yeah same, it just happened to me. 😫☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set It Off Midnight Tour 2019 • • • • • #concertphotographer #torontophotographer #torontophotography… https://t.co/p5f1gahc7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 12-year-old friend Sam is showing me my first episode of #TheBachelor. This is guy looks like an off-brand Micha… https://t.co/F2AmyBGsgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done Judge Thomas! 1-A is to be protected at all times. Weaponizing the press to create constant demonization… https://t.co/yJj8hA0O29]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nofilterneeded #sunset #lastpicfortheday @ Longbranch, Washington https://t.co/nDOWQ5uCXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got some Late Night Bingo Shenanigans Tonight! Come play some Bingo with Me #denonsunset We got Prizes, Cocktail… https://t.co/WRY3mDtuTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect under $100 top for a date night or GNO 💜 On another note I just finished baking a cake which I don’t do… https://t.co/h4xm4ViGRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for some Alan Jackson! Great night with great friends❤️🎙🎤☺️ #alanjackson #alliantenergycenter #madison… https://t.co/tnA5byfAVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s crossover, the #Nissan #Qashqai... I liked it a lot with a manual transmission, but this week’s has a C… https://t.co/g1wbnh2zWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your client looks like at you and says, "thank you for listening to me!" Have mercy! Pulls all the heart strin… https://t.co/6JFvwumGvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicalnutcr1 It all began when we first legalized this slaughter ....give an inch, they want a mile.  The murde… https://t.co/HMtjppAZVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me está tentando mucho lo de cortarme el cabello por los hombros, por favor aléjate impulso de estupidez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink seen you on Ellen and heard you barely sing a portion with your thundering voice..you are my Fav Lady!!!   I… https://t.co/tVuvQHqFII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaldwellUBB @DavePayne18 See you tomorrow and welcome to Sunny South Florida! 😎#305]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC In the same vein, why not keep inner-city schools open late. Kids could get homework help me in a safe quiet e… https://t.co/rgMD6Cin7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[:: just walked by a pick up person at the Pittsburgh airport with @chrissyteigen ‘s name on it and now I’m on high… https://t.co/XPFIf8gSZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cruicej He wrote a dissertation defending his stance. I mean, twenty some pages after the initial twitter blowup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome Video by Jason A! The Truth May Scare You  https://t.co/8ghUXe1oWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only part of stats lecture i understood today was when i sneezed and the professor said bless you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you’re having a happy Saturday! I spent my afternoon walking the river walk in Stuart ☀️🙌🏻😊 https://t.co/38dBABeqK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @MichaelCohen212 Those GOP members today show how complicit they are in trumps criminal actions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much to be proud of @NJITFacilities. Incredible season for the DeSales Bulldogs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is goodT. Niggas was tryna make my court date ON my birthday but they messed up so now it’s moved to April. 💃🏿💃🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly I used to really like you and your optimism but the fact that you don’t see why this is problematic..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Macattack11 says that AirPods are still only for rich people. Is tardy wrong or am I finally rich? #ineedanswers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any other sps teachers who needs more books for their library, chk out https://t.co/KZKrX5XHH2! Brand new bks for $2 and under! #winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbcooper0690 @cspanwj Referring to 44 adding more debt than every other President from George Washington.  That de… https://t.co/aYkAFkdoAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jami in CA purchased this super soft and flattering v-neck sleeveless Banana Republic shirt today. It’s been a sloo… https://t.co/T8KRe082wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I go downtown, who knows what might happen, I might get us all in trouble.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarikaDouglas she slept w more guys in 4 months then I have my whole life smfh 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifesafeast @MaxBoot @PostOpinions As what’s his name said in his standup comedy routine, “I’m from Europe, you kn… https://t.co/jWp3sLSRfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HopeFloeck @ag_guy04 @tvfarmer @milkbarstore Time to rotate to the soy oatmeal cookie recipe--just for some diversity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenrubin Yes! And we are both photographers! In fact, I ended up photographing her wedding! It was awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean You know... I really don’t like you. I wish I did. You’re so enthusiastic. Sometimes I crave that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLTumulty I saw your post &amp; was like.... “What is this? I’ve gotta join in!” ❤️📚]]></document><document><![CDATA[📁 Documents   L 📁 Music        L 📁 Ariana Grande             L 📁 Albums that did not deserve a Grammy                   L 📂 Sweetener]]></document><document><![CDATA[As being a polygraphist child I cannot stress how the media puts such a bad image on how polygraphs  actually work]]></document></documents></author>