<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I support Vida De Auto, LLC and wish them luck in winning $25,000 in the FedEx Small Business Grant Contest. https://t.co/IiAyca7V7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsfandTV You’re the best!  Get ready to see this face in warsong !! https://t.co/AVRMwFu5ZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsVINCENTJay @therodproject @lincolnablades So y’all just thought I was crazy out here.... aight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that wasn't an attempted COUP it will have to do untill the real think comes along.  The 'JUST KIDDING' defence… https://t.co/E2HOZZjcH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s a good one. Quick hand and knows how to pitch/compete. Rare combo for a ‘21 in the “throw harder” era.… https://t.co/0EOO1EZEnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that sit window on planes and stare out the window instead of closing it are trashy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notthefakeSVP Depends on age. 1 to 10 bucks accordingly. Or Xbox gift card.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howard Hughes locking himself in his theater being completely naked and losing his goddamn mind is how it be sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[As seen in NYC today Lion Dances celebrating Chinese New Year. https://t.co/KfHBOPPt25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maniuhg @CNN Yeah, you keep telling yourself that...your media is as fake as it gets . And remember, take care of… https://t.co/4MYJAWJHym]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2019 Russian Roulette with a Tec SIZE #MED extendo  #larryjohnson  #volvo #asheville  #lakers  #HOOPDREAMS… https://t.co/tEOpt9nda6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenMsft Is there any way Microsoft interns can attend if they're under 21 and might not have a parent able to go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning at the end of my 12 week program using Wendler's 5-3-1 programming I took 460 on my joker set.  I hit… https://t.co/rBFEDBTyi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@80sWrestlingPic Most devastating moment from my childhood hood @garyvee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabathascheer honestly the result of this has just made me realize how childish a hormonal lil girl could be. Good… https://t.co/AbLLhDcTQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATeam members- don’t forget lunch in my room today! Bring something to drink! #fhsateam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Medical marijuana bill #HB136 advanced last night out of a House committee during #kyga19. Read release here:… https://t.co/GUx4RjEtyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dublin Me Luck by @11belowbrewing @ Edojin Japanese Cuisine — https://t.co/53e2byOPh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TheCampingRush. Not sure how it took me so long to realize this but have you heard of the chaos theory? I’ll p… https://t.co/jWNmuP36Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comeroundfullO Proud of you, Kristi. Don’t try this everyday though! 😄😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine having a bricked shoe. On your foot. In public. Left to stare again at your phone. The only domain to locate sympathy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPawluk @Zalman888 @VirginiaYankee1 It was hard to predict Verlander would pitch as well as he has in Housto… https://t.co/ZCTnqN0FsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come home from work, zach does “i pooped 7 times today” great thanks for letting me know 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LamandaMB I understand that but you know most people will devote their entire days and lives into a job. They’ll s… https://t.co/4tDxaWDJFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it all so far! Lots of picks including our own, kravstov from last year, sign Pannerin in the off season and m… https://t.co/rhAWXDlTvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cswaters1 Which social platform? Also, does this mean I'm an Aussie, now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardRalls @BrettThackABC27 Delayed due to the cool, damp air locked in. Develops more tonight and tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MamaSarahCNP @ClancyFOX45Now I do that too! My son loves them. We call it “ice cream” haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time you see a brother down Stop and pick him up, cause you might be the next one stuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone that participated in this deserves to be in their own concentration camp, except its overseen by Hitler inst… https://t.co/RmhyxQiMta]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in the downtown Lincoln area tonight, from 4-8pm my group in the UNL Sales Center is raising money for Al… https://t.co/SPUsTYyq5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975TheFanatic @samwils18 @samwils18 always shouts out Coatesville and for that, I think she deserves a nice tall g… https://t.co/hWEHjlogmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great read from @EmJensenWrites and Laura Wifler of @RisenMotherhood...Don’t Put Your Hope in Date Night https://t.co/3C5GRc6FpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DARKMARK_ Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy            Ki… https://t.co/1mYrTIiIi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its Friday!!!! #letswork (@ In-Shape in Antioch, CA) https://t.co/yISJo0MkPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VirtuallyYours6 If it makes you feel any better, listen to any song Jim Steinman wrote. They all start quiet, then… https://t.co/BeksWQhPvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice Spread 🧀 #CheesePlate 🥖🍇🥓 #MarinaDelRey #Rooftop @ Marina del Rey, California https://t.co/OFm5JTLS1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alai2016 @theTylerTrent I applaude you for doing this. Gives hope for the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[High five @tyrona! OMG, this was the B2B ABM MSO @LinkedInMktg deep dive I needed right now! Must see #High5conf pr… https://t.co/k6AHl5S4c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any server asked #MarkTConcannonSr “Would you like another one (meaning, drink)?”  He would stop them in their t… https://t.co/PGiRUgW4hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Metro Toronto Convention Centre https://t.co/yf5G4lfSNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Credit to the dudes who have revitalized my enjoyment of the Sweet Science, whether you know it or not. @Hafwell… https://t.co/15zYtSbhZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and watch this team!  Every time they take the floor they create new @BigSkyConf and @VandalsWBB history!… https://t.co/EwKa1fQ5gI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrhlC Santa Fe New Mexico would be better than above for what you have listed to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day here in Seattle. Looking forward to this one! Lucky to have some special Ladies in the crowd watching too… https://t.co/rTKLhYnCvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERYONE from Korea is coming to North America this spring, but Epik High fans are coming in STRONG and selling out… https://t.co/NtXAPhAxb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfterHoursCBS @ALawRadio Mr Big Chest. Tell me, who do think you are, Mr. Big Chest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easy, it has been a long season. 2nd win over a ranked team in less than a week is worthy of celebration!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Kamala, We’re not a nation that says these kids get minimal education and these do not.  My educator… https://t.co/fTutUiMqgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIP  Taking a break from con prep to ink a Wonder Woman sketch by the amazing Jim Lee.  - - - -TAGS. #drawing… https://t.co/oS9MY15KBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briarhaint @TacoAffcionado @Cubs I don’t give AF about you and what you claim to look like..:you’re just falling i… https://t.co/XcOeIO1M9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luminyan_pf @Spicy_2018 Those are some beautiful pics Luminyan'san 🌹😊💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristiancrespoj DIOS MIO!!! DIOS PROTEJA A LOS NINOS!!! ESE VIDEO ES SUFICIENTE PARA NO DEJAR A MADURO Y SUS SECUACES VIVOS !!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 19 years old. If you pinch me because i’m not wearing green, well goodluck Charlie]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts the whole team when your point guard struggles to score. Lonzo needs to work on his shot and consistency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you pray for anyone you tend to motify your personal attitude toward him. Norman Vincent Peale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennLahmers Happy birthday! Have a great day and awesome year ahead. 🎂🎉🎂🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/7/2019 - 20:31 Temp: 48.9F   Hum:  85% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 30.011in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.01 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[First logo. Streams are gonna be wild in June. #NintendoDirect https://t.co/5vTEUYZZdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarrenBuffett on the #RiseofSocialism: “I don’t want to do anything to the goose that lays the golden eggs...We’ve… https://t.co/INf2VjQZC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SECNetwork @KentuckyMBB Y’all hyping up the 1st and 3rd best sec teams like crazy, bring that same energy next Sat… https://t.co/biSJi2fIPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneHarl0w Maybe they are confused!  But I love the UK and I thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XZ2K65Xzzu February Wrap Up &amp; March TBR 2019 #booktube #starwars #metallica]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in El Paso, TX? View our latest opening: https://t.co/ycKCLhixI6 #Simon #Sales]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @lskurrus How else will you prove what a great negotiator you are!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vQBHNjlhzc “I am a #humble soldier.” Todrik said. “But, if you’d have me, I’d love you unconditionally… https://t.co/uIkk8Z8k6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AM570LASports @RobParkerFS1 @RogginAndRodney He wanted Lance so he didn’t have to play against his D.]]></document><document><![CDATA[China just approved Donald Trump-branded spas, escort services and massage parlours https://t.co/FRo8epUeq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Roy has been the HC, Tar Heels have 3 titles. Duke has 2. Go back and read tweet. Overall, Duke trails UNC in… https://t.co/jwceGhe7B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrewerBoston25.  North Weymouth.. Not much to write home about. Trace snow with light snow 33F. #MACocorhas melt down precip 0.01"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajotac Grease fue hace 40 años ... y ella a los 35 todavía estaba en High School, con razón era tan tremenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kernowco I like living here a lot . It took my fiancé and partner to show the beauty of Arizona (Tucson) but I fee… https://t.co/4HL6ZBv76y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dance10Alan @kaitlynmount @DWTSJuniors Artyon got jobbed. By far the best entertainer and the most passionate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I watch #LohanBeachClub I can’t stop lolling just thinking about what @LarzMarie and @ecareyo will say in the… https://t.co/vpfk8EOo3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#zoe in concert :) @ The Cosmopolitan of Las Vegas https://t.co/cYXuonpBHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You should be glad he’s putting his attention elsewhere rather than putting you in jail where you belong]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is NOT what we’re willing! Just you wait til @YasmineTaeb wins that primary. We’ll see who slides down whose s… https://t.co/gn0L8kF7YE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger uo early making a little noise at the Genesis Open.  31 on the from.  Goes out and Eagles the 10th.  Let’s go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKavulla @gabeaschan @jt_hammons @drvox That is not how I read proposed section 37-2-133(b),(c)(iii), and (e). Am I missing something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got the trans out all by myself 😁😊 Going to continue removing parts and then hopefully I can start cutting! 🧡☢️☣️… https://t.co/7tukN11936]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo: Matt Veen's last-second block, all-around team play https://t.co/mDiWClFsks … lead to Mullen's 59-56 victory at… https://t.co/JvkZ8hrDOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkJonesESPN @nuggets That’s right young folks, I’m good for 7  minutes of buckets then one week of epsom salt!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esse tweet é de uma deslealdade sem tamanho. Primeiro que conceito de esquerda e direita veio da Rev. Francesa no s… https://t.co/3KEnFxlNeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roastyraccoon You know you could run you probably have a pretty good chance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Souvenir is soo old Avril! I am crying listening to this song. Is the best song so far! @AvrilLavigne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ewwjr53 @dpwhitten You “forgot” to reblock me after posting the screenshot, Eugene. 🙄 https://t.co/Fac3PcIHi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t get this hype with me, like @typicalteresa was at the LA show, at any function... BYE 👋🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to make a video of sounds entirely from my old @gibsonguitar J-160 acoustic... https://t.co/iSmGGn4hQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a difference a couple of days makes- today's view from the office not quite as good as earlier in the week 🙄… https://t.co/iP03OjybTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJWashington Thank you for bringing your energy.  We appreciate you. #WeAreUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktvanderlip @ChaseGoodbread @AdamSandler Except it wasn't his mom who said that; it was his wife. Also, Boucher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like we’re all on social media for the same reason...we’re here to build real meaningful connections that we… https://t.co/yUvHuHI9q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woah #AVTweeps there is some serious editing going on here... like they are possessed by some unseen force   STAR W… https://t.co/FPJhnYsjl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do they call it comfort food? I sure as hell don’t feel comfortable afterwards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you on their private snap story but they’re not on yours https://t.co/8gMogi8hll]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a couple people from my high school in the conservatory in Chicago. I CANT ESCAPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[solo cypress . #tentree #h2ography #tree #liveauthentic #outerbanks #cypress #thebalanceofopposites #cloudporn… https://t.co/3TcKq9zoNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_bianca_garza7 LIKE I SAID. lol. You don’t hurt a boys momma. It like messing with a girls dad. It’s unforgivable]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Lapis lazuli, matte onyx and sterling silver men’s bracelet ✖️ WEAR GREGORIO NEW YORK ✖️… https://t.co/Pf7huDr2xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMacMahan Me when Justin says lebron is the GOAT https://t.co/5xoVs1PBqf]]></document></documents></author>