<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I have failed at going to sleep before I have to go back to work at 3 mins you the 16hr shift I just did was not go… https://t.co/1QAchcbCmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCoachGibbs @Justin_McIsaac @nhsportspage We still love you Coach Gibbs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the most amazing time this weekend with my boyfriend and @wet ❤️ https://t.co/YH4iw1UguX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Thanks. I really want to know that the rumors of clearances were over-ruled by a President who was a… https://t.co/vL7pBdmmeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlighty60 @People4Bernie @OurRevolution @NomikiKonst @dsam4a @RoKhanna @LaborforSPayer @4HealthyCA @NUHW @PDAHCare… https://t.co/19XXuKs0sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was invited to speak with high school students at a career day today. First, I had to get them to *Jodeci harmony… https://t.co/ig4BWHchfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarzGurl I want Cobra Commander , thanos and Megatron to run for president . #pick your poison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerrellSandefur @thistallawkgirl They had the best Finale of any tv show ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to come out to the DBS Charity Fashion Show this Sunday March 10th! At Stones River Country Club 1:30-… https://t.co/llCneSwzGX]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing that truly gets my heart beating, is seeing teammates love and take care of each other♥️ That’s what it’s all about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOVING that @AlyssaMastro44’s new book got a shout out at #AdvanceCamp immediately followed by Springsteen outro music! #TheRising]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregoryy2k @NASCARONFOX HE IS NOT A DIRTY DRIVER. HE IS A 7 TIME CHAMPION AND HE WILL BE A 8TH CHAMPION  BABY 💪☝️👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradKelly17 Didn’t go so well against Baker....  I actually like Debo Samuel.  He’s a very talented guy, but not against my Dawgs.  🐶🔴⚫️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot more comforting crosses have arrived!! We have lots of great designs plus keychains!! These always go fast so… https://t.co/Sc6fznXM0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Construction of 30-Foot Border Wall Begins in California https://t.co/CKYleeWpDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are some websites where i can rent textbooks for an affordable price???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 50th Anniversary to such wonderful people and parents. Mike and Andrea Tomchak Congratulations!!! Truly a mon… https://t.co/YqbIcpXgHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherThePig Kisses Back Esther! ... (you are my computer background for today!) Throwing kisses to everybody that comes by.]]></document><document><![CDATA[work!  #ultimatecircuit #studiofitness #fitfamforever #515crew #smile #getsummerready #515crew… https://t.co/qOka8byE34]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES❗THEY ARE BACK! KICKING UP A STORM WHERE EVER THEY GO⚡ DOG'S MOST WANTED. #DogWGNA FEEL THEIR THUNDER⚡… https://t.co/7zfAlaASzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTrueGreatOne @NatShineman @nataliepichler Samoa shouldn't even be in the top three.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you weren’t taught how to be down for someone like they’ve been down for you and it shows...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did You Know? At any given moment, there are at least 12 unused condoms hidden throughout Landis Green! Stay safe, Noles! ❤️💛❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei I can’t even!!!  Go girl. Keep giving it to us.  We need to hear it all]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna have to let everyone know that God really did bless us when he gave us @latcoftus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcdays Chad is gone and said his goodbyes to Stefano. Now it is time for Tony/Andre @ThaaoPenghlis to say Hello D… https://t.co/RLQpbHRyc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Et boum. Le site https://t.co/pkprFdJD6W. On cherche toujours des partenaires prêts à assurer le bien être dans leu… https://t.co/thJP7cuWoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tahatan_Ahote @david_fuj I hope it works for people. Depression is a terrible thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into an old friend today. Time fly’s by us so quickly!  Here’s to all my brother and sister firefighters out th… https://t.co/PJGrVcFIgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@desiderioDC @BresPolitico I appreciate our Dem leaders being thoughtful and cautious, but if there was ever a time… https://t.co/up0S9CZ8vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptgarrett3 We may have different definitions of a deep dive! 🙈 But definitely some good nuggets in there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on my way to Manchester Airport. Me and my family are going to Disney World in Orlando, Florida. Our flight is… https://t.co/xC4reK1292]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kittery looks to update policy on medical marijuana usage in schools.  @WGME   https://t.co/LZyiisEfhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iankh My all time fave guest star on the Muppet Show was @alicecooper #SchoolsOut you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Winter sunrise in my neck of the woods..❄️❄️❄️ @ Caledonia, Michigan https://t.co/bZhB4Ko2iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living in Florida means going to the Starbucks in Disney Springs to get homework done ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loveforrealstar Awe, thank you so so much star! I love this! So beautiful!💜🌻🌻🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I think of my daughter as commanding NOT bossy.” @nicolasmarcoux @DianeKazarian @PwC_Canada @monaghiami… https://t.co/vO9ioGnnTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan please stop talking. You sound as stupid and dishonest as the #FakePresident you are attempting to cover for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Wendy’s on Clemson Rd is so ratchet, idk even know why I bother 🤦🏽‍♀️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iacob920 @AldrinMaxx @RodPDavison @anaililmi @Lamarsemx @mauricio_sanche @beto__34 @labarquerag70 @FreundCarlos… https://t.co/aLn6QnC1lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is sooooooo classist lol, now we attack poor people for being poor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Will Smith said “This world is not going to break you. We won’t allow it,” I got a little emotional. Nothing b… https://t.co/UJ3o0XigSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d0peangela will never not hate once in a lifetime i will fight on this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lostal21 @Bigb7893 @NikkiPav @wweshirtguy @TroubleDVJ @BrianVistaAZ Morning all... Happy Thursday. Think I got a c… https://t.co/SzY1rENr3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know my dad is about to say “stop losing weight” it’s called high waisted jeans DAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork Sounds like he’s threatening certain Republicans who new this was a set up.  Minus one   Uh oh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always feel hopeful for the future when I see our @HighlineSchools students. These young women are the next gener… https://t.co/zg5VIq6CoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women’s Day Thought: it’s funny how certain species’ males straight-up die or get eaten by the female… https://t.co/8PcUEPVlNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFPhq @sendavidperdue Hmmm. Didn’t he vote for the tax cut scam that added to the deficit? Hmmm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red,                                   Like the eyes in your head,            Pack me a bowl and light up… https://t.co/tifCunefWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even have enough followers for y’all to always be saying stupid shit to my tweets. I really don’t lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the odds to bump into my friend from Vegas in Florida at the same day time place?? #florida… https://t.co/POJulToe51]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCHI23 @TVGMike Classic Art!  Except I know he's been married to his high school seeetie!  As far as slow horses.… https://t.co/gk00SKjrvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling ALL the love at @orangetheory this morning with my favorites!  Happy Valentines Day!  #ValentinesDay2019⁠ ⁠… https://t.co/P8Hon80VPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber why is it? My Uber express is several dollars more than my friend next to me. We are going to exactly same pl… https://t.co/NOgbOW7u8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the kinds of decisions GA lawmakers want to make for citizens because they trust government, not women an… https://t.co/9iv301KxXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially accepted my offer of admission to the Master of Ed program @QueensEduc today! Feeling thankful for the s… https://t.co/eVu61XvhLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@usernamesloane Between motherhood and teaching I have superhuman immunity and the ability to ignore almost all que… https://t.co/4K2exVtEzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[funniness coming your way. #funniness #chuckle #smile #comic https://t.co/aHvIzoC8xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m really upset that @Hallmark is not going to be carrying @missjillscott collection anymore. I love those card… https://t.co/tW7nvTqilm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@constantbarrage @JuddLegum They should ignore them.  Can you say perjury trap?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman  @GOPLeader  @GOP  @Sifill_LDF  @NAACP  @ACLU  @splcenter  @SenateDems  @SenSchumer  @HouseDemocrats… https://t.co/Xy2PaI0JJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump HIGH SPEED TRAIN WILL CROSS THE CARAVANS OVER QUICKER , “ BUILD THAT WALL “]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was a stop before leaving Tampa the #watmongkolratanaram was something I never expected. On the river and all… https://t.co/oaeNqYtYkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things may not be going so well in my life right now , but I truly thank god for everything! Specially for blessing… https://t.co/cOBtDogAOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought for sure today would be the day I look under my sink and wouldn’t find a mouse. I was wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your hair matches some street art it’s gonna be a great day! #blogger #bluehair #purplehair… https://t.co/iTUVV9t6KI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moral of the story is apparently the best time to bump music is after the leasing office is closed when there’s nob… https://t.co/CyYiSluEKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody People who don’t have dogs just don’t understand how much love there is not just for us to them but f… https://t.co/SYlCWWJqkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaLoder_ @timothylyrics23 So this is why when you get picked up by an agent they end up coming out with a ne… https://t.co/iXMW6JUF4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMama2G Time freedom and the ability to have limitless income potential.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrWhere are Republican Leaders in SUPPORT OF TRUMP.....why no declassifying of Fisa docs....no investigation of… https://t.co/UO3dpmPzKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliecast4 My 10 am students!!! They distract me with their sleepy heads lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find #cohen to be a credible witness as well as a man full of regret about his life choices and now taking respon… https://t.co/ok0Eu95Ay7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comisariojob saludo Profesor Job Gaxiola. un gusto saber de ti y tu familia en el ejido la atravesada.🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suburbansxcum he did apologize earlier this week but it feels like the voices that were harmed didn’t receive any respect tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish Aria would stop growing I can’t believe how big she is already 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will give my paycheck to whoever finds the person who did that to this poor doggo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @erikajayne walk directly into her glam squad while in the Bahamas is such a vibe. #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OzarksTonight: MSU Professor Dr. Benjamin Onyango is going to Kenya this month to create a new master’s program in… https://t.co/baYAuc3tvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We go to the Smokies annually, and I can’t wait for our trip this year! 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoopiGoldberg @DavidTennantPod I pray you are feeling better I know you played God before.  But my prayer is dear… https://t.co/LZl0qsroFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to pick my love up at the airport at 5 A.M. and I’m actually incredibly excited about it. Longest seven days of my life without him ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing our 09 boys too @TaylorGraham26 @JamesRiley7 @patrick_ianni @roger_levesque @JhonHurtado34 some of my… https://t.co/lnIlvaQHS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjlovesamerica @pinkk9lover @GOPSenate @POTUS @ROCKONOHIO @BestBrownsFan @AppSame @LVNancy @adjunctprofessr… https://t.co/AqMcA2IgPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furtogo @cspanwj These stores are competitive to the cent. They aren't playing silly games as you suggest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you sure you want to do this Jenny? Prepared with everything that comes with it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoxComm  Huge thanks to Jacob B23715 for helping us get our WiFi sorted. He was friendly, professional and patient… https://t.co/YEjI3nYBWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leilani and I slept in the guest room last night and Javii was bugging for us to go to the room but I fell asleep s… https://t.co/ttH6tkn4xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup.  (from The Princess Saves Herself In This One by Amanda Lovelace) https://t.co/nlJosp51Y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mazel to #Israeli #director Guy Nattiv #oscar  #Skin an important film about #race &amp; #hate in this country.… https://t.co/dLX3tzSiVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Austin_Wright7 this is why I don’t trust Hazel with drive thru windows 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows No more, make the election equal.  if those outside pay all their bills so should others running fo… https://t.co/vdeIdWqDC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G2Services No trap or float attached, just a pile of line right under the surface that you could see about the tim… https://t.co/BbTSoGIIVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathypetreebeck Come to one Get Fit with Fowler and I will show you!!! 😂😂🏃🏽‍♀️🏋🏼‍♀️🧘🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 You are a DEPLORABLE Slime Ball. Drain The Swamp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sansasrark Yup. I may be black but I hope their(cpd) racism gives him the sentence he deserves instead of two months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry, but can one really argue “my body my choice” while also arguing for mandated vaccinations? I’m thinking not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelHardenONDP If we don't stand up to bribery now while we still can, who will help when we can't? Despots can ar… https://t.co/tGb5aAsHpT]]></document></documents></author>