<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MVrydaghsWHIO No no no. Say it ainРђЎt so. I want sunshine and 80s. My wife keeps saying hang in there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AafLegends @keshunfreeman @TheAAF #OJAYS... I will always love my momma she's my favorite GIRL...­Ъњъ­Ъњќ­Ъўі]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emilystellaemi2 @isabenfica51 @alisonblamer @willtravers @Freja_Petersen @EevaPaavilainen @klyonskalmensonРђд https://t.co/nF77ZZfdTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our server finally got updated to PHP 7.2 and of course the two dinosaur sites that we are hosting went down.   AndРђд https://t.co/Eej61l6vrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ducks #floridaphotographer #florida #swfl #swflphotographer #waterbirds #birds #photography #wildlifeРђд https://t.co/sNzc8BQSgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closed around-the-clock for construction til may 2019: alt: new bern ave in #Raleigh on Milburnie Rd Both NB/SB b... https://t.co/sFRv5Px0Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend I look forward to packing supply boxes for our troops serving here and abroad. This is a wonderful orgРђд https://t.co/rA0lFDSjyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy se cumplen 32 a├▒os del dia en que Luis H Alvarez le pidio a Felipe Calderon tomar las riendas de las ActividadeРђд https://t.co/eYBd8kjXke]]></document><document><![CDATA[That R. Kelly video is as equally hilarious as it is sad tbh. Like man, thatРђЎs why you have to always be cognizantРђд https://t.co/Il68fYsjFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoePritchard21 You posted one of my two favorites.  This is my other one.  Simple #NASCAR #paint #SamBass https://t.co/WDA5ZLHL6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overnight, I got my hands on a copy of #MichaelCohenРђЎs prepared remarks for todayРђЎs hearing. Here are some highlighРђд https://t.co/jZHn2ezXyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gun bills make history in House, face uncertainty in Senate https://t.co/BkMfUfgqFw via @ConnPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching The Masked Singer finale with the family https://t.co/9dnwYO3BTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Are you happy @RandPaul. Do you realize how stupid you look. Which of course comes from what you are. TheРђд https://t.co/dTCKLSJaR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter is such a f***ing joke for pushing this. Officially another wing of the leftist agenda. https://t.co/zPtG3lHW9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillibean557 I guess the kind of person who lives in his mommas basement and plays video games all day might be eaРђд https://t.co/SyKvyxDWnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюIt's not that diamonds are a girl's best friend, but it's your best friends who are your diamonds.РђЮ ~Gina BareccaРђд https://t.co/Kq7yMn2C0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asaprajy That opening scene is on a whole other level. Absolutely bananas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardoHq @CorruptedPOD @CountdownEnded @SmallafroGames @ScottyStyles29 @RealBluEEaZY we all knew that was gonna happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EmanuelGonzalez is dirtier than a toilet ­Ъџй in a #sportArena @50cent get the bag ­Ъњ╝ #letsgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barstoolpizza Sorry Palm Beach County failed you. ­ЪцдРђЇРЎѓ№ИЈWhile you're in the @westpalmbch area, try @1hotpiepizza ­ЪЇЋ iРђд https://t.co/l0p3MTNfgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@votevets @jonsoltz I pretty sure he said if nobody is going to help me build  my wall, I,ll build my stupid  wallРђд https://t.co/JsPuwZO9Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 20 - Balance of Power:    Bernie Sanders' 2020 presidential bid reopens questions about whetherРђд https://t.co/gfBhnLZ42K]]></document><document><![CDATA[#futurists Investors-Academics-Industry-Government-Entrepreneurs @theNASciences today | Honored to share the stageРђд https://t.co/COQGmK2yix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGGBoxing @DAZN_USA Even tough i think you won both fights the next time you fight Canelo you will have to take itРђд https://t.co/9NwYDcx5K2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double digit dave with the horrid trip. METRO GLIDE still good enough to win. @IsleRacingPP @gabe_prewitt @MattPresto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuathegawd drops a visual from his project РђюSevenРђЮ https://t.co/o9PHRJImKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюNo way youРђЎre NattyРђЮ   Probably best compliment IРђЎve gotten in a hot minute   Sure am tho, Nothing but chicken cooРђд https://t.co/GolYDcBEUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just guessing Jack White might not be high on draft boards this spring #dukeunc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think @AOC and @JussieSmollett should go bowling together.   They need a bit of fun to get their mind off their sРђд https://t.co/yffmHune4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reid Golloher lost his quarterfinal match. He will now wrestle against WF tonight to stay alive. #MiltonTough]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SOS #StopStateAidCuts #WeAreTRschools @NewJerseyDOE @GovMurphy @NJSenatePres @jimholzapfel @AndyKimNJ @DrLRepolletРђд https://t.co/XZBfrkAlRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan I am genuinely sorry that you represent my state. YouРђЎre arrogant, defiant and blindly loyal to a man destroying our democracy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Into the unknown with @fender @bossfx_us @empress_effects @jhspedals @strymon digitechfx ehx @neunaberaudioРђд https://t.co/Ak2vE8WuUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he still isnРђЎt top 5 or close to Bron x MJ. That РђюMamba MentalityРђЮ tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing the music of Red Dead Redenption 2 on today's show! Tune in now for discussion on news of 2019 and the sounРђд https://t.co/itBc6BYImk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy poca gente te quiere ver triunfar pero esa misma gente que te desea el bien no te quiere ver arriba de ellos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryankindell9 @lkindell3 to the only Bengals fans I know, this made me think of you:]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last ride, it's Senior Night, be sure to show some love to our seniors at tonight's game as we take on Cal StatРђд https://t.co/GPDBSdyfdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much more strength than you think. IРђЎm always here if anyone wants to talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@people Sore loser?? Did you say that when you lost the Oscar about 30 years ago???? Actually it should have been Bohemian RhapsodyРђћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been on this real Chaka Kahn kick recently.  Her VOICE, my Lord!!!! SheРђЎs up there voice wise with the other greatsРђд https://t.co/JwMEwovR3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why isnРђЎt my destination location shared with @lyft drivers when ride is requested, @AskLyft?  I scheduled a 630amРђд https://t.co/nVYESOSQAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brozoxmiswebs Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ Рађ РађРађРађ             Ser├Е breve:                Un videito Jefe DiegoРђд https://t.co/S7MKWot9FC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Article 29: The Marks of the True Church We believe that we ought to discern diligently and very carefully, by theРђд https://t.co/VpxI8OoZYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeyMick @BarstoolReags @JackMacCFB classic Mick Man. This is why you were dismissed from Memphis back in 08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Damn u could have gotten simple Ben if ur looking for a token]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh the plot thickens!! (Michael Jackson popcorn gif) @CardsFromAttic @WatchTheBreaks @CrackinWax]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember showing this kid my РђюcrushesРђЮ outfit (he has like an emo/street style so he be dressing good) And he goeРђд https://t.co/VPcNLdKiTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[­Ъцћ ... ­ЪЈА Home ­ЪЈА ... ­ЪцЌ (@ Sunshine's (my) Grotto in Ardsley, NY) https://t.co/aeCrQ6lEX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Рђю04 girls bringing home the gold from PDT with the Rush Select team in Arizona!! https://t.co/IITMumx410]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4AqFUvGxgl #Brazil is once again reporting a substantial outbreak of #yellowfever. On 6 Mar 2019, BrazРђд https://t.co/rCLFYcnGmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cavallokane @TPM @cdelbrocco IРђЎm not comforted knowing that the CIA kept Will Hurd on staff for so many years, thaРђд https://t.co/9Rgh782xMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcACaputo @TheRickWilson @RealJacobPerry Some poor motherfucker doing his or her job shockingly unaware of your tragic backstory.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaybeRealBrando @weshardeniv @scottEweinberg @BRlGSBYBEAR @netflix The stuff about Disney pulling its content offРђд https://t.co/jTSsUiz6QH]]></document><document><![CDATA[any of you fine folk have a dvd copy of the original karate kid movie I can borrow? #neverseenit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thor_benson So far my 40s have been. My 20s and 30s sucked. I finally have a good career, money and my shit together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters ISLA ISLAN          ISLAM           GRAND SLAM            THiSANOTE WASHINGTON D.A.            DISTRIC-T (Рђд https://t.co/E1wzvZN7UE]]></document><document><![CDATA[YESSS!!!! I donРђЎt mind driving 10 minutes from my house to be here! ­ЪњЂ­ЪЈ╗РђЇРЎђ№ИЈ­Ъцў­ЪЈ╝]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved celebrating my birthday tonight with my twin brother and our families. ItРђЎs the best way to spend it.  We cРђд https://t.co/sfrY6cGqRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tear the fascists down - Woody Guthrie https://t.co/FkCx5cRgqC via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevelaprade @MLeach680News You got two options based on word associative value of your last tweet:Рђд https://t.co/4woXCIdDq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pels made the right decision from a value standpoint to wait until the offseason. But I wouldРђЎve completely undРђд https://t.co/kL7X7W3vJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Toronto! :) #Sunrise 07:39, noon 13:28, sunset 19:18 EDT (UTC-4), March 10. Day length: 11h 39m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюTo create the best experiences you need to understand how your employees work and what they want to achieve, not tРђд https://t.co/s4d2NbFcEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamePV IРђЎve been in the process of deleting all my old content off IG today and itРђЎs pretty cringey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveRushin donРђЎt forget those truffles tomorrow ­ЪўЅ @BallAndChainPod @RebeccaLobo #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOLD PREDICTION: Bryce Harper will sign with somebody TODAY!  I have zero idea who he will choose but he will makeРђд https://t.co/GPuAZyk5ew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comicsandroses My LCS had their shipment of Girl in the Bay delayed.  Hope I can get it this week.  HavenРђЎt read RРђд https://t.co/yE5zeULpdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBaconDiaries I think IРђЎm glad IРђЎm not your co-worker. Seems dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elguapo64 @gaye_gallops That's what Momma used to say so you know it's true!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Girl at the bar: Oh my god was that your girlfriend puking at the bar?  Me: nah, thatРђЎs my Fianc├Е. DifferenceРђд https://t.co/FFeuYAoul5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thegoodnite #shawnmendez #karaoke #inmyblood @ The Good Nite https://t.co/ZN33AsnmP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im vibing to playing some xbox anyone wanna stop by https://t.co/0IuOJndKPJ #mixer #streaming #gaming #fortnite #talkshit #catchup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianColbert27 Try blue apron they taught me how to cook. Ton of different options and styles. Healthy too.Рђд https://t.co/5Hxf5qqgFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at CenturyLink? We're hiring in #Littleton, CO! Click for details: https://t.co/u5Ms7M3WHn #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lorena1Chavez @epigmenioibarra @lopezobrador_ Esto es como escupir para arriba.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $1,313.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $Рђд https://t.co/mAWTKRJ23i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleveazey @TheLibertyBowl Dude, you are killing our chances at creating a secondary market for these things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serge Ibaka puts his hands around Marquese Chriss' throat tonight. Someone around here will still be bitching aboutРђд https://t.co/i2XY5x3GH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShockZ314 @fat_pretty_girl @jenmisstx @MrLSmith21 @OrganicBeefcake Wrestlemania match ??? @TheBethPhoenix coming back for #OneMoreMatch ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraotaDigital CON LA SALIDA DEL DICTADOR MADURO TENDREMOS A UNA LATINOAM├ЅRICA UNIDA Y CON UN FUTURO PROMISORIO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TodayРђЎs headcount: LPC 67, CPC 35, NDP 10, BQ 2 + Weir.  14 ministers present (lots on a Friday), Hughes in the Chair. #QP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sluggish Blue Devils barely hold off Wake Forest  https://t.co/j3l651qgJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepClayHiggins  The Majority of Americans actually didnt know who you were until Yesterday. IРђЎm so glad you showedРђд https://t.co/2HCn3ti1GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndkirschmann You have to follow all the meerkat twitter accounts https://t.co/DEEn3bBJpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bfverano @KristenAshly I agree with every word there was no other way anyone was going to accept him as a characteРђд https://t.co/VjZ6AT673D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill HeРђЎs not worth millions in the NBA bc heРђЎs ineligible to be in their league, which was collectively barРђд https://t.co/HDUCuXXBBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlitas @KamalaHarris Yea!   Like AOC.  Someone with a background in stealing tips which is a resume enhancement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюThe luxury brand will debut a series of TV commercials featuring a new campaign called "Rise." #Cadillac will alsoРђд https://t.co/OC8J64vIUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blade Runner (1982) with Fritz The Nite Owl and @niteowltheatre - 11:30 p.m. TONIGHT at @Studio35!!!!!Рђд https://t.co/7R61VABjC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shamusroan13 @MomO5Tiff @JannaKilimnik @WakingWoman @KristinaNadia @judyohtweets @of_ramblings @tiredmama99Рђд https://t.co/hVi8RHyTZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I decided to make the pizza burgers from the @minimalistbaker cookbook. DoesnРђЎt that sound good?! They looked amРђд https://t.co/WPfwY94wL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Live Wire by @ocelotbrewing at @OcelotBrewing Рђћ https://t.co/MytlgLmCur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kia_soto Isnt it funny they decide to play real journalist the last few weeks though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoeTAlusa @i_womb @coolp100 @bethanyshondark Obama and his administration implemented that and same sex and otherРђд https://t.co/aly6ncCiaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAFromBK @JeremyGregoret1 @DragonMom98 @JustPlainT @SandiMarie79 @ByCharlieRicker @lno09281978 @Jack_WanderSРђд https://t.co/YwpTfKiMBQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where old Grampas can get a cheap ass omelette a vanilla milkshake and a bribe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh itРђЎs Saturday and friends are in from out of town! Shots of #CrownRoyal Apple are in order ­ЪЉЉ­ЪЇЈ   #diageorep #keystonecocktails]]></document><document><![CDATA[ItРђЎs #RunningTipTuesday! Did you know that the majority of distance runners suffer some sort of overuse injury eachРђд https://t.co/jjHae02mvI]]></document></documents></author>