<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Office Manager" at Kelly Services? Apply even if you're not a 100% match. You migh… https://t.co/7rCEc6k7Hz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think a nigga exist that’s not fucking friendly 🧐 you bitches gotta start getting set up I’m not having thi… https://t.co/PMVL1KtQKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe after this national emergency he do a couple more before end if his second term. Health care would be a big o… https://t.co/rAPsN5lFZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinkerTASH_04 Oh bye lmfao... you have a huge ass and you literally showed all of it... don’t compare 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to see u at @natprodexpo #expowest next week! Sharing #sustainable eats #frozen #fruit and #veggies !🍌🍍🥭🍓🥕🥥… https://t.co/YUWqr10Na7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlYourPalster Ide more than likely just drive! https://t.co/ywArdD0Z7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muddy_taylor I’m off but yet I still wakes up at 4:00 and 6:00 for no reason 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNVenusiii @conservmillen @MeghanMcCain 2/2 and has $25 copay for most docs...20% coinsurance for tests etc of the… https://t.co/YSq8xSk8VX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandradarin1 @mlbrisse Wonderful decision! Our Lords door is always open for you to receive absolution in the confessional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4 styles of runway walks Presenting THE CROSSOVER WALK #videographer @eightpspi #MUA @MGBeautyHouston… https://t.co/0XXQxduQYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Workshops all day, addressing important issues, watched Director of DCI present issues facing the faculty shortage… https://t.co/mWl873YPfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is tough my darling, but so are you.❣️ #proudmama #happygirl #modelinthemaking #beyoungbewildbefree @ Casa Mon… https://t.co/Ho7RynAdAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather be written out of the will than have my mom post more hideous pics of me on Facebook. https://t.co/gPP4rfcOC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially after getting cheated on three times, you thinking everything good 👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylAnnPeter2 It was great, wasn’t it. Loved the ending when he stuck it to Wong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyniathomassie Hey 👋🏻 @edison_central6 have you shared the doodle for @google opportunity with the students? Deadl… https://t.co/HdiY63ldxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the mention @StephanJMyers #RomanticSuspense #militaryRomance #mustreads]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cycle I’m on has to break! Psycho I gotta keep caged I got some vices to fade! Fighting thoughts All thru the day!… https://t.co/CiRu7K8xGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blondetaki I was just thinking the other day, I’ve literally not heard anything about her for months]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on hard earned win last night, boys! #AshlandProud #Tomcats #AshlandBlazer #KHSAA #StateTournament… https://t.co/cICdCUG7LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't miss flowers blooming at #wintergarden #cutetown #spring @ Downtown Winter Garden https://t.co/ZGvGQnZ9C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[so proud of my best friend @ian_k13 for graduating from Jet Blue University as the newest flight attendant 🥰✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher It’s because as awful as Trump is - Democrat’s in power is even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@appliedspiritua @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump No dear heart, stay at home moms should get a job. Ho… https://t.co/sfIpZKPMYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @AndreaBocelli on #PBS. A special for his birthday! Feliz cumplianos, Andrea! #HappyBirthday 😁🎉🎶🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 of my fave before/after pics. This lovely sched. a series of treatments to clear up her acne before her wedding d… https://t.co/0DzoYVWNCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We started today #2019february17 with a midnight slumber party!! 🍫 🍰 Yes that is chocolate cake with chocolate chip… https://t.co/lOSl3pM8TO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristanSpoof i’m actually crying that u responding 😭 thanks for letting me troll lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@feliciawalthour Yesss, definitely not trying to force her but I do have an induction date set for Wednesday (I mig… https://t.co/cAGyROuwgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPWellman Also these headlines should include the word "indicted" in his descriptors...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianneCassidy @PolicyLover I don’t need you to root for me dear. Have you seen my life? I get help because my fam… https://t.co/WiY7sJqV7c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ISnowNothin @CPThrio OMG YES I used to be my friend groups human IMDb and google. I am Chandler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I rip this mans #vape from his hands and throw it on the #subway tracks? (His is vaping on the inside platform)]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛠️ BUILDING A BETTER 🌎 ⚒️ 👇👇👇👇👇👇👇👇👇 #MakeSocialMediaFunAgain #MyCalling 🚫♿🏳️‍🌈😁 💥 RETWEET DAILY PLEASE 💥 https://t.co/F0NpPolKgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at B&amp;K Richardson's Crib in Mount Horeb, WI https://t.co/hs6psARmIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’ve learned from binge watching all the seasons of @bondirescue and the @bondilifeguards is   1. Stay between… https://t.co/9kkK6qUs5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHertling @JenniferJJacobs We'll, he isn't uninformed, he just won't listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory I figured that out myself. I am just a retired lowly diploma graduate RN from 1968. Even so we worked 36… https://t.co/U1h44yCL9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis I just checked my photos and most have disappeared. I had many religious pictures and others. I’ll s… https://t.co/8jHi0PYnex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Furniture shopping makes me so happy yet so anxious. Decisions decisions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh my god i’m actually crying he’s so cute :( if he didn’t buy tex a new ball after this i’m fighting]]></document><document><![CDATA[2day i worked a clopen, got a latte spilled on my new jacket, n had 2 many fookin rude customers talk shit   things i have had: it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x0MDx0 Exactly. Like you realllllllllly think this works? And FRFR dude if your dick was that great i would alread… https://t.co/EPMmN2Ipl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever my #favoriteface to come home to! 🐶 Seeing my pup instantly makes everything better!✨💫 https://t.co/EVbGzhdDOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Olicity fandom right now after that promo... https://t.co/JfvKeyzotg]]></document><document><![CDATA[No better time to try mustard on a bagel bite than when you’re hungover as shit. Yes, I liked it. Would donit again… https://t.co/TStOznTEKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s ready for a day of Razorback BBall??? #DiamondHogs #FASTEST40 #wps #GoHogs 🐗🐗❤️❤️😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actions are very telling. People make time for what they want. &amp; if they really want to do something, they will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelwalexande @iff_or Derp has the finest ear furnishings. https://t.co/NdhPD0q7db]]></document><document><![CDATA[handcrafted antiques and imports from India! https://t.co/Qc9acMRo7X https://t.co/coDLDkUohS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have anxiety and you incessantly shaking your leg next to me and in turn shaking my seat is making it impossible… https://t.co/kR9J20Q7zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The discussion often lands around getting a shiny interface rather than looking at the human problem and exploring… https://t.co/Zvj1baJicQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electricasoul Lmaoo tea I’ll be buzzed off of one I’m that case some are just too bitter for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I for one don’t feel safe at school anymore. Why do we have a school resource officer if some creep can not only ge… https://t.co/Px5JVIDCTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do ppl dress cute for class at 8 am, i’m lucky if i show up with my hair brushed]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I will make with them a covenant of peace, and will cause the evil beasts to cease out of the land: and they sh… https://t.co/tLKqvetYaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoKupsGo That means so much &lt;333 so excited to work together again :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casually looking at Louis Vuitton Bags, might fuck around and buy one 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[my friends, my family, God, Obama: you tweet to much  me: i’m gonna tweet that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop this madness.  If transgender people want to compete, let them compete against each other in their very own tr… https://t.co/iq4aw43n8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoxybooMagic @DediShannon @LegatoTia @timlt4 @TewsTinamarie @marythemedium @Haifisch_Von @DeezaNeeza… https://t.co/XvbsHB208a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soul_of_Nowhere @cw_mills Always wish I had an On/Off switch!  But really...don’t be so worried about riding with… https://t.co/zyXn4LeO7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHSLionsSoccer As the mother of a GK, I support this philosophy 100%. ⚽️👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drayah15 Just way til we’re ballin together next year! Can’t wait balla]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay for hometown shows! Super hype for @mattnathanson @TLAPhilly #singshissadheart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@farah_zera You’re late... 😂 and I didn’t say all black women I said black Women WHO. So if you aren’t one of those… https://t.co/YfrD82r0Ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching saturday morning dance is always a good time since I get to hear how all the kids genuinely think I’m like… https://t.co/1Ey6D06fRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is 2019 HOW are people still using the wrong there/their/they’re, your/you’re and to/too ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[WWE fans who are going to the @wwe raw at @StateFarmArena Please keep it clean when @ATLHawks my come back #TrueToAtlanta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cranky_yankee @lacefire7 @SpeakerPelosi The woman from West Virginia had the temetry to actually speak of border s… https://t.co/WiuEuuTBu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t seen #LegoMovie2 yet, do it! Not only will this song be stuck in your head; but, although everything… https://t.co/f1C20o7gkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really impressed with @buffer Love  #thescienceofsocialmedia podcast and see you are also teaching classes on… https://t.co/FmgIKSku1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandmother was a libra and this was so true when I had her in my life prior to her passing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicardoAdams I'd be honored to have your follow !  #ArmyStrong #MAGA #NRA  #VIP on #TEAMMAGA IFB #KAG2020… https://t.co/zW7OTh18wt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulMarcGoulet  Love the picture of the group in Saturday's meeting.  You know why???YOU A L W A Y S  DISPLAY JOY,… https://t.co/qO98NKNRwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not this one. I disagree with the "too divisive" comment. But every other point she makes is solid. Y'all keep unde… https://t.co/FzajihLFkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Mexican ass really was about to flip this chicken breast with my hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3sticksCGCS @SyngentaTurf How often have you tilled the area? (Also, aachoo! 👃🏼🌾)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comaford Live the diagram. This will be so helpful in our Women's Wednesday class. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharon_cantley @vroberts9 @MissytheB @lynda3035 @BloomNight2 @marisbellamy1 @Marina935home We are doing fine, than… https://t.co/E6CbHNVsmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#icant with matthewjduggan21 #LOL #coworkerfun #tinyhat @ AMF Bowling Co. https://t.co/n33vn9F5eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriends niece put on clear lip gloss and he goes “why you put on all that lipstick you lookin like a damn pot of cooking oil” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @alexnazaryan lunacy and complete lack of comprehension of the English language besides--you can't… https://t.co/BRqJzybPqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesleyvancey have you seen wait until dark? it’s an audrey hepburn horror movie!! (don’t worry she doesn’t die)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenLeeSamar @LearnWithStumpf @HHSK8Knights Thank you for all your support and encouragement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe wholeheartedly that this is true. Hence, my nomadic life. @nickfrancoart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dianeinarizona @MargaretJosephs Yeah not her show, she’s just the original an oldie but not a goodie!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ethics teacher: you cant write this paper in a day me: watch me  *later* ethics teacher: you cant read Kant in 30 m… https://t.co/qbISkHpyu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord, thank you for allowing me to see another day! #Blessed #HighlyFavored]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizzieBroyles Same I lost mine and I feel like my belly button is naked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pam_brundige @MaryKeithBare1 @whazittoya @OttoSalaj @shawnalaree @patfoster698 @sealmh @CalynaHaunt @daynaltyler… https://t.co/jnPseUb4JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kybelle1957Liz @cspanwj You live your sheltered life and I'll live my life...Why do you care about me anyway's...i… https://t.co/DCPvNILaLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really losing the joy out of everything. Nothing excites me anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alucino con el trabajo que han hecho (como siempre) en @pictoline para los #Oscars . 👏👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broke my heart putting him on the trailer to head for Illinois, but this makes it all worth it. Makes my heart happ… https://t.co/dOYMYU9bVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaFunGurl @MisleaderC @strom_annette @esadah @Barb81146 @Cha51brolll19 @CunningSq16 @AussieDebBell… https://t.co/xbka5CCYC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_Zelinski @tokyotrojan @NoahCRothman When AOC speaks we need to listen. It identifies how many who voted for her,… https://t.co/IGTJ79NtMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachmarksmith @KCurl_2 @RazorbackFBRec @RazorbackFB Thank you for celebrating My Young King!! Warms my ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFerika I love to nap but I always feel so tired and drained when I wake up from a nap. #contentchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to say, I am a mother, I will always be a mother. I admit to being a mother.]]></document></documents></author>