<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio Switch to night shift full time and I find out Amy is not on https://t.co/rSZs6ci7Ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMotivation to that guy with his daughter on the uptown 6 train. If I’m only taking up one seat and the space… https://t.co/ix6hphKt9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Madea has won a whole lot of ‘em Oscars though! 😂👏🏽 @tylerperry #FallonTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksenijapavlovic @AOC Y’all should really drop this. He needed the secure email access to have access to her calend… https://t.co/0Oa9jCWR3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we can yield the faculty of our speech to the Spirit and speak in an unknown tongue, surely we can allow the sam… https://t.co/bTuGc2Bj0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatorsFB @KeiwanRatliff @CoachDanMullen Coach Mullen is the best at welcoming Gators back home to the Swamp... con… https://t.co/SaW1lZkF73]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Xbox/ PlayStation in the next year released a new console would you buy it ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardoScalaRider @BMWMotorrad https://t.co/fVmCY1PV0i https://t.co/WwpIH0EZSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @RachelStarrxxx @iamspanishdoll @therealJuliaAnn @GothCharlotte @EvaNotty @HadleyViscara… https://t.co/84AXzDELKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 Liberals have completely lost their minds in their quest for communism, infanticide, and open borders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to get serious about investing in transit and connecting more Minnesotans to opportunities in the… https://t.co/l0KTChdnLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to present some interesting trauma experiences from @UTChattSurgery @erlangerhealth this morning… https://t.co/y5Ong1iQxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsBayleyWWE I love both of you , thanks for whooping nia and that loser ass they had it coming .  I knew you coul… https://t.co/VBtFKQi4CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaRKaplan And if they dont do what their constituence want, they better start looking for a different line of work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind The enemies of democracy are dark money influence, division, and selecting coverage which represents p… https://t.co/Rf5YQwIh7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please take a moment to look over and sign if it resonates with you.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYIslanders @ledpipe08 @zeeker11 Run them out of the building lolololololol what a shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/xEbpTDuvRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlohaHa59067534 @Jenn198523 @SenKamalaHarris Yeah she’s a liar a typical corrupt democratic politician from the gr… https://t.co/7xJEFfROS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenchamp10 my tweets give you this reaction, your snapchat stories give me the same one (except maybe even a me… https://t.co/OhDMkBpa5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykorderas Yes. What made him the best was his performances? look? Mic work? Combination? Many believe his matc… https://t.co/62oOZ0dUid]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the first time I remember mom @Melaniehicksxxx taking it up her ass... pretty damn nice https://t.co/rHl8TXtUrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrabienMedia And he has done everything he could! It is not his fault the American people are dumber than an anvil… https://t.co/lP48BbYZrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cappinggoat @fairgroundsnola I’m (again) in the #1 on top, but 3,6,8 also useable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro, those look like 18 year old kids. Soulja, you was seriously nice many years ago but do something else with you… https://t.co/qJqewJOELe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen when you make her go off so intense from good timed hand grip that it shoots a big hard pumping peice… https://t.co/n0IEAOKxCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Jackson’s voice is distinctive, powerful and dramatic. This record underscores all of those points. From 1962… https://t.co/OXRdsbuBgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A GM who’s going to have a top draft pick (again) and not doing any scouting is certainly an um... unconventional a… https://t.co/2YcoAp5ftM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the emoji I use to sum up my life at the moment: 🤷🏽‍♂️. Lol! What’s yours?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being interviewed after a loss. Not fun.  GG to TSM and always make good on a bet -  @RiotDash]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA referees are a joke. That is not a technical foul. @NBAOfficial can’t have a thin skin like that when 2 of the… https://t.co/bg3JyX8vyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Managed a Be Our Guest lunch reservation this morning. I haven't been since 2014, so I'm interested to see if I like it or not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must be March Break. I’ve bumped into a half dozen teachers already! (@ Detroit Metropolitan Wayne County Airport -… https://t.co/kTQagFC6kL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A killer song from my boys Small Town Titans called “More or Less”. Recorded at #hybridstudiospa for “The Hybrid Se… https://t.co/zunfiUiL52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all of the women who aren’t good enough for me https://t.co/ZCm8AnfCyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegHarr06653947 @shiftywatt @Bravewriting 👆brand new account this mint, 6 followers, arguing with everyone ......… https://t.co/bajpPpd3ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SquawValley get record snow. Open till July 7th.  Ski July 4th holiday !!!!#GlobalWarming  hmmmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS FINALLY HERE! HAPPY RELEASE DAY @BettyWho!!! #Betty #StreamBetty #BuyBetty https://t.co/1WKT9uwltz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro I hope he is a better actor than he is a criminal. Because he is really bad at being a criminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snacks Did he think you were gonna get a sack if the center didn't "serve" you? He apparently doesn't know what a NT's job is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude I fucking hate the way they cut my hair dawg ughhhh I’m just gonna tell my unc to shave it all fuck it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ozzythepainter yeah and lizzo relocated to LA didn't she? hippo campus always touring out of state hell they're in… https://t.co/Q5iTgEVJ08]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was advocating @DrJacobsRad not lobbying ??? Was he registered? SNC-Lavalin has had 19 contacts with the PMO sin… https://t.co/y7Xy69YEv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATabarrok 1. Something very relevant to your field—in 1996. 2. Not sure, your CV was last updated in 2009. 3. The… https://t.co/QQgwkK4WWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost from @ArtofSacredSex  This moved me deeply...   #TheAcademyforMen #JustAddSkill #LaurieHandlers #tantra… https://t.co/GfBhB4tCxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falling asleep to lightning reminds me of summer in Phoenix (see thread), and that’s honestly... not a great memory]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmieswain moving some weight this morning in our NFL Pro Day Training. Power Clean 335#x3 #grindtimefit… https://t.co/vbHs0RNEeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickmon1112 @discordapp What about pub corn? That shit will break your teeth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmanderz https://t.co/jVqXBtBASn  They have a bunch of different ones if you go to the main page!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i used to feel bad for vanya in the umbrella academy but now i hate her so much omfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Is B-Roll Important? https://t.co/6yt82MbXc2 via @YouTube @petermckinnon @MattiHaapoja @CaseyNeistat @YTCreators @AaronMFilms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phantom 4 Flying Over Anderson Ferry https://t.co/0RPK95UekO via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to give this bitch the Sopranos special. What u say @CBurleyESPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if in captain marvel the after credits scene has Scott Pilgrim appear https://t.co/FErG700RDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got done cleaning up the snow/ice/slush combination in the driveway. It's a weekend thing here in Iowa now! St… https://t.co/937KWtxYIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Episode Alert 🚨 (Direct Link in the Bio) #podsystem #podsincolor #podernfamily #podsbyqpoc #bhm #podcast… https://t.co/Hy7bfTC5JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danrivoli @StreetsblogNYC @jonorcutt @Komanoff @DavidWeprin @AARPNY @AARPNY did not endorse congestion pricing at… https://t.co/B1KE9Jz6Nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill In Berkeley, is it a criminal offense to punch a conservative activist in the face?  It wasn’t when I live… https://t.co/YD1r9JJld7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This core exercise will help develop those flip turns. #usms #mastersswimming #swimmerproblems #MondayMotivation… https://t.co/4OlQxl6s6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to the current road conditions, Wabash City Schools will be operating on a 3 hour delay for Wednesday, February… https://t.co/3em5heiuK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olympicchannel @NBCSN I wish @ChadSalmela was commentating the women's 30k. These guys are good, but Chad is Chad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaTeague15 i would but its 4 am here...I'd end up on #LivePD  without the live lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WL8on3 @PressSec @BennieGThompson Another corporate loyalist voting for trafficking, teen prostitution, crime and… https://t.co/rPd1KIFgYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_babb @sully7777 You just asked. They don’t have to bid. I guess Barton could bid. You know, somehow the mana… https://t.co/ZaKXiuDDJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWStream Hope Jamie will give him some of his earnings. When mother Vince reads that tweet hulkster won’t be coming back to wwe .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone, somewhere has something on the Grahamski!  Perhaps it has something to do with the Trumpski!… https://t.co/s35bNzqlWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[To give without remembering and to receive without forgetting. Amen. #generous #grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiantSalted Hey man I’m really sorry to hear about this. I appreciate you hanging out tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see Spadaro is back at work on his burner account.  Really sad that one of the most powerful priests in the world… https://t.co/bkXir0PmS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time has come for you to lip sync FOR YOUR LIFE! @RuPaulsDragRace #Season11 @WorldOfWonder #DragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecreasedive Get @WyattKat3 on @thecreasedive. I want to hear the full story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMayer28 Hi!!! Still early but every projection I see has us going there if we make it. 👍 I think we could fill… https://t.co/IFnAsSkP74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strawberry Festival 🍓 Good vibez💯 Great food🍖🌭🍔 Big Smiles😁 !!! @ Strawberry Festival Neighborhood Village https://t.co/UWLHdnHTR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[4.2 treadmill run in 33:06 7:52/mile 142 Avg HR 622 calories burned #thankful #fitness https://t.co/EmFsnxYi2z @PlanetFitness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time will bring you to peace. Time heals. While that time passes, stay who you are as a person, be careful with sub… https://t.co/jTVaaS3hrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @MichaelCohen212 And that fbi raid of his office to get privileged client info is illegal and appall… https://t.co/B96L6h8ZgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackmurphylive @GoldmundUnleash @Delicious_Tacos @jondutoit @TrueLegendFilms Have sabo on too. https://t.co/UKCZ38GKoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all the insanity that happened at @papasandbeer this weekend. Can’t wait to get home and cuddle with bae. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6. I’ve been nominated by @SteveGriff9 to post covers of 7 books that I love; no explanations or reviews, just… https://t.co/nTs7JAZFFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We wrestle #together. @GonzagaSports @GZ_Wrestling #MenForOthers #HailGonzaga ✊🏼#AMDG @DCSAASports https://t.co/v5mDlWmOIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael17311045 What blows me away about Bay is that to start his career he made three of the all time best action… https://t.co/axAYcIfH1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single one of Nicole Holofcener’s scripts for her own movies is better than the script for CYEFM but that’s t… https://t.co/NkUKLOmAYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sports_Aaron @KidNesto03 @coachbrea @ChrisDuerr Packed house last night! Fun atmosphere https://t.co/vMScb3eeeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny @UKJBB @AOC Umm..."Bunny?" If @aoc was afraid of people "making fun" of her, I don't think she would h… https://t.co/5KnDaSRFms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharpFootball one of our favorite listens all the time. Please consult w my team, the Philadelphia Eagles on not j… https://t.co/u8cK3kdhJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @Debby_Villegas @SydneyDChase @robin_ked @anna_deardorff @Michael_Hudak @DrWhoisin @MarilynLavala… https://t.co/hxpwr5pTyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying some 2A state championship basketball games today.  So proud of my high school.  Both boys and girls baske… https://t.co/HFMkOzRpwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanPre88872565 @QueenKarma69 @AdultBrazil @PQColor @R_sidney_V @janklaar2 @Bigtitbabes @suprshok @badkittysub… https://t.co/BN0WbrJxoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti This image says it all. Using the flag as a prop. A crook next to old glory. Pathetic pathetic pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorMalafaia Homossexualismo é condição também. Intrínseco à natureza humana. É por isso que existe em toda soci… https://t.co/jOBd2DlgGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DutchRojas @UnbridledMd @misterchambo @moylubimykroko @LeahHoustonMD @mloxton @physicianswkly @HCUnmaskedfilm… https://t.co/ggVspb8bQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyle_mace I get earaches like it’s my job and gum never does any good. Using a heating pad or holding a hot mug to… https://t.co/QeZ8IV8LhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joe_RODO I have 5 practice alarms to snooze before my real ones go off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I so quite ? Because I'm getting shit done instead of talking about it for a year .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolcomenter @johnblake02 @Dragon_Bawlz @TonyGrossi Dude you’re grasping at straws. Filling Jamie Collins spot /… https://t.co/kRFlFlJbg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karissaaag @rebeccamarrieee @sandyyycheeks_ Miss you all so much already 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holy_schnitt Lol, no the ladies would protect you, but I made a mistake on my taxes once they just send you bill. A nasty threat too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Leaked Chats, Nebraska GOP Gov’s Field Director Pushed White Nationalism:  Bennett Bressman expressed his allegi… https://t.co/zZD0vHgWzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cybraryman1 Please visit me in Swansea the next time you’re in the area. We would be honored!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jerk Chicken Burger with Bacon 🥓 #ChefBurnZ @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/vSTkLHDbG7]]></document></documents></author>