<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you care about kids, teachers, education, your taxes, Arizona or journalism, you should read it and then subscri… https://t.co/eyqatiLly9]]></document><document><![CDATA[12:53 Temp. 77°F, Hum. 44%, Dewp. 53.2°F, Bar. 30.00 inHg, Rain Today 0.0039 inch, Wind 111° 1.1 m/s  #WUTV #knchamps26 #WECTwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[These #pizza slices have a crispy thin crust and slightly sweet sauce that you only find in #nyceats. @ Joe's Pizza https://t.co/16SMaTAV7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candice Accola and Nina Dobrev Pose Together in Their Very First Photoshoot https://t.co/BUQLBX87aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@137pm @garyvee Who did your mom stop you from thinking you're stupid when you started to realize you couldn't read… https://t.co/JQVyIviBNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liztc2 @KatBenn1plus2 Whenever I put All in the Family on she makes that same face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@complexmath I have 2 levels banked and am toying with the idea of adding in a Fae Patron and taking a level of Warlock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikeggibbs Yes. Why is Canadian mainstream media dragging Peter MacKay’s sorry ass out into public again? I don’t… https://t.co/Ihb6M3GGOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[YouScience is here!  Available now for all 9th-12th graders in Pontotoc, Lee, and Union County schools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrate international women’s day by picking up this great book from an industry pro - only at… https://t.co/uNpptjlmNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKidPoker Because all three sides, Democrats, Republicans and the person testifying (obviously Cohen in this case) have an agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredZaifman @EdtheSock @londonmusichall Followed me today too. Awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s your pick today in Phoenix at @ISMRaceway? I’ve got Brad Keselowski for the win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwoods55 @PatriotSally Checking the effects of cow farts https://t.co/OzQIiwJHcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this what the QAnon whackjobs meant when they said Trump would expose the child molesters who walk among us??? #kraft #epstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pirro is really a monster. How she has a show I have no idea. Oooh wait yeah I do fox news home to racists and hate… https://t.co/1w6cyKpPwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it be a good time for all the left-wing lunatic‘s that do not like President Trump or America to get on the… https://t.co/QbnEjWcTMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My First car was a all original 4 door 77 cutlass.....baby blue with the white leather top...man i miss that bitch… https://t.co/jHVHep1vSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@North_Resists @MikeTay60703904 @HeatherMallick @TorontoStar For clarity- it was her job to overrule the Prosecutio… https://t.co/kMrzrBpFDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnePatton comments on Fox. says 1 of 2 things about her, she’s truly naive that she’s a token or she knows she i… https://t.co/1yzuvmq3jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way all of you who followed. Jackson life were always suspicious of his behavior...the two men claims were c… https://t.co/DfGTJwt7T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CordulaHansen @AltspaceVR Virtual Reality mimicking Reality - love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paranoiacs The amount of Zevon he played after the terminal diagnosis was announced is circumstantial evidence in favor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubsFanHan @brielarson Same group said shit about Black Panther when it came out too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#2020goals for my business. Looking for ya'lls loving support and holding me accountable while I go on this journey… https://t.co/vtmgWZv74V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord Rothschild Confirm, Trump Removed In Mar 2019?The Illuminati Controls the Deep State! https://t.co/XO5122TyEm… https://t.co/FBP6mQyhjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @GregShugar @realDonaldTrump Stop being a black American racist...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martynwendell The Fall is wonderful! My buddy in HS would rent obscure movies that we'd watch, and The Fall was th… https://t.co/S0XYy4jYfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bob Arum: Wilder-Fury II can do bigger PPV numbers with ESPN backing https://t.co/3MOFlCtIcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The politicians have been "talking" since Ronald Reagan was President and nothing has been accomplished. It is grea… https://t.co/q5XpzicSJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone go check out my good friend @ky_klicks Patreon page!  She has a ton of amazing rewards and some awesome se… https://t.co/r6ntVbNHgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Jordan gives all buckeyes a bad name. He is a piece of trash. Just something to ponder on this wonderful Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRByrd3 @Forrest_Barnes @PaulHembo Yeah but the contracts are like 12 years so you can make@more money in football… https://t.co/59eJxHzusT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coastal Walk - https://t.co/CX6htT1qgU #booklover #writing @ Rehoboth Beach, Delaware https://t.co/1dLKqVNq8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeAreTheNews You are against President Trumph like the rest. Face it, wait till he makes his decision then make th… https://t.co/ygeQMuokjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillysport A sellout of more than half of Nova fans. More alums in NYC area than anywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaseidler The "no position players who are tall enough to ride the roller coaster" team]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFoodie8 Turners Dairy In #PennHillsPA is the absolute best no doubt about it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy sitting next to me on this flight is probably around 60 and has a bag full of mint hard candies that he’s o… https://t.co/NQqIRDcRVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who Ever Said Angst Ends with Your Teens? . . . But actually, you’ve never played roadkill before? Come on!  . . .… https://t.co/r3jUtCGpDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clash of KingsGoddess is coming, come find your goddess! https://t.co/SPizSbUDhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sayyjoee @slightwork352 @samspiegs @CoachJaysmith18 @BillyEmbody @JeritRoser @gabrieldbrooks @DemetricDWarren… https://t.co/Kv4Ilv3opg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith Did it ever occur to you that if a pro player can't stop smoking weed there might be a bigger issue… https://t.co/nE6YFTh4rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drax: "That's a made-up word." Thor: "All words are made up."  I've tweeted about this before but it delights me th… https://t.co/tCNDY2Ie5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Millennium Flacon crashed into Lake Michigan, and I am afraid I couldn’t dig her out. Shot in Feb 2019.… https://t.co/r0oEhfkDMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lvlightsfc Would have rather not won these free tickets.  But I guess I am back at Cashman on the 30th #vivalights]]></document><document><![CDATA[spring glam! #nars #AnastasiaBeverlyHills #morphe #spring #influenster #FentyBeauty https://t.co/HptquHRcv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so hard to like girls as being bisexual, I’m attracted to lesbians and gay men and I’m like boy wth can’t one… https://t.co/Bsth0tfu1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help a brother out  For real-time crime and safety alerts in your area, download the Neighbors app. Here's the link: https://t.co/nw9Bghk5hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t act like y’all ain’t never climbed in the backseat of your truck to eat some Skyline after dropping your kid… https://t.co/gAcJeHZdcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Harvest Red by @MetierBrewing @ Métier Brewing Company — https://t.co/8xQFFnCOqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarAndBrew I wanna day yeah. They have them all over. I’m surprised one isn’t in SJ yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, as Medicare and college for all/any will garner more resistance. I think Amy’s approach if one step-at-time i… https://t.co/4hwt13mr01]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Country for Old Men and The Departed are the only two films in the past two decades to be my personal winners. T… https://t.co/Kgi0P4tdTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fake fuck with me back then but it’s getting hard for you to fake it now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima watch that cap go all the way up too *double entendre too don’t ask me how]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Boulevard Heights, Pembroke Pines, Florida https://t.co/zoK01SL4df]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...we switched to this new ISP awhile back. Was skeptical at first. 100Mbps down AND up for $50/month. No way. We… https://t.co/RSFBSVfPvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not many things prettier.   Some people like nature. Others architecture or art.   I prefer a ball being lifted ove… https://t.co/M17Zd86ZFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel New York City - Chelsea in New York, NY https://t.co/lcRThbyiD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtlevy I think prerequisite to this discussion is viewing the relevant Hornblower episode, “The Mutiny”. Not only… https://t.co/QOc2w1qa7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like little brother to try an upstage the Hawks on they’re big media day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CityofMcAllen: You must allow @CCharitiesRGV and @nspimentel to stay put at their current location. https://t.co/XbEQwyA4aU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I care that Gott Man (allegedly) paid DSJ? Do I care that DSJ (allegedly) took cash? https://t.co/iu1rhiH4W9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessieNOlson @PaulaRe56252389 @doc_tdg @DJNazSD @pwhitaker62 @lynngermaine @davisallen46 @WagonKnoggin @hoxie_jack… https://t.co/3XhLMIZ6aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayStation I forgot trine was a thing. I played trine 2 a little, years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComunicacionEc @Lenin @BancoMundialLAC @AxelVT_BM @LasManuelasEc #LeninDelincuenteOffShore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I agree James. He’s a piece of shit. Anyone that could shoot a female officer with no warning like… https://t.co/dNX7YGKO0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kick1972 pourquoi Cadotte n'a pas fini avec un arrêt Jordan? Pourquoi on a fait passer son procès devant les procè… https://t.co/1DzoGinoU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time, energy and focus are at your disposal every day, use it. -Unknown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyYunker1 What do you think 🤔 about this....if Lions want to get rid of Stafford as much as it seems trade them… https://t.co/nlH7eirxMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[SF police investigating death of Public Defender Jeff Adachi, but do not suspect foul play https://t.co/QN8gPZR9P0… https://t.co/70Duif8RFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[An AMAZING Cake! Dad loved it! 🤗💥💥 Thank You! pastry_katmcg Sorry it's Non Keto. @ Muse and Market https://t.co/ZQtGvTcGC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[First of all, fuck you and the clique you claim. You ain’t shit. If you were in front of me I’d honestly shoot you… https://t.co/FY7kHNOiEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCandDigger @alexhawkxxx @PupDigger @scallysex @hot_connection @gayporncrushes @QueerMeNow @LittleGayBlog… https://t.co/dWUOvMWQC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes, it’s okay to fight fire with fire. my flame won’t be put out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchyGallo @joeyalfieri I believe the coaching decisions made on this road trip will cost us big time along with… https://t.co/5dhoZ9Vfwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juliette Barron, aka Family Dollar Jewels #chavezhighschool #classof2005 @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/geTPq0F43o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seeohellee Just think, there's probably a vibrator out there running Android making this not a problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Evan_Forman @LookingForTelos I’ll back him up - read Alien Bodies first. Pretty easy to jump into and it’s one of… https://t.co/zBaPgIF1jR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CopsAreNazis Not yet, it just started yesterday. It's probably going to get worse before it gets better. Thanks though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@posey_miles LCA🦅🏈 in order to have a great team you must change The bad culture Of disrespecting authority Coaches… https://t.co/440JpFAfW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaySton72555025 @MattWeaverAW I could gripe for days about the struggle of running a TrackStar. That differential… https://t.co/Elt8k17Caj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join defendernetwork for Conversations and Coffee series gives the Black community an opportunity to engage up clos… https://t.co/KTLJIRE3vr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I like pictures of your dogs and every day I couldn’t care less about pictures of your dogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOBIpod @BadIdeasPodcast @Michael_Leal @TPCCafe @Scareythoughts2 @BesottedGeekPod @PittsburghNerd @pinkolliphant… https://t.co/HUMwIKzMSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although I'm a terrible barometer for chess skills, I am continually amazed with my kids' skills. I'm betting withi… https://t.co/gTWtXjFxvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're going to the "SHIP"!  Come out Saturday Morning and cheer these young men on as they battle for the City of A… https://t.co/gbx3LXSVJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyWilson @AnnWilson And he probably said the same thing about seeing you two! 🤩@RobertPlant @ledzeppelin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nysportsfan2015 @EastBhamKid @NickM538 @madShana @DiStitz @_WeAreND_ @G792Mike @Zalman888 @LifeGal4 @Amber00924… https://t.co/PLeBmmbMK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CruxEZz @PurpleFilms88 If it’s not amazing I hope they wouldn’t even try]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_christopher @WesleyLowery It is definitely more embarassing but I’ve also been known to patronize that bar during important games 😬😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3LWTV @CBSNews @GayleKing Seriously, this is celebrity news.  Can you please stop the distractions and talk about… https://t.co/8vAn2qBw78]]></document><document><![CDATA[SI NAHUEL SALIERA, SALTARA, ESTIRARA LOS BRAZOS, CERRARA LOS PUÑOS, SEGURO EVITARÍA GOLES RIVALES, OJALÁ LEA ESTO O… https://t.co/J9wsHx8E7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcwestwood Thanks for re-mentioning this.  Trumps friends and supporters quickly forget the problems Trump has with mouth diarrhea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealHughJackman @donaldglover Good lord I didn’t know he was a midget!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoscoeBDavis1 @BetoORourke @JessicaTarlov @FoxNews Looks like a horse and cattle auction?]]></document><document><![CDATA[BIRD BOGGLE: help @rescue_wild find this spoonbill with something wrapped around it’s neck! The bird is in the area… https://t.co/enOpokuXuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why not Great Wall of China? That at least kept invaders OUT. Berlin Wall had to keep people IN. #BuildTheWall #MAGA https://t.co/7L8DOvFA4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@townhallcom Or, as in my case over the years, when things changed from time to time, I neglected to increase my withholding!]]></document></documents></author>