<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Crimen puso a gobernador de Tamaulipas, revela informe https://t.co/8eJktBcSQ4 vía @El_Universal_Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielrskinner If the @ameriprise building is a dry ice factory, then yes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaOnlyLivvOnce @sarahloganwwe @RubyRiottWWE Tonight made me realize that the Riot Squad will never stop pillaging… https://t.co/bTZGe2kntM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how even as a young adult some still lack simple discipline]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙋‍♂️ maybe we should cut taxes on the construction of affordable housing if we’re in an affordable housing crisis… https://t.co/xrGnlrpOfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlottesville City Councilors Heather Danforth Hill​ and Kathleen Galvin​ and Restauranteur Peter Castiglione joi… https://t.co/SEVIQxoaJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the highlights from The @headcountorg Retreat!! We did some amazing Team Building Exercises, learned some B… https://t.co/hkQcjHYtt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flats are the superior wing. Fight me. @WestoAdam https://t.co/GmA1yWjMKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people aren’t occasionally telling you “your preaching is too deep” AND/OR “your preaching is too focused on app… https://t.co/vccLqk6GFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBoeckner Jews are Pretty brutal they like to acknowledge intolerance towards them but say nothing when they cas… https://t.co/nQf1G4Z4Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisneyParks doesn’t do student discounts for park entry...what’s up with that??]]></document><document><![CDATA[My basketball coach in hs always told me “you control your future, everything you do is based of your decisions” an… https://t.co/2lyALB0Dcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now @WORXTools Aerocart is a 9-in-1 All-Purpose Carrier. She’s a natural at marketing! https://t.co/ErjzR557L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.I.P father I love you so much ❤❤❤ be with God. My Superman. In memory born Thursday November 14, 1963 - died mond… https://t.co/24unDWJjjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spoolnpull @true198 @spectatorindex These are just personal attacks. In the reading, I have no idea what positions… https://t.co/Otj0g8NUEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CIOPDFW https://t.co/xjMMEhP7ls via @CIOevents Looking forward to joining @kenpiddington to talk about the risks a… https://t.co/JC2JOcZ2BX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it's good! Damn good actually. That's my one problem with @PolarBeverages A lot of the great combo flavors are… https://t.co/elWMEWoIen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eklund Miller did all he could to be on the West Coast for his wife. I highly doubt he will accept a move back to… https://t.co/44M4LpYVXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Just shut up you obtuse dullard. Milton Friedman said :  "It's just obvious you can't have free immig… https://t.co/7uOkVUtszq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Downside - Preston’s baseball tournament is rained out this weekend! 👿    Upside - we now get to go to Waco for a… https://t.co/H9PvfKDDzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venezolanoenpie @gabylugoarcia Como integrate de VP no quiero ver a ninguna chavistas incorporado a ningún gobiern… https://t.co/PBJPhWPPrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[LSW Hurdlers, see you at 3:00 at the school. Let’s meet in the lower hallway by the aux gyms. @LSWGirlsTF  @LSWTitanRunning #LSWHURDLES]]></document><document><![CDATA[boiii.. idk why I agreed to go to sherlock’s but man this shit hasn’t changed at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tj_mayes_ I had to hold back in a meeting today. I only had 7 thin mints]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @southernwayjim @RealMattCouch @DaRealGrizzle @SuperEliteTexan @TrumpOrBust2020 @buzzman888… https://t.co/dA9GAWHDpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARHoopScoop They just want next Saturday to pass.... then the few in power who are against the move... will breathe a big sigh of relief..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum @Cernovich Can someone tag every author and broadcaster of each piece of content?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I kind of respect the fact Cardi got back w/ Offset.   Other females would’ve had a new nigga in like two weeks 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsabelTurrent pertenece a ese sector que se sienten dueños del país. Para ejemplo vean el uso de esa aristocrática… https://t.co/IMd6gmvOzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Starbucks in Shelton, CT https://t.co/zsYbXgNu48 https://t.co/VtSFMDfKy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those just discovering the line-sitting/standing thing, it may not be glamorous but it is actual work.  It’s pa… https://t.co/KWGOrGxTdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orrrr you could just go put up shots in a gym with the round ball that you actually play with and learn that way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 @tbell1968 He was fucking around on his ex wife with her for those two years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved all of John Candy’s comedy skits and movies!  Hard to believe it’s been 25 years.  RIP John Candy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaronzioVance Hey man I totally steered clear of al the drama between Khloe and Jordyn. I mean I don’t even know a… https://t.co/h0UjyAbMeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Coach Miller and @HanoverMBB on another HCAC title.  Coach does it the right way and gets everything ou… https://t.co/UTjb73yJGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Hey Kamala , time for some Justice for Jessie- tell him to turn himself it - A-hole 🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched  A Star Is Born for the first time Saturday. Bought the sound track. Watched him and Gaga on the Oscars. Br… https://t.co/gQFgfB0VXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RussianAssets #MAGA @AliVelshi  Looking forward to Ali Velshi's production of RUSSIA, IF YOU'RE LISTENING. On July… https://t.co/XIzAGGaIfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StaumontSZN is officially on hold. I had high hopes for him to make the 25 man, but hopefully a good outing at Oma… https://t.co/ZGA0RcgM0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[On March 1 - 3 I will be presenting on the Main Stage of @Wisdom2conf in San Francisco. I am amazed to be in the co… https://t.co/Q1mqnSQVPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveThunderfan @three0threes Wasn't him and Noel much higher at the beginning of the season. Also, I am specifica… https://t.co/r3gAEqBEYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaloneTalia happy birthday potato head🤪🥳🎂 enjoy today n be safe today lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #FAKENationalEmergency does not exist according to Trumplthinskin. https://t.co/95zeeBV2kJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing encapsulation of #productculture mapped to #lean #agile and #designthinking !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenLHall1 So true. We're a commonwealth in trouble. Putin rejoices as Trump undermines our sense of right and w… https://t.co/nAZdMLQrVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @_sallyxsquirt @GentleLilBird @JessikaGotti @Maxx_attax @x_summers @JennaIvoryxxx @AliciaSecret @HimexMarie… https://t.co/6GSJJjU6VB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yeshua_porvida Mention the Mormons, JWs or oneness Pentecostals and few say anything. Those "faiths" deny the deit… https://t.co/8XoH8HLKO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkACollett Good news they now should receive minority scholarships !! RIGHT ,,, yes that will happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boogie2988 Lots of Fallout 76, and hopefully some of @TheDivisionGame Beta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iris and I except she wants to be on the WWE shit and I just fuck her up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikemullen_ Is this punishment for the teens, punishment for you, or a mixture of both?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NastiboijDrake That’s what they do here for the thrill posting it online and don’t the police know the b8 spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We put weight on what and how much we think people need to know. But perhaps what we should be considering, is who… https://t.co/SkumePyIVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews In a courtroom this statement would draw a speculation objection. It was designed answer to bolster the ‘fear Trump’ agenda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECHSinCFBISD @CFBISD Chris B. presenting a Rotary 4-way Test speech Carrollton @rotary https://t.co/tDfZV7gHQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarsEclipse I dabble with both. I bought one when they first released and I also have the Smash Bros. limited edition pro controller]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Kofi fan myself, but I would have loved for @MustafaAliWWE to have shined in that match instead. Hopefully,… https://t.co/Y6BP1c9jIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrozenSicleGirl That's not the right one I saw another site that had the odds that were a way better than that I'm… https://t.co/p8NBOsmvIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamconover What's even worse is that homelessness could be completely preventable all together but that doesn't m… https://t.co/qZXimqNcBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Runas091120 @MCU_Tweets @MarvelStudios @brielarson We’ve had loads of “man only” team up films Relax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court documents detail that Kincaid allegedly left alcohol at the victim’s home as a gift, introduced himself to a… https://t.co/Ddxe5hSlq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect #escaped #classic #rustic #rugged #beater #precious #authentic #oldies #💛 #beauty #oldschool #gem @ Glendal… https://t.co/mGydqllMQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leviticus 26 {THIS TIME, Joseph's RUPTURE into Captivity is “Cut Short” to 2520 DAYS instead of YEARS! Ephraim, or… https://t.co/mM9kFOUwUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastianpinera Y también pídale a Insulza que le pida perdón a los venezolanos, la Patria de Andrés Bello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BVelasa97 @qtf Mira chaira lo que le importa a la Zopilota @BeatrizGMuller primera caracoles de México tu comentar… https://t.co/NI3mCULPKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BC3inAZ As a victim of a similar crime I, respectfully, disagree. You don’t get it until you’re in it. It is what… https://t.co/YP9fcGr0eK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenCurry30 Nice. Still think Wham Bam Can of Ham makes for a great colorway!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Skiing ⛷ weather ❄️ . . . . #winter #fun #newjersey @ Mountain Creek https://t.co/JwBvnTikDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realistzen I turned it down because I already had one, but the gesture was definitely appreciated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carrie_gee I do it so much that I type question marks after sentences I'd say with extra rising intonation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You wake up tomorrow and the only song that exists in the world is loser by beck (1993) WYD ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew I wasnt the only one. Every baseball guy I know cant resist some dry hacks in front of a mirror. Lol every t… https://t.co/B0lNbyfurm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SER1897 I think it would be zzzzzzzzzzz sorry I nodded off thinking g about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbarolo Great spring break! Beach by day, Pride and Prejudice by evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vbspurs We in amateur radio have a term for ones such as these ladies:  Lid -  a poor operator; one who is inept a… https://t.co/TJCRSPTMWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 straight days of tests, and I found out today I got A’s in all of them 🥰 look at my God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bitterwhiteguy If I end up playing MLB The Show 19 as much as I did the last few years, I probably won't but I kinda miss it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The basics of horror are you need someone to root for. Either a hero fighting a monster (GET OUT) or a charismatic… https://t.co/hWRZa7Qn7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobcesca_go @MalcolmNance 2020 will take place without Prisoner 45. The question is what did Flynn say about Pence… https://t.co/G6vrEFTndU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up poor in Sharpstown, from when i was ten years old i dreamt of the day i would have the opportunity to make money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Jo Jo White died. If you played guard growing up in Boston when I did, you wanted to wear number 10. Period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathleenfugle @makeymakey @smartinez @gravescolleen @garystager So jealous of this library! #makered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_svpremewitch I keep track of when i turn on uber to when i turn off uber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__feverqueen It’s just way too depressing for me idk I don’t think I’ll ever be able to watch it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a video of every student in America walking into class today after daylight savings time. https://t.co/dgH5pOFomg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessyMarv86 @Katdaddy23 That's facts! Will never front on Coach Calhoun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyMesleyCBC @AndrewScheer @lraitt Really earning that $650 million bucks eh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typically occurs during work presentations and any game of #ApexLegends. https://t.co/74KpbrOI7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A WALL of HIRING at the Border of Pres. Trump's STAFFING  THIS NOTE is LegA-L tender For STAFFING… https://t.co/kxjJCfT5Zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always wondered why California has open borders with Nevada. They’re ruining our culture! JK, of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RestDay. #Me 👉🏽😂✌🏽🐦 @Sixp8ck - 📷📹 #ShreddedBeyondABSolute #PeopleWhoLifts #MyOutlet #JustEatSleepLiftThings… https://t.co/80UDPGAQii]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find it interesting those who write, act or do music or any other platform for entertaining others that those not… https://t.co/zwXgqWeol9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniumHammer Nah. We just den‘t believe in gods because the evidence for them is not there.  Combine this with t… https://t.co/iRK99Lg9Oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aitch2O81 @Made_Man_5 @sonnie_inkstar @Mathieu_Era He got a better chance of winning back home tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ As far as I am concerned, he is a mass murderer and should be imprisoned.  Hopefully one day soon abort… https://t.co/N1xJu7vrZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodyLeilaniJ @morganisawizard @Zach_Wallen @Alfred_Zepeda @CelestialVampyr https://t.co/h7hiVFnAgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think god is in favor in anyway to kill babies. Maybe it’s the Devils work their trying to get done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From enneagramandcoffee on Instagram, evidence I have been appropriately typed https://t.co/cLeLDPttYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 3 year old son is watching kingdom hearts walk throughs on YouTube. 😎]]></document></documents></author>