<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Colton is to Cassie what Khloe is to Tristan. Just take the L, bro. #ItsANo #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleismyna2 And hell I’d say that was some expensive sex, but he didn’t get that. Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @CIA @FBI @NSAGov @ODNIgov @DeptofDefense @realDonaldTrump We will never forget how Paul Ryan, speaking fo… https://t.co/STN6HQNTAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMplusG Another one who blames HRC for everything.  He is on chump’s payroll]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on down to the bluegrass, young man. The love of the BigBlueNation awaits with open arms!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuintonLucasKC Please. I have to find alternative routes because of potholes that cannot be avoided.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CrohnsDisease needs a cure too, everyone’s walk is their own.  Praying for cures across the board!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonasbrothers Done signed up...😊 Hoping I be the lucky winner, would be amazing 2 win as it would be a great early… https://t.co/dXQgnSobXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karaswisher @mattgaetz @TwitterSupport please ban him - this is a threat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarnellDaHustla @GrimKim I literally just said I support your campaign. I’m a prison abolitionist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is cool bc I get to show off my favorite color ❤️🥰💋 https://t.co/MZ2EcXKnbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[finally got my car back and my friends asked me if I decided what I was going to name it.  I did. Nobody liked that… https://t.co/hyBfgtiBiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 @sooze555 Correction: The lies are up to 9041–Trump told over 100 (one hundred) at CPAC after his flag hugg… https://t.co/LZtd8JD0a2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday #lovewins #dated #traveled #engaged #fought #married #watchedtv #hadkids #plannedhisdeath Just… https://t.co/sGGMkcjB1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pixies|Weezer: Such a fun show! Please excuse the videography, the dancing did not stop. We need to go on more date… https://t.co/74IbA9q4w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to our @USCDM family for this sweet surprise that was waiting for Braden when we returned home last night… https://t.co/kL1vTPfziV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allywalker1 I’m at a conference @CPAC and yesterday I had seen @VanJones68]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me acuerdo que antes sólo quería andar en fiestas, y ahora me siento toda una Doña pero es que estar acostada es lo máximooooo😂😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daylightsavings #anotherstormcoming @ Terry Allen Realty https://t.co/IDsvpwDYJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[that damn smirk he gives...... he can literally ruin my life &amp; i wouldn’t complain &lt;3333]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathyhadenough @JulieSummerman @DoloresManley4 @ShaunaPembroke @canadiandaws83 @nicosgranny2000 @tetsuki… https://t.co/MdwJEtn4iA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The staff and I enjoyed celebrating #GoTexanDay at the office today! 🤠 https://t.co/1BIJs1ATKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olekzap I pretty much constantly have 50% off rides because of how much I use them when I’m at conferences. Lyft &gt; Uber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TootBhad My entire family is OBSESSED!!!!!  Like nobody can talk while it’s on. You can cut your arm off but you b… https://t.co/UF2RyC4IHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[so far i’ve gotten $150, some chocolate &amp; news that our condo is booked for destin in june!!! v day ain’t all that bad folks 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I found out that green tea shots do not contain any actual green tea. Everything in life is a lie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using #paint to #glue #stuff down left this effect on my #fingertip And, my hand just happens to mirror rhe #pink b… https://t.co/TyddEeix6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Creasy74 Yes! It's a buffalo tooth I got from the Bone Room up in the bay area. I put it on a thin chain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeRay_Shawn Thanks Shawn.  I don't do dairy either so I will try the oat milk.  It's hard to know how much to add!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump foreign policy under attack from all sides at European security conference https://t.co/XWwLMH3FP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crochet macrot blanket @ Fulton County, Georgia https://t.co/AHnBymsWQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValetinesDay2019 Flowers 💐 from a special friend whose friendship is more valuable than all the gold in the world.… https://t.co/BE6utm0hFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thirst4dodgers @lawbibliophile @nerdyDodger @DodgerFoodie @Dodgers @purabruja @BoyslnBIue @AmandaRTubbs… https://t.co/DT2IvqsZrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest mid-afternoon treat is @drinkh2rose rose water 🌹 💦 ... it's so refreshing and helps keep my skin glowing!… https://t.co/twR0YcWcvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @TrueBlueHeidi a dynamic woman that keeps her teammates empowered and inspired. #InternationalWomansDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life happens, and . . . I am a control freak? https://t.co/Hai2MnRIPK via @HollisterBoston]]></document><document><![CDATA[But as for me, it is good to be near God. I have made the Sovereign Lord my refuge; I will tell of all your deeds. Psalm 73:28]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be cheerin’ on our Titans! 💛🖤 #TitansAreChampions @ Kolf Sports Center https://t.co/MG74cKzAC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictures along our run this morning in chilly, windy SF. Prepping and catching up with @ls_disneyrunner while she g… https://t.co/ohjaHQ5Jxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPHDallas @BishopJakes @FirstLadyJakes Good Morning Family! ☺️@DeborahJCotton1 @holderbaby1 @Journi @Ura_Jae… https://t.co/THHlohF3kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to this event on Wednesday at @RyersonLIZ!  #legaltech #LegalInnovation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suite à la séance d’informations du 6 février, le Conseil s’est penché sur les préoccupations des gens.Le Maire et… https://t.co/glKwKbntsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid So the toddler in chief fired him too. Trying to shut him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow every time I put into the universe that I’m having a bad day, it’s gets worse. I should really learn to sffu huh 🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTGenter @ExtremeHotDeal Can you book it through the Marriott app or only Expedia?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad @michellemalkin called out Conservative Censorship on #TuckerCarlsonTonight  (referring to Laura Loomer) @jack You’re a damn Liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think people forget that musicians/celebrities are humans too. They’re humans who get sick, get tired and need re… https://t.co/CrNyYGH0en]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL. I am in a Roswell, New Mexico stupor. If you’re not watching this new show, you need to be. It’s so good!  #RoswellNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My manager pretty much copies and pastes the schedule every week, so I’m not sure if she’s aware I’ve worked every… https://t.co/zeTut3Yp9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @mitchellvii @PoliticalShort @Ron4California @JacobAWohl @ali @AGWilliamBarr @drawandstrike… https://t.co/sePl1Zd4pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecleptic76 @rascalmain Probably @tempusrob he’s the best..it was on @overwatchleague twitter the other day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which is MA? You want the legal putchasecage of tobacco to be 21 to protect “children” now they’re not children? https://t.co/1KhY7DhirG]]></document><document><![CDATA[this photo from ABC News;I dont see nobody boycotting Toyota for supplying ISIS with nicest trucks in the market.De… https://t.co/7t05VHzz3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to give a shoutout to @steadyhandbeer.. good beer, . Might be my new favorite Atlanta brewery 🙃👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AVSafeStreets Oops,  that was meant for the I-5 ramps 2 blocks west! Same goes for the 2 ramp as well! 🙀]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you believe ppl see spiders in their homes and just let them live???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all can raise money to get a pedophile to get out of jail ,but flint go fund still don’t have clean water 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, the best piece of advice I’ve ever been given is ‘you only have one shot to notice a haircut’.  My entire… https://t.co/AQYMyhtOMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those kids who “played house” with their cousin have corporate jobs now smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a gorgeous and unique piece of furniture, or have a tired piece that needs to be brought back… https://t.co/hSntuWUu2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracy143DC @lounginwithtony I think it was just filler so that Chad could have that moment with Stefano's portrait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction Demand....spoken like a true communist who wants to rule and shut down free speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanellMidwest_ @tayeechanzzz Same !! Just had it for the first time a few weeks ago !! So good. -When it’s chilled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weightwatchers ever since I have rejoined I have trouble using the app...I don't have time to keep entering my nam… https://t.co/aqB5HkWLfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosamillll my patients keep assuming I’m 16 and then asking how long I’ve been a nurse (which is always fun to ans… https://t.co/5ichapheiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg so many talented supporting...Ashley Jensen, Penelope Wilton, David Bradley?!? Love it so far!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom’s always finding ways to make traditional Dominican meals vegetarian for me and I appreciate it so much ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to ride on my first MG float! @NMRLaBorde @amajaxn #CHNOLAproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Kassie_7 @NFW22b @Bravo_Snark @lisarinna @QVC Lisa Rinna sells size 4XL clothes, but calls women she knows nothin… https://t.co/XtZZSlejO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all, @andrewkrycek writes fantastic music. In fact, I’m over the moon to be singing some of it this year. I h… https://t.co/LXDhJ8Ha8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Taylor 🎸 #FireAndRain @ Dunkin' Donuts Center Providence https://t.co/mZhYX2xdqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got a lot on my plate right now probably more than I’ve had in a very long time so it would be really apprecia… https://t.co/0r5dzuL0Uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart Where would we be if the Democrats didn’t take the House? https://t.co/qV8RRNaJ2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOneNOnlyDT @AnnCoulter Pres Trump has not failed his base Toots. He did all that he legally could thru the Sena… https://t.co/AGO91fR72U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dom_woodman @dan_shure @pandoramusic Bummer! Though I'm exclusively Spotify now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought she couldn't get any crazier.  Restriction of having kids what ever the reason is socialism.  T… https://t.co/qpBKYPK9RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NahBabyNah I’ve not yet seen the interview yet, but it sounds as if he’s eaten some #HumblePie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePerezHilton I agree with your sis on this. The challenge is cruel in general. Who ever started it is a jerk. Gl… https://t.co/w0PzBEP54w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all dudes really fight over a girl who’s been with the whole crew ? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreggA2684 @KateRogersonTV Kate will be there, I am going to be away but we will both be at the A10s!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom Well crap! I haven’t watched the last episode. You’re the 2nd unimpressed disappointed viewer. So here it goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I saw things I imagined...” @solangeknowles 🎶  Me too, sis...me too.  #Solange just summed up months of therapy in… https://t.co/oRVl3doFpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was 9° when I got on the plane in Fargo this morning. It was 86° when I got off the plane. https://t.co/SsbKBFCTEL Florida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapaTosta122 @Blindman_54 And some will never give him credit for that.  Which is tragic.  Because he's one of the… https://t.co/ETU5KWfuO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have $15 in my bank account for the whole week, looks like I’m going on a fasting period 😛😛😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally bombed two exams this week but the JONAS BROTHERS are BACK TOGETHER so all is right with the world. this… https://t.co/GUL8qxNG56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoGoGoing hey #hb3 might get pieces buried as amendments that we are all watching for, but it isn’t being heard in… https://t.co/2R3G9adyIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yes. This seems legit. Heelo from super legitimate @Apple customer service, for sure. https://t.co/fUyEdiZUkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure OU scored 22 against ku in the first 5 min at home... currently 23 through 24 min at KSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaObell Hope everyone is getting tested, since they all wanna mess with each other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@authorlatrice @CjWalke19139700 @MBWorkhouse @TheTigerWrites @WDFosterGraham1 @Misty_Bridge @PurpleQueenNL… https://t.co/jwyFkK2VVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, let me #humblebrag and say I turned down the bacon onion croissant this morning too. Ladies and gentlemen tha… https://t.co/M5Tpz1lXZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the girl at the gym absolutely wrecking the squat rack with a hat that says “Wineo”: I think you are my soulmate 💕🍷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how to explain this but Jeff goldblum emits so much Mr. Ratburn energy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Walls will be torn down eventually. It happened in berlin and the great wall in China is… https://t.co/JcjZgYmani]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oriolessoapfan @safeuphigh Ah, Manny! My OTP of GL. That first time Michelle saw Danny, I just knew they were one… https://t.co/S0AhCMGVM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Website training for the board members of the Jacksonville Camera Club complete. (Check!) Been nervously anticipati… https://t.co/0NEVwcNhY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cannabiscommunity #buy #my #ebook on Amazon dudeweedsavedmylife #cannabislatinanurseceo #rsoheals https://t.co/WgsQssc9Z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything about #SXSW  The live music everywhere, the interactive things to do, basically all of downtown #atx vib… https://t.co/FCGBoT0l3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madeourlove I thought it was https://t.co/IGHSyAfUNM. as much as I love Nick, Bradley Cooper's voice was perfect for the song.]]></document></documents></author>