<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[separate yo self from so many people &amp; so many otha thangs &amp; you'll feel so at peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama not only who got away w/this deception. Many dems in the House also unqualified foreigners. Worse, some runni… https://t.co/4vU5x5lFJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ignorantusua11y So wait did they give u 1s bc ur a stripper or bc u asked for money specifically to give strippers]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I’m watching Green Book but having a Captain Marvel combo.  Makes sense... https://t.co/C6rKSXVxsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can listen to Sunflower 🌻 on repeat all day @PostMalone @goSwaeLee 🔥🔥❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennedyamara1 @yikesitspam @PalayeRoyale @SebastianDanzig Yeah hopefully you don't. Yeah the floor means your closer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Possibly no collusion for you but definitely DELUSION!!!🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children and husbands are off limits but @melissagorga "you need to control your husband!" #RHONJ #DoubleStandard @BravoTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 please please please don't show his picture again.  it literally makes me sick to my stomach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna host an event. like a workshop maybe ? for high school students trying to go to college, trying to graduate… https://t.co/b4Fuma1kwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's half of my #concussionresearch team. I honestly couldn't do my research wo them. At our monthly meeting we w… https://t.co/MxPi7STwYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Others can treat their sketchbook however they want, but mine has always been a place of experimentation an… https://t.co/yP2Oem8ppH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad day for fashion. I’ve looked up to this man since childhood. Absolutely crushed. #RIPLagerfeld https://t.co/RlJvrFZ8EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReverseKarma11 @lee_mv Nothing about this #Imposter surprises me anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vauntess @BillKristol Understand the question just fine but the 3 predecessors suck a** so we 51% rather just stick with what we have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grommit56 @AngryRaccoon2 It's got to be NY style! Who the hell ever heard of a square piece of pizza????? Even the… https://t.co/8Je994s1ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[It so damn cold out here the damn ice on the  car took about 30 minutes to melt 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliciaEDove Well...I knew you long before your current boyfriend...in fact you were the one that introduced me to… https://t.co/uNPHBv0vPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec Wait til you get a load of Prez Harris’ declaration of national emergency to pass gun safety legislation.… https://t.co/EyjM7wHFAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What is said about men often has as much influence upon their lives, and especially upon their destinies, as what… https://t.co/n23h3LUq8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone knows of someone looking for professional graphine, charcoal, and colored pencils. Lemme knowww. I got th… https://t.co/aWSPjWhSgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recuerda que todo lo que sucede es una bendición. Descubre los milagros que suceden cuando sueltas y confías sin ex… https://t.co/RzwuCUq9fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to tonight’s read! This graphic novel from reyterciero and Bre Indigo is a modern retelling of LITT… https://t.co/CsxZCcos7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Bonnie. Our budgie died last night while laying.  I feel horrible and helpless. She was otherwise perfectly hea… https://t.co/Wd7FlOqFES]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of people making plans that involve me without telling me about the plans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From all over the world people gathered to Send people out to the nations, to share the good news that Jesus is ali… https://t.co/BWFlnOV6Gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sondralocke  Seriously, @TheAcademy you forgot one of the best!  #missing #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepping for #artdetour31. We will have 4 presses running. These tags will be on the Potter. Come see us Friday, Sa… https://t.co/lkslqV2TeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#word #cannabiscommunity #cannabislatinanurseceo @iamcardib #haters #newmexico #dudeweedsavedmylife @amazon… https://t.co/AtxrMJAYeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bowdereck @jailbirdmelly @harleyjennMC @midnitekismet @livelovebe https://t.co/tK7jO7FmW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las fotos con más glamur de los protagonistas de Premio Lo Nuestro 2019 https://t.co/zSgIpCfzqI via @Univision @Thalia_Bella]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom told me that lady Gaga used to hang out at my uncle’s restaurant/bar before she was famous and I am so sad he didn’t befriend her 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITArchitectBill 😂 maybe I’ll order a white russian at airport #TheBigLebowski]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶Hello, everybody I know in the Bay Area theatre community Well hello, everybody I know in the Bay Area theatre com… https://t.co/V3oB3o0j70]]></document><document><![CDATA[The VR revolution is already here — and it isn’t gaming https://t.co/Cp4Uc1g8oy via @thenextweb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got almost 3,000 views in 4 days so it’s a not to slow but still steady climb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge my sword to the realm! I just entered for a chance to attend the official #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How… https://t.co/GhKAV13uuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseForrester So proud of you Chase!!!! This is what can be accomplished with hard work and determination! Go get… https://t.co/BdtlY90Iut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody should quote JFK every chance they get! @BetoORourke @KamalaHarris. @amyklobuchar   Forget all this "progr… https://t.co/KxGPHrocSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enchanted__tay @nypost NEVER EVER SAID ANYTHING WAS TRUE! U DO NOT KNOW ME SO KEEP UR MOUTH SHUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @RealAndyPanda The election should have been nullified a long time ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaneShowAM @InternJohnRadio That was insane. He loves his girlfriend https://t.co/huLPyooMUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews check your screen image showing Aurora INDIANA. Should be Illinois of course. Liesch was reporting from Pratt building.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are an architect interested in working with #cohousing communities, please consider attending this conferenc… https://t.co/T2jxntTN5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wherefore we receiving a kingdom which cannot be moved, let us have grace, whereby we may serve … https://t.co/5aJAVpgFl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reetaville_com Totally agree. I still have some frozen from last year that I use in smoothies 🍓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please sell it to @JeffBezos so he can go through the basement vault and release all the interesting news on… https://t.co/HcbLkrphkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s the one person or people you would love to meet? It doesn’t matter if they are dead or a live. Mine would be… https://t.co/8CAjH216Vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[D'Souza UNLEASHES on Democrats over endorsement of post-birth abortions https://t.co/vgaRCgv7Hf via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #QueenNaija for #SOCIALSTARAWARD at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too ❤️❤️ https://t.co/x1degrYtox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump The second round of emails appeared because of your jackass. Your hands are dirtier… https://t.co/wazQSWeip5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to be testing out some new products today and I realized my brushes definitely needed some TLC!  Of cours… https://t.co/2U4B8zyw1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[tRump and the GOP don’t realize the ride is over. We have woken up to trickle down, tax the middle give to the rich… https://t.co/J9fMgypLpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Pennsylvania so much but after I get my degree I can’t wait to move away and start super fresh 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to Lindsey Graham?  John McCain must have spent most of his time keeping Graham in check. Must be rol… https://t.co/QfZKN0LYKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still more to do with this guide but my entire walkthrough (plus some other pages) for #MetroExodus is done!… https://t.co/Bqn89EpRQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A Healthy relationship will never require you to sacrifice your friends...” https://t.co/zd6WUaVKlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children as addicts. Alarmed doctors are now treating Fortnite-obsessed kids for mental and physical health problem… https://t.co/VQUj7zO3eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually kinda sad that we don’t see @janemarielynch more as Diana Reid in @CrimMinds_CBS. She’s so good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s Tony Stewart?? Don’t hear anything about a Tony Stewart at all anymore!! I knew there was one out there somew… https://t.co/Kuq5awcf9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithroysdon @DomenicaReports The things journalists will do/risk for free food, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As quickly as you can, tel me your favorite Happy Hour spot.... and go! #Happyhour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona sports had Paul Goldschmidt, Larry Fitzgerald, Shane Doan, and Steve Nash. But ZERO CHAMPIONSHIPS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxsuBoobie This is out , it’s too many older people around and the kids so comfortable with it 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day, one step at a time.  #enough  @marchforourlives @everytown  #MomentsThatSurvive… https://t.co/FRdZoK8YeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚠️‼️NEW MERCH DROP‼️⚠️ CHECK OUT OUR GEAR ‼️🔥🔥 FREE SHIPPING WORLDWIDE 🌎 https://t.co/62es6c7Qyz https://t.co/dfxCsOPtLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are our streamers? @usmcsky @dizdezSky @realSILSKY @JiltedZ @Mntdewmania @Banji3001 @j570ne4d @Themightychops… https://t.co/3NwfXJHAHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedMeansGo33 10/31/2005 Aaron ran an amazing show where he intrvd many former cia employee's including director's,… https://t.co/3Fpht3m9RD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Secretary of State Henry Kissinger — and the Saudi royal family made an agreement. The United States w… https://t.co/yXu5WtoQok]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at LIRR - Port Washington Station - @lirrdeals4u in Port Washington, NY https://t.co/wJIQVja6SD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lepton939 @maddow This sounds like something Space force should handle 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawmakers consider bill that would require people to be US citizens to vote.  @WGME   https://t.co/EAiVjCZGsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenSigrist This looks great. Do you have these materials? I’d find this useful for some PD I have next week. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for the 1st school session with @Lovettsvillepe here at @MoveMoreUSA RVA. Representing @HanoverSchools along… https://t.co/XMb8l7qiKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes YES, I use a straw! I do not put my mouth on a glass used by others!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Everyone,   Saying the Israeli government is corrupt, has ZERO to do with the Jewish people. Just as being pro… https://t.co/I6TBSrvTav]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to welcome @EnidWeisman #mayor @cityofaventura to @LaPoderosa670 con #ColFarias #ElMundoAlDia hablando de… https://t.co/l1ZPdr46yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verndog68 Thanks.  Sometimes, my anxiousness gets the best of me.  I will take a step back, and breathe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try not to concern myself with shit that dont have shit to do with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[The list of children in my family: Ariel, Winston, Trinity, Hayden, Gabriel. My sister got a voicemail reminding us… https://t.co/xA9hHFl0nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buzzkillary i think there's a coffee shop like right in the middle of where we both will live. and also i'll be mo… https://t.co/ibDzvzkFaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[As hard as I try and be over it I can’t be. I need to step back for awhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[The YMCA is so much more than a gym and swim, we partner with wonderful companies like Garten services, and provide… https://t.co/3ucoaStUzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[New CVS bed sheets:  Zero thread count, all the discounts. https://t.co/aZrZC3GY5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SophiaLamar1 @cheeriogrrrl @sweetangelface He's still reading Dick and Jane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sannalukas @lesleym91733192 @Chris_Datson @mymotivation_uk @cdmeditation Thank you very much for the RTs! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a phat tax return and immediately losing it to credit card debt is a great reminder to NEVER have credit ca… https://t.co/H0BtUudcJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortnite ruins my life but dan is in a 20 pound sully onesie what the heck this is hysterical]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mexican friends be so confused when i hit the woah 🥺👊🏽 bet they be like *y esta pendeja que esta haciendo*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaStJohnBoxer @TheArtofJulian @kristoffstjohn1 @TheStJohnFamily Mia ....u can do this again ...one day at a time.… https://t.co/GY2O6pxf6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky me, sitting with a group of #ML @GoogleDevExpert for Keynote #TFDevSummit - with @jerrykur @regalandroid… https://t.co/KVwzpsWgTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarleneKeener @Carver926 Let's be honest: they'll just let old people die when they get sick, and people with unus… https://t.co/w4h0baYa2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTG_CEOGEH @AnaSGrey Mommy will get well fast with all the Daddy and fill in Vivi kisses. 😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuseofIre @Gayer_Than_Thou YES - they would never have been  hemming up great, huge trains, amirite??  #TCMParty #ThePrivateLifeofHank8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minus the cream cheese on her face 😂 she looks so grown up!!! Shirt by allison_in_wunderland. ❤️ @ South Shore Chil… https://t.co/BnZTx2qvNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRguyGreg @Genesys Thanks @HRguyGreg I am by no means a professional, but I do like seeing the @Genesys employees enjoying themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no difference in the corporate ass kissing between corporate Dems and the GOP.  There are too many super s… https://t.co/nClzWSK2og]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF?  BEAUTY - GODS CREATION - PROTECTED , DOES NOT INCLUDE ABORTIONS ! YOU THINK GOD IS PRO- ABORTION ??? Then the… https://t.co/VgbeP6IijE]]></document><document><![CDATA[of people pouring in affects coordination among the various arms of the overstretched enforcement agencies of Europ… https://t.co/lXh66mB4Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lady just asked my officers if they had any niggers to arrest for real crimes.. 😫]]></document></documents></author>