<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ScubaSteve757 @_ethiopiangold All I see is profit, cheaper than a lunchable and it’s a meal ready to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night it goes down... @mannie_bentley  performs live for tuellanitra birthday kickback.. at k n b lounge..… https://t.co/mnquIFZ8bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really shocked that Former President Obama hasn’t claimed that he made these peace talks happen with North Kore… https://t.co/7BnUA8Hmmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very funny stuff. This could replace SNL, when the public gets tired of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At last. We will have our answer by Tuesday 😎 👊🏽 @Tyson_Fury @BronzeBomber #WilderFury2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely idiotic and without merit. Does anyone realize where their bread is buttered?? @allengilmer https://t.co/Q6oHSqdHbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we are again smh. Lakers down at half to a team we cashing. Smh. We need this game for real for real]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol my guy is killing the game. But I know you has hella sky miles with all that traveling 🌎 he doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpMyPres @realDonaldTrump @Lrihendry @LeahR77 @jjauthor @EmfingerSScout @AppSame @mjgranger1 @IngrahamAngle… https://t.co/LmGLrZ0yWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only “Happy Valentine’s Day” I’m getting this year is from my Alexa... #HappyValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[And on the sixth day, that which is the seventh, God said, "Let this bitch wither up and drop dead, most despicably… https://t.co/DGPvQotIRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJGWrites @joncoopertweets Sarah Sanders you've always been full of shit but your being real ridiculous now. I fee… https://t.co/eM8ttbLUsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You keep re tweeting this!  You must be guilty #DUMMY! If #MuellerInvestigation don't get you then The #SDNY will!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s March 9th, how many wins do the bucks have? https://t.co/PhbX6KtPW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lillydancyger @awpwriter @Powells @alexanderchee @lacymjohnson @ReemaZaman @likethchampagne That looks like a fant… https://t.co/vcR1bn7Fs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/15  SGLT2 inhibitors block glucose reabsorption ➡️renal glucose excretion ➡️glucose levels⬇️  Because this has no… https://t.co/l9VWNUQGgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Process vs. Everybody  #HereTheyCome #trusttheprocess #ttp @ Wells Fargo Center https://t.co/PzBD9aisKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @PaulinaPotus No she shouldn't be at Congress and I could probably name a few others to, but there's… https://t.co/4qG2pSZRLG]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my 30th year @sacbee_news and this is why this is still a great gig. Amazing effort by both teams in one of the… https://t.co/QERaymi35j]]></document><document><![CDATA[So the American people who don’t agree are just living in the cheap seat while you and Nancy Pelosi are in charge.… https://t.co/fAQDYC0oh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxCruzTX @BernieSanders Or people are just idiots. Maybe he needs another vacation home, he’s entitled to that ri… https://t.co/bzYv5A5UMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tchoopsczar Umm. Slapping the backboard cannot be called goaltending even if the shaking affects the shot. It’s a tech or nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engineers: Invent Amazing Dream it, Build it! #EngineersWeek https://t.co/Es7q1gwtre]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Think I Have To Go To Gov Ball On Friday Just To See Negro Swan Performed Live]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraveSampson It was mostly an experiment to see what the process is... https://t.co/H5nZ6lsK2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a gay sports wear dance party tonight at a bar and I’m considering it alone 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[👣☔️ Footprints #bayarea #eastbay #film #california #movies #disney #sales #love #fun #art #technology #restaurant… https://t.co/RKB9n59kPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boston25 @JimHawkins4Rep doesn’t think stepping in and telling all parents what to do is intrusive. Even though re… https://t.co/z2csRJUYMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think the Cubs naming their spring training home Sloan Park is a nice tribute to Ferris Bueller's girlf… https://t.co/IwaQJLNmt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The blessing I just got... can’t NOBODY tell me God aint real! He hears your prayers and he sees your cries! 😇🙌🏽💙 #PraiseBreak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day everyone ! Someone loves you! ❤️📈🎁 https://t.co/um2pQ2ZLRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's what Tucker Carlson said about @iamsambee after she called Ivanka Trump a "feckless c—" last year   “That on… https://t.co/UeAwRnzUE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Me Niego (feat. Ozuna &amp; Wisin) by @ReikMx on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/LQ27aqi20K rolonononon!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @warriors with get_repost ・・・ 📸 Sights from Draymond's court unveil at the Oakland YMCA 📸 @ Oakland, Califo… https://t.co/VUgnjCjgis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two months ago I booked an AirBnB in Philly for DMBs shows in Camden and Bethel between June 14-19th only to find o… https://t.co/AxdqgW2C58]]></document><document><![CDATA[#childhood #boys #CT you know the deal climbercam largebutterpopcorn #writersofinstagram #poetsofinstagram… https://t.co/CAgd1Jkm0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this clever there's something wrong with you. https://t.co/YokXfbEReV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ole Miss fans are throwing their drinks on the court at the basketball game. What else is new? 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way... what a comeback from Ramos explodes with hard upper cuts catches Santana flush. Wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanbeckwith @saletan I think it’s more arbitrary than that. If he thinks you are on his side or can help him, he “believes you”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Drunk @mattgaetz Threatening people is illegal #Resign https://t.co/VzLsR2Lfe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danjlevy &amp; @annefrances releasing certified bop #ALittleBitAlexis https://t.co/72099Gz9kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recording the.marquee with #MyNameIsLamps at fuelmusicstudio stay tuned! Heres the official meeting for the upcomin… https://t.co/zStQUDBFT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇳🇴👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Se!💝 Miss Caroline Marie! carolinemariea96 The White RACE Norwegian BLONDES👑🇳🇴 Women Are Th… https://t.co/oPwK8wlyBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is some early morning light coming in from the east. An overactive imagination would say those are condos from… https://t.co/ycr00JMw6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFPDTenderloin That is ACTION.  Thank you to the real and honest police that are risking theirs life's for us.   N… https://t.co/wdoCqaufqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Nothing. I had no idea of a job or career when I was a kid. It's a silly question to ask a kid since… https://t.co/RriTJVYuE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[not even ten seconds into the video and I already feel sick to my stomach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAlbright Obama got the same line,  managed to rise above it somehow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TipMahoney @GormleyAlbany If felons go on criminal juries, cops should be allowed on, too. I’ve been called but ha… https://t.co/JWOMQj8Vsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BBC Radio, announcements, and #HoustonWeather updates... all brought to you by yours truly!!! 11p-5a on your #NPR… https://t.co/mJGgiEzZFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[From My Book Heavenly Bodies and Human Souls: The Testament Of Solomon “Solomon’s wisdom consists primarily of know… https://t.co/rU5jaMv9in]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Coast Invitational. @ Reggie Lewis Track and Athletic Center https://t.co/fpxSkN85Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeGiza @WEEI @RedSox Awesome to have Sean McDonough back on the #RedSox - The Best!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GulpingMonkey maybe not to your narrow, pathetic mind https://t.co/kLJ5VAyIOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Office Party by @TheAbitaBeer @ Plantation Woods — https://t.co/880zfKtkPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlsenThielenCPA WHAT how to protect gangsters , with evil intent https://t.co/dz9EhGvjlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods And the disappointment of the government when weed tax revenue doesn't come up to expectation and t… https://t.co/PK8xLfeDpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seth Hoopes scores takedown with 21 seconds left in sudden victory to defeat Chase Proudfit, 4-2.@LancasterSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big win for @TUMBBHoops in Dunph’s home finale. Let’s Go T-U!! #TempleMade #GDQ https://t.co/TmaVZ75vyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is KV the #PeoplesChamp? She managed to get me out of work on the busiest day of the year 💗 to be her wing woma… https://t.co/iIosoMUQRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hyphyfriedrice You: Infinity War is the most ambitious crossover of all time.  Me: https://t.co/Vlguk2Iq5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[While there is a lot of excitement about the new Samsung phone, does anyone else think $2,000 for a phone is pretty… https://t.co/oGfJyg7UcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmarcrubin @KISSOnline @genesimmons @PaulStanleyLive Did u go to the concert tonite?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance It's time to remove him from office.  Nearly every day we get a new criminal act that he is or has… https://t.co/SdHvKKaNB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Journey Continues on to The Next Performance Book Us @ City of Atlanta https://t.co/b2rUYkBr6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ravensjeff We appreciate viewers like you and those who help us with reports because it makes our science get better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annual St. Patrick’s Mailer to our clients is in full effect! #remax #lehighvalleyrealestate #ninja #palottery @ Al… https://t.co/Dkf1BAQypH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexandregarcia Tenho amigos de Cúcuta que fala que ele esta mito louco, a síndrome da paranoia de ditador pegou e… https://t.co/UJbhGyLPVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When purchasing flowers for someone ALWAYS remember to take the price tag off.   Thank you for attending my TEDTalk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[what I tell my roommate when I wake her up at 4AM bc there’s a cockroach on the ceiling and she’s annoyed with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas I am worried that with elections and the World is so wise of T… https://t.co/Ja8NmaXXvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[All day long, everyone has been posting about their favorite romantic movie, this being #ValentinesDay and all, so… https://t.co/zmVTqt9Odn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanfordBSB @E_Rex23 Great stuff kid, great and dirty stuff Erik Miller https://t.co/7sfwqhBN8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeseniaAngel9 Ayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy when you gonna be in town prima? Welcome back to the V!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Need2Impeach @Kokomothegreat @pebbles9010 @JussieSmollett  donnie, get off your orange dildo and… https://t.co/GzbKubXCc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iz_harris I spent a good chunk of my morning binge-ing your channel and your work inspires me to do more and I hop… https://t.co/ln6Qr4cRUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phaedracook I don’t dispute that there was a scene made and some inexcusably poor behavior on display. And the doc… https://t.co/a9LXes1SRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbw_latina_milf well are you interested? I'm here at the Petro exit 219B off of I-5 here in California?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alsboringtweets @JerryRecco back before we were all paranoid, when we would hear about something for the first tim… https://t.co/9lP9WdMTdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xxTDA_Haroldxx @Gfahlenbock Damn straight Harold. Buuut... lets not forget the ones that are a tale as old as time. https://t.co/SkYXp4Wwuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost spent Valentine's Day alone. Thank God I actually have friends this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Axis IPA by @RealAleBrewing at @easytigeratx — https://t.co/JAVQeKqnbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap, I didn't know how badly I wanted @KikkomanKitchen apparel until @primitiveskate came through with a SOY… https://t.co/wiXE7DtzYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. All flo guys should work for free so wrestling “fans” can blow 6 bucks on Starbucks each morning or drive 60,0… https://t.co/jAtQ7C3d4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[i understand why lsu’s coach gets suspended, however it’s the @NCAA hypocritical nature in all of this that blows m… https://t.co/lwziCQFMOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @WitmerCarl Three weeks ago, Muller was going to give his report on Trump’s collusion with Russia. Bu… https://t.co/58bSpWmeqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foie enrobed In floss; porcini-specked gnocchi. These should be on your list. @ Tony's https://t.co/AtXKVfUHFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geth_the @getongab Probably if they allow Firefox add-one since Pale Moon is based on Firefox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbreaking America: A NEW Short Film about Solving the Corruption Crisis https://t.co/pa5Dm17uDp via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UlwellingRacing He might get the chicken but ain’t getting those biscuits away from me fo sho 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s dangerous to go alone. Take timhortons! #gloriousgeekdom @StrasburgPotter #coffee #gamer #nintendo #nes… https://t.co/lkVDg15XXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarthaStewart @HenryLouisGates @PBS Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music… https://t.co/xcSM7ETVdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Templo Sagrado @harleydavidson em Peterson's Harley-Davidson of Miami North https://t.co/zio5OdVVHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hateful left is at it again  @KristenMeghan https://t.co/FwTLVZxs9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Jack #23! Go Flyers! Good job Keely!!! #dayton6th https://t.co/DsCdrNDHfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salon Solis in Sea Cliff, New York is now carrying Ryan Scott! In addition to traditional salon services, you will… https://t.co/l3aGPSJAUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: The first elimination belongs to @AJStylesOrg, as he hits @SamoaJoe with the #PhenomenalForearm!… https://t.co/Zf0yIWatIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AMERICA there are those who are the b"ouchs for #PresidentTrump they need only one thing!  Preparation h! there's… https://t.co/FMyrpOQvvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I was #driving to the metro this a.m. I saw AT LEAST 2 dozen vehicle drivers on their phones, heads down then up… https://t.co/nMBvYZetXU]]></document></documents></author>