<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@robotviking I have been using eyeliner for a looooooooooong time hahaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @RODEOHOUSTON for havin me! That was a blast! #TheHideout https://t.co/WfX5LIZaRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @realDonaldTrump  Trump’s plan to take back $2.5 billion in California’s high-speed rail funding is the o… https://t.co/dM1bB24EvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert Wind community come out and have free supper for children 1-18 yrs. of age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vjtx0 Have you seen Cash App? Try it using my code and we’ll each get $5. PVXDKBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: 15 mins later** pays all bills to current, that shit is half way gone. 😑😩😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until Chicago police department shows PROOF, I’m believing them! This is the same police department that COVERED UP… https://t.co/Lg51sv5ukL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun with odometers... #hondacivic #highmileage #244244 #goal250k @ Ohio Wesleyan University https://t.co/DsfVHG9toO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trending on social media Tuesday - @wfaa #VERIFY post about Holiday Inn vs nursing homes. #IAmUp #realtalk  https://t.co/9UqyWpVKrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardD114 forever - you &amp; me 🥰 I love you sooo much Howard, thank you sweet man ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So are the employees who laughed and told racist jokes and went along with the existence of the "black guy printer"… https://t.co/g1ds8iy7jX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to day drink on the beach and watch some summer sunsets already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh absolutely I can see it now. President Biden and Vice President Harris. Has a nice ring to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing stresses me out more than choosing my classes for the next semesters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easkelton @TanELLclassroom @ECISMLIE Beth &amp; Tan??? I'm so happy for y'all to be there together.  #ECISMLIE19 https://t.co/xKyptYHvu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFecich @DrJacieMaslyk @DrJHarmon Can’t wait!  It’s going to be EPIC! #ECET2NextGen #Nan3EDU https://t.co/VZ8usY8zJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching all the snaps from my friends for spring break at SPI makes me want to be there so badly 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greysthinking @GreysABC I was happy she got to say goodbye and that Owen got to keep the baby. Now will be and Amelia survive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over here working on my #TombRaider goals 😏 .  Swipe for goal 👉🏼 . I'm curious 🤔 What are your goals? Fitness… https://t.co/twyycAK3xU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crews say no evidence of a person on the ice, they think the dogs got loose]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why feel low on energy? When you can fight back  with itworks confianza. Email me biancaisfit@gmail.com… https://t.co/tIVXTaayuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can say I’ve grown a lot because the old me would have went crazy, now I just block mfs and keep it pushing 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my patients drive me nuts is it karma for all the people I’ve driven nuts in my life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to meet girl friends on bumble yesterday.. started reading bios... then deleted the app lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article makes me feel hopeless for the future of humanity and our ability to make good choices for ourselves.… https://t.co/7hC0bVMfu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really terrifying timing! I hope @POTUS  was made aware of this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually remember most of pickle fest yesterday, (key word being **most**) and I don’t know whether to call that a win or a loss honestly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes @june64911952 What happened to the United States of America? A straw?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I seem to be able to catch a break I have to deal with backstabbing two faced lying soulless hyenas....… https://t.co/VPJuzRvWjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paaatRiot101 @mysterysolver3 @RealJamesWoods @realDonaldTrump @POTUS STOP CHILD PROTECTION  SERVICES  FROM KIDNAPP… https://t.co/gdtL9ZTm1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheldonPapp Appreciate it Papp, always means a lot coming from my favourite DJ 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd doc student successfully defends her dissertation proposal. Proud advisor! 👩🏼‍🏫⭐️ #tosteteam #hookem https://t.co/KzOhJOwLA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLawyerDiary After opposing counsel began giving me requests and demands at a deposition that made no sense, an… https://t.co/2UIRmwk4xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[They pursued him over fences through numerous people's backyards, until they killed him in his grandmother's backyard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertNotDeNiro @Spotify I love Apple so it works for me. Didn’t know Spotify did that though. Good to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG girl,you are so stuck in your ruminations of what you think are real FACTS!! LEARN TO CONNECT THE DOTS!@AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time in three weeks I’ll be ocean side with my love oh and Tommy 😂🏖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNoRoleModel @Lord_Lightskinn I didn’t reach, I just used the premises to form a conclusion. Your tweet may have… https://t.co/Zuyk9LCRdm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @DonnyDeutsch   He is so funny, honest, and NOT Afraid of @realDonaldTrump    Keep going on MSNBC.  I’ll loo… https://t.co/rsCY0Gk3ym]]></document><document><![CDATA[Author purchases swag.  Blogger makes a post stating they are looking for donated swag for giveaways.   Author dona… https://t.co/aMwd6y6pJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlenCasada @GovBillLee When are you asking @TNStateRepDByrd to resign?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog and Joel Embiid share the same birthday (March 16th). Excited to celebrate both of those 🐐's next week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSWPrincess @JynErso_Patriot @Milliennial @EmmaFrostResist @TrinityResists @Clara_Resists @DanaScottLO… https://t.co/WFsnOed9BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almond trees starting to bloom in East Bay. #eastbay #realestate #gardens #landscapephotography #lafayetteca… https://t.co/78hb2E258W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your solar install may need an electrical panel upgrade.  Let @SunEnergy8 consult with you on why you may need to d… https://t.co/zrh9Gf9uI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks I've yet to receive notification from any representative, and the issue is more severe &amp; pressing now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelDelauzon Bless his heart ! Lord Jesus please give this dear man the best restorative sleep of his life...Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aug1405 @GodFirstGina @Kimthechef @midwestmom18 @bigmac7x @Surfernicole1 @LonewolfnDuke @skimo1977 @baldeagle1961… https://t.co/7kj8NZhwDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VivaLaLiberte @Graham63227548 Lol right! where are you? We want the details! Lol https://t.co/YPepVK2rCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow #HIMSS19 has been an amazing experience! Looking forward to celebrating #MEDITECH50 at our customer appreciatio… https://t.co/pBsq8yDUT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylaYaweh This is true for men and women though. I've been with both and both ain't shit 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Birds #thebirds #sistersarasphotography #shootwhatitfeelslike #bird_lovers #birdbox #birdwatching @ Buhl, Idaho https://t.co/waGjRbA54o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awe, he’s so awesome! And anything is possible if you believe in it! 💜😊👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t that sacrilegious? Don’t you sign books 📖 YOU....wrote? @txstarkeeper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Belloelquelolea Y obligatorio ser condescendiente con el Mesías y no pretender tener criterio propio]]></document><document><![CDATA[MONDAY FUNDAY 🔥⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ Legs are feeling toasty today from this workout I did yesterday. nothing ground breaking. I do… https://t.co/SZTuvZAqk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[no bozos in my circle, they get cut ✂️ @ Brooklyn Steel https://t.co/TeJxlDB83z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannbon Okay but I actually thought it was funny! LMK when you’re done!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlassHouses_ @dontshootskrlx @blessthefall @SLAVESOFFICIAL @capsizeband See you in Grand Rapids 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newton 26, New Site 15. Halftime. Newton is 10-of-15 from the free-throw line, Mew Site is 8-of-12. @DJournalPreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[E-learning is posted! All classes will be using @GoSoapBox today! Be sure to read the assignment for an extra credi… https://t.co/sOCqWseNLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV @SenatorDurbin @stinchfield1776 You are the one uninformed.  Gun violence is the National emergency.  The ma… https://t.co/bLN8kQ7olF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @dbongino He has it on his profile that he trolls you. Is this not a bit weird? 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so damn sick and I can’t sleep so Jeff cuddles up to me and passed right out. I hate him and I might punch him right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@outlawjw That's a given with that stupi looking face she has.  She's got stupid written all over it.  And that big… https://t.co/VlI9GOCbqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I also saw a white woman put her tracks in this morning in the bathroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[So close to finishing this first draft. All I want to do is rewrite the entire beginning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoetontheLake @Maggie_Klaus @joncoopertweets @JoeBiden @KamalaHarris Biden has a very shady record - don't forget that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[plz god i just wish people would start using the correct form of ate/eaten in a sentence 🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Block 2 rocked their 3rd Diagnostic so we celebrated with a root beer float party!! So proud of these readers 💕… https://t.co/jICKcg7xM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zelgetatwizzer @cathrynlavery @ring They don’t have the fear we have in nyc and leave doors unlocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NthingInPrtculr @FLOURNOYFarrell @oneconnelly1 @TerriakiSan @775AC @WonderBitchToo @sjosephs53 @Numbers28… https://t.co/TJEwNsip1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[We go into a bike shop in Olympia. Highly rated. When I ask about a specific comfort gel saddle he mansplains and c… https://t.co/qG157ocWS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scarlettqmusic @qa36auh @CouponistaQueen @babs_haynes @grub_ro https://t.co/52A6UCjwbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malfunction54 Omg my friends have all the best food lined up for me. I’ll be waffling next Friday though so see you next week @TheLab_ms !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeWWoHP That ain’t it ;) it’s bc we’re snacking our way through nyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kafine Listen to @davidaxelrod’s Axe Files podcast interview with him from last year. So good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fr seen this guy reading his health textbook at the gym today. Whats your excuse to not study? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silau25 @pampisford @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM @vallouard @leonalombaerts @rayanf9416 @MelindaYoe @Indinlily… https://t.co/DENERP9wuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[just thought I would share how thankful I am for where I am at. this rainbow is a metaphor of college, it was rainy… https://t.co/PV1ylMP9jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado They'll hire Paul Blart,Mall Cop,to patrol the entertainment at its finest along the Broad Street Lin… https://t.co/cGmireXk2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Varsity Baseball with the win 10-0 at home. Way to go fellas. https://t.co/iDs6jbhjkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I observed the Pen tool in Illustrator seems to work best when anchors correspond w inflection points of curves, th… https://t.co/isLQrh0UoK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it comes to requesting or bringing to light inaccuracies in reporting, “You can’t subjugate your clients inter… https://t.co/VgghLv3gLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re not gonna believe me but a squirrel just crossed the street on the crosswalk with a walk sign. i’ve never been more impressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Evidentemente están con el grupo terroristas Hamas https://t.co/zznJnVsw25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sublime drive across the desert in this sweet ride! Thank you @audi ! The perfect way to see the beauty of Nevada!… https://t.co/ffdyssjv0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the rodeo. #cowboyup #cowgirlup #rodeo #isadrake @ Pavilion for Agriculture and Livestock Education https://t.co/xCbbtuTqxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking gross! A place I used to love and called home for a few years. Sadly given away to the losers in life while… https://t.co/M5cKlWfDL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr is lower than pond scum. Sen. Reid retired after a serious injury. He had a very successful career… https://t.co/dwpRbKogA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr How about the MAGA Coast Guard dude that had a hit list for all of your father's distractors? He's… https://t.co/TSCiTUtIfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We expect more of our children than of gun owners and gun manufacturers.” -@RepDean https://t.co/a3jp0lqIyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anyone confirm or deny that @iseestarsmusic played Two Hearted last night in Houston with @KayzoMusic because I… https://t.co/eMf4ed2Tcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents Day @realdonaldjtrump. A true Leader like you deserves to be acknowledged.  Tamara Cole]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cozzzyboyz @Sirius7dk @TheChrisMosier A whole three of the millions of women participating in sports. That's not a… https://t.co/NHBIGWgNDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump HITLER WOULDA loved her! I mean look at her. She's the perfect end product of his breeding program to… https://t.co/V1GRlf2asM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard work pays off! I have exciting news &amp; I feel like I can’t get home quick enough to tell my hubby! 🤗🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that out of all the cats in the world I end up with one that has sinus issues? Like it been almost 23 yea… https://t.co/42DNuXfKOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelli_Fields @PFDSullivan @AGirlInPhilly @ConshyBakery @DeniseNakanoTV I’ve had 2 cups, I’m good now :-))]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop messing w this man who clearly suffers from dementia. It’s not funny and y’all need to stop egging on this shi… https://t.co/4X4Tn3GwCZ]]></document></documents></author>