<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[“What the hell is even that?” I’m so done with the internet for tonight #lol #bruh #NoChill 😂😭💀 https://t.co/MjviIYKKAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zonum_ettevy @Mimunoz2387 @realDonaldTrump O hell yeah. That is awesome!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Groot baby is ready to party! #iamgroot #groot #ilovemyrottweiler #ilovemyrottie #rottweiler #rottweilerpuppy… https://t.co/G14iBfEjkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcairports how am I still at this airport and can’t park. Three flights idling for the same gate??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drreynosa @Miguel_layun Si, Edson es bueno también, pero...creo que Layún puede aportar esa experiencia en momento… https://t.co/6Gfk1ZhsJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather alert: Wind Chill Advisory until Mon, Mar 04 at 12:00:00 CST. https://t.co/8Otz5FPJ6z #MorrisMNWeather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes life’s better when you’re laughing #SheLickedmyear #blessed🙏🏾 @ Hudson River https://t.co/i4pcwLEgm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenB_9312 @gumby61184 @woltz1975 @SportsCenter Can you girls please take me out of your little sixth-grade snit… https://t.co/uYy6FngYFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystalbuinews Nice club to be in. Thanks for reaching out, Crystal. Hope you can grab a few screen grabs of your… https://t.co/OxItU4jgZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol, so yeah that’s me up in that coaster. What a night, thnx @trvisXX  @therealmikedean yall put on a hell of a sh… https://t.co/keeHY1iTp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolandreww someone just quoted my tweet and said byzantine... this tension https://t.co/AN0hOaPRtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[how did y’all make sure your teeth were clean with braces because mine feel dirty no matter how hard I brush 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanstruyk Numbers will be a lot different in middle/Southern America. Moderates will lean  Biden and Beto. Wait f… https://t.co/LRA3znFczN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sxdoc @Annabarbe6 I will fight Sharia law as long as I am alive. It is evil. https://t.co/Cu0iBsGMxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback: Anthony Hamilton concert in Kansas City June 2014 https://t.co/THMpY5YFsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @TheDemCoalition He's a vile human being and should be jailed for rape and many other crimes against humanity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richard74195773 @BEEKS_511 @anhonyf97 @shaac75 @therealcornett @SenFeinstein https://t.co/4KDOJFGAdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT  LORD, WE THA… https://t.co/7IGAqc1YK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dealing With – And Covering – Devastation https://t.co/Vf58LjJ9Yh via @radio_ink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunTheJewrls I read and collect them. I haven’t read any comics from the past year but I love the Steve Ditko comics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I make a mistake.. and I'm not talking to who I think I'm talking too but it is fun and harmless... I Kno… https://t.co/uE7xfFZW0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Gee.  I see Progressivism as a cancer that has been metastasizing in America since Wilson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t wait until someone’s funeral to say something kind ABOUT them; say something kind TO them and build them up t… https://t.co/Y1VMZLlXeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had Fun shooting bockfest 5k runs this morning looking forward to hoops tonight @HughesBoysHoops @TaftNation… https://t.co/Koiez1Uksr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Bangor Airport baggage claim in Bangor, ME https://t.co/DfJpZH1tRX https://t.co/6EAGUnSIoG]]></document><document><![CDATA[5314 W 8th St 5314 W 8th St, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/SRQWTBDjom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else super uncomfortable with how close Brad Cooper sat next to Gaga?   Um...definitely some heat there. #Oscars2019⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gadiadelman Demons , all of em. Scum of Scum. I’m going to buy a tree 🍊 or Pomegranate , maybe Fig. And plant it f… https://t.co/o06cbLAcsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems this way to me: When it comes to @AOC  @TheDemocrats: YOU'VE GOT SPUNK! @GOP: I HATE SPUNK! https://t.co/hGWDjhZY6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a fun trip down memory lane. Some entries for me: Early Dynasty Warriors on PS2, the first few Ghost Recon… https://t.co/ohQfhyJ8xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Shabu at @SHABUWAY for lunch with my brother @MrBarker718 https://t.co/nbyHVaHpkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Blame sexism when people think you’re full of 💩! Is your bestfriend’s name Jussie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco When Obama care was ramed down our throats ! What did Congress do ?it was so good for us… https://t.co/uCljZ668k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JIDsv U were given a lot of dope eating spots here in the CO. Enjoy your time in the city bro🤜🏽🤛🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 @kchernecky If this guy was working class he would be doing the Thorozine Shuffle in a rubber room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1010WINS @CBSNews @CBSNewYork @cbschicago @cbslosangeles @CBSPhilly @cbsboston @CBSMiami @NBCNews @NBCNewYork… https://t.co/hLa2GhnrXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been challenged by @macgregor63 to post the cover of a book that I love with no reviews or explanations - ever… https://t.co/qvZFPgdkNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FisherStinson Randy Stinson is a HUGE steal by SWBTS! He is going to be awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@otreborsal @YalitzaAparicio @PremiosOscar Pues no llegué dijera el peje]]></document><document><![CDATA[i always wonder if the lifeboats on @TheQueenMary  are the originals or replicas?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Catwoman2011 @CHScarolinagirl You and me both...the proper English that is🤣👍🏽 https://t.co/RvNREWpj7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRoberts any comments on Justin Fairfax? Justice Kavanaugh would love to hear your thoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously am so thankful for people who serve in the military and protect our country. I literally could not do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristaRompolski @mhhighered I previewed SmartBook 2.0! I work as a DFC so they did a training with us. The way the… https://t.co/nbCzuAxVLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorburrowes Well I couldn’t get that far in the video. It was only seemed, especially compared to the whacky fe… https://t.co/tNUrvSWwgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kileym88 @DKPghSports @penguins @NHLBruins @jaredmccann19 Appreciate you reading! Would have been tough to bet aga… https://t.co/hKmjpR55cg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, so, SO much! This is awesome, thanks for sharing @JayRCallahan ! And #ONWISCONSIN 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's your culture like?  Great mind at work here.  I continue to see the importance in effective communication no… https://t.co/sOrAnjbysq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damindiavlog Just seeing this. You both are correct, sometimes family over everything else. Hoping everything works it's way out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damon261 I do think it’s a similar concept and I wouldn’t be surprised if synthetic vs analytic thinking had something to do with it....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just say No to the ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS!  Fly one of our DRONES on the border day and night!! WE CAN HANDLE THE TRUTH… https://t.co/nLG7mhOXzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseOfSparky I knew @VanHyfteJayde was going to fit in well at ASU and her career is ready to blast off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nevaevapressed @RealCandaceO No. Candace is misreading aoc intentionally so she can go to one of her long time prepared lines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[6. Jets via Giants - Josh Allen: Edge, Kentucky  7. Jags - TJ Hockenson: TE, Iowa 8. Lions - Brian Burns: Edge, Flo… https://t.co/8E7RKheJdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaRealGrizzle @jgus525 @charliekirk11 Easy there, Wouldn’t want Booker gettin a boner.             #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Oh Adam why don't you do your job, you hater, you mad, little schiff, you probably got picked on for… https://t.co/ADUaKQuKK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[so my client today, made it aware to me, that I’m the most recommended and have the highest ratings out of any busi… https://t.co/UEPfo8HFls]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/FxQvA4kAvi #thats your song wera @atoyac123 @Rorschach_AbNb @BlueMoon_AbNb 😂😂😆😆😆😆😆😆😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate Another reason why Putin rejoices as Trump and Fox undermine our sense of right and wrong, moral authority,… https://t.co/pqZLg8WjFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordBobbyConner @kare11 Explain what benefit that would have. Do you know the real reason rents are so high. Do so… https://t.co/pJ63y4vMVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UofMemphisPres Ummm...Hi Doc. It’s Ron Childers. You wanted me to call about the autographed ball... https://t.co/pRFvnIlL2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilterlessFemme I never read the comic so I don't have that perspective to compare it. I was disappointed with the… https://t.co/ieAP4Ykw3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/hJbQSTkGR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are #QPR fans upset about what Deeney said about last night being like a Cup Final for us? Nothing else to play… https://t.co/OdqgZW4rXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The league looks at everything that’s the least but questionable. I’m not sure if it was the Coburn hit that did th… https://t.co/SLv6gbnlfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’d think I’d be surprised, but I’m not. if he is not impeached before the termination of the 4 year term, well t… https://t.co/6dhe6Lpa9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 10 copies of the most important comic book in history https://t.co/k665QZn2dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@multimediostv sr chavana aqui estamos viendo es show como siempre nos puede mandarnos saludos para abraham y laura linares de Laredo tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyHavenstein @60Minutes holy shit... you make me laugh harder each one I read... dont stop https://t.co/hPv7eiUa30]]></document><document><![CDATA[i still think about the time i left my purse at a restaurant and someone i went to school with messaged me about it… https://t.co/WdIZWU5ybq]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE WEEKEND AHEAD!!! 🍀🎶  Friday night: roadiejoes 🎶🍺 Saturday night: @cowboycoastoc 🤠🍺 @ Tops Cut Off productions https://t.co/7ZfCZug7lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just not up to early right now and too busy with work we will do better 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianV_96 @CallMeCharx @SonicHockeyFan @foxygrandpa62 'ear that? You walk the plank!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligatory Sebring pit lane photo. @ Sebring International Raceway https://t.co/8cZG27rlQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared Yes, I am sure we all would like to know more about Debbie and Don. #UDAddendum… https://t.co/KTP4FzXeQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously thinking about formally writing all of my relatives and asking them to remove any pictures of me from Facebook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To determine whether your parent is a foreign diplomatic officer, your parent’s accredited title must be listed in… https://t.co/z1jpxAWb3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magazine collage art - think I want to do a huge canvas but with "kitchen" words... https://t.co/bptBMaehZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DellDracula @zhang_hanyun @aicforever @RiversofGrue @WadeJo8 @SusieDavis1974 @kreepazoidkelly @SCRMRadio… https://t.co/38CZiJm271]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grace_14516 Good morning Grace. Thank you. Have a beautiful day. ☕️☕️😊 https://t.co/IrInO4pEwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codeofvets @Jamierodr14 We have a men’s prayer meeting this morning I’ll include this precious girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff I wonder if she will call it a cage, a prison cell, or a detention space when she is behind bars for he… https://t.co/uqCytS8dRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 9 of trying to figure out why one of the only thing that mattered to me was ripped from my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Senior Night. There isn’t a more fitting end to her career at the Yum! Center than that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumbs up for solar! California's solar energy push. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarEnergy START HERE -&gt; https://t.co/1ZikqEryja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynicallyYours But you're an equal now. And have been for a few years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good on @AppleMusic for recognizing #InternationalWomansDay, but in doing so the UI makes it impossible to browse t… https://t.co/kRW1uu7OMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Indian guys go on the TV YEAH WE ARE INDIAN AND WE ARE GAYY... My dad turns to me n goes DO YOU KNOW THEM?? -… https://t.co/DaE9cHByfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been a bullish Monday so far.  Took some options right at market open: $X  5/17 $21 calls @ .99  $DAL 6/21 $52.5 ca… https://t.co/k2h1qAx0XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class today was amazing!!! Come tomorrow at 11am bkyogaclub @ BK Yoga Club https://t.co/WiyKKuwAE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having dinner (@ Local Lime Rogers in Rogers, AR) https://t.co/N4ozc2ywLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanDobson_24 @ty_mclain @marchesseault8 @megangwathney @chloooomarie You can’t explain the greatness of Texas to… https://t.co/xDHNlwMeka]]></document><document><![CDATA[on some cocky shit, i can treat you better than anyone else has ever treated u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldKutney @curryja @PaulRoundy1 Peer review in "climate science" is a joke. It's all politics now with very lit… https://t.co/1TBQMaVIkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that owners found it more palatable to pay Kaepernick in a settlement than risk facing an arbitrator in a… https://t.co/wAL0GdYXOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evilrich3845 @__ephemeroptera I have an Xavier as well... and he is DMing our game tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent picture from Garden City Beach, SC to warm up the Cold. https://t.co/OoSKGJ4hHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sketchmazoid I'm pretty jealous. Nobody has ever said anything mean about Dan, and I think that's when you've truly arrived]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themanspyro97 @MyNBAUpdate @KDTrey5 @dallasmavs I don’t believe we have two max slots KD wants 200mil or close to… https://t.co/LJcNWkVsB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left my wallet at work I had to think about how much gas I would be wasting to go back and get it. Not to mention i… https://t.co/mgkmQIpeO5]]></document></documents></author>