<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Yo, @Nike! @adidas got @kanyewest to perform on their campus today. Can we show them how it’s really done by bringi… https://t.co/yrpyr5iPQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenMonsour12 @realDonaldTrump You are the strongest man I’ve ever seen! I would compare him to Winston Churchill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Potty training day 3. Haven't seen the outside world since Friday. #stircrazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my word, this broadcast for @libertybaseball is the worst! Video looks like it's from a flip phone and these dry… https://t.co/bgN4IFZUw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics No more dynasties from either party!!! No Adams, Roosevelts, Kennedys, Clintons https://t.co/wVbzontYvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like I’m going to miss out on the #TWUG. Good night #BHFamily @DonnieWahlberg have a very good night!  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@royfbush @_rocketsauce I went out and bought some last night because all his diss did was make me want some]]></document><document><![CDATA[A caso alguien va al cine a las 3:00 pm? @Cinepolis o por qué poner solo en ese horario la movie 🙄 @GlassPelicula]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite time of day is easily the 3-4 hours I have the bed all to myself before my husband gets home from work. I starfish SO HARD ⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj After the armbands...Hair Length was the Protest against the Vietnam War]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting - As our society becomes more tech integrated, we may need to improve human connections (empathy,… https://t.co/0FcYqqzsuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[His name is Pip &amp; his cherry eye has been fixed. :) https://t.co/juJb6iqYaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump If he is innocent of any wrongdoing, why doesn't he relax about the Mueller report? Ma… https://t.co/Pbzt63BgMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam's reaction to hearing the crowds cheering in the theatre at the Outlander Fan Gathering in L.A 2014. . Credit t… https://t.co/VDprV7neNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Souper chez les beaux parents ça ressemble à ça comme musique!   #Party 🎆🎆🎉🎉🍺🍷🍷  #60s https://t.co/5qzfX5upUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanetteEliz Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ #us #uk #nz #ca #dating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @VP #PenceKnew Flynn was compromised. #RussianAsset Manafort picked Pence for VP #GOPWarOnWomen #MeToo… https://t.co/vCe4coErIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me chuckle. #funniness #tee-hee #smile #clever https://t.co/iLi7qD9fiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[so happy to find out that so many couples i thought had broken up have indeed not broken up]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a giant B. And my initials are BB. Naturally I feel this wall was made for me.  Also this blouse deserves its… https://t.co/cfH1RpmgWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorSAL @CPAC @realDonaldTrump Yes, and he was arrested yesterday.👍🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[My neighbors looking in people apartment trying to see if they lights out to]]></document><document><![CDATA[And by “us all,” I mean the amazing sex workers and committed accomplices I’ve had the honor of working beside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mention early retirement, pays 35-40% more than same job in priv sector on avg, way more job security, gold-… https://t.co/JQK4lrhEsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Action Points Assessment-  Analyze how gender issues have been integrated into your innovation cycle. Self assessme… https://t.co/3IVv8SvLc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[2018-2019 Basketball Season was officially wrapped up today with our Awards Banquet. I guess we officially have a S… https://t.co/XxWroUCvlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHelman blaring hotel de ville down middle-of-nowhere new york state highways at 3 am. see u soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody in the serving industry should be out getting wasted after their shift tonight. Black out bbs, it's okay. You deserve it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelersdepot I find it very interesting that neither of the interviewers asked questions of importance. They just… https://t.co/nS62SrqDnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightOnIt1 @neontaster @Stichtag @billmaher I honestly don’t know what his claim to fame is]]></document><document><![CDATA[smirk. When you need to tell someone exactly how much you love them. | 21 Times Text... https://t.co/1dBQ5eM6cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s a wrap! It’s been such a beautiful experience working with @ashleydubose and everyone else during her resi… https://t.co/jgi5WbwlhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to all of my friends on here who are still awake after whatever concert they’ve just been to. I see you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is my baby a teenager?!?! Alex- Happy Birthday!! You never fail to make me laugh- I love you to the moon and ba… https://t.co/PKIoqIuQ56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HippieVol @8MillionML @gr82btnvol @leighalice24 @angrysatan6661 @jamesonandbeers @Shawn172510 @The_Fool_Monty He is spoiled rotten lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having an anxiety attack in a store is the worst here why  1.) your In public  2.) you feel like everyone watching… https://t.co/I0vkfCdau4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbitiousGirl02 That’s what I’m trying to find out what’s your true God ordained definition of submission]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riddick_5 @OFemmeFataleZ There are some problems with in the white community but there is also problems in the bla… https://t.co/8Oko32CxDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t open my messages if you’re not going to answer. Especially if we are having a conversation. Like really??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus said to her, “ I am the resurrection and the life; he who believes in me, though he die, yet shall he live, a… https://t.co/hF63NBcOoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought they were singing “when a cowboy trades his sperms for wings” I need to go to bed lol #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[So full from sushi, I haven’t ate this much sushi in my life. Currently in a sushi coma 😂😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @RamonEGarcia2 2 The Dr’s were just treating for pain management. She asked her what she was doing we… https://t.co/TembqWCQ1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biology PLC flash gel lab training with ASIM &amp; HudsonAlpha #HooverPride https://t.co/TvqO5g70ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 types of marketing personas ... when ‘to thy own self be true’ ... is true💥💥💥 by @tomfishburne https://t.co/FteH2tBTWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hardcore on the train of redrawing old OCs. Here’s Ophanion from 2007 when I was a freshman in highschool ✂️ She wa… https://t.co/BwFlDcGZHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[for those who don’t know, I was hit by a deer last week, my car is totaled, so if I’ve been MIA it’s because I’ve b… https://t.co/E99A1uG3Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrea_angora @iicardi7 Cansar ? No creo la verdad ella es muy realista en decir las cosas como son, creo que a cu… https://t.co/Sx2yoLbhM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re at work living your best life!!! I ain’t going back and forth with you niggas!! 😂😂😉🎉🎊 @ Metro Bladensbu… https://t.co/CKJ0slN9yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bckrda One would think MSM would be interested in the Kushner family trying to get a 1 Billion $ loan from the US… https://t.co/YijtzXZ1wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinCasas_ @NGSSMadeMeDoIt @Kel_Grigsby @ALepeRamirez @Eduranmath @spastorEUHSD @onecentplus @pscasas11 @flavia_casas 💙💛🦅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m getting a Subaru none of you bitches better judge me it’s SAFE and FAST and CUTE bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[CEO Ouachita Electric Cooperative has made sun power a cornerstone of innovative programs serving a high-tech corne… https://t.co/ZosmDS1Ioq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just for a sec. lookin like a licc #NewProfilePic https://t.co/G7WmNcls81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was so happy to see @C_JJ_Rozeboom and @erickleinschmit tonight! It was a shame @Dcox_22 couldn’t make it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puppy love!! Come check out all the adorable puppies available for adoption at the @hwac! . . . #adopt… https://t.co/4YPcr6wfdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnderSecArmy @ArmyHouston @USArmy 1/4 w/die of heart attack. HC won’t tell U it’s muscle knots. You accumulate kno… https://t.co/zHqF8yQFpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes You will succeed!  All the best to you as you travel each step of this journey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw on here that someone said Dunkin’ Donuts coffee was better than Starbucks....tried it for the first time. 😒 I… https://t.co/UWctynOjEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @Liz_Cheney Please. Funny how the GOP is all over this but have no comments for Hyde-Smith, Steve King, DeSantis, Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPAmericanMom @amyklobuchar So I’m still upstairs but reading transcript as updated!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Well MATH and METH are only one letter different. And you aren’t good at math!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BamaEd @CreakyJoints So true! We always find the strength to push forward]]></document><document><![CDATA[This breakfast joint is packed.   I go and put in for a party of one. (Follow me on Instagram @NicPartyofOne!)  The… https://t.co/C8eGRUlrGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terrycrews What kids actually need: a parental figure who loves them, regardless of gender.  The fuck even is mate… https://t.co/VoQgEa5d08]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the adhesive we use in our shop. It’s $40 everyday pick yours up now!!! Dries quick and is great for classi… https://t.co/RG8N3NeFIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemme clarify for those of you living under a fucking rock, these are benefits of caffeine/coffee. Y'all go ahead a… https://t.co/hRCWD2ddpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwilson_wilson @NLL @lyle4thompson @ShayneJackson32 @Staats83 @mpthirty @miles2thompson @GeorgiaSwarmLAX… https://t.co/JBLizneGfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want lasagna, a hair cut, and a clean room. I can’t do the first, shouldn’t do the second, and don’t want to do the third.]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait until Avengers: Endgame breaks my heart into a million pieces!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for what? #democrat #BULLIES, literally do NOTHING good for America? OR @gop, @POTUS dumping MILLIONS FOREIGN… https://t.co/Ywe4aWVdt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great time yesterday lobbying for the ERA at the Georgia State Capital. It was wonderful seeing our democra… https://t.co/MOUwJXq0ML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCTSubway just told to get off downtown 1 train. What are we supposed to do if we need to get to south ferry??? S… https://t.co/h33K0WGD3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KasieDC @RepDebDingell @kasie You could have just calmly asked Moms and Dads to keep guns in the home secret and l… https://t.co/JBSj8IE6AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#neighborhoodnights dinner and cocktails at @SlipstreamDC is looking mighty delicious. https://t.co/WO9WRUluLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking to @ShopLocRaleigh today at noonish about having your best year yet by reclaiming your calendar, rethinking… https://t.co/dMAgoNl1Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be weak looking @ my memories cause me &amp; tae used to be so childish but bold 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoBeletsky @Surgeon_General @NORML @JulieKJohnson @AOBempah @PaculaRosalie @SLandP Relevant: https://t.co/9LC4NhW8ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️seeing historical artifacts relating to my ancestry #knowwhoyouare #geneology #Ancestry]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; clear sky temperature up 2°F -&gt; 10°F humidity down 84% -&gt; 78% wind 8mph -&gt; 5mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[The luminous @esmewang reads from her BEST-SELLING essay collection, The Collected Schizophrenias, and then chats w… https://t.co/c6rXupdRTA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my #writerdirector reel is adding so much stress to my life 😬😳  #FemaleFilmmakerFriday… https://t.co/kkTK4WbIO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I’ve ever seen the same chick fil a worker more than once?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBloggess I am an Aries and that’s why you didn’t have a chance. https://t.co/Jz5qjbDbS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you attending IWCE this week? Stop out to see Ondas Networks’ mission critical mobile command center at booth 1… https://t.co/BWD790duVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok thom you have convinced me that US is a terrible place to live. Listening to you makes me feel terrible and I lo… https://t.co/xgizLL9sC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington Trained Guatemala’s Killers for Decades via @thenation https://t.co/XY2NcUUxdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronMcNeish “Churches”... and she’s an alternative music artist. I’m an alt music junkie, but I had to ask my 1… https://t.co/aDasWqYPub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoloYung11 @jordaaanrenee @nickk__21 @HeavyHenny especially uncle gleaph 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful- An Italian Town Fell Silent So The Sounds Of A Stradivarius Could Be Preserved https://t.co/ERUD4CyyjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I sit and think.. “Damn, men really out here thinking they own the whole world”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sketcher1223 @LauraleeB4real @DougDavidsonYR You're not alone. Just not the same without Doug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stweetnsour The Quran instructs her and all devote Muslims to KILL the infidel let that sink in , chains are irrelevant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMBalasar Bahahahahhahahaa you look like Munch when shes surprised and makes that face 😮😮😮🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Western Day at school means Alexa was coerced into playing country music all morning long. #highlanderschool 🤠🤠 @ L… https://t.co/E2eMFAH0Xq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else having problems trying to buy @FLAGALine tickets on @LiveNation @Ticketmaster #help!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild Saturday night after a day of sample sale-ing at our SF showroom.  Want to have 🍷 but worried I’ll fall asleep… https://t.co/y7nMr6hFLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook Rose McGowan is a poster child for dysfunctional liberals. She killed her child to pretend that maki… https://t.co/UWQpsMM0kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were maps that lived, maps that one could study, frown over, and add to; maps, in short, that really meant som… https://t.co/ppp3pUqxnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever found yourself SO mad that you can actually feel the legit nerves in your body getting HOT ?.... BUT the g… https://t.co/XimXFFJ9EB]]></document></documents></author>