<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Been having a bit of a rough patch... to help lift my spirits tweet at someone something kind then retweet this pos… https://t.co/GI8Pm38sk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from PH03 at 6917 Collins Ave Available for sale. Contact me @ 786-269-1043 to schedule your private tour.… https://t.co/CfldTjBKsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Yeah just like two different laws for Dems and Republican. If Republicans had done what Dems has the… https://t.co/UMaHDzSrAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlinnation 2- wouldv'e saved my life, now too late, new one metastatic, stage IV,  So learned hard way, being all… https://t.co/L5fz050xOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad had pancreatic cancer if you can wait a minute I’m thinking with you Alex your strength is awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OperationOppo @stockguy61 There are protections in the funding bill for the butterfly place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddienavarrete @EdSarkiss Thanks @eddienavarrete looking forward to this much anticipated chapter! ☺️😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the featured reports - https://t.co/pqMI3QEGDQ Factors are varied, and methane is also involved. Intermitten… https://t.co/nfjggOpHVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re making and shaking ice wine martinis in Madison! It’s the 15th annual Ice Wine Festival. Tune in to .@wkyc! 🍸… https://t.co/z0jXfCAdPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[From experience people think your crazy when you can see them...When they want you to see them. PR even listen to t… https://t.co/TexYqp0pDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even bout to lie I miss this girl so much. Nobody will ever have the personality she has..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday...At my Uncle Buggs cooking for him. He called in for a special request.😁 Anything for him.… https://t.co/hkSTQ8UadV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherrybombmami Okay I'm getting mine in April, if you get yours before dont tell me or show me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really just can not wait to finish my test today and come home and take a nap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Stay away from facebook. Don't read anything about our DEMACRAT nominee, Russia will attemp to divide us. I was done in 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meat and Cheese tray at #starbucks   Yum #Starbucks Thank you #starbucks   😋 #food #meat #cheese #foodfoyoface… https://t.co/SuBJZQQWVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so selfless &amp; i will never find it in my heart to give up on someone. we are sad boys today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into @BaronCorbinWWE at the gas station last night. He’s such a cool dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a year!!!! Happy Anniversary @MKCard96!!!! Love you, @geoffcard and Jimmy soooo much! https://t.co/He2ytpspGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dontated to Andrew Yangs campaign for a future future and I encourage you to do the same #yanggang]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like how everyone went south for spring break while I’m over here like... going up north!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Health Scams Exposed | Drinking Diet Sodas Linked to Increased Stroke Risk https://t.co/9olHXWHo29]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my doctor says I’ll need to take a few days off from exercise. https://t.co/rhCB6w46Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Rancho Cordova, California https://t.co/zOdtEejzZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Delicate #iHeartAwards #BestMusicVideo @taylorswift13 @iHeartRadio @taylornation13 #TaylorSwift i💛TS 💗💗💗💗💗💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VerlorenZaak Thank you. Scout had on a red one but he somehow got out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmcgloin69 @PolitiBunny You’d figure that people who lived in snowy areas would know about snowplows...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Registration is now open for the @Hoteldataconf https://t.co/ChQWxD32IL  Thanks to @tambocreative our registration… https://t.co/DCEll9zoCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetOfSpirit_ @SonOfGodAndMan We really are going here this week. Damn. I suck at sarcasm. I’m gettin’ ready to T… https://t.co/TwqWkbw2YA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vendaval @KenJones707 @PlanetLuvie @neeratanden I’m suggesting we deal with the reality of republicans in power]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanRGallagher aiden is not making some general point about adopted siblings, i genuinely don't understand how ev… https://t.co/XxMlvYmwCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @spinnershells ! When we get together this time let’s try this “Flamingo Margarita”! 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA wey que verga ganaaaaaan inventando, haciendo historias. Niñas entiendan alv que no me pinches int… https://t.co/nopFCseTBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sro1962  Hi, can you please follow me back? I would really appreciate it. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noooo tension in that limo on the way to the group date. #TheBachelor 🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Face painting in full effect at #UNITYfestival 🎨🖌 #SoMi #blackhistorymonth #givingback @GFFNHELP https://t.co/krznR3XD99]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jill said he liked Scott sorry but addict isn’t good for another he pushed demi into doing it to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sea of flags as women strengthened by God work for Justice in the whole world #EWCSW @ecumenicalwomen #CSW63 @ Chur… https://t.co/glgZF2UFt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hazming21 @jjodi237 @jeremy_gehrke @JeffKrimmer @HeinrichCraig Of course we could meet up. Tomorrow I dont have to… https://t.co/tYzwTyMHMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s February 14th and you know what that means?? Yup you got it, gotta pay my credit card]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHowe My daughter (and youngest) seriously considered that! It would have meant she left with the middlest who i… https://t.co/ZWREBV3Ylp]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA don’t eat Little Caesars pizza and you won’t have to worry about coupon scams]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s rare when I eat breakfast. I fast, works better for me. I don’t miss breakfast food but tonight I made breakfa… https://t.co/g84KE0aCP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysDana @Veriphide @Stephaniefishm4 @arapaho415 @dwinfrey72 @RighteousBabe4 @MountainsStars @MingGao26 @Ex67T20… https://t.co/xrAV8WEs39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay!  Today and everyday we celebrate the creativity, ingenuity, strength, independence,… https://t.co/upw1P1Fp8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im an actress. Check me out. I knew my lines and stuff.  Watch “Jasmine C. Robinson-Drama Reel 2018” on #Vimeo https://t.co/r05HoxLptZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job #JussieSmollett for taking valuable police resources away from victims who really need it!  And all becaus… https://t.co/Dw5NrBF9qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking tight bruh. I hate this state. I hate this culture. I hate this country. I fucking hate humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @AsaHutchinson So was HRC emails and Benghazi “partisan” so your point?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you flip your calendar and see @WContreras40 you know March is going to be great! ❤️ #cubs https://t.co/j6pjBdAlxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i wanna hangout w/ people, they lag. &amp; when they wanna hangout w/ me, i lag. 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo ahorita: Escuchando español + typeando inglés= espanglish disaster #poderoso https://t.co/qT8GhNJSs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olivianuzzi I get it but it went on his IG live. He’s taunting the Judge at this point. Lock his ass up for God’s sake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I do!! I have an amazing man!! I love you Joe Benivamondez!! ❤️🖤 @ Abilene, Texas https://t.co/JeQJj4PFIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing how productive you can be without getting out of your pjs or leaving your house. 💁🏼‍♀️ #ilovesundays]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some familiar faces here! Hockey legends @SamiJoSmall @JenBotterill @AngelaJames8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our BBots getting support from our Erie Feeder Cheer team! @grandviewel taking state by #StVrainStorm… https://t.co/v2dlrIPpPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had so much fun doing this Valentine’s Day story! These j-school couple stories will make your heart melt ❤️ https://t.co/nQU8LpApAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Taste and see that the Lord is good; blessed is the one who takes refuge in him.” Psalm 34:8 NIV… https://t.co/ZcswcYCHwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Us at this Event : Rainbow Consciousness Channeled ART  #reikihealing #reikimasterteacher #art… https://t.co/2Ni4bfIpH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@njterrie @IdahoRoadapple @tess_tess2 @Catlady628 @criteria681 @kimmybeaa @dorisat58862534 @DarCie287… https://t.co/bha3GZnhZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to do a 5 minute children's storytime audition for my interview. I'm thinking I'll play Someone to Lava on t… https://t.co/vM2byTWPM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattconte I bet @DevRelCallum loves that you took over on me &lt;3 oh wait, I demanded that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KojionGuitar I wasn't sure so he died before Jason was. He was born in 1975,I feel better  now! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Kim Jong Un never intended to give up Nukes. In fact, he's building an enormous underground tunnel… https://t.co/rzdzOgYjbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[God does his best work when it’s DARK in order for you to live an eternal life in LIGHT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #FortMyers, FL! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Benefits Specialist at Chico's FAS #HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wiles_x @realDonaldTrump Nice try.  Another white guy, trying to scare a woman.  You think I don't know what abort… https://t.co/8WxJH5bADJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[He also made fun of me for how I “ate like an ape” bc I only used a fork to eat and not a fork and knife like a PROPER LADY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite thing is to listen to my pre AP kids teaching each other. ❤️ ❤️ ❤️ #mykidsrock #mdpurpose https://t.co/tK7qlwgqqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ozzpack12 @george_capen @jocowboys87 He knows nothing about justice or national security]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump This is unbecoming of the GOP to publish such rubbish. Time for the Chairperson to step down.… https://t.co/opH4X2jsVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy shopping in #sagharbor today during #harborfrost❄️ * * * * #happy #yellow #sunny #saturday #friendlypeople 😀… https://t.co/DnckAGEh2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics I saw a report where you said that the Obama administration had no scandals.  Do you really think it's… https://t.co/sylFOyqRVY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Bar Number is 48962. He violated 18 U.S.C. § 1512. He could be ch… https://t.co/7ila6co04v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back on an airplane. First flight out and there’s a maintenance issue. Going to my happy place. Going to my happy p… https://t.co/fJYPYYwmdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FixesItself @roseymelhill @sarasotamike66 @TuckFrump61 @reallisacox @SpiritualMarie @american2084 @thinkingtime55… https://t.co/8WigOYsT9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Things I'd Like You To Know About MS And Me.   1. Don't feel sorry for me, but do me a favor by learning more abo… https://t.co/ZIM1fW5IuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are struggling with sleeping/insomnia, this nature sounds might help you to sleep :)… https://t.co/2uftdhB3IC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamKhloe on @TyltEnt—Khloé Kardashian is allegedly leaving Tristan Thompson over cheating rumors https://t.co/MNPy22LycL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gossipoftheciti You said this was gonna happen weeks ago, that’s why I never said one thing about the situation ca… https://t.co/m6BxeLmrs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__arlicious Aye bring me some food this weekend. 😂 preferably fiery crab Mrs. Big Baller! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week taping of StyleCheck was full of laughter with @BUtifulbyCandic filling in for @clthebrand @afroschannel.… https://t.co/76afnZDt96]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Michael’s gone, but it doesn’t change the fact that he destroyed these people, and the world still goes on loving… https://t.co/Icv9aRqwr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCFirstRead Correction on statement made by anchor in regards the people that are most affected. https://t.co/YVSMnFa8Gp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dramariabatista @rksevenup @ydanis This is about child snatching not apprehending criminals]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man just grabbed by arm on the bus and asked me to sit down and claimed to know me and I’ve honestly never been m… https://t.co/8ShUUHyJZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had my social media since 7th grade and today was the first time I’ve ever changed my username. Excited to finally be a Gilger. 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸 Very good! Here I leave the pencil of one of my new work. Black Canary a great fighter and with a power of sonic… https://t.co/mk8B4AKWlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s happy 😃 I’m happy Good Day God Bless. 1 Enjoy this Sunday. 1. 7. @ McDonald's https://t.co/5OOAy60Osg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilNasreddine @disgruntledbill @icemanwbs @Mjhtwh @nafsnep It doesn't make sense at all. No AHL is in the same place as their NHL one]]></document><document><![CDATA[So pretty soon "As Time Goes By" is on local PBS and I am torn between that and NBA All-Star stuff and if you don't… https://t.co/Z8tX14YZY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyRDaniels @healWRITEnow @PovertyEdge This message is often echoed in nurses training: "It's not about you, it'… https://t.co/wsPAPjeVcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NottyRenee @kelseydangerous I’m on my third try. This one is more successful. I’m just mad my SIMs get really fat… https://t.co/UXDCg2Cgnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosesdaughter61 @OfficialAnitaSt @xaanzmasque @VitalityBio Humans who obsess over Christ always shortchange themse… https://t.co/SFfr12msHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iniguezmari_ That’s okay! We should definitely plan to go soon with the girls though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two different dates.  "Laughed" them away with my humor. Now we are buddies. No romance anything.   God when?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving everything about this video AND this squad - great season, @BSMGirlsHockey! Specials up to Seniors Sally, Gr… https://t.co/Tz6DDsPbeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ça moi à chaque fois que j’ai du retard sur mes règles mdr alors que I ain’t get no dick for almost a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t want Marissa. I want you to be the real you.”  Sounds good. Don’t mind me while I wear my retainer on our overnight. 👍🏼]]></document></documents></author>