<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FBIChicago @FBIWFO @FBIMiamiFL so I think you guys should listen to me because we should all be extinct if it wasn… https://t.co/cI1nwNCr3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBMSwrestling @LBHSWRESTLING @WAVEPRIDE @nickmenkin Congratulations!!! Guys Embrace The Grind!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope @Hugeshow is right! But Michigan will have to find a way to slow down the Sparty offense. They clicked in AA… https://t.co/BhQTKgc7b2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Coach Streit and @BravesBBall1 on the big win over Piper, 67-60. It’s a great day to be BRAVE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamezHomey This looks like the #ForgedinFire testing. It’s a show on @HISTORY can’t be sure tho. 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dusting of snow in Portsmouth NH, but a #Blizzard of #KNOWLEDGE unleashed inside @TomIrwinInc #innovation seminar… https://t.co/hxjzya0V90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Highway_30 @Alyssa_Milano HI. I WATCH YOUR VIDEO (OR READ YOUR POST) AND CLICK "#LIKE" BUTTON UNDER YOUR #VIDEO IN… https://t.co/pFbCPWHkQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[First measurement was 6.8, second measurement came up to 7.5. You’re supposed to take three but I’m convinced it’s… https://t.co/8o2vhx4YhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey @shaunking The focus on the wall is to obfuscate the fact that the enemy is within.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steel_Curtain4 I do not know what is going on, but the Steelers need to get it together and trade AB, they cannot… https://t.co/LQlVXwZfXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkk9lover @GaetaSusan @SpeakerPelosi @ROCKONOHIO @BestBrownsFan @PhilMcCrackin44 @DaRealGrizzle @AppSame… https://t.co/BO7VkP832N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradA53472906 @eedoogie @MartyBrink @DaveLittleBigM @TheMeadowlands @kenvoiceover @JessicaOtten1 We'll get'em tomorrow night bud !]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re watching you @senatemajldr  &amp; we’re coming for your seat!!! #EnoughIsEnough]]></document><document><![CDATA[me in middle school arguing with the kid who came to my bday party and left early with a goodie bag like they weren… https://t.co/giUXZnsi8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTVQBryan Lol. Then they both walked away like another day at the office...🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelcoDelphia #Delco's finest beer? It's #cantastic. https://t.co/MUO2HfDl0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Blackface shit and utter disrespect of African-Americans in all facets is fucking exhausting. During Black His… https://t.co/xxDw7FxbQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaterTottMusic Better to over-think!, than look stoopid!😂 https://t.co/96rR0KV18T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg it was just for some short seconds, but he looks awesome, can't wait to watch this!!! Most definitely my favori… https://t.co/BkFzmReQLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all weren’t on twitter when hunter Moore was here and it really shows....]]></document><document><![CDATA[TICKETS SECURED!!!!! Can’t wait to be in Prague with my boyfriend and best friend❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ #ABGT350 #TMPRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobVila HI. i WAS #SUBSCRIBED IN YOUR #CHANNEL (OR ADDED TO YOUR #FRIENDS IN #TWITTER) AND ALSO , I CLICK "#LIKE"… https://t.co/ljX9M1UKLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Legallaw1 @BandB_CBS @WayneBrady I agree with you ma’am, sorry for your loss. I can imagine how this must affect y… https://t.co/sMOLnSsUCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3WinstonSalem @F3WeFoCo @F3_250   5 for the week. 53/250 YTD  16.58 for the week. 157.75/500 YTD  #F3TwoFiddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gdtbth @StateofBall @NCSUFans @_callmemal enjoy Roy. Agree, he's done a helluva job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gatlonbat @ceostroff @peterframpton @MiamiHerald @teamtrace @mcclatchy DavidWheeler Newtown Dad said. “It is going… https://t.co/L9TiXGx0zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenyaDigIt94 @PeteClassy @Rob_Fleming @BCNDPCaucus https://t.co/Wj4lGwiRfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boosplodge @ProjectClassic1 Alan actually plays the trombone on that Jive Bunny   It's the John Anderson Big Band, not Glen Millar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipAustin7 And didn't it work. For someone responsible for Preparation, I thought he was woefully unprepared fo… https://t.co/TDvF5lihFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SobchakValentines are what you need today, Lebowski fans. But that’s just like my opinion, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming up for that summer Gospel Doo Wop sound 🎼🎶🎹🎤 @ New York, New York https://t.co/BpXXDjXFjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my 180 lbs. Leg press heel make direct contact with his balls. He is now sterile and unable to procreate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Local12 @Bob_Herzog @SPCACincinnati @JohnLomaxWKRC12 What do you smear on your face besides makeup on SPCA Day, Bo… https://t.co/KK46noRtN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelMilloway That XD money can’t pay for the trip LOL 🤓 https://t.co/xZIiE57soP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are an elite team and your best player scores 42. You win every time. Rockets are not a top 4 team in the We… https://t.co/GsHyNKz01m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @Grandma_Shelia @FoxNews @IngrahamAngle Your average FAUX viewer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FundamentalHype @BayStreetBulls @mmjinvesting @aphriainc @ChrisParry @equitydotguru Blah Blah Blah - I did - I sol… https://t.co/4hMTs3Ze7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I think Ben won’t even be playing much longer, and I also think everyone knows that.   Why get traded so c… https://t.co/8JcQ19Xdfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSM_Chica It'll be ok chica, last 5 yrs I've had numerous surgeries. They'll take good care of you]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was 4 or 5, I was called up to be the cute lil audience helper at a magic show, and every time the magician… https://t.co/1B7bf6AcwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok my dad and grandma are the worst ever. Gma: whites date whites and N*****s date n*****s Dad: yeah now a days you… https://t.co/UzvSqTgXxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Sounds like a “dog whistle” as the left says about Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @EufyOfficial and sister companies, and would love to try some of its smart home products and cameras, but t… https://t.co/37PnfwIIiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@animenaruto17 @GhostShellZen @FUNimation @marchimark You are using the tweets in a public utility in an attempt to… https://t.co/FOcJTmzu6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Priotess @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump Well it shouldn't upset you 1 bit. You did it right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What business in America will let Millions of Americans die for profits? The Healthcare Industries, Republicans, and their Shareholders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philafitz @BoopStats @theaceofspaeder Ricketts had 1 hit, a single, in 20 major league plate appearances]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorDScott You want to make that statement under oath? Proof? Thought not. Hypocrite fake preacher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's beginning to look a lot like winter...... @ Holland, Massachusetts https://t.co/JgJAo8mVap]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Forest Hill Church - Fort Mill in Fort Mill, SC w/ @mandyhyder https://t.co/zaEazDCVuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because when you’re being eaten by a Bear, it’s customary to blame everyone but yourself. —————————————… https://t.co/sEEB6JNoJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was either 24 or 25 when it became a thing and every damn radio station in Austin would not shut the fuck up abou… https://t.co/ziBOJgCbep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handsofstone_99 @CapFriendly @EJHradek_NHL I more meant "Quinton" vs. "Quintin" but it's spelled differently on ea… https://t.co/hKjDUufeAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @latejulyorganic I just tried to buy a bunch of your bacon chips at the #Westford whole foods on sale, but they… https://t.co/4VqnbKSBJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d probably be the same as the kid bleacherreport  @kyrieirving  #thebestfeelingever @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/2V0NDY32MH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the best you can with what you have. . Don’t compare yourself to others. . You’re only human. @ Rancho Cucamonga… https://t.co/WdrjDyaCuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then why did he, and Ivanka lie to America publicly about this multiple times? Because it's a shit story about nepo… https://t.co/RQrfON9J63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommytomlinson I remember when he was in high school with @renfrowhunter. It is hard to beat the mid 80’s era.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OregonMills I shouldn't say pick #4. Ping pong ball slot #4.  #zion #bulls]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this night six years ago I booked my first show. Booking shows is a fuck ton of fun and I strongly recommend eve… https://t.co/E3POW1Tf6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhookstead @DailyCaller Might give you time to pickup a book &amp; read about George Washington....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geeeezer #Blackhawks #turnovers #killers #CHIvsDAL  Started off looking good and then... aaarrrggg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teesymone_ @Pariiisxo Change the way you think can stop some problems. Example. Most people have lazy money in the… https://t.co/aujIBWe2Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[this weather would be so much better if i got to spend it layed up w/ my boo...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣A well crafted “about me” section or video should convert viewers into customers. 👉🎥 In this video, I’ll show you… https://t.co/vqSS6WWUPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPC_Tweet_ID @SenatorKarnes @MikeCaputoWV @wvhouse Don't you have Muslims to go hate today? Don't waste your time… https://t.co/lWtAWHt3eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun way to get ready for Spring golf, practice some basics like set-up.  Wonderful indoor experience!  ⛳️ @ Blue Hi… https://t.co/jqdD0d6npt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey dipshit, he announced before tgat NK was going to denuclearize. Remember he told Americans they can sleep easy… https://t.co/svgG1HIrSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Resurrected IPA by @4handsbrewery @ Big Betty’s Dump Station — https://t.co/S4LffZ9usA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BwireMsanii @AjayaDivine Can't vouch for them boys, I only vouch for Jesus, the Christ.  Son of God, Son of Man, T… https://t.co/keLdVCFITP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is beautiful.... I need a clean version for my phone wallpaper lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Beverly is gold on the Mic. He has a future on ESPN for sure. Give him a show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk Donald Trump Got $17 Million Insurance Payout for Damage Few Recall https://t.co/sfCPM5HeTc. CAN’T THIS ALONE PUT HIM IN PRISON?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrrlGhost I think deign and illustration are places you can get away with having pink hair. It has never stopped me from getting work tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost How about condemning Trump for hate speech &amp; anti-Mexican speech, anti-Muslim speech, pro-nazi speech, etc. etc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing breakfast sandwich from the DuPont farmer’s market. @ WMATA Bus Stop #1001535 (42) https://t.co/H6sqzYJd94]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I play Pathfinder. #ApexLegends #LETSRIDEAZIPLINE https://t.co/gdmBPI50Ia]]></document><document><![CDATA[*THE RED🛑CAP OF EVIL,RACISM. PUPPET, TRAITOR, CRIMINAL, LIAR, UNFIT MISTAKE FAKENEWS TRUMP.*AMERICA🇺🇸IS BETTER THAN… https://t.co/N9EQT2swjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ma5RN @acv69cardenas @hospitalclinic @idibaps @EASLnews @liverunitclinic @macarlotal Felicidades Andres!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @maxrayriek, just checking in to say hi. Miss working together. Hope all is well. 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien It defies common sense, logic, and I suspect those are Graham's words and not the voters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateKennedyxxx @RockyEmersonXXX Wth. Lol act 2 I'm intrigued after reading that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Camila_Cabello should I do Rock or be Mr right furreal life question you are my wife either way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipotleTweets what is the point of ordering ahead when you’re waiting About 10 mins regardless?? https://t.co/GJEXCFdUnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bleything Where is this secret location and what are you hiding there?! Internet of things, indeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Renate1217 Happy Friday Renate! Is there a holiday they forgot to mention to you? 🤔😳😂☕️☕️♥️ https://t.co/pfcZN10Jmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 How many times in a day can his statements make me say "what a moron"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job @HoneyCreekIowa? Concessions Culinary Supervisor - Globe Life Park in Arlingt… https://t.co/t6XPXzeGAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyhawk Nothing makes us smile more than seeing our children succeed  Nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bagleyriskmgmt He needs to come back...great kid and tons of talent, but another year with more talent coming in would be good for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson can we talk about something #LakeShow #Lakers https://t.co/sFw4kaTg5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasa This is me too. But I started reading the Arts section of the paper again because I know there will be crossword entries]]></document><document><![CDATA[Members of the committee were out in full force today knocking on doors 🚪for @pamforpa! #VotePam #SD37 https://t.co/ltWI1H5mqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch @nanstl_13 He needs to leave my money in savings alone and sign a check. Try sign language or simply… https://t.co/Bg9pUzMNAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the days when I wake up in a good mood for absolutely no reason 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the fuck does Webster get a dictionary and I don’t? I thought this was the USA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvmidd85 @Scottke59 @therealDJDoing @Beard_Vet @Genemey56 @sgcostanza @killabeas69 @Timoth5141 @laj951362… https://t.co/Hw2uNLf1zJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Your ranting only feeds the anger . Anger makes you a fool you fool .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the 35% @mongodb campaign got a response from @awscloud - personally i think getting the API for this DB… https://t.co/hrEQC6K8pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is incredible! As #Crew96 fans we're lucky to have @wil_trapp as our captain for another year and lucky to hav… https://t.co/SWNr2Aups5]]></document></documents></author>