<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This beautiful digital illustration by yours truly is from today's new blog post, in which you can pay a visit to a… https://t.co/I70PVAJmJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Progress. Warrior women. Such a pleasure the response everyone is showing me. We thank you and are so lucky. The… https://t.co/XTTPuif3zL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I was eating shrimp and my boyfriend had never had one so I gave him one and this hoe TOOK A  BITE FROM T… https://t.co/Xz0eqIA18M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louis Tomlinson – Two of Us @Louis_Tomlinson https://t.co/WcbzF9h5mO 💎💎💎💎💎💎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ten months after Backpage’s shutdown, sex workers are using an array of imperfect websites, if they can find work a… https://t.co/GbAzATyVYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just figured out how to delete old stories from Instagram wowww thank god]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traci520 @obvious_ideas @Paul63B @Nativeesoul We never saw original video. Only saw that one photo. Hard for me to… https://t.co/d8ggJvB4ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump LG must be getting blackmailed]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY MARCH!!   The March Literacy Newsletter is here!!  https://t.co/MciZPG1Sv9 #SOELiteracy, #Marchisreadingmonth… https://t.co/sC39VOEaI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Goodness— This was sent in by a viewer. This is the school bus and Rumpke Truck that crashed leaving at least 9… https://t.co/aHyW9LnE1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My receipt after I leave @Target even though I only went in for 1 thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOTODlSNEYLAND It’s just posting pictures, some shirtless maybe in just underwear. Either to for the sole purpose… https://t.co/vxIOl9jaY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CartoonzNCereal I mean, shit. It’s Sunday. I’m not supposed to be thinking this hard today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSalesforce Awesome!  You inspired me to check mine,  i normally just check that app that shows me new followers… https://t.co/3gn965kAZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Saturday and that means it's Club Night at Young Bar. Enjoy a Blue Lagoon for only 25rmb or Black/White Russia… https://t.co/ZlpDU1ZwpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget about our Fundraiser on Sunday morning from 8:30-10:00 with Cheryl E. Wood and Diane Peck! It's for th… https://t.co/mFj5gv5LW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a thing. I now want to make more things. #Succulents @ Durham, North Carolina https://t.co/Qkn6Lxuc0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it! We are excited to present today at the SEAT-J Conference. https://t.co/I1yzYDzdXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My take:  as is said here, quite possibly what's needed for real reform of the policing system is putting it in the… https://t.co/U0At5sIlnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaySteeleRTV6 @rtv6 @pedrokaawaloa @BroadwayIndy Did not nail it - but tried!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhmhart42 Yes! RAINBOW: A First Book of Pride publishing in May 2019 by @MaginationPress @APA @jenmurfee… https://t.co/tlZ2F4qTaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeachSoccer Congratulations from Carlos Torres and family!! Proud of our Bearcats 🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a blessing to this confusion that is happening around us right now. It is still screwed up and there is st… https://t.co/jhr8yHoYLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @NBCConnecticut I think I found your newest reporter!Nicholas is 8 years old and battling epilepsy and cerebral… https://t.co/NAPa6CDyzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staying out late on a week night like 🤩🤩🤩 Wouldn’t miss this one!!! #watchparty #beatVegas #GoStars]]></document><document><![CDATA[First lull in Kashmir since latest India-Pakistan escalation https://t.co/hGSwFllqk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[LISTEN! Every amazing thing that’s happened in my life I’m like, “is this from when my grandma and ma prayed over m… https://t.co/h8tj6MexxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am happy flying Alaska going to DC sunshine and snow! #iflyalaska #happyhour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marouf08 @NBA I agree but you do have to admit he looks fluffy and breathing heavy ! Needs to get into game shape]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I was a late bloomer and never had a mix tape/cd made for me growing up, it is now mandatory for anyone who’s tr… https://t.co/pusrxyN4Jz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreavillamon Lo dijo en entrevista para @telemaxson  puedes checar la página..buenas noches!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week ago today I was presenting our #scicomm research at #aslo19 in San Juan Puerto Rico. #eddev #aquaticsci… https://t.co/Tu9SEBbV6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up in the church - one of my “norms” was my pastor had a 20+year affair with our church’s secretary. She wa… https://t.co/FCBO73fMo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Luke Perry. You were my first foray into loving the bad boy. #LukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerp1215 @Steveonomics I think we can all agree this needs to happen yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s session is informative, engaging, and inspiring. Thanks for everything @Ctr4CHR!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning café @gloriajkenyon @BabyGo2014 @AnaMaria_pasch @LadyWiseWorld @LavaletteAstrid @drwilliams7777… https://t.co/jS4HGbmU54]]></document><document><![CDATA[With reluctance I admit, he is from the school district I worked for. People have actually said ‘such a nice man’ w… https://t.co/6gQce2EXZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead I know I am going to be on the edge of my seat while watching this one.  I don't want anything to h… https://t.co/rU64jnGlEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[birth control and weight gain::  It's often a temporary side effect that's due to fluid retention, not extra fat.… https://t.co/HsdTcpm3He]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m falling asleep 😴like I did earlier... this stuff needs to pick up, this is why I have to rewatch it, what did I… https://t.co/yPsaGORSLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @davidhogg111 It may or may not be a good time to read The Parable of the Sower by Octavia E. Butler. Depending.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been to #Phoenix these last 3 weeks. Guess that means I should be headed that way come end of this lease. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chooglin1 No one sane has time to keep up with their shit, for all we know it's... https://t.co/9xwMj7TOr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthieJack I am completely bummed I missed the scorpions under black light...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lolliexddd I think it’s cause we both spent too much money already lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[last year for FPD☘️ I was eating my weight in Jell-O shots at frats and drinking vodka crans at 7am   this year I w… https://t.co/OaWcqJwmJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ga7ahad Thank you!! Hard won wisdom, for sure. My takeaways after 33 years orbiting the sun 😉✌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you live near a retirement community when the sacrament talks are about senior missions]]></document><document><![CDATA[This day. Staying at a hotel in NYC near where I worked in the ‘80s. Not much has changed, really. Don’t give up. D… https://t.co/DCDqyuQovU]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday queen, you’re the funniest and best coworker a girl could ask for. hope your day is as fab as you are🖤@_leachapman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to decide whether I should clean out the fridge today or just move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtrc @JennyHRay @wcmtuk @R_E_Kasprowicz Hmm I don’t know anyone doing this (I think) but maybe @erin_ottmar does?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our AAU tourney scheduled for this Saturday, March 16th has been canceled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abuela Paqui y sus nietos 💕 #2019 #february15th #sapoverdetuyu #birthdaygirl #familyaboveall #allyouneedislapancha… https://t.co/qUIYjlOUQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atensnut Juanita.  Have I told you lately that I love you...your frankness is nothing short of amazing. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week I made an impulsive trip to NYC and it was one of the best decisions I have ever made. I’m so grateful fo… https://t.co/lrpbZn6nlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me looking at tweets that directly relate to the issues I brought up in my speech https://t.co/t6sAfCVS3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gkane0415 @ABC @ABCWorldNews 1 fundraiser, 2 MAGA rallies and lots of 🍳and 🏌️‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh okay everyone is getting a lil somethin somethin see spicy...except poor Alice. Dang it Alice don’t do it. #GoodTrouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to @NYTEvents at @sf_curran as a build-up to @TheJungleUS opening, which was an amazing discussion on US immig… https://t.co/Uz5aDIVkvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear most the time y’all boys are worse than females when it comes to drama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco You took the words right out of my mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama could execute Rocky Myers any day now – and he could be innocent. @GovernorKayIvey must grant Rocky clemenc… https://t.co/UONt36eT2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latelateshow @kevinjonas @joejonas @nickjonas #LateLateJonas #CarpoolKaraoke  https://t.co/MefjPS6Dpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Too many Poor people are Breeding when they can't even afford to take care of THEMSELVES...So 'one' i… https://t.co/Ce4Kere131]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope... my mom is a saint and knows I’m stressed from law school so she will clean my house for me while I’m in cla… https://t.co/iLeKCDwdk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KRogersdotter @samsanders The first is a perfectly good pickle sandwich. The third is a decent sweet kid snack (al… https://t.co/atC507LWgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SaveTheBabyHumans  #DefundPlannedParenthood #KillingIsNotHealthCare #AbortionIsEvil Taxpayers' $ cannot provide ab… https://t.co/RwB94FqL2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on my friends pattern and winding down before bed. #knitting #yarnitude #hearttoheart #halo #unsc #bedtime… https://t.co/QUyUXtJTit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Williemaj @Timcast I know Facebook does because there is an outsourced company that is in my city ... apparently t… https://t.co/FacrFOWSXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frjohnhollowell And everyone is tired explaining what the Pope "really means' when he talks off the cuff. At some… https://t.co/LTxiJrfBwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @Herbert_L_Reed You’re supposed to be intelligent, so why can’t you understand that they are the SAME!! Yo… https://t.co/S8Hut1HRJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wkyc I absolutely agree with him. And I think an investigation needs to be conducted what congressman and woman ta… https://t.co/ZXeeBXgICn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this stuff so much!! #fnxambassador #fnx_fit #fitnesslife https://t.co/Qr6kLGzKOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePlumLineGS @LibsInAmerica @RepMarkMeadows If the Republicans were truly Patriots and not power hungry self.serv… https://t.co/UEUCNOpa3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @BenBobickWRCB your enthusiasm for our program is awesome.  We’ll save you a front row seat next year when we m… https://t.co/w7ewyL4XYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seungjjanggu I watched it. That was just one line. They went on to talk about how they had interviewed N.Flying an… https://t.co/9YqA5eNlHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really?  Funny, but I read about more corruption surrounding the 2016 election all the time.  That election was not… https://t.co/bIQArqmNBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 2019. Ppl need to realize I’m probably gonna forget I left you on read]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boy is at it again and this time playing Clyde!!! 🤯 I can’t wait!!! @Iamjessecboyd is doing big things!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tag, your it. And everyone else that’s joined-pass it on. (Tagging is not my thing...)@behindblueyes72 @michie8… https://t.co/2bUCXVQrRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosD27801704 @CherubNation @LavaletteAstrid @pkamla1 @NYCREMilton @1228erin @letgolifeflows @jill_magnussen… https://t.co/jIZrwh0AXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I just realized what’s this stupid shit app I see porn gay ppl and somebody put a toe in their dick 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_67 It’s good to have some time to decompress. Our hours are extended today thru bag night... 8 am to midnigh… https://t.co/fTFmiSmcej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney's  Storybook Collection  Volume 2  by Disney Book Group Staff  Copyright 2002   Disney Enterprises Incorpora… https://t.co/qRRMS1XfOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The addition of music changes the tone of the room instantaneously.”  ~ Tisha Richmond #setthestagetoengage https://t.co/yVN8LepXFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1000wattmarc between our political climate and this news - I'm about to unplug. Ready for more leaders that lead w… https://t.co/GgOVvmPUOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked for a label maker for Christmas and once I got one, I looked up the names of all of our porch plants and th… https://t.co/Vp3lRyvpCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiskeyRiff @DierksBentley @brothersosborne @KaceyMusgraves @KipMooreMusic @AshleyMcBryde New playlist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe Ivanka Trump has accomplished more in 1 day than AOC"s busiest day flying burgers and beers. Appears that… https://t.co/1p6eyrNIDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillyeaglesfa1 @LNW4Trump @gatewaypundit I'm the Boss...what a joke. The little darling reports to Soros along wi… https://t.co/8qRQSKsjaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those type of friends that help you vacuum your vehicle after a good wash &gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be #WithAll Board Member, formerly The Emily Program Foundation, strengthening support for eating disorder… https://t.co/PiF31Coq0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLind Does applying for asylum fall under US law or international convention? Just read something re: no access to… https://t.co/nqF6s0rxH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASegar @theEVENTmpi @JackMLeith @Stephen_L_SF @WeAreNoPants @Visual_Coach @ShooEvents @flowchainsensei @agroebbe… https://t.co/HE07jylP1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada que mis papás se van, les quiero encargar ropa y zapatos y ptm no tengo dinero para estarlo gastando así cada 3 semanas 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can hear the rhythm of the Lion of the tribe of Judah He's doing a new thing so we're singing a new song  not a b… https://t.co/z38v8ZAj26]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he brought out the Asherah from the house of the LORD, outside Jerusalem, to the brook Kidron, and burned it at… https://t.co/Wo8JkqJjct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewACherry Milo (poodle) and Otis (schnoodle) #LoveYourPetDay https://t.co/yqaME5sAXE]]></document></documents></author>