<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the impact hockey has on my life is fucking INSANE. i can have such an awful day but the moment i turn on the habs… https://t.co/0c4CCrwHRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[prioritizing my life and my health has made me a lot less popular and i don't want to care! there are times in my l… https://t.co/2gg3tll8Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I adopted this amazing creature 3 years ago today and as you can tell by this picture he hates it here. ❤️ https://t.co/dXt8kEfwbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Why don’t you face accountability for not paying back and current taxes you old windbag?  Shouldn’t throw st… https://t.co/x5b3CaOHJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skeeterosenbaum @MichaelAvenatti Please help #KatlynAlix #JusticeForKatie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t feel like I’m getting through to you. Let me paint this clear. Life is short my dear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely learned a lot about building a racecar this year. I’ve done most of the work on my car myself and can’t… https://t.co/ZABXhBiYyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@archigerm 🤣 It’s just a starchy seed that is “supposedly” healthier than rice ... still cooking rice for Ray though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sure isn’t pretty...but most things in the gym aren’t. Working on getting that stability back 💁🏻‍♀️🤸🏻‍♂️ @ Genes… https://t.co/eCLLUc64cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[was gonna say YAS OLIVIA COLMAN MY QUEEN my night has been made nothing else will upset me now but HELL THE F NO no… https://t.co/Oj2JoGXrxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgracemarkham @Best_of_PT Lovely! I like that you said it felt familiar - I've never been to Bermuda so now I'm wo… https://t.co/RIqoQPd0qE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC (4) 10 who were destroyed at En-dor, who became dung for the ground. 11 Make their nobles like Oreb and Zeeb,… https://t.co/SfV3xzcLHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_Anahata You doll that’s why you’re still responding. Can’t let it go. Who ganged up on you exactly? You’ve been… https://t.co/kGb6kWyOBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FacialRecognition  Why does #ML #AI Matter? The #DataScience is plain. When will the algorithms (correct) __suffic… https://t.co/0r96DX62kU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrEarpLA You are a ray of hope for us. I look forward to your tweets everyday. I agree with your wisdom and unders… https://t.co/ZH3phclFIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched all 10 eps of “The Umbrella Academy”. Really enjoyed the first few but thought it lost some of the intrigue… https://t.co/8RChjJ53th]]></document><document><![CDATA[Falafel, the ubiquitous street food of the Middle East  https://t.co/Q9gqYvSBET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Lol says who?  What do you know that we don't?   Not about that anyway.  There was an injustice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ginette722 It is! Hands down one of my favorite Netflix series to watch. Plus she’s in Cuba now- we need to know how the trip goes lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thebestdaysparttwo; #horsephaseforlife @ Timberland https://t.co/VKtYNEE5gX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TallShipProds Absolutely appreciated, love this series &amp; Diana's books so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateAronoff Someone is bound to point out that his efforts to put a carbon tax policy in place have failed - three times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathcor @Berlidge @David_Leavitt @realDonaldTrump Maybe you might want the rethink the way you handle things.  Goo… https://t.co/18sWWx5zDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @BECCAcosmetics @ForeverMalika @Sephora @ultabeauty @Nordstrom @Bloomingdales @QVC @cultbeauty Will get it, Looks Fab-U-las]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shariah law is INCOMPATIBLE With the Constitution... https://t.co/kkroOQMwRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[this traumatized me for a very long time when i heard it on the news. it’s one of my worst fears when flying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@midnitekismet @KimberlyThorne9 @HereForTheTea2 I mean, ya'll coming for my wedding and allll...:3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RieMcAz @DallasDietzenba He was pure evil. And most of his abductions were in broad daylight in well populated areas - beyond scary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnaBarley @Isabella_Gomez @OneDayAtATime Mine has been Lydia since we could make our own avatars. 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida has elections that would make this look like Mr Rogers neighborhood 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_marcearias_ @bsvalencia_ I’m criticizing his filmmaking, not him as a person. You, on the other hand, seem to hav… https://t.co/Z3GMkv2Nm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new play of mine will be in New York City again. I’m honored to be part of the EstroGenius Festival this March. O… https://t.co/FvPVR6bG19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we have to accept things that will not change and decide if we want to stay in the situation or be the ch… https://t.co/Iif50nJXh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkitoKrod @sianoresist You’re welcome! I can’t take credit for this hilarious photoshop, but it’s certainly an i… https://t.co/dbXptuA2Eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrokerAceKid People, Jay is the “real deal”. Gives so much to so many.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 You're about 60 too, light. Either way, he's still vile &amp; repugnant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way people react to sing song’s result is more entertaining than sing song itself 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free Live Money making monday masterclass: Automate To Elevate💪🏽  Get on the list to grab link! Info in bio!… https://t.co/MyqfrZDK4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has chosen me to nap on. I feel honoured!!! https://t.co/JJRnAyvgIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m struggling with accepting these random white hairs on my head. It’s not enough that they stand out like shining… https://t.co/H5Lckl3iiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler Doesn’t even sound like a real name.  Is it a nick name like Gianni Calamari.  Sounds fishy to me...,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDLHughley I'm glad you and wendy cleared the air however you are still the best looking dude on the show! :p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exact same. I’ll wear hoodies and sweatpants with a little lashes and lip gloss popping type of thing going on 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. @SenSherrodBrown  I am ashamed of you, and the 43 other NOs. May God save your collective souls👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Alex i couldn’t really get his satevo step cause of my damn sneakers . But fuck it i was comfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kitty #lost #afternoonwalk @ JCC Pittsburgh - South Hills https://t.co/UbcYiGmKOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about Ms. Awawi’s career helped us understand why and how we use stethoscopes and protective gear in a hos… https://t.co/NHnyUj2I94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Meadows trots out Lynne Patton to refute Trump racism accusations https://t.co/Lb98Ox315v via @nbcnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my class, a man said the NY law  "allows women to abort babies when they are born" and this girl and I looked at… https://t.co/pc64hh7YvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating my birthday Caribbean style lol you see him...#djbmore @ Da West Caribbean Bar &amp; Grill https://t.co/COQyeDO4IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hija de #comandos #omega7 #cuba #anticomunismo #losterroristas #terrorists -🇨🇺 💯- @juliagallardo #julia #oshun… https://t.co/zdanmZR3fS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Sitterle crossed 35K. Time 03:42:52, pace 10:22 min/mile, est. finish 11:35 am https://t.co/dVlKPruD3E #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Augusta, GA? https://t.co/nsnYgnG8mw #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking the necessary steps to keep that image off of my TL 🙅🏽‍♀️🙅🏽‍♀️ I REBUKE IT IN JESUS’ NAME!! https://t.co/rtFOW6ynqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Just_someNobody @devincomiskey @DeFede @CBSMiami @Patriots I agree but these woman are being trafficking against their will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casecec #casewinter2019 Pasco ,WA Hybrid site starting strong 7:00 am! https://t.co/nqklukBDOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BeeLane @jasminekaderaaa Lmao in my defense the first time I watched it, I was on acid so it was really fucking with my senses.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real estate and employers dominating #FairfaxCounty's economy. Of course #Amazon has a place in this.… https://t.co/FADNVAL1EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atensnut And what side is Feinstein was never held accountable for her actions]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so fucking shook that someone made me feel like I was mentally crazy when I was right all along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflecting after the Van chase🤔 #💣🔨⛏🔪🧨⚰️ #justsomefellings@thatmoment🔥😡🤷🏽‍♀️ #haveagoodday💕 @ Center City https://t.co/WlggABbFXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eweather13 Found the driveway...14” Higganum 📷and JohnDeeregirl @kmosk3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a prime example of whites thinking they understand what is best for “everyone” in the sense that they can’t… https://t.co/eDlAPJ2ptN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity This woman should be EXPELLED @realDonaldTrump  @LindseyGrahamSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but @BhadBhabie snapchat tv show is my favorite and I love her and relate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some seriously fun ideas with these 13 Life Hacks for Parents. Creative problem solving from Princess... #laughter… https://t.co/tqgHP4pTE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President you are doing an outstanding job! The Democrats will not be happy with anything you… https://t.co/VUdr56EKH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redzdonUTD @jamesrobsonES What happens if Poch starts slow after the way Ole started?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toy viendo al amor de mi vida con el amor de su vida, y pues qué sad 🙁😕☹ guey te verías mejor conmigo, neta neta patineta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnELTenney Maybe if more people wore them in RO tonight it wouldn't be so nutty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredZaifman @Ont_AGCO @TweedInc Hi Jared, Would love to chat with you about this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @fightbobby Since the Shield kicked your ass last night at Fastlane, are you going to have @itsLioRush fight… https://t.co/ohrG9SqytX]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this humorous there's something wrong with you. lol ;) big curvy plus size women are beautiful! C… https://t.co/kn1wcj8an2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel If it’s a crime he should do the time. He was able to plan it out like premeditated murder!  He’s no d… https://t.co/4TWPKdWpGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the kind of girl who's gonna make you wonder who you are and who you've been]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not rocket science...the best workers are also your hardest workers in their jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SEASON of MIST Webshop Newsletter March 4th: SAINT VITUS, VLTIMAS, NUMENOREAN, t-shirts, CDs, &amp; more!! https://t.co/CzCltt6dLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big facts thought people who don’t like you will talk down on anything you do because it’s YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_maarriinnaa_ he’s like “ bitch i dare you to move or touch me. do it.  pussy. “]]></document><document><![CDATA[After missing #World #Salsa #Summit #2018, it was truly surprising and amazing to win 1st Place🥇 for ProAm Just sal… https://t.co/obcjOLNwNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guaido no debe entrar en Ve ezuela. Debe trabajar en el exilio. Lo necesitamos vivo. El mundo va a ir adece deemk]]></document><document><![CDATA[State bound baby!!💜 @ Columbus East High School https://t.co/Hc4Zi5qoUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just one of my 4 total cat whys... . These kitties are my babies and I work my booty off to care for them. I'm comm… https://t.co/S2h6WgfHNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmedLutheran @VicCervantes3 @VedanticFlaneur @Vito53904302 @gneely17 @SaltLife_614 @mikethomas585 @arc76676… https://t.co/1Mwk7ZNE9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s another Manicure Monday. I recieved these beautiful colors in my BoxyLuxe Rose.  The brushes are perfect and t… https://t.co/JPOCKi5PV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please, no more school reach calls at 5am telling me no school —I don’t work there anymore. #losemynumber. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo I just laugh, walk away, and drive him insane with bad jokes😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akhcky11 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @JBenShade You call them evil. Trump does same and you call him Mr. Presid… https://t.co/0sKfdKaAtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[maybe if I do 100 jumping jacks then something will finally happened to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i say I'm hungry n u respond to my snap i expect you to ask me what u want lol.. Tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Innovative combinations of flavors and textures @hazelrestaurant is an impressive additions to DC’s restaurant scen… https://t.co/CovESBEeaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubycramer @BernieSanders I realize the truth hurts. We can only heal if we all face the truth. Those corrupt supe… https://t.co/4Y8601XINI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah, and Mexico is paying for it right? And you’re getting ALL the money you wanted, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine having a girl who pays for your car and then having the disrespect to cheat on her. The audacity of these m… https://t.co/uhapvNMwo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So..I got up this morning, prepped for court,I heard a light whisper, "your fears are like Dragons guarding your mo… https://t.co/K3jLeXLiFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want some chai and a blanket and maybe a Harry Potter marathon...or game of thrones. That'd be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinchVintage Yea! I got it! Andddd, I love it! TY Sis! Sometimes it’s like being on a merry-go-round! 💕🌷💕 https://t.co/2p0bPVu3Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brofessor_Bread "Jo it's your birthday, you are a woman and you are in Canada" - Zack and Frank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraGaskill @tempusviators @tweetmommybop Hahaha I have that-a muscle relaxant!! 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I have a list of all of the  required documents a minor needs to have with them for a flight from Miami to Braz… https://t.co/zF62E7rLA6]]></document></documents></author>