<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio sir - I just watched you on Meet the Press. I am not in the 1%.  As an small business entrepreneur, “… https://t.co/xiRVF0rNzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to be 45 minutes late for work because I went to school instead thinking it was Tuesday    how’s your day going]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you supporting sustainable practices in your school community? #SuperConference2019 #Love4EcoSchools… https://t.co/MSacDDNq3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0egUmoe97I Carlos slims helu OBAMA Hillary Clinton phone deal gets Washington DC in prison this week f… https://t.co/0MUFCFjGGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad. 😢 Was a huge 90210 fan in the 90’s.  #RIP Luke Perry #DylanMcKay #BeverlyHills90210]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidakascooby @benthodg @nytimes @realDonaldTrump @GOP LOL 90% of the media is leftist... that's why you fake lib… https://t.co/xAd5MAvNsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lazy group think by the National @nba media is getting tired. Perhaps the @bucks are really really really good.… https://t.co/lTILXMNzpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norberto @BarrazaAlmazan recomienda tener los depósitos de la basura temprano en las banquetas, a eso de las 5-5:30… https://t.co/f2xkr0gN2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kickin Sass..... YAAAASSSS!!!!  I’m looking forward to representing @winstonsbest at @SipandSwineBBQ next weekend.… https://t.co/kf7Mv1GaS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish i could post my whole video, this was one of the most beautiful moments i have ever lived. i felt like i was… https://t.co/8LDOyXlwYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView I praise Tlaib for standing up to him because Meadows is a racist, just not racist against his family!! Th… https://t.co/XHvv3vNVrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just pre-ordered my copy! Once it arrives there'll be just enough time to read it before giving it to my dad for… https://t.co/Y4787Z1SYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCLA professors conduct #research on effects of #Woolseyfire on local #ecosystems. Because fire was preceded by ye… https://t.co/2ZJmCHu2er]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VibesBaseball hey 👋🏼 when are you going to start selling jerseys? I already got a hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Proud of my son Drew (@drew_jw18) who was honored by the Carlisle Area Rotary Club as the Outstanding Student of… https://t.co/9SuVrDJ79o]]></document><document><![CDATA[They think a coup is a two door sedan but a Trumper will probably own a pick up truck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[craving another #mushroomswissburger from @Whataburger 😍😍 ugh they have my heart #deadassmyguy lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This White Person has a Black Friend. You Won't Believe What Happened Next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is a hacker?  A hacker Is a creative person and creative programmer, cryptographic, who have knowledge about ne… https://t.co/DcWej7aXTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new term in leaving out any actor of the #Oscars In Memoriam should now be LOCKE’D out instead of Farina’d. Act… https://t.co/Y9CGJAouF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValLeblanc @ChocoPoire Ça fait du bien de se jaser à sois même parfois]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got Lori Harvey on my wishlist that’s the only thing I want for Christmas 🎶🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay. I’m down to make it a month 😎 next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I wake up in the morning and find Conservative trolls followed me during the night. https://t.co/5nEWuFSIFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wright-Rawls drives for a bucket and Central is down 43-41 with 18 seconds left. New Oxford ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holder is a disgraced AG  - he would be easy to be convicted - he should be treated as a criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beginnings or The Egg, 2019, acrylic/paper, #markperryart @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/ZQn7UoiSBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, Ho, @PimlicoRC! BWI (which is physically closer to @LaurelPark) clearly supporting @MayorPugh50 in Park Heights… https://t.co/JAujO0DmuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timbotron65 @wthrockmorton Because their purpose is to rewrite the Civil War's history on false terms: that of the… https://t.co/7fTv4iPx8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost You can't identify with this because you reject Christians proving your extreme bigotry so let me e… https://t.co/mvgO0KRDkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to some jams with @charlieengen  #Repost @ideologyband ・・・ Buy or stream our new album on any digital platform… https://t.co/Uw6KZEvYQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that in the year I turned 50, the Muppets are 40, Haunted Mansion is 50, Marvel is 80 and Mickey is 90!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is covering the Luxor and why? And what is Hyper eSports Arena? @ Luxor Hotel and Casino https://t.co/VDurFt64mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrpbandjelly @560Friedo @nickcrimarco @DonnoAndFriedo @AlexDonno Where is your truck usually located? I think I’ve… https://t.co/uwhEljcJvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invest in our Football Family by making a gift today!  #RedRaiderPride https://t.co/6jjK4zzWSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regging this new single w/ @bmi then it’s going up for digi distro. Coming soooon! 😛🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡ Bravo, bravo Santo Padre Paquito !  Todo feminismo acaba siendo un machismo con faldas.  Estoy relamiéndome de gu… https://t.co/MlNARZfBe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esos eran tuitazos en 2009 2010 de la época bonita de Twitter nadie de ofendía y reíamos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowlero Mar Vista 12125 Venice Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90066  https://t.co/dA8lfZMyIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertyBlitz @FiveThirtyEight If he or Bloomberg were the Dem candidate, no way.  Just my opinion of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFGiants @BusterPosey @BruceBochy Well then Bruce, let's kick some ass this year then okay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend gave me both of these wall scrolls several years ago, and I've always been curious as to what they say. My… https://t.co/PJVji69oJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way how the camera man was holding that camera. He's a legend in the making #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome week at #exponential with the greatoakschurch team! It’s awesome to think of all God is doing in our nation… https://t.co/SaUscrvm7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottfundirant If you’re going to make your decision off the weekly, you should let the week play out 1st. Looks good so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SqlBenjamin @GarthMJ Wait a dang darn gosh minute!!! Garth is Canadian??????  Now that explains a lot!  ;) (Kidding!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @cenkuygur @YouTube You are nothing more than a water boy for the corporate elite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📷 with @OhioStateNewark Dean @MacDonaldBill and @COTCedupres John M. Berry. https://t.co/mDsGXIKws2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onewiththewater CVP Historical Water Allocation as of late Feb announcement: 2018 - 20% 17 - 0% 16 - 0% 15 - 0% 14… https://t.co/FIl2khBGww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romequaggans @BrianShearon2 @Dalaswag1 @SheaSerrano So HR doesn’t have to be forecasted? HR strategy is an enormou… https://t.co/iy6jGG8DsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of Kylie and her teammates!  These girls have grit and A work hard attitude!!  Fun to watch them!!   This is… https://t.co/IsR9PAAMoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weather for Geneseo, IL, brought to you by Weather Underground: https://t.co/KmLv52tpKb https://t.co/BEfi8nn7tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s hot, who’s not? Tell me who rock, who sell out in the stores? You tell me who flopped, who copped the blue dr… https://t.co/QGnSuqAe1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSchweitzer Unless you are talking about another jesus I call bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC SO FPR YOU JEWISH NEWS MEDIA MOGULS LAVISHING IN ALL THAT PHARMACEUTICAL ADVERTISNG MONEY WHO GAVE BUSH AND… https://t.co/cb2pFtmg7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit He's lucky he didn't do that to me I would have shot him for his trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacecoast_stve Heck yeah! After I had a trigger fail during Falcon Heavy I made my own for all launches from ther… https://t.co/ndFmAzuh4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cute_Idiot That’s so cool! I wish I had a third sibling that could have picked the grass type haha. It’s gotta be… https://t.co/8BjROkMBE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eroticCJ They shouldn’t, I’ll say that much. Hoping for the best! I need to check with @NelsonRockingh1 for a sit-… https://t.co/D7JzluAcT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/QA2jw1NZGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 4766 N Idlewild Ave #WhitefishBay #WI  #realestate https://t.co/oldtvcGcnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hallmark wants “sweet” novels by unagented writers 65,000+ words for possible publication. How many will reply? #WritingCommunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Billionaires are smart with their money. They don't spend it on trivial things like you and me.  Billionaire char… https://t.co/2YGxCpp4x3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at Hoodoo Comedy Club for this sold out show with Gordon Myers Aniria Turney and Johnny C @ The Ho… https://t.co/2RQrOjVi1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LionelMedia @KennethSPower I'm in the 3rd group. The one that doesn't give a damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t do it with renowned faculty like you @ScottShikoraMD Thanks Scott!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBeatWithAri @AriMelber She sucks. She’s a monster of her own making. She has long since abdicated her responsib… https://t.co/RkyA69lnlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkAgee Weird Human.  At this point, makes more sense that he was told to post it as opposed to today's explanation theater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted to sorry to everyone who been trying to shoot with me getting my talent test done today been busy trying to get new car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hell yeah! #bjj #jiujitsu #teamrhinobjj @ Meridian, Idaho https://t.co/cNADgdtQPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @JReyes_NP for inviting me to the Hall of Fame Academy Regional Showcase! https://t.co/KsaWWuDhO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bawadaba @xMOxJOx @DaveRamsey You're right, people who dont care about loved ones (or dont have any) dont need life insurance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You wanna talk about awkward moments? Once, during sex, I called Lois 'Frank.' Your move, Sherlock.” — Peter Griff… https://t.co/BiysT0ES0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[well he should have known that begging wasn’t gonna get the job done. https://t.co/rBzLr1vtm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when black ppl say “oooooh” in-unison after some crazy shit pop off. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA A MERI CAN PEOPLES. YOU SHOULD COFIRM. WHICH JUDICIARY JUDGMENT JUDGE IS LEGAL AN… https://t.co/TmugBbe1qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Trump not only isn’t worried over impeachment..feeling he’s immunized by the increasingly corrupt #GOP controlled… https://t.co/5KtCDMDeRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[PMO cannot allow an investigation into the #SNCLavalin corruption.  It would spill over into at least 5 other areas… https://t.co/TPfzicK9qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchellSpeedy @john_seebold @Trav_Graf He would pull from the hog's snout!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andersonDrLJA They have  been waffling before the machine was invented]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else think Kerr got ejected because he was bored? Or to win a bet with a player?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next team spotlight will be raided from the Portland Metro area, stay tuned for the interview and article announcement!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beINSPORTS @SergioRamos estos madridistas comentaristas de Bein sport en Espanol no se dieron cuenta del golpe con… https://t.co/HINyJ1advg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bucco_Blast 2 years several months a POTUS win.. and still crying about the person he beat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to literally stick my fingers in my ears at work to avoid season-5 #GameOfThrones spoilers. This is proving mor… https://t.co/P8rGt8Hdc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nelsonwendella @realDonaldTrump Yeah!, because he couldnt find an American woman that would put up with his crap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricJRacy @RockCrusher2 @timothywjohnson @shannonrwatts So you dont want to ban the AR. Good. Jt shouldnt be]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening Saturday.. Cant wait.  #arizona #phoenix #laveen #mesaaz #glendaleaz #scottsdale #peoriaaz #church… https://t.co/L7tqyc26eZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#admitmoviesyouveneverseen  The fyre documentaries. Or from my understanding, white people scamming other white peo… https://t.co/e7u0nTPpIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sternshow I would recommend NO ONE bother to download your garbage app. @SiriusXMNFL @SiriusXMNBA @BustedOpenRadio… https://t.co/iT4UY2Vhhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimBurrows1266 @Starbucks @iSocialFanz @Schmittastic Outstanding https://t.co/ljCGFtuTv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's tea:    )         )        )    )     (         )          ) _(___(____)____(___(__ \… https://t.co/aRXfQ7Zl4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak @ScottAdamsSays @ChrisCuomo @realDonaldTrump Bro we are still looking for Obama’s birth certificate.  Take it easy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avernalaw Nah, just saying that coding is a direct replacement for traditional schooling for everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA @FeliciaBoltonTV The first of many proposals she will turn down!! This was spooo cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @MacNicol1957 Do you know any lawyers sir. Can 63 million people sue @JussieSmollett and his cohorts in th… https://t.co/AGGdejiGcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperiorDynasty @NateIsElite @PrimeGilmore @tombrady_NFL CLEMENT TD WAS GOOD, POSSESSION OF BALL 2 FEET IN BOUNDS,… https://t.co/2ViUQ5ZwyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham: From one of Trump's harshest critics to Paid Trump Sycophant.... https://t.co/E1yrIA95Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ask_Spectrum Why do we not have Sport time Ohio in Dayton. Trying to watch Crew game but no damn channel. Directv… https://t.co/YU6Vlq5ARC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noicenick He doesn’t know the right time interval, tell him to carry the 2 over to simplify the equation lol]]></document></documents></author>