<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If one remains a billionaire for life, then some people in that person’s wide circle have been financially abused b… https://t.co/eWy5JwOHgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmiketrus @ChrisCuomo If you aren’t smart enough to understand what he’s done then you can not be taught]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm so I started watching #DatingAround and I totally thought THAT GUY from THAT MOMENT would have been trash the… https://t.co/Oe3VCuZ1C9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always use my card at Sonic and I wish I could put a tip on card. I dig out all my change if I don’t have a dolla… https://t.co/KYh7E7q1pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro anyone else obsessed w the Chris watts murders like I am???? I can’t stop researching themmmm ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats, I remember when a few coaches said he ain’t all that! #Proof #LoveIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[...building with good  reason in plain sight!!  Wonder what THEY had that we don't  know about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[comparing how underdressed we are for the weather with my friends is my February past time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mark. My unofficial twin brother.  The one always standing beside me through every bad hair cut, har… https://t.co/kG47Mx2eij]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lovemysonthedad #babyboyjoy #missgrandswhenimnotwiththem #grandparentlove @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/4pyN8oEzu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really we are phunny thing is it's been a very good stand by https://t.co/33VKlt1Agd and @DHSgov against you clowns… https://t.co/6NtkCpfhq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEB this is the dog food you are providing. It's all juice. Not acceptable https://t.co/MkWaHxs7YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@js_tut It has! It’s taken so long. I hope they actually like me and my work]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach David!!! “This burden of always trying to do the right thing will bring me to an early grave.” #BoomerangonBET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairekittridge He is the worse!!! My dog has more personality. #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackallisonLOL BITTER being the operative word.  And Bernie supporters must be the UN-BITTER.  It's gonna kill som… https://t.co/2YHX7nYXpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever get “follow suggestions” from your contacts and end up on a stalker trail because you have no idea who this pe… https://t.co/hKrDVrfS64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews BREAKING NEWS for Spanky McDotard: No matter WHAT happens with the Mueller report, rest a… https://t.co/McJcrBz7SX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me channeling my inner @RawBeautyKristi ....    "💕OMG...she is such a precious angel 😇💕"  (said in my best Kristi k… https://t.co/eYL9ea0WPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope I never see her again lol and that’s why I don’t bother associating with his side pieces]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @estebantam  to post pictures of my 7 favorite books....no reviews needed.  Each day I wi… https://t.co/VrmzES81Hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Elana_Brooklyn - this is such a critical fight to hold corporations accountable at last!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter Liar. No wall is being built. You're a criminal and cretin and a POS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg1217 Agreed. Dildo=safety, objects=damaging and scary. Always chose safety when it’s an option. Pay money. So worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TasteOfCountry @TasteOfCountry: @dustinlynch, @carrieunderwood, @brothersosborne, @martinamcbride, @CarterWinter,… https://t.co/ujXPvXVRzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcoming March with a beautiful new collection of all things happy in warm and wearable colors 👏 #comesinlikealion… https://t.co/WVP78pxp8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently she graduated with the liberal “Everyone Gets A Trophy” degree because her actions speak volumes about w… https://t.co/aWYC9bQtbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm currently awaiting this bottle of pure goodness! I've been out of my cleanser for about 2 weeks now and it's st… https://t.co/zFSlBqK7G3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, international development portfolio has always been a junior one. Changing Minister 8 months before… https://t.co/bdqTIJxrAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've had several years of strong markets pushing prices higher ... how much has your home appreciated?  https://t.co/7ECj49IavR]]></document><document><![CDATA[does every girl have a ton of crying pics? maybe even a whole album titled “me crying”? answers are pointing to yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funky sunrise from Tuesday morning 🙃 #sunrise #nofilter #rhodeisland #tuesday #ri #lilrhody #iphonephotography @ No… https://t.co/tyiUWnxVpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets That is true‼️ Trump really killed the Republican Party last night‼️ Trump actually just helped us… https://t.co/yIMObhfnJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a talented young woman! Britt Stewart danced in all three High School Musical movies. She also danced in La La… https://t.co/belAfUVrn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi escuela es la mejor en muchas cosas, menos en no querer que entremos tarde mañana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si ariana grande y justin bieber had a baby this is what it would look like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is half a year old today. It's breaking my heart. Stop growing so fast. https://t.co/f80fAjucPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[You put a bunch of 23 year olds together and are shocked when they’re not ALL ready for marriage???????????????? #Thebachelor @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessmarais__ Gives her the same unsolicited advice about being healthy that is given to larger women]]></document><document><![CDATA[O confeiteiro mais badalado dos últimos anos embarcou na maior loucura de todas: abrir uma loja! O @BachourAntonio… https://t.co/bkLXm205xi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my relationship with my boyfriend we can just laugh and laugh and it’s the best fucking feeling ever ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The use of my van. #whatacookiecando @ Santander Arena https://t.co/mikIeh93Yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView Does anyone almost feel sorry( of course not!) for Putin? He chose the absolute dumbest man possible to st… https://t.co/FSKiniDep0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hol_Lis @GusT_THD @adriennekolb @nyyroro @Jeremy_Gray_HD https://t.co/55i5DJ2IjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep, she’s single - and GLUTEN FREE!!!🤣👏🏾🎉This beauty is out here spreading love, life and cheer on this fine Frida… https://t.co/d8vkHTlCXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyanroll !!! with yr leo moon more like self-critical of others as much as ur self-critical of urself bc u put a l… https://t.co/FwkOdGJpKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nandogarz Girl I attempted to watch that trash on FOUR DIFFERENT OCCASIONS and NOTHING. https://t.co/YFYyMdVS8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nocknock6 opened my eyes to this at a young age. Truly remarkable speech and literally, the only speech from Mock… https://t.co/87ffJc6hdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my old coaches texted me and was telling me how proud he was of me and it totally made me cry 😭💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yet what is due me is in the Lord’s hand, and my reward is with my God.” Isaiah 49:4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredthSalenger @pattonoswalt @perlapell @NBCAPBio @GlennHowerton @nbc As someone also raised in Virginia, I’d say… https://t.co/68fLJw98IU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margaretcho @LibertyComedy So exited to see you tonight at 7 @margaretcho truly one of my favorite comics:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early with nsanorthtexas ! Ready to Power up and learn something new of course my #ningxiared… https://t.co/Ro90Ah05pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ve gone off THREE times in the last hour ask me how close I am to ending it all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burgundy awareness necklace-Swarovski crystals-sterling silver-Believe pendant! This piece is very personal for me… https://t.co/SZH0CRl8kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaLeMusique @JussieSmollett @JAKESMOLLETT @jurneesmollett Zip it cabrona!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beaSTINGray #marketing #websitedesign #socialmediamarketing @stingraychs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh! So awesome tonight being on this great Women in Careers in Technology panel @whitworth comprised of ama… https://t.co/8ta7xmAEhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wore it better? 😂⚡️ #harrypotter #pig #whoworeitbetter https://t.co/1w2OBarqme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a few drinks with GW last night 🥂 @ Baird's Tavern https://t.co/tlXJg898d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Century21 the office across from me is killing me with a terrible scented candle.  Sneezing and a terrible headache 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__sarahrenee @Nanderrs I’m not being aggressive at all? I’m merely stating what happens in the dairy industry, and THATS aggressive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain snow mix today means @ChuckBell4 gives today's weather an 'F.' But he says we could hit 70 degrees on Sunday! https://t.co/h9ECWaIvGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why when people you kinda close too, don’t tell you happy birthday, we get mad?😂..well I unfollowed you if didn’t t… https://t.co/Q3d58B5ZIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Osteria is beautiful!  #LoveOnTheMenu. @hallmarkchannel @BarbaraNiven @MelkeBranding]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain lion rescued from tree 50 feet above home in Southern California https://t.co/YgNNymegc4 https://t.co/lExhP4ihaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trubiskytits @STLMattinals Literally half of our starting rotation was hurt 😂... But, I mean... https://t.co/Ra5zLcEfuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I’m pretty sure I have strep and still no one will take my shift. Cool. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damn.. speaking up for yourself and stating your mind feels fucking good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday on @Snapchat, I was added by a person named Telemarketer. They used my phone # to find me. I never added… https://t.co/cuJu30Bmh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roseymelhill @Samuel_Murai @nicole_staal @FixesItself https://t.co/XlaNT74jyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲Con Sue Photography and Design🌲  ♥️On-Location.... March 9-14, 2019♥️  🌲Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌲  ♥️This… https://t.co/f5BAFkqF6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanHilferty @PressHerald @DavidLarter @thisdog @KevinMillerPPH No problem with a president accepting lots of mon… https://t.co/vCSKiKqAeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Digital Summit Seattle and I’m excited to learn from my fellow marketing professionals. #DSSEA https://t.co/bLdPd5OL3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlessaStepanova @dougmeehan @antoinetteA @randypricewcvb @Met_CindyFitz Actually footage of me realizing I could s… https://t.co/0eaiMmZmm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, CO🏢👻🌬💰🗝  Think of the Stephan King or Dumb and Dumber!😂 https://t.co/DT1EPX4KMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khuey_ I’m just so confused about why SF Dems act like Feinstein is anything other than a huge bucket of 🗑. Also I… https://t.co/2vAMF7c0yW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cantrellmegan22 I literally watched this last night and cried I hate my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m coming for ya, @alasdairnichol and @NichoLowry! https://t.co/eUBiNV85nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some "days" with regard to this whole "national day" nonsense that are truly laughable. Nat'l Pancake Day… https://t.co/1e2t4MumOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @realDonaldTrump Typical!  Whenever he doesn’t have an answer, and right before he starts lying, h… https://t.co/subfYbJxLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kiki &amp; I have been hanging out a lot for almost two months now &amp; she still can’t handle me 😂 #ImExtra]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you #13 DeVito Syracuse Nation 👀🏈, #BoscoIronman, #FootballMomForLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Battling the cold in Montréal with hot chocolate is the only solution. https://t.co/XWdZptPmh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an actual angel on my hands here 🙏🏼🥰 @ Euless, Texas https://t.co/vPI648ZVt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#latergram thankful for a sunny day, and a wonderful road trip with my love s187o @ Cowboy Harley-Davidson of Austin https://t.co/pFjXpyoI8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLodgeMusic @MoodyBluesToday @Fender @PRConnect @Ampeg @GHS Absolutely love you guys!❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️💕💕🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said... Girl, I wouldn’t do it if I were you. It is impossible for me because of my #gender and my #skin.  I s… https://t.co/5uWU0lVFqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando estamos llenos del amor de Dios, podemos empezar a amarnos a nosotros mismos. Podemos empezar a retribuirle… https://t.co/ts1tf7wOkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice Democrats want to shove their ideology down our throats w/o discussion. Many ppl are interested in at least… https://t.co/MoL7397Ep7]]></document><document><![CDATA[BABY! YOU’RE A LIAR BUT I LOVE YOU!  NOW GET ME OUT OF THIS MESS I GOT ME IN TO!  And l ain’t sorry for puttin my h… https://t.co/BpDpPSFZ86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerellaWeinberg #msasecurity took a senior dog from a #veteran and #glenkucera stated in writing his intention to… https://t.co/YVWf5X952T]]></document><document><![CDATA[always my favorite weekends 💕 @ East Carolina University https://t.co/hmiwCuR8La]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_prall @stedwardsu @DeMedeirosJoe Andrew, we are so glad you are part of the leadership team!  Thank you for you… https://t.co/sLZZwTHgTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN too much water pressure the granddaughter green hair Geegee92 as more looked the noodles weenies as triggered… https://t.co/w5OJB4eDT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaInxs2 Originally Ohio &amp; now my second home beautiful coastal SC- The Lowcountry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who raise your standards.   #joinfreedomlifestyle  #balancedliving  #motivation https://t.co/FB0rcSk6pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @AOC You really missed that Feinstein reference didn’t you? Oy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cee_cee_lina Literally purple shampoo that stains anything. My shower curtain has been ruined twice. My brand new… https://t.co/VRNekXaH0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisArcher22 this pic of you came up in my FB memories today - 5 years ago in Port Charlotte. Hope to see you tom… https://t.co/74EjgbXq9n]]></document></documents></author>