<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[just  need   a  bark  form  all this  people here I'm going to Gunnison Colorado for  a  fall day  I wish 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wexxis_ Probably not bet because I don’t have money for a wedding, but I’ll change your name to wife in my phone 😂💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn't how boisterous the winds blow-JUST TRUST IN THE ONE that's has the AUTHORITY to make the winds become st… https://t.co/UUnbv6BiJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMeltonGSO I know I know I have to trust God with our country, I just hate the slave trade and what they (Dems… https://t.co/O8EHRlAkAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[First playoff win for the Sonics!  Brady will play again next week. @ The Middleburg Heights Recreation Department https://t.co/sHB3aFshEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@an_DREA5 So am I the one who finds him funny in this scenario?  I never misled him on that, the day I fake laugh t… https://t.co/EiRILOSpgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have been up most of the night. Today is gonna suck. https://t.co/4a7XFsPpEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Geese, you idiot... how does the military show respect? THEY BEND A KNEE! How do plays of every sp… https://t.co/2iwDjHZJFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @HvonSpakovsky @POTUS Do you choose the USA or Donald Trump? It cannot be both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is truly unsurprising that someone who makes their money flogging overpriced crystals and posting faux inspirati… https://t.co/RCNDj1dUAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[64 WB down to one lane at Mercury!   Gilmerton opening 7:15 AM Coleman opening 10 AM  Live on @WTKR3 https://t.co/MB8daxxyAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise, the sophisticated and classy Lady M looked stunning, and did a beautiful job on her #oscars performanc… https://t.co/0d4VHGlcTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs your getting older...#readingglasses #feelingolder @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/jXOUO0OrVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[you want some entertainment. I know you do. Lol, funny pics, humour quotes, funny jokes, jokes funny, hilarious fun… https://t.co/HKA5oZjSaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure is just like a box of chocolates ! Have a great safe week ! In the words of @officer_jill @warwickripd it was… https://t.co/fXNO3r92ox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAAVRGSJ I woke up to my mom several times force feeding me cough syrup and then walking out of my room without a word]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else ever have a sudden urge to get your shit together? Like keeping your house spotless, saving money, work… https://t.co/RKSC9N3Gqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey if everyone wants to check their blindspots when switching lanes i think that’d be super dope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarofaloWX @BrittanyBegley @PassPort_Life1 you trying to go to Japan? We need to see this view.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mads__campbell wow we love girl athletes who support each other #TheWestMovement]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need some vitamin me in your life🙅‍♀️💖 . Leggings: lurvsportswear  Top: @9two5fit  Shoes: @diemmefootwear… https://t.co/BdHB18yYzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlfreeman888 Or a roll of toilet paper. They might get the hint? 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kssullivan123 Why do u wanna spend $50 on a bsuit? Zaful bikinis are like $15 💁‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I was physically at the meeting, but it was only announced that the vote had failed 4-4, not the breakdown of… https://t.co/z00qWelmfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why are you so thinned skinned! Imitation is the highest form of flattery ...or haven't you heard… https://t.co/jqMaVvntcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Colorado. Full grown, adult ass men with full beards have no qualms with popping off to Party in the USA at… https://t.co/GFMM4aaXcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Consequences, punishments, anything!” Kennesaw State senior in this social media post speaks out, demands official… https://t.co/F3ql7qSp0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TGIFmorning @Souriswingette  #NationalMargaritaDay  https://t.co/xL7yKDcHtY Margarita Salsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you text with commas and at least semi-correct conventions, you're my type of person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do group projects ever make you want to curl into a ball and cry and then you realize your future career is group projects 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ellidilorenzo Love you for this, Elli. This shouldn’t be as rough a day as it is and I’m happy for everyone who ha… https://t.co/9ruuVXQKeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to kick off the week 💪🏻💪🏻 @ Gallaudet University https://t.co/EMYnIpehak]]></document><document><![CDATA[And democrats are not to be trusted because they did not hold up their end of the bargain that time either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the kind soul who hopped off her treadmill to fetch my music box (iphone) that flew off mine this morning: THANK… https://t.co/PEzkUbm140]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel our future is getting brighter.  I am so happy that we have female politicians.  They are an inspiration for… https://t.co/beK844XDYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, happy happy Wednesday.   Always remember you are responsible for the energy you bring.   And, you hav… https://t.co/xsltSFQzSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doritkemsley1 @BravoTV Absolutely shocked by the story of the dog. I can never look at you the same way again. The… https://t.co/LC4lSROH9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color pop #talenteddesigners #thebestindecor #casualluxuryhomefurnishings #is #homedecor #personalspaces… https://t.co/nKDej7IWBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piper's at the vet for his follow-up appointment.   They're going to draw blood... God help them! https://t.co/PFG17VTcKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂When you’re trying to shoot promos for #ABC and the #Oscars  Never a dull moment with Eddie Flores 🥰 https://t.co/3zgY4MPcIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miner_pilar @isaimarivent Pues luchad por lo que queréis.  Si otros pueden ¿por qué  no España?   Hay un lugar par… https://t.co/UplRMs6mDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[me on my way to calvin klein to see shawn mendes’ ads 😛✌🏻 https://t.co/7il1A7FNuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #valentine @moizalladina with a haircut and drag #bingo couldn’t be happier!! #livingthedream @ Downtown Manhat… https://t.co/PsziA57AcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_queenofcool I am struggling with tobacco. We can break these addictions because we know those substances are poison for us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@netbarb987 @krassenstein True.  And I am thinking maybe the SDNY will bring the Trump criminal Empire down through the RICO Statute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 Before anyone comes for me I should add I’m saying this from a place of love. It’s awkward and conflict… https://t.co/oId22hTCif]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ex literally makes a playlist for every girl he talks to then just renames it like how fucking pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because they're not duplicitous - children do not know how to dissemble, how to be one way and act another. They ar… https://t.co/l5HY3USbX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Why should he, he has already made himself look like the ass he is!😂👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re an adult you can tease your Moms 😂 what she gon do? Send you to yo room? HA! (Unless you live with her then um 🤷🏽‍♀️)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Perfect example of what is the matter with today's society. Get a freaking grip #WakeUpAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boltyboy @smackhealth My inflatable menagerie...sigh. Guess I get new animals for #HIMSS2020? Hint: 🦔🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[To anyone that suffers with anxiety/panic attacks just know that you’re not alone. We can get through this together. 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyPlaskett @Bakari_Sellers I’m coming back to the Virgin Islands because of beauty but now coming because of b… https://t.co/6ck01jX8mV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so important to allow your children the ability to get out there and to not hold them back! Also, loved readin… https://t.co/oL2mok9DmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do guys have a special class they take on how to break a lady's heart I mean come on now? Let me do something wrong… https://t.co/A2ShYuSoO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[clink clink                               𝓫𝓲𝓽𝓬𝓱 https://t.co/fCcDziYtgK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fahaley @dawnsherriff2 @GaskinsJaymee This was almost my pick for today too! Love Love!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion, being a visitor in a hospital is much worse than being a patient.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come every time I do an assignment I facetime like 3 different people for help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaishii I can’t believe someone who worked on Sailor Moon and MSGN knows I exist so umm. I’m glad you like it!  ( ᐡ.  ̫ .ᐡ )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darrian_Justine @jalendw_22 hit up @kristynlee11 she'll get ya covered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamelaspablo @JAMA_current Reporting of relative instead of both relative and absolute risk is a key point ! Well noted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my first time getting a pedicure was when I was in elementary school with my older sisters and I remember my sister… https://t.co/8kwtTcXiN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @RobinRoberts Despicable interview . Jessie got away with all this mess due to being Politically Correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Minimum wage is an entry level job, you work your way up from there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs well Fox is following suit with MSM as you absolutely stopped talking about the “NATIONAL EMERGENCY “ sb… https://t.co/zpvgzsoHTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinpanetta @Srganuch I LOVED IT!!!!!!!! It’s such a perfect slow burn story! Sweet and cute, but also really tug… https://t.co/9hgKgWbBko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFTompkins @TimForgot Tax the rich and stop corporate welfare perhaps?  It’s handled pretty well in most other progressive countries!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @MisterHudelson  to post covers of seven books I love: no explanations, no reviews.… https://t.co/mZfjJ2UbQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Olympic track cyclist Kelly Catlin died Friday at 23 https://t.co/CD38JIJvEF via @YahooSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyePatchGuy This is an extremely funny tweet and I hope we’re still dragging fat wife guy in 50 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On to na sebe @KHaring75 takhle nerekne, ale to, jakou sekci @FootballClub_cz dal dohromady (a ze dvou tretin sam n… https://t.co/mz1hUR62Au]]></document><document><![CDATA[Copyediting and proofreading is a dying art. The TQM Team includes grammarians and proud "word nerds" who are dieha… https://t.co/U4nAXc3RBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at City of Beverly Hills - @cityofbevhills in CA https://t.co/edMZcC5FW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever had high expectations of somebody &amp; they let you down baaad? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my little cousin is THE CUTEST HUMAN BEING ALIVE I CANNOT DEAL https://t.co/SLuZY5LDMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming up before our first Middle School Golf Match of the season. Let’s go Lumpkin! https://t.co/cauXVZNm7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shut_da_fvck_up @julesgiron_ just cause you dont, doesnt me others dont johan smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today @iitnajera said “drunk me loves me too much” I wish I had that much self love lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi, @Wendys, I need to post a complaint.  WHY DO YOU KEEP MAKING YOUR DIPPING SAUCES SMALLER??????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IviRoller @ThisIsROCK2019 Still waiting for my chance to meet @GavinRossdale @bushofficial ...unless, if you count… https://t.co/saR470HtmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco Main Library invites Xu Fangfang to introduce her memoir  Galloping Horses: #Artist Xu Beihong and Hi… https://t.co/orIfyrYoBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @TheDerekEngel from @GHSMustangsFB highlighted in this video! He’ll be attending the @LoneStarCamp on Mar… https://t.co/EJrY5qiEnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devin61743489 @realDonaldTrump Jesus Christ cares and loves all of us!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#heaven #Austin #Jacob #gonetosoon #crosses #signs #heavenisforreal ...This was amazing, this was right before our… https://t.co/HKrug8bQT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@veracruisin @nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni @morningmika @duty2warn Thank you so much, I am, and h… https://t.co/RzqHzpDsud]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Horror Story Freak Show Jessica Lange Gods and Monsters https://t.co/ktKd3ciZo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[No lie tho I’ve missed my fat boy SOOO mucho I use to be with his fat ass everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take me back to the weekend. This night was not long enough. 🏒💚🖤 #ridertownusa #goriders https://t.co/BEq3ez0L4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s probably safe to bet that no one named Hickenlooper will ever lead this nation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrmdHales @_Astro_Nerd_ awwwwwwwww snap!!! the only arachnids i will willingly go on record saying that i love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open season on the flyers charge a flyer player that's ok but if the player tries protect himself he is in the wron… https://t.co/oo0owEIoUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That part when u apologize for an argument attempting to be the bigger person in hopes that u might get one too....… https://t.co/h8rfIMG32g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idgaf what you say UZI IS THAT BITCH, BEEN THAT BITCH AND WILL ALWAYS BE THATTTTTTT BITCH. periodt]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's funny @MeghanMcCain, b/c when I hear the name Tulsi Gabbard I think:  Anti-War Vetran. And when I hear the n… https://t.co/UZvf0yPOuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coworker just interrupted me while I was trying to listen to Rep. Cummings’ closing statement. Someone send me the… https://t.co/V7xHEePoBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I posted a pic w my friend from 2 years ago and #oomf commented on it like he so fine then came back and was like “… https://t.co/iFFafr1Q3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusseDenise Thought you might be interested in the Dale shirts. Didn't know if you saw this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeahNtuala @WomenoftheHall @mindykaling @amyschumer @Oprah @chadwickboseman @Lupita_Nyongo My grandma Jean Martin]]></document></documents></author>