<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@theklecan_23 @LamarJacksonEra Just heard he was a diva in the lockeroom along with AB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When went to India for the first time at the age of 27 I had a dream where I met the Monkey King and he taught me h… https://t.co/wnGPYlWSwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIGGYDABOMB @theBSOLZ Didnt mirotic make his debut like last night lmao if we are really analyzing “Most Valuable… https://t.co/yurku5UbVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud to celebrate these beautiful, brave, strong, and amazing women! Three cheers for them and ALL of the incr… https://t.co/JxFmWXBOns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at CVS Health? We're hiring in #Arvada, CO! Click for details: https://t.co/ahoNXCoAxU #Pharmacist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAmberPitt Nothing says “I love you!” like the transitive property of envenomation! https://t.co/gSwXKn4bOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caution is out right before the end of Stage 2 @ISMRaceway. Looks like the 88 got into the wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[that city they call Long Beach.. @ Hilltop Park https://t.co/dbb0FXPkFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabethnews12 good morning mazel on your awards you deserve it hard work always pays off 😁 https://t.co/NYdpqU1DP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickzurich Oh yeah.  It needs a full upgrade for sure.  Just saying the fan experience was much better than Cub fans here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took home a souvenir from the expo and came across a skateboard deck of the fallen angel Harambe… https://t.co/ldImly1NnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick put together of vids from our Trailway cam(really driveway) 😉 @ Stamford, Connecticut https://t.co/ILl0vS55sX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sahuaro's Alyssa Brown had a game-high 35 points in an epic battle against Pueblo and Summer Fox (33 points). Most… https://t.co/O7POmvymeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably one of the most pure and beautiful interactions I’ve ever seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should know this, but does someone make a good full frame pancake lens for Sony E?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiTownFan4 @RealSkipBayless I agree..but Kyler will find it very difficult to play QB in the NFL. I think the Rav… https://t.co/gRWbIh6Jzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is late, but 2018 🤝... 2019 🤙🏽🙏🏽 Big moves coming📸  #Cali2K19 #photography #travel #vacation #life #moment… https://t.co/GEDHxvFtU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@619_8549 @PinkNews And until CRISPR comes along and changes it, sex is an immutable characteristic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nckirkpatrick How do you like it? Curious how good the court side broadcasts really are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMurph207 The floorboards were worn. It smelled faintly of dark roast and ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If that’s Sonic, I don’t think he looks all too bad. That pic of his legs though were cringe lmao. Looks a little m… https://t.co/ArqKvyiR2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night seems surreal fucking #P1s are insane.....i asked my lady what she thought and she said, "damn feels lik… https://t.co/Q74oeLXPLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@am19211 @ProfEmilyOster @ChicagoBooth The good news is you earned a Wikipedia page.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know if I ever mentioned (on social media) that I was writing again, but I started two weeks ago today. Wri… https://t.co/Gk0cnlaBqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking for a trump signature on the Bible shows how functionally illiterate and stupid you are. They are probably t… https://t.co/7zqeoL52Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me or you don't really realize who's  in a relationship until Valentines Day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see my friend Viking Mike in Vegas yesterday! Guy has amazing energy and the stars aligned for him to show… https://t.co/W8G4CgzjAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[To people who have an uninformed opinion about this subject, there is a bill that has been introduced EVERY YEAR, s… https://t.co/Fikvb77a8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kiffamorr @VadnaisArmand @RichardGurin1 @lincolnqc Y’a pas de honte tu sais. Y’a des programmes d’alphabétisation pour les adultes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReedthePhoenix @JFowlerESPN That’s ridiculous! Ben always takes the blame!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaNocturama Te entiendo muy bien; pero recuerdo igual que lo que hicieron los italianos con aquel Duce fue también muy político]]></document><document><![CDATA[Splitting the R train in downtown Brooklyn seems like a bad idea. Aren’t most people at that point through passenge… https://t.co/btti3tAbdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[3️⃣ days until the North American Tour kicks off in Miami, Florida. https://t.co/fa8OpeK36I https://t.co/FfirngYWtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d love to see former sports stars start purchasing franchises. The modern township rebellion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STL teachers upset over low pay, are taking it to court. @rhyan_henson is live this morning #TISL @ksdknews https://t.co/ehgFjaM6ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red, Violets are blue. The old logo was better SHAME on you! UofSClove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokerCookieM Multi demensions is where Quantum Mechanics picks up and Stephen ends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaVelleNeal does Romero start the year in Twins bullpen or AAA to get used to relieving?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a productive meeting with Tsering Tsomo and Dolores Montavez-Ruz from the @YWCAToronto about ways we can addres… https://t.co/w8zCVYdmjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OverThe_Hodge But facts KD over did it lmao bro too nice for this man😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafhotshots @SBNation @TheAAF @aafAPOLLOS @aafiron @aafstallions @aafcommanders @aafexpress @AafLegends @AAFFleet… https://t.co/BkivrfAG6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith The Knicks young core is a lot better than the Lakers young core!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is beauty in the struggle, then I must be a absolute marvel. #Outdoor 🔜 @ UNC Pembroke https://t.co/e2jyELiWrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats HHC member @CE_Wrestling @Col_East_Sports for an impressive 5th place as a team out 109 schools at the IHS… https://t.co/vDjD6ZQjK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtLOL @RandomNewsFeedT “Single instance” LOLOL. Like it wasn’t the prevalence of hate crime hoaxes that made people suspicious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajp01961 @TomiLahren Lol yes I’m sorry but I only have one brain. I don’t know everything but I try not to confuse… https://t.co/hXl1p6zyA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNewsTHINK I’m sorry he can’t and won’t.  There is no way this country is ready for a Jewish President. G… https://t.co/iojvxrNROj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu @awelab1956 The English is still a little off.  And I'm leaning on @BotSentinel as much as I can.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett next time you need to get attacked you should call #tonyaharding. She will get the job done right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC people like @MarketUrbanism @PeteHarrisonNYC probably are within 2 degrees of separation of this data on concen… https://t.co/5ZrgouWDVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone free to hear from my friend tonight? Most do not want the mega bucks but just a few hundred is what gets peo… https://t.co/1PlaLs13EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkankHu84875708 @WeDontHateNick 📖 all I could find was this.... https://t.co/vY12poUONg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BungieHelp hey whats up with this? Havnt been on for a couple weeks and emblem seems to have been taken away? https://t.co/Ijh2In4FGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Georgia Military College football highlights Glascock County High School https://t.co/q0Mw4lc9Qf via @MaxPreps @Malcolmclayto14]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone y’all know buys a Tesla there’s a chance I helped making it 🤯🤷🏽‍♂️💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo: creo que me tiro pal concierto de Bad Bunny en New York.  @AppDemography: a mi no me gusta ir a conciertos, sol… https://t.co/3Wy1IVir3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredRizzi @atrupar The Senator has it wrong. Trump loves Donald Trump, full stop! It’s not about his family!!!! P… https://t.co/wiCztB6Fd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAwmn99 @MaggieS17641641 @TulipsinJune Yes I do,  because I think all women are beautiful,  in their own unique ways  ! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleKingOnAir @DorothyDalton23 Apparently I come off that way, too. The key is to not care. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steve_Yo @_gebby @davidmhoover @titleist3ru @SnitzCreekBeer @mattymcconaghy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneilv @VMwareEMPOWER I will DM you when I get back to my PC. However I think they are US only codes but worth a shot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @YouTube @rkelly @xrey1 @OhioBot5000 @GeorgeWBush__ @AE911Truth @JebBush @9_11_IsAnInside I predict TWO m… https://t.co/1YpmhZllJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamStites_ Bengals about to mess around and sign Ogbuehi for 3 years $18 million]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brown Dwarf by @Fusion_Brewing @ Fusion Brewing — https://t.co/o7uzCHXRcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deuce_bigalow68 @clydesconnect @FaithCampbellJ1 @PrinPeta @katheri64795347 @cbeaux @Greg_MarineLab @bate_char… https://t.co/ze4ZNAHzls]]></document><document><![CDATA[El día de hoy acompañe a nuestro Señor Gobernador @Javier_Corral en su mensaje con motivo de su 2do Informe de Gobi… https://t.co/FupwdmoXib]]></document><document><![CDATA[#grateful #walkwithfriend #friendship #losgatos #rainyday #nofilter #noumbrella #california @ Los Gatos, California https://t.co/kjBj3YfXRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier The same reason why students wearing "black lives matter" get harassed and insulted by MAGA racists… https://t.co/HtSo78a6sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impeachment_T0 @DonaldJTrumpJr Yeah good luck with that. Trump wins landslide in 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Chris1Banjo I’ve seen the work and focus you put into this game. Well deserved bruh!!! #certifiedsavage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_FourVERTICALS_ @westcoastrich1 We got two decommits this week. Betting Miles goes off tonight. https://t.co/MZtDfFwHCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[They may not be on crack, Sir, but they are most definitely on the Left. Only there do you find the belief that if… https://t.co/UnepIyXlQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of my guy @JoetheVideoGuy , @gibby_wcu and I now can say we have a VC of the year in our “coaching tree” haha… https://t.co/zx2URjWD4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah OK, now do something else, just not your bullshit ass scandalous crap you usually do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People still mad about boogie on Golden State? Look at his numbers when he’s on the floor... if I had to bet he won… https://t.co/ONER1Aq1iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCAPP4U CEO Pete Nielsen lucks out with his seat on a flight to Sacramento- and gets to talk substance abuse treat… https://t.co/KMgKlLuxHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartmindy Still playing the victim. I would say man up but well you know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJ TIMOTHY @DJ_TIMOTHY_CPR live on air now at @grooves_radio https://t.co/UviEFS39QX later DJ @DJMANGO6 followed by… https://t.co/s3CW787Grb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS She still needs to be investigate for u… https://t.co/Y1Hz3iiP3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTuckFrumper @funder This guy  thinks the gun violence in FL is being caused by the unfinished Border wall🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it's time to go to bed if @JoeBudden is up lmao... my dawg be up mad early]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suprslimey @irock_headbands Are you saying he ‘can’t’ play defense or doesn’t?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m gonna go out on a limb and say Pitt wins a game in the ACC tournament next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently it was from McDonald's. I remember throwing fits when I couldn't use this plate. Now I don't even know w… https://t.co/CEbjp6KyOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swamiill @DexHinton @big_business_ Are you saying Future is committing tax evasion, sir?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MapleLeafs Hey Cliff Fletcher talk your son into trading Simmons to Toronto or you will disown him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5EiywTifBR if anyone is looking for an electric forest ticket check this out 👌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAdamSass It was the first episode!?! There shouldn't be anything to complain about yet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalloveyourpetday @downtownmb26! You make life interesting.  #frenchiesofinstagram #frenchie… https://t.co/jC61noJ6xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh? 🤔.  Granted $100 million isn’t a whole lot in today’s spending but this is interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acoyne I really don't understand why its so hard for the media that scrum him to ask that question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesse_crow Oh crap, okay... maybe I’ll keep it.. but I’m still very upset over this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what they say. You will never be appreciated until you're dead and gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMarkway @JenJenday5 @11TDay Sorry Coach D! I was hoping AB was heading to some great place like Arizona!😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[High School Musical, ELF, any of the Lord of the Rings, Mamma Mia #AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inger39 @marcorubio no sera fácil generar toda la electricidad que necesitamos si las cosas están tan mal como dic… https://t.co/RtlFhYLjMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many raced to the store yesterday to grab the 2 things that are some of the fastest expiring things you can get… https://t.co/4GddWWac3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the Bryce news comes in when I’m in a freaking meeting.    I can’t believe it’s really happening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABC this morning news These so called political experts are really ignorant talking about ACR NY Congress woman run… https://t.co/bjKToMNsn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delta 8 hrs on DL126 flight from Madrid on a 767 with 4 out of the 6 bathrooms out of service. Attendant in first… https://t.co/KoFWmYmJa8]]></document></documents></author>