<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dog_rates @GBeckTV 🐇 Awww ☺️ Benny is so adorably handsome, 💙 beautifully colored!!!  If I didn’t know any better… https://t.co/sKWgULd34Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beerguypdx @cellmavin @EspaceChimay @JohanBBT @badhopper @wolv54b1 @JonMontag @lhtetrick @Just4BeerLovers… https://t.co/euiAoRRnJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing list has been formed! So proud of the committee and thankful for all their hard work! Can’t wait to reve… https://t.co/w5MJ2IOsf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk what to listen to right now while I’m working, please swing your suggestions my way!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evasivelogic @walterowensgrpa @realDonaldTrump You are kidding, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[what’s the point of doing favors for people if they don’t return it when needed or asked ... like i love helping pe… https://t.co/LiCTraQR0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JourdanLoren Thank you for the offer. I found a great deal through @SouthwestAir with a financing option available to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raybbay101 @confidential16 @ORSchools You’re welcome! You did amazing last night! Proud of all of you! 🖤🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[vai doer tanto deixa a mia, makenna e a catalina!! Conexao de amizade que nunca viii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RenoCoSheriff Use your brain not your foot on gas pedal!  Buckle up and slow down! May our Deputies and our other… https://t.co/XlAHJA2rgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needs to supervise me more closely....I am like 5 seconds away from adopting a dog at least 20 times a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog keeps jumping in the bathtub with every storm tonight. I have gotten her out twice. At least she knows where… https://t.co/Vis4WsOA3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firefighters prepare to lay fallen Oxford Fire Chief Gary Sacco to rest.  @WGME    https://t.co/4seiGhJacm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky to work alongside some inspiring lady bosses. Everyday is International Women’s Day in D262🙌🏼 https://t.co/W41Bnsqiij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrstine16stone @CT3GUITAR I will literally jump through the roof if they ever come back to @wilkesbarrePA , Chris… https://t.co/HqrteCbZKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Take the first step in faith. You don’t have to see the whole staircase, just take the first step.”   Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sensible? You just said that “if he hadn’t been friends with Trump.....”! So why is any punishment sensible?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler__pierce Did you see Mid90s? I feel like that movie did not get enough attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day 2019.  My hubby and I celebrate another valentines- 35 years and still going!! “Love is not a… https://t.co/nT7ZXq4gae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why a Primary Challenge to Trump Would Be a Good Thing https://t.co/Y1tUBRkIhp interesting perspective from one of my favorite Virginians]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article in @MansionGlobal Thank you to our amazing PR team @DouglasElliman 📲 for a private showing.… https://t.co/JEUh1dzu0U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter in Canada 🇨🇦 #thisishowweroll @wrdsb #canadiankids #sunshinecold #dressedallwarm https://t.co/xVggduA07e]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell y’all my grandma is my hype man , she is forever telling me I am cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t say I like @Hen1111109 playing against @Cirilloconnor this summer but looking forward to seeing them on the s… https://t.co/SgXYfWxVqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣TALLAHASSEE COME SHAKE WITH ME NEXT WEEK!!!! BEST SHAKER GETS A PRIZE https://t.co/KvDAG2SZu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also can we just give a huge 👍🏼’s up and high🖐🏼 to the @OkemosBoysHoops student section! You guys are the 💣.com https://t.co/NyNz90vCNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally do not know how people live their lives without their car windows being tinted??? https://t.co/Y9OhvjanJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Astro_Zach I feel ya, we are spoiled here. But at least you got to see the midnight sun rise and crackle to life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m choosing my future! #setgoals #becomemore #thefutureisbright #dontliveinthepast #createyourfuture… https://t.co/psFq1Luvnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the night ends I want to make it clear of how much love I have for you. This year that we spent together has… https://t.co/ZxLHMbYPeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregorytangelo 4) Having a Second Lady working for a school that discriminates gays is not good either, it looks e… https://t.co/BD5UVoCpdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @realDonaldTrump your daughter #IvankaTrump has created millions of jobs just like there were millions of ille… https://t.co/QhEh12F1n4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swapithealthy and @wearerebol have teamed up to serve the wonderful families at Neighborhood Alliance in Elyria, O… https://t.co/bDHRR9MwYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 For everyone saying Sergio stole it, well, it is an old joke, so don't sweat it. An interesting tidbit.… https://t.co/Vtj0kIwbfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c6Lifeform @TrumpOrBust2020 @TheDemocrats @DNC Well trheir answer is well we will just print more money....omg are… https://t.co/uLwe3GRJD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WentRogue Still sore after losing the Chou (丑) Comedy Role  to Junior, I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doom1776 @intheMatrixxx @POTUS I haven’t noticed them doing that but merely stating the numbers on the charts. Eac… https://t.co/zj2zhtxGbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I introduced one of The Netherlands top talents to @MarioAndretti yesterday @rinusveekay lived up to it and won… https://t.co/hEaW5wmbg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is absurd. #humor #lol #grin #amusing https://t.co/UcWQVfxua4]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case there was any doubt....Willow the wonderdoodle still detests her human’s early morning alarm and workouts.… https://t.co/eMFaYx8Ek2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews A  it-real-journalist interviewing a not-real-president. A can miss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leonardo_Padron ⚠️⚠️⚠️      COMO DESTILAR       AGUA SALADA https://t.co/3WLI42fWia]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know how dumb people are until you work in customer service. ESPECIALLY as a manager/supervisor. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PETA Oscats: Check Out 2018's Most Animal-Friendly Films and Stars https://t.co/b9qnJQfN9M via @peta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain So that lets you off the hook when it comes to telling the truth?  I suppose it does hold with the conservative brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadwithLoveRRV @Nayalla334nd @pkamla1 @mindfulheal @annemariayritys @gary_hensel @LewisHowes @DianneD03113533… https://t.co/ocBvKwS8Ed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@galaxiou @parscale I don’t like paying one penny to support baby murdering, or illegals, both of which you seem pe… https://t.co/trKejgsPjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham Thank you Reverend Graham for your intelligence and quoting of Scripture. We certainly need it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want to wake up any of my friends to take me to the hospital so I just asked someone off tinder]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁣⁣ Grateful to all of the humans who have chosen to authentically support the career of the EXTRAORDINARY TALENT th… https://t.co/332TUmeqMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: can't find a cute guy on instagram or anywhere on social media my friends: https://t.co/oBnYeK2eBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does it seem that I’m the only one here that is NOT ALRIGHT with just speculating this? Will he? Won’t he? What… https://t.co/sdeDLYnCA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who forgot to post this on Valentine’s Day jsjs 💕❤️ #ValentinesDay2019 #ocxcanon #LittleWitchAcademia #LWA… https://t.co/Kpma32YtXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to the office this morning and realized our cleaning crew did it for me, thank you DOME. Saving my life 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers! Sip, savor...#Breathe Happy Valentine’s Day! https://t.co/5d6ijJm0wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little cactus spine was in my heel and created quite an annoyance for two days, but it is out! Now I have a ve… https://t.co/ZZEpxHAb8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pupper Joe Biden is watching the Lance Mackey movie, The Great Alone,with me. We love Lance! #uglydogs… https://t.co/xwIdLgKVDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XplodingUnicorn I asked my then 8-year old to pick up her toys. “Sure mom, but remember...Rome wasn’t built in a day.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MACSports @WMU_TFXC @WMUBroncos Congratulations ladies. Tough without your coach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJTRANSIT_NBUS bus #9019 has graced our backs with water bottle stuffed seats this morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emily is not thrilled with the cage she has to sleep in. Staying the night hoping she feels better in the morning.… https://t.co/Gm3HeuWBcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kept my Doctor, @cspanwj I am proof that Obama didn't lie to me... I also had BCBS Ins before I qualified for The… https://t.co/Wi8YRgEYFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PMI_Rochester It was my pleasure to present to the brave PMI members who ventured out! Looking forward to May!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The second leg of the relay for the Celebrate Life bus has turned into the cheerlead express. @recordonline https://t.co/IN9CeSU3Cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt @LaynieDane If its a movie for people who aren't assholes to other people, its a pretty affirming sign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favourite thing about designing the homes of other people is getting to tell their story. Every project we do, w… https://t.co/aDm8N1I2zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 7 Principles of Fitness. These are the things that I prioritize and why I do what I do 😉 powerhousegymlic  What… https://t.co/KDlai5jbAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter We keep ignoring you, but your still here running your big mouth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quality of our water is a problem everywhere and it’s still not even fixed in Flint Michigan. We have the answe… https://t.co/dhXg64RC2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keeping it #REDforEd for teachers, support staff, students, parents, and All Arizona!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had one last jam sesh to 22 by @taylorswift13 before I am no longer 22 🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s me with the tea again. If your child needs glasses and you provide insurance for them- make sure you get visio… https://t.co/BnyVqRiBH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few of my amazing female colleagues @sidewalklabs. The entire team has prioritized #diversity to get us to a… https://t.co/FSEeVfGWD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/2MFoefzZEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we should make cigarettes illegal all over the world and make marijuana legal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankLawrence You guys shouldn’t call yourselves that after losing to the Rams]]></document><document><![CDATA[staying up until 4am writing a paper that i could’ve finished in 20 minutes if i had more than two brain cells to r… https://t.co/SYaU3j3q5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hello_kissy Once I had someone eat my lunch at work &amp; wash my dish after. I def had a Mental Ross moment then😇🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beerdazed @Just4BeerLovers @DRE_Go_Fish @DENTONCBC @badhopper @ephoustonbill @JonMontag @JohanBBT @OkiTimes… https://t.co/4Rx1N4RYFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told myself I would lose 4Ibs by the end of the week. Lost 4Ibs by the end of the week....  Now if I could just do… https://t.co/w8Hybk0fib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrisAndersonTV @7News @AmakaUbakaTV @clamberton7 @alainapinto @KaitlinMcCulley Lucky Charms is my favorite cereal… https://t.co/42K9wKKId8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayitoMenco @Aracelitimi @lopezobrador_ Somos una montaña para que se recargue en nosotros y nosotros en usted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday to 2013 when I had short hair.. and shout-out to @giopresenza for the beautiful portrait he made… https://t.co/QyUT6kAWTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchoolOfNursing we work hard to understand our students learning style to contribute to their student success]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw Rafiki in Tampa. More than friends-lovers. And their families, community. Yes the music too. With me still]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jsaguilar11 Wish I could retweet this bc it’s 100% accurate. Your closet is my closet 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PtboKawRotary thanks for having me in this morning to talk about the challenges and opportunities ahead! Great que… https://t.co/EylQVp5ndo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think print marketing is dead? Think again.💭 . And follow the LINK IN BIO to learn how to use direct mail to drive… https://t.co/e0ssIaBrdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes @DoranyPineda90 I wanted #Roma to win an #Oscar...#spielberg is being eletist.  I saw it in a theater. It… https://t.co/34iFHxlpMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the not so distant future  Year 3000  🛸🛸🛸🛸🛸🛸 #LA #lacma #museum #buildings @ LACMA Los Angeles County Museum of… https://t.co/tu8tBYKIzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you can’t go to bed because someone is enjoying the fireplace. #mabel #catsofinstagram #catoftheday #heat @ Fr… https://t.co/9xpOQWRpqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve puked 3 times already today.... and it’s only 7am ......I am dying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished #TheUmbrellaAcademy ...not bad. Makes me want to listen to some Bangles now. https://t.co/hRbA9RAIQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson @brittanitaylor Bought it! Can't wait to read! Love you guys❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dems don’t like my tweets. I see. Look Dems I don’t vote on empty resolutions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JuanSanchez, CEO of #SouthwestKey #immigration #detention based in Texas, resigned after 32 yrs. Melody Chung, CFO… https://t.co/gW24QjdNgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump @VP @SecNielsen @SecPompeo @DHSgov @ICEgov @KellyannePolls @PressSec @SarahHuckabee… https://t.co/kaD5wMV24l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two new girls just walked in trying to work on a Saturday night lmao okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this funny. 15 Poses and Tips for Selfies https://t.co/um2tIg8agV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain't nobody gonna do it for you Pull the trigger Maybe, you should pull the fucking trigger]]></document></documents></author>