<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lotta people rag on LA for being filled with flakes, but rescheduling the same coffee date over and over is the most consistent work I have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breannathomas21 Oh my gosh yes!!! The only one I like better is Panera. Love the texture of the KFC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going down!  Nikki is getting the glam on for our client Jen.  #boudoir #promakeupartist… https://t.co/EHQpj2kF8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@remotetragic You’re coming to NY for Mania week?!?! *looks at list* Oh girl you’re getting some hugs from me!! https://t.co/hREEtk8iQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WorldBookDay to #celebrate, I'm having a #booksale for my #debutromance SKATER'S WALTZ. #99centsale… https://t.co/SHVmb6lK0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oct26bby Yeah , I mean when I work I’m walking up and down and my feet get sore , so I give these girls props but… https://t.co/R4yS6X706c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get why everyone is mad at Jordyn but... why tf is no one talking about Tristan??? Like bitch he was the one in the relationship!! 😒😒.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s food was stupid amazing. Not pictured, those bomb ass Brussels Sprouts that we all devoured in two sec… https://t.co/MxyIXWddor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN No wall was mentioned in this reporting. No national emergency. #TrumpFakeEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flowers and chocolates are not the  way to my heart, but ice cream or candles might just do the trick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex What don’t you get she told her side should we not trust a black young lady? She didn’t have sex with him... stop the bull!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you respectfully decline your favorite flowers on v-day? It’s becoming a crisis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah @ReginaKing OPRAH ENOUGH!! DON'T MAKE THIS RACE ISSUE ANY WORSE. IT'S  A WORLD OF OF PEOPLE PEOPLE OK I WOUL… https://t.co/p6tMUekKqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a yogi, I think about the 4 Puerto Rican revolutionaries who felt they had to take up arms. Could they negotiate… https://t.co/XmD3SF3ipi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newmusic #🎶 #comingsoon from #rappers #singers jwillzfromthe201 jsavagebh my son and his uncle R #fire 🔥… https://t.co/tcWClB1gxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's going to do it. As far as I'm concerned, it's just setting a precedent for the next (Democrat!) POTUS to decla… https://t.co/HD8BVT6hez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Limbaugh is as big of a fat, slob, mean spirited, lying blowhard as you are Donny Boy, if that's possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Nope. Stay there. We can prove you were right in your own mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heuceda Jaja no, mi amigo es gay😄 justamente por eso se lo mandé a él, para no crear malos entendidos]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so awesome!  Congrats, my friend!  Well-deserved!  #PABankersWIB #WomenInBanking @PABankers @PattiHusicCEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fuenteseliz Muñeco de cera, Chávez no vive ni sus restos descansan en paz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GOPLeader: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg of course I will always support and pledge to #applejuiceproductions @ Columbia, South Carolina https://t.co/rwQx0ncMrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doms definitely my best friend; he’ll drive all the way to wherever I am (the city ) to pick me and her up, take he… https://t.co/OMK2SqN5AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buuuuuuut you’re still trying to take away our right to choose what we do with our body and cut funding to a progra… https://t.co/u1c7nPvGUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrived predawn, before security even opened. 😴 https://t.co/Q5xe1Yxxs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 4 paychecks I haven’t cashed yet. I’ll go head and make a trip to the bank in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Footage of @BobBuckhorn practicing for his next career. @Uber’s leveling up! @StephSmithFL get ready for a PR night… https://t.co/RixGv2cWzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @American_MBB tourney begins Thursday with the first RD (3) #TUMBB will likely get  (6) #WichitaState who plays… https://t.co/HbcfPW5Pq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[iconic, if they tour I’m going to lose it &amp; I’m bringing @Dariangeorge__ with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about mammals at Pinnacle Mountain! My niece is not convinced that armadillos have fur 😂 https://t.co/c5nsR08YS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is true, My President has been harassed since the presidency began; that's envy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperWiki OMG that's a lil creepy, except I'm pretty sure someone tied some fishing string to that swing to screw… https://t.co/a2fBEIkHry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ottawa Hospital - Civic Campus https://t.co/6JzRqmgOXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember the nights I prayed for this, and it’s only the beginning. Even though I’m exhausted, I am very grateful… https://t.co/F9mIgmRoWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Issa Vibe It's been a minute.  #queen  #somebodiesmother  #fashionexperimenter  #fashionmaster #issavibe… https://t.co/RFYpX7j9Ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraEatsVeg Yes! I love the beginning seasons. Honestly I’ve been loving it up until season nine and ten!! I mean… https://t.co/mAtCNFh5TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team update: Florida State: 11 Georgia Southern 7. Great game against a good team! Way to stay strong eagles!!! #GATABABY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@star_indie @networkindie @BamilMusic @_maddiemueller_ @DanielleVHaskel @SophiaDaniz @jimenar31 @Delerium65… https://t.co/YUEdgbURmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I go with you to class and sit there, will it motivate you to come to lecture?” 🥰🥰🥰🥰🥰🥰 https://t.co/bwnXxSUlaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP TRASHING OUR PRESIDENT! WE DO NOT CARE ABOUT WHAT HE SUPPOSEDLY DID YEARS AGO IN HIS PERSONAL LIFE! WE CARE AB… https://t.co/ZThAAgt5OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eastcoastgirl40 Nice!  I'm waiting to finish my basement to have my own She Den...granted I'm single and live alon… https://t.co/ROtZBiwbaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney is in my blood, I am who I am all because of Disney. When I had nothing I had all Disney, Thank you @Disney… https://t.co/rc7QGhs59j]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your life was as bomb as you portray on social media you wouldn’t be worried about mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot ... Helen Keller #ENLIVEN #bebetter #qotd #motivation #quotes https://t.co/Ig78HmIz1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[At it again with the green juice. Celery juice is one of the most nutrient-rich juices. The reason I love it is tha… https://t.co/6mjVmrkFqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you need to know about @SamTinnesz : he just bought internet on a plane, just to be able to use gifs. https://t.co/zEtifUhMm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoftSolutionsTM No need to apologize. I was just jealous. :p But it's nice to know I'm surrounded by well-spoken people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferYovino @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott No, I believe it was made in Toronto, but the story takes place in NY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey PLN Friends!  @KhrissyB413 is showing me such a great time in @sunvalley before #RapidLiteracy tomorrow! https://t.co/FudVHbFgkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where should we go for dinner in ATL but be back early and it’s cold out there and let’s just go to bed Challenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES! All of you ladies working together created a phenomenal show 👏🏼 #womeninfilm #RepresentationMatters… https://t.co/OJJdTOJbqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsPackyetti It was amazing to meet you. I didn’t mention that I’m the CEO of @SwipeHunger, committed to ending col… https://t.co/1nxOIC3tlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musiklpn @aravosis @mschlapp @TheJusticeDept Thanks for posting this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstasiaWill @Taylor_Heinicke That face painting was the cherry on top!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch this past #BostonTalks speaker perform her original raps and rhymes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Nina Simone but I know full well what her breath smelled like. You do too. https://t.co/aF26MfX9rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[All our work getting a passport for the youngest is not in vein. He can still go on the epic trip! Sigh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4am and the things that keep me awake are the fact that South Beach Tow was all fake 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[After one: Indiana Tech leads Lawrence Tech 19-10. Kauffman leads with 6.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No me había dado cuenta lo mucho que extrañaba a mis bebes🥺❤️ #JonasBrothers https://t.co/6LCEfeEhOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had another Stuffed animal request last night! Mom joined in and the daughter was thrilled! 🤗 Question for ya....… https://t.co/ZG9k52WEG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@12thplanet rocking our Dino pashMIna! 😍 🦕🦖🦕🦖🦕🦖🦕🦖🦕🦖🦕🦖🦕🦖 #12thplanet #elektricity #pontiac #detroit #michigan #edm… https://t.co/lZWBgTFpV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicolaou_alexa @HRhodesEdu Why for some schools is ok not to have metal detectors? How do we really make sure that… https://t.co/bL03d0Qh2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[umbrella academy you are KILLING me with this season end cliffhanger. when do we get the next episodes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Asian Am, specifically. Also, idk? They're both small New England towns so they're pretty similar.... Maybe St… https://t.co/Nqbu3Z44EV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elementary teachers I need help! Looking for series recommendations for a reluctant 2nd grade reader. Anything alon… https://t.co/FZpWV4Lhyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Seeking No Illusions” Tonight 6:30-9pm Harney Sushi Oceanside. @ Harney Sushi - Oceanside https://t.co/FPyUl6zK7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conquered the elusive macaron last evening. Attended a class at Crate Cooking School on Greentree Rd. Awesome time! https://t.co/ddfDDntDrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump is a Christian..but you cant see it because the enemy your father satan has blinded you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨Ft. Lauderdale work views 🏙 #work #fortlauderdale #southflorida #realestate #luxuryrealestate #beach #ocean #sand… https://t.co/x1L4pwxvXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 3570 S Ocean Boulevard # 908 #SouthPalmBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/XbidxzShWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg #DwAir #wheelsup #loveeternal ... Do you realize those words scare me... Feel much safer with your feet on the ground.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatonequeen Not a bad idea but have you thought about just creating your own management company? More direct and… https://t.co/yaBkoUhzek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have heard of a number of these types of situations. Her language to staff and help would make a sailor blush.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch "Growing the 'Idea Garden' on the Great Dat TV show https://t.co/yeiKKVK9ad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstridO I never even think about that when I see a woman in heels, my first thought is “how can she walk in those, id be on my ass” lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting Dr. Seuss inspired pajama day!  @DrSeuss #ReadAcrossAmericaDay #ReadAcrossAmerica @LegendSprings @DVUSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @ATLUTD lost. @NUFC lost. @USWNT tied. Good news: My kid’s @iafc_blues team won. 😜 #smallvictories #glasshalffull]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayleighschultz Sometimes when I watch videos of Rihanna she really reminds me of you. And I’m not just saying that to be a suck up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super fucking annoyed this morning so listening to The Hives very very loud 😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡😡… https://t.co/7Se8gD7xRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the cemeteries in Malta because they just have such a different feeling to them than the ones I’ve been to i… https://t.co/LDyfXQYbU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told this girl in the fitting room her bodysuit was cute and she told me where to find it in the store but… https://t.co/RCwtHA1Zd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[soooo i spent vday eating so much food.. my heart ((and tummy)) is happy 🥰😗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me this morning waiting patiently for my next training! I love eXp! This company invest in making sure you’re succe… https://t.co/Dw0WBUNO8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGinBigD He wasn’t ever even considered the best at his position. How can anyone say he’s a goat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really interesting reporting by the Washington Post on the motion they filed today with the U.S. District Court in… https://t.co/s1kVrOnlGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: my name is Sunny and on top of being a #drpepper junkie I also have Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis or… https://t.co/e7GJpWXICs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen I’m not technically a millennial but top sheets are evil and are just there to sprain your feet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m 100% convinced that most of these combine drills don’t actually prove anything🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity She calls being married to three Isis fighters a PHASE? Hmmmmm....I call that a choice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pax527 @Bakari_Sellers I’m in a 42 year misunderstanding with my Mother over beets. Yet, they always find their way into our fridge. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emkristen @SnoozeAMEatery Yes, thank god. I need some Spuds Deluxe in my life pretty much every day. 😍😍😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect #FBF and #internationalwomensday post  Last year @ciroc @followemve @iamMaddieMey honored and celebrate… https://t.co/Zj1xnO0Rdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @1210WPHT Radiothon is underway at @ChickiesnPetes on Packer Avenue in Philadelphia and we’ve already hit $13,0… https://t.co/wBoCRzMWst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take the @airportag shower curtain challenge that @supersnail19 sent me!  I’ll post mine below.  #avgeek… https://t.co/h9vj7uXDI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetMissMagee @PaulaEbbenWBZ @wbz Congratulations!  What a lovely story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beautifulday 😎 is it spring yet?? 🤷🏽‍♀️ #malibu #lunchtime #lunch🍴 #cali #calilove #la #losangeles #jeans #casual… https://t.co/Z0YMlrLXgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MetInKC Pretty much it was me stuffing popcorn in my gob think’n that’s pretty swell. https://t.co/B9aghdcvZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final preseason game for @realsaltlake &amp; then it’s go time!!!! 💃🏻⚽️🔥💜 https://t.co/onk1xs8K7u]]></document></documents></author>