<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Omg some of the hive are gonna see me when they watch the full video 😱 #Shook I can’t believe I’m in a video that g… https://t.co/rSgSaDgc6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armarquina Y lo del magnetron maduro se lo copió de la película oceans 13 que dejó sin luz a Las Vegas así que el… https://t.co/Y9roqzIDEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auxonic @ladybugspicnic @cmckenney Everything is fine everyone.  Greenbank / Pinecrest sidewalk from Transitway to… https://t.co/euMIFuUd1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy the day, Salisbury/Charlotte, for the rain returns tomorrow! #PaddlesNotPedals]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Sketchbook Vol. 1’ Exhibition at Sugarlift https://t.co/pHlBo3fOT4 via @epochtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump What a bunch of really stupid ass people. When I was growing up being a Republican… https://t.co/qUd6JDwmO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marine1279 fighting off the absurd tax breaks given to the investors and millionaires is well worth it. Furthering… https://t.co/bausaeDkHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanwlod Omg I totally do !!!! @ChipotleTweets when are you doing this with my poems?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessica_mess33 @funder His boyfriend, for instance? #ConfirmedGOPBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Jesus: ‘It is written.’ Satan: ‘It is written?’ Know the difference.” -Andrew Wilson via Matt Smethurst #church… https://t.co/osVdmrYjti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rascal Flatts would blow up with their cover in Cars a couple years later. Figures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many dog hairs gone and now the car is clean, so I can roll the windows down and not have tons of hairs just blo… https://t.co/r0M7R5FYQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would the democrat party mob people vote for something they don't believe? #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[De-Stress night (@ Peninsula Wellness Center Salinas in Salinas, Calif w/ @raherrier) https://t.co/88HKLJD1h6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a abstract sculpture Wall art it Is called The hobbit https://t.co/rOcX0DAGnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamarocks54 @kenolin1 Oh, you mean he wants everyone to become tRumpublicons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong #KeepFighting #45… https://t.co/rPeJo9yYSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who thinks this is a terrible idea? Great white sharks tend to be found where seals are. https://t.co/mTbwcxekSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chase0724 @jackiecall3 @MSNBC Yeah, back in 2008.  Every year as VP.  And will play a little catch up when or if he decides to run again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflection complete. God being sober and clear headed is so much better than depressed angry and drunk.   Maybe this is the growth...😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logophobe @hotoynoodle @MyraFlection You do not need a rooster anyway. Don’t do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te konn gen ransè nan klas mw lem te lekol men franchman a 31 an map avwe ke neg @sanchristobal3 la vreman pa gen parey. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump to Nominate Jeffrey Byard as FEMA Administrator https://t.co/92JObZEWM7 #HSEM #SMEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarahhhh No. Not sure I’d be into it.  I’m going soon. So ya ass just tell me where’s to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Written communication can have strong effects, and sales representatives should be wary of writing things down they… https://t.co/oFMCI0niMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dee Dee is watching men crawfishing! Yum @ By Lake Waco https://t.co/R3NLlWz2Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remind you Kap had his statistical best season before being blackballed with Chip Kelly as HC and Reuben Droughns… https://t.co/Q9ySyxMDuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump Bigly crowds show up or die in a Prison. This was for sure a mandatory event https://t.co/2OvH38LlQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wasn't @NaomiWWE winning the title in her hometown in a minute and 25 seconds enough for you people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cypresshill @PhunckyFeeltips @FillmorePhilly @hollywoodundead @IamDEMRICK @xzibit You got Coughee &amp; Coffee, !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[College interview for Jake. I have a sneaking suspicion a certain bowling coach is going to be the first bowling co… https://t.co/lOaGlTM8ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dos segundos después del rapto. en Van Nuys, California https://t.co/FQaf61KL6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the @stonybrookalum made it. They are having tons of fun connecting. We made it inside the #distillery… https://t.co/r1E2RtzmEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY ONE HUNDRED AND THIRTY-FIVE @ Summerville, South Carolina https://t.co/QFMT9Y6PnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noland_Parry I guess I was thinking more in terms of the immigrants already in California. It's really an interest… https://t.co/btGOFgK6a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMcMullin The election outcome will not remove Congress.   We are and will remain this - a blend.  The need is… https://t.co/w74F9qqxLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claudio Ranieri was sacked last week?(too bad, he thought he could help a team in shambles)...Just found out now on… https://t.co/HGCkMTfvPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexVorkov @hotdogcinema @NYounker It's both, and a lot of people haven't forgotten Vic Morrow and those poor kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder if a flight to oil will occur like in 07 and 08, i keep seeing info on drillers and integrated oil companies… https://t.co/rBFpuKURF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 14 - Evening Update:      How Parkland parents and lawmakers built relationships to help prevent… https://t.co/YwLfpe6p1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny @aprillynnclark @drfixus Right. Holy crap. We agreed on something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[doesn’t “I don’t know how to show my feelings” sound like a sociopath to u]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s March 1st! You know what that means! 🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀🏀 https://t.co/iEkmC1jwDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelbessey9 @realDonaldTrump @RogerJStoneJr The post was made on Instagram. So if you’re looking on Twitter goo… https://t.co/oU3feXhjGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. Trump, after reading your Twitter message, in which you once again attempt to smear FBI Agent… https://t.co/HzTkJxxlS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport You do gotta hand it to her, though, that was a Trump tweet through and through. She’s Bizarro Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricky_martin @VenezuelaAid Que decepción Ricky a esta derecha homofobica le prestas apoyo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump American consumers pay the added cost of the tariffs. More out of our pockets to finance the explo… https://t.co/RktOg9iygv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaguMonero No hay fundamento legal para sostener la consulta "pato",ya son gobierno y sin ningún problema,podrían… https://t.co/1PsI0BQmBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Buenos días! / Good morning! / Magandang umaga! / Bonjour! / Guten Tag! #ptseminary #ptsem #pentecostalseminary… https://t.co/8uU1J3LPQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks since you won’t allow staff to take “trash” at drive thru including your old cups. I highly recommend ad… https://t.co/dWDQrF6Gtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[watched survivor season 33 it was ok i will rate it 4 out of 10 now on to season 38 so far not great season 38 epis… https://t.co/ywW03FwhHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to Clallam County for letting us use equipment for snow removal. https://t.co/D7PJWk4S7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tdn_twit 😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱😱y los delanteros aztecas donde están no ce dice que son la octava maravilla del mundo como goleadores]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not everyday that you see your congressman at a cartoonist’s retirement party. The occasion called for a shame… https://t.co/P80FaVry6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flew back to L.A.  after another great weekend of Rainbow Warrior  #HawaiiBSB bumped into Iowa #Hawkeyes at the air… https://t.co/SJR8sOBOti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTimJennings Go to any Bed, Bath and Beyond and they’ll let you fuck one before purchase just to make sure you g… https://t.co/QfVJMAsJE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother, Ruth L. Munro, RN was a nurse during WWII.  Stateside. https://t.co/FRJXtrBIeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/0hSrQ9CCUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maniac1776 Does he hate me? No. Does he have a transgender son, two queer step daughters, three neurodivergent son… https://t.co/rDDaHRdxh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @GOP Imagine if that was your son and you heard the smegma blob say that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demeatloaf @cavs @KingJames Rj and Channing made the team fun but the 14-15 squad rolling into the playoffs was a… https://t.co/Xz0xEQA4M4]]></document><document><![CDATA[For as much as Border Patrol agents put themselves at risk every day, finding this was just disgusting. So disrespe… https://t.co/n5Yud0X8tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: @browardsheriff confirms off-duty deputy was attacked by another man during domestic dispute in Lauderdale… https://t.co/clm1w3fd18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayGritty @AOC Ps.. no one cares if you’re gay. Do you have s male vagina?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please come out and support the Wolfcreek Family. @parents4edu_SF @COSFGA @CoSFObserver]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheerUPDATES you blocked me because I questioned this post? I was simply questioning how he was able to legally po… https://t.co/9FKZyMAY41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahira Khan shared a picture of her favourite magnet and the Internet is in fits https://t.co/IYOIy5poRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very explicit but this is rehearsal for First Lady II  @demarisharvey and @therealkdeezy murdered it!!! We start fi… https://t.co/ORZUBehEBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weareamerica #Time to #EndIt. #support #UnbornBabies and #freeLivesmatter! #Build a relationship with #God and… https://t.co/qU10cmElvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArdentFox @squigle13 @cspan @senatemajldr Don't try to confuse me with your degree in biology that you grasp ANYTH… https://t.co/9XjOPJ0nqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NezbaTTV Yeah I just went out to eat and did something that everybody should do at a restaurant and the waiter was… https://t.co/GSlFZAYLna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iivveeyy A&amp;M will never give up having 7 home games per year. Only way I can see it happening is if Arkansas game came back to campus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 @MikeOkuda Call the school board. Call the principal. ACLU too there are some serious issues here. Y… https://t.co/pNAHAigmin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi You want us to believe that #IlhanOmar is simply naive when she make anti-Semitic statements. Lady,, sh… https://t.co/w2Wav2JYb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TW2CayC Well good evening to you Lady Cay and thank you  for the shout out!😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just looked into it, turns out there’s this thing called the 1st Amendment that protects the “freedom of speech” in… https://t.co/5rWGChUOXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL I’m sure the will blame the fight on Old White Conservatives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This food area off the 8th hole @genesisopen is the California that years of TV promised me https://t.co/dp5Xr6D2ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason @ewarren @amazon @AOC Ha captive audience of voters in Cali and NY. Imagine what it would be like if there was no electoral college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wetnasty Ah, I see. So it’s as if they’re trying to put a spin on it to elevate it to a revolutionary act…?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol omgggg ppl actually hating on me rn on twitter and talkin mess??? I didn’t even know til someone told me. Been… https://t.co/0Spb25iSvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[HELLO    GOOD  MORNING 😊   AMEN,    GOD   BLESS. https://t.co/I9CGliml9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonCortesTV Every time I watch Fantasia, it makes me think about it. It would be amazing if they did that in T… https://t.co/KoBXFzNmAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Twitter friends...if you haven’t read Andrew McCabe’s book “The Threat” you are missing a real treat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigkelo1 @Taurus_Simmons1 @HVJenkins_PTSA @TheBigGuyWJCL @xixnyne @ESPNCoastal @DennisKnightSMN @WSAVConnorD @GregTalbott]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Rutger Bregman described as an “historian?” He only has a BA and an MA in history and would not be qualified… https://t.co/r7HbRj7OpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @pitbull in concert today. I must say I was HIGHLY entertained - thank  you Mr. Worldwide!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RJ has never seen a shot he doesn’t like ... if he’s committed to shooting, it’s going up - no matter how bad of an… https://t.co/IhYLqsZwO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@owlahs @Terclub1 i mean you right, you right  but people can still wait for a song]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @NBCLA @AdrianNBCLA @DaniellaNBCLA @ShannaNBCLA @BelenNBCLA @latrafficgal @ToniNBCLA @MekahloNBCLA… https://t.co/xPGvcXNsTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys should check out @PodSaveAmerica's interview with Mayor @PeteButtigieg. He makes some strong points about… https://t.co/AAIG4ENbhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikePalmCirca Hey, a little help please. Is Wofford listed on the sheet or in the "Field" for NCAA basketball tour… https://t.co/y0dhuGYd1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pelon_73 @manuel70m @ElPincheJuan4 @Gamborimbo76 @maskarita4 @unttalhanckoc @davidant264 Jajjajajajja se guntan la… https://t.co/hsNQY1h3QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya mandado raza al chori tan temprano? Esperate wey todavía ni son las 8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Space Ghost is one of my favorite cartoon super hero’s from when I was a kid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are they sure they wan to do that since trump wants to invade Venezuela to build a tower with Russian laundered $$$?]]></document><document><![CDATA[One great tragedy is that we seem to forget a common good that forces us to focus on we not me, us not I, ours and… https://t.co/Zev62B6S2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimNaught I have fwiw deleted the tweet about thinking I remembered a photo, since I haven't been able to find the photo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsvncheznxb @sarieprom @TimVoyce @melprom @SwiftestNinja " alright y'all I can only have 3 chik fil a chicken nuggets this year."]]></document></documents></author>