<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me happier than looking up in the stands and seeing this beautiful girl repping that blue and orange!… https://t.co/DMuyOp9hdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have never road tripped by yourself. Let me tell you it’s a great time you drive check out nice scenery and… https://t.co/A7WEvbKIo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillBeckner @SVC_Bearcats @SVCHoops @TribSports @PAC_Athletics Best of luck, D. Thanks for all you did for my guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get me a plane to Berkeley, and an apartment, and I’ll take care of these assclowns for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimforge I just watched this as well.  After watching this and the Pat Ryan (curling) episode, I love how this sho… https://t.co/smi68HaHUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[As of Wednesday night, #Raiders figured Antonio Brown was going elsewhere. Compensation was steep for both Brown an… https://t.co/kLfHzxaelW]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if you needed other reason to extremely dislike this old curmudgeon, here you go: 👇 #MIGHTYDucksofAnaheim]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women’s Day - a chance to celebrate, a chance to take stock, and a chance to build commitment so Paki… https://t.co/nVoi05UjEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UteGorilla @MarkAurelius9 @robr0013 @cooterbobjim @sunlitgold1968 @Tan_Mart21 @vakaviti @inkedtater @dGod23… https://t.co/ayiCWGOL0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LackadaisicalS5 ROUGHING THE PASSER WHAT A JOKE! BRADY BELONGS IN HIS PINK DRESS! BUT MAHOMES GETS SMASHED NO ROUG… https://t.co/qDT1X5xN9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Típico en los robolucionarios buscar un culpable de la inoperancia de ustedes ,son crimínales ,causantes del desast… https://t.co/xvDmTlw6Ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentASJax @NateMonroeTU I would pay cold hard cash for a Monroe/Martineau debate. It’d be like clash of the titan… https://t.co/hCsKBZHQnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fetish vogueing &gt; Let me show you how we do this • https://t.co/eBEAJ99EjF https://t.co/v4pAiE7ndw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Admirals Club in Grapevine, TX https://t.co/4kKTSRVkDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NSchlange @zenj8 @WMarkPorter @John_F_Kennnedy ... cooperating. Become an actor in the movie. (Graham).]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a fun day teaching the basics of fishing and kayaking to our K-3 students. https://t.co/i8GhdnJ1MY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattness21 I’m not positive you’re 16 yet in any category but chronological. No wait and grey hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scheme master Joshuazilla. @ Pine Hills, Florida https://t.co/AO1briFshe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am running to provide a new generation's perspective to our fair Borough with a fresh set of ideas for our changi… https://t.co/JpRg2ij63V]]></document><document><![CDATA[i miss summer, i miss seeing ashley glow, i miss my skin being tan, i miss rachel breaking her fingers, i miss goin… https://t.co/w5L0nGwCgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCrimian @BR_NBA @bayharding11 What you talking about? I’m tryin to get that FIRST ROUND MONEY SON!! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rib test underway.the riptangles are running smooth and steady,fueled with Rockwood Charcoal and Vaughn Wood Produc… https://t.co/GtvcfOks0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! ¡Feliz día de la mujer! 😍😁 https://t.co/jgUGoqHE7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations #DaddyRUF. Thanks for scaring me/ making me so excited @1035KISSFM @AngiTaylorKISS @fredonair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anissaacarroll results are in...you’re automatically my valentine for lyfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been listening to @OpposingBases on the way to school in the mornings. Now the boy is building ATC towers out of ma… https://t.co/0adkj4klpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 También tienes razón en esto, trato de armar revoluciones en todo el mundo y envío cubanos a morir en… https://t.co/Bx8gYKF8Aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyadcock @RED_Cinema @Lensrentals @fstopHQ @CanonUSA @ikancorp @BLUESHAPEUSA @BLUESHAPE_IT @filmschool Debating… https://t.co/axgrXlbVdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@world_partnerss @totalake @KAG4All Added to my previous answer you say it is a not a matter of money?  Yes it is.… https://t.co/wO8fvCQcMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN I think the president Needs to open up an investigation into your family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenamricher this is a real question - what are the biggest companies in York PA? I thought you'd know this answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, @Katie_George05 should be running the mic at the all star game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a third job yesterday and let me tell y’all that this girl is about to be on her GRIND all 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are tv shows where former house burglars teach people how they would break into their home so they can fix it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOKED. RAMBLINGS  https://t.co/xUCPUatzqm @ Pearland, Texas https://t.co/j29vGPxGgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey Of course you would say some ignorant shit like this, they voted and continue to… https://t.co/GzuaycwueV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobProvince @chadfelixg @lgbtqnation How dare these brave against the grain individualists not vote lock step!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that new tech, and still the most important new feature of the Q2 is *water and dust resistance* which is a ver… https://t.co/PWVydveiC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back2blax The talkative ones trip me out the most. “Put ya finger in there, rub it, lick it....” niggga! We didn’t discuss this but ok 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boogiecousins heard people talking shit about his defense so he got 3 steals and 6 blocks tonight lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen You should, it’sa great stress release.  I get lost in my art]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I started wearing my glasses again, turns out I’m more blind than I realized lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JWWins @BreitbartNews Shark News-when all you cronies in the FBI, get prosecuted..and the attempted coup gets expl… https://t.co/ExKb6oXfFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I hear when our neighbors yell: YOU DON’T DO SHIT FOR THIS FAMILY YOU’RE AN IDIOT AND A DISAPPOINTMENT  What o… https://t.co/2Q8d8eUPer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ultra Music Radio (@UMFradio) is LIVE!! - @EvolutionRadio (@1027KIISFM HD2) | @iHeartRadio: https://t.co/bLZ8CK9Loy  👍😀📱🎙🎧📻💻🎉⌚️🏖🏝]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t make some dogs give up a bone they are chewing you’ll get bit, even when you can prove we’re on the right… https://t.co/8U5ca4HUGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk Well then take your blonde mustache a****** and go away no one cares about you fuck face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somuchwowswow @valsrapidservi1 There are times when they are very salty. But 7/10 times I go they taste delicious.… https://t.co/GnE6tUhnKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acofarstore is a scam site. They take your money but never deliver any product. Do not buy from them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Model3Owners @seanmmitchell I dunno, I have to defrost mine with by breath sometimes on the S. The X isn't so bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanG_Arango I already see it happening  as you may know we do a free pick up game meet up every week... so the mo… https://t.co/tTCZxABcu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almagarcia04 Me intriga saber cuánto puede influir una persona en los gustos de otra 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonLaCanfora Isn’t this what was reported on Thursday night? Lmao. You’re a complete disgrace to the @nfl. I can… https://t.co/HAyhrXYfrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwkwardGothma @Brettals01 @martialdark @Halloween_1014 @SeraBoo @Pezzy777 @Grimnir15 Bad side? I’m just being....… https://t.co/wNhKvQqeys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leader of the free world. We also used to have one of those. Long ago and far, far away?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proteus Parade #MardiGras2019 #NewOrleans @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/QYzfOhfMDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eternalluv0408 @biogeek7 @PreacherSix Lol I think you're safe Maria!! 👍😎😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you #gma. You’re the best thing that has happened to me. Don’t #ever leave me! We’re gonna have a good life!… https://t.co/rRFGZqXzFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What u thought? Goals still get made bih #swerveaction @ Old National East, Georgia https://t.co/4mO5H260XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 home opener on Tuesday vs Bradshaw Mountain (Prescott, AZ) at Tempe Diablo Field #6! First pitch at 6:00pm. Go… https://t.co/abpHlKL0SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @LBCeleste @realDonaldTrump I just gave you a list of 35 things. Also his campaign manager gave polling da… https://t.co/2VwDCxmV7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBennyBash @AmericanAir Dude this sucks... I’m sorry..  maybe there will be a cash prize at the end in the form… https://t.co/qFk0964XF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hear my sister talking to our cat “Mister Shakes, do you want to listen to emo music with me? Or we can do… https://t.co/cedTHHaeyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opposite of last year, I think defensive players will be the big draw of just recently graduated players. Looking f… https://t.co/a6rkf4i66n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just think the Eagles are going to go against these ferocious quarterbacks like Eli Manning Case Keenum and Dak Pre… https://t.co/lOzMPZUe5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twittersupport you literally just banned this clown. time to ban the alt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re in store for another beautiful Sunday #onlincolnroad. Whose ready for a little retail therapy? Enjoy your day… https://t.co/mJ8Za3UBiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Do y’all make this shit up during your phone calls or is Steven Miller making up fresh crazy for you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSTRodB 100% agree. He knows how to make the proper moves without blowing cap just because he has it. He also know… https://t.co/aWUyHv3ORr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkAtdisney Can Drunky save WDW from the diabolical plans of Mad Scientist @derekburgan? Can he withstand the wa… https://t.co/tcYQlYnLJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon Thankfully no. It’s because I work under a union collective bargaining agreement. But most folks eithe… https://t.co/2MdjdAKIEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdrache I honestly wanted to work at a service station when I was a little. No lie...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Distract from the White House dumpster fire and Trump's treason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mois 6 sans prendre de pain au chocolat : l’envie de succomber à la « chocolatine » se ressent]]></document><document><![CDATA[This @Kehlani mixtape is soooo good! I really want more! Favorite tracks are probably #LoveLanguage #NightslikeThis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pillars of truth... #ThisIsWhatISee #aNGles @ Supreme Court of the United States https://t.co/KUk6x5X2tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bama_sims @wshane_pursley5 No...the preacher should be fueled with passion drawn from a personal application of the text to himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyMystique_01 @Blazin_Chix Wow she's beautiful and I love her sexy smile]]></document><document><![CDATA[WILL END UP GETTING 6 MONTHS PROBATION AND A NETFLIX DEAL - UPDATE: Jussie Smollett Facing Up to 48 YEARS Behind Ba… https://t.co/a5evt5WEyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirlineFlyer Yeah I’m not sure what airlines and aircraft don’t have screens for that. My airline kept screens for… https://t.co/qcXPcgJRg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masterfully done. Tons of flavor. Having lunch before Monster Jam - Drinking an Out of Time by @OliverBrewingCo at… https://t.co/ZDx9PVMo48]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robb_Ellis Exactly. You can only do so many tactics and strategies but if you have no work ethic, will or emotion you never win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give GOD Praise @FBI @FBISanFrancisco @FBIWFO @FBIDetroit @NewYorkFBI @FBIMiamiFL  @ChiefGodbee @LouisFarrakhan… https://t.co/cxxu6liVwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TropicalJay97 How did they hurt the economy, where are can I find numbers? Interesting you call them illegals. Don… https://t.co/wXLXhm5crp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another one of those "what the hell was that game" games from last season's forgettable disaster. Safe to say… https://t.co/1dsWN9qplA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are looking for @RepAndyBiggsAZ to respond, don’t hold your breath.  He is a coward and will do nothing  but… https://t.co/L3MHeYJqoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, It’s time for another Black. Angry. Educated. (B.A.E.) podcast. On this throwbackthursday and flashback frida… https://t.co/V80K2AKivs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yc 👨🏿‍💻meek stay clowning himself posting videos of him failing it’s great lol he posted him falling down the steps a few years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was I looking at? 👀 #daily #pics @ VIDA Wellness and Beauty https://t.co/sxnRDK89iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone will disappoint you at some point. Don’t take it too personally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsBernBrah @BizNasty2point0 Parise got off easy because of the partial lockout the following year. He didn’t play… https://t.co/MmC1QtgKSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how everyone is asleep over in the US but we barely waking up here in Japan]]></document><document><![CDATA[NFL Has promised to hire SMOLLETT when he's released Their spokesperson for their so called police protest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @obrienmaggie17 @lagaviota521 @grogan537 @berracahband @BestEverYou @helen19242686 @SanaMello… https://t.co/1qvQDF1FTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi Gras is over so I guess I have to go back to being an accountant. https://t.co/CbDgcdklzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revolutionwifi @jsnyder81 Notice that this was proposed in 2017 but the depreciation happened much earlier https://t.co/9xCG17rO7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haskett___ Good game, next knock down those freebies, don’t leave any chances for you opponent at the end 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_payton @George_01998 Definitely. But it’s missing a vent to the right of the radio. I’m an ac guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielgilman I know you are busy. I’m done at jcc as of  Monday.Can I have a few moments of your time please? I’m… https://t.co/oornNAqzuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[ohana_kitchen_cocktails @ Ohana Kitchen &amp; Cocktails https://t.co/IPvtlMQQ06]]></document></documents></author>