<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ScottWalker @AOC You’re jealous because she’s in and you’re out loser.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Poor baby. I even have an issue with folks who put their dogs in the back of their pick-ups.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol fun fact I was gonna transfer there but once I got hired I heard the screens were falling out of the ceilings a… https://t.co/B2pBc19P3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Orlando, FL? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/47afQMHg1T #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing reminds me of the indiscriminate disposable income in the United States more than the amount of fight fans… https://t.co/p1U436DCQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember once a camp counselor told us that there will be a day when it’s inappropriate and not in our best inter… https://t.co/5NlBDVPxmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100PercFEDUP They WOKE Up to See the REAL DEMOCRATIC PARTY MOB of TURMOIL and HATE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1 year to the best and most caring boyfriend a girl could ever ask for. I’m so grateful for you and everythin… https://t.co/7pnsaZuoFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @CoryBooker @BeefUSA Disrespecting other people is juvenile]]></document><document><![CDATA[My California Space Center in Los Angeles is shaking the premise of how things are done on Earth and how they are b… https://t.co/6LcbEtI1gB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patient with Chronic Pelvic Pain Presents with Severe Swayback Posture does matter! Swayback posture is when the sp… https://t.co/XK3D7aLrpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I??? Love her?????  (also fuck Iguedesman and Joo for the racist/sexist jokes though)   https://t.co/bakkmDU9wA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now playing on Starfire's Country Music w/Trisha at Night Wave Radio (https://t.co/OI5xIMNO2M) @nightwaveradio1… https://t.co/wALCHe8tlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yesss indeed! #SamHeughan  Thanks @lemonandhugs for sharing! #VanityFairOscarParty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anna_lardinois She'd have been born in the 90s and I thought they were still teaching it then. Right? Inquiring mi… https://t.co/HtwfWydfae]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚗 New Honda Civic 🚗 #SOLD and #Delivered to 🍾 Another Happy Client 🍾 ☎️Contact Me For Your Next Car☎️ 📲Tel : 818-44… https://t.co/WzsM5QAVuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHERE YOU GO I'LL GO  motherfucking shitballs I am going to tear my eardrums out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belyndaazavala casi me pegan cuando dije eso de bad bunny 🙄 cuidado amiga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist That is awful! I was raised a Catholic but quit because I will never forget getting slapped in the face by a nun !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please include your white paper co-author emails in your  #astro2020 upload forms, thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was an awesome experience for the students!  Thanks to @merr_10 and @MersSandy for all of their hard work to m… https://t.co/kR72LPQddF]]></document><document><![CDATA[in honor of the Robyn concert tomorrow, here’s my fav unofficial SNL bit: https://t.co/TOpkLTjWeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder that Tom Cruise's role in The Edge of Tomorrow is actually an 18-year-old Japanese man in the book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most romantic Valentines day dance at a wonderful romantic venue The California open https://t.co/e5DdME8QEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up to Jamie kissing me on the cheek goodbye this morning. It’s the little things 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[#disneyworld #disneyworld #universalstudios #simpsons #dream #gratidao 🙏🏻 em Springfield Home of the Simpsons at Un… https://t.co/GsDVrPey5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[jordyn woods is full of shit. she was definitely throwing it back for tristan. fuck outta here talking bout just a kiss]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll bring the whole fam to the @chrissyteigen household for dinner. I love the zucchini fries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No you're wrong of course socialist communist democrat...he's right...we have a GREAT PRESIDENT BEING INVESTIGATED… https://t.co/wlNWFy9AA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday Monday. @ The Residences at St.Regis Bal Harbour https://t.co/SSlBIjEfv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RungeKaren Yeah, it's definitely damaged after three years of bleaching]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Sigh* on top of those Yoshikitty animations I also built a Yoshikitty puppet. I'm still working on her in my spare… https://t.co/SDit1VVJO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one and only P-Nut❤️ @ House of Blues Orlando https://t.co/6c2p4eRGgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother asked me if anybody brought me chocolates and I said no. He was like “dammit” lmaoo. Sorry bro I don’t g… https://t.co/OmMBhm0emV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never gave up anything for Lent before, never practiced it. But this year I wanted to try it out.  So I gave up: Re… https://t.co/bLCJ0KeaDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[YOU GUYS! @McBentleson is the #genius who came up with the idea for @kfc to follow “11 herbs and spices” on… https://t.co/tM1KFwGwpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headline: Man attempts to be “edgy” in order to stand out from the crowd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[proud moment: my sister has been able to see and meet most of her favorite bands — something she didn’t have the op… https://t.co/OvsLuoNlbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people lose weight in relationships?????? I’m trying but it’s hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankLuntz Seriously?  Are companies like Walmart willing to help American Companies?  🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[The state of things at my house. #pug #blankets #saturday @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/n4CtJZSCM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katpa73 The GOP’s wet dream. Total control over women &amp; female children’s bodies. Disgraceful &amp; inhumane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love @PeteButtigieg He impressed me even more in last night's Town Hall. #MorningJoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldengurrll Don’t let someone who’s corny enough to take shit to social media get to your head babe! It doesn’t e… https://t.co/RnJH7MmERT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New Classic 👑🏅|| #TheTruthisHere || #ModelModays #photography @B_Great || #Model #TRUTH  #Lingerie… https://t.co/VuAU5yEDwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The glass is always half full - the inventive, resourceful history of #beer! #craftbeer #tech #water]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilax3l @mindyobizz95 @Opinionated____ @MTVTheoCampbell @CaraMariatea3 @ChallengeMTV My apologies YOUR*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @MomsDemand Ever since 45 started acting like a bully they all started doing the same thing.  What happened to decorum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend has been giving me so many hints on my vday presents and I’m so excited to see him tomorrow awh ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta @chanelwestcoast typa laugh and I’m sorry to everyone that has to hear it🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[BLESS HIM PRAISE HIM WORSHIP HIM GLORIFY HIM LIFT HIM HIGH SHOUT To HIS GLORY! Stand Still In HIS HOLY PRESENCE BOW… https://t.co/k3ZloreNfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing so many people with roses in the streets makes me so happy yet so depressed at the same time 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m confused. Why is life so confusing at times ?? College is like ... school in general is like ... me trying to f… https://t.co/bQ8jgRixYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-10. This is how I’m going to spend my snow day. #newsjunkie https://t.co/VVY3Z3Eovv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @AlynthiaCurtis to post a picture of my favorite books for 7 days, no review needed.  Today, on… https://t.co/BFjofzhfHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeIicious @isntitromantic @RebelWilson You’re gonna love it! You’ll be laughing, crying, and singing along to the music]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could this have something to do w/President Clinton firing the FBI Director the exact NIGHT VinceFoster was murdere… https://t.co/vPEQu0dFWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so tired of seeing the same people on my tl at every single show every night lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because everything in a JTS is weird! @ AdLib Theatre https://t.co/7WPhMRS1t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s gunna die one day, hopefully old and grey, with a song in his heart that never left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sold out!!! Night Market  #soldout #hadablast #supportsmallbusiness #supportlocal #thankful @ Alma Mater Tacoma https://t.co/MfqvDSAPPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gas-guzzling car rides expose AOC's hypocrisy amid Green New Deal pledge https://t.co/sHI1R3RwRt via @nypmetro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachsyme lol i didnt really think it was but doesn't it look like you! and adding to my kindle list now, ty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay but the actual winner of this game was the sick tie-dye shirt behind the cuse bench]]></document><document><![CDATA[If love was labeled poison, we would all still drink it anyways bc it’s like a damn addiction]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton POTUS is doing 100 percent better than you were groomed to be president while Donald Trump wasn't that's why he 100 better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@relipoli @the_dol @lisabeej @KonstantineinCA @thelaurakoski @avngangel @frankieindc @ChelseaClinton Are you kiddin… https://t.co/SIE2VLKcyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyleeone @StaceyHPFA @SquanGirlsBBall @njbelles @FMasonius @EllenMasonius @TerrapinHoops having watched them bot… https://t.co/bSqZxadJvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: "You know what, I'm only half organized, can we move our 2p lunch date to 2:30?"  My GPS: "You have arrived." https://t.co/XK86gsOlZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_W_White @kerrischindler1 Why do you get such joy in being such an egotistical jerk?  You realize that this p… https://t.co/EXmEE4ie1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LGKITTEN @BretBaier Fry liver till browned with onions. Then put in a tomato sauce gravy. Simmer for 45 mins. Only way I can eat it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalsMLBChamps I’ll be facing that in roughly 2-5 years. Shits wild. I feel for people man. You never really know… https://t.co/LNZpZLiMiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[When that guy’s been talking smack the whole game &amp; you gotta foul to spare at the end...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday #lookyourbest #style #styleblogger #stylebook #fashion #wearhat #wearitnow #blackandwhite… https://t.co/GdRxo8kPNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socalusa @RawStory @NicolleDWallace This needs to be replayed and add a time line to it.  When the Russians were i… https://t.co/yr3DjjDATH]]></document><document><![CDATA[To-Do List  ✅ Open Twitter. ✅ Learn something new. 🔲 Invent time machine so that new thing can be unlearned. ✅ Retw… https://t.co/mG23lTTHGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet the best things in history were created while someone was either high or drunk 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really clowning right now! Loving this second win for Mahershala. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Norfolk State University Dining Facilities: New Food at Norfolk State University - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/cRSI2y8vuZ via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you noticed the Dems are never satisfied? First, it was 1st semester Abortion, then 2nd semester, then 3rd sem… https://t.co/WB6Z1uviEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[grabe Lord sobrang bait mo sa’min! 🙏🏻 after moving out ngayon naman sasakyan. thank you G! 👆🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MillerAngieOTC @OTCedu @ortpcl “...become students of effective teaching.” Yes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friyay!! Everyday is for flowers...✨😊❤️🕊🌱💐🌸🌼🌷🌹🌿✨ | 3.8.19 // . . . #daylilies #lilies #pslilyboutique… https://t.co/JLBOwFTbTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT Nunes, along with my dimwatt Freedum party Plant Lamalfa are the only white Wing bigots left standin… https://t.co/hM85APeXYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelle_spenc @roseymelhill @american2084 @OnlyWhiteTiger @kathy_markovich @ivyjofreeman @BubblesResists… https://t.co/a5rf2hWbp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[girl just rolled down her car window to ask if I was okay bc I was listening to sad Taylor Swift. Women ! Supporting ! Women !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonwpetoskey I was hoping you would post this. I was going to go through the DVD’s when you are speaking, just to… https://t.co/MYcW0PDQv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzie5197 @msmoon61 @keeshond81872 @twittersecurity @JennyBeth326 https://t.co/Xy3rteKphk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne I want this sooo bad!  I so hope I get it for my Birthday Friday! 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for moorecoffeeseattle to be open in Burien, where I don't have to drive in circles looking for parking in… https://t.co/bmntFw6dUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have spent the entire day trying to figure out what time it is. Tomorrow should be entertaining. #timechange]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chickenprincess @paulmac708 Fav scene in Money Pit. And there are so many to choose from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bigsale #globalpetfoodspc #customerappreciation #food #treats #toys #local #dupportlocalbusiness #sale #pets… https://t.co/RZjfTdubhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson You are so right, and you can expand that. “The return of fathers” who love God would change a whole… https://t.co/owcY2uX2Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeanineC @mithmar @T_FLgal @V_Max @ncar999 @lasky_ron @Patti_Sc60 @Mossimo122 @brookesmiga @OutOfRegister… https://t.co/K05F6XemQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[spent so much time in the casino these past couple of days and I’m already craving to play poker 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graue Of course not, but we’re talking about the same subset of people who honk incessantly because a person bikin… https://t.co/u1ntzjUiJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Putin Worst  #Dressage horseman dictator ever.   . Bouncy, bouncy, bouncy bounce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose ABUSE is ABUSE - some clergy clingers go along w whatever they do - this is horrible to do to an infant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music friends, my brother  has written  a  #beatles  book.  If you  are  interested,  check it out at  https://t.co/UoMWwd1wZt thanks!]]></document></documents></author>