<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum @TexDem_Dkos Complete scum who needs to be scraped off the face of our democracy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeHolly81 @realDonaldTrump Everytime a Democrat whines... https://t.co/BTSEKtm7B0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fried Brussels Sprouts at @eriestkitchen are the bomb, but wait - check out that beer battered cod - it’s the s… https://t.co/3BZ0n31MKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon50376907 @winstonCovfefe @PDplorable What's that going to prove? How many people actually do a census I know I never filled one out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherFleece @politico Horrible but true. The dems choose this path, and it should cost them in more than a political means]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagentaWig @SmallsLife Haha I remember now, telephone sanitizing company lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acserrao76 @jonhagedornmd @choo_ek @medicalaxioms @RUBraveEnough @TomVargheseJr @JulieSilverMD @Surgeon_General… https://t.co/YrTNxA8rwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let no man deceive you by any means: for that day shall not come, except there come a falling away first, and that… https://t.co/x2h0JbsF1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I play in a screaming band so that people understand me even less than they already do]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 I had this guy blocked before his tweet made the rounds, so he must have been horrible here for years (since I re… https://t.co/ut0O3FtAdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marymumbler @kikibee 11/10, can confirm, i don't even know how to take care of myself when i'm sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxRRymer @OptimusRyme what a normie meme bro.   i’m with you @OptimusRyme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He should probably hide under his desk pissing his pants while they test nukes.  Like Obama did for 8 years.… https://t.co/djRmeiGgSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the MN Speaker supporting @realDonaldTrump’s agenda and his tweet this morning is awesome. I commend her for… https://t.co/UIASP1zkNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsaacsHauntedB See, I like to think he's Not Huey Lewis, from Die Hard, who everyone THINKS is Huey Lewis 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanelleaclark3 Do it get like a big ass tiger or something😂 maybe even a self portrait on your face? New moves right there🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait until me and Brie go on daddy daughter dates. We are gonna ball out no 🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningBriefing I think having electoral vote to national vote would just switch concentration on swing states to… https://t.co/ypTaeXfFWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats RM Girls Softball on their 3-2 win over Oxnard High today! Spartans Elevate-Together We Rise! WE&gt;me! https://t.co/zbRvPIxPX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time today at The University of Iowa with @IowaHoops on an unofficial visit. Huge thanks to Coach McCaf… https://t.co/lktOb8EWgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@violeta_garac @YalitzaAparicio Y por ende, no estoy minimizando el tema del racismo a algo banal, así que relájate un chingo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only girl i care about is my rave bae . AND I DONT EVEN FKN RAVE NO MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: Don’t chew gum around me if you can’t keep your mouth closed.  Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch and strolling the beach on Boca Grande Florida, GO GREEN! https://t.co/fokLNb8oPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XRays_Insider Sony have the market covered for disco helmets, magic wands and dildos. I would much rather wear a o… https://t.co/9jDMGwZJIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:28 remaining, tied 1-1 but Tigers called for a trip. @mshlamhockey @YouthHockeyHub @MinnHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening day of the HS baseball season for Hayes and his senior year.  Love watching him play!  #playball https://t.co/bcRqCZN5AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for Coach @RobertPerron42 and the entire @CatawbaMBB Program for winning the SAC Championship‼️ 📈🏀🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTomDem Thankfully she didn't spend much time there, but wholeheartedly agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawarma before Captain Marvel, because (@ Sheshco Mediterranean Grill in Grand Rapids, MI) https://t.co/UCscThKuKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are an American citizen, please do not do anything illegal, because you will be arrested and sent to jail. W… https://t.co/BJn2uzbdGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jimmy Here’s all the White light I can muster for your left ear’s health... have you talked to Ian Punnett about yo… https://t.co/vVvIJQ5WIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordy019 @TomFitton @easkelson @gatewaypundit Funny, the same thought came to my mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[who says White Mages aren't as cool as Black Mages. Look at this badass from Super Smash Bros!  #finalfantasy… https://t.co/0FDhQyES0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UdallJoyce No unfortunately not, I was back due to a bereavement, so didn’t get chance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the @nfl Combine comes to a close and this years class continues to prepare for the #NFLDraft some advice from… https://t.co/XWyugTmf0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesonCoop He’s a class act, and one of the few remaining enforcers in the NHL. I always enjoyed watching him pla… https://t.co/byrVbqA9Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sticky #precum #Cum #strokingmycock #cock #cocktribute #masturbating #cumtribute https://t.co/4eWQCjCUf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep on Lovin’ You by REO Speedwagon makes me turn off the radio. #TheSong___MakesMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Q1gFBXkryM Little @AdamSchiff AKA 'SHIF FOR BRAINS' AKA CROSS DRESSING TOKYO ROSE #DsSleeze has nowher… https://t.co/NYNZvJSrhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came this way illegally go back to where she could make things better!  We don't want her here the way she displays… https://t.co/uZAhhHDpnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in tomorrow night on FB Live at 7:30 to hear Mrs. Criswell read a bedtime story to her little dragons! You pro… https://t.co/2BV0vBOAGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lincoln leads Urbana 47-31 with 1:43 left in the third. Railers have never been threatened in this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Aims to” preserve, but actually has no preservation provisions at all for intact historical bldgs or features. Vag… https://t.co/zhfjTNV2Q6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews You won’t even be a part of the discussion by then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacywernick No one else has emerged as a serious candidate (for this election) and there isn’t close to enough ti… https://t.co/xiBTK27uCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump faces legal issues for the rest of his presidency, no matter what Mueller finds: President Trump is likely to… https://t.co/LJPb0dNQJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[our little quadrant in calc def pisses off scafine but its okay bc we funny asl when we bully everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saunieindiego Water conservation is a way of life in California. Good times, lean times, all the time.… https://t.co/cUDliCtP9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone better appreciate our efforts today because I typically don’t wake up before 9 AM 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third option I could just continue laying here wrapped up in blankets like a human burrito until I fall asleep. Mak… https://t.co/SruISfYTSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep! That blown out tire will slow you down! @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/qyO3puPYlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahCRothman @AOC allow me to explain, I’ll use round numbers to keep it simple.  10% of $1m is $100k (Let’s call… https://t.co/y6Fot66TuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_Padival @enn_nafnlaus @PlugInFUD @CGrantWSJ @markbspiegel @WallStCynic Hi @S_Padival you're a huge idiot and I a… https://t.co/BeiJ1qqs39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeCalderon Y pensar que hay gente que todavia te añora "FeCal". Mejor hazte youtuber* , con eso de que hoy en… https://t.co/VWW0VF5VC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanebible @justme2andu @rfmmoran @nancylees @Ehukai411 @KirstenPowers @LLinWood I mean let’s be honest: isn’t tha… https://t.co/kpSORO3fBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden saying America is an embarrassment. Bernie saying President Trump is worst President in history.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @First_Watch - Dania Pointe in Dania Beach, FL https://t.co/cgC3LFizeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please go to https://t.co/EdnU9SIYvD for my latest update on a Major High Winds event this Sunday. Widespread power… https://t.co/S3dZhAzJUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBNation Anyone on here who actually think he’s going to play all 13 seasons in Philly has never seen overpaid sup… https://t.co/YwOF6ZYzMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerriGreenUSA Saying people are devisive who are right about issues is devisive. Self defeating argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cookiehead702 So bad. I see giving some slack especially on like open dunks or layups, but it’s ridiculous. And I… https://t.co/D6QM7db5nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC shame shame shame on you and your inability to post reporting on an actual criminal conspiracy ...DHS/DOJ/FBI… https://t.co/EUtlFVRxzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad things happen in life and there’s nothing you can do about it. Wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esta foto la tome ase ya un tiempo y quería ya compartirlo con ustedes esta vez ya tomando mas serio la edición, la… https://t.co/CxnLxu65tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFienPrint Like... they’re waffles. They aren’t exactly hard or expensive to make from scratch. Had she literall… https://t.co/koBzPwRzq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ltdsoltd @WhenstonedC @TresaBridges @SSG_Davis_Ret @Birdseye1 @CarolGarofolo @intelligent50 @Whichsideareuon… https://t.co/x5D49ZTYVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Boston Museum Of Science.Experience the application of scientific thought.#boston #newengland https://t.co/vq0MppArDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richgilberto U really do t know what u r talking about. The bill Medicare for ALL  uses Medicare as a guide for al… https://t.co/QzkwsNrZHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saviez-vous qu'il y avait 500 000 stagiaires non rémunérés au Canada en 2013  Le débat éternel sur les stages non r… https://t.co/byfolKgYGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the most intense day.. spent the day with my GFS sister because she had surgery, so I needed to watch the baby… https://t.co/rJqbv5jClR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradKrysko @DM_19XX @RedWingDiehards Tank, tank, tank https://t.co/02XFU3aJNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #EastOfCarrboro:OrangeCounty on Hwy 54 and Bethel-Hickory Grove Church Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love watching Russell Westbrook play...  But this was by far his best assist of the night.  https://t.co/kqYeWuDUOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelRyanRuiz Unheard of from top players even. Much less from one who’s yet to prove their worth. This will eff… https://t.co/vPnMB4nRG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaMarcotte 7 year olds are ESPECIALLY susceptible to being told they’re special, particularly by an internatio… https://t.co/MSlAi7Ln1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t neva took a L in my life ESPECIALLY when 2k start cheatin! I QUIT QUIT QUITTTTTTTT , how my whole squad mis… https://t.co/eU9xNCRJDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicaBurton Are you trying to tell us something with the "goatsy/goatse" thing, or are you lucky to be young enough… https://t.co/GntYQMMkjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Será que tenemos de presidente a un dictador en potencia? Parece que @andresmanuel no tolera la resistencia a su c… https://t.co/wkuF388sOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[EOS R I just ordered this beast today, I’m so excited to be joining the mirror-less Family. @CanonUSAimaging https://t.co/RihUBewwcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wise words indeed, which we should all lay attention to. #IStandWithIlhan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello!!! It’s Fridayyyyyyy! ✌️😎💨 That means I’m back at @page71lounge in Studio City tonight! Let’s GO!! @ Page 71… https://t.co/NTjEgjqOYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta This internal/external banter leads the public to wonder just how "out of touch with reality" these folks ar… https://t.co/OU8UnP3ML8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latrobe390 @Steelersdepot He's a bumb turn the narrative anyway you want. How many playoff wins does he have ? All… https://t.co/h6Iz4WMOYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrendPrimo Poor baby, and I bet she didn’t finish college so she can find a good job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of complaining about Zion’s shoe failure, how about @DukeMBB gets athletic wear which hasn’t made in a faci… https://t.co/8qD0ajsnig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashley_quan I’m not a car commuter. I use my car to travel around the city. I don’t  commute. I save hours by driv… https://t.co/neLBcxmLFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy man, he really had a good year on the field too. Gotta finish the job to get the check]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should be arrested I copped so many. Call the weatherman, it's raining @BoroInc Bring the truck around back, I bo… https://t.co/HQCcVVObPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haddy54Harriet @JerryFalwellJr @ArkEncounter Why does a god have to have genitalia?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_vladeck @greggnunziata I don’t really mind if Ms. Flores has a different ideology.  What disqualifies her, I… https://t.co/zs1yixFGsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday everyone.... now that the Sun is appearing earlier!!! Have a great rest of your week!!  Come on Spr… https://t.co/vktaHaJsRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejoy500 I have an actual question, How does the throttle hang on a drive by wire?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aeropuerto Internacional de Chihuahua (CUU) - Gral. Roberto Fierro Villalobos - @omaeropuertos in Chihuahua,… https://t.co/MZVq1XHVBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone keeps hopping on the mustang bandwagon bc of higher compression and more gears 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uncle John Sedgwick, Commanding Officer, VI Corps, Army of the Potomac @ Gettysburg, Pennsylvania https://t.co/E5aDsX4DNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marinaaaa_g I was thinking about that but I would have to get two different kinds 😭 my eyes are dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlyersGuy8654 @Joshclarky316 She most certainly is Tim. She is such an angel and myself and @GG1997_GiGGles really love her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case folks are wondering what my #ValentinesDay card to @TheMCapp looked like. Thanks @sixers! https://t.co/xki1RW3d42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherNut27 right, certainly not due to the lack of precip this winter]]></document></documents></author>