<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IamMbali_M what? no lmao I just thought it was funny because she’s the only person I’ve ever heard say that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home bound 🗺Just over 1,000 miles of road ahead going to need plenty of energy to stay awake!  • • #roadtrip… https://t.co/bF5TMgX4Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching 1987 Duke and Anna to cleanse my pallor from the 5 minutes of current #GH I saw yesterday! Duke and An… https://t.co/hG6j0dwk4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today would have been my Maddie Moo’s 13th birthday. I hope she’s getting all the pets &amp; treats in doggo heaven🖤 https://t.co/3nki34HvkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a stylist, and I don’t really do fashion week (anymore). Turns out, I’m not the only one... here’s why. 🚕👠… https://t.co/IIDVGKImPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be a adopting a baby mallard duck this coming spring. Name ideas being accepted now]]></document><document><![CDATA[ya. 'happy' #womensday to the democratic #woman who accidentally voted and got more prison time than #manafort. not… https://t.co/UMev8aGoxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the #RileyTornando is pretty cool?!!! 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼Thoughts @jacksonrudolph2 🤔 wonder if your friend… https://t.co/7ke1IboozS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought the cutest spring jacket at @TommyHilfiger because one advantage of being an employee is the 40% discount.… https://t.co/xxDooxUV6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate really just looked at me, said “wanna hear a creepy prayer?” &amp; then proceeded to recite the prayer of Saint Michael lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIMESUPHC: “Women are not strangers to adversity” Woman from the audience shouts “damn right!”  #TimesUpHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working until 1900hrs. (@ BlueCross BlueShield of WNY - @bcbswny in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/yfMcWrSvgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cornelldolanpc @CarolinaGirl585 @CanerdianGirl @RadioFreeTom To hard to make your grandson understand that you nee… https://t.co/ajsTgaP3jY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal is the place of dreams. Jurassic Park. The Mummy. Harry Potter. My inner child is so happy. @ Universal O… https://t.co/L1Xu5wP3bL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kiddos in my hood are playing outside right now... at least it’s sunny out?   #wiwx  #MadisonWI https://t.co/atUfVg4KEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s friday and I’m off, if I don’t end up doing something I’m gonna be upset]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so annoyed today , I’m at the point where I’m about to clock out and go home !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never before has a party had the entire news media and Hollywood  at no cost to them 7 days a week 24 hrs a day pus… https://t.co/xfzjwlxlPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all the space you have when you don’t block the doorway on the El! #subtweet #cta #talesfromtheel https://t.co/afNCvyhVWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uy ya casi se cumple un año de estar super deprimida, al grado de perder mi quincena completa, después de comprar h… https://t.co/DcoFDTBUUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Donald Trumps dog everytime Trump tries to pet him https://t.co/tVzJVeEM2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLongWriter @allahpundit We're already among the few countries with the lowest emissions.  The climate is always c… https://t.co/wRXYngSI1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddyharmss @RileyMariee_ when u followed me i was like wait what lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mc_garvin 🙌🏼🙏 “But that's not how it played out. The consequence of holding everyone accountable to low level test… https://t.co/Hp5WGJZ4xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in the name of relativism proclaims himself to be god, bc he knows everything and he knows what is good fo… https://t.co/Sy0UmBSsg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oOParkerOo @realDailyWire @Ellison_utes Social security is not working.  Veteran health care is not working]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurvivingGrady He will also take over as King of Wakanda post-baseball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessMinchin3 Haha. Sabi sa Rio daw safe kasi liberal and tourist city.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cnoy19 and we are off #niagrafallscanada @ Niagara Falls, Ontario https://t.co/nIjVXVQTPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ober is HBP but that's all in the home half of the 4th. Still 0-0. @_arson back to the mound.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamUpRGC @motorcymick @DjRaison @chrismurphys @NannanBay What does this poor Yemeni child dying of starvation at… https://t.co/wreyBwCSDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @JoeBiden Biden… Apology tour 2.0… Shameful old man shameful. What happened to you??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day prose for all Bluebeamers!  https://t.co/JSpZcfVOnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I I want to see these guys so bad!!  Help me out y’all :)  just entered to win tickets to see @whydontwemusic from… https://t.co/gxubYnmLpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gang goes to Vegas. #teamprorer #jackpotultrarunningfestival @ Cornerstone Park https://t.co/Aks12ZR62i]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girl jumps up on the right as soon as the ball clears the fence @Moe_Funderburk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya me vi 😎@atraccionMX @JORGEODEPINEDO #BuenTeatro https://t.co/OpJOVl3rrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing getting me through the week is the fact I’ll be w my favs @pagenkopflouis &amp; @jonah_pester ALL SPRANG BREAK starting Fri]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park Place Apartment Building in Seattle, WA https://t.co/BCMJbwTMQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amobrejas essas pochete eram muuuuito populares em curitiba há uns 10 anos entre os raveiros]]></document><document><![CDATA[when is hbo gonna drop the trailer for the last season of GoT. IM TIRED]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm here for physical therapy. So when I meet them my thoughts my change. But so far, I'm highly suspect😕… https://t.co/Ssvv4IvG1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SWilderTaylor @ssrewind @mattfondiler @SwordAndScale @WonderyPodcasts So I checked sticher and the episodes are mi… https://t.co/P7owtZJC0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKendraHorn not sure I can make tonight’s meet but my health care issue - diabetes- pharm give dr’s free range o… https://t.co/WbLGjRZDZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awiesnergroff @ThingsMSKidsSay @pattersonaubrey @Bill_Huber_ @MaireCervenak @heARTISTatWORK @MrNunesteach… https://t.co/gTvfXLoVFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just how much of America’s money have you wasted on trips to play golf or to go back and forth to Mar a largo? Soo… https://t.co/aPolnofTlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[What takes longer? Writing a research proposal/manuscript or the time it takes to update all of your professional f… https://t.co/S6ekgRgokw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh. Only in Chicago can I finish a long shitty shift and order mock carne asada fries at 5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 Day KNIFE Juggling Challenge: DAY #1 🤹‍♀️🎪😍🔥🔪 YAY it’s back!!! 😍🔥🎪🤹‍♀️ -I had so much success with my 30 day jug… https://t.co/RRMZoti0FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is outrageous! We could really use the support of #LGBTQ allies right now: Proposed Tennessee law would make i… https://t.co/aAQ6gQCHqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgamorin @bugabea @LourdesRapalin @meap1 @MIRIAMROD61 @MIRIAMPOR3 @Nai248 @marieladepaulo @BAlzogaray @nicmit Grac… https://t.co/DbT0KkbYJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your amazing, heartfelt, high quality work @digitaljustine your vision and art inspire me! This is fo… https://t.co/Bha3L5ItaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know the name of this @janson_chris song...but I’m fairly certain we were lucky to have heard it played liv… https://t.co/QmPPTnAalH]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches come to school on valentine’s day like    ✨ 👁 👁✨      ♥️      ♥️            👄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every girl who got flowers today is “the luckiest girl” and has “THE best boyfriend/husband.” Y’all gonna fight to… https://t.co/Cs2eSC8WE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any certain viewer after watching too much of #TheMaskedSinger ...(just joking)-JW 🤣 #humor https://t.co/yynOG3XdGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate a muthafucka that throws shade when he’s mad, like ohhh that’s really how you feeling huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya’ll I’m about to see Lisa Fischer LIVE! (Thanks @naima for teaching me the way with your Music Sermon!) https://t.co/Kid4HZ7fTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These photos of my husband and dog laying together crack me up idk why 🤣 https://t.co/M7uEuQIiE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wtva Live stream on Roku Tv.Columbus,Ms. @WTVAalan @WTVAWeather @ https://t.co/Ddk96H44c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[an update on how she’s doing (:  its been 2 months already! https://t.co/9l8XnOLdc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[6thBoroughBoutique https://t.co/lIfiPwQ9gO Get your shop on like I love the initial necklace and get your special d… https://t.co/pYOdXfMZBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personnalité de la semaine: Clarissa Desjardins #santé #neurosciences #entrepreneuriat https://t.co/R0ceEjSA2C via @lp_lapresse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people tell the world everything then get mad when people criticize them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystinaArielle @executivegoth I hope I have the privilege of meeting both of you some day 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning everyone 😘 @ Forest Ridge, Orlando, Florida https://t.co/57XbSYebZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StitcherSupport I'm using the Web Player, I want to sort my Podcasts into Comedy, News and Music is there a way to… https://t.co/SoyAabw0VW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cellmavin @cedarflats @JHMSparky @badhopper @birrobeerlovers @beerhunter74 @ManvsAle @JonMontag @mtravis63… https://t.co/1o4HW1Cnaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealRozz54 @BrianPaulStuart @MELANIATRUMP @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump I mean, look at her father and brothers. T… https://t.co/bnyaBFKC9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoraHusky It's my first time adopting a reptile and it's the best decision in some time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah Rebecca!!  #Repost @suncafela (get_repost) ・・・ ☀️HUGE NEWS - Announcing SUN CAFE SANTA MONICA!!☀️You asked for… https://t.co/zRG8cUQyxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this is what you call Purple! Glued together with Rick Simpson Oil! #420presents #420girls #420life… https://t.co/Fyn9cdS9tT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump The loon propaganda strikes again! It’s not a crime to write a personal check before he was President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics This was a year ago. I’ve been really saddened when these kinds of pieces are brought back over an… https://t.co/9C1mp6GUGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as you get back up...great information to consider from our own @netlogxTeam"s HR Director @ChabotVicki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get yourself a rocking chair you should not be allowed to run save yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a feeling our @AlaskaAir flight just got canceled due to not being full, which is super shitty if that’s the case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would like to hear from Stephen Beigun more about strategy of sending @realDonaldTrump to negotiate with #DPRK dict… https://t.co/M2X8VSIvkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDPattillo They won’t they proved that in the last election.. fuck them]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 weeks ago at magic kingdom I saw a dog wearing shoes and today at animal kingdom I saw a dog wearing a tiny straw hat 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertcarlyle_  and all the other talented actors and actresses are  missed and all had an impact on our lives mor… https://t.co/wQ7jCvsBQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will try to sleep 😴 one more time 😉... aquaman expanded my sleep by 1 - 1.5 hours from 3am to 4, 4:30. I need anoth… https://t.co/alZjN1hLcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dumb ass thought it was a good idea to do 5 shots last night for absolutely no reason. My limit is two. https://t.co/QSbhGT7Yp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[GYTO Day 1 is about to start and I was so excited I barely slept last night! At a time where morale is not always t… https://t.co/QLNcnzCtbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s tea: Valentine’s Day is just a capitalist ploy for people to demonstrate their ‘love’, but if you really lo… https://t.co/tGxuA3GdbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone talking about how they’re glad they waited for the black air pods when no one even knew they were dropping… https://t.co/BuF5Xidyov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I swear i’m fine I dont mean to sound all pessimistic. I guess i’m just growing up &amp; realizing everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate being a college student and having a full time job. Yayyy for no spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauramarano I can’t wait for your new song! I just know it’s going to be AMAZING! 🎶♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re back in business, babies! #music #cabaret #bigshow #elcid @elcidsunset in #march2019 @allenequincy is having… https://t.co/ywByEkOZ5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is she? #storybook #sessions #classof2019 #seniorphotographer #seniorphotography @ Edmonson County High School https://t.co/Dpx6Hq64NQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adriaanbacker @EddieDonovan @realDonaldTrump @doj @FBI Our president is working on infrastructure and cheaper insurance for everyone!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrokenBookPod She came home from the campfire for Thanksgiving, but she definitely was not the same person after e… https://t.co/bWHai6oqnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEHermanCain Maybe because she represents an entire generation that doesn’t know much about history or economics.… https://t.co/NL8Zc1ZB3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was honored to sing at the funeral of my sister's mom. God made it work out perfectly!!!!🎶🎤 https://t.co/00dAS1ZFqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinDazzler @richardmarx Again Daniel-Do you shower young boys with attention and expensive gifts? Do you have y… https://t.co/eRlyWQYA9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sedan Service Number (703) 459-9666 Call us to Book Sedan Car https://t.co/BgkuFPmX7x https://t.co/xFESBhxOHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChubbyGoddess Lol everybody had Eve fucked up. Especially when she was yelling at Cecily to get out the tub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraotaDigital Lo que busca este circo es un gran derramamiento de sangre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wherry_lisa @JennaZarafonet1 @ChilisJobs @Pad_Charten @NicoleD61188790 Oh my gosh! This is precious! And definitel… https://t.co/MZAnFPXu6F]]></document></documents></author>