<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Westlake, TX? View our latest opening: https://t.co/w0tV5dPyuR #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to go surprise another deserving Midlands educator.  Don’t forget to send us an email at TOW@wltx.com… https://t.co/9RF9YDs4PI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think if my baby daddy get a bitch she’ll understand that I want him to give me a baby and this ain’t got nothing to do with her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayPatriot I was just beat up by 4 anchormen in suits and ties! https://t.co/QfcozWeCns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @FinnBalor @fightbobby @itsLioRush @BraunStrowman @BaronCorbinWWE Love it! #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need me a woman in her 30s who gone take care of me until December when i graduate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys I have NO Barriers for LOVE! I Merely have Proceed with CAUTION Signs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction Prop it up? Fox News gets more viewers than cnn &amp; msnbc combined. Good luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[tag yourself on the dude on the left, distracted and refusing to follow the agenda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You're wrong there pal. What did Ronald Reagan do at Reykjavik? He went there ready to b… https://t.co/8bPikaLZBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniversoDCnauta @whorunbey Tão fácil de entender que ele só quis dizer que no universo do Shazam o aplicativo se chama Capitão Marvel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRE4Life @mlboscardin @DarcyKriha @hodge_jami @hpeine @adamdavid223 @Yloves1 @OlsenEugene @NTDSE @MeganClarkeELC… https://t.co/vr6rzgswDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midlakes will again be the regional opponent for section VI...Southwestern v EA tmrw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nedryun @casey2513 Wow, may the fleas from 10,000 camels infest her armpits, in a celebratory way of course!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend has been such bullshit that I've just realized all I've eaten is some fucking Cheez-Its and two ham sandwiches. Fuck it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @mitchfaccinto and the Western Metal Company 37 team on claiming round two with the Kings of Thunder Wi… https://t.co/j20Zd7oL4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matizaverde @lopezdoriga @lopezobrador_ En campaña Vi muchas obras públicas por parte de la derechaira Andrés Manu… https://t.co/Qcqsdor2uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consulados en Miami retrasando el trámite de connacionales bajo excusas de falta de documentación, te refieren a un… https://t.co/4yQeOxhXsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Religion is the opiate of the masses! Trump just proved it in Alabama, signing bibles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder... what grade level curriculum would this cover? https://t.co/4PLfJpg5bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skillsy75 Hal when was the last time the Preds came together for a game let alone 16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica Buy a duplex. Live in half, rent the other. Set a goal to save for a new home separately and mainta… https://t.co/35NJxNvyXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrentOlsenXXX Trent, you are a beautiful addition to the 8tb family.  I can't even imagine how excited you must be… https://t.co/0AYaby0w2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what is the biggest change? C- in my grade most had nerd things but would often not admit to them.  The younger… https://t.co/E7CnJRAfh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A creative legislative solution to demographic shifts creating enrollment pressures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @lyralawxxx @KarlaKush420 @xoJillianJanson @TheRebelLynn @SyrenDeMerXXX @AshHollywood @lolamarieukxxx… https://t.co/Jm5MctkyRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Nos la debíamos desde hace 4 años! ¡Gracias por la visita mi Pacorro! @ Universal CityWalk Hollywood https://t.co/iyU0a1MOXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbapollard26 @NASCARONFOX @JeffGordonWeb @AllWaltrip @chaseelliott #wheelman #kingoftheshorttracks]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABSOLUTELY NO PROGRESS WAS MADE. Yet Trump gave more legitimacy to a murderous dictator of an enemy state, embarras… https://t.co/cSIkdNdk13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatGirl_Jackie Worst pain ever. Mine dislocated 6x before finally having surgery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CleatEliteAnfro @PaulHembo @Mo_Cain Counter point.  100% of MLB picks will probably not get CTE.   Or a dibilitati… https://t.co/JBjbdARqCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brucebanner5280 @DanielW37136702 @tsnurds @MickWest @briancoxlive You guys are funny 😂 I hope you guys meet up for… https://t.co/HQxxPoUU3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DAmador1793 I’ve gone to the ends of the North East and searched far and wide for yung Rich. Nothing found. We nee… https://t.co/Yo7FY0hUjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DD_Jessica_ UNIVERSA-L        VersAtile UNIVERSE This u note is VA-LUE tender for A-LL debts public And priVate LE… https://t.co/tNSfxxgz2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilmBabyFilm @SIFFnews No, I didn’t ugly cry. I don’t think I liked it as much as you did. But I did fall to piece… https://t.co/YFWWxlAPO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This defensive effort since midway through the first half has been just mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t wanna wake up from this dream . . Model @roxell_photos  . . Photographer/stylist @MikeValen  . . #rose #mood… https://t.co/FT88f7ZWBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys hoops- FINAL- Geneva 45, Wheaton Warrenville South 38. Vikings win the Class 4A Metea Valley Regional title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImAdamHawk #Yo Adam! What happened to Griffey the Astronaut Cat 🐈!??? Is this Edgar DOGtinez !?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joshua_E_Kelley @TrigonTurf Curious to hear how it works. Wanted to try some at HP before I left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HungerFF @FfurryStud Love it and at least he thinks he was being sneaky about it and love you guys. https://t.co/tC9Tnh5P0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 Hey Paulie &amp; your💩attorneys  👇🏼👇🏼 https://t.co/O8RapwHFxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coyle, Reyes, Silva, Barnes, Sands win in St. Pete https://t.co/Fbcv7ums1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put yourself around people who want to be just as successful as you and I promise you’ll win]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full disclosure: it does read like what I said. My intent was to say that Wheeler was the only politician who spoke… https://t.co/oUt0xDF5I3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWildFeathers I would have loved to come out and see you guys but couldn’t but I’d love to purchase a Poster of… https://t.co/hCscXCxmx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyXxYall @JillSchwab3 @KyleCoroneos Maybe. You and I will never know thankfully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods What's his job? What has he done for we the people? What did he do b4 Trump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a couple chase their 2 year old around the terminal at O’Hare reminds me why I’m not ready for a kid anytime soon......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ep. 722: Aspire to No Goals with Michael Covel on Trend Following Radio https://t.co/GjyAgAvFvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your significant other asks what “your song” should be, always say something by Lil Yachty. You’re basically b… https://t.co/SYQFWeCZpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[What grown man doesn’t know how to ride a bike??? #TheCoolKids @TheCoolKidsFOX https://t.co/uIJxF8YL0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#قرأت بأن التغير هو الثابت الوحيد في الحياة فإما أن نحاول مقاومته أو نقبله عندما يحدث.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day, when nobody is looking, I’m going to steak the artwork off the wall of a Taco Bell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eileen176 @RickPetree @realDonaldTrump with his gross blunders, abuses of power in office, and subservience to Put… https://t.co/L5qBkPogFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaOnlyLivvOnce in elite dangerous i am a bounty hunter my ship is faulcon delacy krait mk2 it lean meaner it a com… https://t.co/C8Zw0LZnMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @DashaFuentesWWE @KristinBTate @itsgabrielleu @elleduncanESPN @MissPressler @kayleighmcenany @serenawilliams… https://t.co/tJZuUUbjtE]]></document><document><![CDATA[3.6 plus. It's wet outside. Rivers are going to be full for days. @ Tahoe Park South, Sacramento https://t.co/UQj05Jf2L6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LondonRobinson @Econsultancy @xeimmarketing You have to bring that suit to Toronto, love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will blow your mind. It’s the Marvel Universe with the special effects stripped away. https://t.co/j0LkWS81xG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BassMastrMahnee @sabcdave @KamalaHarris Will gladly take my employees and taxes with me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonConklin5 @StarsUncovered @erinenderlin @EdmondCrabtree @LuckycharmMw @aloettecindy @country_promote… https://t.co/77cQEfkGY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganMerrick @ChrisBonts @BarnabasPiper Interesting. Did you sign them? This is the first I’ve ever heard of the p… https://t.co/GWkuIA9B5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoTheRed @Mobyhaque1 Who would say that . . . So called supporters that were City fans last season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan I just don’t understand why this is even a question. It’s totally unfair to the female athletes when c… https://t.co/tEAdA72Hxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of the fans of said genre/nerd spaces. By doing what she can with the relative power she has, she's democratizing t… https://t.co/176YyZ6xTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Obama, Hillary and Brennan (who used his position in the FBI)  collude… https://t.co/O5nyNqNLgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TankIncU @dfalls1552 @bedevilme666 @harjo111 @mauidiver1 @GaryWalters66 @janasea21 @Stephen57036680 @TodKAGWarrior… https://t.co/03XdZeQs09]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if anyone called @brithume “adorable” when he was 29 years old, or if like @AOC he just expected people to… https://t.co/GoYibA9DJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendanSchaub @bryancallen bring back fighter and the kid 3D!!  I’m on the train]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm very protective of my lady friends believe that. Even if they don't ask for help, I will alway be there if anyone bothers them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcarter73 @KarenPollock100 @LindsayHoyle_MP Michael seems to forget https://t.co/mhNTdmGnCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So incredibly proud of my @ahsindians football team. Their efforts in our new strength class and after school are b… https://t.co/tZ4GtpD5dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. This. This. These actors. En Mexico? Mas Europeo que la boina. Llegan a actuar en Hollywood? Puro traje de ch… https://t.co/47vNefEA9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fruitbouquets the office I sent your product to closes in an hour and the bouquet isn’t even out for delivery. Wha… https://t.co/TnCsqSsTUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lno09281978 @SandiMarie79 @JustPlainT @kyle3787 @JeremyGregoret1 @DragonMom98 @SabreKevin1639 @G_Ray34 @jimmyreu81… https://t.co/42Wpm6rSKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yates 21 Faith Family 20  End of 1q  @abc13houston   https://t.co/tDwoQuoiHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NITE NITE Good Night 💤🌙 😊 Sweet dreams in Folsom, AL w/ @1angell18 @jeremy_voss @cdn_made @runwiththehurd… https://t.co/Ns8wQzQdVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoying this one - Drinking a Dark Heron (2019) by @fremontbrewing at @olytaproom  — https://t.co/KhI4gaEOcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dontshutusupp Muslims will never simulate into your collective or western society. These invaders are taking over… https://t.co/MKzRsJjJaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@German_Titans @AtoZSports take best player available there are lots of good wrs that were drafted mid rounds or later]]></document><document><![CDATA[*CHESSSSH* "Houston we have clear night skys and nothing to do in the morning seems like a good goodnight for a lau… https://t.co/T2bHhOQ5BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peach things that can stand to be nerfed Fair hitbox can be reduced Back air kb could be reduced Float time could be reduced]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not sold on the premise of Measure What Matters that #OKRs were foundations of the successes. I believe it was… https://t.co/Oi7bsqawHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 year ago. Wow. 😱🤩#weightlosstransformation @ La Grange Park, Illinois https://t.co/zJwtck4zLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceLP4NV Wow !!!! Thank you for the correction. That is something I have not seen cleared up in the news. They o… https://t.co/gUP7xupY18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle Early College scores 5 quick points are end of 1st quarter to cut their deficit against @FinneySchool to 19-… https://t.co/zH8YaNgWpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disagree. I trust Lou Lamoriello if he says the right deal isn’t out there. If Garth Snow says it, he’s full of shi… https://t.co/jtUanob3DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SUPERKICKERA Whatever that shit is that blast out the speakers when tomossa arrivals. Awful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leslieberland Thank you for sharing. I've always loved that song and she has a great voice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Physician: Love Thyself https://t.co/OOwgqxJSXQ.  First thing to do is put on your own oxygen mask]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, 1st get a list of claims - each has been proven wrong, each year they fudge data, they destroyed tons of data,… https://t.co/7twnaoUhKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outdoor and wildlife photography at Honey Island Swamp in Louisiana. @gonola504 @asmpnational @cajunencounters… https://t.co/TJZfP7MrD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Fear &amp; Self Loathing in Las Vegas at #geekbowl ! https://t.co/7OHAXcUBtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't that be amazing if GoFundMe was set up specifically to help Democrats but not conservatives? We didn't rea… https://t.co/VVjOqMiDyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is interference, JUST as much as it is holding. Terrible officiating. But what else is new.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met the legendary kennyrodgersthearcticfox so I had to take a selfie. He does throw one heck of a jamboree. @ Beaum… https://t.co/Q0Jgtmd84z]]></document><document><![CDATA[E tenho carinho especial pelo @fredgol9 pq um dos primeiros jogos que cobri antes de mudar de área foi @AmericaMG x… https://t.co/zAvQ4rpj0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skye2477 Who blocked you? I've been blocked by a few rabid feminists. Good times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddya_torres @Ojoos_de_Bruja @islademiencanto @LcdoTrafala @boinaverdeyulin Buen provecho y excelente día Limbersi… https://t.co/JuiVBUCSy8]]></document></documents></author>