<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @captainmarvel @TheRealStanLee @MarvelStudios Same. @ThatKevinSmith My kid looked and said that was… https://t.co/CH2L07sgPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#finally back to the gym. Sick of being sick. Feeling so good!  #gymtherapy  #gratitude  #healthiswealth @ Planet F… https://t.co/V0KmXG33ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Summer That is so cheap and demeaning people who wear that have no self esteem.  No class , dont dirty your hands with that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Company founded by Ocasio-Cortez in 2012 still owes $1,870 in taxes  https://t.co/IoA1e5tVLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KejonJ Kejon my tweet was literally me calling her out not be agreeing ??? Let’s use the brain God blesses ya w ❤️❤️🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@storgovnick @SenWhitehouse sen whitehouse we like you please continue the good job you are doing and run for pres… https://t.co/RgwlgX7RrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMalorzo @moinanderson @A_Badassunicorn @medpepper @witchofgric @Miss_Lulu1 @coyotechic90 @stevie76 @gany760… https://t.co/jE9M3lZUd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my work family! 🖤 #ThisIs33 @ Hacienda Sarria https://t.co/cPFewKCc7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valkyrskuld did you hear? Wardruna red rocks Oct 17.  Tickets on sale Friday 10 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the challenge from @MrsAkhteebo  @ihenehanross to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no rev… https://t.co/Na8mx8QkRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 puns for this morning: -My friend couldn’t afford to pay his water bill, so I sent him a “Get Well Soon” card. -W… https://t.co/lco2bulQ0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBWorkhouse @authorlatrice @CjWalke19139700 @TheTigerWrites @WDFosterGraham1 @Misty_Bridge @PurpleQueenNL… https://t.co/Sa6UebavlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need more friends who like shopping for makeup and getting pedicures😫 I have to go alone now wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god Garrett from Pretty Little Liars is PAOLO VALISARI FROM LIZZIE MCGUIRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InPAINpatient @DawsonInga @SGottliebFDA Well he’s unable to look at the faces of the peoples life’s he’s destroying. He’s just a coward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fbf   Essence Black Women In Hollywood luncheon is always an honor to work on!🙌🏾  The luncheon is always a room fu… https://t.co/ujU457kviJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#uglydogs I’m finding it hard to be as happy as I should be for Blair when Nic is struggling so much! I didn’t mean… https://t.co/3SEz6onAWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remi🐶💙☃️ #chipmunkpatrol #snowdog #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy #lovethemback #petsofcanidae… https://t.co/D5V7T4qv9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful #moon this morning #downtowndallas #GoodMorningTwitterland 😊 https://t.co/212DTKbsN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not fake, I just know my worth , so sorry if you are offended by me 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Please, please, please stop this dangerous and terrible talk about our country's pu… https://t.co/D5kXTujdeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/7YRh8cSmJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pverel Slot racing was thing that helped a friend get over an addiction. 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[What say you, @michaelrkingjr? Could this be a thing? Dogs vs. the hogs? (I’m goin’ with the dogs.) 🐶 #lisnow… https://t.co/SeDpTCHIT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDataGal  Can you help my NYC elementary public school students from low income families  with Virtual Reality h… https://t.co/6JGsveeX2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im in shock. but if I am your Broker for a Buyback, and u have to buy on Bid, wuldnt it be my duty to get you best… https://t.co/V2wWFeEfSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[let’s play the game: is Lily’s flight going to take off or continue stalling on the runway as freezing fog continues?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisduane819 @educationweek @DTITeach has a course and it sounds phenomenal! #delechat]]></document><document><![CDATA[From dance to metal. The two work so well together don’t they? 😜🤘🏻👯‍♀️  . . . . #studiovibes #5150 #guitaramps… https://t.co/wHvfqCs3h8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could you possibly report on progress as it regards to firearm registration, strong and fair immigration laws, and… https://t.co/Ghskwi8jtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTVAJoel @WTVAjohn @WTVAalan hwy 4 west Dennis https://t.co/Tq9WbnQko5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did y’all see Charlotte Rouse is closing? That’s 3 huge retailers in the last year that I know of. Toys R Us, Payle… https://t.co/GvQainrIFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is #InternationalWomansDay   This here. This girl. She’s one of my favorite warriors. She doesn’t tweet bu… https://t.co/njMNv3xi3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mondays are for waving goodbye to the weekend and holding on to the cat pics. Anyone else stay up too late watching… https://t.co/fAsHUspfxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meaghang Hadn't tried it witht he @ just their name. That got me more results but not quite there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy He looked SO amazing; I don't care what Tang Lollipop has to say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We look forward to seeing the amazing pics and articles from the Denver Post that are relevant to the positives of… https://t.co/9vDaBdHPCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday I read to the grade 2 and kindergarden classes at Heatherington School for their readathon. I want to thank… https://t.co/cDdRMFtK4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s adventures included #lotsOfFood and #CulturalExposure #TravelOklahoma love doing life with my partner. Toda… https://t.co/vj15VECi3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarethToGo @MovieManifesto @GuyLodge The press (I’m one of them) may favor certain narratives, but they didn’t inv… https://t.co/Jvmy6Um2zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlairBraverman @JanaKay4 It was perfect... Glory was adorable and hilarious and sweet, and ate a lot of cheese.  W… https://t.co/90Co3WLMWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pop up show for my favorite band, in my favorite record store, in my favorite neighborhood, on a gorgeous Sunday.… https://t.co/vibpZmd4t9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToneOzMia Thanks! I'm trying to stay awake so I can see it from my backyard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @Kaleb_Karr !! remember when you back handed me in the face in 8th grade? ya me too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than deciding not to skip a class because of fear of missing something important but then just watch… https://t.co/xzsrwTE0k5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m catching up on this week’s Jeopardy’s and I’m so proud of myself because I got the constitutional amendment mat… https://t.co/mMLCGwLHmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔹🔶BAHM Magazine Spring Editorial 2019 🔹🔶  Blue Crop Top Shirt: Buki Akomolafe bukiakomolafe  Blue Silk Pants: Ezie… https://t.co/LdEqH6GUoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sovereign_ale @marianahdez18 I really want the @jamescharles palette 🎨 @MorpheBrushes #makeup #MakeupAddict… https://t.co/CdWD7TIT2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CDLouiville19 #CheerDerby #WeKnowChampions @CheerDerby  great weekend with my amazing team💖 https://t.co/5CBI5dSAZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mama long legs 🕷 wearing @xixpalms for @mimiredboutique ✨ | #pourstyles @ San Diego, California https://t.co/JQGbtxuULh]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jbdwK1jHsM created from home cooking photo with Oilist #ipad app]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson LOLDemocrats have TWO GOVERNORS THAT WEAR BLACKFACE, A Congresswoman that said anyone pro Israel is… https://t.co/4I6PeBCovD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see a lot of @MadCoSchools people in these pics. Great to know that our great district is partnering with… https://t.co/8gaBqUPKRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherEdc I wanted to get a pedicure yesterday but my cars battery had other plans for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to Ethiopian Airlines, these are the nationalities of the victims that have so far been identified:… https://t.co/nuEBtN8QAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a HUGE wrestling weekend for so many of our wrestling friends and family from the high school level to the… https://t.co/yj85SzWhso]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always wonder why the camera crew never reported creed to the cops 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sqwii I HATE these analysts those SCOUNDRELS!!! should the debt level worry us @Sqwii ? do you know where buffett… https://t.co/8ouFgWhA8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madison_Rose96 speaking of are you working tonight or are we chilling??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neelyspice @scottykummer @ajoneswilkins Guys. What would you do if someone copied your website, you write them a v… https://t.co/RomrBfAfih]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was talking to my boyfriend about my current financial situation and he said to me, “in a few months, once you gr… https://t.co/NXT2826bd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the last day of Tampa’s #CommuterChallenge19 I carpooled on the I4 corridor to Orlando and back. Dread that tri… https://t.co/CGsXdNZdCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[E. Marie's Southern Style Spicy 🌶 Fried Cabbage🔥🔥🔥👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 #MyPotsAlwaysClickin DM for private dining / special event… https://t.co/aQ8N3wWljW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Got freeze-dried cheeks?  We got a fix for freeze-dried cheeks. https://t.co/G8c1dbpKP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the bigot who questioned US Jews loyalty...and the @DNC said nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Hey.  That looks like an Army-Navy Surplus store to me!  Did you find the BOGS Boots?  Because the BOG… https://t.co/xt8PWRuWFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d0minique_xoxo Lmaooo trust me girl no one wants to see drunk Flo, she a WHOLE trip😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kharyp Yeah. That list of, if Obama had said it, did it; is so long. Unbelievable how the @GOP Ignores all that Tr… https://t.co/GkxENIi8Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was so tired. He gave it his all! So proud of the growth, the determination and the love of the game that he has… https://t.co/KiBflMz6FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FantasticBeasts @WarnerBrosEnt @jk_rowling   Did I mention I’m part Veela? #ElleTheAuror]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StinaLeicht How much joy do these people bring to lives of many, many strangers? I sincerely doubt all of them col… https://t.co/dHubHZFLKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s also crazy to me because two of the people who commented being “upset” about this i met personally and it breaks my heart gtfo pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassChallenge celebrating #InternationalWomansDay and the fact that we are #BalancedForBetter with our awesome tea… https://t.co/ON9cczZYDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Sunday isn’t a Sunday unless your dinner is being made in the crock pot]]></document><document><![CDATA[So why hasn’t @KylieJenner delete all her photos of her so called “BFF” off of ig yet???Cause boo @khloekardashian… https://t.co/nAZJfbttog]]></document><document><![CDATA[America what Cohen said about Trump anyone that follows him will get hurt as he followed him. I believe Cohen on th… https://t.co/jd5DVk7JCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lingling:"Yikes! Felix, did you hear that ? Lake loons calling, frogs singing, crickets chirping,owl hooting, and w… https://t.co/8loscIsMGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valentinifrank About time having Mac &amp; Felicia in Ryan SL people #GH55 @JohnJYork @KristinaWagnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I feel like I’m having s panic attack every time I leave the house. #feelings #gotmemessedup #]]></document><document><![CDATA[SISSSSSSSS he really gon disrespect like that ??!!! 😧🥵 #Alligator #MONSTA_X https://t.co/PzSTF5bkCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWorldOutOfMind Ha! THIS tweet   made for you:  Oh, so you think the word "epistemology" is bad? Well, how do you know that you know that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcmfanclub @JohnCMcGinley Stan and the Highway patrol cop from Wild Hogs. Red and Dr. Cox. MacGruder and The White… https://t.co/kFEQ0HCSXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feria de trabajo! #ElChiquilínTodasLasMañanas en La Grande 107.5 https://t.co/6Dp0gyY1xs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 I would lock him up after this.. totally unacceptable but he will get away with this smh. What kind of world are we living in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoursTrulyTheDj As you should. I know some niggas that say if the sex bad, they’ll leave her. Like damn. 😂 you mus… https://t.co/0rNFaqMevv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Who cares. When those people raised a million dollars for Zimmerman to congratulate him for murder I kne… https://t.co/byKdrboIts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinEff Minor ills I wish on people include: hangnails, canker sores, stubbed toes, paper cuts, gum in hair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep. So I’m just swooning over some of the images from this weekend’s shoot. I mean look at this one...💗… https://t.co/hwPfPO1xfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such amazing talent at Pinoy Voice hosted by the Federation of Filipino Canadians Brampton! Thank you ladies for sh… https://t.co/2fAjx8djFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 oranges / blues and yellows are my fave together. I like yellow and pink too. I like yellows and browns t… https://t.co/OzOwhF47Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Religion  ”You're gonna die. Do you want to have some sort of system, or you just try and cope with it through mas… https://t.co/xmIBm12hiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why people take my tweets serious 😣 half the time I’m making shit up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_C5 @BenLewisAus @YorkshireSmash @Matthew669691 @CarsonGarrard_ @SamTanginoa @JillKassidyy @vannabardot… https://t.co/x4mz4Oqv3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie - The world's most beautiful woman, with any expression. But totally transformed by laughter....… https://t.co/sWf456W9Iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the POTUS doesn’t know an MOU is a legally binding contract and makes a fool of himself on int’l TV with the C… https://t.co/Uq5TboWyLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I watch a JCole performance it reminds me when I seen him less than 3 feet away . God it’s such an amazing feeling ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalemGenseke @KatieCWrites @PIXY727 @nicwillwrites @AlexHarrowSFF @NicolaYoon Thank you, Salem!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lead1225 I don't need any religion or god to have morals. My atheist parents taught me how to be a good and loving person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special counsel Robert Mueller will not deliver his report to the Justice Department on Friday or next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Running behind schedule because I lay in bed doing nothing in the morning because I can’t get myself out of bed is my life]]></document></documents></author>