<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Frank Schwindel’s homer not nearly enough to rally the Royals https://t.co/eL7ka5BD4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrLexJay @katyb_spencer @JimCanto @Howdy_Doughty @GabrielSurfCat @MattJ_O @joshmccormack @jesserker @wheresdanith… https://t.co/d28311cjWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrdcsc This comment leads to a discussion of quickening, which was the focus of theological discussion on abortion… https://t.co/s8TPckEaCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burkeeboy Lol. Remember how you'll feel when you're finished; I mean after the frostbite thaws and the pain goes away. It'll be worth it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontHarrassMe Lol I feel u. I’m doing Jamaica next month. I’m usually in Vegas or Miami those times. It be kinda d… https://t.co/0j7Rb8WboF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since when did Rachel Maddow become Mayor of Lexington ? She hates anything white or southern .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love @colton that’s my guy.  Why @CassieRandolph have to do him like that man smh.   Got me tearing up lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pogoboii31 @k_ovfefe @SentinelVI @doctorcherokee @cenkuygur @Shem_Infinite @petestrzok Yeah but he has SHORT FINGERS so whatever!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Business Insider: 8 of the biggest scams to avoid when buying a car. https://t.co/ix8Uv8k2b4  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need dual monitors this morning. Onloop  Het Nieuwsblad was live for both the Women and Men! #trekraceshop… https://t.co/TkRORowepO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaymesL I’ve always thought of Highway 33 as the dividing line. Anything south of that is shared brewers/cubs country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is the last game for the #Nets before the All-Star Break. It would be great to get that dub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si un hombre ejerce fe, y camina humildemente con su Dios, podrá tener poca educación, podrá ser considerado un hom… https://t.co/pWYhRV1oRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed to Church Under the Bridge. Preachers ng on the Woman at the Well and learning to live in the Living Water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I wake up sweating one more time I’m kicking everyone in this house out omm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSCOOK2234 @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS I agee BUT he got this tweet RIGHT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Jefferson, North Carolina https://t.co/yDGmAe9ELg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aviatorslife @nowthisnews President Trump thanks you for your support. https://t.co/zSaDfD2QA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[51 seconds left 1st half Winnisquam leads @MascenicVikings 23-22 and has the ball after a timeout.  @nhsportspage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Not one of them is worth spit to me. Socialist clowns that want Obama era garbage x10!! Not one democr… https://t.co/YoCe8xKt0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cfraizer Oh my goodness! I really like ‘Starship’ but I think mom had a lot more fun shooting ‘Frightners.’ Not th… https://t.co/8NOLQQXJ0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACClippers Angel Delgado can PLAY.. 20 and 8 to start early vs @windycitybulls #NBATwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Melania. We need to slow our roll. We laughed and ridiculed her clothes and high heels. Said she was tone deaf… https://t.co/t5bs2N5zHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Houston #Quinceañeras Gallery by Juan Huerta Photography prices, packages for your 15 https://t.co/3n0l07A409 Paqu… https://t.co/xlWzUaWxGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrGeneSports @NFL @JoeFlacco @Broncos @Ravens We spending 40 mil on bums at the qb position and we’re somehow gonn… https://t.co/vhmYIkZQdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I'm going to make my drawing in to a shirt... good morning.... @ Tolleson, Arizona https://t.co/dIAtBJmqDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J1MMYMATT Or when it’s raining *imagine if it was colder, this would be snow*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geopolitrending @LionelMedia Almost like an English king on paper? I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth.… https://t.co/7ysSIlPLRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 and I still on mission to live a healthy lifestyle and I just finished another amazing cardio workout Powerho… https://t.co/cVwW8MKNth]]></document><document><![CDATA[My work wifey got me a Valentine's gift. 😍 @ JD Earl Waterworks LLC https://t.co/lHhNWzIIcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLCRichmond @FoxNews @googlenews Don't think so! You did that all by yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we at the point, yet, where our Leaders will stand up to Putins revanchist goals - these are acts of war direct… https://t.co/rbxw10EYQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I've the important things in parenting covered https://t.co/uZDOumLNlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude is still trying to make this a story. She told you directly that she addressed her controversial remarks and t… https://t.co/VS90xIHD3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro We are going to have such massive, massive debt that even our great grandchildren will have difficulty… https://t.co/9P8EzxOckn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USA_JLatini @5b20be6386164f8 @AylaForTrump @CatOnA_TinRoof @AmericanVoterUS @AnnaBel75130179 @ShariGalvez @mdevel… https://t.co/Dab2oNgMn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JUMPFORCE loadout. @Rhymestyle @VampyBitme @EmperorBigD @BandaiNamcoUS @KenXyro https://t.co/i9roRdrWhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GitRDoneLarry Only if you dip your burrito in a jar of cold nacho cheese]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fcoxx_91 Yo skip is wrong we got many allstar players on the EAGLES SUPERBOWL CHAMPION TEAM. He needs to put down… https://t.co/ELhpdvfmna]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just remembered that the last time I was in Los Angeles I found Connor Franta on tinder and I had to go back and… https://t.co/YSflaSQeTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[How’s a girls DMs be after she changes her bio from “taken” to “single”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oralnut @Lickmenow20 @PMarizzle DAMM I WANT A FEMALE TREAT ME LIKE A BABY TOO, SUCK ME DICK TOO PUT ME SLEEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red Devils get on the board in 4th. Williams lead off single, Potwin sac bunt and Highline throwing error, then Pay… https://t.co/u4goDwkGjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farenelli @SharonReedCBS46 You’re assuming I’m assuming. Be patient, I’ll get back to you on the homework assignment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValleydaleSBC Brother Johnny Hunt is a an excellent choice and a great man of Christ @rickandbubba @macbrunson  praying for Valleydale now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jean__Emard @RobertBrodeur13 Vrai en théorie, mais quand les gouv. qui se succèdent utilisent mal nos taxes, éject… https://t.co/EYoXesUzll]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has the @BYUSportsNation Karma. No surprise here... 🔥  That is a BOMB, @jensen_rylee!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterframpton We’ll see you in Charlotte. Oh how you helped a young man far from home in the early/mid 70’s. Amazi… https://t.co/ndYlmfPv1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how people in those movies or shows forget to put pants on... that was me today! Got ready for an audition… https://t.co/JoiAEnUqQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look @TheAcademy Award Winners #Oscars #Oscars2019 @ladygaga and #BradleyCooper stole the show https://t.co/vPH9aL139Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TipsyAstronaut @DS9Doc @IraStevenBehr @joek_j @LSnailham DaVinci FTW! Can’t wait for the @DS9Doc!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceFiamengo The marketing department for razors went with bad, the marketing department for deodorant goes with… https://t.co/snKRBenl5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHarmon_BYB Matt,, I'd like to award Charlie the lost gifable dog on Twitter. Let me know where I can send the… https://t.co/Hw7Rk2IrBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: we’ve made it to the show, hats off to everyone for making dreams come true https://t.co/pBVYCdMWKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @SeldenGADawgs Dear Hoda Muthana I have a phrase for you.    “ you’re outta here”]]></document><document><![CDATA[From our @ingerrandcfm campus in Davidson, sending out a @halfwhistle #custommade #heart #bowtie… https://t.co/4oD8AULDVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLUTD @MBStadium Ready for three points and can’t wait for the rowdy and super loud crowd tonight at MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Clark County Fire Station 19 in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/bpspBuKf2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando empieza la difuminadera Fuocaultinana, a uno le cruje la esperanza.]]></document><document><![CDATA[La carta fuerte y con mucha expectación fue la presentación del nuevo teléfono plegable de Huawei Mate X5G en el… https://t.co/9zYTvGyypa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeathMetalAF @YuriBlataku @GustavoArellano @Smile_Lee @HeavenSentTweet @latimes @NewMexico 🔥 This gonna be fire 🔥 https://t.co/87WJ03qQ7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Sunday turns and a return to the scene of last season's unfortunate end. Felt good to slay that dragon… https://t.co/fDVpHys1fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time seeing one of my favorite artists Chris Lane in Savannah again! He NEVER disappoints when I see him@live… https://t.co/eyF0FSTwLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[does this mean young teens are going to start writing Jonas brothers fan fiction??]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life knocks you down you gotta keep up dust yourself off and hit that shit back twice as hard! #NeverStayDown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Florida Beach Day!  Celebrating eli_the_crusher’s birthday!  We’re doing it up right as well! @ New Smyrna… https://t.co/lIIR08j4TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[And on the interstate I keep seeing the exit to Orlando and since I’m the only wrestling fan here, no one was tryin… https://t.co/yG7GSpGRpQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @KimStrassel And anyone who pushes that line of BS in a national newspaper is a partisan hack.  Looking at you Kim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I was just thinking about things I needed to tell you I need tomorrow. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyGirlPerson You say such nice things, Old man’s heart all a flutter; Hoping I’m worthwhile...  😂😂😂🍸😜❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dungeon and dragons? "Dragons and drinking?" "Drinking and Dungeons?" "Drinking and driving?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another VA shuttle trip today. This time his driving was ok but he had on loud talk radio the entire time.  Was not great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I REALLY hope Star Wars Edge is open in Disney World by the time I arrive  🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAntWright Speed, balance, ability to shoot or pass a basketball on the fly better than most. Look he isn’t a ju… https://t.co/SNey48zMnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexG_III Hope you rolled out, it was a good one. Especially in Dolby 3D.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum @ZimmermanRob @HeyTammyBruce @FoxNews @SenSchumer @BernieSanders @POTUS @VP @KellyannePolls… https://t.co/sYltwucFJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who says the off-season doesn’t have highlights? #fedoraweek @jasonffl @TheFFBallers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @NBA I feel like J Cole got small ass hands but that could be me]]></document><document><![CDATA[can't seem to produce much which is tantamount to high treason in a productivist society, I don't want to accept my… https://t.co/FUhtjeQi8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhbroncofan How’s that... LeBron by far the better player. Kobe isn’t even a top three Lakers player most likely.… https://t.co/tl63xJVGdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouisColeMusic Whoa I hadn't heard that. Damn that's sad. I'll be on the lookout too]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys are a blessing to Kingston #ygk take a look a what they got up to last week. 🥳👇🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to see @GearMadison in her natural habitat. Thank you to the ladies and coaches of @UHCougarSoccer for welcom… https://t.co/ZHSebQE3j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hibillyby @bigheadtaco And this is what the internet should be all about, good people and good doughnuts. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melaninmarss i called back but i believe i was met with “i’m going to bed” 🙄 foh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino - @hrhclaketahoe in Stateline, NV https://t.co/s6t3wFWKta]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irrespective of that fact a disabled sept 11 paramedic being cut with the excuse of I can do light work when I trie… https://t.co/CTMwQrDwEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarynPittman crashing here in NJ. 1 am becoming 2 am. Good luck and run fast. (From your top NJ fan)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as an example of how far our use of words and context has changed throughout the years, the phrase "running a… https://t.co/uqgZVhl2hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching one of our favorite bands at one of my favorite venues! https://t.co/3DvYT9SwZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really!!??? And all of the “Alt-Right” anti-semitism!?? Who fueled and normalized that!? Anti-Semitism is a right A… https://t.co/CjF698D7tO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThoughtoftheDay – “Go after your dreams. Succeeding or failing is not making it to the bigs or it’s not necessaril… https://t.co/MqJK4AvsWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball Season Senior Year was the best thing from High School ❤  Besides the 9 point L at State 😂 https://t.co/jnQztPV2oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've got Joes In different area codes (area codes) Area codes (area codes) Joes]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOPCI Jonesboro did great serving breakfast to the Teachers and Staff at Rex Mill Middle School! Thank you Breakfas… https://t.co/2nVktxpXx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow , if I had admiration for @Jim_Jordan before, now I’ll tip off my hat and proudly express my absolute respect f… https://t.co/BAHKIM6YFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GasLightPolitic Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente SDSU Aztecs coming into their own as tourney time approaches. Boise heading the other way.… https://t.co/upDWMYx22O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self-explanatory. . . #thelifeofaclothier #worK #mensstyle #fashion #quotes #dapper #suit #words #success… https://t.co/WtzQtfZP2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[NPR: Felix Sater, Allen Weisselberg: Trump Associates Lawmakers Are Interested In. https://t.co/ClRhvhheS7  via @GoogleNews]]></document></documents></author>