<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I grew up with parents involved in community theater. I learned to work lights and sound. Eventually it caused me t… https://t.co/1gGiWXplk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP We can not afford the #democratagenda at all it is very wrong!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CFRA Seriously, what’s with tiresome grievance mongering and virtue signalling from Ottawa morning news/talk radio… https://t.co/e9WkMCrOjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the past few months I was going thru a deep depression.. I had lost my job, lost my car, lost my girl, lost my… https://t.co/q8EdzG30sE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlloccaMirella @HEMIvik Good morning Mirella! I hope your Friday is fabulous. https://t.co/ALed0wxdFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BumpyKnuckles In Canada it’s called using it to jail people when it’s illegal and then one day the governments lik… https://t.co/dIjWQsWjIx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frankfort dominant to start. Falcons lead North Marion 17-2, 1:32 1Q #wvgirlsbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darren Smith is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $2,307.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $… https://t.co/kJBgmz9jUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Falcon: Opens 185 S Hibiscus Ave on Hibiscus Island. 12-2PM today. Mid-century, huge pool, 4 bedrooms. $1,85… https://t.co/lTkBESG5xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harryreis @NTarnopolsky @LahavHarkov @seffikogen Just for the record. Disqualifying of Balad and a Jewish candidat… https://t.co/eFhH1iXSoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillCorbett He was a quiet neighbor. Always just kept to himself, officer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a forest industry in Northern Ontario shutdown killing towns but companies still cutting logs putting them on… https://t.co/XwdSZZYlEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Mr President please convene a bipartisan group to fix immigration and a special counsel to… https://t.co/GoWnf0Tt8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spanish warship ordered ships to leave British waters near Gibraltar - https://t.co/YUCpdk89A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darn, cream cheese always works for us. At Petsmart (and probably other such places) they have a crunchy dog treat… https://t.co/SZYXRESCiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast If the socialist left love the idea of taxing people then why dont we do campaign finance reform slap a 40… https://t.co/R9r8yVAUAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fuctupmind @RubyRockstar333 It’s still out there and is being retweeted! Love it! #MAGA2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Would Mike Lindell be saying now that Trump was chosen by God if he had just said no to crack when Nancy R… https://t.co/ofETyWPDgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @OVCSports basketball tourney but hey...a fella has got to eat, right? Hats off to @kmcguffUTM for knowing a… https://t.co/nXn91iBHdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m praying for every Man of God today who will open the Book of God so that the Voice is God will be heard, the Wi… https://t.co/ML5wu8nAK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubSainz Creo lo mismo, pero siento q seria un buen estratega! Me gusto cuando le dieron la oportunidad a Chucho R… https://t.co/PkVgqADW4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianIsSuperRad @itsjessipashia It’s nice to know I was part of at least two of the best days of your life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait 🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼riokid 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇧🇷🇧🇷🇧🇷 . . . . . #jiujitsulifestyle #brazilianjiujitsu #mma #bjj #jiujitsu… https://t.co/0khLoMmzno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5NEWSJoe @5NEWSGarrett @weatherdan I noticed the temperature kinda stopped.  It's chilly with these clouds now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashadWisdom @yoboisin @HarrisSavion On that crooked Eastside! Something you don’t know about @RashadWisdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregXMitchell @Razorsmack1 @above_the_chaos @CCM1956 @77HippyChick3 @Flagwaver11 @RealDocBrent @flowersoffate… https://t.co/4RXi6m0TCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found an old picture from 2007 when I coached junior high football for @tea_titansFB. The legendary @Corbinback5 wh… https://t.co/Hm7u2xnAo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gottawearshades @EcoSenseNow @tretorns @thatcoffeywoman @Greenpeace You do realize you just showed yourself to hav… https://t.co/A7DyAGPzmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 2 more scheduled, please make your voice heard.  Super beneficial! @ Prince William County, Virginia https://t.co/V2PvCmbFxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if we all go back to the stone ages we will not stop global warming and cooling! Only uninformed and political… https://t.co/G7W3zmRF12]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to read to @DarciMarek and her students next Friday, March 8 and I will have some silly socks! I would L… https://t.co/IHHCAJZyXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know Seth you know I have a stick in my ass most of the time but if you see me in Miami this week just know, all sticks removed]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW! Drum cover for “How To Survive” by @OMandM . Link is in below and in my bio! Let me know what you think!… https://t.co/7kpIwpJg3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to get the latest on the legislative session this morning thanks to the #AustinChamber and glad to hear… https://t.co/VrKT1O06oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TviewBasketball - 64 Lubbock Monterey - 48  Way to finish strong fellas!  Finish it off tomorrow against… https://t.co/4LgoouxDrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly if the #MNF team doesn't hire @PatMcAfeeShow ... I ain't watchin]]></document><document><![CDATA[how can one be so ignorant?! take better care of your child &amp; obviously yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janet Napolitano hid out from our little informational picket today in Sacramento. What's she so afraid of? A fair… https://t.co/B5UdsRGk22]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to hangout with my cousin that I haven’t seen in wayyyyyy too long! Here’s to resuming our relationship… https://t.co/2alMxeweMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[State pairings just released by KSHSAA. In 1A state at Dodge City, Berean Academy (22-3) takes on Caldwell (23-2) a… https://t.co/Zae6UcWq4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_pickett22 happy birthday cam🥳 have a good day but Evan is still my favorite pickett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazingatheist The actual conversation was on how to fuck a sheep. You face it towards the pond and slip 'her' ins… https://t.co/VgDhyuxo9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Jean_Phillipe_ @YoutubeProfeser @FlatEarthRT Or! Because I’m not a monkey who believes anything I’m told, since y… https://t.co/5XbcyhGkES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ackenheil99 @GavinNewsom I am in agreement about the possibility of misunderstanding ... I may have with you but y… https://t.co/VxTPIOgbFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[We flew into Sacramento today to get some off site work at the home putting green of @bryce_kvick Turns out there’s… https://t.co/FC9nWuYXBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep Breath, Deep Freeze.  “If you tiptoe into cold water, you’re missing out on the rush of plunging in headfirst” -Simone Elkeles]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess #patriots #offensive #freeagency board TE: ASJ M. Bennett  WR Dorsett Hogan  K. White (Chi) T. William's (… https://t.co/tIjeDXQpsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#batteries low https://t.co/W6mQbOEXWf #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/Oj2NqtTvqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[*actually I said Ant-man + Wasp meets Nick and Norah’s Infinite Playlist because I wasn’t confident the person I wa… https://t.co/hYGvyBYPHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great presentation from @abbyhamblin to start the day on journalism x social!  📝📲]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know damn well everything I am typing right now is being Censored by the left before it hits the net.Fuck you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mathpocalypse I am jealous. Terrible at Pac-man games. Above average at Asteroids ☄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWWings I sent you a message and never got a reply. I'm extremely disappointed in the quality of this double stack… https://t.co/CcxEtwStPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol threw pickles on the glass at this steak and shake! Awesome night for Gibbs Racing and his family. RIP JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBasedMAGA @Vicky4Trump The law in our country should not differentiate on Religion.We cannot condone one relig… https://t.co/nvzHYu3p8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_activeeric @Nickj_La This foo is thinking about next week in rosarito haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder OK just put all illegals in these states.Especially California they want em https://t.co/uVPDIAQRSr the wal… https://t.co/jpf9WmoOpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday’s with Brock the Shepard! @ Mountain City, Texas https://t.co/xP6BLn13ho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChibsRSR Also push comes to shove he can play on the outside. He's fiesty and rarely gets called for penalties. He… https://t.co/CtSaZFPUQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look! Another awkwardly-posed con picture! Back with Amiculus for a second day! @ Great Lakes Comic con https://t.co/uf8wIW4S9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at WDW Magic Kingdom. @ Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom https://t.co/g7JoZ56tlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent 15 hours changing a song today hopefully it sounds good when I listen again tmw! 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your paycheck is bigger than what you were expecting 😪❤️  I’m gunna miss working nights and all this OT pay]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven't had the breakfast burrito you are missing one of the best meals in #tacoma. Thank you for what you d… https://t.co/zFWTDyabIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NBAAllStar #NBAAllStarWeekend dunk contest so far https://t.co/5twPK4qSTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great time last night hosting an amazing event for https://t.co/bG7yP9ggFR raising money for Children Menta… https://t.co/4OAwnz762f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chan_miyanaga @tuujac @BruhReport @EnnisHarmon Electricians and plumbers must receive training before becoming cer… https://t.co/5YYtPbMpvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The miracle of birth right before she board. I’m glad we were able to call for the paramedic before the flight take… https://t.co/tmb5rrWQU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Apollo’s play San Antonio tomorrow for some Sunday football and I can’t wait....it’s like a dream come true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMoreno1015 @LakersNation And it took Beverly this long to become relevant.  That's nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dam liar blaming trump surpporters he’s a F’N liar little sissy pussy that’s hollyweird people of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS is where they REALLY get you. If they can’t get you on that bull, it’s taxes or support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flydownthefield I am! I’ve spent the weekend at mom’s over in Lauderdale County.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday @BrendaGremli Can't believe anyone wouldn't want https://t.co/dEH03uYLJR not want a democracy in America… https://t.co/RNeNFI9I5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol #boysingsfrozen @ Westpark, Roseville, California https://t.co/6dLlDFpWXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I properly used a ref for once. I might write a blog post about it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Your Gratitude is Strong and Constant, da Movement of da Things You Want will Always be Toward You💫 @ Occidental… https://t.co/z9F5JBJ43d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the desk with @AliceMyNBC5 and @CaitlinMyNBC5 through Wednesday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morningside College senior indoor women's track and field athlete Aurora Arevalo (Lenox, Iowa) was one of 16 athlet… https://t.co/KpJ0Dmer0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talbot isn’t better than Stolarz or Hart. Get a defencemen for Elliott and MacDonald! @JameyBaskow @BroadStBull]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whyyyyy are my Iowa Hawkeyes a favorite on the road today against a decent Rutgers squad and I’m going to it from n… https://t.co/7MfbU8fJUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielpavon23 @monicataher @la_chele2 @waraujo64 @nayibbukele Pues la lista sube cada dia cabrones traidores corru… https://t.co/KHaLo0eSQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[She proves again she’s the idiot most people think she is! She is the one playing the race card and using it to sti… https://t.co/B5XpxKfean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner HAPPY HAPPY BELATED BIRTHDAY WISHES TO AN INCREDIBLE WRITER DIRECTOR ACTOR HUSBAND FATHER SON... YOU GET THE PICTURE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[watched the sunset tonight on the rooftop with my baby 💕 https://t.co/XtsmQPEEts]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m a bit more than halfway through my paternity leave, and I must say, I don’t know how people make it through… https://t.co/x6hfot8Pup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronit_b I sort of felt good about this the other night—good as in “I’m not sure this is going to blow up into a bi… https://t.co/Ta7OwP1bKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it's love when she says we will be the cutest couple when we go to the nursing home stage of life!!! #Goals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeaconUpdates Shocking that when we pass it on the break we can convert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caranorth11 @imiancrook @getRocketbook @BethanyLearns @AnnaRoseLeach Did that work? All the writing just went poof?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElenaCardone @GrantCardone  just recently got turned on to your show on @Stitcher and am crazy about all I learn f… https://t.co/qWg6tqPTlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newish, and somewhat controversial, @CDCDirector sending better signals. https://t.co/IacCFHieqm via @statnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Bastardi sounds like the Italian plural of bastard; seems appropriate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon County Brand Stout (2018) 14.7% by @GooseIsland at @zombieburgerdm — https://t.co/5dEqsQqLIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students Love Green New Deal... Until Hearing What's In It https://t.co/8x0oRzRc4Z via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizCratty @Model3Owners @elonmusk @ValueAnalyst1 @SPEXcast @Robotbeat @John_Gardi @SpaceX Probably recycling every… https://t.co/74QO8mCvK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #devil you know is better then the devil you don't know... #Pursue #excellence ... don't let time and age take… https://t.co/fiD69PEkPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeratanden @Yamiche Baby boomers are dying You’ll be a full fledged progressive soon You’d better start working o… https://t.co/FhQf3s8s9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't believe in abortion but this was one time I  would have approved]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MRojasOfficial con la primera carrera impulsada de los #Marlins en este juego y el Spring Training.]]></document></documents></author>