<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[asmr is stupid and the food/chewing at is the WORST. it’s disgusting, just stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th Birthday Coleman! Hope you have an amazing day! Love youu🥳🎈❤️ https://t.co/EaHR752Qv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cassadymcclincy So excited 🙌😱🙌😱🙌 #twd #twdfamily PS. Your doing AH-MAY-ZING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaPustor123 @odyssey158 @LHeraguemi @SonjaNi41294318 @Goddestofhunt @yolande0218 @LiseNilsson2 @ElenaFadeeva3… https://t.co/Jd2f2RbkC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight, furfriends. 😴😴😴  ________________________________________________________ #weenteam #dachshundsofig… https://t.co/HEyLDRwRiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter @lehimesa He's so full of shit! The pity party isn't happening. He can sell the house and scale down… https://t.co/sukaJ2nkUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olga Bauer: Collage of Dreams #gallery209  #gallery209art @ Gallery 209 at A&amp;M2 https://t.co/nscPY10sqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about you guys, but I think I’m going to watch the #Buffy movie with @KristySwansonXO and #LukePerry t… https://t.co/DRsmthxqY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s valentine’s day and i’m spending my 17th year alone. honestly so used to it at this point i’m not bothered but… https://t.co/RAP1bXGlrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[STORM WARNING today continues in Florida with @lakeeriesball! Keep building on the results so far on opening trip o… https://t.co/gRAdHTpm2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me support this campaign from https://t.co/AXV6uUFZ6s https://t.co/lmZXPKciCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are they hiding - what does Trump have on them - they are throwing the duties in the oath they took to protect… https://t.co/VamT9RLBpc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IRONNUMA @mitchellvii @Maggieb1B @gatewaypundit Goober she is. Picking your nose for answers she is. Reading the leaves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDKA @steelers @JoshHarris25 Who’s Josh Harris? And why the heck would it even matter now? 5yrs later #growupkids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTechRabbi @ClassTechTips @PhilipPulley @LFlemingEDU @HollyClarkEdu @annkozma723 @KristenBrooks77 @dbc_inc… https://t.co/LUjIaj0tVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MirusCo @rubengluengas Me encanta ! Que ya se encuentre en Mexico !! Lo admiro mucho Sr Rubén Luengas!!!ojala pron… https://t.co/m0M2ELQWiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was @pertheast 1st Budget Advisory Committee meeting. It was a good learning opportunity for me as a new… https://t.co/bIXFPUMHWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This us how you know I haven’t been to the FL mall in years, there’s a @Tesla store???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s the night where we *lose* an hour of sleep 🛏😴💤 ~ Oh, goodie...😒😏 #DaylightSavingTime #SpringAhead https://t.co/vYuEa3s2fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting into the spirit #day529 #fitlife #ljinla @ FrenchQuarter NewOrleans https://t.co/HmvMAbc7Be]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkimTheRail 🎶Up, up, up to the Heaviside layer...🎶 will mine, Coco, Gus, Mac, prince Charles, Azi and more. Bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son so my teacher fucked up my test and I just had to go off on him , sir correct YOUR mistake]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just started listening to the audiobook version of Kens, written and read by the author Raziel Reid.  I recommend t… https://t.co/98dDLOMJkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dra_oraa @martaxadn Matagal na akong followers ninyo, bilib sa lahat nang scoop at sinasabi ninyo.  But we have to… https://t.co/3elRWKcoV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did my best and my best is enough @TheAcademy https://t.co/oq9C1yUJgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Rob Gray is out with the flu...not good for the Ants, as he leads the team in scoring with 17.2 ppg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joni Taylor gets some snuggles after Georgia shoot-around! So cool to see her family at practice and at the games. https://t.co/eTkMXxvfpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean_C_Larkin I really love Ferris Buellers Day off! I probably missed spelled it! lol! 💗🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[DOG LOVERS: Happy RILEY, 3, AT GRT RISK hrs from now, #nycacc! NH 'cuz growled a lil during bath! He is good w/kids… https://t.co/wH6Sv5q04S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicole1124 @GodFirstGina @luluHru @joe_nuzz @Freedom2713 @TheBestEver234 @wwwillstand @1776_eye @cali_curmudgeon… https://t.co/EMULIvWuo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@km_spanish @KMeKyllo I always learn some Spanish when I’m in there! Love watching the kids having fun while learning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn @XTRIALlive Or anywhere else!   Very few riders in the world are capable of the things these guys do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it actually time to leave already??😩 Have has the absolute best time with @sheldonbeavis this week... am so so g… https://t.co/p78o0G2PoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just read that San Antonio has it's first confirmed case of the measles https://t.co/yXzOMfHIJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We take crazy hair day seriously in my classroom #believeinbulldogs #hlstreasurehunters https://t.co/qZs1qjfkxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeBEST  @realDonaldTrump  @FLOTUS  @SecNielsen  @SenateGOP  @senatemajldr  @HouseGOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday you crazy llama! Let’s go skiing! @ Mt Washington NH https://t.co/g52L603UBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s NOT enough (and i can’t stress this enough) candles in this apartment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianblain Has his Americano and is ready to sing some songs for you here at the dromtaberna for the torontobluess… https://t.co/b1L0BMY4dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay what look at this tweet, i got fucking 6 hours of sleep last night  how am i staying up tonight later than the… https://t.co/kM0vujry6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major S/O to the UPD officer who saw me walking home alone from the library tonight and gave me a ride back to my place ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motherdaughtertime Angie ditches us for her friends 😩😭😭😅🤣🤣😍😍 #walkingonadream #catchmeimfallingdown… https://t.co/1U3HqSf37z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special shout out to @js_ohpa for hosting our send off to @GiovanniQuiros2 https://t.co/uGS8Jcw7ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You need to get a job. What does it feel like to know your crime family is finally going down?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thyroid conditions are literally horrible because you can loose a bunch of weight really fast when you have a flare… https://t.co/DLGqrsfmdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[District court grants stay in @NuVasiveInc litigation against #Alphatec   #OrthopedicNews #LegalNews via @Ryortho1   https://t.co/9QmcPnUAgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t read @adult_witch ‘s “videogame zinesters” book or @BossFightBooks book, read this, then go get those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I look at this photo of the breathtaking DeAngelo Jackson (@MarqDB), I can't focus on anything else.… https://t.co/JVQ1t2wz4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sofia and Melania step up as you enjoy my homelands so much. Protect Indigenous children instead of holding them ho… https://t.co/7KEFFfvlN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle and move on. I'M MORE CONFUSED THAN A CAMELEON - Hipster Apparel - Skreened T-shirts, Organic Shirts, Hoodie… https://t.co/E9h4OzHh2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland After finishing second two years in a row in heartbreaking fashion, and facing one of New Jersey’s mos… https://t.co/Y6WkDQaviO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@My_CountryMusic Out now! @HomeFreeGuys bring us a moody video for a cover of a wistful country classic ...… https://t.co/BEgxDfMoF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The number 1 thing that puts a person with diabetes at risk of complications is having diabetes. #t1d #livebeyond… https://t.co/dzrWEuAVSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SavageSunday. @ChelseaLuna18, @JamesTheFAM, look in the background. This is from your livestream earlier tonight.… https://t.co/pFV3YJd5wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed with these shoes! So comfy and they go with everything. ❤️ . Shoes were only $10 from @bcftweets 👠 .… https://t.co/Wp8UHH3YXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Huntington Hospital Cafeteria in Pasadena, CA https://t.co/hU5eUWrMyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[- rolling back acquisitions will result in undoing the efficiencies and conveniences of vertical integration - look… https://t.co/Mt02dNgs8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IdahoLark BTW, I got it treated quickly after I noticed a bump on my back, and it turned out to be a relatively mild case, thankfully.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustMuteMeNow @nowhitenonsense I saw no point in that movie in which a white man saved a black man. I think it was the other way round]]></document><document><![CDATA[CHAMPIONSHIP SATURDAY  Girls High School Hockey   #1 @Mercy_Hockey vs. #2 @GPSBLUEDEVILS  3:15PM Great Lakes https://t.co/BXfNL06U5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oprah @GayleKing @SRuhle @cla_re_p @emmplouch @MPCelina @morningmika @maddow @JoyceWhiteVance @Mimirocah1… https://t.co/Imc87sgRjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a bad habit of forgetting something at absolutely any function I go to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HazEdStyles94 @HSHQ @KaceyMusgraves @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter @goop maybe her little publicity appearance on SNL backfired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmcanasv @diaz25643422 @RMpsco18 En las malas es cuando hay que desgranar los problemas, buscar dónde está la raíz… https://t.co/wPDUo6Wvno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamYouTube @BallingerMom @YouTube @YTCreators @PhillyD Thank you!!  Policing of inflammatory propaganda needs to happen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinseyZG @ChazCasual When eyes reach the slit level that you wonder how anything is visible #LeeConquersAForty]]></document><document><![CDATA[America, take note.  (And I highly suggest you start watching Peep Show if you haven't already) https://t.co/IhiiyvD1XB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benjaminkcuevas @hugh_h @beyourbird Hahahah so good of you to not take credit 😂 this is before any of us were frie… https://t.co/6zVi3474u7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The penalty for treason is death..... lesson to learn so it NEVER happens again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a feeling  that Harper  wasn't  going  to come to Cubs. Not too worried.  They'll  be fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanleyRoberts Trick question. There's only 28 days in February. And I'm not allowed to drink for medical reasons.… https://t.co/No9Jgwt8jD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cujoknows 2.5 hr flight to Denver. But are there any flights at this hr? 🤔😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop Spanky needs new crayons, the latest coloring books, some cartoons on CD and some snacks to keep him occupied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookw0rm79 I don’t even believe you’re older than me lol You don’t look it from your picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand a person who don’t understand when they wrong and try to place the blame on someone else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMFifthCircuit Right? Where in that form would one put any description, other than of the judgment or order from which the appeal is taken?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bingewatching #leahremini #scientologytheaftermath with keitha.johnston and I just couldn’t get this comparison ou… https://t.co/OmagMQH9r1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foodallergyuk @iris19jones @amymaytrust @freefromfarm @GemmaEvans Agree that its important policy makers understan… https://t.co/ykOl1rhGEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTomReed you’re on the slippery slope with Trump. Get off the Ways and Means committee. Your character does not… https://t.co/I3aEoD93D0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broadcity @nbcsnl it’s time u have these talented queens host ur show !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m texting my mom and was like “thanks for coming to my ted talk.” and she said “you didn’t invite me to your ted… https://t.co/rnFYzGG8Q5]]></document><document><![CDATA[All signed up for Christian mingle... User name: SaintInTheStreetsSinnerBetweenTheSheets... Oh, wait am I doing this wrong? 😂😂  #singlelife]]></document><document><![CDATA[That 3am coffee. Yall I love what I so and u should too. Dont miss this opportunity put of fear. Let's so it now 💍💍… https://t.co/Yhr9jW8Ttx]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the shoes and half the clothes I have, my husband buys it for me because he knows that I won’t spend money on it. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinVerlander Happy Birthday JV.....I'm thrilled for your success, but I still wish you were throwing the heat f… https://t.co/FJMtT5wted]]></document><document><![CDATA[my jersey clients really are so loyal 😍 I’m dead booked the 9th &amp; the 10th. &amp; sorry babies, the 8th is a me day 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 I can’t imagine any dog who would enjoy any time with that son of a bitch. Apologies to female dogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even more interesting is that I have no money and they ain’t coming to Texas?? BYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey @AlejandroStyles @MizunoFootball @RondaRousey I loved the attire it looked badass just like you are ho… https://t.co/XAe38CgNTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daddieant13 @ryanveryawesome @BuzzFeed I agree that it is sad and I don’t think that the majority of men are evil… https://t.co/vLUnxeDjsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this money I’ve been putting in is only being taken away from me trying to get my new car 😭 #overit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mk11 story mode looks amazing!!!!! Can’t wait!!! But looks like that leaked pic is real after all so here’s to hopi… https://t.co/4oTbxxPJjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you can’t tell if somebody is a hobo on campus or some crusty college kid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I went to the rr in spank it was guys and girls in the same restroom with different stalls maybe America needs… https://t.co/dNCL7gSpHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that naturalized citizens should not be allowed to make and pass laws. Think about what has been past by th… https://t.co/i3DJ4cflVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a wonderful evening @ElmwoodDotCa counting down 100 days left with our grade 12 students. #makingmemories]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who use ellipses instead of real punctuation are either incredibly lazy or love indecision. Or both.   No on… https://t.co/rS4jkqX9kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cheerleadersvsband #cheerleadersstillwon #cheerliketheresnotorrow attucks_cheerleaders @ West Lafayette Junior-Sen… https://t.co/efJsFmbjmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissasArmy Many prayers for @MelissasArmy She shouldve never been charged! So many others in prison over the jun… https://t.co/q9yxAjDLA8]]></document></documents></author>