<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@guberrocal @salkinstitute En qué labo? (Pues deberías venir a visitarme lol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thankyou muscletech for all the #help #32lbs of #leanmuscle in #90days @sx7revolution #test4k #claelite… https://t.co/hlMmkzK9Tw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Currtis25Harr actually Nia and Tamina winning would not be that bad of a thing plus set ups them vs bailey and banks at mania]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diarioas Y que ha dicho de la habitual vulgaridad de @Simeone ? Una verguenza del deporte mundial, debe ser suspendido]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarwoodUnion wins first playoff game since 2013 4-2 over @CvuAthletics Lilianna Ziedins with two goals, #vtplayoffs #vthshockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the transformation and meltdown of Antonio Brown, how could you ever invest in him? TV Shows, Blond mustac… https://t.co/m4ckUETAj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edward Little rides Gipson and Maiwen to regional final @ELHSEDDIES https://t.co/2JzuuGAu9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdriscoll03 @PeterCooper Agreed. Without the cash infusion, it may not have lasted another 2 weeks though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveePena im sure im late on asking questions u to @FilmGob  but all this talk of justice league and justice leagu… https://t.co/V1NJqNsEG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielFLacy @jwgiglio Good thing screenshots live forever... https://t.co/i0onlUun1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[You didn’t grow up in Chicago if you didn’t randomly get Pulaski day off school for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, she says she thought Joe was a clown for the alleged sweatpants incident, yet went to seek his council when she… https://t.co/p5BoZDM96Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CP0031 Thank you for being a kind and caring man.  The compassion and love you have shown the Anderson family is w… https://t.co/0e3X6WTjf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does it still function. The NEWEST phones automatically start malfunctioning when a newer model is announced. S… https://t.co/6kx0p91fsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful 🙏@TheEllenShow  @CaptPaulWatson @Seasaver @FLOTUS @GMA @NatGeoChannel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished #KingdomHearts3 today.  I feel like that’s an accomplishment worth Tweeting about because as an adult, fin… https://t.co/D3UVe4FqcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be silly. New twist for #TheBachelor a la Survivor. Now they are going to bring back some of the girls in a j… https://t.co/f1mkkyGBni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitlockJason Youre being disingenuous at best saying you want him back in the league. Stop it]]></document><document><![CDATA[And who would’ve guessed this Dunn and Del Zotto line would be scored on?? #stlblues]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMotivation If it ends in -day, it's a battle to be won. So, win something toDAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 BINGO of the decade,but already known by myself and others. 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGWylie I’m literally *cackling*!!! Ranch on everything omg! My sister also puts French dressing on her pizza.  LoL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devin's highlights from last weekend's Tournament.  1st Place 10th grade division. 🏆🏀🥇🏀 https://t.co/EnZFLtr9mS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone I know in Chicago is thirsting for summer like I’ve never seen. Summer 2019 about to be full of nothing bu… https://t.co/nOf78uqWdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the gym today to get ready for the @WACsports basketball tournament 🏀 https://t.co/hMZkDEmLMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure those are two different kinds of shield... https://t.co/nw91rPN65u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MombaPatriot @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Time to stand with Trump❤️🇺🇸So who will you elect for your next President 😡🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, goes to show that ignorance is bliss, and that bliss will end the day it affects your dumb ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilyseh @stephgracela You are totally wrong socialists creeps . You the murders democrats are killing babies and th… https://t.co/q4XXGxvsza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarencehilljr Same old 'Boys, thinking one helmet at a time instead of spending to create a mosaic with interlock… https://t.co/Rf3aVw3UTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino How ironic, on the day William Barr is sworn in as AG, that the Mueller Probe is wrapping up.  Can you say 70M$ audit? 🛎]]></document><document><![CDATA[The milk delivery into the little box at the side of our houses was a great idea. Why did we stop? https://t.co/GdNz4s7OZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebindley @ErinMayeQuade didn’t read the article but I read the thread, and this is what we were talking about… https://t.co/DyJD7RZFcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanaWeingartner If you ever want to do a story I can get you in with our CEO Dr. Jeff Bill here at Sunrise Treatme… https://t.co/DwGcZd9nQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tradition continues this Sunday on @WKBW. Please consider a donation to help WNY kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna be Gamo's BFF?  Its easy... lol. #gamo #quaks #k9 #GermanShepherd #Love #california #cali #beachlife… https://t.co/qRomeIVVNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning New York, time to seize the day #CarpeDiem #Meditation #MadisonSquarePark https://t.co/lp1IJ9xeBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #NBA not having @DaRealPetey doing the #HalfTimeShow is an absolute travesty #AllStarWeekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Weed and coke deflation rampant- demand at decade long highs - Donny working for the American ppl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@va3ks @MT9345 Wait. They salt the sidewalks? Goddamn things really are better up north!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apartment Transaction Alert: San Jose Apartments in Jacksonville, FL on Smithfield Rd just sold #multifamily… https://t.co/8JibWzRvez]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Soulja boy said "Yeah Yeah Ka-Boom" I knew I lost all respect for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escucha este episodio de mi podcast, TecnoNews, TECNONEWS: PRIMERA TEMPORADAhttps://anchor.fm/edgarmendoza/episodes… https://t.co/zzhzLHliQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaranjaKeita @leftistcritic @carrielogo @Wekhevixwaz @asia_vs_life @mpixelpop @ZakiyaChinyere @ZalUIbaorimi… https://t.co/IwyZtwPy9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally did a #DrunkenCollegePizzaReview while hammered 😂😂 Dominos should not have gotten a score that high and how… https://t.co/D8iLXfnAaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Firehouse Subs in Florence, KY w/ @cincy_kat https://t.co/KyT1CdibLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNNFL @AdamSchefter @SportsCenter @JFowlerESPN I do not who else to tweet but please, please give this man serio… https://t.co/9ENrfi7Oer]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all gotta pay attention to the shit happening in Venezuela . that shits sad asf and no one’s talking about it🇻🇪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every organization must establish a “farm system.” Establish partnerships with organizations and institutions to de… https://t.co/TIKR5A4mUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curve of forgetting, wait what? @lead4ward #DHSthink2019 https://t.co/mzKdZ4MePf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Is there anything normal with any Democrat that's currently running for the Presidency ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwittsMcGee The area where I am is really up and coming, by the new outlets, ferry, great food etc. I am soo Brook… https://t.co/cgvBIcVtQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triste e desanimador ver esse vídeo do Fellipe Bastos. Uma porrada de motivos para gastar o Fluminense e os caras c… https://t.co/itWw1uZcgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pepe1807 @Excelsior Decían nuestros abuelos (que sí eran sabios): "del dicho al hecho, hay mucho trecho".]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm following the original disclosure timeline for the iOS Issue. Before anyone asks, no this won't "give you jailb… https://t.co/apacEQTp51]]></document><document><![CDATA[She dressed like a velvet piece of cake and if anyone one ask for a piece I’m going to blow out all the candles. CR… https://t.co/7wLxGDvsYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMikeGreen54 Sorry. Back for a few days with no retraints on my smartassedness. 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united thanks to this delay on UA 1802 my connection window in Denver to Detroit is now 0 minutes, with no updates… https://t.co/auFwWg8Lxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diego Sanchez defeats Micky Gall by TKO in the 2nd round, on the  #UFC235 prelims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summershamrock @Kieran_IsAGod @BeckyLynchWWE The problem with that is everybody knows the four horsewomen history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessibabi69 I just feel like YouTube is so easy to get away from just child shows I’m not gonna even try to lie an… https://t.co/Co3vzmAuqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#streetart #losangeles #artsdistrictla @ Arts District of Los Angeles https://t.co/lEekavDfAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesWoodson @Raiders @AB84 @TankLawrence @NFL Nick Foles.  Antonio Brown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @bracketdan @NotJackKemp - Hey 2 years ago when we were visiting schools for our daughter she wanted t… https://t.co/4MNYZqXDUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradhoylman  KNICKS OWNER - YEAH 50 MILLION DOLLAR TAX BREAK - NO SOCIALISM HERE - JUST PURE CAPITALISM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great combination of two organizations that make affordable housing a reality in Tampa Bay.  Thank you… https://t.co/bBTUj5W1pE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsjo12 @grayduckvodka @chadgreenway52 @insideedgegolf @Rwheeler13 @Bogeychoi Let’s go!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[who gave Himself for our sins so that He might rescue us from this present evil age, according to … https://t.co/Ah4x5gcY7W RESCUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of Liberals are looking into #pizzagate for the first time thanks to @JustinTrudeau upsetting the apple cart… https://t.co/u4cT3UeOx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigdickgothbf I’d tell you that your a pretty boy when sucking my fat cock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In one sentence Alex Jones defended himself from saying Sandy Hook was fake and that aliens are making animal/human… https://t.co/eVlj7nyGZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whoadon #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/jkCsoKQ5ux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting to roll out @MicrosoftTeams at our workplace and really liking it so far.  I do fear the built in meme-gen… https://t.co/AKBZbH4665]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias por lo que me tocó. Por eso todos en la casa te amamos y respetamos!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[t doesn't take a genius to be a troublemaker. Soros is a troublemaker. Their pie in the sky ideas will remain pies.… https://t.co/vd5WzDd40C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRUNKKZ3 Is there Rank cap news? A lot of people are wondering when it’s going to increase to 150 or more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelthedisciple You have to first define with clarity what the argument is, because what is not clear is the subje… https://t.co/X68j16v69S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Is it possible that @realDonaldTrump hired a private investigator to get dirt on the complicit republica… https://t.co/kNZtXVuXqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lahiem11 @PeterB1tch47 @BGSU_Hockey Yo man, this username is a bit messed up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very big heart. Arteries and veins coursing in fat outside the heart. A reminder. Take care of that miraculous or… https://t.co/NvUdGMw2mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always have ptsd of a highly ranked Purdue team going to Minnesota https://t.co/TUBqpRcWyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[(prediction) 4-1 #Sharks .. I'd be shocked if #Habs win tonight .. and it's a whole less fun watching w/out the kid… https://t.co/82cVDEHZj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTV_PowerPlay @Puglaas I don’t understand the 9000 jobs comment...these are just Government contracts that would g… https://t.co/sRnv2VcydT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michael_nielsen Incoming flux is all net inward flux, not just that incident from the sun. This increases with the… https://t.co/jV43WChd8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple donkeys from today!!!   Tried a new area and caught some toads.  New #dockside 📺 coming on this fun windy da… https://t.co/0e97JonXP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019年3月9日星期六晚上9点，中国民主党在纽约时代广场进行第421次茉莉花行动，抗议中共腐败暴政，声援大陆民众抗暴斗争。 共三十七位党员参加今天的活动。德国电视二台对活动做全程拍摄并对王军涛主席进行采访。 https://t.co/c67xnQY5Ah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw @kathygriffin heading into LePolitique. #love #fucktrump #imwithher #firecrotch #imnotmadaboutthis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinche @mateus cuidado con mi @jeremy_menez187 le pegas con el Valero y me lo hubieras  lesionado otros 4 meses, cu… https://t.co/HJu0FmSiCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day with fire and tea! #studioremington #remington #baltimore #waverlydarkblack #bars #firegood #snowday @ Stu… https://t.co/A1iMg4HDps]]></document><document><![CDATA[So there’s a mysterious number that keeps calling me and leaving this message “Shame in you christopher. You forgot… https://t.co/alfpbeQaT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 2 of our Donut Falls winter hike!  The reward of pulling a sled up a mountain is riding it back down! I was re… https://t.co/IwxKbMhp3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[If saving the world is a “purity test”, it’s a test we all need to take.   @rgunns and others have done fantastic w… https://t.co/LvlVGusN2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulioCNav De hecho nadie esperaba nada de esas peliculas y estan buenas jajaja yo voy al dia con esas, lastima de… https://t.co/EUPFrm8PrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nico_w1992 @latimes Probably depends upon a lot of earthquake factors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Video of Donald Trump Forgetting Melania Outside the White House Is Highly Akward https://t.co/AlsbTxz6sA via @Cosmopolitan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metterò te a guardia della mia ingenuità... #falcong #newjersey #wof #blackwolf #americanwolf #symbiosis #wildman @… https://t.co/oxVwZebxYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blog Post #10: Today’s post is from Theresa Christensen. She’s a colleague I first met when we were hired as admini… https://t.co/wODoiaaz9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeBierman We're all so proud of you Gabe. Things spread around here quick. Alot of good people were following yo… https://t.co/JI5qkLJ1kr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My opinion: She thinks she is Nancy Pelosi. Off her rocker. In the toilet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeejayOttley @chloknightxx Number one cause of death for women until 1900]]></document></documents></author>