<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Cause a ripple effect today with your one small act of kindness @spasailors.  Get inspired by The Sanwich Man!… https://t.co/QuXyC381fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felinefine11 @JuddApatow That’s what I thought. Someone who worked closely with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impactful. Worth your time and reflection. What Poverty Taught Me About Being ‘Too Generous’ by Kristine Levine https://t.co/SxPLiHj6pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethanne_132 @Starbucks No it’s literally made with all foam it’s gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LLPOS When does the next new episode of criminal minds come on please sir. I’m going through serious withdrawals. https://t.co/d1VCMiTaXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[the struggle of having strict parents while having friends w/ lenient ones; i can’t go out at any time given. yes,… https://t.co/i9XmfK72sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSchlemmerWFPL One is free conference and one is not. If I’m missing something, I’d love to be corrected, but I do… https://t.co/U7bnOOkGvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle The only saving grace,as a funding bill it outdates with the new fiscal year in Oct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I’m rly sad bcuz this is the closest I’ll ever be to the dudes ever again especially because I can’t bloody fi… https://t.co/WhsggjJq1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Mao &amp; the frosted trees... #MrMao #CatKing #HummingbirdRanch #LionAtHeart #frost #trees #frostedtrees #cats… https://t.co/vvnOA6Kw5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hi, nice to meet you. Dr. Leslie Berntsen, sentient archeological relic.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experience healing pleasure,Enjoy our magic touch,relax your mind and body with well trained girls and free warm ta… https://t.co/2v6l2DqOKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregpmiller @SethAbramson Yawning..lying to cover his ass...where are the TAPES??? He said She said is BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if it tests my father or just my mother. My mother's family is from Tennessee Western Virginia.  My father… https://t.co/Y42ZIt21sR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertdunlap947 @Maggieb1B Bro “Will Bottom”.......is the most made up name for a gay dude I have ever heard 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlatomsmd @realDonaldTrump Withdrawal of life is murder! Look it up in Webster’s dictionary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Rainforest Is Not For Sale https://t.co/uYqQ2qvG7H #WaoraniResistance via @AFrontlines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super cool day at the capitol for #Techday with @Cherwell. Hearing @jaredpolis speak about blockchain and learning… https://t.co/zZbKhjSpep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate people who say shit like “food makes me happy” .. nigga duh everyone likes food]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anitagill_gill @LeanneMcQueen1 Who would not do so for such a good baby?  You are a good mom/dad all dogs need a l… https://t.co/83abppFTdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaureenRedig I always refer to my loved one as my son or by his first name. He is my beautiful boy first ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hidden_Flaws_ Nah girl call them up! Tweet them and you’ll get free food]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harry78278936 Hi Harry, this is regarding some T-SQL basics/ refresher right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been passionate about the importance of the education of each student. I love working with young people. I l… https://t.co/EB879mm4p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @GOPChairwoman You don't stand for life or humanity when you won't pass background checks in the senate. You d… https://t.co/ZC18IJjG4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Because I haven’t found my sound yet, I’m still experimenting with different sounds...” https://t.co/sViQp8ec0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapping up this three game road trip for @UVMwbb in Durham tonight! Cats already snagged a 9 point victory over… https://t.co/65LwyeARah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjnichols @WarwickRaiders @nnpscte @NNPSYouthDev @jasonhollar I’m in awe! She’s making it look effortless🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a great day to runDisney! 🏃🏻‍♀️✨❤️ . . .  #runDisney #PrincessHalf #FairyTaleChallenge #19point3 #DisneyRunner… https://t.co/e38E5Us548]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@PathtoRead is offering a new workshop in May! If you're a school leader considering implementing PRESS, this is f… https://t.co/FvjtARyWsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really amazes me how dumb people on Live PD are. You have no DL and yet you wanna drive around with a whole lot… https://t.co/644bGHt98Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh the idiocy @KittyBhagat @BlakandBlack @lilith2u @progparty @haloefekti @ChrisFDonahue @cliffpotts @Communista2… https://t.co/5eLph1a6CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@japastu @TheRealStafford @GHFantasyEvents Lol!!! You are too funny I bet your wife has lots of fun with you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMillerTime_6 i love that you and kaleigh support my lifestyle. true friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night at the @ChickfilA  Avalon for Spirit Night celebrating #ExceptionalChildrensWeek!  😃#community… https://t.co/a5Dwqk3rMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theeagle Thanks for your diligent fact checking. I appreciate quality journalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima be mad if I wear some shorts &amp; a cute shirt for today and then later on a damn cold front comes in 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite, but most exhausting holidays! 💞 #ValentinesDay2019 #FREOwls 🦉 @FreOwls @CitrusSchools https://t.co/VOrF5olyUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the prophet went and stood by the road waiting for the king. He disguised himself with his headband down over… https://t.co/7X1LKQf4MT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/gMuqw6lDhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even though I FaceTimed Cindy for an hour and a half last night I still miss her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Please hurry and arrest this asshole and charge him with Treason! We have a Russian agent in our White House!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m seriously having such a bad day. Literally the only good parts were my nap and getting my impressions done for my alingers surprisingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @izadaisy1 @JohnHookfox10 @sxdoc @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Well thank God our fore fathers had t… https://t.co/rS4iWiUg5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @mremmulp But they want to confiscate regular citizens guns?]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭😢💔💔 #I_miss_my_grandparents_💔 @ Mandaree, North Dakota https://t.co/Y6T30rPetZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to @GayleKing - I've been critical of Gayle in the past, but she rocks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahora resulta que la responsabilidad del Estado recae en periodistas... Vaya vaya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MirunaGrety Alright class! Let’s see if I can show this in class today without crying. Bets anyone? #SMMLU19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movement is like the best song-compliment. It’s a modern devotional, full of religious analogies and powerful verse… https://t.co/iHADoiALjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you have a phone if you ain’t going to answer my dang calls like biiiiitch answer !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @RepDarrenSoto Being afraid of gangs and domestic abuse is no reason for asylum - it is not persecution fr… https://t.co/h45QezqQeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indian River County benefactor Ken Wessel arrested as part of Florida human trafficking sting https://t.co/C85XAkPT5W via @tcpalm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaneKpack Your house is quite obvious, my friend.   Also, I miss my labels at Pearly’s. It was one of my best label times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share your thoughts with Beto on the issues that are important to you: https://t.co/OK6GcbrGnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriousAllianc Continuing to send prayers, prayers and more prayers and hugs and lighting candles. Love you all.… https://t.co/rcBVPpU2BJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danabrams @9P @AETV I’ll have to take a shower before #LivePD starts so I can immediately get in the bed when it’s over ‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Journalist Jorge Ramos and his crew detained after interview with Venezuelan President Maduro  https://t.co/S8rcdA8vdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mildly critical language still being used to calm black people because our lives are two for a penny, will not… https://t.co/CUVmwRua5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Maybe hold your disappointment until when ALL the FACTS of this case are known?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it a play thing to do the thing where you're almost always talking about two things at once?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been challenged by @JoshRay711 to post 7 covers of my favorite books, no reviews or explanations.   I will t… https://t.co/N4oXyYNTPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I still cry over my dad...  I really just wish I could see him again, hug him. Half of my heart left… https://t.co/54cIppxAhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy said, “you must be a man, then.” because I didn’t respond when he called me “little lady” on the street at 7a… https://t.co/QaqLOg5Sn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I just wanna rip shit off the ground in places where people are not expecting me to pick up heavy shit off the gro… https://t.co/yEcUbVvR8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieGeist. @MSNBC @MorningJoe   If I WANTED TO WATCH CPAC I WOULD HAVE!  IF I WANTED TO WATCH FOX, I WOULD!  So.… https://t.co/zKpfEFcq4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisKTLA @MeganHenderson I heard the news bout the beer so can I still drink my 12+ bottles of corona lite a day and be safe lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need this when kyle and i have children even though he will argue that it... #funniness #lol #smirk #farcical https://t.co/pmbO63U5Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 Talking forthrightly about systemic issues will help computational agents assert themselves appropriately… https://t.co/4RERnAXUbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excelsior Se debe sancionar por ese tipo de agresiones.  Hay que respetar a los agentes de tránsito, y policías.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my best friend and mom are taking me to the beach and taking me to hold a sloth for my birthday!!!!! I’m so b… https://t.co/qJ8vfBXpVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alessiacara has such a beautiful voice singing #LovemeTender on @nbc #ElvisAllStarTribute]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finish this year strong @julliaaJimenez      https://t.co/q1ktcxRJjw https://t.co/6CfthSRH2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynhtaylor @MensHealthMag Ben will subtly nod if someone is wearing the same headphones 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[《KATHY》 Back to basics ❤ #harmonyofscienceandart #blondeandcurly @ Color and Style Salon https://t.co/p9o8s3eGUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinMcbroom @CatherinePaiz I’m literally at work waiting for this documentary to drop 😭🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[fala mal do feminismo, do movimento lgbt e do black lives matter mas prega o fanatismo religioso????????????????????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[CEO @dsw_us @RogerRawlins speaking to importance of differentiating customer experience to grow DSW. #Shoptalk19 #TPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigAfrika88 I’ll miss your sense of humor off the field— who will be in all the funny promo videos now? 😿Good 🍀!… https://t.co/c210X72GJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished reading @ContactPoint’s Devotional, “Thy Kingdom Come” from “The Bible on Business” reading plan. I… https://t.co/jKs2zGWrnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[seeing @TheTechRabbi twice in one year...#iste and #prizmah2019   Lucky me! https://t.co/OAPBrSVBjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both my babies crossed today and I couldn’t be more proud 🥰❤️ #TBS #PA #Spring19 https://t.co/lIr261czD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhaivyd @Librarianista @TorresRayMN @JeanWagenius Isn’t that worth $5,000 a year? #txlchat @atpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woo Hoo! A full day ahead to build a bigger science strategy toolbox to take back to my classroom!! #MSTAMICH… https://t.co/HvcUBkld4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[All them triangles on ya face to “highlight” isn’t necessary. Slowly build. You’ll save product too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexieGarciaa True fuckin story!!! I thought it was just me feeling like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the past year, there haven’t been many days that I’ve missed working in a bank. I miss bankers hours today, though. #PresidentsDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh coming home and remembering that I have Clouds moms pupusas was EVERYTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msbedlam_caz @DoItToJulia5 @ABRadFems @TeelaWild @MorganeOgerBC @preta_6 @FeministCurrent All of the other women o… https://t.co/Nz4dQ0KW8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you feeling a bit down without the sunshine?  It's been foggy &amp; cloudy for over a month. https://t.co/9aEDtgXYGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_spates @harleyjennMC I've been wanting the blue one, since I used to wear blue on my lower lashes to enhance my blue eyes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magagary687 @AOC She also thinks that the reason that unemployment is so low under Trump is because people are working two jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook @ILMFOrg she has no evidence and this is part of the push to get Muslims in office and Sharia law an… https://t.co/5kqpKUEHdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slwein @kates4cubbies @MrFrankShirley @george4593 I’m more knowledgeable than most guys I know, and so are the fem… https://t.co/rX0csLE9iZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OriginalJokeOfTheDay (from yours truly🙋🏽) ~ I always ask parents when they first found out they were retarded, and… https://t.co/bpVyYusTJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ram21096063 @DalaiLama How lovely and simple this universal concept is that even a small child must grasp, so how… https://t.co/3gvE1K1RiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJFox side question, did someone from the @IsenbergUMass staff professional development day committee contact you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to major in Nutrition but I want to also major in Math ughhhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliansRum @MrEarpLA he goes back to the days of the Iran-Contra affair and  Marco’s family of the Philippines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdirito @TVext modern_day_athena @bedgo15 yellow.brick.rose treylaing @IsaiahSantel ivanmoody jaybo_white white… https://t.co/GOGu3X9dGb]]></document></documents></author>