<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m a lot more interested in what people propose to do for us than I am about their meta-struggle with other elemen… https://t.co/P41WYkklzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turkdaddydollar @JeanieBuss @MagicJohnson Yeah it's a train wreck coaching front office players all accountable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent i love bacon Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just added to Scotty’s Studio Cereal Stash! Limited edition @kelloggsus Banana Creme @frosted_flakes !! https://t.co/JhLf3IqSOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Democrats have sent our American   children into another death. https://t.co/cc8zvL8BXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyGuiltyDesire is to play my video games with a third party controller.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaidersReporter Yes, also discovery is expensive and often a pain in the ass..]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wildcats baseball team starts a doubleheader against Cal State East Bay at 11 p.m. today. @theorion_sports… https://t.co/3n5nO9ryKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[BRAZILIAN JIUJITSU gives kids an amazing platform to develop their physical abilities as well as focus, discipline… https://t.co/cRVX2GUEFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so unlike trump to believe another world leader over the evidence about murders they are involved in... way ou… https://t.co/Ci0pP2nNX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t hang out with me without coming away with at least one reading assignment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever cam up with “ bros before hoes” never met some of my old friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @HPScotsBaseball fans, I’ll guide you through the action today as the Scots take on Independence and Boyd from… https://t.co/Hs0oVnZrDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ring_jarrett @bobbystonemusic @realDonaldTrump Not a single bit of real or credible evidence. Since Mueller hasn't… https://t.co/Zam8Q89fIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey Fat Pants, bars in DC are opening early to watch Cohen. CANT WAIT!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how people always say, “The book is better than the movie/show?” That is not the case with @UmbrellaAcad  #UmbrellaAcademy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight 1 of D2 Women's Weight Throw is in the books.  Former Durant prep Brinn Grunder sits in 7th with a best thro… https://t.co/P4NxAHJ7FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seattle needs to get its construction game in order. Too many lanes blocked off in the U District.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A little free in free trade sure will help American Ranchers &amp; Farmers Thanks Mr President]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chennyoj @ChelseaFC You have to adapt to the strength of your players which he has no clue how to do. Seem like you don’t have clue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wasted possession will come back to bite us now. Unbelievable.... wow just like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quite possibly. But when I look across the street at Pickle Research Campus and see grass, I have to think UT sees… https://t.co/aM6C6F0Ari]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Ima keep my mouth closed and keep my thoughts and feelings to myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartysaurusRex @dallascowboys gtfo you jason witten hater #IfYouKnowYouKnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comments https://t.co/4RA6BXQBvB @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believe It" https://t.co/iemJEDt5SZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @rey_atl @jonz970 @raducom @NascarLv @robbiegel @x123dottie @MAGAgirly @SwettmanF @mary44614 @BennyDrille… https://t.co/2eM2yMsDtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warrihood Love it, but I think I’ll just make some chili for now. https://t.co/rbtWsh2MVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFPfaff Steve Jobs just rolled over, gave you a thumbs up, and went back to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Juicy Brut by @ShortsBrewing @ Little Bit of Life Ranch — https://t.co/SJnkyThiJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming up!! Be sure to watch your Roadrunners take on (RV) Loyola (La.) at 10:45 am!!! #BeepBeep https://t.co/b9UkGql6RI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, I stand at the door, and knock: if any man hear my voice, and open the door, I will come in …… https://t.co/ciSXyANwtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister Holly is getting married next month and I’m not quite ready for how much &amp; how hard I’ll be crying at this wedding 😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss shelbybilby The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Beaut… https://t.co/9wYOjeHF2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceTwoWavie @dabbingdezi69 remember when u and bre were fighting over a fucking brownie at cheba hut LMAOO all the crumbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[tondragregory and I are learning the power of project collaboration more and more. Stay tuned for a OUR STORY soon.… https://t.co/zTjcK2Vmfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHelms @nascarman_rr Raylon Givens would have cornered him before he drove off turn 2!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ine of my favoritetv shows is #HollywoodMedium...or as it’s called in Middle America, Hollywood XXSml]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StopBurningBridgesAndDriveOffOfThem @falloutboy #NYC #NYCphotography @ Ed Koch Queensboro Bridge https://t.co/LvdXA5igRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s on my mind I find it funny/awesome that @realDonaldTrump has been awesome in office and all the liberals and… https://t.co/dVJHO3uEAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_TrueMac @jimsta29 @nytimes America has spent more on protecting European freedom than they have on themselves.… https://t.co/4hQqlXHg0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryDeMuth Mary...have you worked with any of Dan Allender's material at all ? I heard he has an online course for sexual abuse survivors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorjeschneider @simmonssteve When leafs fans talk about class https://t.co/AaAUgbaGMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneunderscore__ @brianstelter Is that "news" factual reporting or wishful thinking.  #BiasKilledJournalism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighGreco Make sure to check out my mock draft version 6.1.256 this monday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When chi chis dad wanted them to get married goku had no interest in it whatsoever aside from getting  the dragon ball her pops had]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a cancer and that’s why I just got home and I’m going good thank y’all for the birthday party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I sit here in Vegas airport ready to redeye it back to MI, I reflect over the weekend. But I have a few weeks to… https://t.co/RjGcSCNaKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakersReporter I’m not even angry any more. This team simply lacks Fire. As much as I don’t really blame Luke, a c… https://t.co/18X9UU6hDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke What exactly has @Kaepernick7 done for the black community? All he did was kneel. Once his skills di… https://t.co/2F0P5pk8Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @Cern_lXXl @horusrage @PrinceOfAtheism @PCribbett @BlancoIndian @CingetoOfBelgae @zapher134 @selgowiros… https://t.co/JhX8wergUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[...elated to return to @MBQTMT next week, #sharing and #learning with the fantastic students of @RyersonFCS’s… https://t.co/HH2IDGsCIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSteveCox @EmmaSegasture @thenation @johncusack @BernieSanders We are off on a tangent. You seem to have taken… https://t.co/7lTVnNS00Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Monday nights are for eating a whole digiorno and half a box or thin mints, while watching First Wives Club. https://t.co/V75tgcf8Us]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I drank up all the money.”   Warren Zevon, “The French Inhaler”  #relatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[From End of summer 10,000 miles to end of winter: Tree, Shadow Of Tree, Pine Meadow Lake  #blue #summer #winter… https://t.co/zsTusy295D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManzanoJavier87 @lil_leo1145 Sapingonauta , sabes de la historia de Cuba lo que lo mismo@que@Diaz Canel es preside… https://t.co/m8HO8T2gFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[to love oneself as it is, is powerful. find something you love about yourself and hold onto it.💛 #selflove… https://t.co/rw0l3r2acL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 111 años del nacimiento del líder democrático más importante de nuestra historia. https://t.co/2w2s0Kpuaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm, what should I throw next? A candid moment from the wonderful #KreweOfRio #MardiGrasParade in #LafayetteLA -… https://t.co/HAqAMbvOkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giants win 75-65 over Lawrence Central.  On to regionals championship against New Pal at 8:00 pm at SOUTHPORT… https://t.co/qouxVOvB18]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sigs4Soldiers @ATLBravesGirl12 Wait! What? Did I miss something? I was watching a spring training game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy on my team in Apex Legends is named “bigbabyvapeboi” not positive it isn’t @DennisHChrist]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a launch! 🎉🥃 #westwardwhiskey  #oregonstoutcask https://t.co/yChcoOfbIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow imperial milkshake IPA... not bad!! - Drinking a Shadow Prophet by @relicbrewing @ Screamen Eagle / Matts Draft… https://t.co/A1UFlepdAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You could of course call the rich what they really are, parasites. And what do we do with parasites?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶👍👀 more very cool work from take2vinyl 👍👍 They can take your picture and put them on recycled records 👀 makes  for… https://t.co/coUgGmPbFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close-up of my Cyclops...and Chimera's backside. 😘💋🖤🖤🖤  #brownjrart #tbt #drawings #draw #artist #art #artwork… https://t.co/cQYivZc1cL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay2019. Women are strong, fragile, emotional, leaders, nurturers....Women are everything… https://t.co/BvgA9CNCFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnWithLogic Maybe #DEW? Crazy, yesterday I was researching Mayotte and 11-11. An Anon shared Mayotte is part of th… https://t.co/csFH6vH3WT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alumni Coffeehouse event, another beautiful day on the mountain with the brothers doing what I love best @ St. Chri… https://t.co/EPzoEHGqz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @realMikeLindell @CPAC Based on this, I returned the “My Pillow” the wife bought the other day.  It looks… https://t.co/253ESZMExi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to be back in New York. thospers @ Tony's DiNapoli https://t.co/k1NqF6Q5xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJSEyesOpened @saltrejo @slcpd @slcmayor @EqualityUtah Bottom line is it maybe a simple assault but it sure looked… https://t.co/urgT7gVsr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingPeachDP @chance4gardener @ipheebzz @wildweezle @stemeakabrunson @holachola @politico_z @JeffJWarwick… https://t.co/xHDL3t60aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte Independence,  we need a a cool revolutionary war mascot that will go through the community and help spre… https://t.co/v40ALteSF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KąDarbėnaiDirbaVisąDieną #XtraLongRead #EnergyDigest (07/19): stringantys procesai  https://t.co/uRdnV6t0gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that was a great game!!!! vegasgoldenknights put up 5 against the @predsnhl #goknightsgo #vegasborn  @nhl @ T-M… https://t.co/YqVA9NXjCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Occasional Cortex has earmarked that money for subway improvements, schools and stopping bovine flatulance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This applies to all aspects of life honestly. If you love what you do, you won’t work. Thank you my guy… https://t.co/Dmv08y4Ea6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I married my Dream last night.  2/17/19 #itsahollowayaffair   We invited 250 people,  270 showed up and showed out!… https://t.co/ec5Yf9uXlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great brunch with @realdonaldtrump , my best buddy, and the Alexander’s @ Mar-a-Lago @ The Mar-a-lago Club https://t.co/ynqPnnn1L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 out of 5 posts I see on my fb news has some kind of meme making fun of liberals or conservatives...my goodness. W… https://t.co/9m8fvuqPhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacopo_della_Q It is said that the sight of Gods own Light Bringer is so striking as to mesmerize any who gaze upo… https://t.co/mDVMqgThZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScoutWithBryan Until we see what Porzingis is, I don’t think anybody can argue this]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I make myself better and fear if I ever saw you all I would be able to do is try and give you a magn… https://t.co/kbsYz4jJFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[2002 AND STILL REMAINED SHELVED! Oddly enough, the revision saw the removal of my favorite track, "You". I have bee… https://t.co/paEhEzL09h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol haven’t been on twitter all day, gets on for one sec, immediately pissed off. ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signs you’re at #MSTA19... @joy_everyday: What’s the earliest I can get in my presentation room tomorrow morning? M… https://t.co/r5mA48Iuby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump Too bad! That would have been another easy win for you, @vp @parscale and… https://t.co/b2WCKc58HW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@playcle216 @Reflog_18 @neorsd @CLEFoodies @LtBakerMayfield @emilyroggenburk @foodsofjane @FearTheSword… https://t.co/gUEEEClRuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaiderMagic94 @Nike @GarminFitness @UnderArmour Always looking for ideas]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't news by now, but Vanity Fair disinviting the #NYTimes to its Oscar party is like Dolce disinviting Peng… https://t.co/RUQYLWtDDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickTurturro1 @SHOsports @MichaelRapaport @madflavor @ABREG_1 @MarkKriegel @BDailey223 @nicktheIII Gonna be a big hit!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffAxisPaint What if we put a wedding shield on the car? https://t.co/Nbz5N3Eyai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosemy_marcus @HamiltonESPN @CoachHarriott @SWiltfong247 @DavidFurones_ @gogetityft Gigem is on 🔥🔥and you can shine in that offense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is my Louisiana fam at ? I’m out here for work for a few months. Want to meet up or grab food hmu!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanTheGawd_ @DaBluMamba How its gonna be played though online or in person?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonaireVolt @GerberKawasaki If you took a Model 3 and turned it into a CUV without modifying the wheelbase then yo… https://t.co/uxbiHnIPJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Easy, we need to return power to a normal American,  who has our interests at heart, and not his own agenda to line his own pockets ,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill The Man tells the Truth...... He's a Truther ........ Barry the muslim is a traitor and liar]]></document></documents></author>