<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s Day 48 of #Gymshark66 and a self care challenge week this week? Challenge accepted! I have a week off from tea… https://t.co/OnKqaKV9dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse We are ready to put you your vice and the cabinet and your kids last one will be sent to reform school.… https://t.co/4IyC3n9Eff]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day back at the gym in 2 weeks. I needed this more than I thought. There really is nothing better than an early morning workout 🏃🏻 💪🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 3 in the morning, and we are in here 5 deep, putting in that WORK! I look down and remember the shirt I’m wear… https://t.co/a8Bd6AtDgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling Come on! I want to know! Were you familiar with @KenyonCollegeVB prior to coming out with the Potter se… https://t.co/mhyOvHLRr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC People before 1/20/17 just "thought" trump was an asshole. Now we "know" he is an asshole plus sooo much more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoCancino Marco, ojalá uds, como periodistas, pudieran hacer un análisis de rendimiento de jugadores de hoy vs… https://t.co/gDhNIoabBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola @SiteOneSupply Palm Beach Gardens, FL! Thank you for spending some time with us discussing our quality supply… https://t.co/PnnuLvhbIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He should apologize  for being dumb enough to let himself be interviewed by the liberal partisan hacks at the NYTs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brown Ale by Fenton Winery &amp; Brewery at @REBrewing — https://t.co/B7eAcDGBWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATrueblood @BleacherNation too bad a bank wouldn't give them a loan to pick up any free agents this winner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Collin_McHugh returns as a starter after having great success working out of the bullpen. https://t.co/3ieId1fmh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[US TOUR DATES AND TICKET SALES BETTER BE COMING SOON THEN (LIKE THIS WEEK SOON) ONIKA 👑😩 @NICKIMINAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you drinking? 🍑🔱 #crownroyalpeach #adultingresponsibly #mardigras @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/9OrpTcYe5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurtisTT88 Frustrating night for them. We’ve played really well and deserve the win, but Freddie had to be really… https://t.co/HhV9OcmeH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriffinSpalding @GriffinDNews @JamesDSmith2 @AASAHQ @georgiadeptofed @MaconBibb @CityofGriffin @GriffinHS… https://t.co/bNFEA01pr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@yashar should produce the Oscars. It would be a tight and watchable 1.5 hour long program]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does that one person always feel the need to wear shorts when it’s 20 degrees outside? I just don’t get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSarumin Been there done that lmao.   Funny thing is, the girls come when you’re intensely focused on something th… https://t.co/WceYA8gRa7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kissingkate10 @chaturbate Happy Valentine's Day!!💋💋💋Kissing Kate. https://t.co/FZpW5qPxMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hades’ Hounds Hunker Down Brown by @Akademiabc at @BeerMeFB — https://t.co/vvwwiUPENE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max out week! Were you completing EVERY rep! This week we find out! 💪🏾💪🏾💪🏾 #F🐶MILY https://t.co/JG0D7PttoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryceharper3 @bharper3407 @Phillies @MLBTheShow @jaysonwerthID Vision approaching 20/12 (20/8 best humanly possibl… https://t.co/VUdFIbEfxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clinton is definitely the one who should be getting investigated right now &amp; not the POTUS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenWo4LiFe Would be such a Sox signing. All his teammates on the Stros say he is better than them at their own pos… https://t.co/Q5Yz3fdzS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think #Trump woke up yesterday morning for Presidents Day, scampered down the stairs, and wondered where all of his presents were?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silver_Buck @TxEx @tjfxh @DeficitOwls @StephanieKelton @CNBC SK is playing the long game. Problem is we're running out of time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then STOP accepting it, you « Euroninnies ».  Stand up to the Hidalgos and let the Catalan people choose!!! 🐾🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachACole I did a 76 mile ride in London and gained 1,300ft, literally impossible in the Bay Area unless you do laps in the GGP Polo Field]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valkyrry @SenSchumer @senatemajldr Really , how fast did it warm after the last ice age cycle Einstein?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daily_Express @piersmorgan @GMB In other words he was either STUPID, ARROGANT OR A CHILD MOLESTER. He bought his w… https://t.co/w3KOMA2Wml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Sounds like you just mad cause she’s younger. Why don’t you call her boo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miren, la idea es esta: Para mi no es práctico ir al gym porque no siempre puedo mientras viajo, ENTONCES, encontré… https://t.co/RlBPqn42zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god that episode of K-on Was hilarious and almost dies of laughter.   I do want to watch more but I gotta go… https://t.co/t6Nx2vh0cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popped and Skrewed: 45's at 33 1/3rd - THIS EVENING at Cafe Bourbon Street [2216 Summit Street; Columbus, Ohio  432… https://t.co/Xuec5rhpIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAAF your streaming idea today was stupid. You made watching on tv a chore. You’re not that important yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuebloRdoSports @TODDALBO @helzer_jack @Kaeden_Bowman13 @MarvinLondonJr2 Exactly. BECAUSE IT’S TOO LOUD IN THE BASKETBALL COURT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenPowers Absolutely a terrible rush to judgement by too many people.  Disqualifying for Gillebrand, in fact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FSU Panel got together last night and hit on all the major topics surrounding FSU football right now   https://t.co/KyFaN9FAe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN IT'S ALL ABOUT PEDOPHILE MOHAMMAD, BABY! https://t.co/pl4k0JTh14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshvittetoe @AtoZSports I know both sides are being physical but there’s been a lot of just plain pushes and movi… https://t.co/gGaRcAlLF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolves winning loose balls and they have the “hustle” factor. Plus, they are packing it in after going up.… https://t.co/Tm8zbmJPJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Friends. Love, Doesn't Always Rule #1. As Our True State Of  Mind. But, It's Forever. The Pure Divine Natur… https://t.co/dP6hl02YYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @KXXVNewsNow @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/GmIUxHAXaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to get hammered with my frands and watch these guys throw down tomorrow 🙌🏻🍺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyDaleTX Please get the Car Dealer franchise lobby stuff repealed. It is an antiquated law protecting against is… https://t.co/Cds8sIGGkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelramon @evamariaseefue @miriam_davila @miriampealoza1 @Florimelda @fb411c0411544db @bendoiro29 Sin nada siguen sin luz sin internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeAGameChanger Lets do this #hockeyhelps (@ Paramount Fine Foods Centre (formerly Hershey Centre) in Mississauga,… https://t.co/Vjpl3qszZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s dinner. I do make Italian food from time to to time... (this is stewed octopus with tomato, capers, pa… https://t.co/0C1GsLg6CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RantingRodger @SparrowPercy @Justice4the21 @redeyes1875 Cheers mate. I am over the pond trying to push this.… https://t.co/rWraJpsLR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios Who does she know who would actually be most people? Sometimes I wonder if the Trumps are really that stupid… https://t.co/nbg4qR6ufd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doomsday Clock #9 by @geoffjohns @1moreGaryFrank @bdanderson13 is one of the best issues in the series, and paves t… https://t.co/526v7O3Zki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeberry @YordiVP Pago defavores,  ya sabemos de donde salió la lana para mantenerlo todos estos años.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Truth2Dj @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon @jordan_sather… https://t.co/ql0E8CPdRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mightyt98 @annam0403 @CoreyTricoli1 I deserve a raise with how hard I work. https://t.co/tadBEFQdh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero ese #GALAXYS10GRATIS que regala @TecnonautaTV!! → https://t.co/Gy1BUUQDe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevenweaven I always heard people talking about it but never watched it, as soon as this other movie is over I’m on it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To all the nerdy girls who hide behind your sketchbooks, don’t be afraid to share your stories with the world.” Do… https://t.co/GjJ3Yl9IUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods She’s a divisive dope ... “paint a photo” .... she spews rhetoric]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fendi Fine...   #AngelfaceMUA #MakeupArtist @ San Marcos, California https://t.co/wtlLsh23Qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natascha_hase @TeciaTorres @ufc Tecia is good straw weight. Mid-level at best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filming G is the most stressful job I’ve ever had by a long shot. The pressure is real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama jenna puts dr.. Bronners on her v Jay because it dries solid.  I assured jenna that I can stop time wi… https://t.co/goglLN60Ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbranham502 @jspalding79 So... we wouldn’t be getting any worse after CC is gone? Seriously though, there’s 6 new… https://t.co/tSOw92Ru0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MexicoCodigoRo @siete_letras @VigilantesV @TamaulipasCRojo @FENIX__Mx @l4nd3t4 @vigilantehuaste @EzequielFloresC… https://t.co/2SQm88fzKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[dreadnaughtyhair Come celebrate @yoda4jedi bday tonight @factoryatnecto @Necto tonight  #misanthropianarcissus… https://t.co/IzUy7bsiRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@votolatino Amount of illegals crossing Pre and post wall construction in El Paso.....… https://t.co/ZS4hyrBmek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandamurpheyy yup, and the parents staged it as if it were a “kidnapping”]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other words..."We need to get rid of him, so let's bother a bully of people until they give us something to get… https://t.co/RhwA5uIXsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We can’t just diss the young people who want to do something on this and I know because my daughter is one of them.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nunca había visto a alguien tan estupido y sin cerebro. Es inaudito las cosas que se le ocurren a este a asno.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartmindy @AOC And, btw, I notice how you like to brag about how patriotic you are. Here's one for you. "Patriot… https://t.co/jP6IDR2bNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yates says again that he didn't think Dowless was collecting ballots, that he explicitly told him no one he was pay… https://t.co/KmnK1HgveA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbillinson @AOC 3 Loser's, she will never amount to anything. https://t.co/GI9gjOcVwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wugrut @BillOReilly Oh, are those the things the Republicans investigated and started indicting people for over th… https://t.co/ZF1dTmT6jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCastronovo If it was an on the job accident  there should be death benefits available-to his dependents]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC is making the most common of mistakes. She's put forth this unrealistic 'Green New Deal" plan and arguing the d… https://t.co/XKBvsAAD8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost go-time here in Pensacola. We've worked hard all day to make gains and I'm going to give it my all in the ra… https://t.co/enCmqILFUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicsluo @calahan_riley @Aseemru Give Congressmen/women 2k ratings from each state like the video game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelOsteen All I want is what I want in my life not what everyone else wants,,,fuck that,,,is that life,,,NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fieldwork Brewing Company in Monterey, Calif https://t.co/qivfTviBOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Nah.  MAGA people don’t act like those fools.  Locking a few of them up should help.  But we do sti… https://t.co/N8p81rWpbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guinz Empire of the Sun, Close Encounters of the Third Kind, oh heck, any Spielberg movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to see the positive to #bepositive. You have to wake up each day and turn your positive energy faucet on t… https://t.co/huuspoQJ5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liberty4Life73 @Kira_Media Yes. A new channel. Meaning one that isn’t here today. Meaning one that would compete w… https://t.co/3DekbXzCwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wtfvids_ @Areas_Abandoned Thats fuckd⬆️ dude should b kicked out of league🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucks getting older and losing the ones that once knew everything about you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Algunas veces Dios pondrá una promesa en tu corazón que es difícil de creer. Deja que la semilla eche raíces. La pr… https://t.co/VuA9n7pota]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best national anthem singer in the country - @GeneraldWilson  #ArchMadness https://t.co/v9s8bngS7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life can be put on autopilot  You will never know for sure  What is LIVE and what is an AI Script]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyAvilesR @CecyDuran ejejej, es una guerrillera, pues, estimada Wendy :).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s2rhs @UCFKnights @UCF_Baseball @UCF_Softball @UCF_WBB https://t.co/lE5M47YhSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Nashville! @TNCRNA @aanawebupdates #TANADayOnTheHill #CRNA https://t.co/ZoSOYdsntA]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIVE.   He is FIVE years old.   Gun violence is the real national emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/aVGH1CS5kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers You are such a f-ing hypocrite.  Waiting until one of the (criminals) undocumented new citizens of Wiscon… https://t.co/MGgmihZVcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purple rain, @Big12Conference Champions Edition! 😈😈😈 #KStateMBB #cats #bruceketball https://t.co/eL9DzRvBgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolynhere Lol I'm going to work because I find it much easier to work with 2 screens than 1 little laptop screen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all of our wonderful patients who are our extended Family! Mazza Center for Implant and Aesthetic Dent… https://t.co/D0rCnJ235c]]></document><document><![CDATA[accomplish great things big or small when you believe much more in His Love than in your weakness.]]></document></documents></author>