<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s a good day to wear my “If-I-was-meeting-Oprah Outfit”. Pink fringe chandelier earrings and unicorn print. Happ… https://t.co/bn8nU7ZAAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly your right!  I flipped on WNBC and was mortified how they nullified the man’s story, blaming Trump!  Talk abo… https://t.co/zOdomuZQzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tropical14ever Jewish folks aren't white. Neither are Italians. But life improves significantly if you identify as… https://t.co/6dKKRfdFM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the HEAVIEST and Fattest Slow Flakes of all time 6 inches on the ground and still coming down!!!  . .… https://t.co/zGzrGgMR6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[So guys, I bought a gym membership today, and as soon as I'm done coughing everytime I walk more than 3 ft I plan on using it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynthiaSchwind @LindseyStoddard @HarperChildrens @ellyswartz @annbradenbooks @joshfunkbooks @Jarrett_Lerner Wow! L… https://t.co/QiEHkt7vp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey luke hemmings it would take less than five seconds to make me happy by following me. just saying. 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was filled with inspiration as we demand a change for healthier communities in the San Joaquin Valley. Organi… https://t.co/R2v8VBRM3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calexity @andigalpern @arieljalali What about Data Science in Culver City? I guess Oracle bought them last spring.… https://t.co/6EZKUuJ7Cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigdaddykayk It hasn’t been announced yet! But I’ll keep you updated 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods If he was found LIEING taking valuable time away from REAL CRIMES IN CHICAGO this dude needs to go to JAIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parksandrecnbc Why isn’t Nick Newport Jr involved in Bobby Newport’s campaign?? #ThingsThatKeepMeUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hired attorney who is representing me over school restrictions told me to dress like a old lady no makeup, grey… https://t.co/P3IXVkX8Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lauren_k_rob @cabooklover I watched it through three different times. I loved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't tell them apart @GregBryk @the_real_coach. @survivorcbs #photo_editor made by @lyrebirdstudio https://t.co/kXcFkRtkgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BentleyAudrey @barbarannott @AlaricAloor @archonsec @DrJDrooghaag @MiaD @jdelacruz_IoT @securitybrew @WIRED… https://t.co/rXwLn7EFh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you been thinking about moving to South Carolina or closer to the coast? I can help. (843) 310-1714… https://t.co/SrF8xfa5wJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was sick as a dog and got emphysema laughing so hard at Alex screaming for Sam Burgess and destroyed my knee runn… https://t.co/UST6QjwtFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericprydz How funny you Tweet this just as I was admiring the view of the  Downtown LV Event Center from a birds-e… https://t.co/h890KR3C5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThaTrapGod @Stefaaanyy So these are ugly steph😢😢💔💔 https://t.co/iUmBuaFChe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FavynTube I think it's called Russet. It looks more orangey in this picture than reality, which has more dark copper to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[That kind of other worldly connection between two people doesn’t come often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las mamás. Ellas son las arquitectas del camino de sus hijos. Parent-school collaboration! Lakeland Elementary Scho… https://t.co/pnVGAQOh8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/3 from my Any Place, Any Face workshop with nashcophoto. Yes it’s similar to 1/3 but I love it the most even thou… https://t.co/iV9gkqs7HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t untilize my synesthesia in my art as much as i have the potential to do so and that’s the story of the girl… https://t.co/n6c8yhqWD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[So khloe has started coming to me telling me about this little boy she likes in her class, and she made me promise… https://t.co/UzsJcTmh7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I’m also so smart, good at setting boundaries and maintaining my self respect 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was such a pleasure to be a sponsor of this morning's Up &amp; Atom Women's Leadership Breakfast benefiting the… https://t.co/5TxMrCQhIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caitriona balfe at the vanity Oscar party @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/ekzCLsdZqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iCapital_ @Waffle_Rewards @_BigBen7 @WaffleHouse @TheSteelersWire @Steel_Curtain4 @Steelersdepot @TheSteelCrew Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FarmersFridge - great concept, great food. My only wish is that there was a pullout surface or small table on the… https://t.co/rC6aTAG9HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super rubbed for the day 👐🏾  This mess has been happening a lot lately. Like I can do so much just to keep my compo… https://t.co/piksMOVGmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MASTERCHEFonFOX I’m watching old seasons... wow @grahamelliot lost soooooo much weight between season 4-5. He look… https://t.co/0qe6PsKDDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[only if u r going to walk me around epcot and pour avocado margaritas down my throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberleyMacL Although the first reply is funny...wait till after 1st round to do moments of silence, Leaf fans wo… https://t.co/rczNATgPvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaMarcus @oculus I’m getting the oculus go Friday and I’ve watched tons of videos I was wondering is there any gre… https://t.co/ceLEoku8P9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idk_mybffWill @iHeartRadio @Y100MIAMI @Z100NewYork @1075theriver @carlyraejepsen @lizzo @kimpetras @HayleyKiyoko… https://t.co/szvLHB1Cus]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Friday #Vibes #prime (rib) place to be .... amazing #craft #beer made In #house #full menu #specials #two #happy h… https://t.co/0wEoTape5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the weekend with my amazing husband in Amish country. We are going to the valentine specular. #mywhy… https://t.co/pbXKu48HAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theikawong The season was great and your interviews kicked it off Great!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkahne @HarmonicHulaHoe So very sorry. And thank your for sharing your story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeweyMargie @TiestoTattooGrl @TheNoahRing @JohnBucanis Well,  Bush was too.  I'm glad Trump is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mario &amp; Jack are the sweetest bonded pair of old pups. Can you help them find a home? #Boise #dogs #fosters https://t.co/PgY7BxyxQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joegooding @TXKenJSmith @RepAdamSchiff Schiff, you should have known from the beginning this “investigation “ was… https://t.co/NaKkg3Y7eQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One man’s trash is another man’s treasure. What a beautiful thank you letter❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceidotorg @cspanwj They are lying about California's electric bills - WE HAVE SOLAR.  It would be stupid not to ta… https://t.co/s9mZ8AjHlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly living my best life and I’m happy I don’t rely on making coffee anymore for a paycheck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BossLadyUpdate @lindsayell @cmafoundation 😂😂😂 yeeeeessss!! I’m already tired lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBuzzOnHR @talentgenie I think we should form a secret fan club ...metal version : https://t.co/edyo71AtcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only 80’s kids will remember this cult movie reference....and a time when competitive female sports were actually… https://t.co/JqdLyK0oi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“At the same time our sexual relationship is growing, he’s working on pushing you away from your parents. Making it… https://t.co/AtAtgt4jRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaysCISDCTE @F1inSchoolsHQ @F1iSTXRC @FISAmericas I'm so glad he came out to speak to the board!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The water was wide today! A daytime look at the Ohio River from Cincinnati I shot from today’s run, and a nighttime… https://t.co/2kpAW2eqBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_zvobgo @MikeTierneyIR So bummed I missed you!! Surely we will have a nice home brew for you to taste next ti… https://t.co/DS7ed7gsvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned something today/this am, well I already knew it, but apparently needed a reminder. I get SUCH great joy o… https://t.co/DUv2QXxgI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@menyvazq @CitlaHM @OSWALDORIOSM @senadomexicano https://t.co/3sVm757BEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veliko mi je zadovoljstvo sto sam dobro upoznala Mirka Butuliju,koji je zaista profesor zivota i vjecni uzor  svima… https://t.co/ruFof5pqAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[one time i didn’t check my bag and i got the food i wanted plus 4 extra  sandwiches and i didn’t even know until i… https://t.co/iaBwwfNQUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump So fbi is always up n up I think not, he is just not scared to say what he thinks.… https://t.co/8863DxNjY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You sure?? #debatable #imnumberone  #firstinline 😛 @ Earth https://t.co/8C73mfj6lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your most welcome! I like to do whatever I can to support LEO’s, K9’s, first responders, veterans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have some of the most dramatic friends ever WHY CANT I HAVE NEW FRIENDS OH MY GOD https://t.co/ZuB1hntmot]]></document><document><![CDATA[he posted on his ig story lookin fine af and i’m all of a sudden deceased. that is all. goodbye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunsets Make Me Happy https://t.co/vB25uti1dp via @YouTube go @bruceKgarber]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Yoga Tree with my sweetheart.  The encouraging words on the wall say it all. @ Yoga Tree Baltimore https://t.co/rOtnyrGuH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristyS1985 @Screencastify That thought is mutual sweet friend! ❤️🥰 https://t.co/VR39YxJ3ga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewmercer Sitting here just watching the inevitable climb to 3m so I can see it roll over. This community is incredible!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlysmom2 @Education4Libs She got to have a Baby Shower that royal protocol doesn’t allow. She’s already gotten a… https://t.co/zb4ktbTp8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnkrasinski @StephenMerchant @TheRock lol !  🐒 https://t.co/2dp2bSF8CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Southern Indiana residents to rally in support of hate crime legislation today at Bicentennial Park in #NewAlbany… https://t.co/CAEI4gi3Sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[the cheer comps give out FANNY PACKS NOW? unbelievable, i want a refund]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the makeup brands out there should learn from @norvina1 and @ABHcosmetics Giving this type of opportunities to… https://t.co/pNl8DdXD2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amysmusings Let me know when you get to the part that matches our recent history!  "What can we do for you?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@virtue2 @OliviaJeromeGH @txOLTLfan @AllaineF4F @artkitchen76 @valentinifrank @nathanvarni @MichelleAltman1… https://t.co/3bKNJ1aGHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJ4JG @petresqr Still trying to find the video &amp; pics! I'll get 'em....grrrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at office of https://t.co/g5nzXlulJz &amp; https://t.co/uuU2piGpa9 in Chicago, IL https://t.co/8y1JDlNvXn https://t.co/3NbIIzVsHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is awesome!  My daughter is in a wheelchair and would love that so much!!  This story definitely put a smile o… https://t.co/fQVT077iwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurielOpina @IvanDuque19 No seas estupido y los que aqui comentan en contra de la mujer, no sean ignorantes. Preci… https://t.co/llRY6dJSQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brightly50 For an acceptability coach..she sure doesn't take accountability for much..except finding her voice this season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaJoh40982481 @PeterOvy @jigsawl35 @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump I laughed at that too. That was my first time seeing a syringe w mj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @NCState!! You couldn’t have a better supporter on your corner than THE @Aaron8News! He’s full of li… https://t.co/NvKWoKa1NW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m saying is this better be as good as the wattpad 1D fanfic it was adapted from.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@provdcrumblover @realDonaldTrump I Agree Proud, Release That KRAKEN!!🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @KamalaHarris Pssst, when you ask for everything free it's called a socialist.  Big Government=Socialist.  Now… https://t.co/STjLN7ieBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[i rated the weather channel app one star because it kept telling me it’s gonna snow in pullman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenniferstump12 @MorganCWallen I listen to that song on repeat for six hours anyways.... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had $1.47 in my account and my taxes just hit https://t.co/WAiLohaX2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhiPhiOhara @ajaqueen Learning this has helped me so much because it helps teach that drag isn’t a one size fits a… https://t.co/z5GZdQJaNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[fancyandfelice  -  Today is National Love your pet day! There is no better way to show how much you love your pet,… https://t.co/pIIh0K3HVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY Brandon and I are seeing Broadway's The Lion King Musical!!!! Currently anticipating for it to begin. Excit… https://t.co/tcO1DenHt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would it be looked down upon to order Popeyes at 9 am.. asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sopranos theme song - Woke up this morning https://t.co/n2a0fG7fIO via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[As creepy follows creep, cue this dude’s inevitable own weirdo scandal in 3 ... 2 ... 1 ... Rep. Matt Gaetz says co… https://t.co/wkVeMr5dzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ourWEHO @LindseyPHorvath @meister4weho on your re-election!! ⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B304SAK @Yr_Obt_Svt @AnnetteBadland1 You are a very talented artist! Great work!❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbcbrasil Por que temos uma mente que acredita e segue qualquer asneira como os místicos deuses por exemplo, nossa história conta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you get kids to volunteer to come to school an hour early? Let them explore computational thinking through p… https://t.co/ftYiSpftbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSherryPagoto A2 Also - strategically use FOI requests and lawsuits (to obtain documents through discovery) and p… https://t.co/N8MTxYS8NA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcoplaza @steve_hanke Despite all the economic sanctions that the US is imposing on Cuba, they have: - No homele… https://t.co/OyacrhcbXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Always fishing for compliments @TheBeatWithAri, you all aight and you know it.😉 https://t.co/euqqhewkn0]]></document></documents></author>