<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9Cx9ZPnT… https://t.co/SWCmD2o7dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth. Applies to real life and to Twitter.   We need fewer “experts” and more learners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This made me laugh out loud! Why Yes that was me trying to walk in the wind @93XRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talked with a @LibertyUstudent tonight who had tears in her eyes because of how deep her desire to serve God in Eur… https://t.co/0EyUwcGWy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philshapiro There's a misconception that there aren't #opensource software for #Apple #Macintosh. Not only is it u… https://t.co/lEx0ubjZ34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awkwardgoogle @KimDHolderness would your family try this project out for us &amp; let in know if it’s a pass or fail?  Pleeease!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaggardAl @VinnyR16 @FNC_Ladies_Rule @KatTimpf @KennedyNation @GregGutfeldShow @reason @MattWelch @NRO @FoxBusiness amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hey Twitter, I posted a YouTube video a couple days ago, and it’s pretty fun, check it out and RT so others can… https://t.co/h3NJSDSSdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrived at the conclusion tonight that Sheryl Crow is criminally underrated and how didn’t we ever see it. It makes me super mad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a Barrett 82A1 50 BMG Rifle from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $9000! #gungiveaway #winagun… https://t.co/pCe9FK6Qja]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoogleDigitalCoaches #Fullhouse #Inclusiveconversations @ Fort Street Galley https://t.co/YnTJY7hSkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elections in lots of my former homes today! #Philly why don't we get to vote as much??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but if I'm IN your wedding I'm not buying you a wedding gift. Idfc. I'm already spending A LOT being in i… https://t.co/dTezWYrgop]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person and my favorite food? Sign me up #DBBwithMyBetterHalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down two pant sizes!! Started at a 18 uncomfortably and now in a 14! @ Target Edwardsville https://t.co/bVzIal685D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree but you made some assumptions about my family solely based on the color of my skin. #CoPolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a girl pretending to like snow. @ Lithia Park https://t.co/LVvHAfSCjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally the most fascinating thing you could possibly ever talk to me about, ever. This just fucking blow… https://t.co/acs76tyv8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1madwoman1962 @karenslinn43 @Shirley82829043 @11syoung @pampisford @Eley01 @Jimmysimmonds1 @leonie_elfreda… https://t.co/SQH9XMR0iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope your day tomorrow is filled with fun and laughter....have a great night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seeay1 @bangkokboland That’s acceptable. 😂 That coloring book is pretty awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Toes In Sand in North Myrtle Beach, SC https://t.co/V0NjDA2Uix https://t.co/2lntciIZ4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliKellyyy @jessicaann1995_ i’m finally watching the masked singer finale. i’m not ready lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fivefifths @DrJasonJohnson @Russian_Starr Great point. There is data, though on black voting behavior broken down… https://t.co/kDinH2nXHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen Loiseau #197 match Drexel VS Old Dominion  Sunday, February 24, 2019 https://t.co/K1oBRCOQ9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for waterfront living in Carmel? Don’t navigate the new build process alone! Call McLean Real Estate today!  https://t.co/T1nnuT0dTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could not be more proud to have seen bite_size4 starring as #Carmen in carmenimmersive at publicartsnyc!!!! Only a… https://t.co/zC2ucTgL7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC I feel it is necessary however Obama did this to bring his healthcare program to force us on inferior care and penalize us if we didn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyHarber @dombrownmusic @duranduran Maybe @DailyDuranie can start one. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I’m gonna say is that I’m so very glad no one is bowling in the lanes to either the left or right of this party at the moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVM437 @Phil_Lewis_ Not sure, but this seems to be maximum yikes, a good starting point https://t.co/E3bDcpc7Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A POWERFUL MESSAGE TO ALL MOMS:  Self Care is NOT Selfishness   https://t.co/nkZSUF0VU8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessSorensen @notcapnamerica He threatened my father's life( dad was terminal be with cancer), and his own.  I ign… https://t.co/Go8sh4nx9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi hermano: esa es tu canción, tu momento de brillar a llegado mugre greñuda y como quiera bonita  Yo: ya se 👀🙄💗 https://t.co/wbJkggSjFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on Chestnut Hill Dr #Medina #OH  #realestate https://t.co/1JxOmbQel0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Meehan_ @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump He will probably try to put through an executive order extending the numb… https://t.co/evT9biw00F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy happy birthday @sarahrosen!!! Your bff (is it confirmed yet?) loves you very much! https://t.co/d1vYJWdaZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like some Disco Diva GLAM on this beauty @sdkile for the _kqar_ Cannon Blast .  Used the @jamescharles X… https://t.co/oYTZNvViPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRonTweets @LeoRules1 @gamermom742 @AOC Bill is not a scientist. Simply a role he played .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spiraled from Jonas Brothers to the HSM soundtrack and honestly @ZacEfron didn’t have to go hard af in this scene b… https://t.co/g8rWu9qZYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbartley6 @stickermule @BethHouf @burgess_shelley @JayBilly2 @TaraMartinEDU @burgessdave @dbc_inc 🙋🏽‍♀️ I have the… https://t.co/6aDN9J6dpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chalky checking out his outdoor cousin @ Bays Arcade https://t.co/pEJDExAH4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh silly me I thought  #entertainment and #fashion was about beauty gosh no it's about bullies #ipaintfree #feedme… https://t.co/8diT6QQlIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 of my #7Books Challenge. Post the cover of a book you love every day for seven days (no comment) and nominate… https://t.co/gV3lqh64Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parenting. Making the decision to either shit your pants while you take your kid to school or let tour kid be late.… https://t.co/z5J7hHAVfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarvinLarry @JakeMc945 When All else fails start investors PrezTrump again 🇺🇸♥️🇺🇸HES MAGA 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @TreyNKennedy, where is your interpretation of girls reacting to the @jonasbrothers making a comeback?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are cops always chomping gum in movies?  Is it supposed to make them look tough? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad came this morning to scrape my car off, only for me to tell him that’s the neighbors car... https://t.co/56spSKUMke]]></document><document><![CDATA[I m running out of faith with our party - bunch of ass kissing politicians - Trump is the ONLY Republican on board… https://t.co/6CZEIukSjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Audiele98365692 @ValleyStarNews Yes it does.  Thanks for posting.  Please share this post with anyone you think wo… https://t.co/00nZnpIqL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy right here is about to be a first round NFL draft pick! @dalton_risner71 you are amazing on and off the fi… https://t.co/WSN9MPAssc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to get a poppy sighting. It’s the little things. 🧡 #californiapoppy #mothernature #bloomingnow #losangeles… https://t.co/FJFGPfQVRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenniferjgoetz @deborah_berch @1eyewang @RyanAFournier When we set up special opportunities for special interest g… https://t.co/W6UTqYrQIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @TheCCnC ・・・ Instead consider these tips... Listen carefully before speaking. Be positive in your approach.… https://t.co/oIXsJznG0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got @thelonelyisland tickets!  I got The Lonely Island tickets!!  The day after the concert, I’m gonna be like “I… https://t.co/1Z9fw29ewL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on getting back together with your ex! It's by far the greatest form of self-sabotage... #humor… https://t.co/j3UECk9at9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Georgia_Roddy @WFAN660 @Radiodotcom There was this one terrible glitch where they played some God-awful show start… https://t.co/7WxpzL7qSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Rocket Space And Art Message   Campaign with Phil_m0z  - Internarional Artis is taking off. My message “Lets b… https://t.co/bMFBrHAGtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s Face-Saving Way Out of Political Crisis Raises Fears Over Rule of Law https://t.co/8EcRKWkbLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 Trudeau,  a man with so few friends that he'll take even loony tunes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckennawads When my stomachs gone and I don’t look like a wide load walking down the street it will worth it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed a wonderful lecture on Vampires by Carley’s former Professor Stanley Stepanic at the Mariners Museum last n… https://t.co/FBCmubjlUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiFaircloth @NKemperman @AuthorLMurphy 😂🤣😁😂🤣😁 https://t.co/28kNLQU7lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you always wondered how to get that perfect cuticle clean up and flawless polish application? Well now you don… https://t.co/JzlI8qH4Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newyork #youdliedtome #snow 🌨❄️☃️was NOT on the forecast when I packed #workinginthesnow #itscoldoutside 🥶… https://t.co/QrFMnlkm0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go get ‘em today @mhshlqcblues! You’ve got this! #workhardplayhard #LetsGoBlues #TeamJen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamsInColor33 @tootlelOops @knickRocky @wgnamerica @MrsdogC @DogBountyHunter @bobbybrown719 @cngoolsby2014… https://t.co/XTo4Ko7OJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I drink I always stop and tell myself “Why I’m I doing this to my liver”😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking facts😂😂😂 literally was thinking this yesterday when someone told me the same thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have good days and I have bad days. Lately, it's been alot of bad days. Please be patient with me.  Anxiety reall… https://t.co/WEYB2J26Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnevenKoala Maybe you will have to invest more in fashion and stop being so cheap lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfpelosi @Pirate2Duck @NRA  Love you back! We must keep exposing the evil they spew in their rhetoric &amp; lies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is amazing!!! Way to go, @CarolCiotto and team!!! Can’t wait to see you all at #SPEAKOutDay!… https://t.co/GP4y8siaaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman Real classy...sorry for your bad case of TDS.  #TDS #DemsAreWhacked]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the insane opportunity to present legislation tomorrow at the @OhioDOs Board of Trustee meeting in Dublin. I… https://t.co/9v40dzZ5m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can be so stubborn about staying stuck! Weird. #makeshifthappen #goingrogue #weretalkinshift https://t.co/IQBVslFgCj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad 2 see Austin still in the twd family even though he is now in fear twd @austin_amelio 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Benjamixn @urbangorillas @wearegorillas @ladygorillas @digitalpoliticz @recapzine @BEACASSOMAG @ScumbMag Bless u hard bro ✊🏽✊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would love to see #KylerMurray run the 40 at least if he’s not doing drills! #NFLScoutingCombine]]></document><document><![CDATA[STEM-A-THON  action happening today at @BHSMarlins  AWESOME STUFF! https://t.co/3wkRO6G03L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump My dismay with the President's new direction increased on Tuesday, when he told his cabinet, "Spea… https://t.co/wdwjdsrLdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#promo . Here’s me singing “Homesick” - one of my favorite songs I’ve ever written. Feelin lucky I have… https://t.co/rm1oN3yqia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaronstew12 @soledadobrien Happens to me a lot! ??? I realize if you are replying to a group in a thread, and you… https://t.co/m4mghnGtxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for the suggest @netflix im doing my fucking best https://t.co/lHeFoIsylX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even care about impeachment anymore - I want the SAT scores!!!! #trumpsatscorewas600]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes yu just lost a fan I’m one of “those chicks who can’t wait to put on carnival outfits and be hoes” @JoeBudden… https://t.co/OaxVwZImXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My morning in a nutshell, me, ny blanket, my couch &amp; my cat lol https://t.co/E2rE9pAPrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMountainEast @WVWCSwimming Where you there? Bobcats crushed it!! https://t.co/K6Q6KMXnzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ripping the brush through my curly hair putting straight up conditioner in it just to get the brush through it 😂🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMEN! Couldn't tell ya how many times cody has done this and then it's magically there... https://t.co/aiRcU3exLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZandEDad @AshTudor888 @ScorpioNan71 @peggyzab @greyeyed87 @maxi_fabulous @pippasykes154 @shannonE1980 @dup_j… https://t.co/Ejjy2n9JXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sunrise doesn’t care if we watch it or not, it will keep on being beautiful and rising to the top, even if no o… https://t.co/lzDaHeKlAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Wiccan series is growing! As of right now I have 13 books planned in the series! #wow #crazy #writerslife… https://t.co/C9Ll2uCHHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @FoxNews You’re a better man than I am. I can’t take it anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gas guzzling car rides by AOC doesn’t show hypocrisy, it highlights lack of affordable options. Especially for a 20-something year old.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YeniVilcatoma2 @FiscaliaPeru Fiscal Perez le dio tiempo de irse, puro show!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God knows our heart. #youearnedit! #Iearned it! @ Sun City Center, Florida https://t.co/GCAkC9t3oJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshPerk Yes! Like a block away! On another note happy belated birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling so incredibly blessed today on what would have been our precious brother Robert’s Bday.And the gift of witn… https://t.co/h5FiVdSwJK]]></document></documents></author>