<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Finally!! #Hamilton @ Aronoff Center for the Arts https://t.co/0kbMPjFiiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Not sure your thoughts but I love it when I see you’re living rent free in their heads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know how to fix it with salt. She just wants me to show up at the Christmas party😂 (locked outta the house)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khemraj08118957 Your very beautiful may I have the pleasure in chatting with?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember that article I wrote about “high-quality” (sic) curricula? This time EdReports is at it again, this… https://t.co/kssmaQGxP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ukfandan37 I just don't see how you can put Carolina and Duke both in there. I think Carolina is 4th #1 right now and UK is #3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnRWebsterMD Multiple clinics accepting Medicaid stopped accepting it as the stronger laws rolled in. Many simpl… https://t.co/n7otF7M9oC]]></document><document><![CDATA[that Galaxy S10 look fire. hey @apple, i hope you’re paying attention. I don’t wanna be let down in September!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess we need a wall around our country. Nobody in or out. Oh wait that wouldn’t work. We wouldn’t be able to tra… https://t.co/tDcNBgF6jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last mullet photo. No more #partyintheback #mod rocker - why @FinaFAM Fina?!?! Now, he’s #corporate #theman @ Fremo… https://t.co/zPhNCK7WV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Ann Coulter destroying D.T. with her insults. Its like watching a Spider eat its young in a Meth Lab during a Hurricane on FOX.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a Carters order TWO weeks ago and still haven’t receive it. I made a Target order and it came in TWO DAYS EA… https://t.co/82tRjph207]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever seen a hockey puck hit both posts and bounce into the net? Well, #Raptors Kawhi Leonard —  on game-winning sho… https://t.co/MM3fRTo3Ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all angels r on the right side..some angels could be demons..or at least fallen..I will choose to be on God’s s… https://t.co/DxG1RbJv3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamRealBW_trade $VRUS I'm hoping this will help drive it home for us.  And thinking this is just the beginning of success for everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winestainedfag @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/VBLNz0YZCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Maher should take a lesson from his hero Hugh Hefner, and drop dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RonWeasley portrait I did Saturday at the #philadelphiatattooconvention  #eternalink #fkirons… https://t.co/NtLJF8JisU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Music Label Spotlight February 22, 2019  Celebrating 15 Years Of Cosmicleaf Records  Fragile Li… https://t.co/fq2Eout6NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCReviewsmang @RandomMnky @doomcock The needs of the many outweigh the needs of the few, so obviously the few are… https://t.co/6S9JrnjH6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes when your 4yr old has a habit of climbing into your bed in the middle of the night you make promises you… https://t.co/Ut3xw1RSVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Album Spotlight February 26, 2019  Featured Albums For February 26, 2019 Piek - Despertar… https://t.co/wQ1vAbU1Vt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just look at this objectively. Mark supports the US-trained "soldiers" that literally threw two-year-old children i… https://t.co/VGNMByZFbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RelentlessEater this the nigga u rate 😂😂😂 the music made this 4x funnier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScotiabankHelps is there a way to see in the app what my daily spending allowance is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Library doors are open to ALL. Everyone is welcome. Whether you are looking to attend a job workshop, learn a new l… https://t.co/b0cNbu586y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrasilianMamba Number 3 bro. Straight up. Idk why the homeland does him like this. He plays biggest in the biggest… https://t.co/YhFnhr2RlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StGabrielLOUKY getting ready for their fish today and tonight. @WDRBNews https://t.co/Ci41XlK8jX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/UhzHe2Ou1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonSCampbell Please tell me NOBODY hears her say this and goes, ‘that’s a good idea!’  🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[But not apparent in your tweet. “The traditional media” places all under ine tent. Trumpesque, I dare say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hautehabibti Try to distance yourself. Think about it. Do you know this person? Are you ever going to engage with… https://t.co/60iyd8hrcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE ROAD TO CALI. edwardjones jpmorgan commercebank #health #discrimination #america #family #law @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/rUiTdJwHyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember people were saying Ronda rousey could KO  mayweather, or be a boxing world champ 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[23. In addition to my full time job, I just accepted a part time hobby job to help run a local game store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Disney I have to say I was disappointed in the room we had a Carribean Beach , the Jamaica complex was under a lot… https://t.co/M8BVjRNZy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick stop at The Link Winter Market. Another busy day of Advance Polls in #YorkSimcoe. Had to grab a cup of… https://t.co/5Z0c1sy3uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TristinNoelle @mollyreneminich Hey next weekend is alumni weekend I guess!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always amazed when someone with the title #ArtDirector hires me for a #voiceover But any title will work Broadc… https://t.co/COXCi4ZYDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep thought: more people need to get their ass beat for being cruel stooges]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @TPUSA @UCBerkeley supporting hate crimes on campus  As long as it's a liberal committing the crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸🇯🇵🇨🇦🇱🇻🇩🇰🇦🇹🇪🇸🇷🇺🐣 #HetaliaxLoveLive  #Hetalia #LoveLive #Aqours https://t.co/6MLxznJIJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s goes for all older people in general, not just my family. That’s wack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Previewing my "Alone" playlist. It's very comforting to know you still have it. #ILikeToWatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sunshine_1601 Now I’m ready to get off work and go to the nearest travel agency 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how much hate mail I might get from this, but I like The Orville better than Star Trek and Star Wars and Firefly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the ceremony and celebration! Congratulations, @EricMcCormack on this highly deserved honour! 🎓]]></document><document><![CDATA[My credit score went up 57 points 😍😌🤑😊🙏💕 good way to start my morning off]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEVER too early to look and wonder about @universityofga schedule. Never.  https://t.co/mEveGEOwkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOfThrones #MeeraReed will surprise everyone and take the throne with the fireball-throwing Children of the For… https://t.co/RmUAGIDHlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV credits our mayor @Mike_Rawlings for the World Class efforts and wishes to continue his vision for South Dallas.… https://t.co/t4uRPBnLqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[They walk around like god,,,,but do not know the right side to castanet https://t.co/YbLXheqk2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dontbeafraid #quote #quoteoftheday @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/YPUZFiqz5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golpe de Estado técnico de Andrés Manuel... el artículo del Lic. Fco. Javier Aragón S. @Elparaclito /… https://t.co/5mfdoNKefM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_S_Dot @WEKetchum he said a bunch of names in that verse  and nothing else. It’s relevant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steve promoted more to.educate people about animals and giving people a positive.believe about protecting their hab… https://t.co/jw9MegSsTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the wasted space out there for these outdoor games, and the NHL doesn't think to fill the ice level with foldin… https://t.co/WgZEhBSCnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @Truth2Dj @SlayerMosh @chriswaslight @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/iWeSylZBQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekatymurray Never actually made it to the washing machine. I’ve had a few late night/early mornings lately. I’m… https://t.co/ONAJDxZ2Po]]></document><document><![CDATA[©Markxdavid Productions All Rights Reserved 2019  #markxdavid #singersongwriter #beatmaker #independent… https://t.co/ITTt5yc1rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlishaGrauso Dude cant let SHIT go and gets mad no one is thinking bout him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg this mushroom &amp; kale slice (also has red onions) is blowing my mind right now. 🍕🍕🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 11:03 to play, Richmond leads Davidson 54-45. https://t.co/623mxi2fc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskerExtraCB He was on the floor for the final 2.5. Must have played through it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHern86 Bo Jackson is the best to play both sports...   Kyler Murray has yet to play any sport professionally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFILE And we are all told that the 39 campaign stops was “not doing enough” 🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the way you say my name  ... 📸: jamierandimaging #muaythai @ Evolv Fitness of Seattle https://t.co/DtHTWOjlzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_kudler Agreed, I encourage everyone I know to pick up a camera in some way. But I shot from the crowd since… https://t.co/nc2LlHGViP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieSimoni @McDonalds If I am the police officer who pulled the driver over I would just be a little embarras… https://t.co/Vhq3OrCtRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If millennials and gen z had micro internships in the gig economy powered by AI and machine learning would emotiona… https://t.co/O8tglklLfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already dislike all these IGTV posts in the main #Instagram timeline. Most I’ve seen thus far are “rotate phone sid… https://t.co/j4gmqd3Idq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of @Enes_Kanter, and I forgot he went to Portland, so it was awesome to see him at the game tonight.… https://t.co/uIkfUHUVCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[VENEZUELA. Comment Chavez a nationalisé les entreprises au Venezuela. Un Québécois dirigeait une cimenterie. Il rac… https://t.co/ae3boXWKGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanObeidallah Is there a list somewhere of these long-standing anti-Semitic tropes? Because the last two new ones… https://t.co/W9t1UzyPEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoveWins by @clara_francisc0 @ Castro District, San Francisco https://t.co/gQXboW56zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does #MLB hold front office staff to different standards then players! I hope this is not true! Domestic violence i… https://t.co/hyQ3y5eGil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Geralvarado17 @Messiatico Vergüenza? Vergüenza debe dar quedar eliminado en casa por un equipo de alevines llegand… https://t.co/YixpG2VwBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your couchsurfing guests come all the way from France, you have to take them to enjoy some drinks with the Sta… https://t.co/N8di9F4wRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[God is good!!! I love Him.He loves you. He loves you more than you love yourself. He has great plans for you. His p… https://t.co/mqwKD8eOlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abarkett17 "If you wear a Boston Red Sox uniform, you have to know what Tony Conigliaro meant to the franchise." J… https://t.co/BxnetHDfZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rigorously follow any and all unsolicited life advice from this wise looking doggo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billmaher the last thing conservative red states want is to be the Next New York or California. But keep up the go… https://t.co/VbN6ktqbNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brigidbergin @ndhapple @bcolbyhamilton @bobhardt @katehinds @BrianLehrer I like Citi Field better within its walls… https://t.co/mfnjwWXBzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsJValencia my son was Born in Antioch in 1987. We lived in Nashville for over 3 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @RandPaul Paul Rand is a political moral purist lacking common sense. He’d rather spite his nose than sav… https://t.co/fMFTTAavfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know if I'm being too harsh to other superhero movies by making @PattyJenks ' Wonder Woman as my main stand… https://t.co/Mx4aYncoN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckm Please do! CF is a service I depend on a lot and have a lot of opinions on, but is pretty opaque right now.… https://t.co/1Tm0zl5RT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess #ScottiePippen was on to something #UNCvsDuke #Duke #UNC #CCB #NCAA #NCAAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel Eh, strongly disagree. Treating staffers like this is disgusting — and decidedly not “badass.” When di… https://t.co/VANsX71NNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Leaving Neverland Doc rn. Maybe I’m a pessimist but how did the DEA not see this coming with him letti… https://t.co/h1196S9kdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I failed that test so bad, it got me thinking if imma make it in life]]></document><document><![CDATA[bed. wishes=sd,h, i the d's, k;j or c to bp, bernie to drop o.  antiwishes:dm,nm,l,h.  M:I.  i want winter to stay, summer to stay away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow traffic in #WestRaleigh on I-440 EB between I-40 - Exit 1 and Jones Franklin Rd - Exit 1, accident at Jones Franklin Rd - Exit 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilshyminsky @ellstar I think the closest Marvel ever came to acknowledging something like this was with Transfor… https://t.co/HCqM3UobOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Veggietales universe is so strange and I don’t mean the Christian messaging.   A pickle and a tomato are workin… https://t.co/XTtsKqWT6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighCiv79 @McAllisterDen @cokewithastraw "Wild at Heart" by John Eldredge is a pretty good book. So is the book "S… https://t.co/b024QVhBBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that kardashian stuff might be real but it’s still fake cuz they fake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: having a girlfriend would honestly be sick. That would be really cool and fun, and I think I’m ready to look fo… https://t.co/dxloFBlhNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sylvinafrancis @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows And half the Republican Congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoo straight up Shouts to my gf for straight fixing my car in the parking lot today. You are seriously the realist.… https://t.co/naRnBfZNtP]]></document></documents></author>