<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m still struggling to understand how they’re going to conclude GOT in 6 episodes...these mfs better be long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checked out at @doubletree BTV Airport, South Burlington, VT @HiltonHotels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump Everytime a Democrat whines.... https://t.co/BmgjFh193A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today Is That Day https://t.co/GugGFaB0Tp via @YouTube #spirituality #love #meditation #spiritual #god #peace… https://t.co/7G8pLjZM8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[dang it i was most excited about this weekend so i could sleep in this morning yet here i am omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @JerryFalwellJr And this poor excuse of a human being is a “man of God?” The worst human beings ar… https://t.co/wztqJR8MIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeWxTV @BreannaFuss thanks for waking us up ladies! https://t.co/SXFeSsZx1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biologygoddess Hahaha..............That is a good plan! Great gif!😹😸😺Got it, thanks, Bonnie! https://t.co/KmFV0Xb5bL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hayward in a double OT dogfight with EC North for a chance at the state tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tastes like Jameson - Drinking a Jameson Barrel Irish Stout by @UplandBrewCo @ Upland Brewing Company Columbus Pump… https://t.co/WXW6h5jM44]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to shit this morning but couldn't go. How's your Friday morning going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaliyah_domena Don’t get sad keep your head up and keep pushing no matter what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHayes63 @BlackTopMediaUK Oh it’s great motorcycling around here, I typically skip doing anything on weekends (dre… https://t.co/YmvpmjAYqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_A10_USA @RARRRRR @SuperEliteTexan @robertdunlap947 @TheSilentLOUD @usmc_army @MichaelDadiego @Pickles0201… https://t.co/411bh3HF56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAlun Not my finest moment—nervous as heck facing those two giants—but they were pretty kind in the end after sca… https://t.co/Bq70QerY6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Columbia Metropolitan Airport - @cae_columbiasc in West Columbia, SC https://t.co/YKfLvHpk6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are more verses I can send you if you care to read them. Just let me know if you care to discuss openly and i… https://t.co/nUk70mV4lb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at OARS Regatta Turkey Lake in Orlando, FL https://t.co/UkdqYSZ18E https://t.co/eTPMI0NUlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the good old days when people knew not to dress above their station]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren ie the real deal  New Deal politician. First CFPB and now a wealth tax for child care. Give no time for… https://t.co/gfIjaKrIZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great Ukulele Circle this morning, with a new high attendance record, I believe! See everyone again on Apr… https://t.co/6mw95PwSbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a disgusting #swamp the #Cult45 #idiocracy has created https://t.co/XcbvOLwP7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[The light can change the whole look of this cup 🧡💜💛💚 #etsysellersofinstagram #andersonandavery #etsy #customrequest… https://t.co/IYl6EbZcXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I want a llama, and a goat, and a lifetime supply of strawberry rhubarb pie a la mode, and a ferret, and a danc… https://t.co/yLJp4HaUKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day consisted of T-Bone steaks, Baked Potatoes (Sarah put ketchup on them🤢), and Kale Chips! I actually… https://t.co/9srishwdqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbrode I sigh to no reply, But rest is sweeter... than midnight—um-Twwweeeeter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HoyconMhoni #MartesdeMhoni @mhonividente 🧿 @ClubMhoniFans @magdaproducer ✨📺🎬🎥 @programa_hoy @Canal_Estrellas… https://t.co/nSfRqjsNMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is a woman thing to dramatically change hair with lifestyle changes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump You’ll be crying and pissed next election cycle - just like when the Mueller report comes out....]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a poor young teenager. These where life #GPC #genericPackCigarettes https://t.co/WBkighHq28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sellner74 @marcorubio @SecPompeo Puppet Rubio Posts Pic of Gaddafi's Murder as Puppet Pompeo Says Maduro's Days 'N… https://t.co/Qes2m7cByY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickieAlan1 @RobinsonWoodrow @mjschneider_777 @screwdriver76 @ManeatGrass @fizermusic @Colossous @endpopcountry… https://t.co/9CEvm6pDg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hi, I’m John Tortorella from Boston and I love to talk to reporters mom’s when they interrupt my conferences and A… https://t.co/oaTT1SoGQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently sitting in an ER waiting room to charge my juul. I’m fine, my juul is not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hatch_chili Thanks man I’m excited too! Don’t worry I won’t let you fall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbrown  I went to your house and I felt like a creepy ass fan bro And i regret it I’m upset because you gave t… https://t.co/jfCot6s9gD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapSheet Rivers and he can carpool again - granted, Weddle will have a longer commute but good for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Is not that murder?? If you kill a pregnant woman you will be charged with two murders!! Someone nee… https://t.co/UmjRWMbbCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcbest Diamond and Silk rap and drop beats like elderly white people, but with less rhythm and no soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTEN Will "New Amsterdam" be stupid enough to cut itself off from its source of funding?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo  STILL talking about Lebron? When the Lakers totally tank, will you still spend all day talking about Lebron? 👎🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le exigimos al Gobierno del Estado eliminen las concesiones a los transportistas que estan cobrando el transbordo,… https://t.co/XzBt6FrLK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[We swept this morning for a W3 - L0 last play for today is California  - 1.5   good luck. @ Cleveland, Ohio https://t.co/hzXoRVQANt]]></document><document><![CDATA[WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY in CT into tomorrow morning for 2-5” of snow here; WINTER STORM WATCH in R.I. for 5-7” ther… https://t.co/tFeP9HKfok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump This woman should go back to whatever evil spawned her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Gase + New York media + garbage coaching staff and a diva RB = Pure comedy incoming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY BIEN  MARIATEGUI NO TE VENDES COMO SOL CARREÑO  RENE GASTULEMENDI MAVILA HUERTAS Y OTROS MERMELEROS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Her committee appointments are questionable at best and politically corrosive at worst.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Fleeing their homes and putting their kids in harm's way of a dream. Now that's inhumane. Do it the r… https://t.co/Jxlfsfun0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds good to me!  #Repost @wpxi (get_repost) ・・・ CHEERS! It's Friday and National Margarita Day! 🍹 Sounds like a… https://t.co/kUZ5aWiYog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Cima Cerro Tetakawi https://t.co/l5aYtuemrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@illxchris you on the Juice World and Ski Mask show in Independence MO??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no sympathy for someone who gets hurt while hunting animals for sport.   If you pick up a gun against an ani… https://t.co/b6Gyuuza4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right side defense again. Alan, you need to sub, quickly.  @fccincinnati @700wlw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC White older democrat I guess his own party far left will label him as a racist he has no shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did a WHOLE routine to Thotiana earlier and NO ONE watched I even death dropped and got NOTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to return back to my Elem School today to be a featured guest for #BlackHistoryMonth thank you @fesnva… https://t.co/hTFuSpFn1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h4ydennn @OfficialCBrown1 Show me the evidence plz how u know he killed them and then I will understand where y’all coming from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyUlmer @TwitterMoments @CBSThisMorning I don’t know how that happened 😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[That last quote says it all: custodial status infects the medical status of patients. There’s no such thing as a healthy jail or prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricFrazee1 @AOC He is the Maker of heaven and earth, the sea, and everything in them-- he remains faithful forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[| It Doesn’t matter where you are now, What matters is where you CAN go |  Don’t let other people’s opinions stop y… https://t.co/kdGv22cCvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @aafcommanders @DarylJohnston Will @bracketdan break out the clown suit for Moose? It worked so well for Troy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheilakathleen @selfstyledsiren @szacharek @TomiLaffly This has probably been done to death over the last 40 yrs,… https://t.co/xNkWYcDYN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arfness @teepeecariad @StokeySye @AlastairMcA30 Oh, you will be fun to debunk. Vaccines can and do cause cancer, a… https://t.co/cjS7iUDywf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This movie somehow eerily predicted Jake Lloyd’s future. This image is actually kinda sad. https://t.co/JfQ0brbItS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You play and perform better and faster when you know what you’re doing, in porn it’s the same way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share your thoughts with Beto on the issues that are important to you: https://t.co/bKtc3BeGkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got winter weather warnings on my phone last and wake up and we basically got no snow, dafaq Iowa?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman @yankees Now is the time to sign @Bharper3407 Don’t let him slip away. Let’s get it done!… https://t.co/WX92bkKQM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnDePetroshow I believe he orchestrate the letter and that never got the attention he wanted it to so he fabrica… https://t.co/q786DSaqkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aspencountry @ShiCooks @KshrGirl @Barry_Cinematic @lindafreeman_ @RCNaturephotos @solhme Thanks Michele!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT @TurnerSportsEJ @TheJetOnTNT @SHAQ what is that hot 🥵 stuff Pay me 2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most beautiful 90-Days in Epcot start tomorrow! Who’s looking forward to this year’s #FreshEpcot? . . I’ve been… https://t.co/UnaHIanG1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VelVelHoller @BoomerangToons OMG!!!!! You Like Tom And Jerry And Old Classic Cartoons Too!!!!!! You Are My New… https://t.co/117QcNmISi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_migglest @_steamy_mac Yes that works i gave up drinking today for lent so i could just focus on getting high lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BugMartini I think I watched about 5 minutes of one of the reruns before I realized my brain was losing oxygen. Fo… https://t.co/KmiociUn35]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re all given the incredible ability to love recklessly... do not take it for granted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump mr. Eric, 60 minutes interview, such demagogy, will be very positive , if we could meet,I’m ready to don… https://t.co/w2thLF9N5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many PNW transplants “miss having four seasons” after experiencing one week of a Northeast winter? This is call… https://t.co/clRb1UBQ8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember, kids: vanity plates should never be inside jokes that are unknown to the general public. They should be a… https://t.co/8tVIOOqOI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPattyNg @drsusan @sulane7 @RossHilliard @PGuptaMD https://t.co/o3Ao1J2uD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amymiller Well there’s one way to spend Valentine’s Day  I’m spending my first one as a middle aged single guy lis… https://t.co/1VVLRGOroP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dhenson22 @remedies_zack My girlfriend bought me the croc slippers for christmas 😁👍🏼😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sqirl's Jessica Koslow to open Onda in Santa Monica with Gabriela Cámara: Jessica Koslow, the chef of Sqirl in East… https://t.co/3n0qGC1GQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashLynEA Thanks Ashlyn! Also just so you know you were always my favorite float coworker at UVH. Love that we’re both bad ass nurses now :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earthquakesApp Salmo 50 14 ¡Ofrece a Dios tu gratitud, cumple tus promesas al Altísimo! 15 Invócame en el día de l… https://t.co/icA0iFXvcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn 😭 Cody Garbrandt stays opening up when he starts throwing haymakers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Into the Blue #blue #teal #Timothycolephotography #photooftheday #think #pose #model #atlantaphotographer.… https://t.co/c9wyVtTK5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Achievement Unlocked: @ZILLAMOROLL and I are sitting next to each other watching Dark Shadows and we each have a cat on our lap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chico adolescente da un bello discurso el día de su adopción. https://t.co/nqph3IOCoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flea333 Hal Blaine was a hero here in Western MA. Someone from our little part of the world made it big-time! Rock in Peace, Hal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megagenesiz @SarasotaPD @elenitaLenDimal @SONATURAL100 https://t.co/iSk7flRZ2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hdawgxoxo Considering this guy thought spain park was a suburb, Im not too concerned with his opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RexHuppke @ParkerMolloy If there were safety in their home country, they wouldn’t need asylum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steves_tire In this video, driving is just like skating and driver is a ice skater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Sinatra @BringBackTheBuz You need to go watch some of his videos online then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jontweetRVA I understand milking the clock with Bone out, but we are shit when we slow down]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topherhoefer @TheMaryLambert @Madonna id say it’s serendipitous, but many things happen for a reason.  #andsuchas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not saying that any of those three took advantage of Epstein’s “hospitality,” but if they did, it should come a… https://t.co/xE0khHh8mt]]></document></documents></author>