<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ Abortion is not immoral 100% of the time, sometime abortion is necessary and sometimes it’s is selfish.… https://t.co/JU34Uauaxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Further on Kings impending coaching search:  Though organization likes Marco Sturm, will not be the pick for this c… https://t.co/rXCX9Bwndd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarlyRiveraESPN "I'm a @Padres  Since day one, we knew this was the right fit."  said no one ever 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unclejoz @Patricia_Traina GTFOH lol! The only way OBJ gets traded is if they offer a boatload.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimJonesSports Very good trade. And I look forward to the 35 points a game we’ll score. But it just means we’ll lo… https://t.co/PL5CICuoWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenagiovinazzz @Unsolved I remember the days of Unsolved Mysteries &amp; America’s Most Wanted. Quite the time in television!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For at least the fourth time in recent years, a Circle S Ranch truck crashed, causing immense pain to turkeys. YOU… https://t.co/vX2nrDuQ6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign up for mission training Sat Mar 30 nlcconway https://t.co/Yf9HsHLmm8 @ New Life Church https://t.co/G2PF2AF56G]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks you never got to be apart of our lives growing up, but you will never be forgotten. Stay strong 💪🏽 dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jacks from Fort Lauderdale Florida. So sweet pretty dog...♥️♥️♥️♥️ #preetydog #pitbull #fortlauderdale #usa… https://t.co/23jpOq64d0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s tea:            )         )        )     )     (         )       )      ) _(___(____)____(___(__ (__ \… https://t.co/kCKEnr8ss0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article. @PhilDaMann  @ShaneyFink  @AbrahamDeWeese  @SeattleSportsU  @SeattleUBase  @GoSeattleU  @seattleumbb… https://t.co/RzmfLu4rrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrestling season has ended.  So we binge, Bolling's vs Gigantor round 3. Bolling's win! #2-1! https://t.co/TUyIbcyVc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conrucinski no barry, you suffer through that flight like the rest of us 🤣💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBenediktM @PlugInFUD @elonmusk Americans in modern USA (CC: @thenewjimcrow), the removal of undocumented children… https://t.co/UGacO52IBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no evidence and no proof and no embarrassment in him! Too bad his constitutes don't pay attention and keep… https://t.co/UzQDvkNAM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Kuzma has to push the “GOAT” to play defense 🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️💀💀💀💀 https://t.co/UZchE4bvP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caleb love is on a different level. On a sidenote I really like the upside of @mehlvillehoops Lamontay Daughtery I… https://t.co/PvjVNDUKz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MMAYNEZ I think it’s so dumb there’s a direct bart connection. There should’ve been a airport connector from mill… https://t.co/fFThnNvAvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoooeeSchmooooe @Benjamin_P37 @ThatGuyTraviiS 35 wins that’s a lot of rng luck for standard haha but give me whate… https://t.co/Dp4SnNrVre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLhistorygirl That’s a great trade for Ottawa. Gets Duclair out from under Torts and closer to home where he could flourish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rcvuGMjTr8 #Classical #music in @stlmissouri this week https://t.co/EA7iCLyopw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hotel moans (number 127)...   1) No hot water in the sink...am asuming will have to run the tap for the next two ho… https://t.co/e4JfaJw971]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week’s crowd in Lafayette wouldn’t even pop for Roman’s return. #RAW https://t.co/GTbpZMF9Ca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your a complete moron, cops and school kids are dying and you create a fake crisis that the border… https://t.co/7bgol0PJWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good boi protects us from Alien invasion 😂  hahahha🐶 vs 🛸 @ Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/zK85BefnMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @ComfortablySmug Shady @USATODAY twitter account did more damage than any of them tbh by stating as fact th… https://t.co/ynDRTbMXO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terencecorcoran The DPP noted that SNC Lavalin didn’t meet the prerequisites for a DPA,and JWR probably agreed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevincwalsh @ElbertLin Yes, and lawyers matter a lot in our justice system, which as Posner used to say all the ti… https://t.co/a0K8iRwrbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChancellorRoe Lesa, We need to have @cboldenjr come speak to our students.   I learned so much from him as a kid.… https://t.co/XYep9KNxxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of bitching about "free methadone" and continuing to marginalize individuals going to the clinics, how abou… https://t.co/6gj22E7fOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zcollins_33 calm down mr. 6.8 ppg/4.3rpg. You just look like a young and dumb bench player trying to play with the… https://t.co/wv43XNTW4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ageybaby36 Umm you needed them to tell you this? Couldn’t you tell by how toasted you get when your white self is out in the sun?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@mcall Top 5 Concerts of the Coming Week (extra): +++ @TylerHilton at Philly's @worldcafelive:… https://t.co/eGjr6jjg1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who have no record of what their forebears have accomplished lose the inspiration which comes from the teachi… https://t.co/esYDlUQpsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, you're out of ammo too, right? "Yeah, Jay. I ran out a while ago." 😂 . Mark and I learned some stuff when sh… https://t.co/BQfnltbmou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing about this picture is look at the smiles:) # thisiswhatitsallabout]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still consider you friends, @spgreenhalgh and @a_llie, regardless of outcome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenInYeIIow @princessmom122 @imillhiser @NateSilver538 @SeanTrende Pick a metric any metric and he is in the lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drove eight hours yesterday to get photobombed by Uncle Bruce. @ Tickets Pub &amp; Eatery https://t.co/ygGll4v0aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArthurCDent @catedempsey Oh boy howdy did I! That's a story for another time, but let's just say I still have trou… https://t.co/3CcLLW3p06]]></document><document><![CDATA[So retweeting this is good, right @NxtLevelBB.  I do enjoy highlighting good team wins and play of others on teams.… https://t.co/tvqPW72QlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[thelacsmusic   #TheLacs #CountryBoysParadise #CountryBoyFresh #190Proof #KeepItRedneck #RedneckRockstar… https://t.co/ydMf5nETsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG @kaceytron and I see eye to eye on streaming categories "I started streaming IRL recently in the just chat..."  https://t.co/l0Y1zuhPOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryannlisanti At least you owned up to using "nigger"....I'm more afraid of the undercover "nigger" users.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News: Just confirmed kyledaniel.music as the opener for the Tootie and the Blowfish World Tour.  Also you… https://t.co/GplvTQkAmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most succeed because they are determined to! 🐅💪🏾 @ The Downtown Cultural Arts Center https://t.co/GOG816y40t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SATXRepublican @migrantsaid It dont work that easy, it takes about 20year, most people do not want to leave there… https://t.co/c85u3pDqo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Bettman’s presser giving comments on the induction of the Honky Tonk Man to the WWE Hall of Fame]]></document><document><![CDATA[I rather not say a thing cause a man leads by example Rosebudd🌹🙏🏾 #chapter35begins salute @JayRFogle 💯💯💯 @ Tempo Lo… https://t.co/23h49uaIbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When is the last time that UND had both the starting goalies suffer injuries during same season?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGJOEONTHEGO @LipscombMBB @CaseyAlexander_ @WSMV Haven’t had me on yet 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole naija parenting discussion is way to complicated for the TL.... a ton of context missing on both sides of the discussion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immigrants arent the whole issue, its the people who are allowed to have guns who shouldn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay did they really just show a clip of Rami not singing for his Beat Actor nomination? Ouch. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMaluskeCTV @CityWindsorON @CTVWindsor You found my spot! 😍 FYI: I sit at first padded chair, next to table]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasmAndMore @AaronSuttles @JHPlott_ @groovybrian66 Right after the football game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Joe, you have my sincerest condolences for the loss of your dear, precious mother. God Bless You All.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elliot_rizzardi I just read the statement:  “Contrary to press reports, we have not received any links to videos s… https://t.co/GTELiFDsc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheeseheadlucy @TheRickWilson @MollyJongFast I mean while taking the pictures with all the " Famous People" what a… https://t.co/DM3hRYFpd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[One recurring theme I continue to hear is the US used to be great at building really big things (bridges, tunnels,… https://t.co/SbYFAdq2Jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great War Update, Mar 11 , 1917: Balkans: Battle of Lake Prespa. The Allies start the Spring Campaign in Macedonia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit is so TOXIC, are ppl not allowed to grow and change anymore? Stop wasting time calling youtubers racist f… https://t.co/DRaVDitrEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino And monkeys might fly out of your butt, but it wouldn’t be the way to bet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to participate at the Virginia Beach Republican Womens Club Luncheon and provide a legislative up… https://t.co/d0iYYyuWyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICU_Recovery @JAMA_current Never could have been a part of it without you and your guidance !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeGuest1 @rgjournalist @petehoekstra Right on!! Hoekstra should have done like trump - don't communicate anywher… https://t.co/6LpgbihCKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman I saw name trending and thought someone found some dirt like they are doing with John Wayne hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said, starting a true freshman QB and replacing almost your entire offensive line doesn’t scream better… https://t.co/NiYS1ykl1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twofriendsmusic It’s Wednesday and I can’t find it on your Spotify page 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LahavHarkov I am sorry, Lahav, but I do not understand your comment. What did Likud do that was fake?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneMarie obviously you’re allowed to sing about whatever you want, but it sounds like you’re trying to turn domes… https://t.co/1f0QUcdwJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTsOnline @matthewamiller it will be interesting to see how Senate Republicans handle derogatory information from… https://t.co/Mlq6hrfPot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe True to a pt as usual u mix facts with poli opinions.  The correct statement is clearly owners collu… https://t.co/bBQaD46AfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[P.S this surfboard belongs to a transient patient who refused to leave it behind to get to the hospital. So now it… https://t.co/cjWOfDZl5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drterrysimpson Shocking Terry! Btw the number of naysayers is getting smaller and smaller...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @OrinXavier: Post 10 images that reflect UR treasured childhood toys and hobbies--no… https://t.co/vaDlNzvZ8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not my circus, not my monkey. Not my circus, not my monkey. Not my circus, not my monkey. #mantrafortheday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll go ghost and no one will notice. Come back n everyone think will different]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markomac316 @steph93065 @AOC And how did the far left treat Al Gore? https://t.co/qZpsAs8vJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonelevation @JustEric It snowed in Scottsdale and Tucson last week.😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a lil upset at myself and I feel like I wasted money buying this “slightly sweet” tea instead of buying the reg… https://t.co/QiCABumBeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This LA thunder is so rare that I thought I was living in Pacific Rim 3 just now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillClinton was the 🐐 with this speech. This was my moms Democrat party right here. Where did this go? Can we plea… https://t.co/GyIuadoRbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gamergal67 Never said they both weren’t. I just said I think it’s dumb that Carmella’s getting the brunt of it whi… https://t.co/1ztEd2rax4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josietruong @LandersonLuke @ElleEos @msmacb @GregShe36955017 @nowthisnews @AOC If they want to keep there native w… https://t.co/p9jQYaQeoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Build an Easy DIY Acoustic Panel Frame https://t.co/y0hUaTCRNw via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lyrics to this song have kind of an MGTOW vibe: watch out, she wants another baby! #NowPlaying All That She Wan… https://t.co/hST9B13DmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @rotisbon and congratulations for a good success for Senator-Elect MKB @ Whitestown, Indiana https://t.co/6YPQGNp1rX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#trifecta next #weekend #FlukesIrishPub @curransirishinn @TollManJoes26 #livemusic #acoustic #philly… https://t.co/6YwKujuEE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Types of literary conflict:  Man vs. man Man vs. nature  Man vs. self  Professor vs. YouTube autoplay]]></document><document><![CDATA[After that they came back out, welcomed on a fantastic understudy and went on with the show - just before “The Rain in Spain”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[USMC Cadence - Mama Can't You See.flv https://t.co/ODro87N7T8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 2.1 mph SSW. Barometer 30.239 in, Rising. Temperature 59.8 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 51%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great trip to KC and heading home just as “the weather” is moving in.  Thanks to all my family and friends for you… https://t.co/KzSsFSv0ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last tinges of dawn #sunrise #nofilter @ Turner Reservoir Loop Trail https://t.co/Z5v8aV7OFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnsmntfuture those kyries at practice today are lit! What are those? Any news on UFO? They black or navy? Heard duke pe QS late march!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time learning from some of the best in the country at the Notre Dame Clinic last weekend!   📸:… https://t.co/oUX3J3K937]]></document><document><![CDATA[*calls work*  Hi, this is Tony I won't be into work today. I can't adult.  Other person: I'm sorry what?  Me: My fi… https://t.co/BAwk0gRQIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MImperatoWESH Because this little bugger woke me up! https://t.co/iA7AhuFanX]]></document></documents></author>