<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Annoying medical update 101: 7 days into this illness -- slept through my alarm this am yet somehow still managed t… https://t.co/tBrnqLI99Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm usually the last up, but my dog snores so loud, I have to ask myself who the fuck is still here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥇Con Sue Photography and Design🥇  🥇Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥇  🥇This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/8NEl881LGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outsiderz 4 Life feat. Aaliyah - "Ain't Never" (with lyrics) https://t.co/7W6GepnDuD via @YouTube @nknewsorg… https://t.co/48GxNu4UyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLBlackStar That's cold all this racism all because of one man this racist Trump they all going to burn in hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maretorliss @latimesfob SO MUCH. *chugs wine and whistles and walks quickly away* 😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a lovely family #dinner at @marissamiceli tonight. The boys were okay,  the food even better. Really dug the… https://t.co/yqC2IxBvqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave it to me to lock my keys in my car, while it’s running for an entire 12 hour shift!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dicen que una tristeza compartida es media tristeza... Y qué una alegría compartida es doble alegria... voy por la media.. por ahorA :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtmoorejt I was in a meeting, so no worries. But I think you’re wrong! Sansa is an incredibly complex character, e… https://t.co/YjzJBP7N8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you interested in Alpha's DC Power training courses? We've added new dates (May 2-3) to the Advanced Telecom DC… https://t.co/ZBZlyRxKn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin' with this sweet boy for a few days. #wereonthesamepage #lazyrainyday #raindaysandmondays #macnme 💙🐶🐾 @ Memp… https://t.co/0mhXbAne0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else works retail/customer service and has to do this ALL DAY? 😂 Happy Thursday beauties! 💕 @ Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/B8gwleCkl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your new, very religious coworker adds you on social media https://t.co/Ik8Yi2Qugd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Mom With PTSD: Journey Down The Rabbit Hole - https://t.co/s0WtbXHDPE via @oc87rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 18th #dool #days  Tues Mar 19th  @gregrikaart @ericmartsolf https://t.co/fsEuxm9BNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️@K12AlbemarleLab truly, I am just extremely honored to be given the opportunity to work with your team. The care… https://t.co/ARfYbqDuXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been a little lazy with this account so today is a great day to make some new friends. Hello,… https://t.co/7MMLcPBmpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In light of #TuckerCarlson trending on Twitter for some unsurprising reason, I once again hope to brighten your tim… https://t.co/TuGTgiUQIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CentristSM @brianstelter @JudgeJeanine @21CF This is about @JudgeJeanine who works at Fox News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dave Taylor speaking the truth on sharing his light, “Why those kids behave for you and not for me? Cause I love em.” #TEDxDaytonSalon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s the day. Come eat spaghetti to support RBHS Spanish Students. #RedBud132 https://t.co/mzqpLtFYoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m about to cuss erryyybody out at fedex 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost been 11 months since Shawn passed away and it seriously seems like just last week he was alive. This ye… https://t.co/Tonasf6Ujf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpikeUnderFire @Chronic_FLKeys @beachbumbjtc Ok, hanging in there!!!u?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwheels74 Can’t listen without your body making spontaneous movements.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time we got in the car for the past week, my 5 year old nephew said “turn on kiwi!” I’m slowly but surely tur… https://t.co/icFhbKaJhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curvy_tweets @MarshallRamsey The university has a fundamental problem.  It is public property and hard to deny acc… https://t.co/c5O9MuNmvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jezebel BUTTHURT LIBERAL MEDIA ATTACKS Tucker 🤣😂😂😂😂😂😂....https://t.co/QyswJF5Cq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyPlateauLife @BarbMcQuade @matthewamiller Russia, do you think they going to allow one of their own get some time. No Way😜😜😜😜😄😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE ICE BABY! The temp is starting to drop and road ways are getting a bit slick. If you’re out on your morning com… https://t.co/5ZW34SxaUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Housewife by Valerie Keogh @ValerieKeogh1 @bookouture #bookreview #thehousewife https://t.co/YhcSncgSa7 via @BeritnBooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theambervaden The darker the better if you don’t want to damage your natural hair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casers92 @jboucek @dallasmavs @BEDGEAR I loved the “being present”. That got me! #maverickwomen @bedgear]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would keep trying to show her and panic like I'm a bad pet owner. Lol The hamsters drinking tons of water every t… https://t.co/MJzQmF55Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACShilton @TimHerrera Encouraging kids to only go to elite colleges for j-school is my #2 media pet peeve, right b… https://t.co/QhF4Y3Vhmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you see someone’s phone and they have you as “DON’T ANSWER - Lauren” like damnn who hurt you?! #oopsitme]]></document><document><![CDATA[will i cry in public for the fourth day in a row today? make your predictions, folks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @StevenRCorey1 Hmmm... he actually stated this during the hearing hence @Jim_Jordan shocked response. I b… https://t.co/BAmDWOWNt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kid just counted to 7 like shes been doing it forever https://t.co/CbDs0yh9rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't trust anyone who doesn't like ketchup or chocolate and you shouldn't either and that's that on that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cristin89731749 @FundacionBADAN Tengo disponible el filgastrim en el edo. Zulia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting news in the tech industry!   Compass just acquired Contactually, an AI-based CRM platform designed specifi… https://t.co/bvcsYkBFnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your dear friend and college roommate see your old car from back in the day! #hondacivic https://t.co/Vdarr9fGYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @HoustonRockets did that I woke up to victory they beat the @warriors 118-112 #RunAsOne #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very, very proud of @cldarveau and his hard work in @APEX_DCS this year. His video and website work are incredible.… https://t.co/sUjSt57ktA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we're staying at @Home2Suites by @HiltonHotels and we just found a used tampon in the dish drawer. Definitely on… https://t.co/06CrMJzgYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immediate family only. Frankly, if I’m on, my extended family isn’t even getting my #.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to attempt to host a #NOTHBAYMeetup in Rochester, MN! If you guys are closer to Roch than MPLS, please DM me @sutherlandsteam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Very impressive. I would have shot the other guy too. Good thing I’m not a cop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa_hiser Oh I went to look for that photo immediately but it was too far back and I haven’t had my coffee yet today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would eat this every day, all day, no question ❤️ https://t.co/HDgaRmZDsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Don't you know that he thinks he's the one to everything first and best?🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in Everett do it at night after the parking enforcement go home for the day.  Yeah, try walking home and hav… https://t.co/wBQlSleX6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS The only story line that I’m concerned with has to do with Hope getting Beth back. Nothing else matters.… https://t.co/3luvxgHnEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EduEngineer @SpeakerPelosi @JoaquinCastrotx @realDonaldTrump There is no EMERGENCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg!! @shanananonsense look at this post.   Sooooo… we gonna talk about the fact that Molly has a mouth frog? https://t.co/gAdspx3mRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjones524 @StephanieKunze @GroundworkOhio @StephanieKunze is the best &amp; we’re blessed to have her rep’ing our district!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m way too jolly this morning after getting home after midnight. It must be because I have my sidekick @AReynaKTVO… https://t.co/DBqCsPe1Iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[great advice from the book #howfullisyourbucket #goldenrule #praise #recognition #strengths #give #leadwithlove… https://t.co/vQc0I1YHb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 THIS toxic water is the EMERGENCY in the United States today.... NOT building an effing wall!!💙Can’t… https://t.co/5G1JGofP8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet people who put their 🧥,🎒, 👜, 💼 in the overhead bins on full ✈️ are the same people who don’t return the 🛒 to… https://t.co/7akeJ9cRxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was raining so I had to bring his surprise picnic inside. Happy Valentine’s Day my love ❤️ https://t.co/4hER28b20b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS approval rating in GOP hits 93%...Just sayin #MAGA #MAGA2020 #QAnon #Trump2020 #GreatAwakening #WWG1WGA… https://t.co/nqRKqIwZ8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought I’d be one of those people who starts to virtually plan their wedding before they are even engaged… https://t.co/LBjawRYJXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRushall @AnnettePimentel @ab_varaham Wow. Congrats! This sounds so inspiring!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil Kim use to be so pretty... celebs really go overboard with the surgeries]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how 1/2 lb body fat looks like.  So far, I lost 3 of these, for a total of 1.5 lbs of body fat.   . . I sta… https://t.co/I0Hc92aaCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/8ErWQHh38P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndyLinda1414 Set the screen for channel change so I can watch it too! Or try to.. u know how it is..,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sunday morning everyone! Blessed to be starting my morning watching @GoodDayAtlanta w/ @RyanBeesleyFox5… https://t.co/HbzoZYGwZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s National Love Your Pets Day so enjoy some of my babies. https://t.co/NRVEiaIrQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to make a living @ Chattanooga, Tennessee https://t.co/kC3dqKVOzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 You wouldn’t want my AC bill.  Yes, we have the air on again today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 goooood morning what’s it doing outside I’m afraid to look ❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WangSquad alexanderwangny 🖤 @ Boston, Massachusetts https://t.co/BV1GqrpTjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stepandrepeat #charityevent @BRAVOMISTRESS #soflo #miami @ Miami Downtown Brickell https://t.co/EKkyiu6M8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw on Facebook my client got engaged at the resort I booked for her in Mexico ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy bday to the person who knows me better than I know myself 😂💛 @natalienlayne ily to the moon and back]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisinghram @SenMarkey Aweeee.... that common sense factor doesn’t allow for finger pointing though. All this du… https://t.co/c8pYGMkS5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[And these are the same people who tell the average Americans how to live pushing their ideology 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting courstide with my sister at #HBCUNight at the @ATLHawks game! Two proud HBCU grads right here. #spelman… https://t.co/I6d6ldPDd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend at #seacsm19 with great people! Looking forward to the National #acsm conference this May https://t.co/FT9x0JJKEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDavis_365 @PolarbearNL Most definitely . Lyrical rap be on to something . It’s all vibes but it’s real life .]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @netflix - now every month I have to go thru my bank dispute charges process because I’m triple-charged (@ 3 dif… https://t.co/uaROZszrs8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dhermann5 It was beautiful!! Perfection at its best with the lighting, their voices and chemistry, and the camera… https://t.co/oQwBVfhckI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really pray that Michael's name gets cleared.. that it's proven without a doubt that he's completely innocent.the… https://t.co/661GGutrKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinktaxiblogger I would start with Boston proper, so would exclude those neighboring towns as well as Allston/Brig… https://t.co/SPO5h6OZWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bridesmaid of the CENTURY! Click to watch her epic toast. I don't care what anyone says... https://t.co/X1T32lcI8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the major keys to life is learning lessons and growing as a person without allowing feedback to impact your self-esteem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maegahan The cannoli was last night! I may or may not have had an assorted box of pastries and perhaps had to take… https://t.co/5mWkxRvqTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the Things the New Anti-Weed Crusade Gets Horribly Wrong https://t.co/R15ICiEtXp via @vice]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I move, you move #standup @ludacris  The @davegrutman Experience   ☀️ 🏖 🏝 at the #GOYA Grand Tasting #SoBeWFF… https://t.co/fMpjb0g6e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend just got my initial tatted , wow. I’m speechless 💖💍 https://t.co/Z8uXyKkT6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdb502 I tweet what I feel, if you don’t want to see it or disagree feel free to block me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some special VIP’s will be invading Stilly this weekend...  #2020OrangeVzn 🤠🆙🔫💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walter_Eg0 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump I am sorry I meant this to go to Brian K. How do o take this off?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not gonna try be something I’m not just to impress you that ain’t it cheif]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my old friends is about to ask me for money and I don’t know how to react]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh the #Youtube tutorial #influencers be having me rolling with that hand when they tryna show you how to do some… https://t.co/2j5uFyQnE6]]></document></documents></author>