<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Diddy Please keep Donald J. Mannion Mount St. Michael '87 in your prayers. He is having brain surgery today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackFritzWIP @JimBowdenGM They better get him with all this hype 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeflonJ0hn You can hear me say fucking unreal at the end and i cut the clip down to remove the profanities afterwa… https://t.co/EOfH3t0VJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lazy afternoon. ••  Sunnies and swimmies by @project_claude. #ILove🍆 @ Palm Springs, California https://t.co/Ypetv2ng2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Midgets were nearly blowout territory, but after a hook shot by junior Tallon Klatt, Dickinson closes the half… https://t.co/z1nl20E41B]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder when it’s all going to stop ‘.’ “ do y’all hear them to or am I just sheesh that’s crazy but not real “ Re… https://t.co/xCkBdX8Vel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wrestlerweekly @MikeParkerNJ @OldWrestlingPic @Larry112066 @dpeck100 @apriceins @ZeusKing_DARK @VintageProToday… https://t.co/T0lYe6dxbO]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when...  🎥 : @KleinschmidtJD @ ROOFTOP https://t.co/tqyFe19oBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Details Emerge About Kolter's Second Downtown St. Pete Tower 🏢🏗 https://t.co/ZieBUT8g4U https://t.co/TnijnZSDHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There’s only things that people did in past lives”  Remember that the next time you’re told about the past crimina… https://t.co/O8ILmX2ZaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inglewood Southside Christian Church: Pray Ahead : https://t.co/4h4r6ApaM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop by GNC in the Winona Mall - Winona, MN TODAY for the HUGE BOGO 50% OFF SALE!!!! BANG Drink Cases, One Protein… https://t.co/Qb1GNaeriw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in the process of writing Trumps resignation speech . Here’s the opening line ... Even though I was the best an… https://t.co/NZhtNd52uK]]></document><document><![CDATA[# I stand with South Sudan working class against the government decision to cut a one-day paycheck in order for the… https://t.co/BraZYwBE1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @ANGELAWHITE @xxxjewelsjade @CoryChaseXXX @kimmygrangerxxx @RICHELLERYAN @fallinlovia @JennyBlighe… https://t.co/DJEGQ8Hzxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[U only gonna relate if we are the same 🤷🏽‍♀️ #youeverbeenloyalgotbetrayed #foundtpeopleaintwhotheportrayed… https://t.co/cZcBVOV9Pc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get enough sleep and man it’s starting to affect my attitude. Y’all thought it was bad now. Y’all haven’t s… https://t.co/YL1azwgruW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I just seen Danny Glover on the red carpet-we at the spot getting litty watching @KTLA ...#RedCarpet #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hockey night in Des Moines, #IAWild fans. Two teams battling for playoff berths and a headliner concert afterw… https://t.co/uccF23ICos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bowen_jason @SGT_T_Fitness @realDonaldTrump I love your story thank you for sharing may God continue to bless your family❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 @DawnforNewYork You do seem like the perfect person for the office of Public Advocate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a winner! Congratulations Scott for winning the Golden Knights Tickets for tomorrow night! We appreciate ev… https://t.co/A8jO3KmYyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You want to have a code for slaying simulator it is:&lt;Qsm5an7&gt; RIGHT there… https://t.co/mfdigtAdOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure hope so im hollering done on guys race move do something. Dangit now see why im contemplating not going to r… https://t.co/KYjlV1q1Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TECH4ULLC @PanofSCU @TSNSteve Better yet, you run your franchise competently and create an environment where good… https://t.co/xnkde9EFGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive @SkyNewsBreak @AJELive @CBSTopNews… https://t.co/IRyXJoXrx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at City Food (Food Court) in Universal City, CA https://t.co/3ygQ1fF5a9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinnySeminole Starting as a recreational leader until I start transitioning into a rehabilitation supervisor posit… https://t.co/34YnlqpmZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angryark99 @cryptomarkets2 @FSCOTweets Canada, it's like Mexico, but without the nice weather and regulation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#orchidmania #clevelandbotanicalgarden #butterfly #butterflyphotography #naturephotography #nature… https://t.co/zeUZaRRNPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time you are in McLean, swing by @loklgourmet for some healthy and delightful snacks, along with their kombucha bar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstridSilvestri Apreciado compatriota Asdrubal, esa gente no merece que una vida valiosa, como la tuya, se pierda.… https://t.co/tXPdUA01AS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great event today! Congrats to Eastbridge Business Connections and Jason Kipfer for making it happen. Proud… https://t.co/ve0OBiNyRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a coincidence, Mark and l are retiring the same year.  #seeyouinvegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenBriney @KStreetHipster Man a whole album that is good, that means going back in time like Joshua Tree or Led Zeppelin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mephit_man @deathsaves @Metallica I now own the one to the right Arkon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michae Jones is now into double figures with 10 points as she finishes and gives @PennWBB a 58-56 lead with 2:54 le… https://t.co/WhKKDaM9Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kgray0121 @alainac425 Wait until you start to get into higher degrees. Such as masters and doctorates and differen… https://t.co/JOZlj8DrU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to Udon Noodles https://t.co/w4ryKOw03j via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Original #audio #content on #AmazonAudible now offering #comedy. “...the company announced a new partnership for or… https://t.co/Z4EHzO11tO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @by_the_ppl @CREDOMobile You’re a Jew hating police state advocate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put in that work yesterday in #ApexLegends #xboxshare https://t.co/tfZOlpAnlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up a few mins ago, and listening to EDM to start my morning off right! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bless up to Jenna for this article. Honestly...it’s not difficult though🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TomGReid @Kathrynclang @socialwebcafe You go to bed at 4:00AM!? Why? #SocialCafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @PillsFor @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @ewarren @SenGillibrand @amyklobuchar @BernieSanders (Weiner’s l… https://t.co/ZecQwTnPkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My niece serving in Japan reported today that she’s more stoked to start wearing pants than to get to call home each week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebenkampfarms @MaizeingPete you want this smoke https://t.co/Za4JDk8Rsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frescomills I’m glad I went to his last concert. I didn’t even know it was his last. Now I’m having an #existentialcrisis 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have faith in your journey. Everything had to happen exactly as it did to get you where you're going next! Gradua… https://t.co/QDI1bL8llx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geokaren @emigre80 @notcapnamerica I saw it back when it came out. Didn’t know it’s hard to find now 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spoutsmith @SpeakerPelosi @HouseGOP @DCClothesline Horse face must be removed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaboybud why because someone reported a serious hate crime attack and they took it seriously?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump wants $8 billion for his vanity wall. How much of that might end up in his pocket? Maybe he’s building his de… https://t.co/mp6CHjGr1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canisius up 65-64 with 1:55 left in the third overtime. St. Francis ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz día de la mujer, hoy en su día deben saber más que nunca que vale más un corazón con lindos sentimientos y un… https://t.co/V1ReP7ukot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acentodiario El líder de este señor es Danilo o Miguel, yo creo que los verdaderos Peredeistas si es que existen,… https://t.co/O00pIVnT4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayvz No idea but I’m certain it’s regarding the wait until @GameOfThrones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWW_ATC It was ugly before the strike and ever since. FCC will have to savor the one shining moment and learn from the rest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road bills moving as crossover day approaches - WV MetroNews https://t.co/SQmW6hYlev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bo_Ty_Dawgs @DukeMBB @TeamCoachBuzz Buzz has been playing without his top player for weeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[willhennessy23 can't say goodbye @ Holiday Inn Resort Orlando Lake Buena Vista https://t.co/thR2slKreu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who thinks losing half your salary or more to support people who don't work is insane in my opinion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toronto- Asif Zardari remain At Large. To arrest this CIA/Iranian Agent is a "Security Risk". As per our challenge… https://t.co/RPQee8o6S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp, I’m sorry Vegas, accidently brought Ohio weather with me https://t.co/Q0doBpKN9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Ivanka say's "AOC doesn't understand the American people like I do."   I say......when was the last time Ivank… https://t.co/9C7znw1sHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[You thought snow in slo-mo was cool? How about snow ❄️❄️AND fireworks🎇🎆in slo-mo! #SteamboatResort @skisteamboat… https://t.co/mCXKqCOELY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizunyan They were lighthearted but the joke “AntMan?? Is it too late to change the name” haha isn’t it a dumb nam… https://t.co/4lSLwvXDa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP to bad you fell in line with Democrats over the border.  We know your names and remember them at the vot… https://t.co/BvKMkES5Pr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasWYoungMD They’ll take one of several possibilities, but claim it is the only one. And juries don’t know any… https://t.co/7AcV3lbTF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also shout-out to @MilkDaddys he's really become a community leader and encourages people to attend grid. Super fri… https://t.co/kL2E5ujfy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gokaiger_Ranger @jetsfan24x7 Take it one game at a time. It's going to be tough staying in first. They need to go… https://t.co/xsk02MwavO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Masters and Game of Thrones all in one weekend. Reserving my couch now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKTS @PaulRudnickNY @Minetta_Lane @Real_JMHiggins @MsHarrietHarris @patiokerr Loved every second]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a couple of _____. #siblings #sisterandbrother #donkeys #springbreak #Florida @ Spotted Donkey Cantina https://t.co/dP17mbjQ1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I get motivated every single day? by Odedra Vijay https://t.co/4EzszAaInm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress Maybe a couple years. When do they open up shop in Vegas?  Imagine those tweets.  I predict Raiders… https://t.co/kcVLV95tar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freakyfootbruh Unless you have uncensored version, I'm sticking to my answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tssaa tried to watch the Mr and Mrs Basketball feed on the app and it wouldn’t let me login, or signup. Says enter… https://t.co/B1vORp0HZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[During Trump’s address to the media be started talking about Venezuela 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antivaxbritt Not sure what possessed me but I watched most of it last night, couldn't finish it. Not the least bit… https://t.co/wCWhNE29bh]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @AGU_Eos: Buzz Newsletter 8 March 2019. The Latest Earth and Space Science News! https://t.co/UQMGZMljH5 cc:… https://t.co/rJsoSHFKOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modern_goat @nowthisnews Hahahahaha. I like the nose of it. Crunch crunch]]></document><document><![CDATA[My one solace of flying back to STL out of West Palm is all the #STLCards fans on this Southwest flight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly. I’ve always been a huge #Apple fan but seeing @tim_cook go from principled leader to smiling - even willin… https://t.co/Onoi6hp1Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riding on the plane with @cam_beckum ... day off to a good start! Wheels up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindseyhoran11 @ChristenPress Apparently the braids make her excellent fast.  I always enjoy watching her play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestKyleNA Finish hunter bro, it’s worth it Akame ga kill Fate Zero AoT Bro I got more hit me up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw someone advocating for pineapples on pizza...It's be your own boys man smh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUCIOS,CORRUPTOS, podridos,descarados,incapaces, sinvergüenzas,sanguijuelas,encubridores,traficantes de influencias… https://t.co/7T88FkxrHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@familyfirstcorp @Bimbys @tweetvickie @Tllee386 @IPOBPill2 @nstar321 @GreenEyedLibrty @robin_delmar @DQuidic… https://t.co/seiidZfnE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people are out there saying “Duke still has other studs on their team they should’ve won easily without Zion” i… https://t.co/0kwg2GsZki]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized @pamelaadlon voiced Spinelli on Recess and I have risen to a new form. https://t.co/jWcaR53iaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of my sisters friends left so no I can go down stairs and do homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julioastillero @larbymx Solo aclarame Julio ¿Tiene  algo de malo lo que ellas están haciendo? ¿Que no todos los po… https://t.co/02swSAKvyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DatDamn_DOMO @rufj09 @RuiterWrongFAN Or something/someone. We can't possibly roster that many picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Dane for being named 1st Chair Trombone in the State of Texas at TMEA. GO RAMS! @Danegerousman… https://t.co/f3FNXL1q5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazyforcupcak4 @EdPowell63 @MollyJongFast @RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Every political and mas… https://t.co/KFSeTLQWVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alai2016 @TrevorPetersTV @calabro13sports @DeltaChiPurdue @WLFI What part of Putnam County you walking through right now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The significance of @SecAzar comments bear being tweeted again Finally someone is speaking the truth about US… https://t.co/CUblH8ZNPv]]></document></documents></author>