<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NBATV But hes not the greatest to ever to play basketball.... https://t.co/9btXHd1XSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was all about helping this birthday girl pick out some  new goodies. Happy birthday Michelle🎂 You look a… https://t.co/jNOk0PO5y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on the update: bonus week is next week and I’m sad but I worked over time and that’s time and a half $$$]]></document><document><![CDATA[He took me on a surprise trip out of town, booked a suite at the hotel we stayed at, bought me a new watch, and too… https://t.co/4rpO63j6UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No mueras por un hombre  Ellos son capaces de ir a tu velorio con otra mujer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontBeSnsiitive @mtracey People of my parents' generation believe corporate media's false and biased reports which… https://t.co/jIItY8RZdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[and then people out here’s saying aliens don’t exist, and we’re the only beings in existence. ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I Just like to shake my booty &amp; fall over like a frozen fish stick 🤣 https://t.co/1ZKk8h6O9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to learn how to meditate and just disconnect from my thoughts and surroundings... But how do you turn off the mind?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo cute my mom and selena called me at midnight to say happy birthday🥰🥳💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[TeeHee! They were there even if not in costume! #PartyOnWayne #PartyOnGarth #BohemianRhapsody 🙌 https://t.co/NyyMMGiVak]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEI certified dentist Silver amalgam fillings are made of approximately 50 percent mercury and when hated from chew… https://t.co/wUdyWMLqCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonBachman43 Nice! I’ve never done it sitting so deep on a hitter, usually I put it right off the front foot. But… https://t.co/jFf5dz9ZEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes, it’s FUCKED up that someone is even putting that type of stuff in kids videos but Milania knows to run everyth… https://t.co/ij4vHyjQRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteeOne @atensnut @BillNye You attack and insult people you disagree with and think you're morally correct. That C… https://t.co/gwuk5GungV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torgerson @seattlewinefood @Seattlemag @GlassVodka @adonisd @fortuitycellars I checked the list and they were not… https://t.co/JTqpHlYZmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[right now, advice is a “one size fits all” for preventing disease and maintaining health.   “precision medicine” is… https://t.co/UlYbfagWdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[really @cosmo??? the chick who said "Guess what, honey? There's a lot of dick out there for me to suck to get on a… https://t.co/9ya645wj1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[What beer should I drink tonight? @brewdogusa doghousecolumbus @ DogHouse Hotel Columbus https://t.co/CR0JJx6aTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Australian Pink Floyd - Chandler Center for the Arts https://t.co/gCDc3tBTo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So great seeing my amazing friends and had the best time !! Love you dennisoconnor kyledavidthorpe and mike_cavallu… https://t.co/SMoPctbqZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JtmYd @Sami_Alabami @ramin__alizadeh @SandraB16901827 @sami_ God bless you too. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRam2 @JudsonAthletics @JudsonISD @rina_hoops is a freaking beast. I have loved watching her play over past few years. She is amazing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the greatest country in the world, Texas! #TexasIndependenceDay https://t.co/MkzpMT96jH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smurphnoff The change of tempo in the music...I’m forever ruined. They didn’t get enough time together!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artceledelrey Slow down your breathing and write down at least 5 things you’re grateful for]]></document><document><![CDATA[since when does billie have 14 MILLION instagram followers??? she had like 200k when i followed her???? damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Google, show me a dystopian late-stage capitalist future: https://t.co/dCwQCGtiil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beelzebub has changed the political fabric of America for decades to come. Now is the time for us to stop normalizi… https://t.co/APZIhR5pHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cara and Zack are just pretending to hate each other in hopes of being paired up in a future challenge together. Sm… https://t.co/wecpJc5gdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi pals! Just as a quick heads up: I haven’t *officially* posted about my new website/ ebook/ audiobook yet bc we h… https://t.co/0XYyFhN2pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oyster, leek, #truffle 😋 manresarestaurant by chef  @davidkinch #DavidKinch &amp; latest CDC #NicholasRomero in… https://t.co/DnM9Bp25xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Such a sad state we are in. Every word he has told us is coming into an actuality.  What else does h… https://t.co/Pn3fIK7IUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckPol happy birthday 🎁🎂! Check @facebook many birthday blessings to you from many! Have a wonderful day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s lovely, friendly, fun and calm. She’s our fearsome leader of cornerstonemilfordct’s Purity + Peace hub! It’s… https://t.co/XPF1IpMv7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to have the opportunity to stand with @AndyMoffit and @RIFoodBank to support @GovRaimondo No Student Hungry… https://t.co/SDBxyfPRmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so butthurt when professors don’t email me back within 3 minutes after me sending an email]]></document><document><![CDATA[In celebration of our Three Year Freeversary (https://t.co/vxXFc3YphT) we are releasing TWO additional barrel-aged… https://t.co/cOjHfDhFIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[boy don't tell me that you chilled and smoked with a girl, went out to a bar with her, hung out all night, then too… https://t.co/mI0rRVyhgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is SINFUL to heap shame upon people for being human. it is a fucking sin to convince the vulnerable children in… https://t.co/RXz9JF5m3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I do is STREAM! #2019 https://t.co/ppXAi8Q6VV @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/SXkHzFODgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO HERE’S THE TAKEAWAY: my mom and I always have the wildest shit happen when we’re together, my mom agreed I shoul… https://t.co/cV5I3vvG3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[View from handsdown the best winery in #temeculawinecountry @Vindemia incredible staff incredible view cozy seating… https://t.co/u1QlgGuaew]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one knows but me and my fiancé have broken up and there’s this guy from my work and I am like slowly falling for… https://t.co/gO6A0PKbRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHilfiger @spidychelle zendaya saw mir tweeted this and went on the tommy hilfiger account to tweet her we love that !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Dr. Seuss!!!!!! Was honored to step inside your magical, wonderful world in our show last year 💛 https://t.co/YSi8gcJSqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and Gentlemen a friendly reminder: please check in on your friends that are moms whether they had a baby rec… https://t.co/0b5ueJE9DC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a millennial in an office setting  is nearly ending emails with “thanks for listening to my Ted Talk” 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing Pilates on the reformer (in California) is hands down the best experience ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tiffany by Big Oyster Brewery @ Tingle's Tavern — https://t.co/WTCFBUfKbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[How To Travel To Paris On A Budget https://t.co/o99LmL3sFb   #Europe #traveltribe #travel #traveltips]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom honest to God just told me to sign up for https://t.co/LzBD7nxQw3 wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good idea if you break them up for lies and propaganda And circumventing free speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy and excited for you @DebbieMcKeon - you’re going to do great things for your new team!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiwassee Tigers and Lady Tigers  basketball regionals are on the same weekend, Tigers at home, Lady Tigers at Oakla… https://t.co/V6ssk26tPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Gay Couples in #Japan Launch Valentine’s Day Legal #Bid to Marry   #care2 https://t.co/xNyWAvxhDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a reason for everything. If you don’t see the reason yet, just know that it’s there. It will reveal itself to you in time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeborahWilk5132 @AllotmentCat Why can't you be happy that the sad, lonely, sick cat isn't hurting anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have the perfect relationship because God knows there’s some shit we gotta work on but dang does it feel go… https://t.co/NaFScrkVcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnCarlson22 @BBulldog_Hockey Thanks for being part of the @BBulldog_Hockey journey esp with the big bros @jwilmes21 &amp; @LukeRegner]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It can be hard to figure out what a student was born to do, and it takes a special kind of teacher to figure it ou… https://t.co/S0xq71rbJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@setzacat I love that fountain.  Do you ever work in copper. I did for a while.  If you do let me know.  I have a b… https://t.co/6XlIwx38SX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Obama's popularity was what allowed him to overcome the Republican disenfranchisement of American Vote...… https://t.co/NMsEKSZOFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Retlouping @adamdobson123 @ashjamesphysio @AshisArmyPhysio @BillingMartin @CombatSportPhys I am not sure I agree w… https://t.co/gMEEuuO8VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night, I bought an eclair. A massive, delicious soft eclair full of custard-y goodness, covered in rich chocol… https://t.co/A11euwuM0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hairstylist used olaplex in my hair when she bleached/toned it platinum white and it is literally so so so soft and healthy. I’m amazed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheView I’m sure it’s just friendship, no kissing &amp; touching involved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilsteady How is Josie going to be in both shoes if this is set 20 years in the future?! 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michigan RD educates high school athletes the importance of proper fueling for performance https://t.co/qgrg16YpYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdonoghue @clarkvalentine Yeah! And when you have used them you should already be comfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaKostele3 @BTS_twt I like gravy on my biscuits 😉 #gravy 😈 https://t.co/7dcs8PZ83O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everybody it is a beautiful day in the neighborhood today for everybody who follows me and everybody who look… https://t.co/yHo6YVA8rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for humor . . .  Growing up, there was a poster by H. Jackson Brown Jr. titled, "Life's Little Instru… https://t.co/Mqc6zeqCwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump we trust your judgement, it's lead us down the right road so far! #AmericaFirst https://t.co/EoFP7k3qx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We CURED AIDS! Let’s see the World for what it is... Rumored Gossip Fakerszzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[queria comprar uma argola aqui mas estou sem dinheiro ate para comprar BOMBOM kk foda negas]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Cereal 🥣 Day!!!! ⤵️ #ScottAndSarah @949WQMX https://t.co/bzi2EtK0Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiHenry @hocnashville For the record, I was REEEEEEEL sassy about that when I went and mentioned it A LOT (if y… https://t.co/vJsTyiWQyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I blame Ryan.  Even when I get home from work at 5am it’s not so far fetched to think someone’s hiding behind the d… https://t.co/EvEVYVz3fC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoochhhhh @ja2cook @Cbp8Cindy @BiscottiNicole @confessions_cup @TheAngelOrsini @hmgivingsoul @FionaMorgan79… https://t.co/Yrn13C85WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevibooo mine are spaced out 3x a day + as needed and I usually use pill bags for timing but I should really find… https://t.co/bZ645IlD91]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing a kids Birthday party tonight...he's only Fifty... Great event space with a HUGE house PA!! Awesome!… https://t.co/MyPFagbmIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u r a man or talk to men or date men please do not talk to me for the next week, unless I talk to you first, thanks 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nothingcanseparateusfromhislove @ Ardmore, Alabama https://t.co/noktahDgZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t mean the media and the public shouldn’t worry about it. https://t.co/jrQhbxU8Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Approaching the Montana mountains on my #roadtrip with @sedgell1 @ Greycliff, Montana https://t.co/xKpmqMglfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katylee816 ✨ // styling @morganlpotter // #hair + #makeup #juliephaxay  . . belifusa // true cream armanibeauty //… https://t.co/U5dU7XMYbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at O'Reilly Auto Parts? We're hiring in #Pineville, LA! Click for details: https://t.co/KA80aZwiwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HistorianMum Thank you for pointing me to this. I'm constantly on the look out for non-text/visual based sources.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkBrazeau @nic24braz @kidderjen1 @CoachEricPogue @MottChildren @EBPartner @RareDiseases @debraOfAmerica… https://t.co/laCQbqrDVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very aware I posted this pic earlier buuuut idc. It’s so good it’s worth a double post 💕😂😍💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9Cx9ZPnT… https://t.co/swDMFKoF8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the #burnedinteacher Podcast where I talk with an #elementary classroom T who was put on the fast track t… https://t.co/mRJm6zSB1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I got to swim w a couple of whale sharks - something I never imagined in my wildest dreams! And tomorrow… https://t.co/DpWsm1Tbv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these girls, both had Homeruns today to contribute to the 11-0 win over Poly. Way to go! @ Grace Brethr… https://t.co/bdAq8xe7a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy Monday ✨ Have you been to @makerslv ?! Well this was my first time and let me tell you, everything was delici… https://t.co/KC8bbiESiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[People may not understand the impact they have on colleagues. Creating an environment of honest conversation is the… https://t.co/sLD7hSibRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I still up like I don’t have to be at my internship in 6 hours 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend sends me photos almost daily of her daughter while at daycare, and the daycare always gives her kid… https://t.co/KcVHvf7Kvi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CadeKnutson_ @madisonbraden_ bring cheetos and beer salt thanks love you]]></document></documents></author>