<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind @mattgaetz To be fair, he was probably drunk when he took this picture.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heavy partisan politics aside, I agree in principle.   In practice, I strenuously disagree. Inter alia, wouldn’t th… https://t.co/J1M4invErk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtEdgerlyFSP It’s a program, it’s never about just one kid. And who the hell said we wanted you back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[**Yo! I DO NOT OWN ANY RIGHTS TO THIS SONG** Just my own vocals... #glittersoundtrack  #mariahcarey… https://t.co/QXR0eVJPhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@floggingmolly killed it in #Indy last night ☘️ 🎸 https://t.co/dvGXaHYqiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mem_somerville Pollan complaining about the pastoral images, but that is what so many consumers have been conditio… https://t.co/qpTel3ZLzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @JohnStolnis @lizroscher @justin_klugh , any of you near the KOP mall tonight? https://t.co/l7dORicKOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bowman_SZN @GordonsWord Lol I’ve see. Sanchez and Barkley take the field years ago it’s trash and yeh thats cool you paid for trash too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liannerowepop @AndrewGillum Just likevthevCarvsn right???? You big dummy]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite buildings in the city @MrDuensing_lhs what do you thing of this Art Deco gem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StDr_JStocks @Curly_One Those 20 pair of reading glasses in the one drawer near the phone got me every time 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to show you guys my #new hat!! I purchased it from wish @ Ups Hub https://t.co/5sWcSbjRsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you had the honor to meet buen provecho founder today, and this drink is the bomb 😊 #2019 @ Mariscos La Rivier… https://t.co/6sVS1qNhYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayGTate @RadiNabulsi Let me know how Jadon performs this fall in the Gus Bus offense 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @RyanAFournier @CoryBooker Pretty sure you are only wishing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnny0723 @KeithSmithNBA Whatcha mean they’re trying to give it to him every possession]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBauters explains LIHTC's wonkiness, including it encouraging 100% affordable projects instead of mixed income… https://t.co/LyQlj2Hjhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever been so hungover that you have your thermostat set to 60 and it’s still too damn hot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in the day........when you heard this, you knew what time it was!! @ Florence, South Carolina https://t.co/soUCyZI1Pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GinaHaspell1 @Paul_Sacca @redbull Adderall brilliant no point in running That by Medical. All They ever Want to do… https://t.co/28UI4I9BjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that we’ve talked about it some, do you coaches prefer unilateral or bilateral squats and why? Can’t wait to hear!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Illinois Society of Fire Service Instrustors for inviting me to Peoria for a day of Leadership and Teambu… https://t.co/2U8l7m3aXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it sad that one of the things I miss most about leaving the UK is watching Graham Norton? It’s all terribly behind here...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJMcKean Wtf is with little Donnie’s handwriting? I always saw his scrawl from miles away as he’d hold up the bill… https://t.co/492LTobGWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carnojoe You got any new films coming out? I hope you can get into phase 4 of marvel. Would love to see what you c… https://t.co/pawCkxA3iv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatsWx @maxduchaine I would say the majority of the Nats most influential social media fans are definitely on that… https://t.co/Ui3mPthEkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always been a firm believer that it doesn’t matter where you meet, it’s who you meet that matters. Whether I m… https://t.co/dU9hJni0Fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DummieyBlondiey @Yamiche He's a Democratic Socialist which is the direction the Democrats are heading in. So Berni… https://t.co/bJKXcmu3bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC ALWAYS paid less than the value they create, otherwise there would be no profit for the executives and shareholders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's gooooo (@ CenturyLink Field - @centurylink_fld in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/0Wtforde0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgfair @brianstelter A real news article about "the media"  https://t.co/DPQY3BtQ7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love &amp; a quick selfie is in the air! Thanks, carlosdom112 for snapping this moment! 2.21.19 @MrsVillasana… https://t.co/WHAVt7UAvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greg_ip @davidmwessel Housing starts have had their weakest demand curve ever, just like new home sales have had a… https://t.co/wh0F7M67gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamsavage3 I don't blame you........, I've heard some shit about that fucking guy......, you can tell by lookin at him he ain't right.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_C_N_G come holla at me, imma get niggas together off the drinks no cap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman Very disappointed that the @Yankees made no effort to sign @Bharper3407  #borntobeayankee  #murderersrow2019 #shortporch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SQUILVAA @CallawayGolf I just played my first round today with my new Apex pro 19 irons.  They are amazing!   Wann… https://t.co/RkrGfATzUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKayaKhianKor This my profession twitter so I’m not going to read...but I will say never again. You got one time and one time only]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flash Flood Warning!  ⚠️https://t.co/7dhEwgTvsV  #ReddingBuzz #ReddingCA #ReddingCalifornia #NorCal #Redding… https://t.co/IlF3HbWKA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@985TheSportsHub This is a story of an old guy getting a rub and tug, what does it have to do with the football tea… https://t.co/NsbIPQY686]]></document><document><![CDATA[SF Glens Soccer Spotlight: Saturday’s SF Preps playoff scores - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/Ub0HOlkWTs 💭🔁♥️ @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anylaurie16 What in the holy F? 😶 he’s with HER?????  That has to be Peter Jackson’s CGI work, no????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFL_Journal when you are Namath you get all of the benefits. Like Farrah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYGovCuomo I am packing up and getting out of New York. Your liberal agenda is hurting my pocketbook. I am sick an… https://t.co/LWvT0Lbvz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live  stream for the meetings this week found at this YouTube channel.  https://t.co/JjkK2SdTJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCUPolo Women’s water polo will surpass men’s polo again this year. New goal for women polo is $25,000 #scupolo… https://t.co/lUbT7rdLW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[do people actually sleep until their alarm clocks go off? I swear I always wake up 10-20 minutes before mine does]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Mc Allen, TX? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/bHHM1vRwLZ #Simon #Retail]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mester_mark you’ve got to be a good sport to take a pie in the face 👍👍👍 so cool glad your suit is still clean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greenskull @Xbox Wait, is @aka_Scratch going to also start rawking the cowboy hat too!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Beast Caged in The Heart of A City // #70D #rokinon35mm #longexposure #nyc @ DUMBO, Brooklyn https://t.co/9K0tRrkanJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoingPOSTalAdam Stranger. First time I'm guessing, friend of second half presenters I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Medical Technologist/Medical Laboratory Technician - https://t.co/v5lR7JOuKK… https://t.co/3J1KJwF25c]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to respond against the pitch invader @JackGrealish1 @AVFCOfficial @BCFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely a wonderful way to teach #blackhistorymonth 💙💙 #readdaily #childrensbooks #library #swfl #capecoral… https://t.co/RdGQXilnzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[20 years later this album is still perfect. #MusicMonday @jimmyeatworld https://t.co/9suOk2WN9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see a journal going above and beyond revirewing manuscripts, to collecting data for future direction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickbegley @Mets Does make you wonder if someone could innovate around the intermediaries. How about reserve a sec… https://t.co/js0xJ5hhVW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GynaeExpert @DrJenGunter Some women may benefit from nonstandard doses and forms of hormones in compounded bioiden… https://t.co/eDemsxIlJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[0:47.6, Q3 — Cromwell 37, Old Lyme 29. @nickwrightcb80 is putting on a clinic inside, and has 12 points in the quar… https://t.co/waieuDLSLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 4.03 miles in 40m:36s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/Sp2nGbMRlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just planning on watching the Sporting Kansas City game on TV but thanks to mcrow91 coming through with the t… https://t.co/0l8I0XMj0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my limited studies bourbon &gt; scotch whiskey. I will continue to research and will update my opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scott Stricklin on Tucker Maxwell’s inside the park home run. https://t.co/TS2Ljik4Bm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Len Kasper out chere tweeting about Huey Lewis at midnight on a Friday. Legend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump if you think Manafort was treated badly pls take a look at Vincent Winslow.  Pardon someone that r… https://t.co/kBRocMvYDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I establish dominance on first dates by hanging a sledgehammer from my blue jeans belt loop]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a fantastic show seeing my friends Tommy Emmanuel and John Knowles finishing up their Heart Strings tour right… https://t.co/c7WWDyUE4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for having me! Lots of talk about @shudder #VideoPalacePod, @Neptunesalad, @thembob, @Chillamson, as well… https://t.co/BUfwLmzFL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really what is behind the new green deal? Communists know that the most effective way to control a country is pover… https://t.co/OFaXAZ1Nk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[are you ready for our Studio 54 party? We are announcing a huge sponsor this week, and then ticket prices increase.… https://t.co/dNUokG3Eg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typically i fuck with all genres of music, but after tonight I have to say IF YOU LISTEN TO COUNTRY RAP I AM JUDGIN… https://t.co/8J4vn6Zm8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone help me wish my sis a happy birthday 🎉🎊🎁 delta09_1999 @ Amory, Mississippi https://t.co/piqQO3io2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nuestros #Socorristas siempre listos para cualquier llamado de emergencia 🚨   ¡No olvides cederles el paso! https://t.co/H8QnTuCj5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAA33 @Global_Futures @mgriffin_uk This is really impressive! I love how light can be used in the 3D Technology! M… https://t.co/w2lEJwasN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SymetraTourCBO @KraigKann @aafAPOLLOS @nflnetwork @AAFWhizKid Off the charts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975Hans If true that officer should publicly exposed and Fired  and anyone in the BYU Administration or BYU Police… https://t.co/3C3iujpzVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quien más va ir sólo al dorado, necesito conocer raza, tira paro @JacoboWong !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to this crew and Coach Chris Coslett! 2019 BYC 9/10 IM Hoops Champs. They are a fun bunch to watch play 🏀 https://t.co/WdjOVVwjMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayo fellas if you get rejected just take the L like a man, you win some you lose some, don’t be a lame]]></document><document><![CDATA[As you can see @BrotherNature I'm THE GOAT WHISPERER🗣🐐🐐 https://t.co/QNw9PkBgR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so glad my mother figured out social media just in time for Valentine’s Day. She’s now sending me all the, “If… https://t.co/ph1GxNriEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanders folks said this week that Bernie would become the early New Hampshire primary front-runner...… https://t.co/a7M4gv6aLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[please don’t interact with my tweets it makes my ego grow in unhealthy ways please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in the #SICU, we had a review of #CRRT and dosing select antibiotics in the setting of various types of dialy… https://t.co/A8GDlBorAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The .@VanityFair #hopehicks fluff piece is exactly how every #Trump -tainted person will be able to go on without b… https://t.co/2zCgexJDlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tankotanko013 He’s always a problem! And wants worse? He’s such a fucking good sport it’s sickening!!!🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mintstro @carg0man @JoeMacofKC @dandemy @Doubles7605 @JustinBartels2 @BNightengale He hit 73 when he was 37. Next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrakman @2chainz @DJ_Muggs @__CRIMEAPPLE__ can you atleast attempt to spell Colombia right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @AOC @IlhanMN 80 Foot tall- 80 foot tall, that's how Big, I want my wall. make it Big , and make it l… https://t.co/JLgm21eH33]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmineSabia Don't forget, she got a sweet 10 MILLION DOLLAR deal from Netflix thanks to the Obamas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck these weak ass hand dryers, GIVE ME PAPER TOWELS OR GIVE ME DEATH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered to win this amazing PC Upgrade bundle from JayzTwoCents! https://t.co/V4ZZa2vBxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marsha07Marsha #theVenutiTHEOREM  This post  written pre President Trump. Convinced that Obama would never step do… https://t.co/9Flf60qRBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first questions for PMJT at the @csa_asc announcement on Lunar Gateway are about JWR testimony yesterday... muc… https://t.co/7APVdOFmBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyMill1 @jazzgardens You look beautiful Stephanie. I Enjoy your music. #Fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grgbkr37 @RodStryker Joe Biden a total disgrace to this country, a man that has spent his whole political career o… https://t.co/7FWmMpY2tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelRonHubbard I think you should re-read my tweet. You seem to be the person imagining what people must think or feel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golfdinosaurrr @MattGinellaGC @KipHenley @KeithNolan59 @GeoffShac @amandagolf59 @BobEstesPGA @TomPernicePGA… https://t.co/EreJbHo8Hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por comentario como este, es que Francisco no es el Presidente. No olviden que ya el Presidente estableció esta hoj… https://t.co/3ANtHnFr5O]]></document></documents></author>