<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Truly I am tired of this nonsense! Let’s get on with running this country ! Your doing a great job Mr President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone is truly happy with their significant other, then you should respect that and let them be happy. Don’t try to ruin it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't it time for the #BoyKing @realDonaldTrump to be indicted for lying under oath? Thanks to @RepHarley for askin… https://t.co/swEqZQHEZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwoz_neworleans @jazzfest @OffBeatMagazine @64parishes Haha thanks and nbd - it’s just funny because it’s an ongoi… https://t.co/TlOSAidXcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[work be so much better when u don’t gotta stay til the end of the night to split money with other bitches]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you are headed out for the evening or staying in - have a happy Valentines Day. #Feb14 https://t.co/xOwQSExOj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My mango pod doesn’t taste mango.. it tastes like mango peach cobbler” bitch what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoyGeorge Looks like the last pic my aunt took before she died but without her in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I look like after yoga class vs what I feel like after yoga class - thanks to @langface104 for a great Tuesday… https://t.co/WO4OWb9Aud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I snapped Mason my lips and he’s all “you got lip injections”, bitch I’m too poor for lip injections. Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being present in this moment, and looking at everything right now, he didn't make the right choice. He made the rig… https://t.co/MsW2YKDXFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off our #D104  D28 merch walk with @RYOBItoolsusa #Develop #SpringIsInTheAir 🌞 @John_Lerch @mbowen_… https://t.co/xjmUEgz9zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, my morning, f#$$in hubby listening to Fox News, wakes me up to vacuum before I go to 2nd job, then complains ab… https://t.co/9reiqPTUoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retaliating??  They were investigating whether your President was more aligned with Russia than USA. The many membe… https://t.co/m2Fh7KCHYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SummerCampFest Lit af!! Can’t wait for the @DizgoMusic boys to crush it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why you gotta love @BakersDT. Helping the IE in more ways than one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuckie, you and Nancy how the two of you have conned your way through Congress all of these years heaven only know… https://t.co/frhc76Wn9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #satchat friends! I’m Heather, K-5 curriculum admin from Hamilton, NJ! #HTSDpride https://t.co/Ox6GPeSJWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#doctors try everything against bullies. And when reason plus everything fails.... https://t.co/IPerzbjvpX.… https://t.co/CO36VIyjDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul thank you for speaking out yesterday! We appreciate you #HearUs ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[this heartburn is freaking killing me &amp; had me up the majority of the night 😭💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan One last thought. I Am not an asshole and I don’t think You are either. There are many ass holes i… https://t.co/OvaS6smX3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LancelotLinkSpy @ccl1311 @AMHotFlash @AviFlyGirl @harrisonjaime Thank you! You are right this can happen to anyone… https://t.co/dYkMT7PEBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% Disney characters. Mostly Eric from little mermaid. My imaginary boyfriend #shitnooneknows]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying my book for our School-wide W.I.G. for reading at least 2.5 hours per week with our students!!! #lex1reads… https://t.co/GnhfvjlvrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s formal weekend friends •• ❤️💃🏻 @ Trine University https://t.co/ooY9egKsJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up at 4am for work. Am I getting ready? No. I'm watching @Jenna_Marbles instead. Priorities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleeyun_nvaazun @Merry_Hippie @oldscool18 @Kiwegapawa @Christo84554035 @Samstongues @Vincenz42493578… https://t.co/nJWFvxtVdC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian you are NOT broken. You are hurt but never broken. You are a strong woman who can and will rise above this betrayal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the couple next door, I get that we are in college and it’s nice to have uh “fun” but I don’t want to hear your… https://t.co/1gNNLOZate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAndersonSK @KellyBlockmp You mean the #Globalist Agenda right?  WHY won't your party call it what it is?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this great review of THE QUIET YOU CARRY- it comes out Tuesday!!! Omg!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volume on! Can we all just take a moment to appreciate the cuteness of Pip’s random little “a-roo!” 🐕 @ Robinson To… https://t.co/qrWGPLEwQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should stay - going from catching passes from the 🐐 to anyone else (except Mahomes- and maybe Rodgers) would be… https://t.co/ePwOHshFWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta love the laughter 7 Things Volleyball Girls Know To Be True https://t.co/REPQ2ETEv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know people don’t think ADHD is even hard to live with, but it affects me every second of every day. whether i’m… https://t.co/wTIUWWIO4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[F•R•I•E•N•D•S•  es la mejor serie del mundo y a quién no le parezca se puede ir al carajo. 🌚 https://t.co/48qw7dqLGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had the audacity to mop the floor when I CANT EVEN WALK... IMAGINE me with a mop with my crutches and gimping aro… https://t.co/WdNAKYNOPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to daylight savings as soon as 1 hour passes, i will be 2 hours ahead. Wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole22___ none of those notifications are from our GC cause ours is dead 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@electrolemon The end of BlackKlansman totally fooled my parents into thinking it was a great radical movie too. Fo… https://t.co/ddC5kVVdUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner I really don’t think you want to state that. Think it through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonestLeYo Dude, I think we should invent a toy. Boxtag, we can work on the name later. Hear me out, it’s a box, w… https://t.co/ojm2P4kJ7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 45: Jamie Lee Curtis as Laurie Strode in the Halloween series. It’s really interesting to see this character gr… https://t.co/BxGEYwOzSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModernismWeek @theatomicranch looking good #Modernism #moderninteriordesign #modernistfurnishings @ Palm Springs C… https://t.co/cRgxMlsGE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time at the @ndctws conference this past week, where I presented my research poster on #prairiedog beha… https://t.co/uG6FxIjwrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shame on you! Are you stupid to believe the ruthless dictator #KimJonUn who had his own family mem… https://t.co/JOFRW9WAbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decent times, decent places, decent people, STELLAR flamingos. @ Motel 6 https://t.co/o5LrYh17ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardEvans40 @SCoRMembers @iirrt @EFRadiographerS https://t.co/HoPW13rHrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The arthritis in my hands make me look like I have dinosaur claws in every picture hahahaha 23 is so fun :)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmcinern @Spartacussin @SophieInCT Have a look at the whole video. https://t.co/Wzm1Q5i8vj … It makes a big differ… https://t.co/wn0Xpq3SUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ma mère, en Malaisie depuis un mois, qui a dû se rendre plusieurs fois à Kuala Lumpur pour un vol de passeport : « … https://t.co/nv3cg9H2vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm voting for #Jaguars for #BESTFANARMY at the #iHeartAwards. RT to vote too! https://t.co/HnVutUjPnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the bottom of our hearts, we want to thank each and every one of you who have touched our lives in so many way… https://t.co/rRqS9XsfaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@longway_trey @KimbroughMarc lmfaoo bruh it ain’t a Hoe jumper 😒😂 im the hostess, what im supposed to wear then trey ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to figure out which is more dishonest (read: more fun): passing or backpassing]]></document><document><![CDATA[T1: Simpson jumps out to an early 2-0 lead after @derickkuhn2 leaves the yard!! https://t.co/GHMDPHMV89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houster4 @Variety The hope we have right now will be all we get then. Still 🤩🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiemcmurray thanks for the memories and many years of awesome racing you gave us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate to see the refs decide a game like that sheesh. Great game tonight at the scope]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Cheesecake factory is hugely popular in Fort Lauderdale. The Thai chicken curry tasted fine but oh dear present… https://t.co/LypnOV1G6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I didn’t go to the Zulu ball this year lol it just didn’t even feel right not going 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eferiamich @robertomonroy1 este año nos encararía qué inviten a #RíoRoma a la Fiesta Michoacán 2019 por favor 🙏❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mindful mediation before my students take a quiz. One of student today started to put away the morning work because… https://t.co/IAwxvJZW7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieMillard3 @Black15Willa @JenLaidlaw12 @ThisTechGirl @ArleneDickinson @smithmegan @stephaneurial @AnarSimpson T… https://t.co/MV1kQBpuxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spotted the @News12LI van at the St James Model Train Club show 💖 Complete with a camera crew and interviewer. Ther… https://t.co/D9OB3P5AxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Professor, you have got to start sleeping” - a concerned student to me...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces, el amor se trata de compartir tus gustos más básicos y culposos con alguien que también se siente cómodo c… https://t.co/CGTpMzh0US]]></document><document><![CDATA[A memory of my cute baby bears showed up on my timeline and now I’m stuck looking at their baby pictures 😭 I can’t… https://t.co/gVYDzHe0gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day!!❤️❤️ Come check out my new video! 🥰   https://t.co/0zZliFMmbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to an insightful Women’s Empowerment luncheon last week. The ladies were all leaders and founders of various c… https://t.co/GKHmUQUp0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day 💪🏻! Check out #whatworks to close the #GenderPayGap via policies in 🇮🇸 🇦🇺 🇩🇪 🇺🇸 🇳🇴… https://t.co/OYPv8NXvkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't get me into debates on how to fix our world. I'll write you 10 page papers. Like I've done just now. I'm sorr… https://t.co/QcgjmJeSvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When I hear ‘hub’, there’s only one hub I can think of...the hub of porn” — Evam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me on The Morning After show where I discuss the future of the #LakeShow, R. Kelly, and AB’s departure from t… https://t.co/3eOEpetJOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My points exactly. We lost a race because of the uproar of something that happened 45 years or so by a man who has… https://t.co/y9DSGqQnYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shocking number of schools also have lead in drinking water. Massive infrastructure work is needed in this area.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Then Bernie needs to step aside. He has no chance. Way to far to the left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all my clients that have reached out and donated!   This dance means so much to me!  It’s my 13th year… https://t.co/RV0taZyfI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buzzer sounds to end the game as the Colts win back-to-back games!! 3-1 final for the good guys! Final SOG: 24-22 Colts #KGNvsBAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find out how the new Ontario Autism Program fails children across the province https://t.co/w91TF0664n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Navajo guy: What's your clans?  Me: No clans after 10   I've always wanted to use that line on someone &amp; I finally did 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 40th birthday sister I wish you was here baby we love and miss you 😩😇 Rip my sister #CarmanWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoMeowChenko I took her as a "rescue" as the man that had loved her for nine years was unable to give her insulin.… https://t.co/al0IErJ9zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warming the cold winter night...  #MauriceGibb #BeeGees https://t.co/8na1kLvIog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhennesseynews @myfox8 Yay, Michael! My first “coanchor.” Happy for you! 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to take a Pic of #Gallade but was too close. 😅 #PokémonGo @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/2aTfSvscxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. He should remove himself from the ticket anyway. He’s sacrificing votes for democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered @SweatpantsCafe 's #SweatpantsandCoffeeDay #Giveaway #CoffeeforAll #Kindness  https://t.co/tDFxcce59O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runDRG @punchupthejam @punchupthejam is my absolute favorite!! The *Kelsey Grammar voice* MMMBop episode was transcendent]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby Beto smashed him with the people of El Paso next time he will learn it the hard way #busta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StatMone I’ve said this many times now in my feed: my point is be kind to the victim. They certainly don’t need us… https://t.co/lQRxiC6C2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off February #EmployeeForums with Marcy. #Systemness #OneTeam# @ChandaChacon @MarcyDoderer @archildrensFred… https://t.co/nr8dOmLISA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HietanenPaavo @VestsCanada the immigration issue got folks started, and there is discord amongst the bigots, with… https://t.co/2zIfHwQojf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanMcMullin I agree with you. How shameful that any one of the others would go along with this travesty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently @TSA doesn’t see a whole lot of cow bells coming through the x-ray machines.  Had to open my bag to s… https://t.co/bnCYbZll2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shawnaaa17 Who is mean? I'll kick their ass. Or look at them disappointedly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time March come around, the people in my life start acting stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyPoleo @FactoresdePoder HAY DEMASIADO SILENCIO , POR FAVOR MANTENGAMONOS PENDIENTE DE LO QUE ESTA ACONTECIENDO… https://t.co/0ho0TiU0Z4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not replying to anyone that I’m not close to today unless you’ve got money for me. Have sooo much to do to be wasting time]]></document></documents></author>