<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@EvCoRadio What about Joe Gibbs three Super Bowls, three different quarterbacks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does your acquaintance feel about Kamala Harris using hers to get where she is today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris What a genius?? And how are going to stop if by chance you become the president? Legalize it like prostitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex4CT @GovNedLamont Tolling is pro business policy? Are you insane? You are making @AOC look like she makes sens… https://t.co/LcyickxYVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got home and turned on @CNN to see @ChrisChristie being interviewed. *click*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gosh I’m so loved. Happy Valentine’s Day to my first valentine, my  honey bunches. Only you could love me as much a… https://t.co/4vyqo6Oy7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen OJ, he’s a really nice guy. Terrible what they’ve done to him. Witch hunt!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bottorff44 @LTJpezcore1 @michaelsobrien You beat me to it Jeff!  That just popped in my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think there is a need to call out bullshit where it is due, and Michelle Malkin calling out “the ghost of John Mc… https://t.co/gQlJi2ocZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidjoachim @KThomasDC Donald Trump smiles, takes a sip of Diet Coke, and puts away his checkbook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Can’t come in to work today. The news said to stay in bed. I can print out the tweet if needed. See ya Wednesday.… https://t.co/lBUtpe1NiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Krispy Kreme channeling our inner Willy Wonka?  Btw closest shop is in @NYCPennStation  https://t.co/GFyZM4zXcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCOTS_Music great show last night, enjoyed reminiscing with Rick about seeing you guys as a new band in early ‘80’… https://t.co/I9DgbDQC6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pitman United Methodist Church in Pitman, NJ https://t.co/ffm27ZMbM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passed out early while watching the Flyers get smoked. Now comes the part where I stare at the ceiling for the next… https://t.co/53GcEs6yEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Just A Vibe  🎤♻️🎧🎹💯📈  #Thejaeminiproject   #richuglyniggas  #jaeclaude100 #jaeclaude #jaeclaudedon… https://t.co/dfJSwssSJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkLazerus If only Seabrook and keith would accept a trade.....they arent gonna win another cup in chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Schmoofy @RohdesRoadies Rolf, @thehankbagwell this guy sounds like you... 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SureWhyNotDora @southerntide @TommyBahama would never lower themselves like this https://t.co/4KVWg0pZ6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brokenlizard @truTV @SteveLemme @alamodrafthouse Follow up tweet. Are you worried that people will read the hashta… https://t.co/PK9STBQuMA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunnyCostaki Ben: we are trading you that way Ab: I want traded this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jussiesmollett will reap what he sows...over n over again if he goes to jail  🥴.  💩😳🙀 @attaboySmollett.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest Confessional Podcast with Alex Hooper from America’s Got Talent/Conedy Central, etc. We discuss Losing a Lov… https://t.co/FUXKa1GKC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @MadMoneyOnCNBC Crammer rammer going for the crazy card huh?  How much did you get paid....?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just gotta make shit happen myself, which is what I’ve been doing forever. Let’s see how this year transpires]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoKhanna @renato_mariotti As a resident of neighboring district, thank you Rep. Khanna. You did us great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is jolly. You gotta make your own way in this life. | 23 Life Lessons You Learned From... https://t.co/5a8Y95jO0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are there any other parents out there who find these "daddy-daughter" events creepy and revolting? 'cause they seem… https://t.co/A7fcKKEnIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Malek put on such an incredible performance as Freddy and just because of historical inaccuracies in the movie, he… https://t.co/zpvEaFUaDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you don’t mention the slow massacre already taking place and try to advance Cold War thinking implying the Ven… https://t.co/Nc4mtyMerH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Final Thoughts 💭 for #draftkings #pga golf 🏌️ ⛳️ tournament @genesisopen at https://t.co/OiS0qcnj9M 🤓 https://t.co/aVX4DBNQhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ok Comrade, you can believe Mr OxyContin brain Rush but I thought you were against druggies? Of co… https://t.co/YPCYXK9yxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it turns out, God is too smart to give my own dumbass self what I think I want. He really do be like that sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up early and working out is a wonderful way to start the day off! @GrantCardone @JarrodGlandt #10XGrowthCon #10Xlife #YoungHustler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @Lagarde @LindseyGrahamSC @MorganOrtagus @IvankaTrump Hey🙋...Hope you, @LindseyGrahamSC and… https://t.co/9L8SOVoSZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsthread of all of the young people out there who idolize him how many of them have seen this on some sort of… https://t.co/sJ413cW5Xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryAkemon @SouthwestAir Good luck! I’ve been at BWI all afternoon.  Maybe I should’ve drove down to DCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Alter Ego by @TreeHouseBrewCo @ Breezeway Nirvana — https://t.co/NhXqo9RJnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop 3: Urban Legend Winery. #OaklandUrbanWineTrail @ Urban Legend Tasting Room https://t.co/ExI5DBZH22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone close to Pelosi should be investigated, cause they're smarter than her. Including the dogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darealjlaw @StrakerSue @OhioStateOnBTN @OhioStateHoops It’s always a Susan]]></document><document><![CDATA[The two of them next to each other... 😢 (and yes I broke down when I pulled into the driveway) https://t.co/h6o1zFYo7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonnew No clue. Sorry Jon, I’m not Yoda. But I know they’re coming! ⚔️🛡🏀 ( personally, I think Ron Harper Jr. coul… https://t.co/r6SbvPckdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extremely grateful for the generous support of our donors. @PresConoley and I are thankful for the investment and c… https://t.co/EgAGWM3gej]]></document><document><![CDATA[New boxed wine from barefootwine  5 delicious flavors to try.   #joecanalsmillville #new #boxedwine #rosé… https://t.co/F4UucOrUiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 consecutive nights of about 4 hours of sleep or less, I think I’m taking a mental health day to get some sleep an… https://t.co/c7N3vuNXXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShazyReplicant @philthatos It's up there with my fav animes other than full metal alchemist  brotherhood initial d Gundam and Macross 7]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think brand of brokerage matters to your clients? Think again: • Only about 3 percent of buyers and 4 percent o… https://t.co/1d1Z67rHGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a Blue bird day!!  @SnowDurango @VisitDurango @Colorado @GlacierClubCO https://t.co/ASiDIuUdWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters @ReutersTV W.A. AmericA?           HI          HAWAII          NGT no God better for one than for Another.… https://t.co/GGaDLS9mLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #FAKENationalEmergency #TrumpFakeEmergency @ABCNewsLive @SkyNewsBreak @AJELive @CBSTopNews… https://t.co/dsc4EltUkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@____CharlieB I’m still recovering from the Kakaley debacle in race 2. https://t.co/cRyBjfe0jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think @DavidHasselhoff will let me interview him since I’m rewatching Baywatch now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddcanofari @hmp5063 @CraigCanofari @RupertPupkin_18 @JayUlak23 @mattcanofari @Shayneayers @SkoalBandits55… https://t.co/Fis5GoegVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to Graceland University's very own, Shauna Reitan! #GUJACKETS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ultimoalarco fubotv 17 dollars por mes tenes todo el futbol en hd especialmente bein sport 1, 2 y 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianroberts1962 @TaylorMadeGolf That’s the info I was looking for. So if I don’t like the X around the greens I’ll… https://t.co/Qig82GtUuB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodluck to @Wachubball, as their state title run starts tonight vs Framingham. Give em hell @rockchalk2chain @Jeremy21Ross]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the person who probably had the worst day was Allen Weisselberg. He’s not a comfortable person today. #cohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IceJJFish Did you really think screeching like dying animals was going to make people like your “music”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romans 13:9-10 AMP—The commandments, “YOU SHALL NOT COMMIT ADULTERY, YOU SHALL NOT MURDER, YOU… https://t.co/u3Vn3JXT3I via @biblegateway]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newly elected Prosecutor Mary Robnett, “therapeutic courts aren’t just good for the individual, but good for the community.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlissTabitha This Hogg kid don't even know how to light up a cigarette]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyCassyCat @SantasCat @DavidWilding271 @Brici161 @gigglingr @NorahNell @peemail @tweetypie54 @3coolkatz… https://t.co/Y3JCH2sY5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad (born &amp; raised in India): people say you and I sound alike / Me (400% 🇺🇸) uh what]]></document><document><![CDATA[scores, and ‘lost butterfly’ somehow surpasses the excellence that was her score for ‘presage flower’.   I stated b… https://t.co/LtPVNCcqkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard a 30-second snippet of a brand new @311 song and now I don't know what to do with the rest of my day!?! @NickHexum @pnut]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't expect the Terminator to be so obsessed with cleanliness. #Robot #robotics #autonomous https://t.co/MmG74G47NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @brianwiqo and Mari on https://t.co/dPx7ZiuLRu is a great way to get through an hour of morning cardio - Study]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember, right now someone is trying to pass laws that are not in your interest and prevent laws that are. This is… https://t.co/LNvco8cfwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. Yes yes yes. I love this. Was so upset when he got hurt in the preseason last year. Glad he’s getting another… https://t.co/3VQ3SNHjFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetheart2019 @Craig5889 @JimCarrey Trump locked them up, stupid Trump supporter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is absolutely one of the best beers out of Missouri - Drinking a Black Walnut Wheat by @PineyRiverBrew @ Big M… https://t.co/mEICFxN9q8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you watch or support Tucker Carlson, you really need to examine yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just turned on #TheOddCouple and guess what they’re talking about!?! LBJ... putting 100% of the blame on him! #Yeesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Syracuse gonna beat Duke twice in one year after Zion being ruled out tonight? 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Time pay it back or in my personal opinion get ready to have some sanctuary cities federal aid revoked  permanently!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemolitionRanch I would and idk I guess my carpentry skills and my moderate aim🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summerbrze1 PPS disconnect at my end. Sorry for the misunderstanding, and I apologize for confusing you. Guess I s… https://t.co/yPtB626f5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh im grateful huh? Well who’s fault is that my dear parent…  Take them meds and vitamins and relax ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope they sign Harper too. Why not? The one team not colluding gets two huge talents. https://t.co/ExwS4sBoBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holding my baby when she was a big baby :) #niece #nieces #baby#babies#love#family#sobrina#familia 場所: Lancaster, T… https://t.co/K6pPR4oE0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo absolutely #savage Prius vibes in my parking deck this AM @xzibit @VinDieselPage @JerryFalwellJr 💯# https://t.co/1hCKpQdcqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your friends love you when this is what you wake up to https://t.co/2YwFSbw1e9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when St. Patrick's day was 70 degrees a few years ago? That was awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pimping has got to be at a all time low because these hoes are marketing geniuses these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[A better version of mediocre is never a winning strategy https://t.co/6P1jwW8gRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrenElias @WPT @LAPC Good luck at the FT buddy! You are definitely the GOAT!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UGACoachNew  Happy Birthday Chelsea! Hope you enjoy your special day!  🏀🐾🐾🏀 https://t.co/mtLGv7qPXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gonna say what all of you are already thinking, fuck day light savings time. Thanks for coming to my Ted talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[disrespecting women by engaging in inappropriate contact and advances? What happened to the pledge of offering legi… https://t.co/hkSIW2nwUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooooo @FANEXPODallas wanna TRY TO EXPLAIN how a convention can announce a guest WHO HASN’T AGREED to even attend… https://t.co/9mgmkaowf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you fucking kidding me?  The pathetic world we live in!  #society #mediasucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Dating Around on Netflix and concluding that I'm not a lost cause, definitely a better date than some of t… https://t.co/kGut6ah0j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeplorableChoir @katiet121 Cant send a card till first of march😣 hope hes better by then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viktoriaarosas @jennatrashewski If I didn’t know better I would have sworn this was Jenna on your account]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrNeil612 Don't trip bro. Do your thang. Let's brainstorm next time you around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump_daddy16 @Chicago Many hundreds of thousands of America public all have dealt with #Local city permitting. Th… https://t.co/imjjtDdeVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestBuySupport why would you want to lose $ when you can just request the same item with a exclusive product numbe… https://t.co/FDMcnYlmhE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimCrise Your point? As the investigator, Mueller had nothing to do with the sentencing. You've been an investigator for many years.]]></document></documents></author>