<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Golden Gate Chapter #40 will be celebrating  our new members.  Come join us in celebrating and welcoming our new me… https://t.co/tivzh1TnQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best parts about being home from school is the glow in the dark stars on my ceiling]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Últimahora @StateDept anuncia retiro de todo el personal diplomático que aún permanece en #Venezuela @VOANoticias]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t switch on me I got big plans we need to forward to the islands get you gold no spray tans]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If he touches you again, I am going to impale him on that desk.” The Dora Milaje are my favorite thing about Black… https://t.co/FSdYd6iWtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsCindySon @katielawll just like when she cheered me on eating five slices of pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitches just want yappin until they put in a situation .. now she there hablando ba ba .]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s that annoying...get off social media - there, fixed your prob for you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @GovRonDeSantis #SCOTUS Uwant 2know why these people R  fighting so hard against… https://t.co/JtDprUluEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be magical. #soundbath #earthmeetssky #newmoon #selfcare https://t.co/8fF9gs61g2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last practice with my new friend, Bunny. Thank you to the @SacramentoKings dancers! Kings Vs Knicks halftime show!… https://t.co/2ljKbNLa1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think again.....I’m not the same girl I was a few months ago, and that’s it I’m done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordaan__nicole i haven’t gotten a state tax return in like 4 years 😂🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeMull77 I really enjoyed your keynote sessions at the Ohio MGMA Winter 2019 conference! Can’t wait to apply less… https://t.co/SLwzsH8Sr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to having @SonooSingh Conrad Fritzsch, and  @8illingsley talk us through the agency of the future!… https://t.co/AEofNoVA2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what happens during the day, once your child is finally asleep, in your arms, every other worry or care i… https://t.co/gDLwQNikqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InAWomansWorld I told your son at lunch today that bugs in the house were his responsibility to deal with. He's already slacking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WalkAwayFromDemocratSocialists @AOC Hey B, I live in California! FU BITCH! #WeThePeopleWillPrevail #YouWillFail!… https://t.co/eJbJBxAP04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the “Mapping your Classroom” session at the Pittsburgh Regional Faculty symposium. Interesting to think of th… https://t.co/Y2XD6F18Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriving from 🇵🇷 we thought we were going to see higher numbers on our scale because is difficult to follow our eat… https://t.co/lubGfPG6Xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wayne_famular @truthforHim1224 @Pastorbobjoyce @LoveBling6 @DIXIEDOODLE12 @Taradea08775439 @StormIsUponUs @VincentCrypt46 Will do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robcesternino @NatalieColeLA I was wondering if we'd get Natalie on the podcast and I'm really glad we did!  I hav… https://t.co/7949jQgrRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMende5 my mom wants you to know you look like Brendon Urie lmao ps. ty for putting up with us 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you and your BFFs are equally enamored with @LisaKleypas ‘s Wallflower novels, you gossip about the previous g… https://t.co/BCH3fq1I01]]></document><document><![CDATA[People really need to stop posting their drama online but then againnnn https://t.co/WDdH6nEVCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikel_Jollett @charles_gaba But there is no pizza. That's the difference]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd-5th grade teachers @FPEcolumbia helping parents understand iReady instruction and preparing for the upcoming FS… https://t.co/gR2Gqck8ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NightsLikeThese #bae #grateful  #lovesac @ Mountain Edge, Clark https://t.co/MOewkUErMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice going #nbc #williegeist report it .. admit you got the story wrong and stop qualifying  answers with a ..but .… https://t.co/DTwvUupWA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prettydeadlady Oh, it totally makes sense why people use it. I just never have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esas palabras en boca de un elemento como tú presidente de los haitianos  ,es una https://t.co/Cup7XC4atA siente la… https://t.co/Fi3GNd0P0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filled up my tank today and it lowkey broke my heart 😭 my baby be eating that expensive gas 😩🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Honor @JudgeMaryYu let us keep our 🔥 Let us both be relentless in our passion for ethics ⚖️ fairness ❤️ accoun… https://t.co/9a9lexcvbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backing off because of the damage to our economy? Can't afford too many more $9 billion dollar payoffs to your base… https://t.co/z2QwEvwDlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can't be friends if you can't vibe to "Please me" by @iamcardib &amp; @BrunoMars #PleaseMe keep the bops comin'.💛🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnapppy14 Seriously how did her friend not fuck him up? Oh lord. I’m a gentle woman, but I’d whip some ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are supposed to leave for Florida next Monday and Elijah’s still sick 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @GCcougarsVB players for holding themselves and each other accountable by making the commitment to get… https://t.co/SyTn6q7fUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EZuelow I had to also buy the audio because the text is small. ::sigh:: please remember those way over 60 ha ha. Q… https://t.co/KSidX0MGYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alyssa just started crying actual tears talking about when she had to tell her teacher in 6th grade that her dog ate her homework]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_UnSilent_ @Jpdawe7 This may be the answer to why the repubs are so complicit. It's the Kompromat we all have w… https://t.co/eoORVcH61f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickwhite1985 Nick, you have to come watch the Oscars w/ us at the Gateway next year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday (@ St. Christopher's in Speedway, IN) https://t.co/BXDIaCTLyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[D27 Overheads looking great @ HD#0276 #OverheadOrganization #SFLOHORG #D9Strong https://t.co/YfnetKzgMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hollaaayyy @Noelle_WasHere If you guys became famous twin you tubers I’d def follow y’all. So you should do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clyanacek Oh thank you, that means so much to me! ♥️ It’s been ten years, but seems just like yesterday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s my first week with stickers on my laptop (seriously) and I feel like it’s going well so far.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary #tenyearswhat https://t.co/KIQzxD3Apz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KREMMark My husband @chris_bornhoft took it when I was driving over the Northwest Blvd overpass as we had to take… https://t.co/xiBjTv5XL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 "Hold on my Heart" by Genesis. I'm 19 all over again and met my first true love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like nobody’s home ...for years . . . #coolfindstoday #photography #photographyart #photographystyle… https://t.co/zellghOolC]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is this better for society? 🤦🏻‍♀️ US needs to wake up and vote smart in 2020. https://t.co/6r332GLQzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m tan, i’m drunk, i’m glowing, i’m truly living my best life in south beach]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you're really into a person when even if you're mad you still prayed for him to get home safe  IBANG LEVEL OF GRACIA TO 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t thank #BACKSTAGE2019 enough for this opportunity to share our #WobbleMovement with our amazing colleagues!  T… https://t.co/cnZaA8fLGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sage...powerful medicine that is used in many sacred traditions all around the world. In addition, it is a culinary… https://t.co/spBSz8tVSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Shepherd’s 1st graders finished up their rainbow fish in specials. Some added bleeding tissue scales and strips… https://t.co/NcyNwDvj4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[No no fr though @brendonurie and @hellosarahurie are such a beautiful couple I can’t even describe it man. Like the… https://t.co/ntt16Suv0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_baliad @glenwalkerktla @LuParker @weatherkaj @latimes @Davidlaz @MarcusSmithKTLA @jenniferthang @KTLA… https://t.co/k0RyKnwKqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL I interviewed you briefly in 1991. You haven’t aged a bit. Happy birthday Ice. 🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The love that Austinites already have for OUR team is amazing...WE ARE READY TO GO TO WORK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely love how Ruzek has stepped up for Voight and has become one tough cop! He was taught well by… https://t.co/BWwk2iAmhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[School boards cancel #classes Wednesday as southern #Quebec hit by intense #snowstorm | CBC News https://t.co/CpeGb76shn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful picture of @SkeltonSophie  #gorgeous @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/gJbnYTxf1E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amaixico @MattsRoadTrip @Sostraveluk @HHLifestyleTrav @GailBenzler @dsouzaashayne @OdetteDunn @travelwithirine… https://t.co/RZyx29J0Ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde que no como tortillas de harina o maíz me da hambre cada tres horas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m taking off on Thursday I’m over work. Seeing how much PTO I got and accrue weekly has me wanting to take off at least 2 days a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at James C. Wright Middle School in Madison, WI https://t.co/viz0Z5dlrQ https://t.co/ldhvvQqU9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNCWBaseball @coleweiss8 That Pacific Ocean air did you a lot of good, Cole! @coleweiss8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilMurphyNJ....This should be law.  Senate passes bill that would keep Trump off 2020 ballot unless he releases t… https://t.co/ZVcGySUiTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs Me either he along with Putin cost us the white house and he's at it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know people that enjoy politics and government are enjoying this I bet..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played Crokinole for the first time. Great to revisit classic games likes this (invented in 1876!) to better unders… https://t.co/5Q6IkP4XOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetgeorge48 @liz_kesson Got to take good care of him Sweet George! Besides isn’t the Old Dude your crew chief? O… https://t.co/J6dA6tYoFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonPardi did not sing When I’ve Been Drinkin’ and it was the biggest disappointment of 2019 thus far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in tonight on Oasis Montage Magazine talk show/108 praise radio!!! 2 fabulous guest: the amazing smart guy, Ch… https://t.co/zwh3tbKPna]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimSimons2 @Dianafowles @TonyaKayFan10 @Cheryl_L_Hyde @GPBGeorge @KnowSmallParts @sarahjeanfry @CCHarrison67… https://t.co/PkgPEw0iQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arunsaini0369 @SCCM True, but when aligning your goals with competing priorities consider that prioritizing your f… https://t.co/lkSQUcD0rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN’T BELIEVE THE SHOW YOU GET TO SEE TOMORROW AT PRONOUN SHOWDOWN we’ve been trying to play it so cool but WOWOW… https://t.co/0XmvIGQbAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please see below related to the activity seen on the former UDD site today.  #Hoboken]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Friday Feb 22nd #Somerville #Boston is in for a treat!  Tickets available with code 24HOUR #AMERICANA #folk… https://t.co/PoeKWnMSFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day to all the badass women in my life. Couldn’t make it through this patriarchal mess… https://t.co/9CHo8SAVnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erianna16 @NE_Newmans @Niktor_Newman @EBraeden @MelodyThomasSco The tape alone proves his abuse toward lovely Victoria]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Wanna Sign A Female Artist To My Label.... Where The 🔥🔥🔥🔥 #FemaleArtist At???]]></document><document><![CDATA[my Uber extremely chatty for 4am and also I slipped on ice getting into car hehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[anybody who thinks Year 3000 is a better Jonas Brothers song then Burnin’ Up cannot be in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) BOE never told anyone they were doing that - the electoral process MUST be transparent  2) how can we track vote… https://t.co/iMcy8kUuUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy B Day to the best father in law in the world! 88 and goin strong love you 😘 https://t.co/XgJCVnQkjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trustnoone54 @realDonaldTrump You dont see it cuz when he  got in the office ,all he Found it was a total mess.but… https://t.co/IpuO0CxmGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate and I always dedicated Love Story by @taylorswift13 as our song three years ago. We’ve been too busy to… https://t.co/fhkIsC74CM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adrimorque It was such an awkward moment 👀🙄. And the headphones situation, I just need to go wireless lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge amounts of thanks to Michael Perry @SneezingCow for helping this old teacher find real life examples to show h… https://t.co/zl5re9RA0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, and I still feel the same way! @ London, Ontario https://t.co/3U1NIXFvcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianneCassidy @PolicyLover And then I told the world how she skipped out on rent, other money she owed, was a tot… https://t.co/lq0mUDWf4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficerWilliam4 Not me..i sleep under a bunch of blankets/comforter but i like the room ice cold.  My other comfor… https://t.co/DdABx9hqGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuancedLogic Bingo. None of that wealth is ever being circulated in our communities. It’s always going somewhere e… https://t.co/np6VW2Im7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana2525 I am 38 and people are still asking me about having children. Nope, I've still not changed my mind. #teamnokids]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who dates their brothers ex and thinks it’s okay? Morgan Hill is turning a little backwoods apparently]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans Will Vote Against Trump’s National Emergency – Here They Are https://t.co/6wVxZ3sq3s via @ILMForg - vot… https://t.co/STIbDcr28i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BANNERSMUSIC You have an amazing voice... Love your music... I thank you for sharing]]></document></documents></author>