<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I see no potential issues with this and am sure it’ll work out precisely according to plan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs morning coffee when you can make some before-school reading gains at South Mountain School!!… https://t.co/ntORVwRVYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote this fool out of office. Native American . Run against him https://t.co/clAneAh2M8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNBooger Could they draft one you believe that’s ready be a starter with the 4th pick?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chadtronic @AndySteinMusic Wait... Your entire CHANNEL and not just a video???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill Forshizzle....I always wanted to say that https://t.co/o04kww1Zxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobGambuti @DAlvearFOX46 @FountainFox46 @FOX46News “Living history” is how they explain it. Just talks about Great Depression, not slavery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfccmoAthletics Sunday Game Day for Roadrunners!! Game 1 of a 4 Game series at MAC begins today at 1pm!! #BeepBeep… https://t.co/m3JEvvtjom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenWest Being scared of Socialism in America because of what's happening in Venezuela is like being scared of fl… https://t.co/tuS1aSKAte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good day with my boy today. Stayed outside most of the day and even rolled around with him lol. I love my best frie… https://t.co/5AohpiNqVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Lakers miss the playoffs but get a Top 5 pick in the draft&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bestest memory is when we killed the Lich King at my place with four of my friends from the raid over. The level… https://t.co/RdEYzXqPAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasGJames @bubba_matt My understanding is the the COB specifically instructed them not to develop a traditional… https://t.co/i8I0BLkhLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icecube Love you I love you ice cube praise Jesus brother the angels looking over you and your family bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it crazy the Zelina is watching her client Andrade and her husband compete against each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think #maps of every big city in the world would show some people living in  isolation from the rest, because of… https://t.co/6r1QHNABOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great topic for a chat! #ElonEd @juliette_writes @Courtintheclass @rcolesclass #ElonEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity watching all the investigations into the President I wonder where is the line between that and a coup… https://t.co/mKYYJR0y9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SadeABC Men Black American Men 🚀🇺🇸 the world is waiting and what are you going to do when he gets it. You both can… https://t.co/SGQ9GcGoZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xpatsxjoshx @MikeGarafolo Belichick and Brady want a WR who didn’t show up for his coaches and teammates in the bi… https://t.co/GJiDFBPZkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey asshat! You don’t get to tell anyone but yourself what to do. You aren’t our mother, our keeper, our boss. You… https://t.co/bsBH2cZKWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bolivarmo bolivar police dept you are a fucking disgrace. you showed zero empathy and acted like a bunch of dicks… https://t.co/rx7lUKMBGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lordwilone @NotMaryJoLisa @AhmedBaba_ @realDonaldTrump U tell me. U are the one on phones with him forever. In ya… https://t.co/sfCWaxrT7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaximeBernier @LauraLynnTT Reducing government securitization of mortgages is actually the fastest way to mitigate… https://t.co/hnCVLMeDSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg On the other hand these politicians are already living the American dream, however the highly dysfu… https://t.co/4qYXC99Jii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christianllamar Bernie is running so he can build up supporters and be bought again and buy his fourth or forh hom… https://t.co/Rne1I3Ctr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinjiPS @Spicxer @MissAmiaSays @Womenthatlost4 @charmcitycop @MarkLTomlin @BoneSpurs2000 @dplymyer @shield142… https://t.co/vGbzCkeIit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @johnharkes6 Have a great one! Looking forward to catching a @GVLTriumph game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music is a vehicle that transports the feelings, the hopes, the dreams, the joy, the sorrows, the fear, the radianc… https://t.co/Wpyl0RPsh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/xSek417HPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife if hoping to trade me in for Bradley cooper.  I fully understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenericID10T @DamonMartin @BlessedMMA @DustinPoirier Because traditionally the heavier weight class always headlines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. Sorry Chicago. You gots too much snow and cancelled my flight. Off to Vegas instead...then home to SF. ✈️ https://t.co/FtIydVkz6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Revkin @Gen_Atomic @NatGeo Why are you talking about old nuclear in a new deal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is mercury is retrograde because my life is fucked all the way up right now lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAllemang @Westside66 @WarriorQuizBowl Thanks for your leadership with this group.  They rocked it all day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you get when you cross an Aussie w/ a Canadian health system? An amazing leader like Heather @CAMHnews.… https://t.co/eBSJrpMrB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss them tight and bouncy. They look like waves now #hairstylist #hairextensions #wigs #dantevelasquezny #nyc… https://t.co/8pZpXDjf7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oDOWrules @Husker_Nick That was 2 years ago injuries.  We’ve progressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well @sharkvoice, if they took #SJSharks Dillion to the box for the punch to the jaw, one of the Wild to the box fo… https://t.co/niQRUlx1BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m now watching this toddler eat spring rolls they brought from home and it’s how I want to spend eternity]]></document><document><![CDATA[took me 3 yrs back in NY grindin to get this Lil headlinin.... so, y'all coming. I already checked the venue lit. t… https://t.co/PyzMu6r1iP]]></document><document><![CDATA[all the disney princesses should be assumed to be eugenicists until proven otherwise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatBShar Congrats, so awesome for you! Hopefully you get to work with @ManaDrake , who is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to have partner in crime @deldelp of @BBFounders here in #pdx this week. We plotted about #PitchBlack, access… https://t.co/BQhIzV1jL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[its so funny to watch ppl from texas/oklahoma act like california is a shithole lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pictured is piping we found in a home built in 1954. Galvanized piping was commonly installed in homes built before… https://t.co/dBb6xdFNdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kamuuei To u as well! N this image is fantastic! Great job with the character, as always, but I LOVE he shine on t… https://t.co/gmF0zhr2lT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews 2) Then...we are out of luck aren't we?  Like I said: Terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At first I thought this said “Unreasonable” and I couldn’t believe that the weather people were starting to agree w… https://t.co/YWQ4sL5ccj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alisonsduncan @walterowensgrpa @AOC READ THE COMMENTS. You’ve been #waltered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Memories of past losses help carry Keith Mitchell to Honda Classic victory. @FanSided @pgatour @TheHondaClassic… https://t.co/n0AR5SyBPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I have wrapped up the winter portion of my season for @auroraathletics, I just want to thank… https://t.co/arF38icsRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposted from @EMPNYC  -  We're in production mode working on past and future  music. 2019 is showing light and sou… https://t.co/9Yk77yrzMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a spare room. Not the ideal house guest, but we’d be willing to take one for the team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerLombardo1 @jetsyanx @JCaporoso But just as you have a strong opinion on Q, I have a strong opinion on Jonah W… https://t.co/cpJIUi7ctA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @Boulevard_Beer @HEB @Just4BeerLovers @impopsy @tilbeerdouspart @BPlohocky @CATbrew13 @JohanBBT… https://t.co/nuimx6Zfgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[BROO WHAT??? This has to stop, immediately pulled the gun out?? He better get fired...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thiccthiccerson I’m not saying a player shouldn’t have the right to rest here and there. Comparing it to someone w… https://t.co/fTiaEWHm5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or, if they do speak up, yet don’t know how to articulate. That just means your org has created so much resentment,… https://t.co/hyJZFG8tyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherWheaton @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump While I appreciate the compliment that I'm 23, you're very wrong on who… https://t.co/nI3YejoGfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nets crush Mavericks 127-88 to end three-game skid  https://t.co/dnRxCDRny2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 He actually looks more human than he does in his usual makeup and coiffed hair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 AM InuYasha marathons make my dreams vivid, anime-like alternate realities where I can wall run and deliver punch… https://t.co/1g9tVf70KR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golf community should do a “Go Fund Me”  page to raise the $50k Moooochar’s caddie deserves! Please retweet!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They made a Blues fan out of me, at that funky little house party y’all up the street🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[First off, completely empty meaningless threat because as long as Trump is in WhiteHouse he has no intention of re-… https://t.co/sZ0Txw6oiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend Beth Rowe is another year older, but like fine wine she just gets better with age. Happy birthday Beth! @… https://t.co/c9Wi5c70b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[El problema no es que crean que la gente es estúpida, sino que están seguros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2go! 🌮×20🍔🐓🐓🍟 (@ Jack in the Box - @jackbox in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/FK0lZ0BjVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFBART 30 mins waiting for a train in Embarcadero and BART send an empty train thru without stopping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scrappy_Pro When and if he sees this it will be FAKE NEWS https://t.co/pd8dEXAiUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is today the day when @LachTalk spends the entire show crushing UL and leaves Cal and UK alone? @TheOnlySweeney]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Antonio Brown plot thickens 😂😂😂 ...I have to imagine that there are people, LIKE HIS AGENT, who are telling AB… https://t.co/R43x6WQ740]]></document><document><![CDATA[After this long week I’ve had of school and work I’m drinking until im@doing cartwheels idc idc idc 😤😤😤🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home. . . #harborisland #tampaislife #tampabaymindset #tampa #tamparealestate #tampagov #tampavibes… https://t.co/9VH9viXLFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why has the Jeff Epstein and trump news about their  teen sex marketing operation disappeared ? Another instance of… https://t.co/W5U5Nn8V22]]></document><document><![CDATA[i THINK I understand the @TrueDetective season finale, but I don’t think I’ll ever be 100% sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @IPS_Mr_Woolford  from Island JPS for being recognized as one of Canada’s #outstandingprincipals… https://t.co/kJNrD1T157]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 That's rich. If any group of people can be compared to terrorists it is the Republican party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💕 Hearing God’s Words 💕 @ Holy Family Catholic Church https://t.co/wpWdBxeFwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liltraina98 @JXetro @jerrytrainor How everyone gets when Dora is on #Dora #DrakeAndJosh #CrazySteve https://t.co/yVMLE5pCYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[More BS and temper tantrums from the illegitimate president. Grow up Tiny. Resign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLifshatz @JoeyMurr Not trying to change your opinion. Just trying to figure out why this line is so small. KenP… https://t.co/qzVIdsj1hZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to receive the TRIO Achiever Award @UNKearney @TRiOSSSUNK. I was a TRIO student @SOUAshland, which helps fi… https://t.co/MRbksSXNSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[TXDOT will have a Moving Operation on IH 69/ US 59 from Grand Parkway/ SH 99 to FM 2218 which will close one altern… https://t.co/ncSfL4Vg3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Clearly we have a criminal &amp; crazy asshole for president]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robyn was amaxing!! I'm #missinguou already #robyn #robynhoney #foxtheateroakland #dancingonmyown #konichiwabitches… https://t.co/Zto8qlWnzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 Reminder, school &amp; offices CLOSED on Monday, February 18 for Presidents’ Day!!! https://t.co/emLcYzQlYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty happy to have had Mitch Robinson at #13 on my big board this past draft, but @willandywalker really knoc… https://t.co/ptJUOnxOBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koreybrowne1 @QuestioningAlly @TalbertSwan Ok dude now take your meds..it will be ok...]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 New Majestic Buvan Remote Control Electric Wheelchairs Silla de Ruedas Electrica para Adultos FDA Approved Tra… https://t.co/KjGC20xlrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPInsidr I have been waiting for 33 years for a suitable barrier at the border...………… guess I may wait another 33 ….…………………………..?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students do not misbehave w/o cause or reason. Shouldn’t we try to figure out the root cause of their behavior? As… https://t.co/mTKWMDjb03]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW...  TODAY...  LET'S MAKE A DIFFERENCE! https://t.co/fpxCENllBh  Class of '82, you know what to do!… https://t.co/7bv29aRXzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PW_Ministries @CherylM12835788 @AAMetatron @realDonaldTrump @tommcclintock “And are equipped with sensors, monitor… https://t.co/5GyY7GMtSP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rklau Freaks me out each time because it’s NEVER labeled where the mystery 2FA and data are coming from. Wish it s… https://t.co/yK6FMpW5Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 He's in with the Russians to get Trump the vote. I am with you.  We need to make sure he is out of the picture fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...in the job security, and in our loss of them all. Help us to experience the impossible, but the real: that You a… https://t.co/PrIpHEeqD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chancehoffmann3 Wentz is injury prone and was on the bench or in a hospital for most of the important ones🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document></documents></author>