<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The #BRBF team is a bacon of hope to our @WHOhd morning crew! Tune in to hear about the 12th annual @BRBaconFest https://t.co/ZzheOjpoe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my friends are getting pregnant and I'm just over here with a bottle of vodka... https://t.co/aMkXPXffwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found the sketch I thought I lost 🔥✍🏽😍 |.Aquaman.|🧜🏽‍♂️|Can’t think of a better way to end my Friday night✍🏽… https://t.co/1jWnnGq7JF]]></document><document><![CDATA[all these girls on the bachelor are so insecure &amp; putting that shit on national television]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheerUPDATES But how did they get hit zero buttons? Who gives those out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kVPOazlana  Looking for an extra stream of income, #PaparazziAccessories is a wonderful company, hit m… https://t.co/8lkCElAPKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylieJenner wanna be @lisa_terror @terrorjrmusic so bad 🍇🍇🍇 https://t.co/WT4u8csXyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact a Knowledgeable #Listing #Agent to #buy or #sell a Property smoothly #Sacramento https://t.co/oh7nyQBDwk… https://t.co/urq7bnVJhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got in another #5k and awesome #strengthtraining #workout with the #FletcherGirls! It was both fun and rewarding!… https://t.co/wAqsloyShy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt with everyone’s favorite mama 🤗. #Repost mamastarrr ・・・ Hello World 🌎I’m getting Glammed by @MeLissaDuranMUA 🥰… https://t.co/cFLpFeaFs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn was wrong and she knows it. But she is also 20 something years old and to be fair she learned from the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Howlsgirl Yes! Of course! I’ll be happy to read and review anything. Anything to support indie authors like myself… https://t.co/uyWeeB3tKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coco is perplexed that her sisal has been frizzled. #CatsOfTwitter #siamesecat #meezer https://t.co/ERkxVe2Lm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thogreiner @kmtani Somewhat ironically, my PhD institution had 6wks paid parental leave for grad students. But the… https://t.co/Vf1VT6jmNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristopherB070 @macrostiewinery @thepinksociety_ @_drazzari @jflorez @boozychef @GailBenzler @Julianna_glass… https://t.co/5ckMNGqH0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Whole lot of people across the globe waiting you and your blockhead army out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you creep photos on insta and come across yourselves admiring your two favs performing their hearts out. ❤️… https://t.co/8gdYYZhruz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4everNeverTrump @MaxBoot @IlhanMN @CFR_org This @davidfrum ; sorry you are beginning to sound like your old self (blinded by the right")]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What about the most hostile and corrupt of a President you are.  God gives people what they need n… https://t.co/R0GxHvYEIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week's Spotlight Teacher for #WonderfulWedneaday is none other than our own Johnny Johnson Coach Johnson LOVES… https://t.co/yKuM8Zy6eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ginger_Zee You Always look beautiful but lately you look amazingly happy and relaxed!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erin_hr Because we thought we'd learned our lesson?   Yeah. Nope. We apparently are REALLY good at electing corrupt leaders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone else have someone always asking what they want to do with their life and you answer along the lines of makin… https://t.co/MSvCdqhcfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NareDavisTV She sure did! Ironically the same people who voted for him will be sad to know he's pulling money from… https://t.co/g0mcn5358J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué onda razita siempre si me auto-hice el microblading jaja quedo cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to #CelebrateMonday then with @sharonmdraper the Ss are in love with Forged by Fire and Tears of a Tiger https://t.co/BeNWoShCpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, join the #sangha at #bhaktiyogashala for #manta #medicine with #johannabeekmanmusic #dcstringer #jossjaffe… https://t.co/ynS7oPe5HY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump You should be ashamed of yourself bragging on You Tube-getting paid to bash our wonderful President. She on you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally just watched a guy at the gym kiss a barbell...weird flex but ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 4 years since Emily and I got off work and drove 14 hours to see #DavidTennant. #MondayMemories… https://t.co/9mSKU7auM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katy_fit I am so sorry to hear about all you have been through. I hope you immediately went to the doc for the Bel… https://t.co/hiyLOcgYbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[No te cierres. Nunca se sabe ...Podria abrirse el cielo!💫 - Do not close You never know ... The sky could open!💫 https://t.co/jFXYex53UX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have met with our soulmates,friends, and have even gone to Spiritual Court for our wrongs, wrongs done to us, an… https://t.co/0QOQTcHisa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best friend, best fam, best roomie 💜🤷🏽‍♀️ @ Columbus, Ohio https://t.co/W8zfZEx01Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsMELINduh Awwww your funny!!! I’m still waiting for my apologies from mine 😳🤣 it’s ok  though they have some tee… https://t.co/jsdWAL8qIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“he just jumped the f****** fence” - @chrisbharrison bc the cameras didn’t record it or anything 😂 #TheBachelor @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 I would be honored if you looked at my Instagram account! https://t.co/JvCXqa0lX2 I have almost 3000 foll… https://t.co/zOhJreIagn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing somthing this weekend. Idc what it is I just gotta do somthing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3gcry @luisitoazul007 @SparrowFranco @YSomellera @EllaCantaloupeH @cevalloslaura @BlancaNayelyNT3 @diprietonayeli… https://t.co/sOs8gD3Ues]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! Today’s lewk* inspired by RBG + Elizabeth Warren. The book is Chimamanda Ngozi Adi… https://t.co/GCvYozKPvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOOOO! I’m still so upset that Joey Fatone got voted off. He was so good! 😭😭😭 #TheMaskedSinger #RabbitMask]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jira is there a way to add components (or something similar) to the next-gen projects? If not, are there plans to add? Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behind every great man is a woman who said “ya babe that’s a good idea you should do that”]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you live you life to please everyone else, you forget what used to make you YOU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relatable Sunday morning clip from @jennydelucia and @danielstolfi   https://t.co/AtaedbR1Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many candy hearts do you think you can stack? ❤️ Let’s  find out! @NISDBraunStat @NISD @NISD_ECE #RootEd… https://t.co/JpuSz1HrQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino I am also dedicated to voting for whomever the Democrats put up. It will not be Bernie; I have tha… https://t.co/Fkbgm3cgT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visiting my girl for her project and lunch 💜 (@ Middletown Prairie Elementary in Mahomet, IL) https://t.co/6vtkAfpUPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaelizabeth_ No but really tho!! Like since when do we not get snow in February 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh can’t even fall back asleep now 🤦🏻‍♀️ imma be sick as hell tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[They rocked @PearDeck assessment to recall research skills and moved through transitions incredibly well to make th… https://t.co/A9hMBkIkHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself My 3 year old grandson refused to take naps at my house,  vaca use the “ghost” was there.   I finally… https://t.co/zDbCmXfC0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioNorthernFB @TheGreat__11 @B_Raddd5 @Moses_Adam_86 https://t.co/hKktLSi6Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muchadoaboutJC It's evidently a thing, LOL. Although, to my daughter's credit, she says it ironically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fuel the J and head on out” I need a friend like Lala. Private jets and white girl wasted!?!? F*ck ya #PumpRules @VanderpumpRules]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s why i hate wasting my time w/ these lame ass niggas bro 🤦🏾‍♀️ my fault for fucking w/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t play with your food doesn’t really apply during crawfish season. https://t.co/HZ6TX1SZg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful western JoCo sunset. #nofilterneeded https://t.co/pnc5m2rMwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got my ancestry dna results back and I’m 1% Jewish this the best day of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I’ve been in the womb, I have been eating Jason’s deli all you can eat ice cream. https://t.co/rQ0QEaMhb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[before everyone posts about how their bf is the best... just know you’re all wrong, mine is. sorry I don’t make the… https://t.co/MKCimyi5oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already at work. Uploading the Coors @ Central Albuquerque Behaves Badly video right now. It'll be up on YouTube la… https://t.co/j2WLN9Dbjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenziebeck23 @fien_charlie @Sparki777 @WildChild69 @LandorMelanie @cheomitII @huskerfalcon44 @HERterus… https://t.co/MUFdZwi6xL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and dad got matching shoes to work out together😩🥰 https://t.co/av3vveLT5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I fall asleep on the couch, fully dressed, with MSNBC on  in the background. Did I actually really sleep at all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone needa figure out if we can eat a animal we aint ate yet cause im bored]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamaalPayton34 @Jrockboxing @JoshuaPrikryl @Sheena_allure When you decide to work in a field such as health care y… https://t.co/NU7ECsA2f0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieBrennan12 @neil_mccormick @picturethis Can you NOT slag off Bono please? Thanks 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf Given Cindy Yang’s presence at Mar-a-Lago, I really want to know how Kraft decided to frequent that par… https://t.co/eVSp7ohprA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassy9374 @pam_brundige @johndrewsmom @abutler04 @richardlsoto @pmmich @dmewing47 @DavidTaylorNYC @SteveCochrane5… https://t.co/qATAoZQv3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[#gravedigger was here @ Walmart Union City - Dyer St https://t.co/jaLbA0J1l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dochitect @CLOSLER @GenCounsNews @Top_Gundersen @kristinadzara Just had a similar discussion with @RachelSalasMD a… https://t.co/HHGt1TOuYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatScarletMoth In the States marmalade comes in jars in a jelly like consistency but I suppose you could scoop an… https://t.co/V4uxTgwzaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Shaun Cassidy, google him since I’m sure no one knows who he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are aware of all that you have to be grateful for, you change your mindset and your energy. Think about th… https://t.co/Dvlfq39iUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched Bohemian Rhapsody last night.  Rami Malek:👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻 Rami Malek’s teeth:😬😬😬 The last 20 minutes: 🙌🏻😭🙌🏻… https://t.co/3OfSEoCDLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDugudichi Knowing that there is good in everyone, because we know they are made in God's image.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did we ever figure out what to do with those tossed salads and scrambled eggs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're looking for a new addition to our social media team. Learn more or apply online now: https://t.co/WKCtdRQRU5… https://t.co/EBMCLMBxIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels Would love to take you to dinner of you come to the San Francisco Bay area! You're gorgeous smart fu… https://t.co/xz3bUO3FYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful to @SmiloTweets for bringing me to The Hill and getting to learn so much from him. The social team is S… https://t.co/epopKfQ0Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAFrench Precedent???  You think Hillary Clinton or Kamala Harris would give a thought to “precedent” if they… https://t.co/MTJBrDi4QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaKolar @_DivideXZero @themediawitch She blocked me because I asked her if she thought Obama was racist for… https://t.co/QgWoMLGvxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rock_Hard_Abbbs Song drops at midnight. Buckle up—it’s gonna be one hell of a ride my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s probably time to upgrade this 6s. @brothersosborne #brothersosbourne #country #concert #music #saturday #dc… https://t.co/d3r6hLpVUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnDsaxplayer I feel that 😭😭😭 what are you doing tonight other than paying bills? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my on hand inventory.. If you see something simply message me. 🔥💜🔥💜🔥💜 @ Leicester, North Carolina https://t.co/mjq8th3PCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You sir need meds or a mental Dr to control your obsession with our wonderful prez.  I g… https://t.co/neUcEFYQz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad just told me so when you begin your new job, cuando vas a ver a tu carbon de novio? LMFAO he really said car… https://t.co/6Q7i7249Mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫Lonely Too Long by @theploveless, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/PbnT8f6rWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition Yes, it is absolutely astounding....his arrogance, and their adulation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenery444 That's the absolute worst. I'm hoping that this was an allergy sneeze...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiverDown25 @politico @realDonaldTrump Youre a hilariously bad liar. Collumbine happened when Clinton was in offic… https://t.co/KiKuvcudzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is literally how my drill sergeant was when we would get mail. He’d be like “wow this is ridiculous. I miss th… https://t.co/PuEdrcvexf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apioquijano @ReebokMx @Reebok Así igualito yo 😏 pero con mis tacones 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parispoems i forgot to tell you I watched personal shopper a few days ago!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No person on this earth I would rather start this new chapter with than my loving amazing wife sadieflower1 so exci… https://t.co/shVfMrt9i8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does dispatch keep fucking meeeeeeee it’s like I am literally bent over on all fours getting pegged right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Danny is an unhinged New Yorker.  Somewhat successful but not really.  Nothing to show for himself so go knock trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to crown our Instructional Assistant of the year tomorrow morning! Who will it be? #LPESWAKE… https://t.co/vh4QbKRwJO]]></document></documents></author>