<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler For starters the pineapple is no longer whole so how can it be sold at Whole Foods? (That was a joke f… https://t.co/BkVTohdxpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una grata noticia: la confirmación de @netflix que apostó por una serie basada en Cien Años de Soledad, la popular… https://t.co/wrCrPyc99d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Too early for popcorn. Girl Scout cookies and coffee are keeping me company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really fuck with the way some people just really vibe with me fr. Makin me all happy and warm n fuzzy n shit. Goofy ass people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SearchQueen @JerryDMayer @RepDanCrenshaw @WashTimes You should research the history of voting rights in the U.S. i… https://t.co/9jT7QiuFlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an extraterrestrial look using my @JeffreeStar #alienpalette and @GerardCosmetics liquid lipstick in 1995… https://t.co/q0ueBVsBHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg @nbcsnl @kenanthompson Your own black people destroy your own black people I remember back in the day we… https://t.co/5w4jl8vhsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gonzaga_Prez @ZagMBB @BulldogBand_GU @ZagKennelClub And @ArmyGonzaga all Senior color guard! https://t.co/4qmNArL35Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want this summer to be my oyster too! That sounds amazing! @BravoTV #SummerHouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all about the Big Hair ➰➰ . . . #naturalhair #naturalhairchixs #naturallyshesdope #curls #curlsunderstood… https://t.co/L2Vuk778pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey, have any of your friends with kids watched the Shrek movie where he becomes human and said, ‘Hey, that looks… https://t.co/EA5Df1R0vN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IYBRobin remember we have to get some picachu for @NotFearix today, since u know. Yea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Can2geterdone @POTUS Can’t judges be arrested for not upholding the laws of the land? If not, why not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danjlevy @GQMagazine @NolanFeeney You are like sunshine on anShitts Creek. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rick_Pescatore https://t.co/JSaf9QSA6W.    Hope you enjoy this.. seems like your kinda Doc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really HAVE to travel for a living. If I become a travel blogger or something like that I need y’all to support me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation - too bad live Pd wasn’t in my home town- could have been in on the bust of Robert kr… https://t.co/3RVTJUVo9J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blacked out for my 22nd just like I did for my 21st.. yikes getting older isn’t as bad as they say]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DahliaElGazzar @EventTechWomen @marie_clair I love the laughter on @marie_clair’s face.  Empowering to be around so many amazing women!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeBouchard19 @TheWestBlock @lraitt @PierrePoilievre Yeah. .. considering it started under Harper....]]></document><document><![CDATA[How censoring works:  Man's nipple = okay Woman's nipple = not okay Man-dressed-to-look-like-a-woman's nipple = okay https://t.co/aGOKrPICXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Rui Hachimura for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/B4JuzOB2qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ayykarly @ayykarly @moore_gabi @Kt_M1339 I’m actually so scared of this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[🙌🏼Big day in Hoboken today.  Meeting with two #healthcare giants to talk #WFM #RPA #performancemanagement… https://t.co/DmvTEXjqHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bren_O1967 @DrJimmyStar @RoverDov123 @TonyaRBlue1 @wyattpauley @greg_dabbs @KinglyT @codieprevost @CodyPurvisMusic… https://t.co/LpPoZ8rE0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just feel at peace when my dog puts her head on my hand and goes back to sleep. 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are saying that they heard a window-rattling boom all over the islands about 3 hours ago. Anyone know what that’s about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the friends I’ve made at work.  They truly light up my day &amp; daily life so much♥️☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait to see where life takes you, as your bestfriend i support all you do, and even if i hate that you’re m… https://t.co/dkglRcgy8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[also would like to thank the dirty chai i just mobile ordered for the exciting anticipation of getting to my office building to pick it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[You want to see a school district with an extraordinary vision for young people and doing what it takes to make tha… https://t.co/fbDIBM1SAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay Tell world leaders to make workplaces safe for women everywhere. #ThisIsNotWorking #care2 https://t.co/yjkp5jj1So]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, puppies are like teenagers, they WANT rules and discipline, but test the boundaries.  You’ll be a better dog wi… https://t.co/y8vM4EX5IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grown up version of a Girl Scout vest @ Brielle, New Jersey https://t.co/oFi5dhVunZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javimerla @BebeRexha @eentertainment @VentaneandoUno @programa_hoy Dejala a la infeliz,  pero se va arrepentir!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw these puppies on the way home. Too cute #adoptdontshop #puppies #nyc #citipupsnyc @ Citipups https://t.co/LqTAoyEe7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually end up putting my foot in my own mouth when I’m mad because I overreact sometimes! 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diversity is being asked to the party. Inclusion is being asked to dance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to mean mug the shit out of people and secretly flip them off, don’t come for my mama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tito9k9 Martes y miércoles sin nuestros días off Tito o sea nuestros findes 😉lo de la locura es 24/7 🤪🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyHansen007 @TheCartelMatt @RealRonPhillips Still can’t believe I landed a smokin hot soldier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s kinda bullshit the nobody in the Barstool offices will talk to Alex and Sofia. Never thought y’all were stuck up like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemonicaBanks @apsupdate We are honored to have you as a teacher! Thank you 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m enjoying this book thoroughly! Definitely recommend it ! https://t.co/D9AFbLMxoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Whatever sins Cohen committed, you have done worse. You are individual 1...an unindicted co-conspi… https://t.co/LEoJxkM9vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day from us! #valentinesday2019 #breannetylermcghee #😜 @ The River Christian Community https://t.co/YZFgieAMhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arkellsmusic I really regret sitting this one out. Have a great night! Save some energy (and confetti) for Buffalo, please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The logo is everything... see what I did there?? https://t.co/ZkyxP9BObv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I’m sitting in this cafe that’s in a single family home structure and it’s all just older wealthy women talking… https://t.co/mp890UZP4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to give light to others, you have to glow yourself. #sheshed #daylightsavings #goodmorningall ❤️ . . .… https://t.co/M6CUcXqD9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Saint Augustine University on https://t.co/mrR6sGGXON. The 2019 Home Depot Retool Your School Camp… https://t.co/fOZBAQ6Py4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emma Roberts looks amazing in litterly every outfit. We have that in common.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJSidBluntley @CrashingHBO @robbspewak Thank you so much :) thank you for watching #Crashing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I live with a roommate. I dream of having my own apartment one day but a requirement is making 2.5 times the rent.… https://t.co/uWlPihLitC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an 3 Prong Spear by @BarrierBrewing/@7islandbrewery @ The Beer Snob — https://t.co/pKieckNzxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QQitsMina @katjexia @soymilkgoth @myuturgy Oh I guess the freeway would probably be okay. But Taipei would be hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaufmanReport @MariaBartiromo @FoxBusiness @MorningsMaria Not of you or Marxism.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a vacation from people complaining about their jobs, especially after spending 7 months struggling to find o… https://t.co/R2RkdOnmXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SundayThoughts it’s time to come together and start over again and we can get back to where we want to be and I am… https://t.co/jhGOsMkMYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice base hit Tristen ❤️⚾️💙 de_real_jesus @ Paradise Valley Community College https://t.co/QXpD5jw8G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get my second brain scan tomorrow and I’m praying that my tumor didn’t get bigger 😩🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfaoooooooo my mom posted a picture of my sister and she’s wearing my shirt and my shoes and now I gotta fight her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two ways to train @northpennymca today. Stopped by this “training” on my way to the other. (Think I’ll listen to Dr… https://t.co/yra2TAqgsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you weren’t lucky enough to grow up watching #90210 you missed out! #RIPLukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how they say you got the real thing when nothing else matters ♠️ https://t.co/EijB1Xx50o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcasabona @McDwayne Hit me up! I think we'd be able to talk not only about building website but building fitness c… https://t.co/WzvqKKxWAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's laughter. dumpaday funny pictures (3371) https://t.co/OgHhCQmKIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trynarepresent @awlasky @wordrefiner @marshawright @Ltd_To_Two @harmony_kent @NationalDayCal @checkiday… https://t.co/cjmws7MrXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of all the interviews I’ve ever conducted in my career, sitting down with pastry chef, founder of @labreabakery, an… https://t.co/zEEn8DzKy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t hate the player, hate the game @ Rutgers University - College Avenue Campus https://t.co/yUclSw1Twr]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of bullshit that occurs while i’m supposed to be writing an essay is insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶Learn your rules You better learn your rules If you don’t you’ll be eaten in your sleep🎶😂 #TheOffice @rainnwilson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cynthia74015493 The Hill is famous for posting ridiculous info.  No poll today will be accurate.  They never have been.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a call with Debra tonight:  Mom: “isn’t it cute that Michael B. Jordan brought his mom to the Oscars?”   Me: “ye… https://t.co/0xmq6jjVYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 39th BIRTHDAY BABY LOVE YOU SO MUCH. THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING. WISHING YOU NOTHING BUT THA BEST ON YOUR SPECI… https://t.co/nyVrSuE9SM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet your candidate for Woman of the Year! Join me on my journey to #cure #cancer. It begins March 28! More info co… https://t.co/skgX3B86zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runnr_az I hope you have a great day! Right now it’s looking like I’ll be at home observing Shabbos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencergibb Olps@sorry! Im    WATCHING BNRAW' (WWE) !  LIVE THESE.  PSYCHOS ! Anyway  I am also sorry to hear abou… https://t.co/Lhj335olp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyallantdf OMG! Found AMAZING crystal/spiritual shop right here in the Cape. So happy! I bought black salt, bless… https://t.co/aytN6yPziY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillRMcDermott congrats on the @RyanQualtrics partnership - feels like a powerfully positive expansion for all of… https://t.co/ZXpYQf6ijU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask his hat is $270?! And what kinda fucking nerd ain’t wearing a watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieDonovan @realDonaldTrump @doj @FBI I agree whole heartedly! Hopefully they will be arrested and put where the… https://t.co/zdFlW3bniz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rehman_Callitri Are you calling my ears big or does that mean something else? 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just 2 more weeks until the #SMR4M returns to the race track for the Turnpike Challenge @CreekSpeedway… https://t.co/F1OJ5eCUmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It’s also that the data we do have—data that policymakers depend on—is bad. You might even call it sexist. We like… https://t.co/VR0ta5nsX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imdanielsalazar @VeraMBergen Super into EOS. Also try Mono, Sigur Ros, God is an Astronaut and the Album Leaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History  March 7th 1965 Civil Rights March Alabama 7th March, 1965 Troopers with night sticks, shotguns an… https://t.co/OeuHGlm5Zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to https://t.co/oarsrQZDr7 to send an email now! Help bring Yasser home]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a woman❤️ that’s what I am🌸 No one will tell me otherwise and if they do I will just walk away with no confront… https://t.co/CFRKD9CIu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsimercer_ Yesss, I wish I had all our old pics and stuff! Good times. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, do you remember when the Oscars had a host? Man what were we thinking all those years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After listening to #Beekeeper Porter I found the #Honeybee Democracy book online to read for myself - love the cove… https://t.co/n6tX3cV8Cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt Winnipeg Manitoba or Minneapolis Minnesota PLEASE See this Namjoon or  any of yous...I'm losing hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Only Anderson Cooper! Priceless.  @andersoncooper   #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough #ResignNow… https://t.co/TyBfiDLYma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Stien OMG !! That was exactly my comment on that !! We're too much alike.  I'd love to make some scratch marks on that !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CommishEileen @thomasrodrigues @JoeCarolloNow @FrancisSuarez @transitmiami @CommishEileen we received confirmation… https://t.co/bnB0ZvHWdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asdfghjkl you’re a night mode baby too???!!! All the more reason to love you more! #nightmodebabys where y’all at?!… https://t.co/4UepAxfd6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hang out with this little baby doll! She is adorable! #newbornphotography #richmondnewbornphotography… https://t.co/0JSYJVVS1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[So he wears button down shirts and khakis...this nigga says yeah I gotta go get me some dickie’s. Like bruh you the… https://t.co/odefE9PyaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤩Con Sue Photography and Design🤩  🥰Like our photos...Follow our IG 🥰  😍This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/c6gOh8pn9W]]></document></documents></author>