<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tammys85 They are sneaky crackhead ninjas. Lol. They learned if they buddy up and slam themselves into my door it opens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off for a fun and #relaxing me day so I started my morning off with #saxonchocolates #champagnetruffles for breakfa… https://t.co/soRlLNuZl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most influential leaders have done just this for me. @casas_jimmy says We are blessed every day with the opport… https://t.co/pqJG7xKrx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, given the amount of warrantless, illegal surveillance the U.S. government conducts on average Americ… https://t.co/OGzWG32ifT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think there is really anything that can make me want to move out of California... but I do need to get rich… https://t.co/VqoVItO0wV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting off #CVSummit day 2 with the reality of current healthcare spending.  We spent too much 😳 We gotta figure… https://t.co/6emmwGliwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar @kat223 Helsinki there were no notes there at all and the GOP wouldn't do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horror Story ANIMATED - "I Used to Work the Graveyard Shift at Dunkin' D... https://t.co/uJTVj8ub7N via @YouTube @CoryxKenshin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Mark Green's (TN) suggestion that  Cohen was a horrible man begs the question:  Why did Donald Trump keep him o… https://t.co/32zOpQeohx]]></document><document><![CDATA[why am i crying i miss it so much this was my Love Is Skit (TAT) 💞 https://t.co/CEuHbCwUAD via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jawofsteel2014 @DetroitLove88 @Twitter @TwitterSupport @TwitterDev @jack @ReneeLibby2 @SavaAnderson94… https://t.co/IQUrqvZzZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[we just met our roommates for next year and i can already tell they’re gonna be so much fun i love them they’re so nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTouchinsky @NBCWorldofDance Every time I watch a show like this it makes me wish I would have learned dancing when I was young.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gorgeous bb and I went out to celebrate her birthday last night! #besties #fancybroads #candlelight… https://t.co/87FrqbHdwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am dreading the day the Four gets into something and has it every fucking where 😩 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Local24Brad @KNWAnews @Fox24News @weatherdan @LanceLloydTV @clarbusta @kellyoneillTV @KatieeDavila @melissahallwx… https://t.co/9xdqBppKtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@souljaboy I know that's right you're worst, so just have several seats and stay away from the mirror because I thi… https://t.co/FX9r8AtD2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I deep clean my house it makes me feel so good and happy. But then I think delanie and George will be home in… https://t.co/31oH0asO7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join Us!!! Good Friday 4/19.... You don’t want to miss it! @ Cathedral International Asbury Park https://t.co/OISpLa6h65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge says he does not have any prior convictions...but there were incidents while he was incarcerated at the SCSO… https://t.co/drlbbLj8mF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The face you make when your Mama is holding a cookie hostage so Candyman can get the perfect shot #RudyRoo… https://t.co/kyGmjiKl9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, this dinner scene where the couple is discussing Buñuel seems to be a nod to The Discreet Charm of the Bourge… https://t.co/bvVnwhGO5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You’re right, @HouseDemocrats should take a stronger stand against you. There were NOT “very fine… https://t.co/5cKLmO5seQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lawindsor @RepMattGaetz @RepMarkMeadows it's laughable to think that the mere presence of #MattGaetz would intimid… https://t.co/5H9IgZZu2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet him that I can go a month without sweets... he knows DARK chocolate Is my weakness #gimmedat https://t.co/AZ21hoMJIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rob_Bradley Haiku:   Hampton almost was gone. We need a sidewalk. Please help us, public safety.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching hubby playing OoT Masterquest Hubby: I wanna be a child Me: Can you go back? *talking about the game* Hubb… https://t.co/vMk0fdNQfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤LHS students and staff donate to the Blood Drive today. Thanks to all!❤ @ Lyndhurst High School https://t.co/82cKk8w5ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OtisWhi27174033 @ann_cannon @krassenstein Oh Donny John loves hiring undocumented workers.  He thinks he’s getting… https://t.co/DkbH2ei9TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You jackass you’re on video saying you believe Kim! Are you seriously insane????]]></document><document><![CDATA[pa' que se de cuenta de lo que perdió pa' que el hijueputa se sienta peor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asalleo @BNCPurdue @Boudouris_Group It was fantastic. I have not seen such a packed room for a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great #edleaders modeling the way! #partnerpride @GregGibson10 @SCUCISD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate looking so friendly bc men and bible study groups take it as an invitation to approach me 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at Hanna B being marure! Like it! #moveforward  #WomenTellAll https://t.co/m6gIOVJr9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really just trying to find some advanced musician friends and jam all the time. I wish it was as easy as it sounds lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve broken into my exes a lot of times so...” - Lolo   Color us shocked.  #BBCeleb #CBBUS2 https://t.co/hQD8aUQK6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot pot. Hot man. Hot love❤️. @ Little Sheep Mongolian Hot Pot, Edison 小肥羊 https://t.co/1t6SW6yo5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTChargerTom @Love4PoliceDogs @K9Garm @UTChargerTom @Love4PoliceDogs  just amazing 😉 job @K9Garm @Kimberl38218406… https://t.co/0uc69l2H5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthark After seeing dispatch comments, I can believe outrage at anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The drama with this Cohen hearing! @RashidaTlaib getting very emotional now talking about race and @RepMarkMeadows firing back. 🤭😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome home @LibertyMBB regular season Champions of  @ASUNMBB 🔥 https://t.co/8Yg6dqODl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t want to pay me what I ask then proceed to ask someone with less “experience” (or less “klout”) and not pr… https://t.co/owMZOez7vC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It reveals a crucial question about how we respond to activists: When should we push back — and when should we wait… https://t.co/FWiSm96ZRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonCoAL_EMA @LegalMoonshiner Wow. Betting the lake is over my old sea wall on Clemons Road!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyThriller69 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews That is the exact opposite of what Obama stands for it sound… https://t.co/nFd3o3JTBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBROINTHEAM that man deserves to go to gen pop after what he did!! #FOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Las mujeres reales no tenemos voluntad”... pienso mientras me visto a las 7am en feriado para una sesión de pierna… https://t.co/JSHoGktero]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobReyes13 @edmaverickmus El crush de mi mejor amiga se fue de after con el:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casually listening to the best podcast ever, @upandvanished, and hear “we talked with @EmileighTV with WALB” 👏🏻👏🏻 O… https://t.co/Quq9Z4nWKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to get back in the gym and put in the work and get where i wanna be. #upfromhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eugene Rogers for your Transfiguration Sunday: "a mystery is not that which human beings do not understand, althoug… https://t.co/JO6cPnIJG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottydog57 @almostablaze @CasaskullMark @ml2370 @HomonLang @ccsunflwer @LinemansLadyLuv @ethan1655 @panekbill… https://t.co/aKofph5NHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my OBGYN asks if I'm sure I want another IUD... https://t.co/5G9M0pu4t7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrysFanGyrl @TheHSCharts I can't stand that little prick Bieber ! Sorry.  So opposite of our beautiful man. He's… https://t.co/zQJNPKPbrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work staffing issues have been so annoying this week. And very unprofessionally. No bueno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zwinak2020 @lucymcbath Nope asking wayyy too much of it but a start! Reality is key Think how long it took! And it… https://t.co/INMGUWyDHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love discovering new bands. Tonight I was fortunate enough to see @punchlion open for @ginblossoms and they were fa… https://t.co/pJ7wjjuQeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that when I’m in the suburbs, people always ask me if I have kids. As if, that was the onl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am cute. I deserve a treat. Or two. Or three. -Cappuccino . . #cappuccinothebunny #rabbitsofinstagram #instabunny… https://t.co/UvpyyO3cm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bratva are Russian Mafia.  I was working on research for a tv show on mobsters in LA.  Please see this. Note me… https://t.co/Eg1IXkyoMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im just trynna sleep but my neighbors downstairs are having the loudest fight ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KitKatPopTart_ @_KingBooks_ @jarpad @JensenAckles I like the new teacup!! But if you ever change from a teacup I… https://t.co/Da8V5lqJZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hands may still smell like crawfish, but it was worth it @ Alex Box Stadium, Skip Bertman Field https://t.co/8HH1TKZMvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reina is a brilliant and talented bilingual woman, who does her utmost to educate the world about Japanese culture.… https://t.co/vTC39ILs0C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DudekLinda @andrerucker51 @Itridpm @landscaperstev1 @SarahGould_SA @evilgrrl @hey_butter @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/iZyhfF8PlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox chyron on piece ab Bernie entering: “Another wacky liberal enters 2020”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily They are so threatened by women that they are losing their minds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_fu66 @peterdaou Yes, but they need to be held accountable. They will justify their part in this nightmare and we… https://t.co/fozkU6GR4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahSabich Made me want to visit all the "Paw Paw" towns in the Midwest! My great-grandfather had a tree in his ya… https://t.co/QNnSkgizvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The frustration a mom feels when @SouthwestAir cancels her daughter’s flight home for spring break( twice and delay… https://t.co/xLRISaDndT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Head’s up, twitter world. #scam #IRSscams #dontbeavictim #useyourhead #andcommonsense https://t.co/YS8gMNX9wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg the gopro footage of me bungee jumping in new zealand is hilarious 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m acting like I don’t work tomorrow. Still wide awake. Is it Friday yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownAngelEyes_ @sylvainreynard @Argyle_Empire @AuthorHKCarlton @TMitBSFP @GabrielSeriesFP Thank you 🤞]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pray #godismystrength #jesuschrist #dontworry @ New Rochelle, New York https://t.co/jcuOLPxf01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Lighten up, please. You sound like someone else. Not a good look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagsBitchs @casey40204472 Too much info? I know. Packing up and remembering my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisa0606 I’m a Christian conservative Republican. 4 yr college graduate. Reg nurse for 33 yrs. retired. I’m educated. Not a snowflake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xiivictoria not at all victoria i wanna get railed by a hot butch lesbian slipp]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was showing someone pictures of my dog i my phone last night and they commented on my selfie addiction and i felt attacked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too, I be attracting older men but by older I mean 80 year old men :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re up now because someone is taking the bus or walking to a Worcester high school, the transportation report… https://t.co/9LBSmgWWnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMchubs we sit passively watching their world fall apart and make NO MOVe to intervene with our modern technologies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crap I need to seriously do something about my sleep... I feel so exhausted but yet I fell asleep so early]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum It’s obvious they don’t want fair they want special 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[There were many good trains to be seen along my walk toward downtown this morning. #stl https://t.co/qz7qAQMeor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climate Scientist Gavin Schmidt runs in fear from a debate https://t.co/G3TNl9Ljvt via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn @GeneralHospital @WilliamdeVry1 When I posted a tweet yesterday saying I was a loyal viewer I had NO… https://t.co/eJU4RZsUPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Campaign Trump: I know the best people.  (Trump supporters Would buy snake oil from a guy in a covered wagon believ… https://t.co/eWgZy1IIgj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BwareOfKoko I’m so mad and slightly crazy that I was hoping she got hit by a car Friday 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImBREzANNE_by rip hunny.. been there done that https://t.co/Cryebt7FQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DEvanAltman (actually i have the PERFECT target material in my garage, we should start our own damn league...as long as we get shirts)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucentKnight @carlatomsmd @realDonaldTrump @LucentKnight. You really have to stay off the drugs and stop drinking… https://t.co/k02jOe5jz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaysees_U Ok pero like chill on me then shit. Not trynna argue, jus trynna not be attacked anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time it starts to get nice in LA I instantly remember why I love this crazy city #75andsunny #readytobird #springisintheair]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfrady_ hello! I love how you can adapt to wherever you go and make the most of everything you do. You're so passi… https://t.co/IYL1Gd7Bmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahOrens @trailhead Send them steps to set up their account.   You should install @trailhead tracker app]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/N4gamUBHoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t tell me @ladygaga and #BradleyCooper did not steal the #Oscar2019]]></document></documents></author>