<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration No! Laws only apply when they totally disregard the constitution and apply to the citizens it prot… https://t.co/Mep8kHUHTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I dream of going somewhere where nobody knows me and just start fresh.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanLATG Huh? Somebody must be paying deposit fees to TVG except on Mondays. Not the biggest issue given Rangers,… https://t.co/E209Bs17S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NHswimming @HawkenAthletics Sydney Bare 3rd 100 breast 1:03.52 30.02/33.50 1.09 &amp; 1.67 drops vs 18 state https://t.co/ZKA0KRVNfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[We working! #lmusftv @ Loyola Marymount University's Playa Vista Campus https://t.co/e6vsSxxxsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Misty on her #New #2015 #Nissan #Pathfinder!! Thanks for choosing enterprise as your place of #business… https://t.co/bfY5yVieO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ange19669107 cet événement est ce soir à bubble room à scottsdale.  I think this is the right way to say the event… https://t.co/yYZQXn7cdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sendavidperdue Wake up America as the liberal leftist idiots who murder Babies and are destroying America from within 😡🤡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovin’ the t-shirt here in @RCSD ‘go head on wit dat bullshit’. Well said @LivePDNation #LivePDNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing I aee from Dems is spending more money. Amazing they obviously have no understanding of who is payin… https://t.co/6dSGmnmbL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is encouraging to see this vote of confidence in Squamish-based Carbon Engineering, one of several BC-based lead… https://t.co/Klt1TBZSxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @MollyJongFast I hope someone confiscated his passport.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flying_squirrel Kind of want to see the corresponding wall of sausages. @FQbutchershop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amysrosenberg @panaritism They are still going up, maybe just as much as they might have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer Group circulating video showing why Feinstein deserves to face primary challenge, previously acted… https://t.co/UmspVZMQev]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of those skiing lessons really paid off. Clementine has a good understanding of how to maneuver down the mounta… https://t.co/4g3RJAkJcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BS__Detector @Azrael2124David @OceanKeltoi @1SonuvaGunn @SteveMcRae_ @BlancoIndian @PhilosophyTiger… https://t.co/YACfENjOkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently studying for my accounting exam that’s tonight and the last one I got a 25% on and my brain can’t tak… https://t.co/HDy7kPkZVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddkitta I like a bigger screen, but I'm happy with it when I borrow @Kresing's go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah right, go figure ...how many skeletons does he have in his closets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaldanaAustinTX @StElmoMustangs @LisaVSaldana @MrMacAISD Yayayay Jake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day at my local @ChickfilA 🤣 #TRUMP2020 #KeepAmericaGreat #FridayFeeling https://t.co/vsHO5t7sHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBAndersen @Stiffelman 📣Since your talking about my neck of the woods now, it’s actually spelled Loudoun County. S… https://t.co/UiEOPXOt9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dussani @JulianRoman Ivancito hijo, te recuerdo que esta norma es tomada del nuevo código de policía aprobado en e… https://t.co/cwKxnWmbBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Animystic by @tiredhandsbeer @ Locust Grove — https://t.co/XGXHuSqQRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctors issue health alert over #XDR typhoid outbreak in Sindh. https://t.co/eDjbhqLjmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna have Mike Trout &amp; Bryce Harper on my baseball team lmfao, I’ve never even had that on my diamond dynasty team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genial la respuesta de la @RAEinforma ante una twittera que se las da de graciosa 😂 https://t.co/RF4aBHGLsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krunkkone Is the 3 weeks in advance best time for purchasing or are you saying in general?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward today to seeing defenders of the president describe a lawyer as an all-knowing person with special p… https://t.co/KMrvjym4jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great read for parents and their athletes. Don’t just quit or transfer. https://t.co/EGAaA4qtXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #NationalPeanutMonth with Indika Farms in Isle of Wight County!! We’re shelling some #peanuts LIVE this… https://t.co/iTTXYsv8zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s  the beginning of a new month, and what’s on my mind right now is what March means for my classes, my upcoming… https://t.co/pyOFMKzLgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft been supportin prison reform den allava sudden he jamned up for prostitution 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full body HIIT workout done!! Post workout PB2 and vegan chocolate recovery and reward going down!!  When I say it… https://t.co/ojj3xyYpTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is already cancelled tomorrow except OCCC, and I’m not even saying this hoping for a cancellation, I’m a… https://t.co/gXKqy0AEIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @AOC @realDonaldTrump A pc is a wack job that has gotten herself on the Obama payroll through netfli… https://t.co/ILiuNTzvhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading Unabomber Manifesto in Irving Farm café to prepare for my Ted Kaczynski reading group.  Thinking, NAFTA is… https://t.co/KyjIqITeCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi It's time to start impeachment process. https://t.co/bTN8HehC1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wise man once said you ain’t never gonna be happy til you love yourz, felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean...could have eased us in a little there Dan geez...I need a drink #ALLCAPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finishing up a thermal scan of a 38MW #solar plant in Antelope Acres, CA. New #DJI #Matrice 200 drone has been… https://t.co/y8WWgDqMUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurry, someone push her over and grab her passport!  Make her try and climb President Trump’s wall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past is prelude to the future. The 17th century Age of Exploration energized cartography, math, botany, telesco… https://t.co/6ZIG0ya7rP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in NM .. NRA Alert: HB 83 is being heard today! Please contact your Senator now @ (505) 986-4300 and urg… https://t.co/ctuWvW88Ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csupp @jeffpearlman I lived in @CityofSgf for 9 years and is NOT a college town #noway #nokind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Predators beat Kings 2-1, move back atop Central Division  https://t.co/8URyJDpOVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The state's director of pipeline safety is stepping down  ://www.wbur.org/bostonomix/2019/02/12/pipeline-safety-director-leaving]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot to ask for almond milk in my coffee today and I haven’t had milk in over two years... I’m going to have diar… https://t.co/Eb9OEoJjOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, M*gyn K*lly doesn’t have a job, which is all the more reason to stop giving her free exposure by retweeting her… https://t.co/Xtg3TsuzHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraClub How "clean" are solar panels (and all the heavy metals) after their 20 year life?  How "clean" are wind… https://t.co/wleC8D9yFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo heute geht es heim. Gleich nochmals in die Firma und dann ab die Post. 60 Tage USA sind dann vorbei. Bin ja s… https://t.co/VlkqK8tk34]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when people lean on the crutch of the CDC as an arbiter of reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@printerman1968 @BBCNews Exactly. Also there have been many babies killed in the terrorist bombings that she , her… https://t.co/yaLltbwV2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattCarterMedia Crashing!? How!? SMILF!? I don’t understand. Both great shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milesgrimes The black and white mode can be cool if you use it right, but this mode is just hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sweatpants but whenever I wear them I always get half chubs n I don’t know what to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate witness says this man can shed light on Trump mystery  https://t.co/1s7MHcCwKL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Heritage, Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/uwhUTZKZfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezbeezy214 @YESNetwork @NYCFC @joetolleson Too bad @RealMichaelKay and the rest of the show don't know anything so… https://t.co/shgfp6ZCBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therookie @sarahshahi I don’t know the answer, but it’s nice to see Sarah again. #TheRookie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @kreisberg Trump is asking his lawyers if he can plead the 21st Amendment...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POWER1061 Only thought is that this secured President Trump's seat in 2020.  #MAGA 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulgalloshow was Omars comment so different than tRumps? https://t.co/L4G9aIkUZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conference tournaments are starting soon.  Here are the lead pipe locks for each conferences auto bid.  Can you fin… https://t.co/lDvrUeelBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two nights in a row of almost perfect sleep,,, cool. I am dialed in for what will be another great day.  Fitness re… https://t.co/uH26TWc6Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: 7 Headphone Trends to Watch in 2019: Do you know that some of the technology used in current headp… https://t.co/j1jh8aOSSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was a college student, I’d sell my ticket for $3k and go watch the game at McNallys or the Rhawn Pub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Intensive Care Unit Registered Nurse - ICU RN" in #CedarPark, TX. Go on informati… https://t.co/Kq7AtYGQya]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDanZak @mobilematt The Senate must have felt her vast wealth of experience far outweighed her hate and bias!  #WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDorts @chrissyteigen Omg Bryan do you not know who that is lol. She’s married to Kanye]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant believe this website is free god bless u twitter dot com https://t.co/jhiwgihQNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeidiFang Anyone have a photo of that thumbs up?  That arm looked LIMP.  I do not think Robbie is lying btw, but w… https://t.co/oIkqRvqw0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's  day we all have love in our lives if you don't  have someone special love yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrington’s testimony is breaking until 1:30.  #WVTM13. #DonaldWatkinsfraudtrial]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snboxing He lost to truax both times. Not fair that he got a rematch n the cooking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Thunder have the most arm sleeve depth in the NBA.  Not only do they start w/ six arm sleeves on the floor — We… https://t.co/oK0dXJl1PO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii No one in media asking about Schiff meeting with a witness prior to testimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teslaownersSV The dopest f-ing P3D ive ever seen. @teslaownersSV Yours is sick too, but I got a bias since midnigh… https://t.co/XY2nhzbRwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to John Kruk during this Yankees - Phillies game has been painful. I feel bad for Phillies fans if this i… https://t.co/FqClVihRQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prince Tramaine💪🏾💯 #Son#Thickysmallz#Melanated#Daddiesboi#Spoiled#Handsome#Nikesweats#Nikewindbreaker#Jordans @ Jac… https://t.co/0nl2jPafnH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markneefuzz They are awesome. Am I too old to say awesome? Personal favorites are Ozma of Oz and Emerald City of Oz. 3 and 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to say it was my 3rd awkward altercation where this little white kid with a comb over asked me why I wasn’t a blue jackets fan..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNEE saquen del aire a ese Argentino comunista, pesimista, nueve negra, grandísimo CDSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanRichman1 My high school coaches would probably beg to differ. @EmersonShawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just landed tickets to see @normmacdonald at the @RoyalOakMusic theater!! Can’t wait!! #Legend #Comedy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I’m not the biggest fan of Kingdom Hearts plot, but if it keeps supplying more The World Ends With You content… https://t.co/zGySfzjF7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS @gatewaypundit The swamp wins again. More proof of corruption within DOJ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniebender Last year at ST, wifey spotted Baez and thought it was Kenley. I was dying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh.. Unbelievable. We gotta review some of these fouls they're calling (and not calling) this season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioSarmiento El turismo contribuye a la disminución de la pobreza en México, es un sector que no hay que descui… https://t.co/3FMnJVeXiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, was truly a winter fairytale. And the most perfect day for an engagement session at the Arboretum. These… https://t.co/HPitenAyjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maperezpirela eso es seguro, el lunes le Mike Pence le pedirá la renuncia a Nicolás Maduro]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dreaming of a firkin Friday.... - Drinking a Spruce Tip Ale by @voodoobrewery at @voodoobrewery  — https://t.co/cWhu0GBf5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t check for anyone . doesn’t mean I don’t care or don’t miss you . I just wanna leave you where I left you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so pumped!! Team SOBBLE!! (Is Scorbunny a new Fire/Fighting starter?!) #PokemonDirect #PokemonDay https://t.co/dLo4mrZVvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @CobosInsCenter Post-Match Interview with @FalconWrestle junior @p_burgdorf14, who won his state opener.… https://t.co/HNz0qoLomQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is #ready for some #darkavenueband this #friday at the #curtainclubdallas in #deepellum I am!! @ The Curtain Cl… https://t.co/tMYrhjxl4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not the Jesus I believe in.   Maybe that means I believe in a different Jesus. If so, fine. I’ll gladly spe… https://t.co/xLFQSClhMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with how bad the Bulls seem to be, people love going to the games. #lookspacked]]></document></documents></author>