<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Absolutely loved spending the whole evening with _dancer1246_  and getting to watch you sing. More than anything, I… https://t.co/QwxXaF68hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Organ donors make miracles happen!! ❤️  National Donor Day is Feb 14 ❤️ https://t.co/w5NbTOsJax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy os tengo súper abandonad@s pero aqui estoy, con una foto de una de mis ciudades favoritas #newyork #nuevayork… https://t.co/B6ceUwPDqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I officially leave the premises that name is not to be mentioned in my presence and that’s on the real. I will… https://t.co/QOhceFjAJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping DM @jasoncmiller play test his new @GaryCon adventure with these cool kids. This was one of the most fun ad… https://t.co/k6Qowba7g3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenRemanent Except I can still see it. 🙄🙄🙄 Lets talk about strippers and stage. Some clubs require us to be full… https://t.co/al9mYGG8b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyMcCarthy should my husband and I call into @TheJennyMShow tomorrow for the Soto Pelle segment? Boy has it inc… https://t.co/IJKMrsaTX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t agree with stripping but people say it’s degrading to the woman... dude, some men literally blow hundreds o… https://t.co/9kYFJnbMWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doug_Hermann @realDonaldTrump No he has thousands of people around him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was DAY TWO of Write-A-Palooza! We were able to bring our stuffed animals to school to use as writing buddies… https://t.co/YSXWIn4b65]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’M BACK WITH “NO HOOK P.T 4” GO CRAZY IN THE COMMENTS IF YALL FWI🔥🚨😈4️⃣ @ Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/4fqqzysyrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A university student taking journalism asked to use our goat farm for her project! Check out her results and give h… https://t.co/r8JPjE79HU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elevatededuk8tr @theNCForum I just started the check in and out with a kid that I struggled to create a plan for and IT IS WORKING!!👏🏽🎉🎊]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 5 days laying by a pool in Mexico eating the endless buffet and some tasty umbrella drinks, I was anticipatin… https://t.co/FsATs91UZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ?? Is what is happening lol to my insta , it’s growing overnight lmaooo wut did I do 😂❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Future of #Healthcare is #Female!  https://t.co/sVznMzzBGm #InternationalWomensDay2019 #IWD2109]]></document><document><![CDATA[(This isn’t even the case but) if Ari didn’t like Demi... who are we to argue? We don’t know these people lol just… https://t.co/ZiRkHtJmF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is disgusting but not surprising. We’ve been dealing with this for years yet white folks want to ask why we pu… https://t.co/19G8ckw39O]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a lot of metal. #metalmouth #eyebrowpiercing #thumbring what year is this @thrants? #tbt #throwbackthursday… https://t.co/MoXZB5K9cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, National Emergency but Republicans, once again, no BACKBONE! THE BILL IS RIDICULOUS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that was the day that I promised I'd never sing of love if it does not exist, but darlin' you are, the only exception 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next week, @mulaney is hosting SNL again and @ThomasRhett is the musical guest!!! My perfect episode!! I’m SO excited 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheShe0430 @lakesha_russell @DoriCreates @lisabuffaloe @harrimandt @SuzanneHarden @jamesha31561478 @Lundy08… https://t.co/lI6MdiNH52]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get an average, according to my sleep app, 24 minutes of deep sleep. So, I’m off to not sleep soundly and wake up… https://t.co/U0Qh39cBiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorraoRead @Arcolamsd @Methacton Can I go to after school performance when my 5th grader goes?  Sorry to be high maintenance😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It seems oddly appropriate that the tweet under this in my feed is @TheEdVerse answering a question about the Realm… https://t.co/7TrK8Y4ges]]></document><document><![CDATA[WeHo Just take me “Anywhere” Chapel djrolandbelmares instagay saturdaynight gayweho instagaymen gaymen GaysOnInstag… https://t.co/hAX8x0LQfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The slick and shifty look my son is giving in this cover photo just made me think of a character @davidalangrier played]]></document><document><![CDATA[El horror del infierno del Dante provocado por Maduro será el precio q deba pagar la ignominia de Maduro porque si… https://t.co/HFBRiZpxLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill That is insane! Where is the humanity in this world. I am disgusted!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pic: how I have to check out my back or back of my hair now. I can’t turn to look at it naturally anymore. Vid: cur… https://t.co/WOuts7AtKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris WTF is wrong with this low IQ idiot.  He needs to resign immediately.  This great country deserves so much better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Digital M… https://t.co/yepnB67bLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not think it calls for what majored in (in study), to answer to basic economic questions. Besides, for long, t… https://t.co/EMKb5pWcJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie Vince is an All-American. We hope to see you in the pool during your next visit home @CassandraVince… https://t.co/6encjuCM4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spend over 200$ at American eagle as if I don’t have bills or anything, but do I regret it ?? Absolutely not. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikaGlagowski @MaryJo44966098 @shartown @RyanPaevey @brooklyn_silzer @hallmarkchannel @billabbottHC… https://t.co/gr0spRSy4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ares_365 Hahaha I I’m definitely a sadist but I cringe thinking about that hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is one of those days where everything is setting me over the edge. Tech support, @dominos getting rid of thei… https://t.co/v3nBincmWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s display was the rough draft of the Declaration of Independence. As one of our top treasures it rarely… https://t.co/QAVFjdqjT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Lighthouse Baptist Church https://t.co/MG0veiUxGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard a great Doug Funnie reference yesterday and it made me really happy. #Nickelodeon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonofmambo @93XRT @LinBrehmer @MaryLDixon I was thinking more like 'I'll sleep in a little this morning because I'… https://t.co/PZyFKW3P5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would also like to say thank you to my friend @RvngoftheNERD thank you so much for coming thru to show love and a… https://t.co/Dk8cPaWqMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on the record saying I love crazy ass @lisarinna #RHOBH https://t.co/nAMbPx9QkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at Wells Fargo? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and inform… https://t.co/lZGC0YAB0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wassernixlein I am counting the minutes.  Let's get this party started.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulesAStrong I don’t even know what to say about it. It’s not often I’m speechless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so ready to go home. If everything goes well should only be 2 more days! Pray for those workers! #theresnoplacelikehome #wilsonflood2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24loves75 @NKOTB Oh... This one of @DonnieWahlberg from #NKOTBCruiseX?  #GodBlessTheRain #GodBlessWahlberg https://t.co/Ip6TY3xbsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realizing I’m the only person in the building that hasn’t had “Active Shooter Training.” That makes me the lea… https://t.co/DH5ekHbVkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nagstart na naman amon bidding sa premyo.. 😂🤦  Uli na kay ready na ang 55..😜 https://t.co/mCakZiLZtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cuds_1246 Jason, Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swithout pay… https://t.co/HmZDmLElMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even tho I slept allllll day yesterday &amp; all night I’m still tired af omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do realize (sometimes) that I'm not actually Canadian but c'mon, there's not a better Olympic team out there.....… https://t.co/4llIKEqQaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[rich got me Celtics tickets???? For Valentine’s Day????? Better gift?????? I think not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blasted: On Reza Abdoh’s Tight Right White https://t.co/PX4wO4TfSC via @bidoun]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dedicated this past weekend to myself and literally had the best time ever.   From riding a scooter in downtown A… https://t.co/Jc38ezHHjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m free!! Going home to relax and sleep and recover!! Thanks to Methodist Hospital and my amazing nurses, nursing… https://t.co/RpHNKhZWEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Heavy Equipment Mechanic - https://t.co/mlpCgmVWRC #Automotive #Frostburg, MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back roads in Franklin Ct. are so much worse than Ross Ct. simply bc they’re unfamiliar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to you Mrs. Robinson #blackleather #lingerieaddict honeybirdette 📸 frankie_rios @ ArtLab Photo Studio https://t.co/3mi4K4VtMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DianneFeinstein and the students — watch all video in this thread to get a fuller picture of the exchange...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blake_Morris18 You might not make it to dessert. I support your decision]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PakTheDreamer 420 on the rocks, go get discounted weed, do a 420 tour (its like a party bus for weed)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrooksABoyd @robertAbooey Also super annoying now that it doesn’t just start after the main show ends like it used… https://t.co/u73o64sO6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThoughtsOfRally Nope!  Don’t think so. I’LL drive u to pet store for treats!!😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate to cut in to relaxation time, but as I update grades, I want to remind HENG/Cohort that you owe me a flipgri… https://t.co/keWYren1u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ombudsman4truth @emptywheel This account RTs Bill Mitchell &amp; other trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winstonCovfefe Boot her out!!!!the law should never have been changed. Muslims do not belong in this government!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transportation works best when we allow people to live close enough to walk to it.  What if #newtonMA zoning reform… https://t.co/DvVUTHhkYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is so cute! Every time she sees my newest tattoo she says, "tattoo removal!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andie_lane7 @WillHoge @theryman @blackberrysmoke @SidetracksHSV Me too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapchat furbaby filters are a thing of beauty 🐶❤️😂 https://t.co/nA5K5i2sEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAKE ME TO SLURCH!!! Tonight is that wonderful night of the month where beautiful people do beautiful things involv… https://t.co/f1BsCrsgIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarah_clowder yep! and ive contacted them and they were basically like 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI 🔊  Check out article on David Cook in Issue Spring II of @Civilian_Mag  NEVER WANT TO BE DEFINED… https://t.co/waPnAjq1A0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCPesmerga @linda_henders1 @MuslimIQ So this is why you brought this up earlier...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@righttospeak3 @LivingFreeRescu @FallbrookAnimal I'm literally feeling sick! I need to take a break from twitter!!… https://t.co/28u31QlBSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game time 08 @LIGullsHockey vs a tough Virtua team #AYHLPLAYOFFS19 #thisiswhatweplayfor #hockeylife #hockeymom… https://t.co/Wl50ZHndsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yogagenie @buzzman888 No YOU are old #BabblingBiden fool .. you will never be #POTUS @RealJamesWoods]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I might need a console to play with people but i don’t want one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking out the carpets - I mean the  #Corgis 🤣on  their morning sweep! They are the sweetest #doggos ... Vesudes MY… https://t.co/p5kkPmV1ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking some time to relax and breathe. Feeling a lot better today and looking forward to a new week. #sunday… https://t.co/Mn9a3HpBJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewdolph Yeah they kill your insurance premiums too. I’ve slowed way down in my “old age.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbleasdale @politicaljimbo @MuslimIQ @houstonpolice I seriously doubt that the police there or anywhere else gives… https://t.co/Tj602XScPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3b: I want to personalize the rotations, activities and books. Hard to manage. #ksedchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the honor of meeting Senator Elizabeth Warren on International Women's Day! Wishing ALL women a happy… https://t.co/qgfft63D4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donidarkowitz @norvina1 @chloeqmakeup @glambymykaila @ArielleMonai @alanaauston @RAGGEDYROYAL @laurrrelyse… https://t.co/aEG8kpYeGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boujee_andbroke My mom had heard a lot of horror stories about the Dalkon Shield (which killed several women in th… https://t.co/dTdd9wFEXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well another Saturday in Minnesota! #winterstormwarning #snowyforest #nancycarlsonart #newdrawing https://t.co/xM7Steo4xS]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 🎁@tperez3826 #GIVEAWAY AT 1,000 FOLLOWERS🎁 . @ultabeauty Platinum Perk - early access for Platinum and Diamond me… https://t.co/gRIe0HSTwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap for @MulhollandWNYT co-anchoring in #Albany he’s back to reporting in the North Country, Monday @WNYT… https://t.co/2pOcnIRdKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many white woman have been caught on video making false claims against black ppl minding their own business? Th… https://t.co/droszcDpqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[grace lathrop really walked around with a pacifier in her mouth for majority of senior year and we did NOT stop her???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlDunn45 took a cemetery tour today and boy, did we have fun! https://t.co/69E7Ismy34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oiselle_sally @ThirdPlaceBooks @oiselle @BreneBrown Ooohh I want to read that one too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tell someone e everyday....we killing the world and ourselves smh like all the movies &amp; books said we would]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theboyonthebike Is there a website or forum that I could ask you a question?  Pretty difficult stance my son has t… https://t.co/T86GrvQOyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StartHereABC @ThisWeekABC @kateashaw1 People of California, I know there are so very many of you out there that sh… https://t.co/eVUduAd4ui]]></document></documents></author>