<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@alishamarss @daniel_cartwell @anthemgame Same here let me know when u wanna play and will jam love Anthem!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to finally have this masterpiece on vinyl...(but I’d probably) feel a whole lot better if side A hadn’t ar… https://t.co/UcnObJM0BX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday present take 2 @ Lock &amp; Load Miami https://t.co/kDDHv4nrKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realginnyrobins The courts will probably make him pay restitution to himself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@preakness03 @tonypearcey_a @CamRan02 Next pitch was the same and he rung him up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all live in California why are you surprised there was an earthquake 🙄😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dream in life, behind eating a beef Wellington at a @GordonRamsay restaurant, is to visit the @windowsdev office… https://t.co/nIKuo1xb0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASE_forAmerica No it isn’t. And electric vehicles are not “for the rich” any more. With the tax credit, a Tesla 3… https://t.co/LN7LPGvPeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Evans (@YahooNoise) was among roughly 15 percent of bracketologists who had Indiana in the Dance entering toda… https://t.co/I17dqq4aSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Endymion Parade #MardiGras2019 #NewOrleans @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/qnkn2ylOmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lego Movie 2 has to be a big disappointment for WB.  Still some major markets to go but just $136 mil global an… https://t.co/FGBo4O7y66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably hardest thing to do is moving on from the person you once thought they were your soulmate. It’s the absolu… https://t.co/MpQLsLQN8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DunOsgoode great meeting u on Twitter, enjoy my latest horror film review CROCODILE https://t.co/PAvOvbdXsq https://t.co/UJavm0MqL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_PonchoDeNigris @yayagalindomtz Jaja cabron eres mal de muchos y creído muchas veces, pero aplaudo tu decisión de… https://t.co/SRW5OO6ZzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo @espngolic @MGolicJR57 is this like a where’s Waldo because everyone seems to be looking for the Buc… https://t.co/fSFbSYMfg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlSkinsFan4Life @redskinstoday_ That would be a steal.  I’m thinking we have to do a second and a later pick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @Acosta Just watched your the70’s episode 2 about Nixon - very insightful into what’s going on now.  Gave me a strange hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidGotNews @realDonaldTrump The Dems don't like people to come to this country the legal way. Because legals are… https://t.co/AyT5u1LbWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawrenceConnol2 But of course! (Awww 🐶💗) (⤴️ hey @darth look who else likes fries!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Trump lied over 8,000 times to the American people since taking office. Why are your ethical standards… https://t.co/aHEZiJWOX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinThomas34 There was a groundhog in that hole I swear. How did that ball jump out for the birdie putt!!!!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 27 - Today's Headlines from The Boston Globe:       House votes to block Trump emergency declara… https://t.co/4VcuWXYUij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last summer y’all said Lebron was the greatest Laker in history and as a true Lakers fan I’ll never let you niggas forget it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElliottRHams @davidfrum @IlhanMN The point is that many of Ilhan Omar's fellow Somali leaders know that she should… https://t.co/Amkg4NIVaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[💦💦💦DRIP OVERLOAD 💦💦💦 $2 TUESDAYS  EASTSIDE's NEW LITUATION 🔥PISCES 🆓 ALL NITE!  VIBE 👉 DRIP SIP TIP OR DIP… https://t.co/ZuzON63mkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The liar-in-chief as seen by other countries. Not very flattering. He is a national disgrace and an international e… https://t.co/KUXbIFHKqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_stank_ I was just about to ask, sativa dominant, looks like it’s heavy kush influenced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/EhdpSo6BDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take a look at the Chicago Bears roster and rank my top 5 positions of need. Where does kicker land? 🤔  #NFL… https://t.co/PNIHmgV7s2]]></document><document><![CDATA[did i really just take a 5 hour energy shot and then chased it by chugging an entire emery drink 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rocioceja_ @alissa_ashleyy So fuckin amazing! This quality thooo 😍👏🏼 yess ma’am]]></document><document><![CDATA[mf telling me that since i’m a “young white man” it is now my duty as the next generation to “keep control” of the government]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorginaAdlam @estarianne It is horrible out there, but i think we have stumbled onto Trumps 2020 slogan "Please ignore the swastikas"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well yet again another massive snow. You know this stuff is paralyzing to things like replacing a heater outside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenToomey You did not listen to your constituents in #PA01 who are firmly against Barr and see major ethical conce… https://t.co/1235Evg5m5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ground turkey, brown rice/quinoa mix, eggs. Makes three heathy, delicious meals. Eating well doesn’t have to be har… https://t.co/ealQjDjbSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetiredDA @therealsusanq @JPVWAG @JussieSmollett @LouTelano @cleared37Joseph @POTUS There is nothing like grabbing… https://t.co/9HyQp1W9iL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyaleciin @YalitzaAparicio Exacto !! y Representa a #Mexico con mucha dignidad !!👏👏👏👌🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portageville on a 5-0 run, thanks to buckets from Bryce Rone and AJ Hicks, 40-39 Bulldogs w 5:42 left]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Art Car IPA by @saintarnold at @saintarnold — https://t.co/CaU5PHHHph]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT @StAugLions: Did you know you can view Sample Menus on our website?! https://t.co/IC46NQStEh  #StAugSeafoodFest… https://t.co/Xtz5lWvTSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyFriday y'all and see you tomorrow #BarçaRayo 🔵🔴 https://t.co/aZkg18WOuW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcrehabexpert I love the forzen shoulder thing too. However I read this at breakfast time and the bacon is pretty good. And I was hungry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEBARBER610™️    TRANSFORMATION TUESDAY 💈  Each good morning we are born again, what we do today is what matters m… https://t.co/6QZkfM71Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GdoubleT United has a soccer team? I think they should concentrate on running their airlines. Last time I flew the… https://t.co/dimF6XQFei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hoopmanx @trigonis30 @TheTraeYoung That’s very true. I wish everyone thought that way. And thank you. He’s working… https://t.co/r45XDFVygl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited about this Wednesday’s episode of Creative Addiction. Here’s a little tease... 🎧🎤🎮 https://t.co/ppqq2l24h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! Working with these dynamos everyday is awe-inspiring 😍😍😍Thank you for being you! @… https://t.co/K1jQWh61ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coaches stop by and check out @RackPerformance at the Cincinnati @GlazierClinics. #gamechanger #wgtrmsoftware… https://t.co/qYnoJdXxqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tesla’s an energy company that uses cool cars to #CTCFTR (Cross Innovation Chasm  You can be the first coming of El… https://t.co/2eM3Vtji0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because limits like fears are often just an illusion... https://t.co/Zfb3v5AlTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentHigley @JoseCuck @mizkris18 Deleted it. The TJ Moe group got me all riled up again.........]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the fire you guys were talking about. Lol what a joke https://t.co/iRkaayYrGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner with Lynn. (@ Emeril's Coastal Italian in Miramar Beach, FL) https://t.co/xGfsJbyLAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Racconto Chiunque abbia diligenza, carta e tempo sufficienti è in grado di scrivere un racconto breve ... un racco… https://t.co/kd5T4GXaUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love these one bid league conference tournaments. Everyone on the floor plays their ass off for the chance to get to the dance!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro FUCK THE POLICE fuckin harassing lil pumps goofy ass and trying to plant shit on him. Body cams show how corrup… https://t.co/zmkTNS2YXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @TiffanyDCross 👸🏾 Sista's bring it. don't mess wit her!🎤!she told him! Stop that Bullshit. When you… https://t.co/Gcp5wqcKUj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@think_again_7 @MichellePanchuk That's a stupid reason not based on scripture, it's clear once again that the quali… https://t.co/rSKYrRJ0IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[TweetI just entered to win a Fostech Fighter Lite Rifle w/ Echo Trigger from @ClassicFirearm! Valued at $1200!… https://t.co/So9xIVAzvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My song, “I Ain’t Playin” just hit 2K+ streams on #Spotify! Thank y’all for listening! 🙏🏽⚔️ https://t.co/hDxwID9w41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gurooghantaal To much silicone.....bs ....she doesn't feel shit. Anything....]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Favorite #Restaurant #OliveGarden #Too #OtherFavorite @ Olive Garden https://t.co/JT82TlS9Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I drive four hours to see the #NHLJets play the #BunchofJerks next Friday? Do I cosplay Don Cherry when I do? https://t.co/pzOsOgHmN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashSevereWx Harpeth at the Williamson County Rec put in near Mack Hatcher and Hillsboro at 7:53am today. https://t.co/nqPbxGuXqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Comedians for years have described a heckler to the audience, “So sad when cousins marry.” Indeed it is… https://t.co/pAOXSQzCBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nets rout Pistons 103-75 to move into No. 6 spot in East https://t.co/X4mUYra0r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@god hi father its me shane your child i miss you hope your fine sorry i been away s searcing  plz look after my wi… https://t.co/fb5Scqe1gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariarenepy Insomnio? No pienses mucho en mi, ya soy de ti, nunca me perderas. Te amo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Maisel @WGALStoryteller I would imagine if Ben wanted to talk, he would have already.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate women who assume every tweet is about them, I promise im not tweeting for you baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayewj9 @MOTSPodcast I haven’t seen the talent that everyone keeps talking about.  Pity and Barco have shown nothi… https://t.co/aHaEV3kXbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No importa los años que se tenga, siempre logran tener la belleza en sus manos, ellas son la esencia misma de la vi… https://t.co/rwm2eb879t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douchebagstjohn @brett_finger If I had to guess, it’s to give Booth more regular time in the E.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1. Session 7. Full body finisher. 👊🏼  _________________________________________  #ljptfitnessretreats… https://t.co/tEpZdxVM5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the McEwen family on your new #chevy #camarozl1 Thanks for joining #TeamTodd &amp;… https://t.co/hrRX8rP8YM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sonicsocial #newmusic #detroitinfoco #saturday #artists @ The Music District https://t.co/XSOjQsIl8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillOReilly Says the serial sexual predator who blindly supports a fascist who shares his worst flaws, you racist, bigoted lier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gil Rodriguez #portrait  #gilrodriguez #losreyesdelcamino #photooftheday #mty #grupero #photo #norteño … https://t.co/OIIlJrn7zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on your Franklin B Walter Scholarship, @sarahschwan207 and thank you @DeSlooverEVG for having such… https://t.co/FibPTNSQFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a real solid show by @ShooterJennings. But I’m surprised that none of them wanted to scrap. I mean me and my b… https://t.co/pubIiCJkf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I wanted to try this, Hey @peta I just hunted the bengal tigers to extinction and ate them as tiger sushi w… https://t.co/NyM2lpa22r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending time with the amazing @AishaHinds  In 2019 in LA and in 2017 at the Harriet Tubman Underground Railroad Ce… https://t.co/T3C5fWik9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was really great to see a few of my high school gym members help out last night with the 1st annual “Brightest S… https://t.co/xz0nMNHeAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hell with y’all and your meadow-on-media violence.  I stand with Kamala.  Sequined jackets are made for trying on.  @KamalaHarris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@north_of_north Have you considered that she doesn't care enough to explore this case?]]></document><document><![CDATA[03•09•19❤️   My Best friend👫... My World 🌎 ...My Fiancée💍... Words can’t describe how much you mean to me and how m… https://t.co/NB8BW0CL6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump if there’s “an emergency” either you go to the border or stay in the @whitehouse but you do not de… https://t.co/ExyCLWYzVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleygennett What you got? Winter blows. I had 2 bouts of different shit this winter. Being sick suckssssss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our problem should be our problems and we should be able to talk about things but if you avoid conversation how are… https://t.co/2w5CmoRpvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[first time executing a hand and not that bad for just the first layer of her story... #StillBeingWritten https://t.co/xzOi53VzWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Those idiots have nothing but hate. Good thing they don’t have to respond or talk excuse my French but fuck them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighters who I feel lost momentum or hype.  1. Billy Joe Saunders  2. Josh Kelly  3. Michael Conlan 4. Jerwin Ancaj… https://t.co/A0EWxxorcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back2backpod @talkhoops @BigWos @pikachuliu @nitzbluv @CornPuzzle @ValerieHoye @Jade_Hoye What’s been your worst p… https://t.co/CpMaNLSLPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of comedy for you. Christmas Family eCard!! https://t.co/oQhLa9zoYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabrieltamayof Man U y Real Madrid... incluso el West Ham tiene más peso que em Wolverhampton... por Dios!! Aparte… https://t.co/FSl6Kb8XoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part it the hurry up and wait! But we are making progress https://t.co/g7tTv47Ya0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump You’re on medication right? If California were a country it would have the 5th largest economy in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Bar Number is 48962. He violated 18… https://t.co/TXlaxEVoRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[stop giving people the power to control your smile, your worth, your attitude, and your day. don't give anyone that… https://t.co/HcBagykCIh]]></document></documents></author>