<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY ALERT:⁣ I have teamed up with some of my favorite places in Columbia to give away some amazing prizes. Why… https://t.co/YesQWd4jfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful friend is suffering her 3rd miscarriage, 4th baby lost. Please hold her in your prayers. Life is so unfair at times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @JerryLOakley1 Where the hell do these Neanderthals come from? Trump has been playing from the Hitler playbook since day one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone is still trying to figure out what to get me for my birthday: https://t.co/SFhPX3R4f1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday 💜#sundaymorning #selfie #mass #sundayservice ✝️ @ Beaumont, Texas https://t.co/kg4tCUOYpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[For sale, @dogfishbeer The Perfect Disguise Double IPA &amp; @ModernTimesBeer Dreamspeaker Hazy IPA https://t.co/4OdQjwWGIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fsuphd2009 I spy the wonderful Mock Interview Mentor Intern Abbey! Can’t wait to pick her brain about the class, looks like it was great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicsardothien This is wild. I don’t remember mine bruising much at all? I hope the implant works for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good portion of my engineering curriculum was presenting content that answered questions without making things wo… https://t.co/iJC68Nf5Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got out of bed then looked over to see this. 😂🤦‍♀️ https://t.co/vfFFcg65xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets Let's celebrate together. Coupon valid until February 19, 2019 Dont miss it only at https://t.co/Zlu6VGRh71 @… https://t.co/MbuF61bZpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning! I’m taking over thebarmethodhoboken Instagram today! Follow their account and catch their stories all… https://t.co/mpLGs5IogM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBrandonDurham @Mattheu @desiringGod Jael also didn’t HAVE to kill Sisera. There was peace between her people (the… https://t.co/x3gA0azUCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I admire the hell out of @erikajayne because what you see is what you get. Take her or leave her but you can never… https://t.co/ymAMPuoOq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Office awards day!  Thanks to my awesome clients for a great 2018 and a good start to 2019 #thankyou #lovemyclients… https://t.co/9kyCXHSfZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little pre-game warmup of deliciousness before hanging with my gal pal for the evening! https://t.co/w8KDk3Wrz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[G-dbless America! Lets be patriotic again. #patriotism #unitedstates #flag #red #white and #blue @ Old Key Lime Hou… https://t.co/jB9Pya2E6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is almost 2:30am in Seattle, and I've just discovered plush avocado toast. Even I'm not millennial enough for th… https://t.co/gleza2lHGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenny approves of our Texan 🦞boil! Nola-approved! jaybee_hughes @awduke4 @3sheetsbar #DukesInHouston @ Westside, Ho… https://t.co/XXgyCReQ9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously cool swag #TFDevSummit  @TensorFlow #MachineLearning https://t.co/xtoLy0U65C]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight I do not dance anymore a little tired but happy tomorrow I'll be at Farytail Lounge 500 west 48th st New Yo… https://t.co/sUA0RnJksr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy because I met a girl todayfrom my photoshoot who got me free tickets to the after party for the oscars ,and s… https://t.co/qV2NUAtvv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect day for a tailgate! @jackfrostracing @ Jack Frost ski area https://t.co/W3nHauABgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, on the real I have so much respect for Hannah B after the Women Tell All.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frozensooner I’d wear a suit and tie to an evening wedding (presuming it’s inside). A jacket w no tie reads more a… https://t.co/mZhhgfV6ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @LaMarsDonuts for my free dozen!!! Sooo good! They were shared and gone quickly!! #welovedoughtnuts 🍩🍩 https://t.co/z7xiXAbSDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefryanscott @FoodNetwork @TylerFlorence Already on my to do list. Protein style.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @LLinWood @washingtonpost Great! They need to be held accountable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to school finally! I miss my students and my library! #mediacenter #library #school #students #Reading]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Spare Change https://t.co/O9TEazAxuN via @YouTube I love this, so proud of my friend Amy Gruber Phillips and @BitterCrushBand 🎼🎤🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tots and ice cream (at @SONICDriveIn in Willow Grove, PA) https://t.co/EbAEz74jFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing that consistant smile on her face because she's treated like a princess by that special young man she never… https://t.co/T8xDBQJgEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the weekend with my new mask @GlamGlowMud firming treatment and terrorizing Tony #beautycare… https://t.co/Pr3ycU7h63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leah_espinoza14: “My professor just said “in yalls twenties it’s statistically said that y’all are hot messes” Sar… https://t.co/0hAKzb8PX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flight cancelled from LAS to PDX. Sent to LAX. Connection home delayed. Guess I’ll do a little reading...... https://t.co/csjem9kwDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Innes434 I can't believe there are 12 people still up at 3:23am reading this.  Goodnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best birthday party we’ve ever been to!  Happy birthday to jack’s best friend in the world. We love you charlot… https://t.co/GLYA7tF36S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Monday I always tell myself that if I can get through this week then the week after will be super easy. I hav… https://t.co/ysTJXrcIyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASPAtweets NASPA has been around for 100 years. I’ve been blessed to be a part of it for 24 years. My roots run d… https://t.co/jcrMP7CSpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If I had one ask of @DCPSChancellor it would be rebuild Shaw Middle School!” @JackEvansWard2 https://t.co/tGxANh6zTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmysSeafood @JessicaDuckWife @GitRDoneLarry @TedNugent @toddchrisley]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't you think you should wait for Mueller to SAY no collusion? He hasn't yet. Or are you manipulating the Senate'… https://t.co/v3Cu8Uig8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[TK wins it in OT and the reaction is priceless #DETvsPHI https://t.co/FOnVAUOKp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Ways to Incorporate Sublimated T-shirts in Your Christmas Fashion https://t.co/CUHmRpUm6V #ChristmasFashion… https://t.co/YMhNHRpizJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDilanianNBC @NBCNews That's okay - there will be more than one hero who makes sure we do see it in all its ugly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde que te conocí no hay nada más que las ganas de estar y volver a empezar 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hunk, Angus, gets his bi-weekly light sessions for Degenerative Myelopathy and autoimmune. We are working to 🛑… https://t.co/AicZiFBBYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a friend/family/colleague who copes with chronic illness, this is an important read. Resonates with thi… https://t.co/KTQG0LulKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call Congress and tell them to give children and families the valentine of #GunSafety! Pass… https://t.co/X1yQEioUN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re logging the Flyers/Lightning game for work and the announcers start talking about all of the former Ran… https://t.co/1f5Pqbcz5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PASenateGOP @JakeCorman @GovernorTomWolf You all are terrible: https://t.co/HxoeUKL60A]]></document><document><![CDATA[only I would have the luck to get pulled over going 2 mph over the speed limit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hayden ready to dive into a Holy Cow breakfast @ Shellie's Country Cafe WEST https://t.co/06gcGPad67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibsInAmerica @realDonaldTrump SERIOUSLY???? 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤮🤢🤮🤢🤮GROW UP !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We can take care of people without screwing up the market system.”  @WarrenBuffett on @CNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday mi amor💙and I just wanna thank you for being you and making me so happy these pass years. TE AMO MI… https://t.co/tO30EJw8US]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TariffMYtaxCUT @cspanwj @RepThompson What about the ones you don't know about Hank😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyFnDanger Sure, I’ve done that as well. I should’ve clarified my question because I’m specifically referencing… https://t.co/WOxuCtuEDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder IT CAME FROM WITHIN 🙄🙄....Greed and power has brought down many.  All tyranny needs to gain a foothold is f… https://t.co/qFRrccvIo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solo quiero a mis amigos mas importantes el sábado y el día de mi cumpleaños jiji😊💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Betticaa @GeorgeArtwell @ingridcaroly @marielamolina @arboldepaz @Norys_Acosta_C @gabyfengs @TachiraFuerte… https://t.co/svNRNpdfKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chachess what happened to all my friends I talked too every night we was talking]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY I'm doing the job I got post secondary education for!! It's been two damn years but damn does it feel so ri… https://t.co/nSC2IBVZsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great resource for our state leaders! 50-State Comparison: K-12 School Safety https://t.co/xuoVdMfb9t via @EdCommission #NASPadvocates]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bae new do HANDSOME ♥️❤️♥️❤️😇😇❤️♥️❤️♥️ @ D'joel Barber Shop https://t.co/hKBoruvKij]]></document><document><![CDATA[i ended up being really judgmental bc i thought there was a right way to do things and ended up being really bitter… https://t.co/k1jmapqGKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty cool @stormytaylor The Manns in the #MTown #MadeasFarewellTour tonite @myV101 @CityOfMemphis @MemphisFlyer… https://t.co/9npUHbXxw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaahidJohnspoon @nerdist Interesting. What is the proposed evolutionary driver for this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m beyond thankful for this guy that made my Valentine’s Day and every day the best🥰 https://t.co/tRazDqGIop]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have arrived. In Orlando and ready to meet folks. #customerengagment #grateful for this opportunity!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulieD55 @RichardWMcclur1 I'M DISAPPOINTED IN A LOT OF ACTORS I THOUGHT I LIKED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Glad that you are speaking out again. What was the catalyst?     #freeyourselffromthemouse  #lovemymoviestar xoxoxo 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick woke me up by FaceTiming me like an hour ago. Which makes me super happy. But Dobby woke up too. And she’s bee… https://t.co/3DI9DTz0nD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheri_lynn95252 @Bozesgirl66 @CheekyAussieGuy @sweet___ash @melissamorris50 @CodiePrevostUK @ValentinoAndy77… https://t.co/LqYDY73OVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My horoscope lately has been too accurate and spot on. 1. It’s wild. 2. It’s getting my hopes up fr fr.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLaLaLaToya If you put your thumb over the top edge, he looks just fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my Uber told me I was beautiful and I told him I like McDonald’s and he’s taking me to McDonald’s I win]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful for the opportunity and grateful for the experience! #flyhawks 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly would feel bad for james if we have a girl. could you imagine dealing with me and a layla jr 😂😭🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mchooyah She just wants to get to a safe place, now, She had no idea she was already in one...America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gngerbrdgrl She cannot even stand alone when making a two sentence statement. I think she is so insecure and appea… https://t.co/CeC3yh6ivx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a little reminder.💗🙏🏼😊 #MondayMorning #MondayMotivation https://t.co/wmiLfv9Bec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doin it for the gram   remedytampa #tampa 🥂👯‍♀️🎉😋🥗🙌🏻😎🍷🍾🍸#lifeisgood #tampa #native #friday #friyay @ Remedy https://t.co/FCRF2mZvSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of us waiting for @LifeInPiecesCBS to come back https://t.co/PE82i9dkp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple hours ago I randomly decided I wanted to watch Grease, and I just got home and found out it's currently on TV 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Congrats to you both, you make a wonderful couple🌸💙🌼🧡🌺💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamg1 @saintdorian @ForecasterEnten You’re using Bernie Bro. A term originated to degrade and devalue supporte… https://t.co/fNQZYuewJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LevyWash @WRALJeff @chouchoutv Aw thank you!! And thanks for watching!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccatmpt @suziday123 @JWinery @CaraMiaSG @TheWiningHour @winegal57 @DemiCassiani @winetraveleats @GrnLakeGirl… https://t.co/L6uqOHE9Rs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promised myself along time ago that if I was going to write, I'd write nothing but the truth. Even if it meant me… https://t.co/amS51dd8uI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyWainSmith You’re funny. We’re all birds of a feather. You and I are still trying to fly but we will get there! Together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler I used to “shoot a basket” with them!! https://t.co/diWL9F3imG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @yashar Unless you live in cattle country, they never outgrow it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bes way to support #InternationalWomensDay! Thank you RI House members!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4months Siberian Husky White with blue eyes.  Wearing blue harness. https://t.co/QHwq6Elsoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karl Lagerfeld, legendary Chanel fashion designer, has died, aged 85. https://t.co/Ou3LrwPW4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shareblue @aussierep1 @snipy Of course they are. Do you really think Mr. I'm special would ask for permission?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scuttlebutt: @PhillipsSeafood is coming back to the district...in Logan Circle? ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ https://t.co/z1Lbq6YIiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moseley_carla @canadiandaws83 @alisoninsco @Mommandem @CunningSq16 @ShapesBlue @DoloresManley4 @ShaunaPembroke… https://t.co/VYo9WVnIIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dump_trump_asap @JohnBrennan @warwickann Brennen has consistently attacked the President, he is a deep state crimi… https://t.co/i63d45JMhy]]></document></documents></author>