<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[An enticing DC #alley. #alleyways @ Northwest Washington, Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/xMmwbEQnGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We Don’t Got Bands For Hoes But We All Got Some Bands To Throw” -Ty Baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when my mom sends me pictures of my baby. Love you tazzy ❤️❤️ #thosepaws https://t.co/GnNKcNsnzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wilberg84 It's been out there.  Every player rumoured to be on the trade block is going to the Hsbs according to someone....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to find someone who’s constantly down to travel for dope house music events like Night Bass anniversary shows… https://t.co/ERyH0anktC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tradestreetpost @RichDevitaIII @BaconDwayne1000 @Devonte4Graham @hornets That’s just wrong. I mean it’s just flat wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elmira #cnoy19 surpassed initial fundraising goal with 10 days left to go! What a generous community we live in! I'… https://t.co/YA1Qm3gP8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s getting more fun watching @MalickViews on the field. https://t.co/JCWG71cNn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are a criminal Donny. #  The most compromised president ever ‘n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MedicalFisher @elonmusk @Tesla I don’t own a Tesla and haven’t ordered one yet, this thread is pretty much until I get one]]></document><document><![CDATA[tfw u try paying rent in brainpower but ur landlord requires money instead :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a cream party!! Should be a juicy time pull up on us one time 💦 every first and third thursday. 🤙🏼 https://t.co/4M4ss9hwri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_BM21_ You got that parrot on your side you’re good. Marry mush is money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast at Charlie Parker’s diner in Springfield,Illinois... homemade  hash and black coffee.. yes!… https://t.co/PB4cKuEdNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about it:  @YFBurnna_cmh (Duke Williams) @dkmetcalf14 (DK Metcalf) @zayjones11 (Zay Jones) @iamRobertFoster (… https://t.co/ATOUZpRA2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilikevitamins @ed_waddell1 @MikeTokes @leach_deanna @realDonaldTrump Yeayeayea...burp.. Same story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_R_607 Been saying this for a while now. Everyone is at fault that this deteriorated the way it did. Rooney, Toml… https://t.co/BOrrblFVvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peace_Janise @realDonaldTrump I live in ny for a long time this specimen is a con and a cheap high trust me you li… https://t.co/bbzpXMbLDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great suggestion to pursue perjury @RudyGiuliani! House Dems should call #DonJr and #ErikPrince among others who ap… https://t.co/by2aByVlRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Shedd, voice for the EMCs on sustainability, coming up at 8.34am on @WGAUradio and you can listen live at… https://t.co/KOtUVtzuud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jahme10 @kayla19981 No sir, I quit for 2 months but then lost my juul I’m literally left with 1 cigarette left, I’… https://t.co/DUKk8cWWAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaEats @VisitSanya @MadHattersNYC @always5star @suziday123 @FoodTravelist @magee333 @MyVirtualVaca… https://t.co/mRDmxMiuAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang clever. When this dog tried to act like she could pull of this Cheeto dress. | The... #funniness #chuckle… https://t.co/A4MkU4XpfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[All your crimes are in search of an indictment! And maybe a @GOP with a backbone and a belief in the rule of law!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The details of this case never added up from the beginning. Now here we are. A lot of people went way out on skinny… https://t.co/buYU4gE7QK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Fat Tuesday!!!! We are making a King Cake this morning.  @shortnorthcake makes some delicious ones.… https://t.co/vXa7vAdtNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself YOU SIR ARE AN AMAZING ARTIST! #i have enjoyed soooooo much the roles you have played Luke and Joker… https://t.co/cKgqezydwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__DavidJoseph @realmikeaguilar @petersongeorged @marcorubio @scottwongDC Pssst....affirmative action goals are a thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@12thEndSports What was the peak webcast viewership for the Women’s Final? #askTESN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationalsPost @Bharper3407 Well done. No reason to burn anything. I have 3 jersey's, all the bobbleheads, multiple… https://t.co/qED3WbstUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the Morning of Premieres goes Out of this World first get blast off with Dela Duck in the New #DuckTales Speci… https://t.co/3NTIOy5QPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is it going to take for the #Pacers to get some respect from people outside of Indiana?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRobe21241883 @abellino @hwestonbull_hhh @RevJeanMDougla1 @JonDoc80 @DineshDSouza @BarackObama Kind of like his presidency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleased that I had an opportunity to thank @scottwilkca for supporting #sb126 in the Senate Education Committee 🍎 H… https://t.co/2m0dAcmnRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy fucking walnuts - Drinking a Cognac Barrel Aged Unrepentant Transgression  by @angrychairbeer @ Angry Chair Br… https://t.co/dXIDtSzfQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Failed tf out my bios exam    So I skipped the class today ?    What ?  that doesn’t make sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Doug Schoen, President Trump is the most pro Israel President EVER!!! Pull your head out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perhaps I’m especially sensitive to bad treatment of patients with #PancreaticCancer because of my mother-in-law, b… https://t.co/vkgj0ZsKFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mara Ebert tells me the Valsoia #gelato story at #ExpoWest2019 #vegan #dairyfree #frozen #dessert #retail #grocery… https://t.co/4nX8XNB9d3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aagreene87 He’s in love with snow. Could t find a happier dog when it’s cold and snowy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas,   Even if you didn’t have an earthly male model to look to growing up or even now, God has provided the blu… https://t.co/0eVOxDrwXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently paid a visit to the birthday boy on Wall Street. Happy Washington’s Birthday! #PresidentsDay https://t.co/KY9dQ2SRHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConsumersEnergy I would like to know what is going on. I called about my power being out at 1am. I have a newborn… https://t.co/zG622gbASS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pintswithjack @GreekCatholicSD @davidlewisbates https://t.co/yHMDUvrciR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jfromtheblock_ @julieejordann You should try so single and so uninterested even though you'd like to be intereste… https://t.co/XOygCEko9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're just a racist like the orange one. Vets don't treat veterans that way. He's going to try and privatize the V… https://t.co/p9jltuvr3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking applications for a new roommate. @timmyhrits https://t.co/ZgrODbrN7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan Peterson on the ABC Feb-25-2019 https://t.co/V9zwL60jwD via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badababa @danceiskeyyaho1 @beinlibertarian @AOC Interestingly enough I was having a back-and-forth with Talib Kwel… https://t.co/aK7E5BH840]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom You should watch his unhinged riff that he was only being “sarcastic” about telling Russia to find Hi… https://t.co/cyHpAtxNdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReBourneAgain so calling it now gable roode cause a DQ cause we need to see gable roode vs team glorious kyep agai… https://t.co/OSJTn0p7zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradySchro That is unreal. Not just the salary equivalent, but the difference between the WAR 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s something therapeutic about playing with your dog at the park 🐕 🥰🙏🏼 Anyone else have a fur buddy to hang wi… https://t.co/heiKWUKUJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC Given that all the big “shorter show” reforms have been rolled back (except for not having a host lo… https://t.co/ibUeYINX42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AwsomeDude1125 @defothebunt @NOTSportsCenter Mr cool internet man acts cool by not caring about people, you’re a t… https://t.co/cx60dDKU8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankFigliuzzi1 @MSNBC @DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace FF, once our house is cleaned of Putin's assets, I hope you'll… https://t.co/juLJeg7JKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billslifer716 @jorychaney08 @joshfann43 @ScottyLovesCLE @ProFootballTalk "When on the field" which is when?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally went to Tempesta Market and tried the Dante. It’s legit https://t.co/pRTSX7Kc1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the cashier working the SIM card stand at the airport noticed that I’ve been staring at her from across… https://t.co/Dl89ltSwDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this news @ELLEmagazine ? STOP reporting mean shit. It’s so bogus, makes me sad. I’m canceling my subscripti… https://t.co/0faop6cyJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse 5-year old.@realDonaldTrump #DonaldTrump #CPAC2019 #CPAC #DonaldTrumpIsMentallyIll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanpaca no dejes el humor del programa en manos de esos audios  q estan pa mover la agujita. Dale vida a las… https://t.co/64dEIlYKB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Expectations! @ #walelm looks like this bright eyed Walker Star is expecting many Valentine's to fill her h… https://t.co/ePfgtLWlXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was excited to co-present a CLE on Trial Practice with three really impressive Tampa family law attorneys. @ Stet… https://t.co/GuTfO16K7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EAMaddenMobile Any chance that we get the opportunity to buy playoff tokens or at least blitz tokens in marketplac… https://t.co/ck11klbZYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harnesstimes LOL that's a good one.. A good. Morning line used to really be a art It's not very accurate anymore e… https://t.co/dwSNbjH1gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiaJaxWWE Hi Nia good luck at wrestlemania your still a beautiful lady despite you being a heel &amp; what they say about you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga - congrats on your Oscar... Shallow is a beautiful song! #googooforgaga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom Joe, what about people who were misled? Were enticed when the institution has firm knowledge that the… https://t.co/3HTBjQz1Hf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnsonemilyp @jbf1755 Taking it out of the particular and the personal -- If historical content knowledge among e… https://t.co/ZMCmhv6uWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PigOsphere @DTech74 @HammerBowling Yeah the deeper I can get in the lane the more comfortable I am, with this pin… https://t.co/mac5Icci2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noeljesse Perhaps the state could buy a copy of #wretchedsaints  for everyone in the state. (10% of the book sales… https://t.co/37zty3x8yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thevickiejay I wa half sleep when I replied to your tweet lol. Glad you de-coded the message lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vandyktra As it is, I see this idea that science has more answers rather than give any credit to revelation or eth… https://t.co/NjUVlrI8ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson singing Never Enough live is incredible. I had so many damn feels! #MeaningOfLifeTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never take nights sleeping next to ur girl comfortable for granted cause some day it could be 12am and ur in a bion… https://t.co/7smDIM8z4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @BernardGoldberg you are right about Brian Stelter attacking fnc where is your op ed about Fnc attac… https://t.co/P558mys9Zr]]></document><document><![CDATA[&lt;GASP!!!&gt; Not MARIJUANA!   If there is any group of people in this world that need to take a toke, it’s the @GOP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyTrask Agree. I struggle to see who this benefits across the board while still knowing that sources are often us… https://t.co/Erg1MZirFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney ~ Dumbo  World Premiere  Hollywood, California #DisneyDumbo https://t.co/pdLkbeJ5Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little comedy segment we filmed last summer  for kwikset  home alarms .. and got yesterday !!this was a fun shoot .… https://t.co/G6mKhNIgqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that you can’t use your Apple Pay balance to pay for digital purchases through Apple is a little silly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraCrowley4 @JordanHerrera_9 I like this one better than Kiki though. Caris. Cara is .... success is ... Cara. Ca… https://t.co/hwOHB385Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Girls1Peli 1,000 percent. Same can be said about a linebacker general at 10. 1,000 percent agree with you though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brendan you are right it is the Post. They are still waiting for the Jets to beat the Pats. 7 out of 8 sounds like… https://t.co/J5JCxOXyTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visualizing success.. ooh it look  good 🤑🤑 @ The Scott Resort &amp; Spa https://t.co/lxA4XAPQI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santana - Maria Maria ft. The Product G&amp;B (Official Video) https://t.co/CPzOASCYTP via @HaileeSteinfeld]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could house both space agencies and a Hilton space hotel. https://t.co/RPkODXZKtJ via @futurism #Space]]></document><document><![CDATA[Image grown women stop acting like they are in high school drama again 🤷🏽‍♀️🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always show sportsmanship! Play within the rules of the game. Treat opponents with respect. Don’t talk to the offic… https://t.co/2BQgisx7Cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmrider Maybe a bit long, but perhaps the best story Stuart McLean ever told. https://t.co/udPPITC3Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Haysville VFW Post 6957 in Haysville, KS https://t.co/LovL8smwRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my home town, Spokane, WA. for the Gonzaga BYU Game. GO ZAGS!!! https://t.co/LcNKSGtawz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mars_Hill_WX @JaxnPoliceDept 👍👍👍  Our police department doesn’t know this. So how can they justify writing tickets… https://t.co/faG2jSZgNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just be honest, there's a certain point to how much I can take before I just dip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Moss How Hamas Sends Boys to Their Deaths – The Case of Saadi Abu Salah, 16 https://t.co/qm2Ery9hq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eenie meenie miney mo&gt; ‘Productive’ talks resume for Raiders’ 2019 return to #NFL @OAColiseum #Raiders… https://t.co/VyAmRVAXDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rikus hair gives you an indication of what realm they are in for further elaboration read the realm of sleep theory https://t.co/PWom2jKJ9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before America built the interstate highway system, trains linked cities to rural towns.   Thay can again. https://t.co/K5OOIjON6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rafaeltheartist #explore #rafaeltheartis1 #hiphop #rap #houstonhiphop #Houstonrapper #indieartist #Alief #viral… https://t.co/7nBSiZBxks]]></document></documents></author>