<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@taniagroe @StormHour @ThePhotoHour @StormHourMark Que impresionante 😍😍 ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I love seeing my friends from high school winning!!!! Makes me so proud!!❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arie &amp; Lauren, Jason &amp; Molly, Sean &amp; Catherine. Also way more from bachelorette lol but go off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VicCervantes3 @Butterfly6114 @Thedrsweetie @DevinnaMargot @TroyAle52891286 @Keeepitred @crashsandbar… https://t.co/LjKNIpiEzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This article is 3 years old?  B&amp;N to Sell Self-Published Books In Stores https://t.co/Z6RVyKRU8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 It is a necessary question if we have older candidates to say who would be their VP. I asked a Bernie… https://t.co/X1cgM9MQYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[this man was so fine to me then I found out he had leg tats and I’m like wow!!!!!!! My standards are on the floor b… https://t.co/6pSnSdr22t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_du_Plessis @Flowerdarby @EDUCAUSELI @tihighered I just listened that yesterday. Can't wait to dig into her book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anneoakli @BillKristol Already eat less meat. Already consider the flying less. But don’t go east just to see kids… https://t.co/bf4u5UxVp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help my friend Jenn. She had been through so much in her life, but had never let any of it keep her down. Sh… https://t.co/K14FsIhbfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go to https://t.co/sfh0skrmAZ to start or join a MFOL chapter in your community or your school!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @JoelleFoster12 Here’s another one. Enjoy 😉  https://t.co/XsvIRSkzHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Dworet told his dad he was ready to commit to @UIndy as soon as he arrived for his recruiting visit. He never… https://t.co/eDFG3sSZKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great thread on what makes the @uwmhcid so special. Can’t believe winter quarter is almost over!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI much of #Venezuela, including Caracas, lost power yesterday and is still without it.The #Guri Dam mentioned b… https://t.co/YWzBgLOuVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Yes he is a convicted felon and a liar..shame he threw his life away for tRump who paid him to do those thjngs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@10GYM can’t seem to get into contact with anyone regarding my next billing cycle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’m doing this 7 day cleanse. I’m already down 3 lbs and it’s only day 3👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump Well I don’t know what you would call a national emergency if it isn’t drugs, human tr… https://t.co/NqtTRdEPji]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really see black twitter fucking with this leaving neverland documentary... 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsKarrieT @RepDebDingell It's a freaking resolution. They dont have specific plans in that thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys Class 3 District 9 4th game -  final California Pintos  62 North Callaway Thunderbirds 65 https://t.co/uoF4LvgAG0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks the start of the #houstonlivestockshowandrodeo where Houston becomes what most outsiders think it is ev… https://t.co/J0EmJIWxhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmchairExpPod @DrPhil I loved this episode with Dr. Phil! An idea for a future Expert on Expert is learning about… https://t.co/XM4Uy18qCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMek Then the rest of us should be ashamed and get lobbying instead of wasting our time here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scholars from @EastEpo get ready to share their learning with the Beechwood community #NewCityCafe @DrNelms… https://t.co/k5SPOUVzgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammi_inCO @LobsterBFFs1 @whitegirlsmooth @BuckeyeCuti @birdtracs @Katie_Elaine012 @lizheileman @tnormandeau22… https://t.co/gI4dIkfMA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm here for the #KindredSpirits party. @amybruni @AdamJBerry @chipcoffey https://t.co/nSe6NgoB5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexFast8 @PitcherList Yeah I’m a huge huge Os fan but it’ll be a long year but yes I’m excited about our future for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great takeaway from the @LinkedIn #socialmediamanager guide. https://t.co/iJmOe4WDOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Franklin Central Basketball Senior Night 2019 https://t.co/8Stb0Em2JM via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brew_emily Sadly, my makeup bag LIVES in my car. I don’t even have any in my house.  🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rather poorly placed promoted tweet/ad down there fam 😬 https://t.co/h7RWvRpkNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have u ever got high and watched how it’s made while eating pineapple salad with lime flavored chips?   10/10 would recommend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is not normal @NRA. Truly beginning to think NRA stands for the National Russian Association.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this amusing there's something wrong with you. By popular request - teacher memes in poster-quali… https://t.co/Reqds1T9fs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJPresence I listen to it to get hype when I’m getting ready to go out]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 I Can't Help It by @michaeljackson @OfficialAlBSure #AOMM on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/YGddpfBAPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with measles outbreaks across the US, at least 20 states have proposed anti-vaccination bills  https://t.co/U32oKyY3Z5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K1TTYMEAN are you upset that I deleted the tweet? I honestly did not think of my tweet as a rape joke. I genuinely… https://t.co/UiopXOhNdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantopping66 @Tombstone1954 @OrenIShiKiddo @America_Working @pokergod12345 @AnnBroo32097973 @AnnaPinyon @NJ_2_FL… https://t.co/JqXRO1E3ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSugarLily @1RealLori @Bmw2163Heart @tillmantweets @busylizzie48 @ukwildcatfan191 @HarrellRyan1 @SpaceForce1prh… https://t.co/C5pNiVvANR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas be thinking they got you before they actually got you #dontgetcomfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was wondering what tf annoying sound I was hearing then realized it was just me breathing 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scenes from Opening Night of GUADALUPE IN THE GUEST ROOM at @WTTheatre 🎭✨ #GuadalupeWTT #aceshotthat  #theatre… https://t.co/qyaRljFd37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_akalaJ The time I was accused of stealing out the pod market because dippers drink machine was down and I went to the pod to use theirs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCASR @NYCACC @Pets4VetsNYCLI @ConcernedVets @USWomenVeterans @VetsAboutFace @NavyVets Please pull this girl n gi… https://t.co/xgnn8TFVxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RightWingWatch Oh dear. I always thought LaCrosse, WI was god’s country]]></document><document><![CDATA[A useful exercise for leaders: Take 10 minutes at workday’s end to reflect on how you reacted to new ideas and crit… https://t.co/4u3pKlRPRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thestate Didn't she already do that working for Trump, sorry she said minority not majority. Pushing bad ideology… https://t.co/aZeY5DIYky]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honesty was such in a bad place two years ago. I mean I could be in a better now but I’m grateful for all the peo… https://t.co/5rPMvGy7hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see some@of my favorite dudes at one of my favorite fests again with some of my best friends. Here’s to… https://t.co/5nKLnyyT1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[conversations wit self @ this hour is just ending in a whole lot of https://t.co/IYylBholm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I watch the entire part 2 of #leavingneverland without realizing I completely skipped part 1? 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing #summertime 🌞 #SummerVibes #summeriscoming https://t.co/YBcv57Wzel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @RealJamesWoods @steph93065 Not soon enough. So sad - large gathering of goofy people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johan1892E Almost trolled Taylor Swift. I wanted to tell her and Luke Bryan I had drank my weight in alcohol and I… https://t.co/9xpOLnv2Bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 @Nationalist_KAG Sounds like the bum is use to court!  I hope he gets the book]]></document><document><![CDATA[#22 Brianna Morales, #25 Robyn Quintana and #44 Bea Tabano 🖤💛 https://t.co/A5Crgv0vEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[قالوا ليش تحبيها دام نھايتكم فراق  قلت ليش نعيش دام نھايتنا قبر  #انشهد]]></document><document><![CDATA[Claim your power right now. It doesn't have to be tomorrow or five days from now. Claim it right now. I will be here waiting...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RenabRN70 @MechiBoettger Thank you it truly is the worst pain I have encountered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_echavez555 @CerritosPride @loo_lewis @N_Vega_Guadian @IamJosephL @KathyValladare8 @franserranomss @ssg_somath… https://t.co/Zij9PYv7fC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ride may have SUCKED today, but oh my god I missed Olivia and Eli is precious 💓💓 https://t.co/fN8fqk8TI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dvlwoman30 @RyanNolan79 @Sportsnet Wasn’t a challenge just a question - I’m always for the players decision, this… https://t.co/KW1sImbxOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les Québécois ont changé pour bien pire.En quoi les Québécois ont amélioré leur qualité de vie?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DTNSocial @IngrahamAngle American's need to want a job!  I'm sure sum do but their many that don't and live off ou… https://t.co/ZdHi8sOwiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @shirfire218 I have not seen this episode since it aired in 1970. I had to rewind the clip several t… https://t.co/LClp2ebkFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really @STARZ?! You're going to do pop-up ads in the middle of a movie?! WTF is wrong with you?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *should be studying* Me: *watching YouTube video “Are you difficult to love?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less Sam Scheidt, More Anna Bon. #InternationalWomensDay #ClassicalRadio https://t.co/K9KGUGnLl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the day! @kingcanfilmfest is the world’s largest showcase of 🇨🇦 feature films. Thank you to the great team… https://t.co/wuQlpD9vUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdothsay @I_Like_Doggos76 You don’t have to insult me to be a superior person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RenzaS @KarenFAddington @A_Sweet_Life *blush* but for real, I just reread it and gosh, I wish people would embrace this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy people ... dancing ...  @IMKristenBell heard you had fun here #partyspot @ The Wilson NYC https://t.co/yhl8K0h2gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TanyaDawnH @realDonaldTrump That means no politicians will be shot. None of them support open borders. That’s just… https://t.co/lBFZwhp3KS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please make an #app for people who are going home drunk from the club so they can stop wasting #uber dr… https://t.co/UDcZUVT6Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule And pray that he quietly leaves if he is defeated. My fear is that he’ll deem the election invalid… https://t.co/4BS11El23U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DohertyShannen I AM SO SAD TOO! LUKE WAS A GREAT MAN! A WONDERFUL FATHER AND FRIEND! MY HERT GOES OUT TO HIS FAMILY AND HIS CASTMATES]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 hilarious soccer memes Hahahahahahahahhahaah #humor #lol #smirk #playful https://t.co/NDuBgryYlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple of questions for any lawyerly types out there. 1) If I lied to my insurance company and tell them I have dam… https://t.co/6Oz3RLFqpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fast movement and more quick touches for Chiara in last week’s session-thanks Empowefutsal!    ⚽️.  Follow her jour… https://t.co/mFk275k4FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win a 50-Inch TCL 4K HDR TV from @Techlicious and @adammesh! You should enter, too! https://t.co/0Uz7n2Hdmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never been big into superhero movies but i cant wait to see captain marvel tonight 😍💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing the last Madea movie with this bunch! #madeafarewelltour2019 #madea #madeafamilyfuneral @ AMC Theatres… https://t.co/zpevcL3a6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leonela_o3 @YouTube @NicolasMaduro Es necesario agotar todos los canales de la democracia. El proceso debe llevars… https://t.co/u8KJnn4VtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mechanical royalties, what are they?! Full video link in bio!  ・・・ You've GOT to know your business!! The Hay Law G… https://t.co/OCjJ7Ha0A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AditiJuneja3 @OhNoSheTwitnt Trump is the best example of what happens to someone who does not read. He can’t write… https://t.co/22IxKhISLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ew why won’t Bernie and Clinton just give up? It’s not meant to be....for them to ruin this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nanibearz @topchef_cici @BlasianSade @princess_mwoods @Amber_Janessa @damnrico @cc_shaakira @trvpfuiishawdy @ashyaspade 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SequoiaTreee @kitcso @Solmemes1 @greggutfeld I never Said that Jesus is white?! Where are you coming from?!  He is… https://t.co/MAugCQGeqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[from my bedroom I can smell the bodega downstairs making sandwiches at midnight :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teoami I can almost guarantee you’ll be fine as long as it’s not over a bone or somewhere sensitive. Tattoos feel… https://t.co/nd6ayaYxq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF YOU SEEKING REAL PEACE .contact Divine One https://t.co/lKlVwsuK87 https://t.co/Q41X9m8CvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women really be bent ALLLLLLLLLL the way outta shape when you call them “sir” 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My gps is having me take PCH to Long Beach and I’m so ok with this drive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayleynthecomet @pienar We did this in so many classrooms in my high school]]></document><document><![CDATA[yall can blame yourselves for no snow days since u all think climate change aint real]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muchas felicitaciones a mi querido @DavidSummersHG  por  su cumpleaños 🎂 🎂🎂🎂🎂🎂🎂 @estamoslocosmty  que te la pases G… https://t.co/4PnyiPqvtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do people drink coffee on an empty stomach—I want to jump out of my skin and kinda throw up]]></document></documents></author>