<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow This is sickening we cave and give in to these f****** Muslims everyday they're systematically des… https://t.co/zpGsJxY7Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Josh for your kind words.  I’m so proud of our team and all they accomplished this season.  We appreciate al… https://t.co/KnLoDFWX4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump and you are harassing, intimidating and lying to witnesses in order to obstruct j… https://t.co/QsnP7UVliR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Light, a bit bitter, not overwhelming. - Drinking a Samurai Shag by @foragerbrewery at @ForagerBrewery  — https://t.co/tRvpZAVGkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realestate residential and commercial 2018 update and 2019 forecast by #nar National Association of Realtors https://t.co/lX6LVR26pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch Live on @nbcwashington President Trump set to meet Kim Jong Un in Hanoi for their second summit:]]></document><document><![CDATA[To live is to suffer but to survive is to find meaning in ones suffering- Fahrenheit 451]]></document><document><![CDATA[This short thread. 👇  (She and I have been to Israel together. So much good there, but also much wrong. The wrongne… https://t.co/X1cf6iOLRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smallworld101k @CrytzerFry @CrawliesWithCri @cyntada Cats should be indoor. Not on a soapbox. But they should.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TostadorSean @mikeprz81 "Jesus Jones mega sets all weekend long! Right here, right now, only on WXRT"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the letter from #sunbiz redCoffee Games is now official! New game studio in the town! @PalmCoastFL #businessNews #gamedev #Official]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m president failure to use a turn signal will be a capital offense administered on the spot. https://t.co/NRxTHicqkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/PLCgoxMEfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCannibalsBand Not NC based but find a way to connect to @andyfrasco IMHO That would be a sick show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@215Wrestling Risky but its wouldnt be something hes not familiar with. Like he  said its sports entertainment it's… https://t.co/5PG34ExB98]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB UNLOADS ON ROETHLISBERGER  “Bro, you threw the s--- to the D-lineman! What the f---? I'm over here wide open! Yo… https://t.co/UIsLzIcGu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats SSCSU_SWIMDIVE   NSIC Women’s Conference Champs!  Great performance!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul So true. For years I drank Kentucky Bourbon.  Your foolishness convinced me, I can’t possibly stomach any… https://t.co/sZAxB2i1Uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For my birthday I want an all-inclusive trip to Napa Valley to go wine tasting 🍇]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be an adventure #EarlyRunInNashville https://t.co/kmHwPlse32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pastrami &amp; Beer - Drinking a Big Wave Golden Ale by @KonaBrewingCo at @togossandwiches  — https://t.co/WNs71revqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard @amandlastenberg shout out @angiecthomas on the @Oscars2019Live_ red carpet and I thought y’all should k… https://t.co/pmLXVuazu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My car got broken into and half my creative  tools were taken, but at least the glass looks like a galaxy when all… https://t.co/AJaVzey5nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[For #WorldWildlifeDay2019 this year's theme is 'life below water', find out how much you know of animals worldwide… https://t.co/7Ja8mQ68MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @aplebeianlife @LindseyGrahamSC Lindsey you are so FOS! youre  panicking. Ha ha ha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattGinellaGC taking a group (4-6) of my old college teammates to Austin next month. Recommendations 4 courses, lo… https://t.co/RgnUA5FeNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bntCSGO @HusKerrs @dizzfila Your hundred of hours against my hundreds of hours means what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaactregzz @LMiguelSalvador @Club_Queretaro @santiago4kd @ABCNoticiasMX Y tu de presidente de las Pizzas de Panem. Ya se armó jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA @NBAonTNT @NBATV @ESPNNBA #NBAdunkContest 💤 💤 💤  How about you bring in professional dunkers! Simply having a… https://t.co/c8pIOWzJVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasmineemilktea happy Valentine's day, I love you chula 😍❤️💕😘🥰😋🧡💙💛💗💘💞❤️💚🖤💕💝💖💓💜💌💌🧡🧡🧡❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dameshek If one bad call was all it took, that house of cards was falling regardless, sooner or later]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VelvetSessions (@ Velvet Bar in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/qTugAz4zxs https://t.co/Xr1No2pXpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new C++ addon for Node.js to push it beyond its natural HTTP limits https://t.co/EswFgnars1  @nodejs #nodejs #javascript #webdev #dev]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulbrindis @mexicanpartz saludos muchachos desde Vancouver WA. Un saludo a mi esposa Maria Sanchez y un saludo a… https://t.co/EC6musD9FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondHoggers @realFRG @theteenager7 Culichi... You better cash big man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elyria's Ben Doehr loses 8-1 to Oregon Clay's Josh Nagy -- ranked No. 13 in the state -- in his 182 first-round match. #LoCoMats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motoridersd Hudson always loved carrots, celery, cabbage. But he would delicately set a piece of zucchini on the g… https://t.co/Kf0O72mSsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[“.. this is Israel, where three gruff generals who lead a hitherto non-existent party ..are the dream team on which… https://t.co/zphQZC8Lfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHATUPRG killed this new “Free” track! This is my new jam for a while! Oooooof🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still believe if CP3 was healthy last year, the Houston Rockets would’ve beaten the Warriors to win the champions… https://t.co/eALSOrF4Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, it certainly looks good! Gonna let is cool and we’ll see in the morning if it’s worth it. #alwaysimproving… https://t.co/MWs8gGbik2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Rees_Mogg We know who you look out for, you and your vicious rich friends, but we are looking out for our ki… https://t.co/job2qZeg1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlowesf makes a pretty damn good burger 🍔🍔 #HungryRealtor #SF #RealEstate @ Marlowe https://t.co/zdoqJ7GqHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you let work stress ruin your 3 day weekend and lose sleep and wake up in a cold sweat and get to work 1.5 hou… https://t.co/rAT18i1deo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chic_80 @StevieSleeves @onacIoudyday @AOC @DavidRutz @washingtonpost Good strawman argument. What should be a crim… https://t.co/37Y8ebLwhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chino Hills hoopers taking another bus ride to Sacramento with @BigO21_ doing the "driving" . . .… https://t.co/OqhivW1sPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its taken a while, but Captain Nog has finally joined my crew. @AronEisenberg #startrektimelines #startrekds9 https://t.co/JVIfOdE4ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc if it sounds like I’m being a simp. I don’t deserve bullshit from a woman I treated like a queen for far too lo… https://t.co/eptgSYjUsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish mother nature would get off her period it's been raining ALL WEEK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing to remember about the ICE’s horrible treatment of 21 savage is that they do this and worse to people who arent famous every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[The person who brought the most blessings to my family was my down syndrome granddaughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malikstrutchen Hell yeah lmao I was watching sports center and they was talking about him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flexapeal @teencreepspod On apple podcasts too. I thought I either bumped the speed in my pocket or was having a stroke 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, looking for a great example of how to combine Healthy Christ centered Living and excellent professionalism? Consider: @MargoDeGange]]></document><document><![CDATA[My civil rights as a POC came at a price paid by others. Today is #HarrietTubman Day. Her life's work must continue… https://t.co/y4ddJGx204]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulatParsonex @GBarta42384 How Do With Nothing But Respect For All ... https://t.co/YYqNeKGnft]]></document><document><![CDATA[and away we go. @ Red Rock Canyon Hiking Trails https://t.co/tQ53IxQn8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinyent @Torrie11 Yeah they sent me the email yesterday :( hope she does a signing at Axxess]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oilfieldtrash14 Your so right but when shit hits the fan they be wanting help from us patriots]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 weeks since a severe chest injury (drs words) and I just stepped back into the gym. Gonna be a long road back to… https://t.co/EbZwg7Ae93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwralex @scottpw7 @Can_Skeptic_Wm @MichRogCook @wattsupwiththat @GeraldKutney WOW! yesterday was a day for trolls… https://t.co/iWQpZ0MLAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying our weekend off at the #happiestplaceonearth 😀 @ Disneyland https://t.co/MxG8PzPTuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My teacher gave me an A- on my “Humanization of American Prisoners” presentation.  Apparently, my content was good… https://t.co/aAFjgbYlcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski @MillerLite Enjoying a Miller Lite before dinner tonight !! Good luck this weekend Brad @ISMRaceway 🏁🏁 https://t.co/GoJYhjTVcl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivilHeathen @YouTube I used to do this with my wife when we were still dating, but we would start movies at the s… https://t.co/QM8qRzodyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalincase You should’ve seen how many classmates showed up and supported the girls team...it was wild 🤔😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I’d could say @rocmarci had great 8 album run but if I had to pick 4 I’d say u couldn’t get a more consistently… https://t.co/sLLxUE0Axk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s good, so I’m feeling great. Call me outta town shawty, every week a different state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonchibnall @DonaldJTrumpJr And do not forget he and his manager tried to divide and condemn, based on a lie, good Americans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bWeeZy64 @WeAreWrestlers Riding hips isn’t the same as riding legs. It was a solid ride to me. Not full of excitement though]]></document><document><![CDATA[Titans vs MOJO both teams fully healthy.. MOJO wins by 4 touchdowns.. https://t.co/UDcbofYXfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realamymholmes In today's day and age how is the Republicans don't hold their debates,    Setup thier own distribu… https://t.co/AoC85VWGiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crulge Dudeeee that’s exactly how I felt the entire time I was playing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[✌Sometimes you find cool, secret little swimming pools in nature with a view that take your breath away. 💦💦💦  TAG s… https://t.co/ZPxgshbEAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandiOnAir #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner #FireKushner… https://t.co/6W15BlvJk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋💅🏻✌🏻☕️👋🏻👑🤩😎😉🤟🏻P!nk - So What (Official Music Video) https://t.co/x48jMI7WIq via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daasha__ I’m talking with the black rims and the black letters on all the names on the truck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are not the real President. You cheated, with the help America's enemy Russia, to win the elec… https://t.co/Uf6o7r5baT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention @NewhousePR students, especially PRL497 &amp; PRL725: A must read!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cdnpoli @jguaido = disposable paper puppet. He can B replaced in a flash. Real questions: When will #CIA pull plug… https://t.co/lHbcKfNool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RancidSassy The International Bolshevik Tendency has a big split over this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Trump thinks the justice department is his own personal police force. He is destroying the three equal… https://t.co/WfbwbYyIVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muscle Shoals | Colbert commissioner offers proposal to revamp SIDC fund https://t.co/UA00fpYqU7.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elinor27652146 @synredae @Observer2541 @deelane @TheFinalDuke @YeshuaLover1970 @Atheist_Dragon @DB_Grimwalker… https://t.co/A1U414DC8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m Smith and in the octagon with the GOAT Jon Jones I would’ve taken the W and went home lol. #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[BASEBALL TIME! ⚾️ South Jones vs. Newton County ⏰: 9AM 📍: Braves Field 💻/📱: https://t.co/zLzFz0hQmx Have breakfast… https://t.co/HE8CwBYBOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got six Catholic hoes in here sinnin' and shit https://t.co/kI5UTeMqNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAOOO...Believe it or not I actually tried to hit this guy...every so often you get the sloppy joe. https://t.co/2EmRQbfJLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_cimini (Sorry if you already know all this--I just really like history and trivia and when those two circles ove… https://t.co/PPjEsnDbpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC statement when addressing farting cows 🐮  “Maybe we shouldn’t be eating a hamburger for breakfast, lunch, and d… https://t.co/A08VfRd7Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marissa_Monroy @austinmobility Are these just for ATD staff? Or all city staff?]]></document><document><![CDATA[time to grin a bit. #hilarity #chuckle #grin #jolly https://t.co/SYyaAF3Fp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN New Jersey man in ISIS pressure-cooker bomb plot case sentenced to 16 years (AP)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curiosos? Está chegando! marcosfreire @PraFeBrum @sonymusicgospel em Miami, Florida https://t.co/nsqU8SHYGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutNmbrdByBoys @CombatCavScout I love these stories, but I can't relate at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was talking about firing housley before talking about firing housley was cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiernana I’ve thought that all along, but the Padres are a dark horse here after getting Manny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @robynkonichiwa at @TheAnthemDC with @RachaelDaigle was a well-spent evening #Dancingonmyown https://t.co/Mv0RLqFG4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatesPhysio @GeoEdResearch @drugmonkeyblog @mholder_conklin @Rick_Frausto @jenheemstra @sbarolo @dnatarheel Total… https://t.co/AQXZSRH4vA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This distal Anterior tibial was crossed with a 0.014 Command wire WITHOUT a support catheter using the Cornidus Rob… https://t.co/o3yip0Ncyv]]></document></documents></author>