<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a NOBO by @MonumentBrewing @ Rodgers Forge — https://t.co/pCzO4VtQwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfw1515 @VaasZhura When I see work coming close https://t.co/4yKsA5cl6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCHOOL CLOSINGS: Fayetteville, Rogers, Bentonville, Siloam Springs &amp; Farmington closed today. More school closures at @KNWAnews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MATTHARDYBRAND @WWE #queencity Charlotte, NC #SDLive https://t.co/0I3CctbGLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza We know that! Anyone with half a brain does. We also know @SpeakerPelosi is afraid of these moron tra… https://t.co/VYmUbNQG4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spotted a pic of our President on the border! The migrants say he’s going too far😂😂😂 https://t.co/T3FGILAFha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ualbany Damien is clearing up snow from last night’s storm and getting ready to fly to Northern Africa and the Mid… https://t.co/MEir32x5v9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the long shots and glad they made a return in Madden 19, but honestly, why tf is it so hard!! 85% of a pick… https://t.co/WPzfElaUec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished #LeavingNeverland. I was sexually abused as a child and I told and regretted every minute of it because I… https://t.co/IvTFJK5Vsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little too basic, without a classic styling. Front numbers way too big.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanJossel @PlazaLasVegas Can she come to the @GoldenKnights game with us 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of Disney Vacation.. @ ESPN Wide World of Sports https://t.co/jGdbhbtNhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohEllison @coy_moore9 Put a little syrup in the middle, then spread it out. I just can’t have it soaked 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  You are a traitor to your country!   You need to resign or we're going to impeach you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time it was a month later. I ate it. 4K and my resale is lower. But, a month? Okay. 23 hours? Within the… https://t.co/bgAcdI8bhB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garcinsu2 Jaja, también había de los normales españoles, más finitos. Lo servían con chocolate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews The greater question is; do we want to exclude the idea of the 1st amendment in public schools?  The p… https://t.co/VhLvcE7E8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erik, No email unties to anyone yet? Does any Referral Roadster show in your tesla account? or anyone ones account… https://t.co/v0Tbq7HUyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any 2D figure can be made by folding a paper flat and making one straight cut. Such a fun morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Throwback to @lilxelly 's Performance @The Art Show for aintshithanded @_diegomontoya 🤘🏼⚡👁️ #XRR! @ Washington, Di… https://t.co/gxuaoqceg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que el apoyo a Maduro dice sobre el gobierno de López Obrador   #Mexico querido, camino a la servidumbre vas!… https://t.co/W2PNF03gjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oigan si jugamos el nuevo #FotoDeTuNovioChallenge para ver quien tiene el par, a ver si lo recuerdan como en el mem… https://t.co/lDiZblXyeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t read this if you’re celebrating #YearOfThePig. Outside of #Vernon #FarmerJohn plant, good Samaritans offer wa… https://t.co/sAzqViAE4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FiveThirtyEight I thought the idea was to move away from horse race obsession coverage?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ether_Detroit @412VIC @RAB88 @cnnbrk I honestly thought voting for trump was the dumbest thing a person could do u… https://t.co/3WrCb5myBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marc_Bertrand Maybe when he said “if you guys will have me back” his real plan was for us all to despise him so he can leave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDavisPlease Heck yea dude! I’m so excited for you! Let’s try to get some a tix together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ending, here, is worth the wait.  https://t.co/Lzkj05PN95  #abc7now]]></document><document><![CDATA[An important energy transition to assess in the context of the #GreenNewDeal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJennTracker saw there was no video yesterday and none so far today. Is anything wrong?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yetidisplay @jpalmiotti See? I knew that asking for the funny prison stories was the best option!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar @realDonaldTrump #PresidentPinocchio is intimidated by #ChampionshipWomen. They achieved everything w… https://t.co/jCrkROEYLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Trump Cabinet Officials Were "Ready To Support" 25th Amendment 'Coup' As Rosenstein Tallied Votes | Zero Hedge… https://t.co/uFlXMUyRQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread. So what will it take to get these whack-a-doodles off of cable TV?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherYuHsiLee @rebekahentralgo @eacrunden The way to Esther’s heart is to take salmon and make a stack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patagonia with bro’s and climbing legend Rick Ridgeway (1st American to climb K2) learning about being a mission d… https://t.co/tDt0EV4Ge1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerryCormierGP @ElizabethMay @JustinTrudeau @cathmckenna @liberal_party @OilGasCanada Canada's climate record is a… https://t.co/wljf3bXgko]]></document><document><![CDATA[First impression was "Wow!" Smooth and chocolatey,  silky creamy and yet bold. - Drinking a Mocha Tonic (Nitro) by… https://t.co/BQdFQbunj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost AN American RepresentAtive EVITAmericA-Rgentina         A-nit ?          A-Knit--L A rick-rAck mach… https://t.co/P1tUv57Fzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CappuccinoYung He’s got a supreme sticker on there - freshest shell in the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recording this afternoon. Finally. More on tap this weekend. #isles @FaithfulIsles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dinkxxxx @LavaletteAstrid @SweeetMamaSue @GiGiBclub @b_and_s_designs @ursobuursula @carole_awebb @billy2kid45… https://t.co/fn96tMlUUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@croselund @cityatlas He wasn't getting mean. It's just surprising to me. No worries, though. I'm sure you're getti… https://t.co/55mP0o1ADk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cognizant is hiring in #Austin, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply: C++ Developer #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favorite #19..love you to centerfield fence and back. Make it a great day😘❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SydGolic Send a picture in Jul when it is 75-80 in CHI and 110 “can’t touch car doors” hit in PHI. That’s their “winter.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyInfo24269521 @MahgdalenRose MAGA? Are cruelest ppl ON EARTH  About fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news… https://t.co/H6HL9aO71N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Def Jam Fight For NY (Request) - Free For All at 125 Street Station (Hard) https://t.co/HXvp0FAs0k via @YouTube… https://t.co/45wgmEf1xV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "ENGAGEMENT SPECIALIST - PART TIME" at CROSSMARK, then look for people… https://t.co/5bNEBhIuNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate tweets that make some random point and then tell you to tweet if you agree. It’s so lame.   Tweet if you agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about the #opm classes I am taking is the people.  They are from all over the world.  It’s amazing.… https://t.co/5erLMXscpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s unfortunate that I have to say this, just because you are my friend does not mean I will wrap your car for close to free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an awesome feeling of peace God gave me as I watched the @Apple__Rays do their thing!  So proud of their HIT today!  Love you guys!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a guy who blew it....to a guy named Blewitt...can’t make this up folks 😂 🐻⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inarueketi @manuhola @Newarkguy1973 @kiaraeshi @Guzabra Esa no es mi realidad ni la de nadie que conozca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joshua has a little pep in his step as he prepares a rear patio for paver Sealing in Port Orange 🍊.… https://t.co/WFuZqteboi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BW952 Lol yeah my friends and I eat and then play golden tee every Thursday 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Soldout @thecomedystore.  Let's just laugh. #fridaynight #yes #comedy #laughter #losangeles @ The Comedy Store https://t.co/rSNDOaiHXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Start the day with #positivity.  Fill your mind and share it with others, it can make all the difference!… https://t.co/YbCwFkEhDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fireside Chat number 1 has been officially bumped from the top spot of 2019 @patyoung44B involved moments. #mdga19… https://t.co/aKeLREvRCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenS_Carter @blackenterprise Congrats!!  Both to you and your proud mom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecardenassan Ibero.. Puebla... Con razón el conservadurismo que no puede ver más allá de su nariz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mark555888999 @CNN Yeah because that's what Trump says. I believe everything Trump says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dabbed up @svddendeathdub and @Oolacile said he saw me going MAD in the pits, what a night to be a headbanger 🥵🤪🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFL @TorontoArgos What a name.  Already like this guy!!!! Welcome to the 6ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the car door start beeping&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; https://t.co/5euZeBThqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @JamieBollWBTV for a chance to talk #NC09 #OYSTonight - if called to testify at any hearing, it's a good ide… https://t.co/4E1UAhK7gJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggabe This tells us Alex Smith will be out for the season. Hopefully he can get back at some point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwtvd so question all the drinks in the show was it apple juice , or Apple cider or was it real liquor. I'm not ex… https://t.co/lynIuaT2uR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fred Bugg with 2 G’s is one of my favorite newer characters in #YoungJusticeOutsiders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejand71152542 @edaccessible @Gabriele_Corno @terrinakamura @AKD09 @RizzoGigirz58 @111ayasuko @PDorancy… https://t.co/HwdjBoBR6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StreihtMenace @michellexdiaz Oh yeah I heard about this dude and his story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And you stand for getting up there and lying to the American people you stupid stupid bitch for backing this thief.… https://t.co/rzNFk3C7AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this more or less than you thought it would be? Report shows true size of tech boot camp market https://t.co/npaSw2a3tX via @EdDiveK12]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is Howard Schultz still running for President? Haven’t heard a peep from his “campaign” in weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching two of my boys dance with a couple girls that could have been from the golden girls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marisa wanted to plan Valentine’s Day this year so she surprised me with dinner at a fancy restaurant in Grand Rapi… https://t.co/peZTLLDQzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why hasn’t @RepMattGaetz had any repercussions for threatening @MichaelCohen212? Normal Americans would have gotten… https://t.co/Xi3YFGmGdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drigssp4mm420 @akaDenza @Ohmwrecker @MiniLaddd https://t.co/ygmNmHHqoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller _No Big Ben, there was NOTHING there, we’ve been hearing this from you for years now! The NFL took Brady… https://t.co/IQk6eX2Jno]]></document><document><![CDATA[They couldn’t even get actors that resembled the record execs. 😂. Timbaland wants his money the right way. Not the… https://t.co/iPZdIw8HuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kiddos on the gondola. @killingtonmtn #killingtonkids #skilikeagirl #skilikethisgirl @ Killington Ski Resort https://t.co/BM2ChCPYGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose I should go to bed. #bear #beard #sleepy @ Burnsville, Minnesota https://t.co/nSq7lv4Gn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen to this conversation an excellent way to close out #BlackHistoryMonth thank you @Robert_Townsend &amp;… https://t.co/vSJCVBHAmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningJoe #IlhanOmar is an antisemite plain and simple. Accept and deal with it!! Thank you @JoeNBC for talking straight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenk620 @casmar27 @DisFunko What’s your number one for Target Con? Mine’s GITD electrocuted Vader!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose it’s time to delete my college internships from my LinkedIn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nanaaaflores According to the prophecy Jon fits it better but there’s also other people the theory applies to idk.… https://t.co/dXmTil35my]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most people are going to act like they care when really they're just bored of their own problems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ogilthorpe48 @Grubhub I switched to @DoorDash the food arrives so much quicker and have never had any issues. I’m… https://t.co/TksJI4gP8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_kellykelly @SafetyPinDaily He claimed he weighed 190 pounds so clearly he's hollow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thepiff @MrPiffles Get to see that cute little guy again this time next week, oh yeah and you too piff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte @LauraPardo1989 They wouldn’t serve any function in global capital if they were assimilating . Assimil… https://t.co/qsUyUpj22E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@closkey08 @kingshammersc @NationalLeague @fccincinnati @MLS @ATLUTD Safe travels 👏🏻 bring back all the W’s that you possibly can 🔸🔹⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @J_CMueller Feel better guy. When this is over Trump will still not be a Russian asset.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Tuesday to all those creating magic today!  #tuesdayquotes #tuesdaymotivation #eventplanner #meetingplanner @… https://t.co/DtrJzQu09y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official UNC staff: “Obama’s not here” Me: that sounds exactly like someone who knows where Obama is would say]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something tells me that the “MoMo” shit on youtube is a secret marketing campaign for a scary movie this Summer. And if it is it’s working.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I already push Persona on my wife and friends IRL so why not on Twitter too? THIS IS A FANTASTIC DEAL GET THIS NOW!… https://t.co/50bMyvJu8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the follow up discussion guide and sermon notes to tonight’s message! https://t.co/cJLgjCCKZm]]></document></documents></author>