<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Oscars⁠ ⁠⁠ ⁠ winners: #GreenBook Best Picture  #RamiMalek Best Actor #OliviaColman Best Actress #AlfonsoCuarón Bes… https://t.co/tBlTBlxppp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenncloud Exactly 😊 i wrote this because I’m actually in a good, high energy time but realize that when I’m feelin… https://t.co/6UviIYKp5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naya1229 Certainly was rude!  What an ass Kody is being about this move crap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizaWallace27 @jeremypmurphy @weatherchannel I’m in Chicago and it is awful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenHodnett @Headspace I find it to increase my stress load when I try to meditate more than I anticipate. Stil… https://t.co/hhe073HIWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[02.22.19 @TheCherShow (@ Neil Simon Theatre - @nederlanderbway for The Cher Show (NY) in New York, NY)… https://t.co/OJykZ7zmBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You do realize Han is as crazy as you. Birds of a radical extreme white supremists  feather, certa… https://t.co/S57fwgpbyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love what I do. I love helping people. I love being a light in kid’s lives. What I don’t love is the disrespect f… https://t.co/qoV3ttTH4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do I exist on Twitter. How will I've had to block people, follow them. It's a nightmare 🤔I just wa… https://t.co/YbgMVnhXDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Told Cody my FPD shirt was tad snug and he said “well do a sit up.” One sit up 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndWhittleFam @americangodsus @TheOrlandoJones @YetideBadaki @MrRickyWhittle @MrCegielski @neilhimself @AbtahiOmid… https://t.co/aQJOh66hpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @shanedawson Where do I apply or you ll just hired .... based on what ... ? What does it take to be pa… https://t.co/TI5mv44VLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Benefits of Reading Books @UFT @mosalty @AFTunion @DOEChancellor @CWATSONHARRIS @TeeRico_LinMan @liifechanger3D… https://t.co/c3pElNjiOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are up and working! Here is a look at your headlines: https://t.co/UoInUc84sV @AnthonyNBC12 @AndrewNBC12… https://t.co/D2AJtwKt4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun building birdhouses with our HLH families at Title I Night with Home Depot! @horn_hl @JMSandz @RkeCoSchools https://t.co/6qMhNkWke7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they ask I make it appear... (for the most part) lol  #Dinner keeping it light. #Homemade #meatball #parmesan… https://t.co/63McX3zDKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @IAmUltimatePred found the @grittystreaking account and started showing me videos and now my stomach hurts from laughing. Send help. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diet!!   FREE  Hey gals!! Not selling anything just looking for recommendations on if fat shaming works for weight… https://t.co/AWhm6gyiH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turtle lovers! 🐢 When you want a classic purse that also has a Boho vibe, Cybele is the one.  This beautiful purse… https://t.co/goTZrGeVGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suzannezeedyk No castles, but there is a fishing pier! https://t.co/ElI4KBi5bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmegery20 happy birthday :) i hope u have a wonderful day ill visit soon💞💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence So sorry you didn’t make it to the White House 🙁 But grateful that you will heal 🙏💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRussellDavis I’m super intrigued! What did they drink and what empowered you to find out??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_realjgoodwin @TheNoahRing He has given me a wonderful crochet talent so I can give people whom I will never meet the warmth of a blanket.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best Valentine’s Day present was going to Disneyland’s Sweethearts Nite with the best #DisneylandAfterDark… https://t.co/FiSGDS4TyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The happiness I feel rn is something I haven’t felt in such a long time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsBessGMS @CPS_SS @ToriPineWMS It sure does! I’m excited to share it again after Spring Break!]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 on 5 again! Go Irish! Go Hills! @FGRGHHockey @GHSchoolMI @ghillssports @mseng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanNeumann35 @JamesxMyall My absolute favorite part. Let me spend thousands of dollars to support my workers, but… https://t.co/pNz5bk7szD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually hate winter, but this is one exception to the rule. Also.. FYI, there is a Girl Scout Cookie finder app t… https://t.co/V4oXHtt5oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpryGuy @ProgressiveFate @susanlbrannigan @davidhogg111 Word, SpryGuy!🙈🙉🙊 Anybody, still using the "#BothSides", a… https://t.co/q3biRU8j8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEM CAROCO NESSE ANGUUUU..... VEM COME BACK DA DEMI COM UM EMPRESARIO QUE PRESTA E QUE SE IMPORTA POR FAAAVOOOOOORRRRRRRRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppleSupport why is my iPhone FREEZING up all the time all of a sudden?? You know that @SamsungMobile 10 don’t loo… https://t.co/rU3gUjFFVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Disagree.   Hard to do much with both sides colluding against you but still TRUMP has accomplished GREAT things for USA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRC @tizzywoman @RepDebHaaland Bless your hear‼️❤️❤️ I felt your heartbreak and I wish I could just make ALL the b… https://t.co/jw5XcZZLJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Siandierra just want air time and some 💵, but aren’t saying a DAMN thing!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always enjoyed drawing and painting eyes. There's something satisfying about the symmetry they create for a face.… https://t.co/bHj0pViIMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaJamesRye68 @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @Sean_C_Larkin @SlidellPD @OHFCSO @SalinasPD @RCSD @NyeSheriff… https://t.co/QtPierIWdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s not the 26th anymore, but I spent all day at a theme park trying to have a good day because it’s been 7… https://t.co/sC5Pty9ZUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RamonFoster @937theFan so happy for You! And your family! And the team! Does this mean another show this year!?!❤️ @jhathhorn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonHStewart @ASAPInfa @DonaldJTrumpJr In what world do you live? You honestly believe illegal immigrants commit… https://t.co/mn5DCAbEkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelbyhotch is literally the LOML and I miss her with my whole heart 💔💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for all that you have taught me!!@SherylKingsberg @BrookeFaughtDNP @LisaLarkinMD @woman_wellness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine looking in a mirror and this is your face. https://t.co/Kb5SAH64uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i do not care about how good you look, how much money you got, the car you drive , if you doing too much or just do… https://t.co/Go3kG080cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he should have followed dear ol dad’s walk in the snow followed by A RESIGNATION]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zuri_too Mr Gibbs you can’t possibly be that ignorant you are a con also . You certainly don’t want to find out th… https://t.co/azlybbKixw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, thank goodness this dress is accommodating... #thirdtri #springbabes #largeandincharge https://t.co/EE9TRNjBqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rachael_Conrad That's just pure statistics honey the majority of people in the movie reviewing business, freelance… https://t.co/xTOMb4NItZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work. Come visit, I’ll be here till 1. (at @Publix in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/j8JlPlnrQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricSnitilWx Thank You!  I didn’t even hear this tonight on our local news, and I live in middle Georgia👍🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaabell23 @m_magallon93 @_RichHomieKevin @____xoyg Hey you didn’t say it had to be fancy lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiralayla @momentoviral Trata de mover tú la vaca, como que crees que son animalitos de comiquitas, noo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life is gonna change so much within the next few months and I’m so scared but having supportive parents makes everything a bit easier ☹️💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[My four year old got off the school bus and the says to me “she’s in a mood today. Not a good bus ride.” I told Nor… https://t.co/OZ9uqklgjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @maddow And Bar's son-in-law just got a legal job with Trump. Doesn't take long to cross the line when you work for Donnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawn41764 @KyleWOrton @VictoriaLIVE I don't trust her. But we just nearly lost Gabby Giffords to a stunt like this… https://t.co/qHsRY5PvuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, you’re on a CTA bus trying not to cry about Alex Trebek.   #FuckCancer]]></document><document><![CDATA[listening to pied piper because i miss them so much and im just being extra emotional]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heart shaped ravioli, our wedding song and our fav wine 🥰🥰🥰 https://t.co/FGerm4QnhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow @RadioAmy @PATGREENMUSIC @RadioLunchbox @RayLaMontagne @ProducerEddie Me and You - Kenny Chesney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myname68160319 @D4NS3_M4C4BR3 @AbiWilks @mishtal @GnasherJew @LabourAgainstAS Honest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleOls16337009 @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump What do you mean I’m “damn lucky” he didn’t have a closed door meeting?… https://t.co/xiZiT7XOOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity is good medicine. Cupcake grenade! Amazing Harley Quinn cosplay! - 10 Harley Quinn Cosplays #humor #giggle… https://t.co/2rtDV8FuFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg He’s one of the worst of them! How could he possibly vote against that?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember I had a tournament in San Diego and my brother used it as an opportunity to throw a party at the house,… https://t.co/RwMqF0YP4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnishinabekEd Our youth did not disappoint! Our future leaders in action. Chi-Miigwetch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetMeAndresYou dude at this point i rather deal w that than this pain, it’s bad 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Facebook pages are reporting Krystal is going to be charged with more crimes. It’s obvious none of them underst… https://t.co/A8GKxlo6cD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RainbowSquidInk But that'll just make it "Raph breaks the internet". XD https://t.co/F8E7WtkwvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[girls dropping like flies on the bachelor lol colton better jump that fence ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TipsyCoachman @BethBourgeois @emzanotti @trumps_feed Thing is, they would help the beached whale.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMSchmidt from @LetsTalkScience talking over lunch about key science questions and how that tallies with tech and… https://t.co/gwsFoni1uL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Military members should fight dangers abroad—not in their own homes. https://t.co/AE87fZDHDq @DailySignal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pullupifubad LMAOOOO OMG IM SO HAPPY I FOUND YOUR TWITTER😭😭😂😂😂😂 g got me rolling over here]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited the one beauty product I can’t be without just adding another member to the Shape Tape family it’s F… https://t.co/IGeXNlXQfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all my friends are so dang talented!!!! @victoriatyler25  so proud of you💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow I’ve unknowingly set my alarm for @BTS_twt cypher 4 and it didn’t even get to the raps/adlibs yet but idk h… https://t.co/vc2ibmafKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday @ Bellingham, Washington https://t.co/wJWgmoPJZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#women #womenempowerment  #internationalwomensday  #selflove  #selfcare @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/fUB9ujcQJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[A new musical set in NY in the 1960's @ABronxTaleTour is coming to #Pittsburgh this November. This musical harkens… https://t.co/TAFUiGUMwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow all my friends are so cool. I mean I have like 3 friends but we all DOPE AF. Quality over Quantity. 💎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I should have ordered Chinese food because this gnocchi tastes like sadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Translation: Other people are reading it and I'm waiting for @foxandfriends to tell me if I should sign it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulKeating259 Dodgers 10/345 opt outs at 3 and 6 years https://t.co/LhAdK2q8xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The minute a man realizes I’m smarter than him is the minute I learn if he’s worth my time or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok here’s some more screenshots before I get clocked from the the local group... why, why is this necessary. https://t.co/VmT542TZYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are the 2019  SEC Champs!!! #Bootup #lsubasketball #secchampionship  #lsu #batonrouge @ Pete Maravich Assembly C… https://t.co/bYxsC2ydF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews I worry that they were sold. There is such a shortage of proper housing and medical care for the childr… https://t.co/HYznGrCH83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone please tell me that Victoria secret isn’t closing down bc of some crybaby bitches 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸This Offer Only For U.S.A👌 Get $1000 Visa Gift Card Now!👉 To get a  free $1000 click on the below given link and… https://t.co/UQ8bSNEivK]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes, i absolutely will go to New Jersey for beach fossils and i have no shame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buzzsaws1990 @dar_uso @jenniferm_q This video will help explain the difference.  https://t.co/4jDEDt1aho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump can father children with 3 women, befriend murderous dictators, pay off adult film stars, lie all day, lock k… https://t.co/Xxu0ZYdmvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessica_roy So glad to be here! You and everyone else have been so so kind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aria_Ash2 Lol my younger sister asked me if she could do that too. So you're not alone haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sitting here watching the @CriticalRole Vox Machina Animated Special kickstarter just shoot up and honestly it'… https://t.co/VR5ofiEWYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local Tahoe Strippers Bring the Strip Club to You! Book us direct! Bachelor parties, Apres` Ski, Birthdays or just… https://t.co/GGi0uw3z4Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi please go hype up my recent! I want people at school to think I actually have friends and flex on them 🥺 https://t.co/vVtx28pSbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told my husband the other day how shopping makes me feel better....until I get... #hilarity #giggle #smile… https://t.co/VrcFeLvyr9]]></document></documents></author>