<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#PicnSave 👽👽👽👽 #theskyisgreen #purpleshadows #green #purple @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/tGtpO062Yc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought this 30 pack was empty. It feels kind of heavy. Oh hai Willis! #instacat #catsofinstagram https://t.co/GfEfFluPO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @gatewaypundit Is this nationwide?  My kids played with their own sex in the sports games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve decided that if i dont like you that you’re not allowed to even remotely like fall out boy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rush Limbaugh on whether Trump is justified in taking executive action to secure funding for his border wall: MUST… https://t.co/kCwKYgi0Xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is damaged garbage not clearance... #99centsonly #runa @drinkruna (@ 99 Cents Only Stores in Redondo Beach, CA… https://t.co/0o6FaRwvQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend warriors! #hiking #parivers #dogsofinstagram #alaskankleekaiofinstagram #ohioriver #alaskankleekai @ Ohiopy… https://t.co/79wxs8NQMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobeffinjones i hope she goes through my account and revoked me of LSA way status]]></document><document><![CDATA['Large-scale' snowfall poised to further bury Twin Cities this weekend https://t.co/G8iBLtlOhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AHORA navega cerca de #Venezuela una escuadra de #EEUU que incluye un portaviones, mientras en #Cartagena fondean… https://t.co/WPk6funAfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IWaveATrumpFlag @ma_liky_ @VoxDawg @StormIsUponUs Look how many follow and it will tell you if they're trolls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked for water and the vending machine gave me sprite. Is this a hate crime???]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend thinks a guy on campus is the next love of her life. He has a mullet with brown hair and is around 5’8” o… https://t.co/cRsSCeDFLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sky is the limit and you know that you keep on...pressin' on @ Breakfast Republic https://t.co/4nAFuQQlx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Changes as compared to proposal pre filed earlier. EV vehicle changes. Also port portion. Those are primary change areas @whnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran into an Allegro at Pitcher's edge taking a hitting lesson!! Well-rounded student!!!! She can sing and hit!!! https://t.co/hgfublONEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Possibly. Volume load per week is most important but appears splitting into 2-3 sessions may be slightly better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 My Mom and I used to get my Dad’s blackheads on his back with a Bobby pin. Damn those hair pins work great👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walk into dunkin for maybe 1 min IF THAT and someone yelled at me for leaving clover in the on car (with the heat r… https://t.co/nPHzZ8a7aQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This jacket is so “all-purpose” you’ll wonder how you lived without it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is not a radical idea to suggest that anyone who works 40 hours /week should not be living in poverty.” #BernieInChicago #Bernie2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Baltimore and beyond, make plans to join us for this original performance based on the #Tempest and… https://t.co/tEwME1GprJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HIMSS19 @NovantHealth you can’t just turn on technology and expect #patientengagement  It must be coupled with a cultural transformation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time we pop out issa movie 👻 @ NOTO Philadelphia https://t.co/lz2UZRsC3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iivid yeah, I need to see the end results on a couple of these images...🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my dogs and every other dog in the whole world so much that it hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study for my Advanced Financial Reporting exam or rewatch #WynonnaEarp on Netflix? Why not both... Thursday night g… https://t.co/yWSbxVZ2Zq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in some Rough Rider gear let me or Brian know! Great stuff!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que curioso no quiero nada serio y ahora a todos les gustó JAJAJAJJAJA kpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really tired of girls treating me like shit just because they’re insecure 💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you can actually see straight before making off the wall assumptions. Big ol ugly ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😮Student loan debt is now the 2nd highest consumer debt category—behind only mortgage debt—higher than both credit… https://t.co/2IaOvZ4Xrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you work in customer service you know wtf I’m talking about. 😂 like I know that I can’t be the same Dani I am at… https://t.co/jrYcW0yQDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[cayceandrew vibing with @kindbudmusic at @erinblackirish downtowncocktailroom 2/19/19 #funkinsoullv… https://t.co/PtrI4KvhdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever I'm in a bad mood, i just watch @TreyNKennedy 's white people video and laugh for 10 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently observing an awards assembly for my cousin at Cook Elentary and I’m so bothered I was in first grade 18 years ago😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimFoustMusic @FLStrawberryFst Knew you’d be happy to be in Florida ...  I think the main attraction is strawberries 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥰Valentine's Day is Tomorrow, and wether you have a date or not, come celebrate LOVE at Hamburger Marys WEHO with u… https://t.co/lqcKTrqkHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you only have two classes a day and the first one is canceled it’s really hard to show up to the second one🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHRLY519 u just summarized all queer people in heterosexual relationships heheheh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else #Snapchat read camera shake? Like my just happened to do thag last night and idk why]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ur ex posts a picture with his new girl but is wearing a shirt you bought him.. 🐸☕️ hehehehe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone pls bring me dominos to work. They don’t deliver here and I’m starving]]></document><document><![CDATA[The podcast my friends and I make is now available on Spotify! 😎 https://t.co/sNKeMV6BeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[RE: Gossip Girl (SPOILER)  This lil Dan detour from my Chuck and Blair endgame has gone on long enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[working on some new editing techniques :)) super happy with the way this photo turned out! https://t.co/CSquKo7KQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna rant. I wanna go off BADDDDDD like I swear the only reason I keep twitter is so I can rant lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @AmFamJohnVB for making it into my Top 10 People I Love To Lunch With #foodies #foodiesofinstagram… https://t.co/EeRVbAn9k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsDoeschner @GlenCoveSchools @AltamiranoKen @GiselleJaclyn Can members of the public attend this event? I am a DOE… https://t.co/IhAOTWy7Ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember the Facebook app #UnBabyMe that would change peoples' posts of their kids' pictures to pictures of cats? I… https://t.co/4GEBYHjQGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a playoff game day!!  The Huskies take on Roger Williams today at 6 PM EST and look to take a step closer to t… https://t.co/saJzWKpJXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[230k people migrated to one city alone during 365 days is fucking astronomical!   Is Dallas having a secret gold rush or some shit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to all who attended our Pampered Chef new season taste testing and product launch and graciously donated… https://t.co/acrtQT87Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a Historic Move, New York City Bans Discrimination Based on Hair https://t.co/4kO1JGPoHT #SUsocialwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case y’all didn’t know @JohnMayer is coming to San Antonio in September]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoveSetMatch_ @Stellarfederer @rogerfederer @DaniCNav @TitanRFederer @noessanta @SoizickZ @RFfan94 @RedFeather_emi… https://t.co/K0yBJQZzzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[det är så jävla tydligt att @mjhamilton_ har skrivit manuset till #svteagles och jag älskar det mer än något annat https://t.co/b8CLZbW04v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contest to win 5-day elk hunting trip in Utah with Don Jr https://t.co/hbXPKEucLX via @MailOnline.  UTAH PROTEST THIS DISGUSTING MAN/BABY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Brecht Stables &amp; Dustin's Place Equine Assisted Therapy https://t.co/yG81H5tIep]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HandsOffVenezuela no more regime changes. Withdraw our troops, don’t arm viscous rebels. Lift sanctions. Return th… https://t.co/0knFVIXxSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OF COURSE #KIM IS RESPONSIBLE!!  #OttoWarmbier's  family rebukes Trump, says #Kim Jong Un is #responsible for son's… https://t.co/fixvZU4dGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKruJue It’s too late for him tbh. Ima try to be happy for him tho because he absolutely deserves to enjoy himself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredOstu @Acended @AMarch4OurLives @MichaelSkolnik Pro choice people believe in the right to CHOOSE. In what world… https://t.co/oJvRLVij5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try not to make a huge deal about everything but apparently that's impossible for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can always lean on your AKΨ Bros! Check out Brother Selene at the Leaning Tower of Pisa! 💙💛#AKPsiXiSigma… https://t.co/zNY5GAWwYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilroxybabe8188 You’re gonna love that one pair of socks and those 3 headbands though!! 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ivereka_ @_ruckin Right! 😂 after the video I was like https://t.co/11cXanXmJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[But you have the best insults to hurl at him. Unfortunately he probably wouldn’t understand them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEN I MESSAGE THEM LIKE wyd DELETE THE GAME BOT AND I GET REPLIES BACK, “sorry i’m not a nerd”, “sorry I have a li… https://t.co/9JDoCo9wN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AU_SOC journalism professor @SherriWrites interviews legendary civil rights reporter @JMitchellNews who spent his… https://t.co/nIWrVbydvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @shescraftychi ・・・ 🚨Attn Madison party people: we’re coming through for a FREE show at highnoonmadison 3/22… https://t.co/wFyuaGHnfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TRONzuercher love you dude. this tour is gonna be epic, i have a good feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it I have a job where I work with people and I still always feel left out? 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvmeroni Yes. I even like to include the skis if I’m feeling real cold 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samsanders Thank YOU @samsanders - great recap. I’m going to share this with all of my BernieOrBust friends who are still bitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of a break and some coffee ☕️ Possibly some pain killers for my leg, but that’s not possible right now 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t cried that hard during anything from the Bachelor Franchise since Alexis made Jack eat a dead crab, serve… https://t.co/b31IrvqlZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dog is chewing his bone on my bed and it smells like shit but I don’t have the heart to make him leave because he is so content]]></document><document><![CDATA[Execs from NJ-based drug companies and others testifying in DC over high drug prices - already facing some tough qu… https://t.co/mhpqW90wn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t party all night with there mom in the dome? 💜💛💚 https://t.co/SFW2BHjPnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO Ur speech at CPAC was awesome &amp; very enlightening. So glad u left the dems behind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[32 pics you need to see before you die. The last one gets me! haha https://t.co/3PWMD1e0zN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am starting my first batch as soon as my ordered SCOBY arrives and then classes begin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardAshton30 @realDonaldTrump Right now the biggest cesspool of corruption is the White House.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My offenses will be sealed up in a bag; you will cover over my sin. https://t.co/Yyt7RUc94e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a sucker for you as always and your new music! @jonasbrothers #SuckerVideo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Styling flare jeans #ontheblog today ✨ Head to the link in my bio to shop my favorite flares, both cropped and full… https://t.co/9h7vWgq4hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1tomstraw @AndrewWMarlowe @TerriEdda @NathanFillion @Stana_Katic Thank you for being part of the #Castle family an… https://t.co/k81SBKLd2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Frats Jump Out On The Club Floor When Down For My Niggas Come On. https://t.co/cBgKVwEEsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait to move off campus frfr but living on campus is very convenient!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can people stop using the word #grit ? I’m uber tired of it. Everyone keeps talking about their grit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaccioppoliMike @BernieSanders @BetoORourke We need to abolish the DNC and the electoral college and install vote by mail nationwide.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RHONJ Keep talking,Jen about homewreckers..Your REALLY convincing us all that your husband DOESNT cheat!!Classic b… https://t.co/eLhYxJpOD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing all my memories from senior year basketball from FIVE YEARS AGO really makes me miss it 😓 and also I would g… https://t.co/imfCFIstOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_flowers_ i read this like "My San Benito starts in... wait.. my...? OH SPRING BREAK"]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP only has name calling left. No values. No ethics. No morals. Only name slinging and fear mongering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It sucks being a girl and going to get your car fixed I know these mfs are trying to finesse me 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama This is what you tweet? Of course I want no one to hurt! However, there are kids with cancer,poor,abandoned... Say no more!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Subjects to NEVER bring up when I visit my family in Jersey, #LeavingNeverland Fuck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not decide on which cute photos to post so enjoy the many pictures of my Valentine’s Day weekend getaway wi… https://t.co/MBU6F5ktXe]]></document></documents></author>