<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@VicenteFoxQue @lopezobrador_ Cambiemos de tema https://t.co/7v7n7qPe04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personal best today in 100 Free: 44.29. Likely tonight back for 400 Free relay. #boilerup #purdue @ Campus Recreati… https://t.co/8FcGChLMEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funkomatic i wanted a comic against a brick wall gif, but couldn't pass this one up! https://t.co/2Ag8GU42cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the @FAANews API feed to @TripIt is overwhelmed. #iFlyAlaska https://t.co/XkPp2RO13O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPO_SaltyDog Damn. You got me.  Oh wait.  Obama was wrong. The ACA has been a miserable experiment for average peo… https://t.co/59Be38EvOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sky13861654 @ChristiWalling @jill_magnussen @gerrinnesmac @malekalby @pkamla1 @BabyGo2014 @letgolifeflows… https://t.co/X5od78yrJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junona2 @goodenough_fu @asurepin @INTENSE_MAN @UrMAJIXF4F @VixenVegas @Lion3m @robmitc69885060 @Morbidmedieval… https://t.co/DkfBigxsBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsdozzy @TheIndieBookBox Generally it's best if you send over a physical copy so we can check it out. Info on the FAQ on the site.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you work with some amazing people when they ship @portilloshotdog's to you. ♥️ https://t.co/kmJ3HvwtLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jooheon 🐝 Jooheon really is a precious lil honey bee but my brain was fried at this point and I really don’t rememb… https://t.co/8x5ILlpmHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicksdjohnson @EthereumNetw https://t.co/6md2dMi0F1 https://t.co/9H16697Fkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOOT NOTES: I wrote about a promising @CedarCliffColts wrestler who had his sport violently taken away from him. He… https://t.co/zwPm9z7QIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clitsanddoobies @DrippinSauceeee Yall mf be reaching n who tf is this nigga https://t.co/eTVEVl9nkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a treat to see “Arnold Marlin” Jesse Chintanadilek have artwork featured in @The_News_Herald We love and appre… https://t.co/DrR37ioXfH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both are now steaming free  @chopsotv https://t.co/83pxPxIy3O via @ChrisTashima who was on a @CAAM panel with… https://t.co/BRUnjzHHUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregorykorte I’d need to think about that more. There would be a problem with Giuliani holding himself out as a co… https://t.co/oA5jrTbntL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a ridiculous example of how poor leadership fosters a toxic work environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Glacier National Park @noshoesnation #KCpirateflag https://t.co/FkUpNDKMu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Scottish Cafu 💜💙 Thank you for everything Alan. The fact anyone could hate this guy shows how moronic our fan b… https://t.co/umfi10MAla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siskaren13 @RayOntrez @HillaryClinton @davidhogg111 This is a huge piece of disinformation and is fakenews lies. S… https://t.co/jycZF5AKJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to start your own #clothing brand, then you will definitely need private label #clothes from Alani… https://t.co/Kfh5cIy0fm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera What the hell do you mean provocateur ,wearing a hat supporting our president is not provoking , you're an ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @IlhanMN I do believe tweeting is is better than journalism at least getting it out of the person's m… https://t.co/420Ry9WZTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 Yeah. 48 for an even 4 years would just seem over the top.   Prick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is National Napping Day.  Ajax celebrates every day very well.  #chicago #dogs #news https://t.co/Ndv4ASlC3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReinaMo53490879 God bless you my sister and Glory to our God.  God is good all the time and all the time God is good.  Blessings and peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would you want to be the Democratic nominated for president of the United States? #democrats #Dems #Bernie2020… https://t.co/5u7SNuDlID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Псалми 39:4-6 Библия, нов превод от оригиналните езици (с неканоничните книги) (CBT)  4 Пламна сърцето в гърдите ми… https://t.co/Qs7QBBYDkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tout ça me semble vrai, mais les petits enfants ont-ils droit à leur petite enfance avec un de leur parent? Les emb… https://t.co/RaSNrEchZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimmaddalena66 @THD_Kendra @TroyDFC6707 Received my 1st Homer Award since transferring to Troy.Scanned and sorted… https://t.co/OMdS8gDQ2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayy, sick of these niggas  Sick of these niggas  Hire some help, get rid of these niggas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp Ms Cupp, have you been following the coverage and the vitriol spewed against the right on this? I am still… https://t.co/CdGFvQ2TL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos @ADVISAusa for another  annual conference full of learning and inspiration! And love supporting @JACentralInd… https://t.co/LywLViShFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck off @peta Steve Irwin was a good person who truly loved and cared about wildlife. He died doing what he loved.… https://t.co/GV3f6enQkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have an amazing day today my friends love all of you so much 🤗 https://t.co/qOUYw7KOaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a really fun night @diavolapizzeria  with synac and @winewithilya Saturday. Ilya brought a phillips hill winery… https://t.co/MO77Emp1ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Smith Jr. on first title shot: 'Everything I have worked towards' #Boxing  https://t.co/n0CvtpTTbY via @nypostsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maximus99728784 @CpheinHein @GM come on https://t.co/w9BholVYAG https://t.co/44xTJhDNQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[5:49 to play, Andover Central with a narrow 46-45 lead on Maize South. I’d say this game is living up to its expections, ya? #CatchItKansas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryxKenshin hello big fan here’s a scary story I hope you like it #sss #SpookyScarySunday #friendshipismagic [SFM… https://t.co/EV0oIyslPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he walked out of the court house. Wasn’t he told the 1st time not to talk about his investigation. I thought th… https://t.co/S7wT63xFUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laceylett @Rafizzy07 @stevejkfor @EnergyFC Awesome meeting you as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd place match — 285 #9 Lear Quinton, SCA (NE-1, 43-7, Jr.) #3 Jalen Stephens, Meyersdale (SW-3, 40-5, So.)  Quint… https://t.co/lJ0iThOR65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatly saddened about Ed Bickert’s passing. One of the giants of jazz guitar and an artist that cultivated a uniqu… https://t.co/qQ3xtBsebt]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the last tweet said (whoever made these prices is an embarrassing late millennial), I’ll still play along:  PG… https://t.co/WpjCZTxp1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good examples of market failures. We just need to make sure the gov intervention is as effective as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback. @DaveyFitness @Devine__Trevor @carsondevine28 https://t.co/521mTgMXSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonGOHubNet Mostly wish there was new Pokémon in the wild, more than one or two at a time, getting boring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling. (@ Arlo NoMad - @arlohotels in New York, NY) https://t.co/T7B2Xh2Ook]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJamesofDfs If you watched basketball outside of the Lakers you’d know Shamet will be in an all-rookie team thi… https://t.co/qJMxHmUeC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build the wall.  And then Americans and immigrants can join in destroying such wall. It will create a shared sense… https://t.co/WlBfdzXdVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneysendall Oh, that sounds like fun! Where are you going? (You can DM in response if you prefer)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshallSbar I want to follow all #Resistance #resist #Resisters and be followed. Let's start our own 3rd party and take our country back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to take selfie in the gym and phone felt like it weighted 100 pounds....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@137pm @garyvee I would ask him if there is anything that I could do for him. He’s done more than enough for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the best days to explore #thebackyard #UpperBidwellPark #ThisIsChico #hiking #ChicoCa #chicocalifornia https://t.co/kHxgNdMba8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThoughFortheDay — #The best view comes after the hardest climb.” #GoodMorningAlabama #amnewsers #EarlyRisersClub #MondayMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It took you 50 years to get there.  Glad you made it in time to serve your country. #CommanderBoneSpurs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicwillow @Jim_Jordan @JudgeJeanine @seanhannity @dbongino @DiamondandSilk came real close]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickMcGillTV @CBS4Indy Congratulations bro!!! Saw a desk gig coming YOURE THAT good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adelauchida Everything ... including take over the world https://t.co/kRYaJOnQ7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampisHere79 @theaceofspaeder The hard nose defense and no fouls is such a myth lol. The game was obviously more… https://t.co/0fP2PfpYWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SammyCal00 @mareybands @Ereeka_xo LMFAOOO YOO! A whole fucking mood bro.. I meannnnn I was with a girl for 5 years - DONT SLEEP! 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CurbedAtlanta. Does 371 E Paces Ferry Rd NE even have any tenants in it? Interesting days in Buckhead Village. https://t.co/vKnJAASted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are 8 big flaws in the new background check bill. https://t.co/1vl11cZcrZ via @AmySwearer @DailySignal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Westfield Indiana is a fantastic place to make your next corporate move and there are a lot of people that would lo… https://t.co/txWtpDIZfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God, I'm asking that you continue to bless ALL sober homes, mental health facilities, soup kitchens, homeless… https://t.co/zjtpcYTMJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHUTDOWNDEPART1 @BamaDude77 @drboycewatkins1 So Watkins daughter is a sellout too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finish line with @RIPpool97 #rundisney #enchated10k @ Walt Disney World https://t.co/CHh0c8OyxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buzzFLYYyear Oh nahhhhh not at all. I wouldn’t be able to come up with the words to explain myself after]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moderately dry with a nice roast - Drinking a Luscious by @alchemistbeer @ Parfu's Place  — https://t.co/RczTQN9mWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSj_Verdadero @L28Justin @Harold_1991tron @SeanSchemmel @thejbblanc Best complement for a voice actor. Thank you very much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m in a pretty dark space mentally rn and hate thinking this way but i can’t do anything stupid or whatever becaus… https://t.co/stDl6gzPPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be adding #VIDEO to our show! All future episodes (11 on) will be available on #YouTube! Here’s a taste...… https://t.co/mIQhDXkgLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya me dormi; no se crean me la goa jalar y me duermo! https://t.co/e0H1wRVEbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So border patrol just asked me if I was a US citizen. And that’s all they asked. I said yes. They let me right thro… https://t.co/2tkOVl0ghT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitney_cat I am following You. Please follow back. Thanks  Yep,#Jerry_Hyde #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1alebey @CrucesSunNews Our legislators don't seem to care about the Constitution!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AllWeNeedIsLoveAnd a magical box of replenishing chocolates https://t.co/4O5rrjSp0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[PG13 is unreal when he is locked in. Hoping Hayward can follow in his footsteps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a MODish by @CWBrewCo @ K-1 Beer &amp; Wine — https://t.co/rCquWfle82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolTV Da la impresión que ustedes se la tienen dedicada a EMELEC, pues la semana pasada pasaron en diferido el par… https://t.co/trymDag61v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@priaribi All @ira talks about is Equinox so maybe you two should start a gym?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSamperO Y el expresidente de la farc santos  que dice. Co su nuevo mejor amigo su MADURO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half: North 34, Euclid 32  Destiny Leo 15 points, Abby Carter 13 for North. Constance Chaplin 13 points and 11 rebounds for Euclid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A cheaper, quicker approach to social-emotional learning? via @hechingerreport https://t.co/VjEtXich5J #SEL #4CS… https://t.co/zpNsy9PtLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pushing yourself to accomplish more day in and day out is great; but at what cost? If you’re not bringing your A-ga… https://t.co/NNDDapW3UC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump 🤣🤣🤣.SEC.ADVISORS JOHN BOLTON SAID THE MEETING WITH KIM JUNG UN WAS GOOD.*HE DIDNT MAKE A BAD DEAL.*WHA… https://t.co/QZB7hP8MQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillgray Ive come to the conclusion a majority of the Russian population is proficient in some form of martial ar… https://t.co/b9WuyNdTy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill HOW is it premature? Trump has committed all of the "high crimes and misdemeanors." With the exception of drunkenness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be clear, the claim that the AUMF covers Iran is incredibly _weak_, as @BobbyChesney and I have explained on the… https://t.co/VwarJCt7TR]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is too interested in these wolves hunting for prey. He better not get any bright ideas when I’m sleeping 👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikelucas64 @JohnKiriakou @DefendAssange @xychelsea What petty, shallow pieces of shit there are in this thread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte Park’s (1918–2010) important contribution to the Abstract Expressionist movement during its early years h… https://t.co/VbJSCoi16z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone on House Hunters: "There's not enough space for entertaining."  Me: "Can I dig a moat and build a wall?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joseph_DeVries @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump I'm from the NYC-metro area. Believe me when I say we DID see through h… https://t.co/oTZ05HvyX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euniceoalbarran @Conacyt_MX @elnocturno @arnemx @CarlosTorresF_ @ConsultaPara @ferbelaunzaran @MuertosDelPeje… https://t.co/HfxyHzzZeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorPein I agree. I just wonder how long that will take for those individuals to be in a position to truly influ… https://t.co/uA4p2aWnSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SierraWritesYA I voted for you to finish your revisions but I also want to say, yes!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lifting of U.S. sanctions on Russian #aluminium producer @UC_RUSAL and the economic slowdown due to US governme… https://t.co/nLtf51t8QU]]></document></documents></author>