<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DaveSolomon72 @NHHouseofReps Good thing @MomsDemand doesn't get freaked out about men in pearls the way they do ab… https://t.co/OZByYAQ9cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you express yourself and they think you tryna argue. https://t.co/h9OHeZVdRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Inventors in action #projectbasedlearning #shinestrong #MPSGreatThings @MrsVerdura @MilfordSchools https://t.co/rUeeXbw7HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtomWillard Sick with what? Stomach flu = use the chapstick. Common cold = the popcorn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe it was because I was with my mom but that server who gave me the free fries was just extra kind. And didn’t n… https://t.co/QdvvGHWIDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taniagroe @StormHourMark @StormHour @ThePhotoHour @BBCEarth Wonderful 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Are you high?  We have no emergency.  Crackhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SALUTETRUMP @PowerTaking @wrenchhead2977 @AbbieRaeMurphy @vision835 @dukefanforlife @bamabeckygirl @billarcia… https://t.co/Ud1vWp33za]]></document><document><![CDATA[What better excuse to unearth my favorite childhood photo than @GrandCanyonNPS’s 100th birthday?! https://t.co/WSmHHQVtZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[So today it's beautiful out but yesterday was cold and rainy and a homeless man called me crazy as I walked by in a… https://t.co/1qrMAhMng8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afonay1 Could you send me the link again ?my phone is going berserk and I loose all my messages]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuhFreezePeach @YousefMunayyer @jonathanchait Then why did she think AIPAC was more loyal to another country than… https://t.co/6NmpN3hMaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really!! Can’t wait til Friday!!!  @duane_piper @HunterBros @jessmoskaluke @paulbrandt @HIGHVALLEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traceyuyen @DrHSpring19 @traceyuyen You would like Slack if you do many activities with work and school in teams o… https://t.co/CDrHmNtCLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know much about wrestling, but this is kind of exciting! #readytorumble #canyousmellwhattherockiscooking  W… https://t.co/9cSDtERwll]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so cool how Tyler and Josh can remember who their fans are that go to their shows alot like no other celebrity… https://t.co/hzZVRDb6yn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen You're one cold bitch. How could you not know you would traumatize a child ripped from their parents an… https://t.co/WnNJNFxbwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitfordBradley @BarackObama As it happens, I’m sick in bed watching The West Wing reruns. I so see you as Josh Ly… https://t.co/xQymxhmRBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only leftists should embrace having zero children ... including this AOC nutjobs. It would make me feel much better… https://t.co/9VaA79fFdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por qué andas* dandole tanta importancia a esos comentarios necios? Les estás dando lo que están buscando, Patricia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Coal is a Dying Industry.  Let It #STAY dead!!  https://t.co/263qmqobjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Siberian Monkey Godddess awaits!  *Photo by lubaphotopro   The Chaplin plays @birdlandjazz  on 02/21/19@7pm(doo… https://t.co/OvvBnslS0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO A LOS ZOOLÓGICOS! NO Y NO VISITAR ESA CARCEL DE ANIMALES Q NO PIDIERON  ESTAR AHÍ! NO VISITEN MÁS ESOS MALDITOS… https://t.co/LOibflytJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instructions when handed my baby: zero Instructions when purchased a dog nail file: https://t.co/5TajWXcjem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burgatron13 Might even be #1 at the pace it’s going https://t.co/8J2n4h5zvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laster isn’t playing games today, 30pts already, more than doubling his previous season high of 13 😯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I owe my entire vocabulary to 6th grade spelling &amp; 7th grade wordly wise]]></document><document><![CDATA[how is it that lakeside can’t even scream for their team.. but the other teams can scream some messed up stuff.. so… https://t.co/N2CbBIr3l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaas Queen! @StaceyPlaskett “I’ve also got work to do. Democrats can walk and chew gum at the same time.” https://t.co/Y4sfQam78J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOHUSKIESWOOOOO @somuchwowswow @HuskyHockey48 I’m gonna need some plane tickets to participate in the shenanigans...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶☀️ Sun sun sun here it comes 🌞🎶 @ Lady Bird Lake https://t.co/vtvvJVvJoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally agree with your hubs  about Luke.... but  I really think it was a pretty good description if you wanted t… https://t.co/In6eUXpf0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight. 2/19. Best Western in Aquia. Group starts at 8pm. I’ll be posting vids and pics from my room. Dm or reply… https://t.co/Zh4TeRSFAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to have a hard time editing this game tonight-too many great highlights! Williamsport at Oakdale! @WDVMSports https://t.co/rUsTE2Y4MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgusting-your wives children mothers must be so proud... and your constituents? All men? I hope this is your swan… https://t.co/321u2Yti9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Saving energy going forward is going to make a big difference in the world.” Thanks @JT_Marcinkowski… https://t.co/jELTuEoyX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah your right the same system saying that you need mental awareness I think she may be right about that by the way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StylusPub @drbeckymartinez and I are thrilled to add to the #ClassIdentity literature and we are grateful to the 2… https://t.co/KgXbkVCSEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t done anything in months and don’t have the energy to so my birthday I’m looking forward to getting out of my house by force]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitleisner Maybe they make a https://t.co/Ow4Z6sOvPU dating site, you better since up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackjonesbabe A leader on gun control for people in Vermont. Because everyone knows that guns in Vermont are diffe… https://t.co/YtzHgQL6MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy, has yours truly got plans as a writer; Find out more at this link right here: https://t.co/ENeE8mJb4p… https://t.co/I6ViM1opha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with the birthday gurllll @maggievlaine &amp; pops at @jtimberlake @ Staples Center https://t.co/ITj2yhPqTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Caroline you need a little more time  I was born in the new place  My age was just wondering if y’all ha… https://t.co/e1vWvjd8CR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes my heart sing... truly. @sesamestreet @SesameWorkshop @PaulSimonMusic Sesame Street: Paul Simon Sings Me… https://t.co/twR44eLXoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up next Thursday! 🎺 #PrivateWax presents live jazz at @cellardoor101 in #DowntownVisalia with The Sierra Pro… https://t.co/IwAQsSDcUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The socialist movement is pushing for Bernie Sanders as the ideal candidate. Has ANYONE brought up… https://t.co/j1lXfNOxS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did anyone else clap at the tele after Lady Gaga &amp; Bradley Cooper's performance? I sure did 👏🏽❤️… https://t.co/eZdSfiCSG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Newyorkers  They live with high taxes, high cost of living, killing babies, congestion, liberals, filth and bad we… https://t.co/Srr7dg5YU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smirk for you. my two favorite gals EVER, hands down. says the dork who reread the smithsonian book of... https://t.co/Hdft8yT8Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickJagger Christopher would wake me before 6am and then after 3 just to talk. Dave started recently but I look at… https://t.co/t6BAYmBKUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tmprowell Many generations have been vaccinated and NO ISSUES . Non vaccinators are a danger to newborns , low imm… https://t.co/fnm3bcrtZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our budget is around one million doll-. CLICK. Off. That's as realistic as the Kardashians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the chances people leave me alone at work today.. I’ve only been gone a week..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCannSportsLaw Nice to know it’s not just Cleveland who hates the Dolans. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a midget on tinder.....i don’t think I’ve ever been this happy before 10:00😂, it’s gonna be a good day💀.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rreagles20 Always, even the past few seasons when the ballpark was empty. https://t.co/IHr8YcyFNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to this weirdo who always wants to match with me. Good thing I’m just as big of a weirdo. ❤️… https://t.co/DZVYpWfiDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helping develop young minds with @CREWHouston1 volunteers showing the career opportunities in #commercialrealestate… https://t.co/S7iGFUb5I6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#first #tulip to bloom #2019 #red #bloom #vibrant #color #japanese #luckycat  #welcomingspring Maneki-Neko Welcomin… https://t.co/Z69VHcYPau]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom swears I’m a weed head...this woman bought me edibles for my birthday 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celkin486 @kennnneddyyy Lmfao just stfu. You sound so ignorant. Hah bye 👐🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it has begun! @JulianCastro meeting with a mostly Hispanic crowd in east Las Vegas. Says he is running for pres… https://t.co/IYueDX5bB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PburgAthletics Good Morning! I can’t keep up w all of these tweets! It’s great to be a Jacket! #GoJackets #JacketPride 🐝💪🏻💥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Snake oil salesman... your going down with that POS Pence. Bye bye Donnie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RivalDiaz V happy you’re feeling better! Can’t wait to watch y’all slap on stage Friday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 How juvenile some men can be. Shows they are at war with women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearpod Transform 2019 Keynote Speaker  #nearpod @BrowardSTEM @nearpod @Glades_MS https://t.co/pXEwbpLKSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was made from Gods blood but Im not God. We do have some of Gods gifts (dont kid yourself) we can create as well… https://t.co/c8N2WbAL0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cold got me up af lol someone dm me their number so we can play iMessage games 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night...Happy Birthday @FloydMayweather #Oscars2019 #psalm23 https://t.co/0Is1Geo66q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CEREALKILL3R @akajeck614 @iamcarlmatthew @duckking2015 Lemme join the party https://t.co/Bhs4ZhFoGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunbabe08 The way he moves for  a man his size kind of defies  the laws of physics😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackson and Brooks both currently ranked in the top 5 of all freshman triple jumpers in IL. https://t.co/q0qdiz12Le]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ephoustonbill @rangercreek @RealBMaxwell @PerzellBrewing @badhopper @qblacklock @BPlohocky @OkiTimes @cedarflats… https://t.co/bMrP4ZrATv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having a horrible day. I let negativity take me and now I’m trapped lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@W_Penn_Power crews replacing a broken crossarm in Freeport. They’re making steady progress today getting customer… https://t.co/BSX80uKx7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[А ещё есть oz (ounces), и они бывают fluid (для измерения объема) и обычные, похожие на граммы. На фотокарточках 2… https://t.co/s8xkCQGWjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dropped off at @FlyTPA around 4:45, at my gate 10 mins later.  That’s that ish I like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overturehes @pinkpolaroidgrl This is the absolute fucking hottest thing he EVER did ! That suit , his butt , we go… https://t.co/KUpweEdbgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA my cat Bianca enjoyed watching the #WestminsterDogShow...while my dog slept through it😂 https://t.co/kzZh7rVusS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brooklynmarie @politico That already happened over a month ago. Keep up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alfre Woodard's new movie, "Juanita," made me think about how much women (particularly black women) need and deserv… https://t.co/PV4AF3LBZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_SaraMarie @Uber Yeah, he also said something to the effect of "women should keep their legs together so they do… https://t.co/XS6iTDJEsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlimShiny82 Good to here. Winter weather makes the best resting weather. https://t.co/XBI67BfECT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is sweet, love is kind.  Distance is mean, distance is Satan❤️ https://t.co/I3gnVp80BM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need people in my damn family to stop writing my name as “Loren”. People who have known me for 30 years still write “Loren”. Stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoneyBadgerWins @mokinenuzo My 7 year old was very clear in the understanding that he was abused, and has been abl… https://t.co/wbS3xgSzUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Much gratitude to Melissa Connolly at @RepJerryNadler, who took the time to meet with us today. Thank you to the Co… https://t.co/ErqeS4IReL]]></document><document><![CDATA[AC/DC - Walk All Over You (Official Video) https://t.co/stRFS0aZsi via @YouTube @9Artemi  You been holding out on u… https://t.co/fPHEzlQbLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoesGonnaTweetU It's a non-holiday. My husband/partner and I didn't do anything special. Just our normal daily rou… https://t.co/iXdRForGtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m out here with lips like these and not sucking ANY dick? Cruel https://t.co/3A4ntNkrQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/3DTbRh7G7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody’s excited about his road trip. #olshep @ Chesapeake, Virginia https://t.co/C1GMPQWF3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@averagejaypapi It is bananas. If we talk strictly W/L column (I’ll leave personal feelings aside on this one)....… https://t.co/zPApYms4E7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it still winter!?? In Florida yes @ Neptune Beach, Florida https://t.co/y48J8hGVu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the YMCA Auction last night. A great time, fun peeps, delicious dinner for a great cause.  . . .… https://t.co/LY7lGEilea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 There are many reasons for mental health struggles. They are real, they are caused by the desperation p… https://t.co/CUoFi2M3yT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConwayRanch @DRFLivingston Name sounds so familiar. Silver charm I knew of. Back then only paid attention to NYRA tracks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSasse thank you Senator for standing tall, holding firm and not being afraid to confront the issues regarding a… https://t.co/9OAxjqxjkW]]></document></documents></author>