<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Nicholeecarteer honestly thats what i thought too..... yet here we are 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyxtopher @SenFeinstein keep listening to others. The world is full of great diversity and you will need allies… https://t.co/uf9gvEX1sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMDillo5 @GodsBurnerAcct Well, Kevin should worry you as well. He has been disappointing as of late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, is this real??? Also watch #FyreFestival on Netflix if you haven't yet....it is fascinating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickibroz but im like almost positive i had some of those on my phone😂😂😂 im just so confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get out those bunny ears 🐰 &amp; send in all those adorable photos of your fur babies! #bunnytryouts https://t.co/RFdysNUnVQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican #Gerrymandering has kept state legislatures #under GOP lock and key for #FAR too long.  Please CHIP IN t… https://t.co/4fOKW17pzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James25866833 @taybaby_45 @KamalaHarris About not getting a mortgage on $12,000 a year?  Can’t imagine why not...]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i was in 2nd grade i got to meet the cheetah girls....that’s it....just had to brag about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[What about whites who call the police on black people for no apparent reason - do they deserve punishment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been such a long time since I’ve seen someone hail a cab, I straight up thought this lady was doing a nazi sal… https://t.co/EIFWp3tcTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Willy Wonka have an entire room of candy if he never had guests? Was it put together solely for the tour? Was it r&amp;d?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adrian_Butler13 @twistandshout1 @TandS_Diamonds https://t.co/iCQGt7bxeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how my country is looking right now. Just like a episode of the walking dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever missed someone so much it literally physically hurts? I’ve had a huge amount of loss is the last 18mo… https://t.co/cngn09x0aM]]></document><document><![CDATA[ppl literally try to make up excuses of why they’re a shitty ass person like we see through it....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikaeladorrell literally. my roommates gonna be out of town this weekend i’m terrified]]></document><document><![CDATA[The energy, enthusiasm, and dedication of @MomsDemand volunteers is unmatched. We will continue to show up year aft… https://t.co/D2vEGhUitU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loudlearning @CoachJRidge @_ShondaHensley @Katrina82677276 Don’t leave yourself off this list, Katrina! You are a true champion for kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fantasy #askedandanswered #livingsingle #soulmatetosomebody #neversettle #love #travel #fiftyandfabulous… https://t.co/kuuKbQEVgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicalibrarian Nice, perk of living in a big city: getting all the limited release films]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity I guess the left is ok w women being gagged and tied up to b sold and children being smuggled yes thro… https://t.co/Zgk6rJrMct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can’t we just say that the government who has been lax in regulating for people’s safety for decades owes us Me… https://t.co/r0Jkogl4HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart This guy has spoken of Cohen and now of Mueller. The gag order has never been in place with him. He needs to be incarcerated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay #BeFearless #BeYOU https://t.co/JOglWRRG97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this guy kidding me! He should be locked up and properties seized . He costs Americans millions !]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's enough in here to make it clear we are messing up the noctural world for wildlife, incl mammals.  https://t.co/c2q3h0phHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe needs to visit a santera she needs a cleaning . My sis lost in the sauce .]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖Con Sue Photography and Design💋  💝Like our photos...Follow our IG 💖  ❤️This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/u1WR4alcAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok will I want to train you how to remote view here so others can pratice if they are bored enough to try something… https://t.co/XH7VfxxVuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quote Trump may come to regret: 'I didn't need to do this' https://t.co/bgGYVraj0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is ridiculous.  How can you give a movie a negative review before it's even out??  #CaptainMarvel https://t.co/S7Ay6CxeWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: From the first arriving crew, to dispatchers, a NEWLY UNCOVERED REPORT SHOWS: Crew was inexperienced, and mo… https://t.co/LFVXn9xOrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dorieturnernolt @EWAEmily I will be asleep before the serious awards but right now it's me, popcorn and the red carpet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarGoshTV  Hey Omar can you help find the person/people responsible for animal cruelty? Here's the link to the ar… https://t.co/DG6i9YxxDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKabakoff @PaulHook_em @TuckerCarlson My response to you is “Look who’s talking.” Your party is going to shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Discover the most mind-blowing facts out there! https://t.co/6uY0BAvNij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like my universe is off centered, not sure if my cosmic destiny has recently changed but I feel like I’m en… https://t.co/8iFavr5VB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaYCarr I was! 4 weeks early. Also umbilical cord was too short so I came out blue from lack of oxygen. Probabl… https://t.co/A09sXZ4jzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AmazingVideo by @ProjectOsmosis re bringing #DesignThinking to young men in Chicago where "violence is a natural b… https://t.co/hYpSF1IqOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope that anyone who reads my tweets realizes that they’re useally ironic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scattered Showers?! You know what. Is that the exit to the left? Cause... 🚶🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their punished if they watch anything that denies Scientology and that’s how they control their people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every single school I've worked at, after a deadline (grades, attendance, fill out a survey) an email goes out to t… https://t.co/fyMCJnBBcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MyFavMurder for such a fun night out! I had an awesome time, you ladies are hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang cute. Awesome and/or hilarious pictures involving dogs (and cats!) rocking their cones of shame - 24 of...… https://t.co/ZB5E8n9jDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You harrassed a good man, President Obama. You lied. Spread rumors about birtherism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this occupied home in #Durham! Open house this weekend at 8020 Rosemont with @theperrygroupnc… https://t.co/ffKgpe0UP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[May you be thought of often. Remembered without question.  And loved without doubt. https://t.co/W1HbUtERPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone should have their confirmation # - contact me if you don’t- we will take team photo in new blue jersey on… https://t.co/rMUq8stQNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Becca has one drink at dinner. Now her cheeks are numb and tongue is now numb. And now she is home in the chair rubbing her tongue! 🙈🙈🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like we taught men to control their tongue and manners eh??   Y'all must be terrible students.  Tf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zappos @danlapidus @SeanRiley026 @JenniferNatalie @dylanparks @NikiKirschner That too!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tadethompson @RobGMacfarlane @GrahamMoonieD I will order your book today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeToyaLuckett You are awesome in your deceitful role, on "Greenleaf!" Kudos to you! 😍❤ What kind of red reptilian… https://t.co/423C3Xgp64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodikantor @AOC Well, no one living TODAY was a slave. Your Grandma was a SURVIVOR. BIG difference!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow we are headed with our students from @UVUcomm to visit @Janedeals to learn about partnerships in online… https://t.co/EQ4QAV7G8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @KamalaHarris SO sick of all the Dems using all the same talking points - do they not have any ORIGINAL ideas ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do boys start conversations and then just stop talking to you? https://t.co/rMBZHpZXof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset on Lake Wellington #lovelakewellington @wellingtonflgov wellingtonflrec @ Wellington Community Center https://t.co/zWLYTJ0kIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[They look like they are ready to kick some ass! 💙 https://t.co/S6TL6QbdMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This full moon got me fucked up the last couple of days. https://t.co/Z7WvpNwnfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC They won’t because they rather create fear among us! She is the picture of the fear and hate ghost they create… https://t.co/f5N14TUd3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man who confronted 2 men breaking into cars outside All Nations Church in SW Atl is recovering from graze wound thi… https://t.co/cegXThU5BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s actually amazing people at th border don’t want their property confiscated for a wall tht can be tunneled unde… https://t.co/AlBP5H0awP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillCarter13 Whenever I leave, I just remember that I’m going back the next weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woahitsanjelica Can you send me the link to your invite for the wedding so I can get the details.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le discours du trône n'a consacré que 20 min au sujet des emplois en Colombie-Britannique note ⁦@Wilkinson4BC⁩… https://t.co/a61iNqpMyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nyotengu is so elegant! 💕 @DOATEC_OFFICIAL #DOA6 #DeadOrAlive6 https://t.co/LcnkTNdyrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my mom would learn but you cant help someone that doesnt want to help themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprise b*tch, bet you thought you’d seen the last of me - Madison Montgomery AHS 🔮 @ Buckner Mansion https://t.co/EEL9NbpesD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddiMellencamp I don't understand how this was a setup. Dorit did what she did which was wrong! Lisa Rinna is try… https://t.co/4OGh0ftZRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind skiing the Saint Lawrence. #frozenriver #winter #ice #outdoors #canada #nature @ Montreal, Quebec https://t.co/THcDghPiI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me before vs me after he says I’m cute &gt;.&lt; https://t.co/YilhMIFYGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRobotDesign @realDonaldTrump No one is with you # the world will come to an end for silly 😜 Democrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did @chrislhayes just say he couldn’t tell the difference of which Castro brother? @MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skaye Real talk. The business model is great, they have low-overhead and a decent product. Their marketing strateg… https://t.co/HbOtBf7vnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_business_ Lebron this season trying to play with the young core https://t.co/mL3bWDdbdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cranky2Sticker @cliett_eric No focals for this Daddy bc he doesn’t want them (yet) lol. But he will be getting a n… https://t.co/vvOTfjOn6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Within the first two aisles of @hm I mentally spent $500, and wanted to donate 99% of my current closet to their… https://t.co/m2NORw7sWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repost from my hacked account, I’m going to post some this week, just trying to get them all up🎉   . . . . . . . .… https://t.co/fC3gKGUh9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I literally love Schitt’s Creek so much I am very worried for my well-being when I finish the seasons available on Netflix.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedAutosport @GuyCosmo @PByrneRacing @SYoluc @AsianLMS I am just gutted for the team. So sorry! 😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching last night's Kings vs Canes game.. that 1st Hamilton goal.. Dion Phaneuf was involved in keeping Saku on t… https://t.co/QYMqmCTx2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump @LindseyGrahamSC Lindsey Lindsey you really cant make up your mind.  Its best to get out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“can we take a moment to realize that i went to sheetz at 130 in the morning to get PODS” phATTTT MOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The finishing touch... • • • #myptofview #ceviche #finishingtouches @ Oyamel Cocina Mexicana https://t.co/wXtwsnxSBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we make this kid the next Gavin. He’s always so pressed about something]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess that’s just something. I have to learn to deal with considering there’s no going back 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[What really is the MAC Cosmetics Fleur Real High-Light Powder? | THE MAK... https://t.co/a0jqSvM68A via @YouTube @BeautyNewsAus]]></document><document><![CDATA[▪️Black History Month Day 19▪️ William "Smokey" Robinson Jr. is an African American singer, songwriter, record prod… https://t.co/NjZvGHrUQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Patrons at Wallingford Public Library are learning digital and technical skills with the help of Creative Te… https://t.co/js3Z78lrHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulAtkinsonPDX Well, it'll be a while before you get to see her at home, but I agree!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexlmiller Yes, and I think very few of us have some ego-driven need to “be the founder”—we’d much rather join ot… https://t.co/LDOvEPYaZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wadeodom Which Stevie song should be on there? I’d also like to add Earth Wind &amp; Fire, September!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryGlassJr @RealJamesWoods It's a woman with a beard. https://t.co/8mapCr5IVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FromTheLabBench @NoomInc @CDCgov The Dept of Veterans Affairs has quite a few mobile apps that incorporate scienti… https://t.co/TdLxdKSGbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[contractors changed all of the lighting in my home and now everything is tinted yellow. energy efficient yes but no… https://t.co/l4ZGj3xY2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nomis97 @chefsymon Agreed has always been one of my favorite chefs to learn from. I loved watching him on ICA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noche Bohemia has the honor to present the singer, Jasmine Mejia. https://t.co/R0x1dAJykZ]]></document></documents></author>