<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Ben's House IPA by @TrueAnomalyBeer at @trueanomalybeer — https://t.co/PrO0fMCbXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fake teeth is such a struggle and none of y’all will understand this unless you have fake teeth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really am at a loss for words, not only for Darius but for the too many other losses, -40, that my dear friends h… https://t.co/Cz2C9hzDKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we focus on providing teachers support and building capacity positive outcomes follow. @MEMSPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvnSosa18 Fidel cacareo mucho sobre la igualdad socialista , sobre los terratenientes y los ricos explotadores, cu… https://t.co/9x6BGL4xXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to give back to the community but you fucking ams man are a real piece of work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socalaura @ARTISTstacy @realDonaldTrump BOSTON MEDIA STARTED AMERICA I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable… https://t.co/fSfDbJFiwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Nextluck12 @KelseyLee6 You just don’t understand what we got going on over here 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up on SNL - OMG  #BodegaCat @mulaney who can up with the skit? Reminds me of lobster skit]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there is a hockey god he will let Isaac Ratcliffe score his 50th tomorrow. At home. Against Kitchener.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out at The Boardwalk with My April and friends in our new home town area waiting for Madman's Lullaby who a… https://t.co/aTpxawu9a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in the middle of a lacrosse weather delay. I told the boys not to use balls in the host’s gym ... so they to… https://t.co/q3XfcNiie1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/l7d6YbwDKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET OUT THE WAY BROOK LOPEZ. YOU IN INGRAM’S POSTER!!!!!!!! #LakeShow https://t.co/BkT7iTrtS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HellachoppaH My nigga. They are hunting motherfuckas. N hanging em. Sheesh. That shit be dropping niggas. Those all bodies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Clara has some sort of barn door thing that's supposed to be a Walmart brand curtain of distraction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A normal trip from Fox 17 takes about 15 minutes to make it downtown to 17th District Court. Unfortunately due to a… https://t.co/a4xp48MeV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inb4chase Lol here’s a grumpy girl from this morning. Still waiting on the dna test unfortunately https://t.co/YdwWdUgt88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMaddenX @Real_RobRossi Lets have a bonfire and pay to have the shirt burned go for a worlds record give money… https://t.co/LUqXHgcsCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[6th match prediction: @SamoaJoe retains.  #WWEUnitedStatesTitle #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job, @CoachAJohnson and our Vikings 🏌️‍♂️ team on a great performance! #BackForeMore #VikingsGolf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing hits that spot on a warm Texas day like some ice cold #lonestarbeer @ Hudson Oaks, Texas https://t.co/opNVMgDJFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Journal_ESprott @UpstateTodaySC @mworsencroft @CCWDrafting got an Honorable mention]]></document><document><![CDATA[@34_91_16 @sundin434 Leaf fans we have so many there’s prolly as many dummies as there are Sens fans in Total.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He was supposed to go to show support.  Not to sign Bible's.  And that's another thing that bothers me.  Very disre… https://t.co/gkwDDIEIH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinerNabs49 @pattonoswalt You're amusing little dipshits, I'll give you that, like the Red Green version of Anonym… https://t.co/uOhBr6P6Vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess @Starbucks strips all its power outlets out of its stores to save money. Well, I guess I imagined wrong to work at a coffee shop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it before this regard to other athletes and I’ll say it again. Zion Williamson should do whatever makes h… https://t.co/gBseBxvOvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMarieBoothe @RealSaavedra I don't except the results of the 2008 election. We need a special prosecutor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pb6980 2019 cutz at hairtwothere @qdeezybcg #barberconnect #razorsharpcuts #hair2there #barberbeast… https://t.co/XRtgyQENyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonwrighteous @IamLaceyChabert @hallmarkchannel @britbristow @IamWillKemp Thank You 😊!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyMiko @rusty_pharris @MSNBC FYI. Not a teacher.  An adjunct professor of American Indian studies, history, poli sci, and pre law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RottenGolfer55 @politvidchannel She is in trouble in Maine, so she will vote no in a desperate attempt to keep her seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still got LIDS to make people "Flip their Lids".. FROM THE GROWN UPS to the kids I got KEMETIC KAPS  That will give… https://t.co/aJIrzr5HRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AcousticAri @JWrestlingV2 I was just like them in 2008 I went through a period where i hated @REALLiSAMARiE after… https://t.co/PYnV7XSflO]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does this make sense? So we should just let them murder gays on mass in these countries??? How can any gay alig… https://t.co/8XZUhYhhux]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh Fish News: Sergio Romo, Realmuto trade reactions, Spring Training https://t.co/teV3WUYW2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯facts!! All he does is lie like those 💩republicans let’s not forget their lying asses @CNN @BBCWorld @FoxNews… https://t.co/rhmdG3MMul]]></document><document><![CDATA[VIDEO: @disneybroadway stars Alton Fitzgerald White, Kissy Simmons, @ashleybrown9, and @Joshuajstrick sing a beauti… https://t.co/EmxYsyCcWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing designs over at annmarielafaucidesigns #bmanpittphotography2019 @ Liberty Hotel Boston https://t.co/bmxpFfuxff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBTA all the lights on the top level of braintree parking garage are out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamrank If the powers that be are smart they'll book Kofi to go over on Daniel Bryan at ’Mania]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will accept only unclassification of ALL materials related to this matter!!  Classification under a Democracy is… https://t.co/C9KFyNc56S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganRobertsMR @NaughtyDebi @Topnotchmilfs @SEX_Overlord @TheAmateurArmy @kymsw12 @Lox_21 @thesexpedition… https://t.co/BZkARZJ7fS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Oh Donny you are screwed. It’s obvious that you are scared. Your downfall will be slow and embarrassing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could go to mia once every month. N I’ll have a good time every trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“U equals U is true. #PrEP reduces HIV transmission by up to 95%. Theoretically if we could get everyone with HIV o… https://t.co/pKbmWOdASp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #ImpactMatters. Choking in from the Greater Toronto Area. How’s everyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsingLV @abc7Richard Seems setback requirements, proffers, and not allowing the ag tax exemption would do a long w… https://t.co/CfevAHPrn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ballinger @finchmachine dibs on the next project. Kevin must be a master craftsman for that price]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying to Indiana Thursday morning so with that being said... Casino on Thursday night?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday February 27 - MSNBC Daily:      Cohen on upcoming testimony: I look forward to telling 'the American peop… https://t.co/1PsDS78rfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out in Brverly Hills. #forgotmywallet #maybenexttime @ Rodeo Drive https://t.co/ep2LQFbjgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ADESA Charlotte - @adesaauction in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/xmwJ14mGNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[At @Donnie_Scorcese COOKING... . . . “ International Superstars,” out NOW on all platforms!!! .… https://t.co/Jf4ISbunzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordan rattled off that list as if he thought he was making a point for himself, but instead just solidified the De… https://t.co/f6Xp4RtY79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weareunited I’m really trying! That was this morning. Temperature is growing by the pass of the hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All quiet now, but Stillwater @ponygb and @WBLGirlsHoops will face off soon for the section 4AAAA title! #mshsl… https://t.co/RslBqFyN0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[45 Priests Accused Of Sexual Abuse Named By Diocese. Satan used these weak men to help destroy Fathers true desire… https://t.co/7i3XvzQrkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge Did sanders try to take credit for diversity. Sanders criticizes the diversity of the Democratic Part… https://t.co/G2kYCBuzTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinerbocker @Mikehomeseller @WilliamMarquar8 @dawizzurd @titletownusa73 @jeffsnyder72 @allensm10514668… https://t.co/eopKzlhFY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you need advice on... Leadership? Parenting? Talent development? Cue Tony Hawk + daughter + first drop-in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters @EmanuelGoldste4 The Dems are done, you just don’t know it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bearcub712 He was specifically asked about smal market teams.  The Cubs have the 2nd highest payroll in baseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsidePackSport @WillBrinson @JamesCurle @slackzac Sure, we might not have gotten a better shot. But out of a time… https://t.co/t1CyIdP3bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ketamine_coffee @officialdrk12 @PERTConsortium Seen on Twitter over the years. Been posted by @EM_RESUS before and… https://t.co/ANhTlnxv8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino HOW MUCH?? IS ""TOO MUCH""???  WHEN DO YOU THINK?? PEOPLE OF PATRIOTISM?? WILL FINALY BE? ""PUSHED TOO FA… https://t.co/Wt9I74IGke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nnnnnicolas @twiNZnyc @jbc30 Well, they can’t be mythical since I grew up in them, but nice try. Never heard of Tr… https://t.co/JgyNyUzfKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileHighKyle27 Exactly. Paid a bill for Verizon and switched banks. Verizon claims they never received the payment… https://t.co/Hcry6YZEQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were honored to have you with us and learn more about your priorities to strengthen our state, @RobertRivas_CA .… https://t.co/9ppRQyMFxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best Lobster🦞 rolls I have ever had the privy to taste #lukeslobsterroll #lukeslobsterbethesda #epiceats… https://t.co/RJNVYRl4ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WxmanFranz If we get snow from all 3 of these events lock it in. March is new winter haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows makes Jesse Helms look like a choir boy. #MarkMeadowsIsARacist but then again #WeAreAllRacist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpmckenna Look, let’s check out the 4 hr long Director’s Cut before we jump to that conclusion...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was stationed there in the mid 70's and you nailed it as a shit hole! Worst duty station ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyTmcg Do you need me to validate this post?  *Ducks, covers, runs like hell screaming how he really does take yo… https://t.co/tegpmRs4I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar is no antisemite so leave her alone Everone needs to face  facts that UN has condemned Israel for human rights… https://t.co/0wY0P93iMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoschonJ This is only the beginning man, and your statement also applies to your teammates. They see the hunger in… https://t.co/SWvwzSDN0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Roy High in Ogden, Utah  to BYU. Watched him as a Cougar and it seemed impossible for anybody to stop him.  Ar… https://t.co/9GCOLGC1sR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get all the latest Airdrop and bounty links here:  1. https://t.co/Ypefjyavjp 2. https://t.co/CL6sIuVxBV 3.… https://t.co/Vz7Zl0KP0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we don’t have enough money to continue to fund the 9/11 victim fund but we can find the money to build a concret… https://t.co/Fr7r20PS1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I thought the economy was great. The best ever. Hmm you are lying about 1 or the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, no tea, no shade, but I've dated at least two people that were very involved in theater and let me just say, th… https://t.co/mw9nNbJtZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed is the man who remains steadfast under trial-for when he has stood the test he will receive the crown of li… https://t.co/CK6p68vnMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordonkeith about yesterday’s show, just now hearing: do you really experience often restaurants with music so lou… https://t.co/QlInJF61Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You never know when a moment and a few sincere words can have an impact on a life.” -Zig ZIglar #Communication… https://t.co/hqbaHR48fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanRiccaboni It should be fun when the Phillies come play my Mets and vice versa.  I feel the the rivalry is going to get started again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan4VT @Strohsahl @coolbreeze024 Truthfully it needs either by Buzz or Ham...  Noles were picked 7th in ACC prese… https://t.co/uRRfxlN7Do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Byron, Adam knows he is going to be removed from Congress. Panic in DC is why we the people elected Trump. He is tr… https://t.co/t5eRyBlD0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayfordyoung Thad was the worst ejection I have ever seen wtf I’m so pissed 😡😡😡😡 I love u Trae Young #Sooners #BoomerSooner]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even remember from the top of my head majority of the women I had sex with. https://t.co/ZfqgmEeejr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Framingham Commuter Rail Parking lot is full today just as the p508 leaves the station #FraminghamParking https://t.co/JzHT5Aq0eS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any kind of criticism gets attention. No criticism gets little or no attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylamb8 So what your saying is Lebron probably was better off staying in Cleveland 🤔?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @gatewaypundit Stupid is as stupid does! Derangement syndrome struck again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobHarig If nothing is said,no penalty. And forcing every ball to be marked would slow down the game even further.… https://t.co/axSp51ENLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HughesSarge Irrelevant if your cost of labor is zero. I’ll bet those were trafficked here and now working to payof… https://t.co/nt8Q3QeRpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamaica Center with a line full@of cold, pissed off would be riders.  Any real reason behind the no show bus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[From left to right.. Healey, Spike and Piper. They LOVE this food. #raw #dogfood #carnivore https://t.co/3w8ZZZwbLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far, not missing a host for #Oscars But acceptance speeches still need editing.]]></document></documents></author>