<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ross_milu @MissAnna_Lee @theNatalieMars @tsNadialove @TS_KimberLee @missannakatt @The_amyjane_ God damn honey, thi… https://t.co/ppywPK5orc]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Cut fiber optic cable knocks out Verizon to mid-Michigan https://t.co/5F7PrYuqCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Benefits of Playing Music Help Your Brain More Than Any Other Activity @johnrampton https://t.co/SA2woOhNT2 via @Inc]]></document><document><![CDATA[pisces are just ok bro !!! don’t let her tell you wrong! my bday following you ! :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:30 a.m. Penn State senior Emily Morrison plays a toss and trivia game during a THON history tour for dancers.… https://t.co/Ug2Un4WmuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a house with a fireplace like this 🔥 ❤️🥂 @ Red Onion Tavern https://t.co/QDQerpTiy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BVintheDro @Lmchristi1 @tammy_maga @Debleespecial @irshroz @JohnCane440 @RealSugarLily @DoreneA @bama_kirby1… https://t.co/9EKbD758uM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have reached out to another friend about it who I know would qualify but expecting a “no” for the same reasons. L… https://t.co/QU27KdunV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CortesSteve America was built on immigration and you have forgotten that. Where is your heart? Immigrants are peop… https://t.co/9sCsxzEKbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalShort Because Democrats never do and they just keep on spewing their hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@9l9_N If you wanna ignore what the man is holding it can be: 🥾🥾= 10   🧙🏻‍♀️=5    🔭🔭=4   🥾+🧙🏻‍♀️x🔭= 5+5x2 = 5+10=15… https://t.co/v9BMEAvqTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is such a comprehensive summary of people's qualms about each candidate. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedfunches @Phil_Lewis_ That meant she didn't give 2 fucks about him going off. Negro, please.🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Maintenance Technician - https://t.co/phjlJubsLP #FacilitiesMgmt #Franklin, IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really like this guy and be talk about two week tonight he really hurt me I thing he really like me but I a fool]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin hugged my dad before he left last night &amp; it was amazing to hear that my dad really appreciated that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see why older people thank God for their “right mind” and health and strength.  It is not promised.  Thank you God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone know how to report a fake tinder account using your pics and name ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JockinRonB Why do you always put the most absurd things on my timeline! What is this nonsense!? 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a hug, and someone to play with my hair or tickle my arm while my sick self falls asleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clairevhill Poppy still posing nicely for the camera, seems to be enjoying the walk. Hope it's warmer for you tomo… https://t.co/bKj1Pq4ORi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregClarkMusic That is what the research says. Why do we perpetuate this system?! Ugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If someone opens their mouth and bullshit falls out, don’t bite your tongue and step in it. Get a shovel and tell… https://t.co/2FGv5wG2Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[if ur tweet to retweet ratio is out of whack i don’t trust u ... u got any thoughts ????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReYesenia  Maybe if she was a bigger person she would stop Impersonating a famous voter from South Gate, Californi… https://t.co/0xF0QHg90z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Order Sel… https://t.co/7Nz0h3AfCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[almost got hit on a crosswalk bc someone’s grandma wasn’t paying attention :-) how’s ur day going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had Cheetos puffs for the first time in years and it was as awesome as I remembered! #nomnomnom]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really fucking wish my grandfather was still alive. i miss making him proud the most]]></document><document><![CDATA[@borrinet @jbj220 @krassenstein Hahaha is that an you can come up with? Calling me gullible? Facts please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabbed last year.  Public domain, at this point. Straight off of Google. I'd grab that⬇, b4 the trolls scrub it  o… https://t.co/CpONoJa5tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slowest Dominos! Order placed at 5:22 online and pizza still not ready smh @dominos  great service smh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessie092859463 @stillngam @HMiglino @BlueTsuni @JustKathyRay @gheetar @yolalindayola @putinsgay @DocHollywoodM… https://t.co/BO22pS5wQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoniDianne @AngelaMLWestmo  loved your session today #NearpodTransform   Can we get a student code for the differ… https://t.co/RoPvsmbVCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that idk anyone else who gets belittled by their mom quite the way I do, scares me &amp; makes me feel even worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the @PSBehrend Public Policy Fund and @lenasurzhko for all things #Brexit: https://t.co/G9xGOP5BVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m actually out of that phase of being a sad bitch and actually moving on and sticking to it.  About fucking time Shay lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieMaggie Don't forget using his own Company DecoLabels for all Signage and Printed Material in the Ontario Gov… https://t.co/KBTs5dffDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nenny21 @Lilajev @KookieBae26 @fuzzysweaterpjm @JessicaKostele3 @nicsit2003 @browneyed_nuna @Luscious206 @jkannie1… https://t.co/Pz9oFSLT7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmamacXRT @MaryLDixon @93XRT Doesn’t that mean you have to host the next fais do do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chick_in_kiev Michael Bloomberg is the man...and. if Joe Kennedy III weren't so paranoid he would be the man too.… https://t.co/sSMbu7G1Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Steve Irwin.  February 22. Your fans miss you too.    Steve Irwin’s 57th Birthday! #GoogleDoodle https://t.co/BT8fOLaWI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you don’t have to travel very far for a view that reminds you just how awesome Mother Nature is at pyrote… https://t.co/tEHbzCsxFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[GENTE EU TO RINDO IGUAL UMA LHAMA PQ ISSO AQUI ACABOU DE ACONTECER: PETER TAVA TENTANDO ME ANIMAR E PEDIU PRA ALEXA… https://t.co/Ypr403G6PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 It’s about time the republicans are furious. It has taken a long time to get to where most of the US ha… https://t.co/cMNXRanMY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deroy Murdock: Jussie Smollett 'attack' melts down as leftists self-immolate: @AOC @CNN @RepMaxineWaters @ABC… https://t.co/L2NrXuOBUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow the news will be about fast moving legislation proposing to tax fart cannons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marriage is a beautiful gift!!!! Choose to keep each other shining! #gn_massachusetts #gracenation#relationships… https://t.co/dNOq9bIo5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que flojera es tener que tener a gente hater en redes sociales por compromiso...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrscapshawbooks @seyabookfest @annbradenbooks Just got my copy today.  Can’t wait to get started!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you ever say no to a Roller Disco ?🎉 . . . #brooklyn #nyc #Disco #Houseofyes  #Saturdaynightfever @ House of YES https://t.co/p6q8SBojA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote about @gifedhockey and @tsamplinski for @GNN_Sports_: https://t.co/cvlif6jIP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get really frustrated, why should i put all this effort in if I get nothing back yah know?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bloggerstribe Hey tribe- I’m working on something.   Looking for song suggestions- songs with a message of inclusi… https://t.co/hFeADujDAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many to name. I'll say that I am particularly in awe of @LMariaRivera. That's been true since I first met her.… https://t.co/EeVt4DraOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to revolt! #alicebirch #thoughttheatre #actorslife @ Joshua Tree, California https://t.co/GVaJlhHGgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greeneyedbrahma Same. I feel like it’s bad for my mental &amp; physical health.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy buen dia #BuenLunes para tod@s, después de un fin de semana doloroso para el gremio de la comunicación y en lo personal impactante.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NelleBot @PeterClines Oddly, most of the people who commented seemed happy about this... But it is a nice machine and it does care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[one of my fave prepreggo pics, thank you for making me a mommy and giving me our forever valentine!!! 💘 https://t.co/5y85BLQvaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol when ever I hear a sick drop I always see drews bass face and it cracks me up every time 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Diego is a secular university although what the students believe individually is a matter of personal preference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A las mujeres intensas no le ponen los cachos... #LaReinaDelFlow #Netflix 🇨🇴🙋🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriInNC1 @PKY92941436 For sure.  I think most that are mostly quiet are really Trump supporters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope your summit went well ? Back home watching T.V and social media is a disgrace . They aren’t… https://t.co/tXdJ3ffzxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[just another casual Sunday in the Jasmine house https://t.co/HwVbI4v5U5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I clean up good 😂😁 #snacklife @ Rideau Curling Club https://t.co/7aq8zno5CU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is saying you’ll wake up early and do it in the morning and then hitting snooze and saying you’ll do it after… https://t.co/dVm6sGNVE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Double_L22 @Lakers @Bucks @Bucks just wanted to give you your present a little early 😉 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danbharris Good seeing you at the desk on a Monday! (No offense to George.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@H_Armer Seriously makes me sick how anyone could find this funny whatsoever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine, pizza, chips, chocolates. Ultimate cheat days out of my everyday cheat days. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History  February 23rd On this date in... 1967...A Congressional panel recommends public censure for Harle… https://t.co/55kZiPWe1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam heughan walking the carpet Credit to @HNewsSource @ Richland Center, Wisconsin https://t.co/ZZ3OWMNmnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@US4AfghanPeace @JuliaNesheiwat @StateDept @USEmbassyKabul @State_SCA Healthcare hid that humans have a secondary s… https://t.co/LnoFpHHUU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealjz24 @HunterHodies Last year everyone thought  the Caps were done when they went down 3-0 in playoff series… https://t.co/43DGwDnv7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllysonApsey @burgessdave @burgess_shelley @mradamwelcome @TaraMartinEDU @jdprickett Sounds super!!  Your own personal cheering section! 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sagreeney algae needs an ideal environment to grow, and you created the environment, without your pond then the al… https://t.co/qgtklIUHYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarely_corona @MelanyyoMelany The cutest boy 😍 https://t.co/raqkgVLLs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @Powersource36 His lawyer probably threatened to quit. He’s as power crazy as trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Shame on you Representative! To have Lynn Patton  stand up as if she is on the auction block was ap… https://t.co/32YuM5eLAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Let’s not worry about impeachment... let’s get him out of office!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Shape Corp.? We're hiring in #GrandHaven, MI! Click the link in our bio for details on this job and… https://t.co/kwDDsSj7gK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsJankord @MissBeckerjeck @TaraMartinEDU @burgessdave @casas_jimmy @gcouros Welcome!!! Follow @hayes_melisa… https://t.co/xvaV1JPGHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back waiting 2 years 4 bon… https://t.co/dkJU1FAreH]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing hurts like the sound of a new cody ko fan (who’s watched approx. 2 videos) saying “BARS” as if she discover… https://t.co/cBp1UxE8aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is going on? 21 horses dead now @santaanitapark 😞  https://t.co/OX2V72jbN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY DO I SPEND YEARS GROWING MY HAIR OUT AND THEN HAVE THE URGE TO CHOP IT ALL OFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome to see @MilesBridges getting some love from @terrellowens when we were rolling on Instagram Live at… https://t.co/eP7igW2Gqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lee Florida I can’t wait 😊 to get a glimpse of your Natures Paradise. 🌲 💐 🦅 🍎 I just want to see beautiful colors today.☝️😇🐶📝✍️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyPaws @Lukericardo @notcapnamerica Whew! I thought you were going to tell me I had gone too far! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesleepyspud He loves in our neighborhood and we’ve passed him on the street like 3 times 🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might take a hundred lifetimes to do But baby, I just wanna be good as you #upnorth #snowy @ North Dakota https://t.co/3beUKkX0nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoOneIsAboveLaw Well I know what I am going to do is.......BLOCK....THAT WILL GET YOU OFF MY THREAD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My childhood pup visited me in my dreams last night. He just wanted to hear me say “good boy” again 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrifying. Indicates Saudi’s knew their act of murdering Khashoggi was horrifying and did their best to conceal. M… https://t.co/UybnqoKHRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES! And his incredibly detailed voice references that influence his voice work and how he chose the Rocket Racoon… https://t.co/VTJXj4WdeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katieppierce @POETSorg @maggiesmithpoet First words I’d read this morning! My own fear-box is buzzing with your lines 🐝 🐝 🐝 🐝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well,history tells us there was a civil war between the north and the south. That was a big division.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Speak for yourself not the American people we are not Embarrassed]]></document></documents></author>