<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I love this place. Highly recommend medical students and residents do an elective here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We up all night from dawn to dusk it’s always poppin! @ XL Center https://t.co/lCIfDqFN6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ignore MCs like beeps, scribbling freedom on pages, My third eye is like pink eye, seen and contagious” 🔥 https://t.co/k0mOloSh4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fapnormousyt sweetheart you are really great 💜 💜 💜, I love the way you do your thing, I love the way you suck dick. 💋💋💋💋💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got this Twitter account for family and friends... All tweets here are originally from Neil Diamond.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survive and Advance... 💯  Round 1️⃣ of the State Playoffs start today. 🏆  Which local team could you see going all… https://t.co/0Ad3jCh8zB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auweia1 @renebfolena @jonbuchwald @justinzollars @sfzombienation @LondonBreed @sfbos @SFDAOffice @TheCoalitionSF… https://t.co/lvJ2bAmCaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBK: We are tied here at the end of 1 Q #WoosterDistrict #TDR https://t.co/aC6ppgq4pM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A título persona, comparto la pena que embargan, éstas, y TODAS las familias y amigos que han perdido un ser amado… https://t.co/UlqALj2TFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyattRegencySWC @Tesla You guys are in Railroad Square??? I roll through Santa Rosa all the time on my way up to H… https://t.co/b6sbeoKfaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to be let down when you never had sincere expectations ! It’s okay Lakes, I follow with great caution. On the… https://t.co/55r6mMLyF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Share your thoughts with Beto on the issues that are important to you: https://t.co/rbLOSjG8dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan Go to hell....you are an ignorant evil hearted person. The most dangerous thing of all is you are ignorant and stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahnpbowman @waddell_adam Of course I think it's good! And sure, we can use vocation language to talk about it.… https://t.co/H51mP05xtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillMew @actbrilliant @jayferro @rwang0 @tcrawford @holgermu @DrJDrooghaag @sarbjeetjohal @schmarzo @APGuha… https://t.co/4fLFiUr9A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[JSU’s Craven launches a sac fly into left to give the Gamecocks 1-0 lead. Nice play by @k_robinson20 robs the Cocks… https://t.co/WZzUzntqgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajaja los del @Atleti pitando el himno del @realmadrid , el himno de la Champions. Nunca lo entenderemos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[gave a talk in my bio class about my project and everyone said I sounded like I knew what I was talking about!😎  No… https://t.co/9N8ECPlkyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#barber #barbers #barbershop #barberlife #barbershopconnect #barbering #beard #beardgang #beards #bearded… https://t.co/3lDg6kjwRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is funny cause I’ve actually hit a kid like that with a scooter before]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayloredBites Right, but what matters is that we’re gay, and that that reality is being portrayed. The film doesn’… https://t.co/6cDliSSvGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachStanton20 @erictrudo @MVCoachR Hands down one of my favorites of all time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Unity #Myth #DefyNegativeEnergy #embraceLove #EraseHate #CourageIsTheThingThatKeepsUsFree  #RealAmerican #TBT… https://t.co/kdDrDBQvFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Jonas brothers could’ve released a song that sounded like botdf and I’d still be bumping it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jorrie and Ava getting some #skating #tips from an #oldskool #pro at sk8charleston today. The girls are loving the… https://t.co/2e8QE1K3mM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treyarch you ruined my favorite game, hope this title dies with the rest of the games that doesn't know what they are doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BTS............ COTTON CANDY MUSIC VIDEO  ARTIST: @parlaystarr thekevinmccall   #film #filmlife #movielife… https://t.co/JuIwo6VAfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningGreetings #Peaceloveandblessings #RespectTheLadies #BelieveInYourself #DefyAllOdds  #DefyAllObstacles … https://t.co/489I0YIzxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer Tasting with shellyprn district96_beerco #emptynestweekend @ District 96 Beer Factory https://t.co/KiUWugn7wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jalencook3_ You’ll soon be changing that profile bio!!  Good luck this weekend #GeauxWildcats]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s bad when the TNT team Knows this guy is a clown #JessieSmollett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTammyGillis Family Day only holiday in 6 provinces wherever you are you are from Man. so happy family day tomo… https://t.co/kerUjCd68i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Colin_Hung @LorriThanos @chipmcintosh Four of my favorite people! #HIMSS19 https://t.co/a4NTRABmG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy v day to Laura Dern (the cat) and only Laura Dern (the cat) https://t.co/3b497PqLNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBigCat @AB84 You go out on a limb like this you better choose the questions and your working carefully.… https://t.co/1vm6Y5WXy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote of the Day: "Use your power, privilege and access to amplify voices that are not being heard, and build inclu… https://t.co/EHc9dp8n6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddHagopian Except that it has been used as defense for shootings that should not have qualified, like over a par… https://t.co/LgNwgyySKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shredding the gnar on this chill wave of anxiety that just hit me. 🏄🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BfloBizDATA @lisapolsterwivb I know, right? An old family friend recommended it. I was hesitant but gave it a try.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy buscando el Twitt del congresista Tubino, , que pida calma y que todo debe investigarse sobre  Lezcano. Que e… https://t.co/nSIb43jFhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenAndWoods @Mighty1090 They’ve yet to make the playoffs without with the team.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtlizz322 I usually do 3 eggs. Disagree that English muffin is unfilling / empty carbs. Only had 4 ozs of OJ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcross610 It never fails that you quote something that was NOT in my manuscript. Makes me think about the merit of… https://t.co/QRbdWiuXJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nolan Arenado got paid big!! 8 years $260 million, $32.5 million per year goddamn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[California winter; I quite enjoy walking home, these days. ⠀ #ShotOniPhone @ La Mirada, California https://t.co/mxAsuGvTKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE Add some sateh sticks with it. Sateh babi (pork) with peanut sauce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 7-8 .. atl what’s going on need something to do need some new homies I guess .. fwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Memphis Your Excellency. @BishopDavidT  May God bless the good Shepherd of the Diocese of Memphis in Tennessee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People have black crosses in their foreheads today and this is the first time I’ve really thought that it is strang… https://t.co/36E0RTSFzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpacialJones He shut that PnR stuff down. The PS4 guy was calling pick after pick. He had no gameplan. That Galaxy Opal Wilt was huge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[News International:     Trump Delivers Blunt Warning to Venezuela Military Over Aid Impasse;       The Vatican’s Se… https://t.co/g38AMDQ7k8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHookfox10 @PureMichGirl @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Obama was a smooth liar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanine Records New Colossus Festival Party at Piano’s: Living Hour #kaninerecords #newcolossusfestival #pianos… https://t.co/fr2XrKsE1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJEllenbecker UNC-Duke Final Four. Zion is back. Colby White game winner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoe_hitchcock the inspiration for this tweet tbh  rip to the og adamstown subs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I watched The Voice auditions on YouTube for 3 hours. https://t.co/dyVlpOwasq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLGigante I don’t think I’ve seen a girl react happier than this. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattschneidman What’s the point of all of this Offense if Gruden won’t throw the ball more than 5 yards forward at a time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is difficult to imagine the damage of the Obama administration. When Trump said I’m going to drain the swamp, no… https://t.co/ZAWQaZMfLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early supporting georgiatechfb @ Georgia Tech https://t.co/Fc466iJv2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I'd be willing to bet there's nothing in the coffee cup either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know i`m not  A KOL - probably have like 5 real people who listen to what i have to say - I,`m 68 - i`m  lucky th… https://t.co/qITieRDHRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 you're definitely a great receiver but you need to stop acting like Terrell Owens and Ocho Cinco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News says the shooter bought the gun legally. Not True. He was an X Con and could not buy a gun legally! The ba… https://t.co/t1ocmf3ZWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't been this excited for a #nascar race in 25 years after watching @mattdracing and @LFR95 @BLeavine last week… https://t.co/ypDur7dhlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson learned: triage and prioritize issues. Focus on the one thing that actually makes your business better. No b… https://t.co/UQBsp7uibv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freshman Gavin Griffiths coming up big for Simsbury. He’s got a trio of threes this quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAIS AAAA Division II Boys State Tournament Semifinal Round  From Simpson Academy Vote for who you think will win.… https://t.co/2EocmnJCJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone fr sick rn 😂 it’s workers in the CDC trying to control population by releasing viruses and limit populatio… https://t.co/Yi4UkTwBqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan Exactly! She is completely out of touch with the backbone of America, the working class. Just as the en… https://t.co/Ur11cBUuee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratification deserves to be practiced EVERY SINGLE DAY! 🙏 What are you grateful for today??]]></document><document><![CDATA[China’s State Media Investigates Fake Followers of Celebrities | Jing Daily https://t.co/SIjA40LfAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoffNutz @jeffbonderacing @GAHorseRacing @SireWatch @sidfernando @HillnDaleFarm @loomsboldly @SethMerrow2… https://t.co/PFT203wP0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking: @SpeakerHanshaw announces that Anne Lieberman, the House’s sergeant at arms, has resigned from her positi… https://t.co/K73frWUJaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.1 mph NW. Barometer 29.818 in, Rising Rapidly. Temperature 47.3 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 94%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Buckman Performing Arts Center https://t.co/uyKTaPukqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some excited rocket engineers @FHGES getting #ready4NCSO2019 - New Hanover Tournament #1 this Saturday, 2/23, 8-3 a… https://t.co/tNtklpDtVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcrypt Can’t.  Beats my generation‘s priorities: 1.  Diet Coke. 2.  Coke Zero. 3.  Diet Coke. 4.  Tacos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quakes99 I noticed that surge in uranium stocks yesterday. But I am Sick of being teased]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USAFootballMT @pntrack @CoachNickNewman @HFJumps @ALTIS @PfaffSC @CoachSanAndreas @StuartMcMillan1 @Chidi1Enyia Do… https://t.co/9KAANtXkLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just chillin courtside with the man @djdense behind the music for the #1🏀team in LA! @ Los Angeles Clippers https://t.co/O8b2x2rfFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Williams16 @ESPNStatsInfo True but it’s very possible he sits out the rest of the season so he avoids another… https://t.co/XMShyNeod5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @EMluvsPibbles @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/EjH6Iyifns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm beginning to believe no one on the right has any fucking idea what the word "coup" means.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firefOxlu @rihanna @Sephora @HarveyNichols @fentybeauty HI GUYS!!! THIS #RIHANNA #MUSIC IS VERY GOOD, BUT SHE IS L… https://t.co/GTbgYjEXig]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone can buy fashion. How do you #CreateStyle #CorneliusHardyCollection https://t.co/y9PRmzCM5s @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/IUPFEa6K8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Convention Center Station (DART Rail) - @dallasmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/2knwgH1z1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobNelson_FUSD @fresnounified @FresnoCountyCA Hopefully it can be a place that will be an example of how break the… https://t.co/kR4hqnIhMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remeber about two songs at the @ReadSouthall concert last night. But I do remember having a damn good time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighGiangreco Lmao I won’t ever forget my freshman year at CUA when a classmate said she was “also from DC” and w… https://t.co/rpzY8vqwyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only in the USA, but it’s happening right here in Canada as well!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GretaLWall @OANN @PressSec #BuildTheWall  #BuildItTall  #ProtectUsAll  #CrimeWillFall]]></document><document><![CDATA[smokin moroccan hashish with my slanted-eye zombie mami, hennessy fill my body]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dennyfrompitt I couldn’t see what happened to trigger it all, honestly. Anxious to see what TV caught.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With friends at Mel’s Dine-In Me being 🤪 @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/OTCXOVCbpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvaziri I stole that techniqe for our large, Drawing From Film classes at Lucasfilm Singapore. Took us almost 3 ho… https://t.co/Go0viFy2iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigwitchershill @TaiPan89597053 @Gizmodo Lol. Star Wars fundamentalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder how long minority Republican/conservative tactics of suppressing/shrinking the electorate can co… https://t.co/G836cLWeR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥💥💥 Thank you harpersbazaarukraine Beauty story out now featuring the gorgeous @danielafreitas_real by… https://t.co/Ohuyctygki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhgurf @RuleChicago @Cdubey_Texas @BlindMelon1967 @beccas1434 @BakerBitchBakes @CandyisDandy100 @CunningSq16… https://t.co/tm0vhSRqun]]></document></documents></author>