<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@93XRT @LinBrehmer @MaryLDixon Happy Birthday, Chicago!!🎂 IDK, but I'be got the cake covered: https://t.co/n1C3Vi2Zec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earpers keep fighting!  Keep voting! We are here and We stay! NoChill👊 @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment… https://t.co/ZEhmVLWgdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow along LIVE!  @IonaGaelsMBB vs. @JaspersMBB   🏟️: Draddy Gymnasium 📊: https://t.co/5AqMml7EaP 📺:… https://t.co/nSuWRatXSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetCouncilNews I’m looking forward to attending the swearing in ceremony &amp; reception. 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tipped off to this swingin’ little speakeasy thanks to abedunk knkx885 @pdxjazz 💙@thankusomuchpdx #youngtalent jack… https://t.co/e9DvRsVcIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenna_brown @NISDSpOlympics @NISDLangleyES @NISDSpecialEd @AydeeUfland @RobinGu17353158 @vikingwarrior99 Awesome!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Docks are literally floating away from their moorings and into Lake Lanier because the water levels are near record… https://t.co/DBG4Ulcxkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta genuinely love and respect yourself FIRST—before you welcome someone else’s love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I will have a beautiful car like this beautiful 1958 Plymouth Fury aka Christine 😎 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/T0CgksVmgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @MillbrookCTE Kitchen and @MrsCTChance Foods II Culinary Class for preparing a delicious spread of muffin… https://t.co/XAGVSjIYjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Images from Vero Beach Fashion Week 2019 are now available for view and download.  https://t.co/C54Yx3TUUg  Runway… https://t.co/QQ1WONy3fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2 Sharing professional development would be another way to build relationships! Invite School nurses to a PD and l… https://t.co/TalFEj4SfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope #westcoast… https://t.co/t8gbP1JQ8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano just heard your stand-up routine.. This is not happening. It has become clear to me that you need to fi… https://t.co/BlFmqV0ibJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special Thanks to @hduncan933 ! See you Monday for the 3rd Period Finale!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning flight back from #SanFrancisco to #Toronto to recruit for @odaiaAI the best out of @UofTCompSci… https://t.co/OUO0DEz1Jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonz970 @Razorsmack1 @BlueStateSOS @txjean2014 @GampyK @bpz6961 @Christina2MAGA @Freddie91162 @startpackin… https://t.co/cjASR4Ak6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThePromMusical So excited we are finally here.  Can't wait for the show to start!  #soexcited #NYC https://t.co/YgHTX8LFTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orvieto2016 @GOP Do you mean like controlling your bladder or bowels?   We have the right to control our own bodie… https://t.co/LI5GftA7D5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day https://t.co/ygIEEwHy3X @HISTORY #TDIH #flowersandcandy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit @AnaKasparian, I haven't laughed that hard in a long time. Here, enjoy this dog pic. #tytlive https://t.co/4ESsFrf8Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasArena9 @MrDane1982 @Gragrl The worst = midwesterners. when I lived there (I'm a mutt, 1/2Hispanic, 1/2Caucas… https://t.co/VnRH8Cwhdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yikesitspam @kennedyamara1 @PayneYasmine @PalayeRoyale Drink coffee like number 5 does if you wanna finish that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me oversharing on social media instead of just going to a therapist https://t.co/CVmf5PBYxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can not wait to see my kids tomorrow 3 weeks away from them was just too long!! #TeacherThursdays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kate_gorney @AsteroidStrike0 Sometimes I just wanna do hood rat things with my friends 🤷🏼‍♀️🙋🏼‍♀️💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthorTherapist Awww Happy Happy Birthday Beautiful Sharon.....Hope u had a fablous day...Love your pics...xxx😘❤😘🎂🎂🎂🎂🍰🍰🍰🍰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daaaaaamn Kylie &amp; Jordyn were straight BFF goals. You can’t trust anybodyyyyyyyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKatieHill We tried federal incentives for home buying and it mainly benefits rich families and helped fuel the… https://t.co/aTHHkzh72o]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, @senatemajldr. It was election fraud by the GOP. Ask Harris' son about it, he'll get you straight on that, but… https://t.co/fHc7Quyip1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve extended free @DCCirculator through March 31!   Try it today and bring your friends.   🚌   🚌   🚌   🚌]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a lil sad cuz one of my cousins from cali was supposed to come down for spring break :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseyBanks Thinking of you during this difficult time, Kelsey. Sounds like he left quite a legacy! Wishing you we… https://t.co/uJYeZ4W5X1]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍@deesnider HELLO MY FRIEND DANIEL DEE  SNIDER I LOVE YOUR SING WOULD YOU COME TO MARINETTE WISCONSIN IS FOR MY 49… https://t.co/LbB4ycDhcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbybonesshow Loved it loved it and seeing as I was a child that grew up with 2 parents who had addiction problem… https://t.co/hlNmB8TbZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the #jonasbrothers @jonasbrothers coming back I’m spending the day listening to their entire discography 💁🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend Countertop event..Set up for success with three stations.    Proud of the engagement from our associates an… https://t.co/oEGcjKtH7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ironekilz @HiddenPeanuts Austin is a great city. When I think of Texas I think it's warm and sweltering. I forget that TX gets snow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping to see all of you on Tuesday 3/12 8EST as #betheone author @sheehyrw moderates #champforkids and chats Keeps… https://t.co/HT05AexsFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz My dad and his friend convinced me that land sharks were real and that one you could get me from the corner of a room. 🦈😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Big Huge Congratulations to @TripleH , @ChynaJoanLaurer , @WWERoadDogg , @ShawnMichaels , @TheRealXPac and… https://t.co/4wlo1or16o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a friendly reminder that Hooters does a shred your ex on Valentine’s Day 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marina935home @sandyincanada @2kewlabs @BloomNight2 @lynda3035 @Tosca3333 @Lpowell588Lady @HackmanPatsy… https://t.co/1wDc69iaym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara I love them all, but I think my favorite was @Billbrowder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spes1670 Wendell Pierce has been all over my tv lately from Chicago P.D. to Amazon’s Jack Ryan and I’m here for al… https://t.co/U01ig42Vo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJerryOC @hallmarkchannel @RebeccaRomijn @LarissaWohlTV @helloross happy partying !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty AWESOME watching the Freshman Boys Volleyball 🏐 EHS took home a W 🎉 Nice job kaleb.williamss 👍🏼 bst2da 🤗 @ M… https://t.co/IPMNnKskO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift has been WAAAYYY too active on her instagram lately   Somethings coming #TS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I colored my entire head purple &amp; somehow, my greys are still shining just as silver as they were before. Someone explain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoeracing @MattHagan_FC @OfficialMOPAR @NHRA @Dodge @SandvikCoro_US @Pennzoil Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[God it’s only Saturday of a three-day weekend and I already want to lock the kids outside and lose the key. SENDHELPPLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ali_Chiasson @jeffrey_vallis @chrisgloverCBC @CBCToronto This was indeed incredibly difficult to watch. Especially… https://t.co/YBUqT4VPMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch plus who wants tickets to the BET they are celebrating their accomplishments by stepping on many peo… https://t.co/nXX788ZAaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m convinced someone stole my 4th grade sketch book https://t.co/qJ6c8Xz9BA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stranahan let your work speak for itself. Let the lord defend you.   Coming from someone (me) who is very defensiv… https://t.co/cqYQoWDChS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We must understand how Artificial Intelligence will be used against us.” ~ @SteveGrobman @McAfee #quote #AI… https://t.co/vUyx0AoOZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched #BohemianRhapsody but “We are the champions” just makes me want to watch The Mighty Ducks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milwaukee Journal Sentinel: Police: Man exposed himself in locker room at Brookfield gym  https://t.co/M36a6dsz77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dougy74Design @doritkemsley1 @TamarGeller Yes, it may be just a tv show but people are still lying about this situ… https://t.co/RdPWRMaftz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dunkin thanks for waking my ass up this morning with your fresh ass coffee 😁🌼]]></document><document><![CDATA[took too much Benadryl on accident and now it feels like I’m tripping balls, it’s fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[sunset soon forgotten. @ Planting Fields Arboretum State Historic Park https://t.co/ZgmPLYGiqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceC4David @funder @RepMattGaetz Don’t you mean “serviced” DC—not “served”—?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junziforhire @Shareblue @CahnEmily @BillClinton Clinton didn’t get a walk but Trump does. Get real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so team replay aq 4 fri ep ng  #MySpecialTatay #MSTHuliSaAkto pro jst seeing some clips here ang sakit sakit 💔 bkt… https://t.co/iNpuM1X3kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#satisfying #sunday #butfirstcoffee #watchingmybabies #horses #coffeeholic #horsesinmybackyard #coffee… https://t.co/KgC39D355S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure the #Oscars are amazing, but season 3 of Pretty Little Liars and the 2 books I’m reading while watching it is better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BondageLand @cruel_vyra @GiadaConey Closing in on 500 updates- congratulations on your milestones. #TeamAlice]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can just imagine how great this feeling was for these athletes #chills #whatamoment #stunning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamiltonJohnD I was singing some original music at the red dog in my hometown! Thanks I love my boots too! They we… https://t.co/O9rLLS4arY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Grace isn’t opposed to effort, but earning (Willard).”   The Gospel message of striving should be clear: we strive… https://t.co/jmDyPJr3j1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When She Say She Love Niggas In Jordan’s But you on A Budget. https://t.co/z9B7nulx9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is SO heartbreaking. Someone tell this guy this isn’t how you parent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to my game and brought me roses, I’ve got a pretty cool Dad ❣️ @MillerMacPiper https://t.co/d5dbbIwNrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lauren6194 @liannall URI: where girls are half as smart and half as cute and still flex on the internet. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I just say how awesome my clients are?! At today's winter wonderland session, we braved the snow drifts as long… https://t.co/luPMoWngAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miz_cracker killed it at the #hatersroast San Diego! Thanks for the laughs lady. https://t.co/FgMux8g1SP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: my baby be cute asf Co-worker: yea he looks like a baby  Me: he just has a baby face but he 20 so we good lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NotesFromNationalEmergency My poor pup is so worried during this #FakeTrumpEmergency. I dont know how much more he… https://t.co/D11cv8isnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Each new trailer gives me a little more Bulbasaur, and for that I am thankful...  #DetectivePikachu https://t.co/oMoI64CnVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJollyFL @Bewitched9 If this isn’t “Witness Tampering”, I don’t know what is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanearlcarley @GrassrootsSpeak It's the fact that he's rich!  Money buys everything!  To top it all off, he will… https://t.co/1kD7x0WQjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A simple, elegant solution and how we vote in Massachusetts. A no-brainer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all know how it’s no shave November it should be a month y’all females should do no make up 🤷🏾‍♂️  March or something just saying...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t be more prouder than I am now. @brielarson kicks ass in #CaptainMarvel . Congrats BRIE. @captainmarvel . https://t.co/ULstF2jpGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day is off to a great start. "Assessment enhances learning". Great way to look at it instead of just something… https://t.co/1UGNaoNoy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpags Wow.  Sorry but if you can't wait until 11 - you are an alcoholic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putnam Heights 4th grade artists! Neutral colored owl weavings! @okcpsArts @PHOKCPS 🦉 https://t.co/LFp3Zpt3UL]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say diamonds are a girls best friend, but I’d be satisfied with some roses. 🥀]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reading gives us someplace to go, when we have to stay where we are.” - Mason Cooley 📚   • • • • •  #picoftheday… https://t.co/JrzWXLL9w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum @TheStoryFNC 😥😥😥😥😥😥 A tragedy that never should have happened. A life ended before it's time. Eith… https://t.co/81gRCbdMTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M4ximr Félicitations! Vous avez raison d’être fier!!! Bonne continuité!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get lost in the blue blue sky  #McLife #sassysaturday #nofilter #city #citylife #toronto #torontolife #nature… https://t.co/9ACTGTM7gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren Your so stupid! Nobody cares what you think......shut your piehole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morgan ate my moms Pringle’s once so now my mom put her name all over them and got morgan her own and put her name all over it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few pictures from the Belle Plaine elementary and middle school presentations today! Thank you for having me… https://t.co/ZjN5P3TY4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillClinton @jguaido Venezuela needs regime change, but as long Maduro has the military support him, nothing will change in that country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Sarah Whitcraft for another fun Rave to Save. One of the best events for the community! You do an amazing… https://t.co/EWE8yztO8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@healthyfireguy @AOC Your absolutely right, men have a say in this. Just because she speaks from her truth doesn’t… https://t.co/InB0z6pNxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living life requires action so get out there and make life happen!!!!  #liveyoubestlufe #life #happiness #success… https://t.co/DVSHw845Ii]]></document></documents></author>