<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FallingDj omg! love it .@steventeaster  .@SynthoElectro https://t.co/MwNxxl1b54]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchgoldich Any time.   You should follow them next season! https://t.co/wezhqmQ6HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some inspiration during miles 79 to 83 this morning #roadto500 @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/yQDGNxn82v]]></document><document><![CDATA[🧡🌳The Wee Wildcats speak for the trees...#LOVETheLorax #MESrocks https://t.co/zamdAdI1jR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold up...Purdue Pete's out here dunking?  If this isn't the wallpaper on Boilers fans' phones, they're doing it wr… https://t.co/Wt7Qc8YqHF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbrandmeyer23 @AINSLIE_23 @LokoLockowitz We should go down to dads sometime. Pro designed Golf courses, casinos ga… https://t.co/BououKwaLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Keep up the resistance be sure to get someone to register and then get them to the polls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredraKodama @Rosie @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/UqvfvvFgGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[QB is the most important position in the game. Kaepernick was not on a roster the past two seasons. In all likeliho… https://t.co/zmoqcTwyji]]></document><document><![CDATA[The past week has been a nightmare for Canadian comedians. With our livelihood’s at stake, we mobilized, and I’m so… https://t.co/SNQacsnYUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican voter fraud!!! No wonder they complain about it so much.  They are the ones most guilty of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how you phrased this. I'm always annoyed when well intentioned folks talking about "giving voice to." Marginal… https://t.co/JHLtUSQmSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personal record this morning when I swam 2.4 miles (Ironman distance) in under two hours, improving by more than te… https://t.co/t7OIFDfO29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anajcmadrid Gerencia financiera y Profesora de proyectos. Vaya manera de enmascararse de esta chavista...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BreitbartNews McConnell has been working with the deep state to undercut and destroy President Trump… https://t.co/LqLPD24iLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Andromeda by @celestialbw at @CraftandGrowler — https://t.co/iGYYMQB4sT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Din Tai Fung Dumpling House in Bellevue, WA https://t.co/MWklSSR39q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ritesh00763 Personally, I believe Facebook Ads is significantly better in developing your brand for over 90% of th… https://t.co/NSRNKo80WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[JB's commentary on the State of the Union  https://t.co/rnPoLCihFV  It's a sad state of affairs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an offseason where Boras/Harper have wanted the public to know any team that is involved no matter how serious t… https://t.co/W9Ijvdoo58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltTrapper @thgrace78_grace @Eskimo_IceGear @MrHeater Nice..Next year she will have some kind of fish finder..Eve… https://t.co/3xF0ESkUqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lily_lovexxx Your a strange one Lily Love. Your innermost honesty is beloved by me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned this week from @NdabaMandela that @Sobukwe_Trust - Robert Mangaliso Sobukwe was jailed for more than 30 y… https://t.co/BxC8n8kZCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rushtheband Ed Bastian, CEO of Delta Airlines, quoting Rush lyrics in article about #parklandschoolshooting      https://t.co/wz9jqItsZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The finished product not my A+ 10/10 work but pretty darn good considering I’m a newb at doing nails and the e-file… https://t.co/p0J94aGsOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to this amazing lady in my life, you’re truly the light in my life and I appreciate you beyond words… https://t.co/xuUvQMfYVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I'm slightly on time, this fucking train. Every single time 😪 https://t.co/WsVdio8KlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@efvogelsang do you have a good peckerwood recipe for me to get rid of a fat ass like you!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of marisa.zepeda today. She scored a 9.050 on Vault and earned 🥉. Keep working Mija and get ready for States… https://t.co/Uls5DyL8iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 2 of #UmbrellaAcademy loooks soooo goood!  https://t.co/nLYzxrdElN  P.S. Damn show made me revisit this.   T… https://t.co/ETtn8XDfNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PizzaGateLibya @davidhogg111 Kinda humorous that it’s his dad and papa is F.B.I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinaPugliese  Can we not make @BTtoronto Kardashian free?  They take up to much air space now.    I am with… https://t.co/BO40hGkFZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwikWarren They don’t want moral obligations interjected with their money making, that’s why they banned kap but won’t ban kraft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_valdez_4 Great work Diego! Excited for your future football career at JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aafiron spending 30min in line to get to the ATM so we can buy beer. It’s 2019, please find vendors that can take card.  #missingthegame]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took a lot of searching, planning and ultimately, a trip to the hood, but I finally get to see #captainmarvel op… https://t.co/Qv5wonj4h1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing some #Apex with my Canadian friend @Karlski_01   https://t.co/1wY2hJm7y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Midday180 This just in. Coach Vrabel doesn’t care for @PaulKuharskyNFL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR SALE         COMING SOON    8206 Heatherwick Drive Brandywine, Md.  $279,000 3 Bedrooms 2 baths  Granite Stainl… https://t.co/HQJTqtbgai]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son attempting to eat a table @burgatorybar. Even their tables are delicious. Snap 📸🍔👼 @ Burgatory Waterfront https://t.co/WxjqqU5TWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will likely have two @UVAMensGolf alums in @TheHondaClassic qualifier playoff, as David Pastore makes birdie on… https://t.co/Kh663ZMqtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPaulson  #offbroadway rt@BradForenza and his play TheRehearsal premieres at #EmergingArtists (… https://t.co/wVuPnQvdiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next person to come to the @DnD_AdvLeague @GaryCon and say “I am Negan.” To @Zombie_Joe wins some @DnD_AdvLeague swag!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if @MSNBC Brian Williams is reporting on the @JussieSmollett Hoax. Considering his own issues with the tru… https://t.co/R3xJgVOHjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would have thunk' Walmart doesn't take any digital payment method. I was keen on using Google Pay, but they tak… https://t.co/neuLRgQwvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld Can’t believe my ears. Juan just said a gay, black man has mental problems. Really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreghHernandez That’s weird bro I don’t remember you asking me to hangout. I would love to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eric_shorey Just mad that you had no black wrestlers featured on black history month just a yuppie but werk queen.… https://t.co/flvrz87SZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katyuskamoonfox I honestly have not played the game in a long while. I did finish it, but I don’t remember it being on multiple time lines?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samuelmartinezc @politicomx @ROMACuaron @LeonardoCurzio @mariocampos @warkentin @anafvega @japonton… https://t.co/QWMlJRfM17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter – Guest Columnist: Why We Must Have a Border Wall https://t.co/usxI3Sk0ic via @BreitbartNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorLites UNM already said they are standing by the decision, so they’ll get nothing from the state, which could… https://t.co/kfwNbbEOwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Or 41.8%.  You lie about approval ratings, your height, your weight, your wealth, crowd sizes, etc… https://t.co/hrqqf50LYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarrowMindWoman @CBuhainBaello @JodyD34119321 @DustinBenge The topic of the thread was about women being in a posi… https://t.co/qAPXAKF4im]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really wise post about social media https://t.co/BHkT43ppOL #militantpositivity #FresnoUnified better preparing stu… https://t.co/jZxaEuA0bG]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY 8 RELOCATING TIPS 2019 | 1000 SUBBIE GIVEAWAY? https://t.co/mnyCpZLPls via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hypeman_Q @videogamedeals I can’t imagine many people did. I suppose that’s why it’s 60% off 2 months after its release.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michell16846017 @cher Your so correct. I should have reread....it is me. Thanks a lot dear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @KimStrassel @WSJ You better hope he follows your instructions and doesn’t quit like the rest. Bec… https://t.co/oPnjZMSsjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing with logos. Glad @PDE_YOUNGNUDY is finally free. Original photo by @levijpg on our first assignment for Nic… https://t.co/PVe1sfE8eY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKatalyst_ @pocvhontvs_ Y’all imagine this were we work! @itstravbitch  @alheli3_  I can already hear the phone… https://t.co/eKAncScKym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChangeTheRef @patriciapadauy @Emma4Change @JaclynCorin Patricia is our queen! 🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahershala Ali joins Denzel Washington and Russell Williams as only the THIRD Black person ever to win more than on… https://t.co/T8FsGToq36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched #FreeSolo with @wrshp_drmr_01 What an incredible and inspiring story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Santa Clarita, California https://t.co/2anVerwAdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigbraowners @IrinnaMoris_Fan @sayangxx @RobertA07340245 @chrisdav777 @number_kuusysi @stu007gots @Miss_Bimbo_5XXX… https://t.co/nTVmIGxAN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheglar_GD @DubbyGoodell Guys will cross the line most of them live check to check]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Double Trouble State Park, Parque estatal en Berkeley, Nueva Jersey, es una antigua hacienda de arándanos (blueb… https://t.co/ZM7hcsa5up]]></document><document><![CDATA[En la familia ya todos se casaron estoy en la boda de mi primo y nada más quedo yo Jajajajaja 😂 no sé cómo tomarlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTheHammer1 @RealMattCouch If that's the case then all the others are "Deep State run TV"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser Why would the Russians want Hillary to lose. She was already in their pocket. Uranium one, she and Bill rec… https://t.co/KyKr8Z5HMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbocheetoh @thedailybeast That is because retard trumpers can't handle the fact that trump is a conman and criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarawestover @casadragones is hands down the best tequila.  Highly recommend #casadragonesjoven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FEMALES DESERVED TO GET HIT IF THEY DO THIS CORNY ASS SHIT. I hate when females wanna act like they big and bad to… https://t.co/uElHbowY5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all girls with butts, boobs, hips and a waist, put on a bikini - put it on and stay strong. -… https://t.co/deFBCJcRBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been traveling non stop for the past month and I think it has been taking its toll on my body. I haven’t had a good… https://t.co/NB9f2Y5LnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshadams137 But it would be nice to have an elite back again, we were unstoppable with hunt back there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomazsarquis @GabrielCBrasil @jairbolsonaro Hey mister tallyman, tally me bananas!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another dominant win. Packed gym and outstanding atmosphere in Rec Hall last night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every war president from Madison on has been accused of that yet we still have a republic 200 years later.  Did you… https://t.co/z0GZ6Loh9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridgestonegolf @THPGolf @rehbirdie @MellowGolf @HArnold22 Wait... I’m invited!? This is going to be sick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was left on my board. I wish they hadn’t tried to erase it; I’d have liked to have seen it https://t.co/ASbdcNIr7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SallyAnnBaker1 @jmcappiello I don't know whether to call it a pet or not but one shows up regularly asking for foo… https://t.co/GTUYpiLsPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patio11 *points to a copy of that book on a shelf in the office* "Just take that one?" Would be a pretty good answer too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @fairfaxcounty and @ffxpublicworks - Thomas said he didn’t need any bottled water, but my wife and I thought a… https://t.co/p5BBr9siIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scattered211 It's gotta be something that would make Michael Jackson look like Mr. Rogers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ComunicacionEc @Lenin Pero tú eres un departamento que vale más de medio millón de Euros maldito ladrón]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Granny Goodness have a Southern cousin named Auntie Bellum or did I just dream it up? 🤔 https://t.co/L3X9TFguIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning to no rain and was immediately blinded by the light. https://t.co/5EzQLtTJWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Naysalvatori @Rechy @stherushcomes @GobiernoMX Perdónalos diputada no saben, es que como en tu Twitter ven trabajo… https://t.co/lNKYS1lvv9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaynaRoselli @KTNV @nicksanto534 Never take your life or a day for granted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJollyFL The second claim will hold true if the SCOUS upholds the presidents action. Personally, I don’t think they will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceAdkins Man I wish I could've been there I love all the singers that was there but you and Blake are my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer She will get lost in the run for president. Hell there might be 30 candidates when it truly starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fitting into a size small again 🙏🏼 if you know you know haha 12lb down :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been a fan of superhero movies and #CaptainMarvel didn’t change my mind. 4/10, had some funny moments and a cute cat 🐈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eichel gets his head slammed and we respond by getting outshot 43-18.  But hey we’re better than last year #sabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy guacamole Bill Nye the science guy’s son is doing the weather on @krqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moment iPhone X! Out in beautiful #SanFrancisco. https://t.co/ySruQErT5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[B ehind the Mask R obocop  I diocracy  A lien 3 N inth Configuration C loud Atlas B lacula  A merican Werewolf in L… https://t.co/i3LtM08Gdn]]></document></documents></author>