<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[milk makeup came all the way through with the kush collection, especially the lip balm &amp; gloss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing poetry @teneshahpoet  Get the book you will love it!!! @ Historic Grove Theater https://t.co/dLr15q24BC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brandon75237540 @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Ok smart one... obviously fooled again by the Scumbag. He lost the… https://t.co/er5L6cDwSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM ALL IN FOR ANY STARK/SNOW/TARGARYEN ON THE THRONE (cept bran) #AryaStark #JonSnow #DaenerysTargaryen #SansaStark… https://t.co/o0MlZy2pSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonSwordNow I don't have a one favorite Pokémon title out of these. But here are my favorites: Pokémon Ruby, S… https://t.co/zVrwQkSmbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[MSM wants to know why Americans call them fake news. They don’t report ALL the facts. When you have an agenda, you… https://t.co/2GXeYMgqy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentrawson Happy late birthday!!! Don't know what I'd do without you. Thank you for influencing my life over the past 20ish years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerrjoseph here’s your screen recording since you wanted it so bad https://t.co/hJ19eHRez1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The camera shy artist is ready to go. Come see us at #SDRocketCon today! @ Scottish Rite Freemasonry https://t.co/MoT1uLTJPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am not happy with how anything is going right now and I have no idea where to start fixing things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMS_FredMacias @YsletaISD @Riverside_MS @RiversideMS_AP2 @ARendon_RMS @SGonzalez327 @RMS_Librarian Thank you Mr. M… https://t.co/ydvjGqomdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless it’s always lovely to see that the visible women tag is bountiful and overflowing with amazing ladies in… https://t.co/PLnBb5rh6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[i honestly don’t even care that i am calling out thunder bay roller derby league, changes need to happen, immediately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodreads I read in morning and at night. If I didn't have other interests and like being outdoors I'd probably read more often.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonaFideSage @simonefiasco Goonette - Plies Tonight - Trick Daddy Sugar - Trick Daddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CologuardGolf week here in Tucson!!  Welcome home #DavidBerganio #BearDown ❤️💙 https://t.co/OAj9Vu95n5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigblagger @theikawong I didn’t see this season or any of them but Ika gave me LIFE with this!  Lol the Internal d… https://t.co/2tfueeQNkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate tryna bring up trip ideas to my mommy. everything is "ine got no money". like ok then stay in Nassau playing broke i gern by myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never fails when I’m ready for bed my son decides to get suuuuper lit  He moves like he’s having a party in my tummy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vixnnixn Why were they both helpful cuz they both are not with the BS lol but as long as I put things back they we… https://t.co/Ne8qnMkCkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[High school students might want to consider applying for this scholarship that were previous district 123 students]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love strong vulnerable authentic people. I am lucky to work with johannamustafa @ Patch Coffee https://t.co/sTbw8cYYV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a promise that Joy comes in the morning learn to wait on God with Prayer and Rejoicing for Joy will come and A… https://t.co/XfOij5a95m]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to get my haircut for the first time in a year and I’m kinda scared so wish me luck 😘 @ Fort Myers, Florida https://t.co/PYTtYHIPeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I've been hearing on different news sources that Weisellberg most likely will bleed the 5th instead of answer questions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will used my Saturdays and Sundays to rap up. Plant this Diamond💎📚 #10 A matter of fact, Jesus told me that the r… https://t.co/ZRYJvsNaMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foggy, pitch black, major construction!   This drive back into town from Rosenberg is scary y’all!   Photog and I c… https://t.co/KeH5s9P1eu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Myeisha_G @Ashhlaaayy_ Honestly we should have had a girls night tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful to terrifying in one note, at phantombway ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ #davidlai GOAT conductor ⏱ @ The Phantom Of The Opera… https://t.co/0LRweW8Lfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarangVipin @nadabakos Good thing Lavrov is in Hanoi to tell Trump how he is supposed to deal with this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My glasses will be ready in about an hour. What to do while we wait? #margarita #killingtime #collegestation #texas… https://t.co/EmCQ1cKvz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when men get together and let loose , guns. Cars. Motorcycle all fun, good job and just talk about old time… https://t.co/NfnKfeXTlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monnerat_clara @goodreads @LisaKleypas SO GLAD Milo is working his magic 📚💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TheRealMattKemp did good work and tied the game with a 2-run home run! #redsST https://t.co/g7SNo4N0C6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aroundphotos21 @Pixxydoodle @Art2Paint @EnjoyNature @the_dairyfreeze @dega_boy_87 @ToddShe72716015 WOW. 😮😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[BUT I did say what was on my mind and what I’m stressing about, so ya know, progress? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to end of my 18 hour work day and lance sends me this. I’m so ready to go cuddle this sweet baby! ❤️ https://t.co/yuh37SHPqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today #CravenCountySchools educators are participating in a full day intruder training with #ALICE #SchoolSafety… https://t.co/J0vPfwL5ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19 #Alcorn_RYS19… https://t.co/Nly7yw8b0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just have to shout out @SofiFrankowski and @DrDDiesel for always uplifting, inspiring, and challenging me to grow.… https://t.co/k4tsAzz9ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesson of the day for my students: 🗣Do what I ask you to do when I ask you to do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BusyElves I just texted my kids ur tweet so they don’t eat there! Thank you 🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_F_E_G_L @BlueJays @TicketmasterCA @Braves Oh which day is your birthday, I know @sajazz  is Aug 27.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No you do not support .@realDonaldTrump if you don’t support his most important action.  Principles should start wi… https://t.co/j4nVWSSQd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us. Great people.  No twitter, design thinking, or other skills needed.  #dtk12chat #sxswedu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I first met this nigga I kept trying to tell him I’m a little crazy and he thought I was trying to be cute...little did he know]]></document><document><![CDATA[how tf am i already about to graduate college next year. life really be coming at you fast]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like my wife’s iPhone 7s Plus we paid a grand for brand new like just 2 years ago is now a 1989 Nissan Sentr… https://t.co/T8AbXMIFwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @TuckerCarlson They did the same to Sean Hannity, Tucker will be okay.  #StandWithTucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @KashDaniel15 for making @CM_Tomlin a sexy beast @hey_kentucky co-host!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you gonna get mad at me for cutting you off but yet you did it to yourself🤧😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darkebrood @pas131313 @KernUnited @clovis1931 @Corp125Vet @JacobJMP2 @jeffjeffries99 @Tmc1650 @ThePatGuard… https://t.co/ERi7L8YiuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My future hubby better ask my dad for permission or I’m saying no lol 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand why drake bell would come perform at a frat party at uva]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great things will happen   #rashford #Messi   #Ronaldo  💪#ForçaBarça  🔥 #SevillaBarça   🔴   #WeColorFootball… https://t.co/qYQVqIsay3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latenightseth just came out with a parody trailer for basically every single movie made by white people for black… https://t.co/jDeC49KVP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonbonmonkey672 @DonnaLaCroix6 @Mistybucketlist @_____dclynch_ I’m thinking he really needs to go back to school a… https://t.co/K86CU5iRDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostSochiFeels I'm hoping when I'm actually in Canada and on Wi-Fi my phone will let me watch this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me making my way to the fridge for some string cheese after a few vodkas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_clark Totally worth the six hour round trip. Was lured by the Sargent and thrilled to see the Van Gogh! https://t.co/lNbVqU8UTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS WHY I DONT FUCK W FEMALES NO MORE (except @ashlelauren of course 😉) #FakeAsses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huevito y yo estamos tan unidas que siempre que hablamos de nuestros problemas los sentimos nuestros, nos decimos l… https://t.co/QD62FSk2Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Feylestiani @sumayasworld Oh yes, I believe her. We had a horrible boss and my two praying  God faring co workers… https://t.co/vXN9Apwjjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntoninaPantera @BulletValentina Feliz Dia de la Mujer y que sigamos adelante con fuerza...may God bless u ladies… https://t.co/IiUz3WbEaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#quote #emotions #anxiety #growth #faith #courage #recovery #love #selflove #goals #strength #teacher #attitude… https://t.co/Rt4v6bZrvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday @S_Desiderio216 !!! im so happy we got so close this year! ilysm!!!! https://t.co/NHugwV82IP]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 + 1 days away #NYC. If you missed them the first time here's your chance to see them again #NEWYORKCITY WHO 🤓: Si… https://t.co/n5RABbpFcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s moving day! Except @matthewverygood gets to move into our new apartment while I work all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bravewriting @PrezHillary17 @Melissa71349052 Exactly.  Sometimes I think I embraced Judaism to piss off my fanatic… https://t.co/Q8uYnXS1VI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one demented woman.  Obsessing over a 1/2 sibling whose real family of friends honored her with a baby show… https://t.co/TnQZTb5Eh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like “friend zoned” guys don’t understand that they can be cool and all but if the attraction and ~special s… https://t.co/oDGyM3Xh5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyRobards7 @gil_lawson @WILLOWOOD2 @kbhnelson @PrimeCreator2 @DeeiaTopp @tee10202 @rmbrice @AboveTheBurgh… https://t.co/Nr9jFM99wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[No choice. Voodoo economics. Snacks for Oscars. #doughnuts #donuts @voodoodoughnut  rules. @ Voodoo Doughnut https://t.co/oEW8tgHoQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickRockbeats 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope… https://t.co/fFXCKc3TPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would do anything for Cassandra to be my roommate. But I know as long as she’s in a relationship that won’t happen lol 🙁😥🥺🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revrrlewis @AOC Utterly adorable! Dogs are definitely the best judges of character. I had a German Shepherd years… https://t.co/O2IpSEsrFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynette_50 @AmateurPoke @pizzalover4189 @JeremyMartinCo3 @JoshuaplaysPKMN @dm_stp @RuanAntunes7 @obi_twan… https://t.co/VYY8xHkFRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sign that the Holy Spirit is in us is that we realize, not that we are full, but that we are empty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyBlackHistory  #Oscars #is #ptah  #welcometoreality @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/n2Kts7PSQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday night in a world of possibilities⚡🙌🏻 . Arkells brought down the HOUSE!!🙌🏻 Tonight, I saw my favourite band… https://t.co/Ny1bR8baOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pisces season has me crying one second getting spontaneous haircut the next]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best cream ever , love how smooth my skin feels and my fine lines are disappearing just a week in use #bosslady… https://t.co/I0W1e4Byba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneGarciaKPTV I hate to get my hopes up only to have them dashed yet again,  but I hope it happens!  ❄🌨☃️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcon__ nah hahahah it’s getting a rebuild so they’re gonna start carrying men’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcjanfan @LoveMJJAlways So many lies have been told about Whoopi Goldberg throughout her career, that she knows wh… https://t.co/ovhnKUBbcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StopKillingBlackPeople 💪🏾 #BlackLivesMatter #HoldOfficersAccountable #AB392]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr Why even have women’s athletics. It’s over, from this point forward transvestites will join the wom… https://t.co/KTZlfFUyXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom shared this with me today: when my great grandmother, an Irish immigrant decided to become a citizen late in… https://t.co/Vbxbe2f1sJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people think that I worship the devil, I can’t change the way i think and I can’t change the way I am but… https://t.co/gKpJ0hxwh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nalani and Katina  From today #seaworldorlando #orca #killerwhale #shamu #oneocean #nalani #katina @ SeaWorld Orlan… https://t.co/zoJwAdy7nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[After an 11-0 start Blair Oaks leads Fr Tolton 13-6 at the end of first period https://t.co/dltXapAr4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones is going to be on during CALI meetings and I have half a mind to turn meetings into watch parties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Larrimarquez21 @OurRevolutionNv @BernieSanders @KillerMike Never. Sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[When not cousin post stuff that sound like somebody did something to her or mad her mad I be like what's wrong whi… https://t.co/3t3M74CHZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllCelebPolls @BravoTV @Andy I don’t think heather or Jill were fired 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XzoZannatul @DianaChantel I know that she is an influencer but she’s asking for reccomendations. Lv is not suited… https://t.co/5lCbMSJ46u]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 de febrero 2019  ¡Feliz día del Amor y de la Amistad! #somostoros #somosprepa16 #somosuanl en Preparatoria 16 UA… https://t.co/PW7Zl94EER]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I didn't already have super cute photos of Ari as my wallpaper I'd totally use this photo!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day by @thisisLANY is absolutely unmatched, nothing can beat it.  Thanks for coming to my ted talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennifer_wyant Well there ya go. 😂 It goes by too damn fast sometimes. Hard to believe it's been 17 years since I was in high school. 😵]]></document></documents></author>