<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KimPollishuke 💥 there it is. Can’t wait to listen to it! https://t.co/4Rn6JEEcOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I. 👏🏽Love. 👏🏽Hannah. 👏🏽G. 👏🏽 That is all. Put a ring on it @colton 💗💗💗💗💗 #TheBachelor⁠ ⁠ @BachelorABC  #Bachelor… https://t.co/EiFEKkt6JL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woody_cindy Ohhhh!!! I want to visit! That sounds like such a unique school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelHoekstra13 Definitely worth the wait. Happy Valentine’s Day https://t.co/wkw3xkp1qY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so annoying how people will bug and bug you for something they need, but once you actually need something all… https://t.co/aumXBhgUOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21ufopilots @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse https://t.co/lknzE4kplf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Celeste_CC7 I know this to be a fact.  I have witnessed it first hand. And I have been IMMENSELY blessed, taught a… https://t.co/aIT5ggmoqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentines always and forever. I love you baby @ International Smoke https://t.co/jwB5ULMqa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awwww but let them in.  Put them up, give them health care and everything else. I’m sure they are good people. Not… https://t.co/zybigjrUbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Toxic 45 you're such a hypocrite, but yet you had no problem ripping innocent children from their… https://t.co/rmSkAMSa2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenfrogy44 @DebraGaskill @tweetmommybop Funny. Thanks for the smile. Updated “Mother’s Little Helper”-]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a footman steps to a gentleman in a palace https://t.co/LHl0sY0ezU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CARRIE rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Po Village #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea  A shy adorable little girl  Br… https://t.co/GT4iYjS4K7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else remember when president trump was running for office and he said that he thought climate change was a h… https://t.co/Qnn1HIIMNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoo like these were all my jams when growing up and I ain't even European da fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter world, allow me to introduce you to my daughter, @Atakigo. A Family Sciences, PhD candidate at @UofMaryland… https://t.co/1miYJqRwdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think that @EmilyHinkler and @ElizabeeHinkler are two of the most beautiful real life heroes ever 💖💖💖💖 https://t.co/CmIEDGfqOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are way too sensitive about these matters. Accept it,  you just spoke quickly and made a mista… https://t.co/KSRCvQaLBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday workout 🏋🏻‍♀️ ✅ 🦵🏽  💪🏽🍑#selfcare  #workout #workouts #gym #gymmotivation #morenasamurai #fitmama… https://t.co/hRGDYdfbSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Sitterle crossed 5K. Time 00:31:54, pace 10:16 min/mile, est. finish 11:36 am https://t.co/dVlKPruD3E #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicoleHCherry  Jorden sent me the pics. Thank you so much for taking them! I love them all. Great pics!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin, the place where you can see a guy pulling a little cart containing three pyjama wearing dachshunds with a B… https://t.co/LdXu3MJahM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought the lotion my mom wears today and now I smell like her and I miss her so much 😂😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you think i’m gonna spend $200 and drive to atlantic city to go to this  you’re damn right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a deep breath. Do you feel that?  You are breathing. You are alive. How awesome is that? You are truly spectac… https://t.co/zgA3Jhr1pO]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLOUDDDDD-TTT game ☁️💧  . . . . #view #views #beverlyhills #clouds #makeup #mua #makeupartist #artist #hair… https://t.co/hlTeokFqMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone please help me for the love of god i am so bad at digital art and i can’t figure out how to color this sket… https://t.co/RFYPrVudDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the bands I obsessed over/met when I was 15-16: I’m so sorry for how weird I was lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s she gonna do when he’s a big boy? #mastifflife #jasperlovesAmslee https://t.co/RZwkxF7kF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeJCarey @davidspruell @JohnLusher @JudyMick @helpingvasleep @stewartbuzz Finishing my Friday-bring the weekend🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny how little Twitter can translate to real life. We’ve spent the last 12 months shitting (rightfully so) o… https://t.co/xU0cS44DOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barb71 @thelastmilehome @iAmBoomerStrong @FMedic921 @bluefamilyprays @ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @laker477… https://t.co/ob6tbEv0kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephen40176348 @Love_Promise_S Yes and it's good to not take it personally. I had this added information: I told… https://t.co/KF2eHji8KF]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Sesame Street was the first tech player in early childhood’ and continues to innovate @sesamestreet #SXSWEdu19 - w… https://t.co/8vIMObhUuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep surrounded by cheese balls a couple hours ago n now I'm wide awake n not even drunk anymore pfft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realOBF @ZellnerCrimeLaw Some of them were attractive men. I don’t understand why they would have to go pay for it… https://t.co/wYOkXcgeyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to you @DanStreets9. Fortunate to have you as my colleague!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Does Marlena evaluate Jordan on Friday? I'm guessing she will still be there Salem time..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orange Beach Alabama Tonight!  Get your @deejaysilver1 merch at the @lukecombs show tonight!!!… https://t.co/c8NRVwZhXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaLuna0 not all babies...remember i looked like chucky...that could be your kid...dont get any ideas kiddo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo unas súper ganas de pegarle un zape a mi uber.😡☹️ https://t.co/66BOLNkfz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJohnnyLasagna @MrsDaniG I need a press agent. Looking for a career change? :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u actually listen to Cardi B and Nikki its really bizarre that anyone would even compare the two. Their styles a… https://t.co/edtrCW2wqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa You also stood by us while we fought for our children’s futures. You are worse than any liberal govern… https://t.co/UL9JZMVVHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want DJs across the country to acknowledge the greatness that is Young Dolph and act accordingly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Los Angeles International Airport - @flylaxairport in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/7XAykaEDHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is laughable. #humor #laugh #smirk #humorous https://t.co/QkvxWhNz1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Santucci @dddaniel059 @ABCInvestigates Its sick. Using our money to attack the guy we elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2ndlast2rise Thank you! I wondered if that has anything to do with them being screenshots I took?]]></document><document><![CDATA[GameDevDrinkUp (@ 3643 St. Laurent Apt. 200 in Montréal, QC) https://t.co/W0hUDyi6IC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyzart50 I AGREE EDUCATION SHOULD BE FREE FOR ALL! THIS IS HOW A COUNTRY CAN REALLY MOVE FORWARD AND AHEAD .... IT… https://t.co/8vJ4sripwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avoir mal en marchant = avoir mal même en ne marchant pas 🤷🏼‍♀️ Merci plate bande! 👏🏻 J'aime aussi le fait que de s… https://t.co/J1VKNSxFkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more people I work with in this industry the more you discover you is passionate about their business and who isn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning the #zonesofregulation from our incredible @WesternYouthOC Ms. Susan this monday morning. Ss cheered when… https://t.co/tcDuUSsGjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says @nomad_notebook @HHLifestyleTrav You'll notice you don't see many women arguing about men traveling solo… https://t.co/9na30oK4su]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko Nah, she will just kerp lying and then telling everyone that Jesus is her personal saviour. #SHAME… https://t.co/xQh4tXPae3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grey #BURBERRYBRIT Crew Neck Sweatshirt , With Navy Blue Logo , Size XL , Excellent Condition , Worn Once ... Make… https://t.co/omTsFVs1BP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @MMFlint He’s not the typical old white guy, he’s Bernie, the man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @Gahbsss makes you feel bad for eating meatball #FitLife #NotMyFault #Biotch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when you can see a transformation and your heart is just so thrilled for them!  ❤️❤️   This program has chan… https://t.co/y2JUuRMC71]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #SprintTMobile Merger: Consumers, Competition &amp; the Future of 5G. Panel debate by @GtownTechLaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[It better not raise the price because a broke bitch neeeeeeeds something like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoOilers_17 I do want to see how they justify this, though. Let's ask some of the Baptists in Alabama who had him… https://t.co/btHupfCD6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEA_Updates in solidarity w/ @OaklandEA! #UniteForOaklandKids #WeAreOEA #RedForEd #WeAreCTA https://t.co/Jf5R4sedjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort plea deal voided after judge says he 'intentionally' lied to the FBI, special counsel and grand jury… https://t.co/SS6cmE68ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mobute @HowardSchultz Now imagine New York City doubling its size but one 10 percent being non white.  Also since… https://t.co/xTNO58BR0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cafe Du Monde’s beignets had me singin’ Anita Baker’s ”Sweet Love” - 🎶🎵just love me sweet-ly  ba-by🎶🎵 Mmmmmmm! @ Ca… https://t.co/7BkKRazCD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well tell em to hurry up! I can't wait for all this to hit the fan ! 🤗🌊🌊🌊🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, students worked on PATHBLAZERS which syncs with their MAP RIT scores. Students are LOVING it and sharing rav… https://t.co/66gaLpNAUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 2 am and i shouldn’t even be awake and i should be studying but instead i’m watching old snapchat vids getting… https://t.co/JaSLiX5qRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Betray daddy or go to prison??   Which will you do???   Flip or prison.  One or maybe both 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[No supero a mis primas, todas se veían muy bonitas y con sus vestidos bien bonitos😍 https://t.co/V6MEEbGjS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricRawsonPhD @TStellingwerff Where is this meeting? I see tweets from people that live in very different corners of the world?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RuthDawg17 @boogietmusic Seeing the at forest was amazing! Thank you! So ready 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The U.S.F.S @ModocNF said this week it will sell off #WildHorses rounded up at Devil's Garden Plateau in California… https://t.co/WnqxybZEQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motivation #positivethinking #mentalhealth #positivity #PositiveVibes #positivemindset #MotivationalQuotes https://t.co/2442HAFDdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The Post Office showed up to my Wedding and this our keepsake from the Post Office.  How cool is that? https://t.co/QjfGDhkGNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have complete confidence in you.  If anyone can, you can.  Also the school lunch programs 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard2380 @pam_brundige @mrpresidentsay_ @The821_821 @seeds4change @kkjn1966 @mayak46 @Trentmw5150 @mipiadon… https://t.co/Ls7zN9rfMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see that the big church in Leawood has heart  and luv for all 💛 even if the national one doesn't #MethodistChurch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe in redemption and second/third/fourth chances when a person asks for it. If Trump could not understand wh… https://t.co/MxSmc66ii0]]></document><document><![CDATA[and a blunt pls I’m begging I had the worst day ever and just finished a 10hr shift PLEASE IM ON THE GROUND CRYING… https://t.co/hSFQObI5HY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltonJo77566083 That Was Tru 🗣️ Message Love That Very Strong Details On Trying to Break In The Business 🎵🎧🎼🎧🎤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CayerFrancine Il y a des journées où c est pire même après plusieurs années 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌇Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🏙Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🏙This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/fGQLDhonAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to get my nails done #badliar @Imaginedragons is on the radio!! Yay!! Happy birthday to me!! I just listen… https://t.co/eCVHmlXqCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoplite300 @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump When was that? Everything Donald touches turns to shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[The homes that dont need a lot of work are sold for more which in turn knocks out the lower class person for ownership #LetItRip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianabutlerbass Waiting for the question asking if George Soros paid Lanny Davis]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 3 C’s that changed my life: Color-Coded Calendar 😂 👏🏼Right @BMcKinney83 @menxueiro @ealy_daeducator ?… https://t.co/hJsDVa4guN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling luckier than ever to have the most sweetest best friend/boyfriend by my side 🥰 never gonna get over you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel Saw you!  Very funny. At first I didn’t like you but I recognized as brotherly love. You were a good br… https://t.co/Sye2sgAaQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Instead of protecting us from a FOREIGN HOSTILE TAKEOVER #GOPTaxScam , Cutting safety nets like… https://t.co/qKDSiRJ1Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[hayleyhruska blew me away with this edit so I had to share another shot from our shoot! I’m wearing queenofsuburbia… https://t.co/OGJTFb5fsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danwarren6 I know Dan.  I feel the same about Bailey.  I miss this sweet face every day. https://t.co/ZdrtSaewlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docrocktex26 @osuguppy R I serious I would more likely say that about the liberal lefts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya ever come up with something that everyone thinks won’t work and then when it does others take credit for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to do a deep dive into immersive #projection play and #videosensing this spring and summer!  This looks… https://t.co/KQMPZo4KM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your time of terrorizing the marketplace are over, @RepDougCollins says to pharmacy benefit managers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booked my room in #BeaverPA for wknd of 3/8. My best friend is getting out of the hospital earlier that week after… https://t.co/B2ggCOlgfB]]></document></documents></author>