<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Big News coming from the now former Independence CC Head Coach, 3 AZ kids are set to play there next Fall fall… https://t.co/fwjIWHtqnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CK_Limited All you have to do, boy, is go out your front door and punch the first big guy you see just on gen prin… https://t.co/SRfBQ2EPJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Receive a free #haircut ✂ when you come in for a color service on Wednesdays this month. Created by #PMTS Learning… https://t.co/GtveXPRWuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivid_1066 @DianneDancy @JenAshleyWright Pulled out from the pumps, turned left to go back to the T intersection.… https://t.co/DVcQmwqppk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattNBCBoston Happy Friday Matt! Stoneham OBS at 5:12: Temp: 31; Low: 31; DP: 28; Wind: SE up to 5; Thin overcast.… https://t.co/NZ11YBkK9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colettey6 @ozarkmountian None of those are accomplishments. Either, not good ones, or not his to claim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Europe #Australia #Italy #Europe #London #Sweden #Pontypridd #Cheltenham #SouthAmerica #NorthAmerica #Germany… https://t.co/xOqa9tusXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@plainjane5555 I think that these left wing looney birds are going to drive the independent voters to Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Russmoore713 @Bcrossover15 @BrendonJennings Fortune left because he thought he was a pf and he wasn't going to pla… https://t.co/9sqv5DeEa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rockets looking good while 3 foul, heavily wrapped up Harden watches from the bench. Nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most people tweeting #GreenNewDeal are attacking the policy.  Same with .@AOC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude didn't your state of the union was for "unity". Now you bashing California really.  You Asscl… https://t.co/cf4QSZ7OQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would think I’d learn about spur of t mom trips been waiting for four and a half hours to get a ride https://t.co/qDyxNCSznQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where have I been??? When did we get lacrosse? Where’s my Chatah stickball players?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Bye season 8” https://t.co/5H28gdjYyn via @YouTube y’all already know what to do💙💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so anxious for the fate of Winterfell and it’s not even a real place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great week of @MagnetForensics AX310 Incident Response class in our US office in Herndon, VA. Really a great class… https://t.co/wfJDtMmdgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriShaffir it’s cool I still like this is not happening right? Did they steal this show from you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardHaass @realDonaldTrump That would be enabling. Speaker Pelosi and House Chairs are not enablers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimharris360 @Wess_Moore @ARHoopScoop did a great article on Diawara. He says he’s 100% Razorback. Looks like his… https://t.co/ZB0Y8Jfyur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GomesBolt @AV_SardonicWaif @AdamTrahan Civilized Americans get extra hush puppies, hold the slaw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Project recess has been initiated... watch out oof balls are allowe!!!! Jeez some folks are silly!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIA STARTING WITH SELFPROCLAIMED PRESIDENT PENCE . SELFPROCLAIMED VICE PRESIDENT POMPEO. I AM ONE WHO GOT YOU AND… https://t.co/hYNfjJSUKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on @jessamynduke hasn’t this dog suffered enough just being just having to call @MiaYim his owner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dearsonyaa Same I’m just barely getting over my hangover and now I’m bored 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[See!?! Jeff Gets it. Keep It going! It’s their for the knowin’ Keep glowing! Maybe you’ll start flowing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler She actually said Israel hypnotizes the world, though I disagree with that statement but she is right… https://t.co/egTg7Ix65v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot988 @Jenn198523 @POTUS YEAH! VENEZUELA 🇻🇪 HERE WE COME. VIVA MADURO. BERNIE AND MADURO,PERFECT TOGETHER. https://t.co/t6rpKYNjew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeuristicLineup @AJFoster916 @BrettFraser @alecworth The last month of the previous season wasn’t the same. Kings… https://t.co/rxNgm1bQsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoxMach_pnoles @VinnieDuber or maybe he is a dead pull hitter and the cage is to the right hahahahahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foxconn @CityofMilwaukee: @WISN12News @CherneyAmharaTV was on location to report 12 @UWM_Engineering students headi… https://t.co/AkdbqRmXQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garza_rodney @davidlagreca1 @BustedOpenRadio I called the 1st segment before the match even started.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jleigh40466485 @JonasAfrend @alllibertynews @OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1… https://t.co/3BY8P5CQXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[New @elkhartbrass Chief Nozzles and Smoothbore in service on all engine companies in the city of Harrisburg. 🚒💦💦💦 @… https://t.co/CICdywhfJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess all *checks notes* five hundred and thirty three of y’all forgot how to spell my twitter handle....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenxvenus Hahahaha having a selfie get no likes is what nightmares are made of  You ain't ugly so you've got nothing to worry about lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet What kind of idiot thinks the earth is flat? Why do we deserve dogs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movers and shakers in this little ole’ Austin music scene. #family #prewitt #davetv #capzeyez #brother #prouduncle… https://t.co/u11ctiPfUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dionysus, I have never prayed to you before. I have no tongue for it. Wine pleases you, Dionysus... so grant me one… https://t.co/vqciq9DrQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a BS show the Democratic’s just put on and again as predicted all one side! Listen to what he says! Will you n… https://t.co/5MAaR2tqVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to This day I still wonder why WCW didn't take this opportunity to completely destroy the nWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t tell me hard work doesn’t pay off. I got here with nothing and I’ve managed to hold on to most of it. https://t.co/Xs1xBRRccb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayleaMDay I most definitely am 😛 and you realize only 60-70 dogs a year get rabies right? It’s incredibly rare. D… https://t.co/h2gglh68w0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me feel more like a ninja than when I have to climb through all of our church’s storage room to get 1… https://t.co/jAX23JIaZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BassNicoh I have 1 green 1 blue , yeah the green is great for inshore (saltwater) but the blue is for offshore , p… https://t.co/CwBjO7W0Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmorris011 not to mention what incorporating the costs of transportation does to "affordability"]]></document><document><![CDATA[13 pax of @F3LexSC got better this morning.  8 took on the challenge of #TheReaper Spooky Trail and 5 wandered arou… https://t.co/rVHMHYI6Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradThor @WalshFreedom Then the cops should never be trusted again, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cedars Station (DART Rail) - @dartmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/jRJczi6R8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your chasing the right dream if the work required made you want to chase something else.. keep chasing 🏃🏾‍♂️💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodmanHoops @Stadium What?? Zion is hurt? Keep breaking stories ya pencil neck fart!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_RHolmes @knarkill @B1GWrestling @ncaawrestling @CrepProtect Your biceps don't count!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Ambassadors rock! Check out this post from @thebbqhead   Thanks Bryan! 🤘🤘  -   @jcflugger HOT RUB cherry smoked… https://t.co/xoVXO3xOPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rehearsal #orchestra #todaysoffice #withoutregardtosexraceorcolor @ National Civil Rights Museum https://t.co/gTiVbPiaGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hell yeah. Just leave the key and make sure it's full of fuel and leave so couple drums , just in case I need to… https://t.co/f5VTgCyuOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wordofgod #odcsuffolk #pastorpeaks @ Suffolk, Virginia https://t.co/hDpfkkjBMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I AM GOING TO BLOCK ALL THE "TALKING HEADS' ON TWITTER THAT I CAN NOT UNDERSTAND!!!! STARTING NOW!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosSO_Moro @_SebastianMx @Luciatraswbcs @VictorCastroCos @MeyerFalcon @morozca @SimonLevyMx @Reforma… https://t.co/aYX74L1gCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomorrowstand @volomike 1: I believe in principles. I trust principles. And I am a believer in the principle of sm… https://t.co/P5MzUcUEI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idhar se zeada jang ka shor mchany waly wo he hain jo sath darn IELTS ke tyari bhi kar rhy hain...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo @MGolicJR57 How many more years will Bobby Bonilla receive his $1mill?  They are very lucky that Bon… https://t.co/BsNNTUEUpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was a sizable sheet of ice outside the door to my son’s school. I was the only parent willing to let my child… https://t.co/sLYblUuQZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseHDonGoL @ESbeINSPORTS Saludos para la peńa Madridista de Providence @RMFC_Providence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahRFeldman Was just reading that part today! Unrelated but from the same chapter- why is Toussant Louverture ref… https://t.co/C86LkWaiN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyBaggYo Pull up I got u‼️ and u can record at my shop‼️ https://t.co/t5PnAQcbnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the first chance to #stormchase in my new vehicle yesterday. 06 Toyota #4Runner 4x4. Surprisingly it gets sligh… https://t.co/dmhDj2nham]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMazepin you think forcing her to suspend her account will make it easier for you to rape her @mercedesamgf1… https://t.co/U17fdo2wa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton You can't really think with billions in subsidies, so… https://t.co/aUK6V0leqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UteJazz664 @LightUpTheU You know that's not true. There were subsidies for the poor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sergio comes to the 17th at Sawgrass tied for the lead with Tiger......and of course he knocks 2 in the water lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[People with coexist stickers that cut people off in traffic constantly. https://t.co/nuMA6uRoZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tons of fruity esters, faint clean alcohol aromatics, fresh bananas and brown sugar notes. - Drinking a Schneider W… https://t.co/Zo3SX1hUf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Particularly surprising given that Dems are more comfortable with pork-barrel politics in general.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President's pro-growth economic agenda, MAGAnomics... 🤢🤢🤢 #TrumpBudget]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennettTheSage  I sometimes wonder why they never did a Mortal Kombat anime.  https://t.co/jVoEP3PeQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #FortMyers, FL job and click to apply: Epic Ambulatory IS Team Lead - Project Manager - https://t.co/JAwKwBlHN2 #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[So honored to lead the most passionate group of educators! @MMS_principals #masdproud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope! Mary Barra sold us out to China. Never thought in my 45 years of buying GM cars that I would say this. But he… https://t.co/K1avQFzXk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottDawsonWWE @SMuehlhausenMMA The little kid in me is losing it at the sight of these two technical madmen.  Eas… https://t.co/CAXv0TOlFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[smile with me. 16 Funniest Pet Photos with Captions #comedy #snicker #smile #humorous https://t.co/LGufRjYeDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will innocent Flynn ever do time? Has he been a Trojan Horse inside the #DeepState camp this entire time, only to b… https://t.co/ttJq8Ps8b6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Restaurant Service and Kitchen Team (2189)" at Panda Express? Apply even if you're… https://t.co/x9Vf4RkWyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE Ohio State la crossed fan right here! @ Ohio State Stadium - the Horseshoe https://t.co/pKPvGqp4fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSMemphis @NWSFlagstaff Will be interested to see how fast it goes back the other way,back home. It was flooded l… https://t.co/0aFYM7YrSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day to be a Legend⚾️🏆🔌#legendzbaseball @ Live Oak Sports Complex https://t.co/WKOl1v2TzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fathers’ Guild Board Mtg! Tx to our almost 1000 Member Dads for all they do‼️ #safg #friarnation #sahs… https://t.co/kvtMQeDJAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[829 Westchester Pl 829 Westchester Pl, Los Angeles, CA 90005 https://t.co/4EUFkfvYhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; @babesome walking into the mall after finessing y’all fathers Nd baby daddies]]></document><document><![CDATA[36 hours after snow has stopped and the buffered Beacon St. bike lane in #NewtonMA is not clear. @BostonCollege sno… https://t.co/GcWSgeJZgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimP123456 @Grousehead @nypost @AOC The numbers seem high..but the agreement states total comp..so factor in healt… https://t.co/ZzhMjLySUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erniemartinezSD Thank you, my flavorless burrito and I appreciate the support. It’s been a trying morning🤦🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/b9qW5akV8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept the challenge from @Jim_Hirz to post covers of seven books I love - no reviews, just the cover. This is Da… https://t.co/dqroeMGq06]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyLeBlanc24 @rottzillasgirl @RealSaltLife @BusseDenise @4judyblue @Cobraswife4life @Varightone1 @Jbriggsy_14… https://t.co/x2kWB4ds0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NoWa0fDeJ7  “It’s not fair!!! I’m more than she is.” https://t.co/KTJu56ayyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when barbers think they yo pops and they know what cut is best for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOM THE GHOST! SUMMONING TOM THE GHOST ON A CURSED HAUNTED OUIJA BOARD (... https://t.co/TLwa7XIut7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although only holiday from Ontario west and New Brunswick still wishing everyone a safe and happy Family Day weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIT works out campus-wide access with #design #software firm https://t.co/AYJ9WH5l4i via @RBJdaily #RITNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brumblesmagee @dlynnbergs This is why getting as many $$$ from the new WCC payouts is so important. Tommy honestly… https://t.co/yESCgn7nBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[U13 Boy's Bantam - Pool B - @DCBA_ def. Brantford Hawks 56-36 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document></documents></author>