<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Another of my favorites from Kirsten’s wedding day last fall, taken by justinkunimoto, hair and makeup by me 💕… https://t.co/S88ijvj7m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Klarevas @Alyssa_Milano @davidcicilline No bans.. or maybe just ban liberals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing my boyfriend for the first time tomorrow since... his wife found out everything, my second episode of me bei… https://t.co/SXd9Ydi1sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[sending my love💗 my grandmother also just passed last night. sending love &amp; positivity 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ericamdif @AntietamRec Thanks. If you were closer you would really enjoy the show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OWFootball I need some! Please send a football player to the library. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnionChief2017 That should be to continue watching their journey! Their journey began on day one of Union’s Amazing Shake!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting 2 on the dragon/koi demon mask half sleeve... #staciblacktattooscom #staciblacktattoos #staciblackontour… https://t.co/omILqGuN0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nerd Win Again!!!!! 🏆#NormalPeopleSuck #BlackPanther #AcademyAwards2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so the night started out great went to the @sanjosesharks game with my friend cordovaariel_  and we won! But on… https://t.co/Qd5AeIfes2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstantesly13 @philkoenig54 @jackson4willis #ditto Our country will be in good hands!]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALLLL this is no joke @madiklause are looking to buy some rainbow kitten surprise tickets on feb 20 HMUUUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshua_lepe @ScottDKushner I can name several more teams I can say the same thing about. But of course, this kind… https://t.co/XQEhMQRuQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondFischer @purabruja The dramatic pool pic is for sure me. https://t.co/ghRWFzn3I0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chung Li BEAUTY... KO! @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/Mdw0moLAoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownEyedGirl23 GOOD! Celebrate all the victories! In your corner cheering loudly for you always!! https://t.co/3tgDEMchnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg headed into work but trying to watch GMA just for a chance to see you guys! #HangingTough30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it’s sexist but not by you.  Because if she were physically unattractive Trump would never have said he would d… https://t.co/V4lDLt3yq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElGerryChicago @silvestrelpv @udlap @AreliPaz @RobertoSosaMx @MiguelMier Escribí esta nota hace varios días, pero… https://t.co/TNyNUWfte0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the #IrishtotheCore #Sweepstakes daily for a chance to win the grand prize and instant prizes up to $100! https://t.co/3aSRkRdceB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I acted different back when I wore a nose ring. The nose stud life hasn't been the same 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[like yeah it would be nice to see everything that happens but like their safety is so much nicer akska]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is already following her on Instagram. It’s creepy. Hope she stands him up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep thinking about the time I watching Nicole almost die choking on sushi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking alongside his lawyer last week, Marks said there was inadequate security in place on the day he was attack… https://t.co/QEnlKTurDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all better get the scary momo bitch off the tl I will throw my phone away]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the perks of having kids is getting spring break again!! #springbreak2019 #shouldigetaspraytan]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@repgregwalden Thank you sir FOR the people!  Big govt healthcare, single payer system is not the answer to health… https://t.co/1rTjpYztzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is the president allowed to go to events with a fake person pretending to be his wife😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop 6: Your Place!! Stromboli!!! #beersandbears #hersheytrip2019 @ Your Place https://t.co/TUsaOMXubl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump #Trump2020 #DemocratsAreDestroyingAmerica #DemocratCorruption #DemocratsHateAmerica al… https://t.co/uhJ8VvSbD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love our girls!!❤️💛🏀📣 Way to bring home the Ring! @hala_corral @PHSLadyFalcons1 @Prairie_AD @CheerPrairie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dukewindsor388 Give these to your Dad 😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘😘… https://t.co/wHZUxTMaUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toast Tuesdays are still a thing... right? Why not switch up your avocado toast with a little mango! 🥑💃🏻 This sweet… https://t.co/UZnEwjpoah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oh_em_rochelle That's it. That's the whole story. It's a 13 year old car, so that's about as exciting as it gets. https://t.co/pZtyszLGcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkythaBee @ehchurchill @hungryturkey007 @establishmentno @freddyrace14 @MarilynLavala @nightOwlbookLvr… https://t.co/TuAH3YTmsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baerriito @liltaquiito @supnesss I’m just so lazy /: https://t.co/8jHlbn8ect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennybhatt @lcheuk @Longreads @713Books @thinkhasie This makes me so happy. I'm so glad you indulged me. And that… https://t.co/pETTqXlgQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes i feel like I’m overreacting but im not im doing just enough bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow day in and 2 hours later of playing one of my favourite childhood games with my favourite little human ever. 📸… https://t.co/MF4oU9L277]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila All you have to do is follow the projections. “I know you are, but what am I?”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always rotting for @iamkamiam_  she always puts up a fight, always competitive, always gives it her all! Anyone tha… https://t.co/bM6DMGqQRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANOTHER FIRE 🔥 IN A SYRIAN HOME! This time in Fredericton NB, this morning. 😭 https://t.co/Qw1cihvIjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackTheLEOs @fairfaxsheriff @vasheriffs @NationalSheriff @FanpageLivepd @LivePDNation @K9sOfLivePD @LivePDK9… https://t.co/qgXYfQyR6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[- mentira, vc não é brasileira - sou - não, vc não parece brasileira - mas eu sou - mas vc não parece - TA BOM ENTÃ… https://t.co/SUriRzFLC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep having this same scary dream and ive frantically woken up from it like 3 times now]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you find out it’s a wig,&amp; not her natural hair/dope afro &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss the other baby brother &amp; freezing to death in NYC @ Starbucks https://t.co/4ZrY2LwJ7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc who don’t agree with me 😂 Y’all know I don’t give a fuck &amp; I’m not debating what I said cuz it’s not changing 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're the Obi-Wan for me, and other such valentines. https://t.co/7AEPoCLVPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i say all I wanna do is vibe but honestly I can’t commit w/o feeling like you’ll leave so I prepare 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freefall alcohol inks #art #abstract #abstractart #painting #contemporaryart #sea #seascape https://t.co/UCMxbMUI2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barnes and Noble is having its 2nd annual Book Haul. As you can see, I got a great haul😁 @ Barnes &amp; Noble https://t.co/Hag07BEyGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolfzyLIVE Work on new concept art.  Heres a couple examples of my stuff 😊 https://t.co/HECr6betT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[google sensed my displeasure and was like heres some wholesome content that you cant access bc you dont live in can… https://t.co/Ahh0LOnyqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who leave voicemails longer than 1 minute should be stoned in a public square.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouKnowMoreNow @maddow And I was the other way around - knew about her work on prison reform - and worked against… https://t.co/tbJholNsJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ba_maca @HowStuffWorks @HonestTea I swear this video will go viral. No one knows how to open the Honest juice pouc… https://t.co/tlJDvR4lVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #CustomerService jobs like "Starbucks Barista [Deli/Bakery Clerk]-3… https://t.co/KudPDJcA4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two #bear #sisters, named Nanook and Tutter, are exploited in demeaning shrine #circus acts. They need your help.… https://t.co/ihTf7cyF6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just thought that everyone should see this pick up line... 😂😂😂 https://t.co/Yjcdt995SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCSO: There is currently no threat to the public. The situation is now under control.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aside from a heavy duty migraine, yesterday was a beautiful day. While in deep repose, my subconscious revealed tha… https://t.co/HNVSuznDGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really @kroq? One might mention my husband @CU4ABeer 🤐 Miserable by Lit. https://t.co/PJR5wQMHfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin HS Sonic Boom is in the House! #EdisonAlumni @edison_school @SFA_SonicBoom https://t.co/oHTewBlNZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do feel for @khloekardashian, because I can see where she's coming from - she forgave Tristan, trying to s… https://t.co/uiUmvHcQsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a full on bromance! Two handsome guys fo sho @Scaramucci @JonathanBennett]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__Danna23 @caitatronn Right y’all hoes leaving me the following weekend 🖕🏽🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[SE eu for pro show, vou tentar levando uma bandeira lgbtq e uma do brasil, mas se eu for]]></document><document><![CDATA[these Ubers take me and I, silent all the way to the place I go #haiku #poetry #poem #uber #uberpoem #japan #DailyHaiku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigwavesOrris @omfcctw @emalkudama Looks yummy... Like on Great British  Baking Show 😳😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vicenews @MadisonSiriusXM I guess that's why my parents did not speak of their pasts as black people,...it was too… https://t.co/0jE3Wz01nN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hart_megibben Love this picture! #ThoseArmsandhands #CantGetPastHer #ShesInItToWin #GoLADYTITANS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My colonists are not  happy with the taxes from Queen Fischetti... Using @Flipgrid to share their voice on how they… https://t.co/wBMr5iTVLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdMass @LivePdFans @OfficialLivePD @Bran_Blackburn @dancesareo @BigFishUSA @Bifflawson @MayorBillCarp… https://t.co/XjzPFP870l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotOmerta Trump tells America that immigrants are a national threat, enough to make it a national emergency. T… https://t.co/bYjYW0LRbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just over heard my 7yo tell me 3yo “There’s no evidence against me, so I’m innocent!” 🤣🤣🤣  His mom may or may not b… https://t.co/Fm78DojD64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS What else is new look around they all over most  Everyday I wait to see who else is going to be charged… https://t.co/0twm7xd4Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx for sharing, @insightmeditationcommunityDC! ❤️ https://t.co/KsB7FEICYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to a strip club tonight for the first time in my life. Some guy pulled a baseball bat to fuck us up. Moral o… https://t.co/M0ELqeSvT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[See if grew up doing this multiple times you would of figured out to grab a wet napkin and just wipe the rest]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING just two days after the sailor depicted in Downtown Sarasota's "Unconditional Surrender" statue, George M… https://t.co/heP1WzHKYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judith82438721 We know he’s Fake, for God sakes fake hair , fake tan, fake President, fake wife , fake university,… https://t.co/taOp9E2W09]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV RED beat the Killeen Kangaroos 8-0. #GoTigers https://t.co/gH63xbSwJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So... I watched the trailer. Initial impression - a minute and half of darkness with familiar voices saying dramati… https://t.co/5mXMwe1mvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesLottJunior @GenieFrancis @MauraWest just watched the ep and WOW🔥😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#picoftheday #centralpark #nyc #blackandwhite #canon en New York, New York https://t.co/UKeNtEfDzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could’ve written you another letter but... fingers cross this weather keeps up so I can blurt it all out in person… https://t.co/kBUgJt64eh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want to know what part of my brain is broken that makes me act the way i do https://t.co/Vqwy39jhgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[*in the car listening to tell me when to go* avner: is this a christmas song]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to need to be hooked up to a life machine after this season!!!! #GameOfThrones @GameOfThrones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lumpy got comfy in my laundry basket #LumpytheCat #catsofinstagram #cat @ Santa Rosa, California https://t.co/2i0qWdwMQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are certain things that don’t bother me anymore like they used to 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VGKWarMachine @GoldenKnights @goldenpipeslv @BarkAndreFurry @VGKFlamingo @justinandgreg @TheGildedJester @VGKim88… https://t.co/TdTiXeRH6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[... there should be a rule... no Kardashian’s related content till after 9am. #theytoomuch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StaceyPrussman @PawlingN @KelleyCostigan @Laurie_March @MaryCalviTV @MhairiCalveyAct @LexiHansler @KateDaviesSpeak… https://t.co/sSDoMJiutS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfc62 I've got a cheap portable TV I'm trying to fix. If I get it working, I might do my best to copy that wooden… https://t.co/Fzibi6Nw0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cool invention for the ladies on the beach is awesome. You will be going to the beach more often withbthis inven… https://t.co/VLid0eg7sY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 11th #dool #days  Mon Mar 11th  @oliviakeegann @TMegiaAI10 https://t.co/6poPfrMz8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP  Not one GOP Rep. even tried to claim that Cohen’s testimony about Trump didn’t amount to wrongdoing. Ins… https://t.co/UXolfSSJDm]]></document></documents></author>