<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KyleClark Was that sent to you tied to a rock through the front window?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kid, if you're coming in 15+ late with a fresh Boba, don't expect any slack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clzimmer33 @Steelersdepot @WillieMcGinest @nflnetwork They won Super Bowls with less think about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[“80+ Basketball” An inspiring true story of attitude over age https://t.co/viId8Jjsl8 🏀 #Education #Leadership https://t.co/0TnBgDfswc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Congregation Ale House Chapters https://t.co/L4YzjjT9gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen again to my financial news bulletin from #WallStreet #NewYork on behalf of @BlackdownIFA on @TauntonsToneFM… https://t.co/bkzrgwoVOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the @TimbersFC were playing a home match. 19 degrees and snowing.  Providence Park would be standing room only! #RCTID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowed-in senior who spent months living off supplies in home, dug out by @OttawaPolice: https://t.co/OJSnod9T7c… https://t.co/82BelCJQOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Do you just look for anything to pick when it comes to Republicans?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@osvelcantu @Skolvikings_1 @vikings_es @Arg_Vikings @SKOLreportSK @realistic_randy @BohlenMatthew La lista de FAs e… https://t.co/Aw3JDsfCVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shayhags Thank you! I think I put too much blue cheese but this is what happens when Mackenzie isn’t with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a good weekend. Dog sitting this little guy, Walking in the park listening to nature, Finding dirt roads,… https://t.co/FUcLeXShKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to @VisitDurango to report on the massive snowstorm pounding the southwest corner of Colorado right now! 2+ fee… https://t.co/3Vrv7zBuvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amelia__bball @SLAM_HS @AEBLHOOPS @Born2hoop2 @TeamBWright1 @wcsBHSAD Say less!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charmie910 @KamalaHarris When they don’t I call them out.  Like Harris.  Anyone who supports illegal mmigration is… https://t.co/h9POBvNlX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck @APjagsbball @Mr_Stowe Tonight in your district game! Defense stay tenacious! #gojags]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craftbeerjoe @GLBC_Cleveland @zappafaye @ephoustonbill @badhopper @JohanBBT @OkiTimes @cellmavin @qblacklock… https://t.co/YBCZ4sylPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday February 16 - MSNBC Daily:    Trump undermines emergency declaration as soon as he makes it;      Developm… https://t.co/p0yowRP75J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CocaCola Hey, here's a suggestion.  On your 12-packs of soda, put the scan bar on the end or one of the sides.  It… https://t.co/zicsDV2aW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews #TownHallForThePeople would making public airwaves free for political campaign ads for a set time redu… https://t.co/0NLVnscJgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who allowed Rani to send me this set?   I’m too hype otw to work! https://t.co/yJL9TWOeND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for another warm one? More 80s on the map today. Here is a quick weather rundown! @WFLA https://t.co/jDwZ21rld8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eventually I had the opportunity to get my own place, but never had the kind of money to eat "well". For a straight… https://t.co/6bBeXxO9f5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going down THIS Saturday!!!!! FREE TO THE PUBLIC. Tyme 2 Network BLACK BUSINESS EXPO. Live Entertainment On De… https://t.co/3IgnbJ4Xgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BronwenWalker I’m delighted #InTheFlesh inspired you to become a filmmaker! Very humbled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have people I send car memes to then I have people I send funny memes to, life’s good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlimLightskin_ Oh I know of hoes will find a pregnant friend and use her pee test to fuck with niggas smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[That hub world in Diddy Kong Racing, but only if I get one of those carts while I’m there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattSerweKETV Thanks for the info, will be an interesting drive into work...!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/fTJumKiNtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think all men should be forced to be nude in public and not allowed to have an erection?]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the next Bank Shot, I hope we hear a one-on-one with James Dolan. You deserve it @Schmeelk that would be awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassiscjo @BillKristol @neeratanden @HillaryClinton Uh... hacked 4 times]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made the move and decided to get clicked up today. Joined the Tigers and it's about to be a doozy. #lafc… https://t.co/xPy5Ke0F14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kokhorseracing @LaurelPark @keeneland Your paddock image is exactly what I normally see from the bar when I’m at the track !]]></document><document><![CDATA[can ppl stop making songs with titles that sound like its gunna be gay and then the song is not gay at all pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel rotten. Was going to fast today. Ate some cheese sticks without thinking. Catching up on the @startrekcbs I mi… https://t.co/7PIHGhVrDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMurphdog916 Absolutely, let’s not forget the clips might suck the rest of the year too, lake shows been strugg… https://t.co/tV401x0UOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeNews  Trump calls says he's popular among 93% of Republicans  https://t.co/MZPv7IlVnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFFGator In a vacuum, what is Godwin worth in your opinion? Either in picks, players, etc. 10 tm, PPR, 1 QB dynasty league]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMaxineWaters @MaxineWaters Thank you Mr. President! Robert Kraft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkitchin63 @TNationNetwork Uuhh.... Let's see, speed limit in California is 65-70mph, 55mph for trucks, that MIGHT… https://t.co/zWZHW3z4Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in Obama Scandal History: The Tan Suit | The Daily Show https://t.co/gEqmbjEZcc via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/YoZiEt2nJk Let’s do this COLUMBUS!  It’s time to rise up DESTROYER NATION and claim your season ticket… https://t.co/qSQo8CTuGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trumpovic02 I am waiting for them to hide behind the "We were born this way" statement. What ever your kink, how y… https://t.co/Ht2BV9GEZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[👍 . . . . . #german #wurstundbier #columbus #ohio #sandwich #reuben #fries @ Wurst Und Bier https://t.co/FkVb90jFiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showers and thunderstorms continue marching eastward across Alabama... https://t.co/eCNqsz5Qex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right when i try to fall asleep this loud ass thunder wanna come outta nowhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarLord8114 @bostonsports351 @FantasyPhill @AB84 @Ihartitz @Raiders They cut the cancer out and sent him to a Cancer research center]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thicc_jonas @aaroncarter @Breitling Hardwork and never giving up is how he affords that’s look up the facts !! why… https://t.co/QNknyoHPkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah reminds me of those drier Haribo gummy bearz - Drinking a Bear-ie White by @ShortFuseBeer @ The Villages  — https://t.co/OJIYs4PZNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing a mother and her newborn being wheeled out of the hospital to the car provides such a warm feeling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Congratulations on your CNN quality of fake and inaccurate news!!! The bar is low for @AOC https://t.co/DUp8uLOFfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austin_spurs @chrissolari @Ttrice20 @AaronsInc @DrJamesShaw Were you there?  #GoGreen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Graph data standardization: It's just a graph, making gravitational waves in the real world | ZDNet https://t.co/wGIEXgIoTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryanNews3LV @GoldenKnights @SeinfeldTV @News3LV Works for Seinfeld as well as #GMGM George McPhee. https://t.co/oUeEk71b9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuchoIbarra690 Venga mi Lucho, dales una lección a toda la raza fútbolera. Un abrazo enorme mi hermano!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean there were other blown calls but how that isn't reviewable is beyond me. Eh well, I don't care who wins so g… https://t.co/q7viNO6jQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING AMERICA TRUTH. I LOVE YOU IN TRUTH ABSOLUTE. UNDER TRUTH GOD AND TRUTH JUSTICE JESUS CHRIST. SO AMERIC… https://t.co/LyLNSwmXML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyDwyer10 Good morning Dolly.. have a great Tuesday my friend blessings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandra_bodyrubs I love women of color, especially latinas curvy figure. Heck basically someone with your look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmoMagnusBane @ChadLindberg Thanks it was a hard earned accomplishment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hakalaka @BrianBabinski @BoozyBeggarChi @HVath82 @chicagobars Brian here is an expert in bags, style and general c… https://t.co/MSM5q5naq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[✝️❤️🙌🏼🥎🇺🇸8️⃣8️⃣Happy 15th Birthday to this amazing , talented , beautiful young woman !!!… https://t.co/ZzcHZ07Oqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotoriousMrBig Dip it in chocolate 🍫 for me daddy mmm looks so fucken good mmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACIE_Roses That sounds beautiful 😭 I remember bumping the water[s] all thru highschool and pieces of a man was top… https://t.co/xaRWsQE1Xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Lebron team blew a 4 seed in the west lead hmm, somehow it’s ok.  To start good and end bad when it comes to Lebron @warriorsworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDebrati Only in Scotland is self-determining to remain in the UK ignored by its nationalist government. It’s nati… https://t.co/jlcpxLPLjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mo_Sm00ve @Maused81 I’m not saying he sucks.. I’m saying he’s not a top 10 player]]></document><document><![CDATA[The secret lives of Facebook moderators in America https://t.co/IDQHum8Q9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, I  know the Oscars are too long, too overblown, not artistically focused enough, too old-white-guy, etc. All co… https://t.co/MuTVhejMwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @AmericanExpress just wrapped up a conference in Las Vegas and planning to work in your lounge prior to my ove… https://t.co/V3DC0gDd6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanicAtTheDisco here at Rodeo.  Yes rodeo scene kids are a thing... https://t.co/jp4S3U1EmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar You mean if I use one on my left arm, I need a clean one for my right arm, etc.?🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #ByeNicki on @TheTylt—NIcki Minaj is corny https://t.co/Va4G36yqu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie. Me and my brother @ReggiePJr on our way. Yup. That's the tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blazegirlsbball My wife told me I can’t make any more videos for a while 😂. Too much time editing at the kitchen table 😬.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@49erFaithful365 Thanks, Bro. ✊ I really appreciate that. #NinerFam #CaliforniaFam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Music Label Spotlight February 26, 2019  Celebrating 15 Years Of Cosmicleaf Records  Side Liner… https://t.co/m3R9runhl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The planting renaissance @FairchildGarden has gone aquatic on #WaterWednesdays with a major renovation of the Found… https://t.co/iaBFxMiWA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[AGENTES DE FISCALÍA DETIENEN A UN HOMBRE EN FLAGRANCIA DE  ROBO A UNA TIENDA DE VENTA AL MAYOREO, LO IDENTIFICAN CO… https://t.co/vjLYZeud9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino He’s got competition from Pelosi, Waters and other slime ball lefties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larryboy to the Rescue!  Free Coffee for the Parents and Grandparents! @ Madison Rose Lane School https://t.co/xDZEyV278A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ You're too kindsa, Jonathan. Pierson is mind-numbingly stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Man should have gotten more love but it just missed the mark in a few different levels. A damn shame. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be illegal for Nee Jersey to do this as its not a legal requirement for any President to show their tax… https://t.co/dFmJ3y1gvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘THE RECIPE FOR IDENTITY’  Positives , Needs and Hopes  https://t.co/CaooZzWhmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught an allergic reaction to something yesterday and broke out into hives... my lip and face are still slightly swollen😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Len_Benhardt Damn my highest is actually 123 it’s pinned to my profile cause Pokémon go was doing stupid shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr do me a favor if were gonna have a space force I want you guys to have a space can… https://t.co/Ld307eVR3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think If You’re Reading This It’s Too Late is definitely one of my favorite Drake eras]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancylee2016 #AnnCoulter's anti #Trump agenda is highlighted by demagogues like this #MIA who seems to have a very… https://t.co/8Jdcd2wOau]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward to going with friends and then getting lost and making new ones! Lol 💯 same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthemgame why are you delaying such a critical patch? Correct the fact your game doesn’t close correctly as it is… https://t.co/jX8VZkEDk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isthatkarolina @AnneMarie Maybe. I just can’t help but take it quite literally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KUSINews He's probably sleeping his hangover off at home inspector gadget.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaABC7 You just can’t hide it? You’re about to lose control and you think you like it? #tgif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already inseparable after only 4 months. ❤️ @ Plantation, Tampa, Florida https://t.co/dlcBk9Mjx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanaWWE May not agree with everything you say, but still a fan of yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjankaa I think I’m speaking too soon but I’m enjoying it a lot so far]]></document></documents></author>