<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[21m btc to be mined, 6m~ lost, and difficulty goes up. Won't there be &lt;1m BTC in total circulation by the end? Maybe less? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @BreitbartNews If I was on the staff of Empire, I'd want him fired for a stunt like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beteiligung an @Rivian: @amazon steigt ins Elektromobilität-Geschäft ein https://t.co/iRAD6ceew7 via @faznet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Range biund Friday’s with chasers losing both sides short then long today all trap games]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends were gonna bring me soup but forgot but it’s truly the thought that counts luv u guise]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an incredible day having @ManuelScott with our students and staff. #freedomwriter #powerofone https://t.co/xlmOtFqjMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriots Kraft made pies for $15 here. Boston Creampies available through the backdoor here in Wikieup.#Patriots… https://t.co/RxKCx3lg2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Maybe when you quote Mussolini to make your boring conservative point where you call liberals fascist,… https://t.co/yxrmzErdi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roadwarriorbard I like to tell people I averaged a triple single during my career. Some prople dont understand and… https://t.co/40TsCde4PG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcsportsbog fwiw to those saying “but the Nats money was deferred!” OK, but that works the other way, too. $ in ea… https://t.co/j6IYE3ykDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameBiologist @Monoclesociety @thing12games @BoardGameSpeak They are both on the front page, but we're going to pr… https://t.co/wYLy80BTuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omar will not respect our American culture, shame on the people who voted her.  Fix it Impeach her.  NOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tajjackson3  I’m so sorry this is happening... this kinda got me down man I can hear how shaky your voice is bro i… https://t.co/NsgzEd9zD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You would be so blessed to meet Bob...amazingly kind and just a delight! @bobgoff @chandabell is one of the creator… https://t.co/yBTEUDqIFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerem_moreau Thanks for the follow! Please check out my blog:   https://t.co/BPzKPSRj1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notre Dame’s Dexter Williams’ hairstyle screams “Philly” but it’s his relationship with an #Eagles player that make… https://t.co/QqWPqqTGkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight we played citadels and listened to the Beasty Boys, Butcher Babies, Rage Against The Machine and Accept. Th… https://t.co/3LWNyzwi1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Greg1MB @babe_ruths @JonHeyman Fuck you Gregory . You don’t mind if I call you Gregory do you lol 😂?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @kenzie45230 @realDonaldTrump All the rail does is allow rich folks to move out of the cesspool sanc… https://t.co/OqQiUeVjnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMauraA I've heard a lot of CRAZY excuses these MONSTERS make for committing murder. This definitely ranks in my Top 5!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished my model so now I’m contemplating if I should sleep or rearrange my entire life.   5am thoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richard_arocha líndas fotos y muy bella pareja un saludo de un colombiano en usa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyUryHolthus @goofonroof @OaklawnRacing Sal's. 50 late pk4  R6. 2,7 R7. 4,10,13 R8. 6,7 R9. 1,5,9 $18 good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I wish season 3’s true detective didn’t end. But wow what an ending 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC6 The state should have been investing all along. No excuse for not doing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Translation -  babies abandoned Venezuela Maduro - enough said. Anyone defending this regime is just as evil as the… https://t.co/RwMJjD9sdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[flyingturtle619 came and saved me from my boring hotel room in Tampa for a bro-date on the beach! Hanging with all… https://t.co/HfBLmIEJoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out at @TPAIN's album release party tonight 😀 https://t.co/JtmRacUz9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveLo510 @tonyposnanski It’s funny. Almost every review of Roma has said similar. It’s a very pretty movie but r… https://t.co/HeQukj6VYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylamarie413 @MsMollyRachael Like I said they aren't helpless and as long they are in familiar surroundings they do quite well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somhenderson At least it spit him out. If I do recall, the same thing happened to Marlin and Dory and they turned out ok🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TacoTuesday made perfect with #WildAlaskaPollock 🇲🇽 🐠 🌮! #PerfectProtein https://t.co/hXILy5zOeX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaraLaneFOX46 Thank you, @TaraLaneFOX46 — you’re a terrific office neighbor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callanbentley Also, perhaps, the evil cut leaf teasel, the bane of every roadway mower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badboy_Rd2 @ZhenosSZN @ChronicTendy @Eagl3FN He doesn’t go to school he wouldn’t know lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StartKyleOrton Junking vs being able to maneuver the “fastest ship in the galaxy” ... It’s like a mechanic jumping… https://t.co/0lalNHRRWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satanisfemale @thisisinsider For sure I mean officers were white then. I wish it wasn't the case but they focused… https://t.co/BGSx6VpBep]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Transactions Representative - https://t.co/6xIFoiKzgf #BusinessMgmt #Bloomington, MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceyJesus @nytimes @realDonaldTrump Their parents could be Virginia Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ngtcollectibles Being from Canada would be a nice touch but screws Rockies.....🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bishubish Ey los 25 millones qie esstamos fuera de mexico lindo y querdo estamos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning @cuesa #farmersmarket in #SanFrancisco ... #travel #foodies #goodeats #freshfood #farmtotable… https://t.co/60palRssEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Letting truckers know to stay in the 270 only lane early will help all drivrts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad about #NorthKoreaSummit Certainly wish talks had ended with concrete, verifiable progress. Hopefully, relat… https://t.co/MISpmhPae8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samantha tried a sea sick patch. This is her first time having cotton mouth 😂 she’s not happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGCBand crushed it tonight in #Buffalo  @townballroom   Made a new fan tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause some days you don't be touching food due to the feeling in the pit of your stomach, this is facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no estaba en la Quinta,  la escuché clarito e igual no me rei, y eso que la sigo y admiro. Hay que aprender en v… https://t.co/IT9L2Bak8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch this great interview with @IamJonSantiago  Proud to have him as my state rep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NWC Player of the year for girls basketball was Blufftons Alivia Koening. Pirates coach Eric Garmatter nabs coach of the year honors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNC @SpeakerPelosi This is your idiot racist bigot. Who along with @AOC are the vile slugs of your party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#metoo #xanaxnotneeded #nobars #nomedicine ok maybe #caffeine #😂🤣 #❤️salvadordali  @CostaDomenic #mydayinsp… https://t.co/3ZJbvZhWIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@praisegirl85 Hi there, I have been following u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the most ridiculous snow day ever. We used to have to fight white walkers on our way to school back in my d… https://t.co/5tBSFHyYMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michael Russo you finally forced me to join the athletic I better get some early scoops during the deadline!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Starbucks at Mariott hotel in Louisville, KY https://t.co/wkUplMA2eN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCenter @AdamSchefter For A QB That's Not Terrible I'm Just Not Paying Foles  https://t.co/ME49EjnKKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so tired of you “i want a snowbunny” ass niggas following me. leave me the fuck alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning and didn't have power at 530am at Kennedy and Radnor Ave @TorontoHydro #GhostTown #creepy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta admit. I flipped off two drivers who felt the need to pass me while I was going the speed limit on an icy two… https://t.co/OgTusG514d]]></document><document><![CDATA[brooke if you see this, i can’t wait to meet u soon and ily more than ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExchangeGoddess I also mentioned to him that it was horribly innapropriate - he got a bunch of shame comments from… https://t.co/6C4uV6JMeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. Easily the worst crowd I've ever seen. Even worse than Atlanta and I didn't think that was possible. Maybe it'… https://t.co/Tofwpd3ZPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCLARENRCF1 lafelipa, marica, ASESINA DE MAS DE MEDIO MILLÓN DE MEXICANOS, RATERA DEL PATRIMONIO NACIONAL RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that say "I hate daylight savings time." I don't think they realize that means I would prefer the sun go dow… https://t.co/ssmnmg0afi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless Stop it Skip! Why you do that? https://t.co/K3ucQpApre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @AngelGotti5 @SpeakerPelosi Don’t forget Kamala Harris ✅.    @KamalaHarris - yes they all Tweeted lon… https://t.co/DGbV1rR7jc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a standard policy of not bargaining with terrorists.. duck girl... duck]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #PYNKFriday again with @janellemonae’s ‘Dirty Computer’, this time with an amazing lenticular cover and presse… https://t.co/VQKJstZWN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie Clearly Washington is a hell of a lot easier to navigate than Boston w/ its seedy,backstabbing,dishonest ,li… https://t.co/4mrt0O3AoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This happed last year at @DunkMSOfficial looking forward to this year! All info available at https://t.co/9zihsctyi0 https://t.co/GixD02lFUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[DumboRATS R To Blame For Shut Down An National Emergency ! When Will The Obama Clinton Crap Era STOP 🛑! All BS !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph ---. Barometer 30.012 in, Rising. Temperature 66.1 °F. Rain today 0.06 in. Humidity 93%]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife thinks I am lame.   Cause I can't spell original.  Wait is that right? https://t.co/aXi9Cly2xE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ The Kardashians and their high-profile relationships with pro athletes https://t.co/q6m3GPAWko]]></document><document><![CDATA[To-do list:  ✔️  Wake up  ✔️  Make coffee         Contact your state lawmakers          about issues that are important        to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[L'imposteur, un bon titre, Netflix doit être à la veille d'en faire une série. Catherine Dorion ne pourra plus dire… https://t.co/mFUQAw5eqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's d-pairings for #IAWild: Bartkowski-Prosser; Soucy-Belpedio; Kapla-Warner; Menell. Starting goalie: Kaapo… https://t.co/qQ9Ujs7uL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jared_Huggins They could if they want 36+ million tied up in two PG’s and they still need to add a few pieces at least so it’s not logical]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CBJ fans having fits over #Duclair’s ice time need to take emotion out of the equation. This isn’t his 4th stop in… https://t.co/Y8aa0IDM4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahcpr Are there letters there? BTW if the Devil appeared on earth he’d sign Bibles too....cf Albert Brooks Broadcast News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else get random bits of music stuck in their head, like, oh, say the ditty Beverly hums to herself in the TN… https://t.co/BQW0HGRqFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLA sad!  sometimes one has to use discretion as to their destinations...  North Korea is not even in the top 100… https://t.co/ojwdn23MNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zack Hess on Friday Landon Marceaux on Saturday Jaden Hill on Sunday  Eric Walker will start on Wednesday   #LSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please do not give in to the demands of the radical left democrats. They do not care about America’s security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this and couldn’t resist #flowers @ Simple Photography Services https://t.co/yEpBa8hFJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian_jenks @TTP_Ray @rayd1475 @ScoopB You didn't hear those rumors?  Lololololol. On that draft day that was bein… https://t.co/GIwkIQvO4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that’s an interesting tunnel. I guess this shares Grr water https://t.co/uO1X6CJ35H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leo, our 15 year old toothless feline King, has to visit Dr. Felinefine tomorrow. He gets so much food in his sinus… https://t.co/C5D2tezJ2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henrywilburn1 @LastStand2019 @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Nah.   It’s a shame you’re too dumb too understand why it didn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn't this look good?  It's a chicken and a beef enchilada each. @ Avila's El Ranchito - Orange https://t.co/wcAbKDvHuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Housekeeping is going to be less than thrilled when they clean this locker... Errrrr..hotel room. Quick turnaround… https://t.co/znvOBzecUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/R6nj3CtYBh  Check the video I shot of vancecreekbridge @ Vance Creek Bridge https://t.co/5BXgWkJDgy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrazyAF_ButCute You’re very inviting sweetie! Love it! 😉😘 https://t.co/zHdMsau6Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the folks that protect him contrary to their oath of office need to go with him where ever that may be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP Guess who now sounds like a complete idiot? Donald Treasonous tiny hands Drumpf is no longer standing with any… https://t.co/JUC6gmehcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AubreyHughFree1 When is trudeau NOT under the influence of drugs? (alcohol is a drug) He probably wakes up high!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying good bye to my current insta account soon to come! https://t.co/ZZSZynnWdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Client: if you don’t insinuate that I won’t get it done in your short time frame I won’t insinuate that you wo… https://t.co/llLgSg3GeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDKA Oh but wait residents and business owners Mayor Peduto and counsel are going to waste your tax dollars to fig… https://t.co/vKf0gO9gy1]]></document></documents></author>