<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I took an edible and did my makeup. Now I’m all glammed up at midnight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mog7546 @lvingfree5678 It doesn’t take FoxNews hosts long to grab on to any event to advance their propaganda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a night off to actually watch a concert Thanks to #vettix we are able to see #kiss “The Final Tour Ever… https://t.co/gSd6uhrGkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaarreaza @TareckPSUV @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama https://t.co/cNGQ5FnOGk ESCUCHA ESTO MALDITA RATA ASESINA , ES… https://t.co/NTC3IKPZC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Amy no I have hidradenitis suppartavia, the mildest dose like my scoliosis.. ahhh these doses. Y’all my disease lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[So.. I a piece of my conch earring fell into my ear and I had to get it flushed out today.. these things only happen to me I swear 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiffanifaison Assuming based on your tweet it was for a fundraiser and I mean that is just rule #1. Honestly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our adorable princess, May #God keep you in his safety, and keep away every devil, evil from your beautiful soul an… https://t.co/QGlVaj3b3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne Talk about an incomprehensible way to say something.  I can't comment on something that makes absolutely no sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the Democrat party of 2019. They don’t even try to hide their radical views 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m the only girl in the world that doesn’t really like getting flowers lol. Like I would rather get a… https://t.co/HXkeG8Rl9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t condone making fun of anyone’s weight , who am I to do this ? It’s his ego that’s large and his stupidity . https://t.co/rEQwbNShw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the game constantly evolving and transitioning more towards power and distance, make sure your maximizing your… https://t.co/Jce3e6qNBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HybridPython2 @sianoresist I meant steroids enhance muscle strength, so does biology in the male. Not rocket scien… https://t.co/vLeSz5npS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princes of variety!! Loving this season of Come On! so far  #떴덥 #떴덥보스 #더보이즈 #보이는스쿨 #the_boyz  https://t.co/1BxWwgfKz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had to mop up the floor after that dunk. #FearTheDeer #Bucks https://t.co/6tj3Dh1f5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun day yesterday seeing the Dolly Parton exhibit (and others) at the @thegrammymuseum, plus breakfast at The Pantr… https://t.co/b1WMYvFeb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[0-10, 10 being super sad. How sad would it be if I went to Fenton’s alone to eat and get ice cream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headdock @katsin @BostonGlobe Trying to. Have been tapered 85% since 07-2017. I don't know what to do I am suffering so badly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I need is.... #coffee ☕️ #love 💗 #newmoon #choosejoy #whynotme #whynotyou #authorsofinstagram 💗 @ Encinitas, Ca… https://t.co/645ucfZsyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nfs @fentybeauty did revolutionize the beauty industry people like to forget and downplay it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter But nothing like small whole roasted potatoes with olive oil and rosemary!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lockers? Dances? Sleepovers? Heart break? Zits? How do you help your middle school students through their milestone… https://t.co/hO9Ndtveca]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m10penny @IWC Myyyyy boyfriend is stationed in fort Campbell and it makes me too excited that I’m less than an hou… https://t.co/p0O4QZrXW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariadorosario o povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I told my friends I wasnt drinking and blacked out that same night]]></document><document><![CDATA[IRA, Foundational Skills, and Guided Reading was front and center for this 2nd grade teacher.  Practice was evident… https://t.co/AJ8zRt904y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UberFacts Or maybe we are just freaks who don't like to mess with perfect cup of joe. @chockfullonuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sk8ksw @usmcdoordie @njgypsyg My daughter became a vegetarian 8 years ago at age 8 when she learned about how we g… https://t.co/8Ypv0tFFap]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now Bryce knows a lot about chicks! We love @gardendaleel and Mrs. Bensko ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-shirt graphic from my first Women’s Grappling Camp February 2009 in Valencia, California. . . . #bjj #bjjwomen… https://t.co/A6dhnmFDQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who make stuff up about other girls to get ahead and to impress a boy ultimately lose. #RememberThat… https://t.co/lRB624Wa4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricFoltz @old_osc @SpeakerPelosi @SenFeinstein @KamalaHarris @tedlieu @SenSchumer @TheDemocrats @DNC @dccc Yes, b… https://t.co/ilUsFvnKRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convinced my daughter’s Dad to get a facial 😆😏he’s really enjoying everything except for the products being cold 😎🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[my choice in careers is not going to allow this but i’ll dream about it while i make my money]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile Little cowards change their sex to take over women’s’ sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day fun in Room 34! 💗  @MsSantimauro @FJDugan @MTPSNJ https://t.co/dDPJmN7KoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird And Judge Jackson says “no problem” I’ll just give radicals a gag order; that should do it, right?… https://t.co/XY49dj3sZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[3s are the worst age ...... like someone please help because I’m struggling tonight 😭😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimi_oolala She really will I’m glad that I’ve grown as a woman and i miss you 😘 she’ll be upset if we kept that u… https://t.co/POgv62x7Zw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m considering quiting music and becoming a cable guy so I can be in strangers houses and look through their things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer, que viajaba rumbo a Los Cabos, vi saltar una #ballenagris, fue algo muy impresionante ya que desde el carro s… https://t.co/bYUvLDMQ0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhondaZimlich Oh girl, I couldn’t fly without it. I’m certain I’m going to die every time I get on a plane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Obvious with comment “This is MAGA country” IN CHICAGO????!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando por fin te das cuenta que solo tienes como 2 amigos y uno de esos es tu novio 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilylahm If you took a couple extra days off between the snow days and the weekends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConductPromo @charliekirk11 Why? Medicare costs my disabled hubs $135/m out of his $1200 check. Had to wait 7 mont… https://t.co/i2BKBR45pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I said I don’t care about the kardashians BUT.. I will say if they use this drama on the show, that’s messed… https://t.co/r5871XU3rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men really ain’t shit. I’ve been friends with this dude for a few years and all the sudden he gets a girlfriend (fi… https://t.co/nfl0seULlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your quick guide to the digital services #tax from @PwCUS @PamelaFOlson and Karl Russo. Tax reform and the digital… https://t.co/yIOokQrBTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re in town for south by pleaaaase stay on dirty or Rainey. Thanks. #psa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Philadelphia International Airport - @phlairport in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/CxJlZvarkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who booked Nicki tour? Some of these shows seem to be in obscure venues]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smile for you. #mirth #giggle #smile #laughable https://t.co/y2AlKC9m0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Laker622 @realDonaldTrump The media helped Trump win the 2016 election.  You watch his speech then you watch their… https://t.co/lDhU7yia80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk IF YOU’RE BREAKING NEWS.. WHY AREN’T YOU COVERING THE CORRUPTION FINALLY BEING EXPOSED ON McCABE, COMEY, ST… https://t.co/EhtnT6Z3ZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[However rare true love may be,it is less so than true friendship. Albert Einstein https://t.co/hT31Bk2crG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve heard having heartburn when pregnant means your baby will have a lot of hair and if that’s the case then my ch… https://t.co/GxJSJX6Osk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not everyone was looking at the camera but aren’t they the cutest?! ❤️ @ Columbia Marionette Theatre https://t.co/ifkcImmkhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re going to a potluck but you’re a horrible cook https://t.co/VsVMkatefQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJDzialo @SocialPowerOne1 Thanks! I'm an animal lover too My baby Little Bit. https://t.co/W6BWJ3fzuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffrey_doucet I almost lost interest with that first sentence, but the end was a hit!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I promise you Twitter, that I don’t give a fuck about when Jim or Susie tweeted or retweeted someone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOOM: Trump’s Economy Just Got FLOODED With Billions Of Dollars And Thousands Of Jobs https://t.co/OYJIQ43tNZ via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another #TrumpHumper. Huge shocker, huh??  #GOPOnTheUSSHypocrite  Second REPUBLICAN Boston #billionaire linked to F… https://t.co/QOdRzp9XHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yung bisita ng may ari nagfufun run siguro panay dumadagundong yung taas e 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angryinYVR @keithbaldrey @bcliberals Here is a compilation painstakingly researched from actual expenditure record… https://t.co/jfzq9T3S3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend's worst friend is here will get out of bathtub when it's over]]></document><document><![CDATA[13. When people seek medical advice for their pets on the internet rather than taking them to the vet...and their a… https://t.co/nm2JX7rnfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormIsUponUs Yea unfollowed her yesterday ... every time a seen her post anger would rise up an I’m like she is not good to follow]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Disease Spread Through Bug Bites Kills Up to 30,000 People Each Year (scary) https://t.co/rOdv8h2vxp #globalcitizen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcdragon @JTreliving @manjitminhas @Guzzo_Vincenzo @MicheleRomanow @lanemerrifield @ArleneDickinson See y'all tonight, gang!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sam: Did you dye your hair?  Me: I did  Sam: Looks nice. Really brings out the depression in your eyes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go off sis 👏🏻 bye bye @jordynwoods you home wrecking bitch, we don’t Stan for your kind🙅🏻‍♀️👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel the same, you are such a blessing to so many. My prayers are always with you and your husband, for all you d… https://t.co/xg05Q8ZJrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimroberts361 I need at least an hour or so! But it also helps when I know I get to have a hot breakfast. Don’t ha… https://t.co/bz05Ty4MGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TGDsquad @freddiehighmore @GoodDoctorABC @gooddrwriters @danieldaekim @todavidkim @SLfrom Yes plz my heart cannot… https://t.co/ig6WWxAcee]]></document><document><![CDATA[PROTECT #ANIMALS FROM TORTURE!  Please JOIN Us to #BanLegholdTraps  now!  https://t.co/78MlmqfaVp https://t.co/aWP6gJJ1GA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemon, honey, and dash of crown. That aught to get me through the work day.   #nosickdaysallowed #cantkeepmedown… https://t.co/jbUtcgq4N1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Allied Universal Professional Security Officer - Oxnard" sound appealing to you, follow u… https://t.co/7wlUobzQ10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiromuWonBOSJ25 Hiromu's Valentine's pictures are out... and he drew himself as muscular... and as a candy wrapper.😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleevxo We needa go to the Mexican store &amp; get some cus ion got nomo lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music Meadows Ranch is a magical place near Westcliffe, CO.  Life is simpler and yet rich with a ranching tradition… https://t.co/Q0iG0JsBOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamscrabble @Cernovich I acquired Wisdom and I keep on learning... When some shout me down, I just let them.  I know what I know....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbrineellis @Rachel_horse64 I didn’t know what coin was so i urban dictionary’ed it. When searching, Connor comes… https://t.co/hmi6u0GNA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugly points at this time of the year = two points move on. Game up on the Pens. #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loretta_Swit @Newsweek @alda @alanalda @AldaCenter I remember it well!  I still watch the show almost every night.… https://t.co/syefDxHKQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the wait, the flight and the cold! Cafe Carlyle is the perfect New York venue to host the perfect voice! Lovi… https://t.co/dbSyxRDBt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeWren @dislaw @TheFlaBar @kyblueblood @diffbrains @DisabilityRtsFL @OHCircuitRider Fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boygeorge..what look you have...you're always so gorgeous looking ..love you boy💋 https://t.co/jG3dZV6L2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter decided to unfollow a couple people I noticed this am. I'm missing quite a few, let me know and I'll ref… https://t.co/K69zy1G8oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, the recommendation is to keep doing that. https://t.co/qLkhUBbCNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mustbeaj_ Good morning 😃 AJ !! It’s gorgeous here in Florida!! Have a Blessed Weekend!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to dispel the myth the our growth is a burden on our infrastructure. @Kriseman #SOTC https://t.co/jbItlxZkEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i have fucking tea to spill none of my friends wanna text back in .00001s like i need them to]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al menos yo si di lo mejor de mi, yo si me enamore pero de qué sirvió? Si al final me hicieron sentir la peor persona que no valía nada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not wanna go to court with him my head hurts and i just wanna sleep.. But i know as soon as i don’t go they gone try some bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the day, everything went to crap and I ruined my hair. It hasn’t grew the same since.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad what happens to children with #disabilities all over the world. We can do better. #SDGs #TeachSDGa… https://t.co/2DiUkMhTye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seoul Gangbuk-gu District Mayor Park Gyum-Soo: Seoul Gangbuk-gu, Korea, Shut down the illegal dog meat farms, marke… https://t.co/j41NJhnAHG]]></document></documents></author>