<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[First time I’ve ever built something. Can only get better I guess. https://t.co/iOzMaiCtMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Competitor’s meeting at St. Mary’s. Inside the mind of a team racing world champion coach. #college #sailing #east… https://t.co/rq6zkI65bS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hill credibility ratings have dropped to zero - all lies, fake polls]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really trying but nothing seems to work right now I miss you so much @OberdierCali more than anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[What should’ve been the super bowl halftime show. #atlhoe https://t.co/CF6tRsCsyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally wtfff? how the hell is making a drink w starbucks and wearing an apron “cosplaying as the working class”… https://t.co/H5TwtnjdNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[... and we’re off again! #sxsw2019 #SXSW @ Austin Convention Center https://t.co/lpz9NwGhh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dumbest thing in college sports is having students camp outside an arena for a week, in the winter, to get into… https://t.co/9eLW5f9DQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @Raptors for a super entertaining evening! Enjoy the all-star break!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday March 5 - AlterNet Top Stories:    Harvard psychoanalyst explains why Trump’s ‘grandiose paranoid character… https://t.co/qLuGo1yJdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You sound like somebody who's quaking in his boots... don't worry just curl up in bed with a chees… https://t.co/oSZPECrQRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The struggle is real.  Epic adventures with Ben. @ Cover All Bases https://t.co/ZcGJaOmz83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shesatornado I don’t know. The media is fickle. I’d never even heard of Jussie Smollett two weeks ago, now he’s a household name]]></document><document><![CDATA[the jonas brothers are reuniting and that has to be the best news I’ve heard all week .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricGuillot14 @TracksideMikeN @cannonshell You fat guys sweat a lot 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Fresno St HC Pat Hill @unlvfootball practice this morning. #UNLVFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning #Omaha!!  It’s cold out this morning so here is a throwback photo.  Have a great day. @OPerformingArts… https://t.co/PqIRxva7fB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen día #FelizLunes...se llama vida...hay que ir por ella...! en Hermosillo, Sonora https://t.co/nfMR6SFUno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox4sportstalk @Aaron_Torres Just doesn’t make it right, it’s cheating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonHeyman That will be waste of money obviously these two gonna suck in regular season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get to work. @david_smarty @Birkrjradio https://t.co/vXHxCrV3hW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#photography #random #city #night #nightphotography #light #dark #traffic #fun #niagarafalls #canada #ontario #neon… https://t.co/u8SoJns26o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance @HillaryClinton Only two you two? Still think it's classified? Still unsure what needs transparenc… https://t.co/PL4cDo9lex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on the 3D model of Haruo, manga and anime High Score Girl. Starting the work. Let's see what comes up. 😊👍… https://t.co/vfUW3T19L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@intellipus ...and I just got blocked by @BabakTaghvaee for absolutely no reason. The internet (and the world!) are going bonkers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenas noches, que descansen y disfruten de un agradable sueño. Nature is Awesome. https://t.co/6kONYRx8TW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantstern @DebbieforFL @RVAwonk @maddow @TeamPelosi @olgaNYC1211 @Mimirocah1 @JoyceWhiteVance @MollyJongFast… https://t.co/mS9GsYZf0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX T-Pain was the most surprisingly good, but come on...do we really believe he's a better singer tha… https://t.co/mHzlndhuQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/OmsDpfXIf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the anime arena fighter community mad scrubby when it comes to how people play and what characters they use?… https://t.co/OYN3ztTFKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Utter bullshit. Republicans have a perverse perspective on reality. Pathetic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @maddow Sure! After all the Chump (Donald J. to be exact) didn't really make a mistake in his State of… https://t.co/xmmmsbRBl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#5G fixed wireless access has already been launched commercially in North America! What's next? Read in the… https://t.co/34cbaohzJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is pretty clear, now, they did something and tried to cover it up and just going crazy now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Midnight is my favorite time of day😜 #TuesdayThoughts #Entrepreneur https://t.co/fYCukGM0m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StableAEIOU @Gingrich_of_PA My uncle didn’t last 6 months once he found out he had it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisella80 Y se pusieron los chalecos amarillos!!🙄🙄  Pense que era broma. Wow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[VVM Movie Awards 2018! Good Movies Part 1 @ VVM Studio Headquarters https://t.co/BOQLua9iDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie  awww...i love the banner we had made for Kimmy hunnie. i am so in love with you, and we both adore our daughter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que estoy destinado a que a cada mujer que le hablé y/o escriba me diga que ya tiene novio.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmommi @PressSec @POTUS We do not have open borders. It’s a myth. Fake news from a fake President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't care about @pablohidalgo anymore.  It's all about @HolocronKeeper now.  He's my favorite Lucasfilm Storygroup dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for attending and the kind words. Credit goes to @VMware @AnnJohnson123 @vmugteam and @MyVMUG staff. It was… https://t.co/nZ0HRZBuR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlakeLinton @SenSanders 23 trillion is socialist debt.  Who’d we bailout most recently?  Farmers?  Bernie simply p… https://t.co/AVngoErfJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BankofAmerica asked me to verify my information was correct. They had me listed as a taxi driver. 😵 Now I'm trying… https://t.co/u0g7A7wjlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could just nap through the winter. Like some mouse lemurs. And also be as cute as a mouse lemur.  Ok, fine… https://t.co/ObZ1guC248]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfternoonNapper Thinking of you. Add me to the list wondering how I can help from afar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelmchale’s new show on @netflix reminds me of the soup! Super funny and they can swear now. Screw @etnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please stand up for the National Anthem...  Three, six, nine, damn she fine, hopin she can sock it to me one mo tim… https://t.co/kht1GX6fnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSCMayor @SethAbramson Actually it’s predicated on the theory that Obama’s policy is better than the one we have… https://t.co/UMXusrYDx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatrinNye @VictoriaLIVE She's a traitor.  She married someone that sought to kill U.K. soldiers.  She gave ISIS ma… https://t.co/DMn2Osx9Nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway #TheEvilLeft If you could stand behind Our Flag hoisting it high, waving it for all our honorable dead… https://t.co/GtOAFao3gz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Mob Psycho 100 comments people made in this video really caught me by surprise😯 - https://t.co/G2t7A40snF https://t.co/usJBW9BmMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ILikeItWhen People respond to my tweets sometimes I think I'm in the Twitter universe  All alone. https://t.co/5mToRL6ZD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 Would love to be a guest on your show to discuss the status of #Disability in America and how we are st… https://t.co/0SAXfuwA44]]></document><document><![CDATA[caught in the moment, tangled up in ur sheets 😇 https://t.co/MM8hIhrM95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodySwainston Feed is first  Genetics are second in terms of performance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burritoblaster sounds like a beta bitch i bet satsuki would eat rats with her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kerri_Lynn14 That seems to be the unanimous answer. So why do I feel so conflicted ?? But thanks girl ❤️ I’m slowl… https://t.co/zaoOcoOLhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right now, somewhere in Vietnam, Trump is eating a very big bowl of Phucked 🍲 #CohenTestimony #CohenCongressionalTestimony #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Max_TO @BreitbartNews In other words he's a fancy man with a big sister. 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayHyber @NHSSCA @BrettAKuehn @Ned_Arick @KurtzM3 @LANEstrongman47 @MonteSparkman @richgray @CoachSchofield… https://t.co/CheWNoOWgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mormon History and Culture : Book of Laman an interesting take on Mormon scripture: https://t.co/MlzDRFhmy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally solidified a squad. Time to keep my head down and grind as hard as possible for FW]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @IlaCorineToon i am so very proud of you and i love you with all of my heart!!!💘 have the best day ever precious!!!😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KumpKump It will change your life (I can only speak for myself, but you see for yourself) https://t.co/DODYZgZv69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KangarooPhysics @SculptrVR @Fr0z3nR I really like this one. It's such beautiful math.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moon landing is fake. I mean it’s still up in the sky so how could it have landed anywhere???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justlnw Jason Lee’s the last person in this world who should be talking about someone else’s appearance and attack… https://t.co/ECBgPrbjrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Prism by @schellsbrewery @ The Starkeller — https://t.co/kJh9QU8yU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I do the PACER test. Then the TA gone ask if I wanted to do a VO2 max test. Anddd I said yea 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week at The Met  #TheMet #NewYork #Manhattan https://t.co/0ViHRTm2x9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm interesting recommendation justification @netflix https://t.co/43QQmk6NFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our seat view. #springtraining2019 #redsoxspringtraining2019 #redsox2019 @ Boston Red Sox Training Center https://t.co/lq8gA12YwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been over two decades since OG Rebel Filmmaker rodriguez made his feature film debut “El Mariachi” with only $… https://t.co/2WX1yecCzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSBoulder is it possible for it to rain November thru February? Even though it’s above freezing my most of the ti… https://t.co/rZUak2wZUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump TheDems are playing Dangerously with American lives by not backing the Prez when he… https://t.co/ThUNbC1Fh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArionAgain Midrange hunter used to have none... no epics or legendaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethmeyers Yo you gained so much of my respect now that I know you love Animal Man. 🙌🏽♥️🦑 #buddybakerforever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to shake off another day of all the liberal bullshit that’s comes our way. God Bless every Patriotic… https://t.co/95UikG1Nz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[just me thinking out loud yall dont mine me 🙇🏿💭 @ Manheim, Pennsylvania https://t.co/SmPRYuQEjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will I regret it if I don't do this? If not, no worries. If yes, it's time for a moment of courage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 @Madi_Czerwinski What exactly is secret? They list all the deaths. We found them in https://t.co/pgLHIOZujY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit gave me goosebumps.. there are some sick fucking people in this world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Misfits gangster still making a comeback. Lowkey tho, I think it's an old video.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlBroberg @deltaracing Congrats on the win at Oaklawn. Cohen ain't bad either]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metallica tonight will be my wife's (@TheresaPeach) first real rock concert. LET'S BLOWN THE ROIF OFF!!!! #MetInWichita]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating women in food and wine: had so much fun joining @DanetLinares and her fellow @IWFglobal members for a s… https://t.co/I7211rtkZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting these cakes ordered for #MensDay this Sunday! #NextManUp 🍰 (@ Costco Wholesale in Inglewood, CA) https://t.co/L2PkUWL26C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am over preachers telling their people, people who have come to know and believe that Jesus is the way, that they… https://t.co/fSsrPbCgxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!!!!!  Fred Rubino Live In Ft Lauderdale with  Michael Panzeca  Last chance to get early bird $20 tickets un… https://t.co/f2dKAeDMn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is this hovering over me from behind me to order a drink shit when I'm sitting at the bar? At least grab my wa… https://t.co/Oz1PRwIXc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge ur mother! (at @ALDIUsa in Camp Springs, MD) https://t.co/jRsJwpG11I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heed my warning. Venture not into the comments section of an article discussing “Captain Marvel.” That path leads o… https://t.co/8sA3Ya9vOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beach Art.  - #beachart #structure #instillation #foundart #beachfun #earlyspring #westseattle… https://t.co/3TZbdshHGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant wait for tomorrow's episode of #TheChain https://t.co/7xGtNvOVj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could there be a more transparently stupid public servant in the world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posting this because 27-years later it’s still hilarious.  Shawn Kemp on Alton Lister.1992.🏀💥😂  https://t.co/IWYylFgEOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[also I'm really excited for my near future, I just need to dedicate myself 🐉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Lebron should fucking prove to them lol fuck off with this horseshit!]]></document></documents></author>