<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When Mama has a  vasovagal syncope  and needs to be flat we try to be flat too. (I’m fine now) 👩‍⚕️🐈 #nursekitten… https://t.co/PPEOw60QgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[People leave administrations for moral reasons and in protest? And Trudeau is in deep political trouble because of… https://t.co/2Q4j9S6Xho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots to LOVE about this #bobandsueproductions ! ❤️❤️ @ FOX 29 https://t.co/AtznmmIH0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent the video of the dog getting tucked in on our family text. My mom responds say it reminds her of Gretl. She… https://t.co/OBSq78ip1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CambreyNoelle Shout-out of love to my Detroit daughter &amp; wondering if you’re watching the #ArethaFranklinTribute concert, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klrawlins There's are like 4 open. All are at least 1 1/2-2 hrs away. No online sales. There are more but not open yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Church points you to Christ, it is not your saving grace.  Our passion for God will lead us to multiply His Church]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best smile in town!! 😁 . #DanWednesday #DanMiller #IJustReallyLoveOtown #SelfiesForDays #OTOWN #OTWN #boybands @ Th… https://t.co/fvxgnhopM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KATUNews Have to ask ... it didn't have Canadian bacon or pork on it, right?  #HadToAsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does my life have to suck so badly?! Why does my life ALWAYS have to be so fucking hard and rough]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the so called experts don’t step in and stop Luke’s abuse of Kate then are they really experts?  They need to ge… https://t.co/LGu4iJ46xN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 💜nail day. My next set. #StayTuned @ Leicester, North Carolina https://t.co/cvvHHlJgcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I’m 1000, and no one I know tweets or follows me...I don’t use twitter. Until @AMillionABC. I’ve dusted off… https://t.co/btopjRFKjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vonklein300 Wrap arounds..I rm they called Farrah if u can find them. Ahhhhdo thank u for sweet words]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to see @GaryClarkJr getting his due.  Already a Texas legend. #SNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lari116278227 @venezuelancon @Somaliweynta Sharia law doesn't apply fairly to a Catholic like myself. We would not… https://t.co/O8jKh55G79]]></document><document><![CDATA[realized i walked out in public without makeup i look like an ingrown toenail and i wanna die]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I’m not quite sure if it’s somebody out there for me...: If that makes any sense 🤦🏽‍♀️😩😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDPuns @lt_gray @thundacat830 Awesome tackle! I was getting annoyed with guy.  Glad you took him down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar Speak for yourself Mr Existential Crisis .*in Carrie sassy tone *]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Maria CA Sun Mar 3rd AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 56 TONIGHT Chance Of Showers Lo 40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barkaman Totally from my recollection of seeing that movie in 1999, as would be appropriate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisst07373986 @thehill My taxes have gone up and my investments/retirement is just getting back what was lost la… https://t.co/apnaDJ3vuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@republiconyos @BenjaminG302 @1zenbitch @Stuffits1 @RMConservative @realDonaldTrump Oh no, it broke all on its own… https://t.co/ORvEUNpykR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Kirsten Gillibrand faced #MeToo complaint in her own office: report https://t.co/zuz5cVz685 via ⁦@USATODAY⁩… https://t.co/2buPbEIzPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidred5sw @FreeGirlNowNYC @dgraupman @washingtonpost @Fahrenthold Good going you too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me this morning at mcdonald’s: “i want the donut sticks because i saw @JeffreeStar eat them on his snapchat story”]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of work and a little sadness went into today, but helped Mom close on her house and pack up 20 years with of… https://t.co/YD1zIaHiBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said it was impossible. They doubted my dream. "February 23 is too long to leave a Christmas tree up," said th… https://t.co/Uf4XFuZA3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I STILL have to do His Will and that’s my point. Moment by moment is my personal goal...like Jesus...I must giv… https://t.co/nEx3RjMzbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marnely_Murray It’s nuts outside. Better calm down by tomorrow. Taking the 8:15.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kpop1978 @scott81209260 @EdKrassen @Bevfriesen1 You know Trump to me as loyalty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to our leadership on The Hill,  Have a super day with the many radical coworkers you created. It’s nic… https://t.co/58XhQ1T2se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawaL51259853 @BuckeyeGurl99 @ItsMeSveta88 @politico They can do both. Dislike foreign intervention and be traitor… https://t.co/KGyB7MiTNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeepIttMovingg @jordanannstocke @elapscher @IlhanMN Interventions in Latin America have been historically differen… https://t.co/cIojPz6Och]]></document><document><![CDATA[@konagrl4554 Thanks. Will try not when I get to work. I'm down to 78% now and we pull into Seattle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys are cracking me up this morning @KennethMoton @JanaiNorman 🤣  #wnnfans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nike promises to investigate why Duke star Zion Williamson's shoe fell apart resulting in injury.… https://t.co/IjzWqFpbTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonjour Quebec!   #Quebec2019 #BigDay @ Old Quebec City https://t.co/1W6eNM7U55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Burgundywave I was just thinking no one's gotten a chance to watch practice yet! Also, I hope someone is keeping a… https://t.co/DU4qVSz2lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it wrong that I’m wishing for crazy snow Wednesday into Thursday so I have a good excuse not to go to the dentist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[my Lustrous Lady Luster!! #LusterPopUpStore  #LusterByNadineLustre https://t.co/Bm4fAv47OR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Realmommabear For Christ sake pick another fight white woman!  Something more important than two dogs doing what they are going to do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Linsey still never had Thaifood !! #GirlBye Thai Is life 🤤❤🍲🍛🍤  #NextStopThai 🛫]]></document><document><![CDATA[a bestie who notices you once in a while &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; a 2nd bestie who bullies you]]></document><document><![CDATA[It meant a lot to be at the opening of theTeen Center at the @BangorYMCA tonight.   It was powerful to hear from CE… https://t.co/oS9t6wp8ZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be fooled, worst seats in the place for 150 bucks, can yiu say the Peoria Civic Center ran a scam on concert… https://t.co/4jmKflq3Pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to my grandpa’s house tomorrow night for dinner and I haven’t been there since before my grandma died. Prayer… https://t.co/oqH8recEYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pillboxz @Rutho_ coming back to this chain to announce THE PERKS HAPPENED THIS WEEKEND  met the friend for the fir… https://t.co/iRFNQzV6nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMAGASteve @crazypoodlemom Why is it the ugly ones insist we see them naked? https://t.co/TQ1EzZonI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just paid off my target credit card and I got an email saying they’re raising my credit limit to $5000 and boiiii… https://t.co/1c4877O60a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSpec Because they do this to every persons driveway and it's the worst part of winter]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could be 10am at work and I’m telling customers to have a good evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Dog Pictures with Quotes | Funny Image Collection: Lol dogs, Dogs 'n' Puppy Dog Pictures... https://t.co/2Qi8kLnZ48]]></document><document><![CDATA[With 15 seconds left, @GT_SOCCER_ #31 gets a #GOOOOOOOOAL for the dub ⚽💪👍 @Russellville_HS Girls prevail over Haley… https://t.co/8Ln9yDzMyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid makes me get up 10 times during the night to pee, and i know its only going to get worse 😧😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashofspadez3 @Pinkadoodlezzz @_AbigayleA @Dewan298 @PostMalone Oooo @ashofspadez3 you're right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adixion_Grupera Hola, me podrían complacer con el nuevo sencillo de @julionalvarez #CuandoTeAmé 🎵🎶❤ gracias lindo… https://t.co/2p5lprdwVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Street Fest was amazing. Only down side was that I couldn’t try it all. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationaWomensDay from the Senate Pages! Today and every day, we are so grateful for the amazing women s… https://t.co/xLDNri0J3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[This fire 🔥 that we call Loving is too strong for human minds. But just right for human souls. Love 💕 is something… https://t.co/zzJrARnLfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t tell if my sour feeling tonight is real or because I can smell these new black jeans I’ve washed twice that… https://t.co/GlMMGmugRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StorySlug @BillOReilly @trumps_feed Harvey the king! What’s worst is the women show knowingly play the game and la… https://t.co/Sfl0IZ8qQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sitting on the couch working on motivating myself to get up and workout. It is only 20 mins I can do this! It… https://t.co/uvdIcpVTRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHOLESALE WEEK!!! $30 + shipping. 8x12 inches. #1  .  This week I will be posting a different work for sale every d… https://t.co/aUfmtiNnl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reason #164738 I miss the game like crazy. The science, the numbers, the breakdown of .2 seconds that will make you… https://t.co/typfm9MPKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be part of New Orleans Entrepreneurship Week co-hosted by @FreemanSchool and @IdeaVillage Check it out!… https://t.co/GbJ3sbG6Fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[also: Scotty, Chris, Bruce, Heath, aND Todd put on an amazing show and I cannot even believe I was able to see them… https://t.co/R70ZFkWJux]]></document><document><![CDATA[trust that’s what was meant to be yours, will be yours. He’s got His plan &amp; timing just right for what our lives are to be🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m trying to find where Spike Lee even mentioned you... what part of his speech was an attack on… https://t.co/fGWVUx8dhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall I was in my bed at 10:30 last night when she texted me from North Carolina to make me run to the mailbox to re… https://t.co/HEy5KHxLI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS @bedevilme666 @Stephen57036680 @KathaleenHarpe9 @monkeyMagaKAG @DoingRight1 @DallasBrownin16 @Dbargen… https://t.co/Gc95DF3Y6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NFL_SiXtH_sEnSe @JoelCP_ I am always watching and rooting on my #1 grandson! So proud of him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun says good morning and good night. 🌞 Have a wonderful day, everybody! . . . #HermosaBeach #hermosapier… https://t.co/y27wbQOOx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now is the time to get your 500hr teacher certification. For many years I have wanted to add a higher level trainin… https://t.co/6n0rYZ29xG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tictoc Where was he last year when I was trying to get help protecting my child my identity and safety!? Feel free to DM me @michealcohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[when do you think my doctor will figure out that “i have a hard time focusing and getting things done on time” is a… https://t.co/OZXse5uXcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing your job can be the opportunity you've been waiting for, to start your own business, be your own boss, and w… https://t.co/qI3XzDc2zP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t have time for inconsistent people in my life and that goes for everyone friends family relationships 👋🏽💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser If he had integrity he would run either as a rethug or a Dem. All he is, is a potential spoiler. Shame on S… https://t.co/qPEh7Jd7O2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrazziTL @GregNorberg Well I breast fed 40 years ago so there went that lie. How does she think people survived th… https://t.co/Nny9PQ6wGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matthew 6:14-15    For if ye forgive men their trespasses, your heavenly Father... https://t.co/zWdwKpDBVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un cliente me dijo hoy que si no me daba miedo que fuera un psicopata maniaco y que me robara, él no sabe que me di… https://t.co/b4gxRjfLpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[i asked one of my friends what his zodiac sign was today and he said “aqueous” un ironically bitch are you a solution??]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PinkAdam feeling right at home on the stage. 💕💗👀 #pinkadam4ever #stickerslap #stickerslaps #pinkadamiseverywhere… https://t.co/quaYQTTEWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ON CHANNEL 11 MORNING NEWS--Deep freeze locked in with single-digit temperatures Tuesday morning https://t.co/8sxblAbm8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice rising about 6ft above shoreline in Oswego...now homeowners fear flooding when it melts https://t.co/EeSN2oyxGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabbyGiffords @ShuttleCDRKelly You still insprire us. Sorry to have missed the special event. We are totally going to help elect Mark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umm yeah, I would like to reorder the weather. It’s too cold out there.🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most bizarre stories I've ever researched is the Duga Radar near abandoned Chernobyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #Sims matriarch died in a pool. I invited her ghost to come back to the household and now whenever she stays in… https://t.co/O1pnzBi7C1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannaFlint Yet again, we'll agree to disagree on pretty much all things m night]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only explanation for me being on two party busses in a matter of a week is that my friends are extra ass crackh… https://t.co/0gIxoxqSvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tournament of Roses was proud to participate in the 37th annual Pasadena Black History Parade. Thank you #Pasadena… https://t.co/h7bbe4nMiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I decide to be productive NOW?? It's 12 and I just got off a 7 hour shift but I'm motived af??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youngjae💚🌞 #TeamGOT7 #TwitterBestFandom #SoompiAwards @GOT7Official  #갓세븐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished 34m:00s of treadmill walking with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/ORkDzxyTpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol if only posting a photo and be 'ive been there' is still a thing for me. hun im done. Dont u ever ask where ive… https://t.co/PrbGuT7oIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheryl_monk @AviFlyGirl @MedicaidNowSC @johnpavlovitz @henrymcmaster And, I know you all have always fought a good… https://t.co/J68V3SVpgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday Darien and I went to the butterfly emplorium, a mirror maze, played in a room of lazers, and more but lon… https://t.co/mfaKeprDu0]]></document></documents></author>