<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mssenator @TwitterMoments @RashidaTlaib @LynnePatton And him getting all tearful when he got called out was nauseating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side note I’m pretty sure my brother is going to get a cat and I’ve never been so flipping pumped in my whole existence]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have trees over our roof in the back yard and the length of the front yard and I keep hearing groaning and  crack… https://t.co/ZEXRX2nQm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeslaArmy @gwestr @Tesla The two greatest quarters in their history. As predicted 3Q2018 will be the best they eve… https://t.co/boAYA47ikB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing call of duty with your side nigga even though you’re trash but he’s fun and patient &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚅PUR⚂GOLDers at Lafollette in #Regional final. Let's go, #Eastside! #wisgb https://t.co/oKsP45CW5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[LET THEM THINK THERE IS A WALL, WHOS GOING TO CHECK ON IT, NOT HIS BASE LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright if I don’t make it to my power hour shift it’s because the Xanax put me in a deep sleep. You can blame my r… https://t.co/phAZaPI13G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear all my grandparents do is talk shit about me, they hate my hair, they don’t like my tattoos, they hate how… https://t.co/47hQiyNUd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think anyone realizes the love and joy this little dude has brought into my life https://t.co/O3xRRla051]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re never fully dressed without second hand clothes - accessorized with a reusable: bag + coffee mug + mason jar… https://t.co/IgJYFA2fr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There should be NO lifetime pensions or special insurance for any of them. There also should have… https://t.co/5SgXACEywc]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever ur feeling hopeless about the world just remember anything u could ever think of or want is available for… https://t.co/gG10hVVbRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leesargent Seeing it Friday, my husband is super excited about it. I know nothing about but it look beautiful and… https://t.co/LQfvZdCIkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days I’ll be able to treat people the way they want to be treated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grumpynurse74 Ugh. My heart rate JUST came down from 6 hours of my own road rage today.. I cannot 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope my friends don’t stop inviting me to stuff cus i swear i would show up if I could 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few of my #vegan eats from the past week: 1) The Classic #Burger from @eatbychloe (tempeh, lentil, chia, walnut b… https://t.co/3igqxKjjXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jl3beast_mode54 Congrats @jl3beast_mode54 I’m so proud of you! Keep grinding!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If our “friends” or acquaintances get mad that we are out here working hard AND traveling- let alone us being indep… https://t.co/oLdQcZXLI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMFelton @GedesBru I remember Republicans getting angry that Venezuela was providing home heating assistance that W had cut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @educationfundmiami Taste of Education event sharing my financial literacy program with MDCPS School Board M… https://t.co/4gyURPLA8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSirTomJones @JamesArthur23 @thevoiceuk Props to Tom Jones.  Looking healthy and still killin it!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, and to add one more thing, I’d take conservatives who are up in arms about this more seriously if they’d stop c… https://t.co/mTjbtBMCvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another year that my Oscars invite was lost in the mail https://t.co/3zITsON81K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxwestart @WayneDupreeShow But, they want to get rid of the Constitution!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLanceBlack A beautiful reality. My heart explodes with joy for you ❤️👨‍👨‍👦]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially become a second mom to my niece and nephew. I’m too young for this lifestyle 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drove five hours to see @tesseractband tonight and they didn't disappoint. Hell of a show, my dudes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mizuki_hana2 Is it getting any riser for you I’ve went through a loss not of your caliber but I’m still not over m… https://t.co/FHDCQK9lqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mary60053440 @Valac666 @SharonG40210896 @NYmitton @TeamSalBrian @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves @735BlackSheep… https://t.co/MCTJMAbpex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Savannah__Witt really got me to start saying “asparagi” allllllllll the time at work &amp; people look at me like I’m crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamJamesM60 @InSpiteOfTrump Just stop please! And go home to mother! I’m sure you must know that Mueller “has you… https://t.co/J56BjZQjdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AngelMessage Tweets OR 5-Minute Automatic Writings.  You can only receive a 5-Minute Automatic Writing if you have… https://t.co/D8N1hRciOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Whatever it is, it's based only on their hate of Trump. He could cure cancer and they would hate him. I'm sooo sick of this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @realDonaldTrump Furthermore,  B.O. FOUND HIMSELF IN A VERY PRECARIOUS POSITION THAT EVENING AS THE SEALS… https://t.co/ispCitZ4Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gallatingator33 @cdelbrocco @NC5 @GOP And you know what’s real murder? All these no good MEN who father fetuses an… https://t.co/tYox8PiOvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alli_huscroft happy birthday Alli!! Miss u hope you had a great day!! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invisible Disease Day....What a nightmare-My heart is especially going out for all those suffering this year. 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump thinks he invented the Fourth of July, Stephen Colbert : https://t.co/0wn6BfOwTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emzanotti @MattWalshBlog Surprised someone hasn't spun hemp rope and pink v hats yet. But not sure when the view tapes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyGoodtimes Been to both. Red Rock is great if you want closer and just a little taste but  Valley of Fire is… https://t.co/wI7iwtZryC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuneMyThang13 @ahardy316 @gaviotita71 @DelphiPriestess @PumpkinKingxxx @singingdoves13 @KuwaTakaSurfing… https://t.co/UHIsjePP89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travelprofs yes! topics, quality and quantify of conversation can influence as can time spent during conversation!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember getting this when I was 10. That little blue power light will shine in my heart forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜U @army_bc @OfficerWilliam4 @OfcrMatt @_1Melanie1_  @EmmadeeH @Windagayle @JeffreyYarbrou2 @DKNE4Sure… https://t.co/ZiZII7Bibn]]></document><document><![CDATA[this will make you laugh. flattering poses for a female- wonder if I can remember these next time I get my...… https://t.co/NGtWKFmdVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for your leadership @TonyRoman10 ! Thanks for all you do for so many of us! Congrats! 🎈 🎉 🎯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MennoPastorAU There are so many electronic devices in our homes now it’s hard to keep track of them and what they do!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This lunch buddy is definitely one of my favorites! #dixon #masondixonline #cowsofinstagram #helikeschinrubs #osv @… https://t.co/mXIiV22JRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmostShawn @ChannelZeroSYFY Into the badlands my sunday nite tv obsession]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Lucas’ roommate doesn’t stop smashing on his keyboard, I’m going to smash him into a fucking wall.. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has visto YOU? La caraja contigo es Peach con Beck TOTALMENTE BRO QUE OBSESIÓN TAN CABRONA XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dad2therescue83 @nytmike @maggieNYT @adamgoldmanNYT @anniekarni All I see is the FBI is on it.  When Mueller’s pro… https://t.co/5nq95rJihc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me pueden informar cuando es la siguiente 3a temporada de exatlon se acaba de terminar y ya espero la siguiente.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ericaestelle @ABCBachelorThe Okay so I watched Women Tell All today and I changed my mind about Hannah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the party begin!  MKE chose to host the 2020 Democratic Convention. BIG for the city!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriasSecret please change the mesh to a different material that doesn’t feel like a nail filer! Please and tha… https://t.co/dav8zGMSqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teemcee I knew I shoulda spelled it out better.. I try to give you credit that you may have some sort of understan… https://t.co/QHFSmxZiAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling kinda pretty today, might delete later😂 https://t.co/Y374TGxkYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for hosting yet another great Wildcat Classic! We appreciate all your hard work. @neoshodebate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Are they spontaneously bursting into flames?!?!?! #TrumpIsTheAntiChrist #ICEistheGestapo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleEmBoogie LMAO! But have you gotten to all the “disability check” jokes 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[A slice of happiness for your Saturday viewing pleasure 😄 @ Lisa Elley ART https://t.co/5z9mqby38t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días me levante cantando mañana de gloria Trevi y espero que mi semana sea algo más alegre que esta triste canción 😭😢🤣🤣🤣🤣 animo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Props to her but on god some of you men need some pussy jeez 7k in 16 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Returning Rescued #SlowLorises to Their Forest Home is No Small Task   #care2 https://t.co/KQjciLNFO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[the worst part about working red eyes is everyone farts in their sleep. i need a gas mask]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amikegreen2 Many don't realize McConnell can be called to testify re: his communications with Trump before, during… https://t.co/LW1XRy12RQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he is a creepy and he likes little girls. He is disgusting. Check out creepy Joe Biden on YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms Jovonda Williams does so much for the community.  The future is bright with heart like hers. Congrats for being… https://t.co/BEy9ippvke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes Yes. And when these big "strong" powerful men are called out about it they turn into the tiniest of d… https://t.co/nce2oZ4QO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are lucky to have heard from a great panel addressing the things that are going on toward education.… https://t.co/GNK3UZFTnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trending product that I will be trying out in 72 hours is… https://t.co/wr72qebbAK #08L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rrbc #rwisa #bookreviews #bookboost #readme #circleofbooks  Member Name/ Author Name:  Carol Marrs-Phipps  Book Ti… https://t.co/gY3Zcg93lS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Please get the Republican Party’s act together and deliver what we voted for when we chose President… https://t.co/RuuJA1V3KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan gumbo + Jazz was a big Mardi Gras mood yesterday 🎉 https://t.co/oHSlyPz1KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Fridaynightlights at #thedarlingmansion it's all #smokeandmirrors ! Such a fun night with the boys and e_r_i_n_s_t… https://t.co/tKgU5LtEMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDubbTGG @MBTA I’ve w really never been on the T in Boston but I hear bad things. NY is all sorts of messed up… https://t.co/ngOa9GSehl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teriface73 @Serremmy @WeesThePeople @jonz970 @ladieann @dianne1h @KayPatriot @Bugteeth1 @charcus007 @lnrdbryant3… https://t.co/qTWuHwEziB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniebender We’re under a contract with our union. But we’re trying to get the company to renew it with pay in… https://t.co/d7yOCafhJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessings for safe travels today as we leave to San Diego🙏 Excited for our school visit to @hightechhigh… https://t.co/mUU3jVdaSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kylie don’t give a fuck about the Jordan situation she over here promoting her translucent powder]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA Cherry Boom Boom is back TONIGHT‼️👑 harvellessm 9 PM   📸 claudio.a.robles  ❌🥃❌ cherryboomboomtheshow 🖤 @ Harvell… https://t.co/s0hxgucInD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even #big #trucks get #stuck in the #snow ❄ If you have enough snow 🌨 😱. . . #snowstorm #truck #FordTruck #Ford… https://t.co/h0hx32hzVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericazisman @FLAGALine @MorganCWallen @DanAndShay @HardyMusic Yeah theirs is like how’s Carries is. It’s unique fo… https://t.co/O0Xr5X6iem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bsteelo @dereklwalker As my grandmother would say...that's just too much like right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nadia_Shammas_ They were my favorite when I was 12, and I still reread them constantly because they're a warm blan… https://t.co/hnhYnklGEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monae_Kel @MeekMill I’ve gone to 3 alone and it’s still so much fun!! Stay hype and make hype buddies with whomever is next to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert Stripes 🌵 Wearing faithfullthebrand #CaraJourdanTravel photo by paigeowenphotography @ Red Rock Canyon Las V… https://t.co/t173KdWOqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just relieved it wasn't the Batman or Superman bed. #AdoptDontShop #chihuahuasofinstagram #doglife @ Denison, T… https://t.co/bOBo755fP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I set up an Iowbi appreciation tweet he does something dumb like that back heel pass to no one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pervert!!! Disgusting, but oh....Run Joe, run!! Get ready to see this a zillion times🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re at a fitness expo when...#arnoldclassic2019 @ Greater Columbus Convention Center https://t.co/jDZwQGuYn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TTChelps what is the YUS line? I know of lines 1,2,3,4 but never heard of the YUS line. Im guessing it's line… https://t.co/c5XVBl2OCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Here are my favorites, Biden, Warren and Harris but still will vote for nominee in general]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where in the hell did THIS pathetic excuse for an American citizen come from⁉️ 🤦‍♀️🤬🤯#americantraitor perhaps⁉️… https://t.co/foMgGx6tYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump to white wash the ripping of children from the arms of their mothers   #InternationWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshNBCNews @KenDilanianNBC @NBCNews Certainly not a policy initiated by or overseen by @POTUS @realDonaldTrump ?… https://t.co/wu2W55RIu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up and ready to explore building bridges from paleo-research to policy and practice in this beautiful setting… https://t.co/QF52buabno]]></document></documents></author>