<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Jessica Mickey crossed 10K. Time 00:58:38, pace 09:10 min/mile, est. finish 9:07 am https://t.co/zj5oGjn77N #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Filed/paid my taxes, and the Sparce Force had better be fucking awesome. 🚀🌌🗿🤾🏻‍♂️💫👨🏼‍🚀👩🏼‍🚀🤖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDoubleclicks Well then.  Have you tried Cattails yet?  Stardew Valley but with cats.  Or so the box says.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bonnieinchgo  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist🏳️‍🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t believe a police officer would drive a car blindly out of hiding onto a sidewalk with active pedestri… https://t.co/ru4CISVTpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do ya ever go back in our mind and think." Boy I wish I hadn't tweeted that." Donny? Oh that's right. You have a mi… https://t.co/sLJ4LRzCwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @aaronschock The guy is right.  Their are district attorneys that would lie and put their  mothers in… https://t.co/9S4Y2Shcfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW Homes - Las Vegas, NV  89141 $429,500 3 Beds 2 Full Baths 2002 Sq.Ft. - https://t.co/Io2CB3tAXi  702-419-4200 https://t.co/iGcNkC76y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump At least that's what people say,  Um-hm https://t.co/vlnsYWhmgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @SarahDOdom to post the cover of 7 books I love - no review, no explanation. On day 3, I challe… https://t.co/rniubyzSZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushJohnNabors LMAO! Newsflash! I knew this story was fake from the beginning. Exhibit 1 and ONLY: A black man get… https://t.co/ISG6n7XkQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy And Use Your Time Wisely. Whatever You Decide To Do Will Effect Your Future None The Less. ------------------… https://t.co/mIqfXuQGxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlierMachar @_Autumn_Tonic @WalshFreedom You are a complete dumbshit. https://t.co/Mz2qmpSci0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtSchlichter Don’t forget about the fake racist claims in 2015 at the University of Missouri that resulted in a… https://t.co/vl8RWn6iRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pasmith I've been playing a lot. With a lifetime sub and a very long break... I had almost 30k Zen built up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a McSwagger's Own by @crookedcan at @crookedcan — https://t.co/XkpHtieY8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theStarWarsHQ If they give me an “Old Ben” skin for Obi-Wan all will be forgiven 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday night training in the #garagegym with #kettlebells #dumbells #resistancebands and a recovery mix of… https://t.co/NKldl0Vl3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pets truly hold a special place in your heart that can never fully be healed once they’re gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIM______ He doesn't "have" 6 years left and the President doesn't "step down" at the end of his term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh God lemme think...Santi Cazorla for 16m is a good shout. Fucking bargain. But if we're talking all time then def… https://t.co/MtL5mbOVLj]]></document><document><![CDATA['I'm not running': Hillary Clinton rules out 2020 bid for first time on camera in exclusive interview with News 12 https://t.co/9rJmvSBFku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commit thy way unto the Lord ; trust also in him; and he shall bring it to pass. Psalms 37:5 NLT https://t.co/bqEPGDJJDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHoffmanRetail @Starbucks Waiting for your @Medium post “DNVB strategies for airport retail” cc @web / @laurenthomasx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomVargheseJr @TIMESUPHC @choo_ek @darakass @janevandis @drjessigold I love your banner on your Twitter profile,… https://t.co/YZzrlTccXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[With that one Pogba should be off. That should’ve been a second yellow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Team Bacon: Bacon is EASILY the best thing to happen to McDonald’s classics. #TeamBacon in the house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not him at all. Every right to do whatever is nessicary to defend himself. #equality]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show though, and things like the bungled “Take Care” arrangement add to the fun. Bradford Cox is the anti-roc… https://t.co/pSyEDOHcHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMcMahon you can is Shane McMahon. Outside Night ok Shane McMahon home night outdoor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/a9fpTAZ2tH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the vacation life right here in Sandusky! Want more, contact me for your private tour 📲 216-244-2549… https://t.co/Ih71LdxR7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come find your new best friend - adopt at the @PetSmart #NationalAdoptionWeekend adoption event at PetSmart Center… https://t.co/Or5DB4BVzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestonSprinkle wondering if you have done an episode of Theology in the Raw on Open Theism? Would be interested i… https://t.co/IWc7K2IHEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeWillie Tonight is the first time that I didn't find the OU band playing "Boomer Sooner" every 30 seconds extre… https://t.co/dP4uloXxyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickwnyc_ Lmfaooo I looked down for a second, looked up and the crowd dispersed into a circle I’m like https://t.co/Wh01ljphLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clash: “nothing to lose. This will be great”  After Clash: “temperature is cool, there wasn’t much to gain.” Duels:… https://t.co/Ip2RNck0uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harold &amp; Elena – Desciende aquí (Videoclip oficial) https://t.co/U1f221qTT9 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nos trataron mejor que BIEN, la gente de @Chivas Y sus aficionados son un claro ejemplo de lo que necesita el fútbo… https://t.co/NRW1nM3QnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@navy09212010 @PaulCharchian Sorry, no. I didn't realize that. I just wanted Charch to know that not all Vikings fa… https://t.co/YFIhzqVEQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole Jussie situation is extremely sad...but this is a fantastic point. You just go reporting things without… https://t.co/WBkt3RFiZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vinte e cinco de Março.  O ano era 1911.  Um incêndio em uma fábrica têxtil começou, fazendo que logo o fogo tomass… https://t.co/jeuYypy9l4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ENC_98 @LizSmit64073582 @GateWorld Yeah, they did the same for SG1 in season 9. We’d seen them in all black for a… https://t.co/BA0ZiyexwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derekdraws @kharyrandolph I think WW suffered from that Link and Ganondorf fight tech demo they showed at Space Wo… https://t.co/UypUkpSU7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksmith474 @gfcronus @kevincorke @StateDept They challenge that denial, of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCALmatters @CALmatters He’s way to busy suing Trump and raising lot of campaign money “for standing up to Trump… https://t.co/oLmZZoveKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Comp(ensation) transparency isn’t about sharing everyone’s salary in a spreadsheet. It’s about giving people a cle… https://t.co/vqA9ZqDaqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rustyhoundy @WillGrayGC 100%. DJ has the athletic talent to be an NFL QB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DollyDeighton Ah tell me about it that and jet lag! In town with @Tribe__Global guys for our America’s meeting lat… https://t.co/VdMIdl3SAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[America was founded by great people with this kind of drive. I’m so proud of who you are, what you stand for, who y… https://t.co/GjmtduumL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dneedles12 I don’t really care about support. That’s what’s wrong with Twitter. It’s a place@where someone lets th… https://t.co/VpCH6MHH3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prepared for HSPUs  #crossfit #crossfitexclamation #crossfitopen #19point3 @CF_Exclamation @crossfitgames @crossfit… https://t.co/ziuyjJFxaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I am getting better because I’m still awake at close to 1am. Guess my energy is coming back? Finally dude.… https://t.co/h4USLrbmaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really walked a dog named Bronx today. What kind of person names their dog Bronx????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BattleCryOfFre1 @suzanne184 @peterdaou @IlhanMN @AOC Now we invoke God. What is it you do that makes you think you… https://t.co/OaEUmhvsTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ballsdotie McLean, up the English! The man’s Irish! No wearing poppy! ☘️🇮🇪👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marlonsarabia No,no es clara, demasiado ambigua y da pie a varias interpretaciones, ademas de lagunas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clippers fall to Coyle 2-1. Eddie with the goal. So proud of this team and how they played all year.  @In_The_Slot… https://t.co/xd0ZMn6ePq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmc2bpc @DisplacdFans @RossTuckerNFL That’s a crazy, uninformed answer. No one you described makes that transforma… https://t.co/jdpNSvYw3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YallGotToChill @MittRomney Rather count on this note to be legA-L tender for All my debts public And private with my watchful eye...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cbp8Cindy @SLBriscoe @cazij @FionaMorgan79 @magee333 @ccatmpt @suziday123 @cowineco @AkronWineGuru @thatsVeryKari… https://t.co/gos1qdDdyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @POTUS Pray that God will help our country work through these difficult issues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Definitely the “death of Stalin”. Most likely too far over the heads of liberals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanFactor @ColtonC81118846 @stefonscovfefe @JohnHookfox10 @DeliliaOMalley @realDonaldTrump @BarackObama Words… https://t.co/Rksha9IkLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time speaking Spark with a book club for the first time! Thanks for inviting me to the conversation, se… https://t.co/0dtV0Ez6J5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CallGod🤙🏾 Kansas State fans help me get my lil bruh on board 🤩🤩 #EMAW #WTDD @DYoungRivals @BarstoolKState]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuroDeporteLN Con ese montón de aficionados que tienen !!!. No llenan ni el gallinero de ellos que son como 5 o 6… https://t.co/jXiI4huLgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight trollin'. The @Lakers "Godfather Package" AND Lebron just got their asses handed to them by an AD-less Pel… https://t.co/FcsT1RG1Ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest finished entrelac scarf with @Knitcircus . Did start over and made it a bit skinnier. I ♥️ #entrelac… https://t.co/V52lIg1KPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[To identify as poet is to see deeply  past the surface view into the very heart and the soul of a world desperate f… https://t.co/yliIq4IT6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fdelatg @TasteAtlas @TacoTrail @XBorderConsul @carlos_glezgtez @gomezpickering @FernandoKras @EmbamexEUA… https://t.co/OYZMnMslpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas No.  It's not.   If he went over to argue DURING the review I would get it, still stupid but get it.… https://t.co/JBEKYj4FDm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super happy with @NintendoAmerica direct! Can't wait for all the new upcoming titles.   But I'm expecting our next… https://t.co/QKiEv6G7QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emailed my regional manager this morning asking him to give me a call to discuss my hopeful promotion along with so… https://t.co/cGRGVSP0hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michelle__Henry It's miserable right? I have no idea what I'm even anxious about. 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmf1030 @jlong63 @CBiggerPic @KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff @DevinNunes Still waiting for the name, date o… https://t.co/vdlirfa69r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning at Malibu. Great breakfast. Fun surf!! #freedom #freedomoftheseas  #inspiration… https://t.co/0dR1zc5G78]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna go ahead and say it: @ZionW32's @Nike's were sabotaged. No other explanation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mail &amp; More on Hollywood in Los Angeles, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/ltZ5Kld0oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody:  me: I CANT WAIT TO REJECT EVERYONE ONCE IM A SKINNY LEGEND LIKE YALL REJECTED ME WHEN I WAS FAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenLynch8 I think we can find a place where you can continue to give back to the game!! 🏀🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't It Romantic: stunningly great film. Rebel Wilson may be the finest comic actress since Mae West]]></document><document><![CDATA[to say anything about it? BULLLLLSH**! F*** WHAT THESE FAKEA**, DEMONIKKK, WANNABE "JEW-WISH" FOLKS ARE TALKING ABOUT! Next. ☹️😡💔💔💔💔💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confused about the Pepsi/fetal cell issue? Here are the facts | Blogs | LifeSite https://t.co/Etzkm1BAQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews The Republican Party acts more like a Fasvist Mafia than political party. Then again Truman called the Republicans Fascist in 1948.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timobros @somebadideas I also just recently discovered the KICKBOXER sequels of which Pyun directed 2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fonvilio @EdweiserBusch @wingoz You must love shopping at Walmart. That’s all you talk about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaganotify @ladygaga Very beautiful young little girl one of and monsters?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HalfPintBunny @diggityddubya @RossTuckerNFL @AB84 @AroundTheNFL @steelers Its called marketing genius, if you want… https://t.co/AXFXwwnYQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last time I came up here, it was 23°, snowing, and the actual Blowing Rock was closed. Yesterday was a perfect, pic… https://t.co/zvp8ThmLVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was on sale for 39.99  I really wanted for a while so snag it  good I finally got it #fresh #callofdutyblackops4… https://t.co/gqNv6YbtPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhh girl you look so nice but your not nice your rude. Look what your putting me through. I never do this to you @showintelll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikki_poulos @Lip_Smacker they got disney ones which is dope as fuck, even though i stick with dr. pepper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cask vs Draft vs Nitro sampler. Cask showcases more flavors, good chocolate flavors, tasty brew - Drinking a Small,… https://t.co/LOSj3Ti0QX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanlynne712 I appreciate the clarification. If it were a reburial I was going to use it for a sermon illustration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[reply to this with an album that has no skips. i’m tryna see something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh great it's one of those "slightly different theme song" days on NYT Daily 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏆 Hamidou Diallo (OKC) vuela sobre Shaquille O'Neal para coronarse en el Slam Dunk Contest 2019. #NBAAllStar… https://t.co/t786Is76IQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSalter55 That sounds remarkably like what ignorant liberals claimed Reagan of doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@basker @DanielleMorrill I found it’s all in getting normal shoes on! Get up, shower, put normal shoes and a nice s… https://t.co/L442sRHUQ7]]></document></documents></author>