<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how much Sophia can travel but there is a zoo in West Pal Beach where you stay in car and drive throug… https://t.co/fwAXcgQQDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EquusNimbus @aarong33 I already took yesterday off 😩  I will give myself the space somewhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a cool experience. #mardigras2019 #knappinteriors #family @ Baton Rouge, Louisiana https://t.co/VNKP5LTrKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I’m not wearing red lipstick.....💋😣 @ LePeeps https://t.co/k4MJfT1kap]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is absolutely beautiful!  Congrats to her achievements, she is absolutely a inspiration to all youth!]]></document><document><![CDATA[every night you should practice journaling, meditating, and cranking that soulja boy. that is the true key to align… https://t.co/JiME1DmUoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A simple prayer is one of the most meaningful ways a husband can love his wife, which also helps her2 find God in a… https://t.co/2q9ruCo4EY]]></document><document><![CDATA[peak of my day so far: I met a man named Michael Scott at my internship.  pit of my day so far: He was unfortunatel… https://t.co/rLW3qlayml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pharoahpharrell I wouldn't say that I was popular but I was well known and so I knew everyone.  I played tennis in… https://t.co/mZGKDK02Uu]]></document><document><![CDATA[In addition to getting another baby in my tummy, Franklin wants a kitten to give to Buddy so she can have a baby too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to represent hundreds  of veterans injured by 3M’s defective earplugs.  #profitsoversafety #corporategreed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet She is so fake that she could never deny it. She has no more business in that position than a snake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re wondering what’s been missing from your Sunday evenings, it’s a grown man riding an inflatable sun throug… https://t.co/worxFAEvHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So proud to see the cowboys and American Indian riding horses, holding American and Trump flags go… https://t.co/1eYSFusFn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kubrickx @mikerphonebrew @RJellyman @Michuntapped @mtravis63 @lhtetrick @dzyngrl @eternityroad01 @AmandabearL… https://t.co/B5AJwVPhef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMAC_SPORTS @CMUMavericks DYK? @CMUWBasketball has won more @RMAC_SPORTS titles than any other women’s hoops progr… https://t.co/JfFTzsaEUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Brotherhood Way Open Space in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/Bi87NHC6Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fav thing about this photo is that in real life Bruno Mars is 5 foot 5, and Cardi B is 5 foot 6. Imagine how hig… https://t.co/CrJgsOpjDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[why don't BART just run the purple line at all times, and cut the yellow line to SFIA at all times? that would seem… https://t.co/IN2nPW6mTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all magic.  God made us this way.  Limiting beliefs, the conversations we have with ourselves and others, si… https://t.co/G33JuEDO3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPhil she kept him away from her for six months because he's verbally abused them and physically abused them prob… https://t.co/9rqiFM6CTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisemullin @FitchKristi That’s how I feel.  I can honestly say my favorite JaSam moments was when they were in t… https://t.co/xp9Hub3o9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday Yeah... all of them... it just that good! https://t.co/3h9rN7gkT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a sign-making party today for our upcoming strike! oakland_ea #strikeready @ Oakland, California https://t.co/fMmAo7jJLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPoversight @DNC Our Lord purposely/ promised(2Tim 3) that we shall see times of evil, hatred, etc. So I'm trusti… https://t.co/qzlSbjl4uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xfinityprepaid @comcastcares I just refilled my my subscription and it is telling me that I don’t have an active a… https://t.co/GDB4NNolHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#faith #wife #mom #family #love #marketing #onlinebusiness #monat #dogs #mindset #gratitude #happy #friends… https://t.co/qFhoIzvGdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregOueilhe @Lexa_Merica @AOC @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @LindseyGrahamSC @tedcruz Next to Llhan Omar!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close up and personal with this custom hot rod style @porsche. . . I love this car, it's so damn wild. . . .… https://t.co/xiMH0Aar9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦌This year the venison in our freezer came from a donation. We were called to collect a buck that had to be put dow… https://t.co/UVEeIoVagp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefrocky413 @tjbogart33 @strom_annette @Barb81146 @ChrisToTheW @Carlos_Can_Do @GrandmaVeteran @MisleaderC… https://t.co/pPj1EGXDzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this is the church she’s going to in her location then sign me the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1COACH_CARTER @EyeAmTruth True that player’s fault... but that situation coach come on....]]></document><document><![CDATA[She suffered long enough the truth set her free let the new journey begin to achieve your happiness  @mainedcm  / M… https://t.co/qfnXOxQStj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McDonalds can you do me a solid and just make a hot mustard snack wrap a menu option? It would make my life a lot easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My valentines included half of a 4 lb lobster, this handsome guy, and #johnwick.  #happyvalentinesday #surfnturf… https://t.co/alcJaSCKYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardinal McCarrick Becomes Highest-Ranking U.S. Catholic to Be Defrocked https://t.co/q7ykuNP11j via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Hourly Restaurant Assistant Manager - https://t.co/Gs6LcYdJpq #Restaurant #Alexandria, LA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great concert last night, got to meet this guy right afterwards.   . . . . . .  #dylanscott… https://t.co/cdOsCeXqLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gotta suck to get fired because of the guy you were flirting with 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seen on my 10,000 steps: Makin Groceries at the local favorite 🍌🍞🥩🥓 @ Dorignac's Food Center https://t.co/Err1sgCsHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[we have some practitioners in the room and they’re bringing up things like compassion fatigue. so much for me to look up later!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDrillSquad Lets go way way way back!  KICKIN AFROLISTICS!  💪🏼 @Afrolistics]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are you do is post negativity, and complain all the time, what people think about you is that you are a negati… https://t.co/E6TVWdsITJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s only one way to end this stupidity, vote every Democrat out in 2020, problem solved!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glitter_fire How do you define the word woman ? Now that you’ve been through all this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveweigel I beg to differ. In California old buildings are retrofitted to withstand earthquakes. New buildings mu… https://t.co/hnt66OicXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying The Remedy at Remedy!  #jameson #gingerbeer #peach #downtown #tampariverwalk #remedy #dcdrinkz @ Remedy https://t.co/FZ4W7pBUCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Self care is important for teens who have busy, stressful days.#thisischeltenham #mindfulness @CSDCedarbrook… https://t.co/Hjjw9ostUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now, all the people who haven’t been paying attention, start to b!#@% #hisnameisGary]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HandmaidsOnHulu give us a new season already 😭 https://t.co/yF0HSxYQCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TriviaCrack we love the love that’s brewing between us, how about showing us some more love through a #spon?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been reframing challenges in life to “What am I supposed to learn from this?”  Yesterday, I did 3 20-min worko… https://t.co/CsJu6HK6FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy @RainDripDrops @HarryWatson1988 @HolmesBooth @MDaviot https://t.co/FEH5XLtlNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fridge empty right now asking can somebody cook. Nigga she’ll meet you there lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast this weekend , made a ton of new friends from as far as Australia and Canada to the USA and Scotland .… https://t.co/oNnjpnbMqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work so hard everyday, It's nice to have a few days to sleep in and actually watch the sunrise from my porch.… https://t.co/8hAauab4Yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[that arizona sky burning in your eyes you look at me and, babe, I wanna catch on fire, It's buried in my soul like… https://t.co/nQWJImbqai]]></document><document><![CDATA[i slammed my head really hard into the shelf above me after bending over for something lower. the employee right ne… https://t.co/31orehIbg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila please don’t use Jesus in a tweet and drop the F bomb simultaneously.   Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not sit by and watch my sons weight go down w/o doing everything I can. Yes @UHC it is a New drug but it’s a… https://t.co/8ix2H9KmF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Martinalove78 Morning @Martinalove78 thank you and you have lovely Monday 🌎🌼🍀🙏🦋☕️🌺☀️🤗🌻🌟🙌🏻🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at 12am: "I'm gonna stay up all night!"😃 Me at 1:30am: ... https://t.co/ErMKFU40cK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive Boundaries- an essential element in trauma informed behaviour supports. @sd61schools   @SD61Inclusion https://t.co/UsOLl2G3sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found an article about the korean war that is written by a korean man who lived thru the war and i wanna use it a… https://t.co/U5TSIREQkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpyyc @GOPChairwoman I wouldnt know what its like to be in a cult, I am an Independent thinker, unlike you socialists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impromptu photoshoot because the sun finally returned. 🌷⚘☀️ #lambchop @ Lancaster, South Carolina https://t.co/foSVc3eCgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker is here for our Rock Star Residency program and a Rock Star he has become! Here he is holding a down stay wh… https://t.co/ZCJedS84Ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[And yet when they watch @SpeakerPelosi speaking they call it normal speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Funny the major networks don’t cover any of his meetings anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missoula people.. our sweet Macy got spooked by fireworks and ran off. Headed south along the Grant Creek Trail eve… https://t.co/NK6mlzK5T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @donnabrazile @HowardU Ms Brazile is a liar and cheater.  Speaker Pelosi, ms Brazile gave Hillary Cl… https://t.co/mkwKuaS23x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m doing 2-a-days right now to kick (myself) into gear! So this morning I did a short #bowflexmaxtrainer program t… https://t.co/QRXyNtwR8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eightiesrocker1 @RockLovesMe2 @LiveMusicAgent @ManeatGrass @MySwilly @clanceman65 @ChipZnuff @OneMoreTattoo_… https://t.co/O4nrJYXXTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consejo de mi host mom cuando empiezan a salir con alguien: "Si siempre se cuestionan sobre lo que hace esa persona… https://t.co/F6UUCBLGpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s reaction posts to #CaptainMarvel are getting me SO FREAKING EXCITED for #GooseTheCat 😻😻😻 https://t.co/wQSAKiRSQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[95 Ridgewood Dr. Murphy NC 28906 https://t.co/XwCqbXJuJO https://t.co/Olebc1JAZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lania_Kea7 @omannevarez @lopezobrador_ #FarsantesDeLaMx   Neofascistas https://t.co/gZfc6VmlHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this point it’s so aggravating when companies do this shit for bad publicity simply cause “any publicity is good… https://t.co/uKtyK4oFdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I’m having an all nighter... My Brain will              not shut down. Ugh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate to beso stressed out that I end up getting sick. God please aid me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That just put their Bias in a more glaring light. Scaliness was targeted along with the rest of the Republican team… https://t.co/tjEVtHJekO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrabowIman He would’ve had an excellent chance of avoiding prison had he not faked a hate crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The basic to-do list for today and tomorrow.  Doesn't look like much, but each item has multiple steps that need to… https://t.co/n1eunnaCkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[H.3973 (24 sponsors including @bethbernsteinsc, @NancyMace, @MPowersNorrell @LS_Funderburk), prohibiting female gen… https://t.co/C4e6PHOJJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC That alone should give you a pretty good idea of his all-encompassing ego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coloradopit God bless this young child of yours; heal her heart, and Her body, please give her the strength she ne… https://t.co/5K86iRrUtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day to all my Twitter buddies! https://t.co/s5nVl3BRgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great chance of making it to the gram #flawsandall https://t.co/i1aDwPczcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nova Senior skates their Short Program at the 2019 Skate Canada Synchronized Skating Championships. • • •… https://t.co/C7yGdrJFLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found a movie that describes itself as “The first ever GAY slasher film” I’m extremely intrigued]]></document><document><![CDATA[“GOOD PLAYERS WORKOUT. GREAT PLAYERS OUTWORK!” Bright future for 1saxby 🏀🙌 #Aip #outworkcrew… https://t.co/arcOeHH0aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other - Dude, I wasn't that drunk!You started petting my cat saying 'LOOK AT HOW SMALL... #mirth #chuckle #smirk… https://t.co/ZcU0XsEVgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zairabc Y una ahorrando a morir pa ir a San Carlos, i can't believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @artytrace I hope Cohen tells truth about paying for Trump ladies abortions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanDerek_ @imlowkeyfamous I meant person Grey. The “hit me up when you don’t have an attitude” was the wrong way to handle that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stale Pirate’s Booty makes an excellent dinner at 11pm. https://t.co/iKp4SwKgLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wx_becks weren't you looking for a lenticular cloud photo the other day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If i don’t say something 5 other people keep getting hurt,  . If i do, i ruin something and someone i care much about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That is your job, you don’t get praise for doing your job]]></document></documents></author>