<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Let’s all wear our MAGA HATS and go to the DEMOCRATS DERBY: 13 Democrats with their names in the hat for the runnin… https://t.co/HpyXwMV4Ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a business meeting but also a gala to attend after. Shop this sophisticated look on our website now,… https://t.co/st7swy3ZGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kleinclaythe_II Ok so like anshow cost and a pair of breeches, then? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[For now while the rest of the photos are being downloaded and emailed to me #NewProfilePic https://t.co/aIkmPxyzjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blokseedac @Cindyb233 @realDonaldTrump Excately why we need to stand behind President Trump and end the democrats… https://t.co/vAjbp7Ehtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieLisa @AlexPalombo Even beer lovers @davewhite4 and @calleenwhite will agree, this is a magically terrible idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did this happen that Cortez was put into Congress?  I don't understand why people would elect this woman.  It i… https://t.co/JVStR6fc9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is everyone so angry? People can be so mean. Let’s go back to..”If you don’t have something nice to say; then s… https://t.co/gAexLas48N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh. 3 years ago it was 67° and the grass was green. Today we are awaiting a snow storm that could dump 10+ inches… https://t.co/UudChDxdlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Telling this random dude what we do for a living  Martina: I'm the vice president of the United States! Dude: Okay,… https://t.co/Pjzb7KL7NX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mientras que estes en la casa de papa y mama, tu solita no te mandas chiquitita.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I see is all these people in companies generating this amazing data that has the answers but that role isn’t i… https://t.co/fVUMgSBp77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraLaura1650 @oldmanluvsmineo @Odonata_Anon @S246278910 @WWG1WGAchicago Lol! Dark hat along with Prince Edward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello solo.moms love getting into the kitchen and getting creative   Celeste London  Holistic Solo Mom Coach… https://t.co/HvYqe8w5om]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🔊OPEN HOUSE ALERT🔊🚨 . . Join me this weekend (March 2 and 3), from 2pm to 4pm at this stunning, 5 bedroom, 4 bathr… https://t.co/Lqk7YazwEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[In any case, our national conversation around income inequality is much bigger than any one person and Bernie has a… https://t.co/J4ukyMfaUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn These countries see him as the anti-Christ he is.  Pure evil trying to demolish decency, democracy and world peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Televisa  #Elultimo Dragon destinada al fracaso, estan promoviendo promiscuidad  y machismo, insulto a familias hi… https://t.co/TYaGnphl4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Think about making a move? Start by connecting with me about it. With experience and training on your side you can… https://t.co/jQT9lxYKv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OncerHardy @hjhollis93 @AlliCamAllison @NGDAverk @giulia_belvisi @MagicBeliever93 @frostgirl11 @StephanieR___… https://t.co/1vJgOUO8IP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshallCohen Glad to see some self reflection by Congressman Jordan. He was indeed a sad display.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junecleavertoo True, my 💔 is broken, so I listen to his music.Maybe Jeter could use him. different Marlins than th… https://t.co/pOSjHo1Hgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyWilliams I am so glad that the purple queen is back in the purple throne. Welcome back, Wendy! 👑💍👸💅✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are days I LOVE my Job. #BTbiosci #studentsuccess #careertechschools]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris This is delightful. Thanks for sharing such positive news. #DAPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richpoetry @TiFanmKreol @HBCUfessions What I sent you also gave other reasons as to why a woman may be dry outside… https://t.co/HDM88oRUMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[buying a white board calendar really does make you feel like you have ur shit together]]></document><document><![CDATA[SPLC Action Fund: Grand jury investigation of school officials into alleged 'school safety' crimes erodes democracy… https://t.co/5tPVx9ra1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJohn_Tex @codeofvets Gretchen, try the Masonic Fraternity.  Or DM me the location and i will get on that for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValerieWeadock I bought some. She won’t use it... it’s killing me 😂🤦🏽‍♀️😂🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The clerk must be thinking, hmmmm.... Wonder what they gonna do😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kvngdab_25 @RodneyTaylorJr6 @RodneyTaylorSr1 look what I found Youth football days Leeds vs Gators championship ga… https://t.co/MGIlwgnSyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jruggiero86 Oh man. I probably won’t be there. I’ve been taking care of my mom who lives with me now. That’s going… https://t.co/wJEtBPIyaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[February average sale prices for LSTAR:  London: $405,186 Middlesex County:$469,094 Strathroy: $365,534 St. Thomas:… https://t.co/KBOuhCy85g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanpertwee @Gotham @camrenbicondova @robinlordtaylor @ErinRRichards Loving the show. Great chemistry between the… https://t.co/SugxfTdZ8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer Good job @danpfeiffer . @DanCrenshawTX seems to be a fake Repub. One of many. #saveAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to watch this kid tonight #beatyale ⚾️ 💥 👊🏽 https://t.co/NzFYMdHsjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ☀️love 🌿drought-tolerant landscaping 🌾anything to maximize water 💧 efficiency #HomeTips @ San Diego, California https://t.co/RLPjAI1Zvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 I learned in 1st grade and the Girl Scouts to come prepared.  This woman is a constant trainwreck...  #ResisterSister #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiniWineGirl @SteveKubota @YumchaAddict @LisaMRomano @OfPainters @JeremyPalmer7 @Oberreimer @nineov @KellyMitchell… https://t.co/otXthBHQWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffin nails in a beautiful ombré for my client ... she was happy! 😊❤️💅🏻😍  #nailsbysaritagonzalez #gelpolishnails… https://t.co/q712xZVJcd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing If you look closely, you can literally see the stupid oozing from their pores.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewkisuule1 @AOC I would agree if they paid a living wage. But instead the company will continue to make money of… https://t.co/4AoiQasqoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is probably beside the point, but the Idaho’s Hispanic population is 13% of the state now. Not 12%]]></document><document><![CDATA[QT with the best company ❤️ @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/jyb6lBtUtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar un video en Los Angeles, California https://t.co/fGKIjrUQGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like there were no cages.  Zoo animals have better cages or nicer environments than those REFUGEE CHILDREN. Ki… https://t.co/VBLziNwa4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes or No 2 finished.....and they made a heart with their hands omg this makes me miss you even more 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMyers1971 to twitter:  it seems to me that the application of your rules is inconsistent &amp; irrational.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t believe them why would these two guys who were adults when they testified said that nothing happened betwee… https://t.co/CHz0jfUiA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @d19fe8 future vision: teachers and AI collaborate to support students in real time and maximise learning achievements #lak19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lavrov, the fucker that flew to Hanoi to meet with trump during the failed, disgraced NK summit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino What is shocking is that our justice department hasn’t indicted all those involved. What is wrong with th… https://t.co/2wibBaIfa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Butterfinger Not exactly liking the new Butterfinger... why mess with the original?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raywylie "Got To!" I couldn't resist! Hope you are feeling great! https://t.co/sjioSkUwQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kidworldcitizen @JoyNicole12 In general presenters pay for registration, lodging, etc. They also usually pay for t… https://t.co/EihqI2dbUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @ArianaGrande when ur done with tour and that stuff can u pls grace us with ur presence on a broadway stage? Id… https://t.co/ZdlPgQDMCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld @TheFive @TuckerCarlson @seanhannity @IngrahamAngle @TomiLahren @KatTimpf @RealJamesWoods @dbongino… https://t.co/JNgBzJxUpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellyakim @pauljolivette80 @TheCrossover I see the only truth you can tell is that Cheryl is the love of your life… https://t.co/waokmH3D5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such great learning experiences happening here. ❤️ that the work they are taking outside this classroom is relevant… https://t.co/9oSwEBu7NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuafiyin happy birthday brother!! Keep doing what you’re doing! You know it’s all love on this side 💛🤞🏾 stay blessed and highly favored!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaMacavoy He’s a cunt married to a twat !!!! What a piece of shit 🙄😳🙅🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was never about improving educational opportunity. #PrivatizingThePublicGood]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whotfisgreg I’d eat it but it’s not pizza. I don’t even like the shit they call pizza here. Give me thin crust pizza without sweet sauce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are cisgender people ever described as identifying as men or women or are they simply who they are?  Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Thebachelor : ... Girl # 1 “he makes me feel safe” Girl # 2 “he makes me feel safe” Girl # 3 “he makes me feel saf… https://t.co/yCV3esDhtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok plane went to another gate and people are getting off. The girl in front of us is also going to Orlando. We’re all super stressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Cardi has a whole baby w Offset, but I felt so much chemistry between her and Bruno Mars lol I know it’s jus… https://t.co/N3EonXPu9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitter is better, especially when it comes to @GUEnergyLabs  NEWEST flavor: Hoppy Trails. Who says you can't enjoy… https://t.co/7GZn1PwRJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Healthy raffle basket with coconut water, pineapple, melon, canned chickpeas, &amp; two apples ✨ #longbranch… https://t.co/VIpq0ODWGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my opinion Asian fans are so lucky cause BTS always gets lit on their concerts. Special Japanese fans. Am I right or am I right? @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it is true that Hannah B is the Bachelorette I definitely won't be watching. She was by far the most annoying gi… https://t.co/at38flb9aH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @1LagerthaLothbr @AnnCoulter Jesus. H. Christ. that’s appalling.  She’s got absolutely no shame.  Then again it’s ann.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am surprised I'm not bald with all the hair I lose in the shower #shedding]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @sejournal, @GrowthMentorHQ, @GrowthHackers, and @quuu_co for mentioning me during your International… https://t.co/H1YaaMwel5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Issa Birthday 🎂 🎉🎈@wordtoJude  Ginaaaaa another yr has gone by and I still couldn’t be more proud of you! You’re a… https://t.co/s205Jk73GM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up today wondering just how drunk I really was last night. Well... I found 3 videos in my camera roll of me ch… https://t.co/cu8Sd3pjqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from work this afternoon, open the door, and I hear my own voice at the other end of the house. Hubby used his… https://t.co/5vWenMyE3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it’s chicken, chilies, onion, garlic and spinach. I think this is gonna be good maybe. #teamhannie @ South Colby… https://t.co/I3tND923Jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans Will Vote Against Trump’s National Emergency – Here They Are https://t.co/6wVxZ3sq3s via @ILMForg - vot… https://t.co/20kOSavhN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don’t think Bernie Sanders is the right candidate for the job and his inability to accept he just didn’t ea… https://t.co/dqRAPN2HkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[me and @JimCarrey have the same hair style and i love it https://t.co/OfOoO1pU3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iwillbreakyeww It’s not snowing in KY either and really it just isn’t fair. Let’s revolt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Philly! @Phillies Jake Arrieta loves us! @visitphilly #CityofBrotherlyLove @SportsRadioWIP @WIPMorningShow https://t.co/geEhUcJ0Ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost christiankeyes with get_repost ・・・ This is been my mood for years… If you have to choose between me and som… https://t.co/tTrXu4c7bE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me on Snapchat @christmaskati50 my emoji is wearing a red jacket with blue hair with flowers on her head]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swea this the mind set niggas have when they text me🤣 .. it be so funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charleslfreemn @WajahatAli @FrankLuntz @newtgingrich Yes! Still, Dems would learn a lot from his messaging tactics… https://t.co/vYhfXS0GVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelalyceee happy birthday to the most kind wonderful person ever!!! Tysm for being great and I hope your day is… https://t.co/v0yFx7KoaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMinkoWFAN talking about @RabbiDMK’s #succah on @WFAN660! #jewish #radio  - awesome show today again with… https://t.co/z577DMqbPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescdwyer Canada’s top civil servant said the same thing publicly today and is catching lots of hell for it. I a… https://t.co/84FXtHdh4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over here peacockin’ 🦚 #andsimultaneouslymatchingthewall #itspeacocknotpeahen #yogaeverydamnday #instayoga… https://t.co/mqTlBIovBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bootcamp bff 🤧🤧💓 ALL YALL FINE MF’s HIT HER UP. She needs some weenie]]></document><document><![CDATA[no words for this one @ Squaw Valley Alpine Meadows https://t.co/v0Ih71rKjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only goal in life rn is to meet any of the football players and become pals with them before they graduate lmaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love reading the stories behind the recipes--and sharing the stories behind my recipes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justicedems @alexandrasiera @AOC @SenMarkey @kevcirilli Radicals wanting to take America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nzraceresults @GloriousAllianc Omg, such a treat to see him again. He looks so very handsome. Blessings on you all. Love you all. 💖💖💖💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than a year removed from tearing his ACL, @Tre4Trey_ got back on the floor tonight for @slcstars   We’re all proud of you Tre!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gr82btnvol @JamesStein9 @GTA_Redhead @madsatan6969 @HippieVol @8MillionML @Smokeyholler @The_Fool_Monty… https://t.co/2WbwpfHzVv]]></document></documents></author>