<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Anyway, I just love it how as a preteen I thought cartoons were for little kids but now here I am, almost 21 years… https://t.co/NkwItjAaZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JusstNaee_ @khloekardashian Do you even know what an avi is?🤣Anyhoo little one🙄Stick up for the family that has no… https://t.co/ZuCrewoXzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Daddy #Obama is directing, controlling and funding his little #Socialist sister via his Alinsky agenda...… https://t.co/fPazO2EgVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@us_poll @kann_van @braun_fay52 @don85375 @chrisoplorable @SwettmanF @enterprise1054 @Kiwegapawa @MikeSchmidt62… https://t.co/OfIHofXgyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bedsheets are all pilled up. I don’t mean the fine cotton linen. I’m talking about the crushed sleeping pill dust caking them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sorry I haven’t answered your texts, I’m swamped at work” https://t.co/QI0MGR5Qj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥 Check out this MASSIVE GIVEAWAY by @RomanAtwood over at https://t.co/MQtG4Vhy9q! 🔥🔥    WIN BIG PRIZES from… https://t.co/F2kpnrUw65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis Dude, you are stuck in the past -- haven't done anything for the future of Native Black Americans.  G… https://t.co/7gAY8PLwfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a sound track to go out &amp; shoot one of your bf’s for actin up. 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vanessa Vangie Mateo: Make Vangie my dad - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/FdScwRXi4p @VanessaVanjie]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of my young journalism career will forever be that my editor read this punny newsletter header and di… https://t.co/qsgXDx4vEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say one thing do another, change your mind 24/7 don’t even comprehend you anymore, want one thing one day don’t car… https://t.co/EPaXBAR4ps]]></document><document><![CDATA[[E N C O U R A G E M E N T . . . |HAPPY HUMP DAY! ✨ https://t.co/PCHXdhCvBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaLK Yes they do.  The hardest thing a pet owner has to do is saying goodbye.  It has been three months and I still miss him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MewllerRawr @BeatrixAnn1 @Tonithecat32 @VitCza @MarsRoverCat @immaggi @WinnieWoo17 @Fuxinchen @Sweetdr17415074… https://t.co/MldQTMMhJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final stats: Stivers top Deer Park in district final, 76-62. #cincyhoops https://t.co/WGvavdJCKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 Not if they’ve looked at the blue-eyed Jesus that seems to be in pics everywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! I want you all to speak positivity into your lives today. And in order to possess such a power you MU… https://t.co/nAufMog6mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love our DeLand community! What fun we all had at the Mardi Gras on Mainstreet DeLand Dog Parade this past w… https://t.co/uFfjHU3Lp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueJays @DunedinBlueJays @baseballcanada @FisherCats @BuffaloBisons @LansingLugnuts @BluefieldJays @vancanadians… https://t.co/eEOY47c3DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[FSU social at NIRSA. My first professional position after grad school. I miss this group so much. So happy to get t… https://t.co/JkWiPrRxKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this matriarchal European island, ancient customs thrive https://t.co/pv3Hi2cj6Q via @NatGeoTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely saw one of my kids dads last night when I was out drinking. Don’t know if he saw me. We’ll find out maybe Friday]]></document><document><![CDATA[My life’s mission is now to get everyone to leave @WellsFargo .  4 levels of supervisors and no one can help.  Valencia needs to be FIRED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[thats the same level of disrespect i feel when yall say it. hispanics included.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another tweet that didn’t age well @realDonaldTrump You’re the wannabe dictator. The only #NationalEmergency is tha… https://t.co/hNDdiECOR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watched one Jacks fan save another Jacks fan’s life using the heimlich before the men’s game. I thought that wou… https://t.co/8F3vvHATuM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citizenkahn Eva is a beauty! I adore her sweater! I have an Eva also. She's a little squirt ❤ https://t.co/Elmat5eHum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump https://t.co/7UQq1IgIY1 😂🤣😅😆 we’re all laughing AT you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamsInColor33 Thanks Kristy! I love making them and it helps keep my mind not so stressful lol.. I do with my ow… https://t.co/IqB7cBnSMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiluRamalho @PatGrant7777 @lr3031 @Jonatha97947998 https://t.co/ob7aVzgRLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Anti christ is already on the scene explaining Why so many people are suddenly gone. He fixes the economy and c… https://t.co/swrrz6nVYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This devious weather has me thinking it’s not going to rain so I don’t prepare for it and once I go outside I’m soaked 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch your favorite girls in the audience of the Price is Right, tomorrow morning 10 am PST. Only on CBS🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because na only arewa guy remain for earth.  You lots need to go sleep inside the sea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jappoffjones Ain’t that dude in the red shirt in one of those Black Ink shows? https://t.co/hnOKogx5j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda__betty @LazyJediBri I listen to an Unsolved Mysteries podcast called Resolved Mysteries. The hosts are 3 wo… https://t.co/fFIWxvO1Uc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigdogdaddylove @WYMT @AndrewWYMT @brobwx @KelliWYMT @PaigeWYMT @JoshFitzWx @JimWKYT @ChrisWKYT @Kentuckyweather… https://t.co/wJlKn2FETz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vegardwikeby @elonmusk Sorry, wrong link. Same content, better link https://t.co/5FDagvER2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nightbefore #oscars #party 20thcenturyfox So cool seeing mike_myers_official @ 20th Century Fox https://t.co/3ECbRHEzXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bueno ya sabemos la historia de como nació la reina pepiada.. Esta es la historia de como nació la Arepa Guaidó! 🇻🇪… https://t.co/0olDL7m29S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_steller I’m sure I’ve told you this before, but Bob Stinson (RIP) drank a full bottle of whiskey that I got… https://t.co/Ksn92qMnJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when @MeganBhanot falls asleep early https://t.co/50M4F8AaEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lloydbassII @ScoobydaDog @ODonnellKarl @micky18010 @RGatone @FactsSupport @Erekose_On_MaM @TManitowoc @ZellnerLaw… https://t.co/u4aNXYaiat]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re listening online, here’s the info John’s discussing now. He backed out various funds. Chair asks, so we h… https://t.co/aHxt32uxlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easter Basket Ideas for Babies and Toddlers from @Katie Clark @ Clarks Condensed #mirth #chuckle #smirk #merry https://t.co/v31ahQg6Ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to work a black snake crossed my path and I saw a dead body so is this bad luck or]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/sf3YABlJqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StaySalty #Miami cc treatfoxes #treatfoxes @ The Salty Donut- Artisanal Donut Shoppe &amp; Coffee Bar https://t.co/hyfZ0l1rlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soon. Spring is in the air.  #bleedblue @ Apple Valley, California https://t.co/9awcpvedPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[almost all of my memes in my meme folder on my phone come from twitter so i just wanted to say thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meowmix2005 Right! So, basicly, you are the nurse of the vet world. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got out of the chiropractor was waiting for the bus it started pouring rain out of nowhere apparently I had lost… https://t.co/vocI3VWA4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know how many women be accidentally giving their pussy away and post-sex claiming it was a mistake? I need… https://t.co/x8vv0YjF9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollandKey @MaskedSingerFOX @MsGladysKnight The previous picture had an error, this one is correct, still the same… https://t.co/qPYL1kxzXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like that y'all... 🎤🎶🎂💛⚡️ #DHBC Fam⚡️ly - 3/18  #birthdaymonthweekends https://t.co/M0tCpEbRYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb 15 Lupercalia/ Nirvana day aspects from Gemini to cancer home nurturing, comfort food and cuddles. #astrology… https://t.co/lJ0L7L5p3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of bat really exemplifies the nickname that bats are called: Flying Mice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOLLYJBIRD @30days30ways @sagebrushfarmNV @ittoiblog @craftyforhome @confessions_cup @Oneexceptional1 @Angir… https://t.co/JMZjqIylzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raymacaricatura Para ellos mientras menos gente mejor! Como cuando dejaron salir a los cubanos en desbandada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas skyline... #roomwithaview @ Rio All-Suite Hotel &amp; Casino https://t.co/CRDI90TjFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my chemistry teacher is all excited and is like “isn’t that so cool?” No, it’s not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention #pageantcontestants  Please visit my website and send me a message to book your In-studio or FaceTime pag… https://t.co/seWQkTBVDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland I've become an expert on Government Employee EXTORTION rackets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NatashaSAlford has a list of recommended tools for digital reporting. Check it out here:  https://t.co/NIbinAQ6kU https://t.co/gnC2e2o0g9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost g.brown_readitagain ・・・ Next month..#ReadItAgain #GBrown #NowOrNeverEP #Lately #MilwaukeeMusic #Top10Shit… https://t.co/eZUTi7G2tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“NoBodY CarEs aBouT wResTlinG”  These 14,000 ppl would beg to differ.  Lol go freakin pokes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You didn’t come into this world. You came out of it, like a wave from the ocean. You are no stranger here 🖤🖤… https://t.co/kAPsLbpk9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gin_discoverArt @EarthandClouds @EarthandClouds2 You’re So Right!!!💞🤗😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[all that matters is margot robbie ordering a drink next to me @ a gay bar in weho..that is all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only did y’all fuck up my order, I watched as one of your “managers” made my bread bowl, with no gloves, after… https://t.co/GraZe02F6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[i Haven’t Eaten one singLe meal today. the only things Passing through My digEstive system are girl scout cookies, coffee, and wheat thins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great night.... #UniverSoulCircus2019 @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/dC3PLeajzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[fake patty’s and a dance competition all in one weekend :) i’m good at decision making]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilNobileJr Happy Anniversary to you 💕 and @FANGORIA 🖤 https://t.co/4BRd2W4jqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly @J_Sump's instagram should be a magazine https://t.co/jXwXETDXxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[e finalmente, esta semana acabou! Eu tive muito o que fazer esta semana. Tive duas apresentações, dois projetos, um… https://t.co/8K2G0HMZbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steph &amp; I with my "aunt" Cindi &amp; my Mama ❤ So thankful to havw them to travel to concerts with!! 😁 https://t.co/sd12Y96OTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Givng thanks always for all things unto God and the Father in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ (Epheisans 5:20).… https://t.co/qrlpwt8vLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UBwomenshoops have it under control in Q4. And Stephanie Reid is in the house. #UBhornsUP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna end up losing my shit if this dumbass doesn't leave me alone!! Why keep trying to ruin my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow What about when Kylie took someone else’s or Khloé originally with Tristian? Man this family drags ya back in...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real reason I love @KimKardashian  is she uses her platform to save everyone. Homeless, victims, anyone she feels t… https://t.co/KijH0NzdwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ernie_plumley @smalltownandrew Hard to believe! She is cray cray! 🧐🥴🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an incredible night at Rosemount High School watching the Dakota United Hawks! Very exciting game and great sp… https://t.co/l5IYL56aSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatherineUNIT2 @EVNow @EricBoehlert The original post said they were booing Hillary -- they were booing the superd… https://t.co/COTy5d2uCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so ugly sometimes i wanna not go out in public ever again cause I'm walking around in this meat prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rappers wanna be atl niggas. The strippers always on dime Atlanta shit. The fake dealers always “trapping” with… https://t.co/VRfNRVuQt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s exactly what the Republicans want to hear! And..NOT what we need to get rid of trump! That’s how we got him… https://t.co/IY5t6oFp6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear brothers and sisters, take note of this: Everyone should be quick to listen, slow to speak and slow to beco… https://t.co/GarZS01iGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinVance9314 Due process. Whatever you believe, the investigation continues and no one Jussie or the other men have been convicted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlentyOfFish I got an email notification from you this morning that someone changed my password but it wasn’t me.… https://t.co/SmUFeQLQct]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep at Denny’s last night &amp; when I woke up my mozzarella sticks were gone &amp; all but 1 chicken strip was left 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Maybe tomorrow”  I imagine myself saying this with exasperation at the inconvenience of the whole thing. Then lack… https://t.co/boS3BQhVUb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. State of Georgia's  Chapter of the Year Award @ Crowne Plaza Atlanta SW - Peachtree Ci… https://t.co/GX3521U8Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magicshcp_ @bts_bighit @iHeartRadio You all need to check out the lyrics of Spine Breaker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[airports must have a spell on their doors that causes complete loss of all self-awareness when entering the buildin… https://t.co/UZm6rtjKi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[love it when i have kids in my backseat and one of them whispers “it’s okay, she won’t notice because her car is already dirty”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTay33371956 Have you lived here to know it’s NOT that bad in the summer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost over flowing #ketogenic coffee #amwriting #bulletproofcoffee #bulletproof #ketodiet #keto #paleo #creative… https://t.co/dMaDotqGVQ]]></document></documents></author>