<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We took my youngest child to the high school open house tonight. He starts next year. Someone has some big shoes to… https://t.co/QahdXlq8X2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely stoked to have done a seen with wolf the energy was great. 😎😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrossingBroad Or is he?!? His plane maybe but Middleton May still be in Vegas! Who knows! https://t.co/UZmxxoFV66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a girl that truly cares about your health and well being. Haley makes me feel so loved and happy in a way t… https://t.co/BUDDEJV1FD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonbamford I'm honored to meet u on Twitter Simon, enjoy my latest horror film review DITCH DAY MASSACRE… https://t.co/6mkMyIPxXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJoeAbah anyone that snatch ballot boxes on election day will die for it, period. Enough of the political correct… https://t.co/7hiCk4jNCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somos hermanos y nos tenemos que apoyar @DrFerminGarcia @manuelpatete COMPLETA: Guaidó y Duque conversaron por Inst… https://t.co/1iBuuKFh99]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think kyrie is capable of being happy. He was on a team that won a world title and wasn’t happy. Now he’s o… https://t.co/VhDQc8n1RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing #Team win over the 2xDefending Champs on the road by the @Suns #ValleyBoyz beginning to put it together!! G… https://t.co/NcCiXaSGc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamispachulis @jonasbrothers @joejonas @kevinjonas @nickjonas no manches. todo mi tl está vuelto loco con sucker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s okay...tag someone who needs to hear this quote. #tagafriend #mindset #happiness #letgo #smile #happy… https://t.co/48bkJAsUGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who had a crush on Blevins as a kid or or is that just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m moments away from asking someone with mad zodiac knowledge to help me out. God don’t answer and I sure as shit… https://t.co/wa9Q7Q3Att]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdw9278 @Dad2136 @FlakesRockWell Geez gonna get Sowder all fired up now. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo 👏🏼 @CocaCola 👏🏼.               https://t.co/AEg0UDtryV via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[South beach #florida #floridalife #floridians #eckerdlife #eckerdcollege #stpete #beach #thinkoutside #repost… https://t.co/8ExJYG4N8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's my party and I'll cry if I want to #Birthday #BirthdayBoy #TheBigFiveFive #FiftyFiveYearsYoung 🎂🎂🎂 https://t.co/75jwXmXoBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey flatfoot, too bad you didn’t go to Vietnam when you were supposed to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Why would someone bring a gun to a bloody parade?” #GreysAnatomy #YoureinAmerica]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigtanktv Check out this highlight!https://t.co/xWAr6cKnYx 6’2 245 DE/OLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reasons why the crown Vic will always be the best cop car 😱🤤 https://t.co/keK4bnAXxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Central Camionera Millenium in Culiacan, SIN https://t.co/rZLdk9aHGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NjTank99 Was thinking of you Frank, when I ordered Wunderbar bologna, while at Stop and Shop yesterday... The best by a mile!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey fam 😚💨 happy saturday 💯🔥💨 useing only a gif, picture or meme show me what type of music you're into atm 🎵🎵🎵. Th… https://t.co/e4rOQy1gV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoanhorseBex @runwithskizzers Agreed! If you really want to experience a movie uninterrupted and undisturbed (exce… https://t.co/LpiQMM8Ez1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:30 in the morning, headed to the airport, have my best RBF on. Let’s do this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seabreeze breaks the scoreless game up with a penalty kick in the 21st minute. Daytona Seabreeze 1, @rrhsknights 0,… https://t.co/mAoNGN3HKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc Waste of time and taxpayers money. We know if Senate does the same it’ll only get vetoed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bernieparent @CMBaseball41 Bernie!! Bernie!! My man!! https://t.co/LQb5Oep7rR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KGertsen @IowaHoops @connor_m30 We tried yesterday with Shon. He wasn't having it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinnnWard @KalebVaughan5 About that... y’all have a great day, see you tomorrow Kbaby ❤️ https://t.co/0YJsHz4jTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LenaWaithe The list of men that have fucked a Jenner or Kardashian are very interchangeable, sometimes even within the family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cruising the #SantaBarbaraPier in the #38Ford. @ Santa Barbara, California https://t.co/LqI7otKGpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fermontyvila You are a person that likes my stuff https://t.co/TDwXdnJQci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurnoutPAC N0 HELL NO WONT VOTE FOR ANOTHER DIPWAD THAT WILL NOT WORK FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGTedBerg No worries ! No 7 sub was also good. The taco was excellent !!! The girl at the counter said it was an u… https://t.co/hIbw7ofDl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is a great time to #BePrepared for the predicted #snow tonight. Is your emergency kit stocked with the items you… https://t.co/H24ZgzpmAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanna say that @SouthwestAir is my go to when traveling. Looking forward to flying with you soon to FLL.   Was… https://t.co/IRZFNi0whH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alpipkin @KimberlyMrsRR1 @weaselzippers What is she implying that southern ppl are all into BBQ.   I call that kinda RACEIST!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To view LeBron through a NBA “Championship Rings” lens is an archaic ideology.  In History, he will Rival/Surpass M… https://t.co/WBB7tlvjmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of #GOESEast Mesoscale Sector Coverage today 02/26 Real-Time #ABI TrueColor/IR with EAST Meso1 (red) / Meso2 (… https://t.co/7g7Yil2lza]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been a long while but finally eating Red Beans Bayou again!  #fattuesday #cajunfood #yum @ Villa Luna Venue https://t.co/7XAVYcLAOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MackenzieStoltz @cloverathletics @Jamie_A_Thomas @joeybbennett Thanks Kenzie]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the one issue I dont agree with #Elon_musk , I am positive #hydrogen is the future of #clean_energy and it… https://t.co/SmTtoX7W4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_talkamania @smarktodeath What do y'all want? Ruby to get a 20 day title reign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEisaAli @AlvaroLevrero @bsays01 @JamesOlley @KentGooner77 @SpursOfficial @Arsenal If that’s a straight red then… https://t.co/i18fzBi0JS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweetus Deletus is prolly my favorite Harry Potter spell if I'm keeping it a band.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure to cop your tickets for Tynan at City bar this weekend. https://t.co/kYh6czmgrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dairy fat: Newfound friend or a foe? The body of data that is starting to show the need for you to drop only lesser… https://t.co/TMeBqlU7T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FelipeCalderon Flipan..cuando dejaras de estar chingando..hasta que te pongan tras las rejas. Eso buscas...déjate… https://t.co/87pZ4Yl9xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeaaa I'll  rather have @tigresdelnorte day than a @iamcardib day in Houston.  no cap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redturn2 @kikehndez Or the next Dodgers Manger.  That loves pasta, of course🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump President Trump, @BarackObama and I pushed you into The President's office.  I'm going to form uni… https://t.co/odFSAqM6I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Data Analytics &amp; Measurement Tools - Think with Google @ThinkwithGoogle https://t.co/lNrShHxcXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevoesports And I have all the respect for Brazilian/other SA overwatch players and have tried to support them as… https://t.co/rEVYvHuaCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kungfookity Your welcome hope you get better soon 😊, how come you didn’t go to indoor yesterday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THS_tweet @AleZ2016 I was going through my Bookmarks!  Who would have thought! Beautiful lesson there!❤😚]]></document><document><![CDATA[if not only to make matters worse, I haven’t even been able to write lyrics, i just keep coming up with random hook… https://t.co/YRFXFn2lXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why I’m sleeping and I hear this smacking noise. I look up it’s my damn dog sitting in front of the fan bit… https://t.co/CIP2szOsrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advierten pérdida de 4,000 empleos más en Matamoros por huelgas | El Economista @eleconomista  https://t.co/VZtGE5aCee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaChene @Lawrence @Thom_Hartmann @SpeakerPelosi @MalcolmNance @dpakman @FBITampa This should surprise absolute… https://t.co/jkKLvmveix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat being President isn't what you thought it was. Was it, Donnie ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comcastcares Thank you but our screen went black today, like it has a few times a week for the past several months… https://t.co/jZu51wMPj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rwandapolice @UrugwiroVillage @RwandaGov @NewTimesRwanda @rbarwanda @PrimatureRwanda @FirstLadyRwanda… https://t.co/UJ3rMnfbOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/0prw2irI4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msjaninelinde @therealJuliaAnn Haven’t you ever been to Clubs in Buckhead/Atlanta ?  So many so many. Pick one. It… https://t.co/KTTbBZc50u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC We need you to rally behind Bernie ASAP so it's no doubt who the frontrunner really is! You can help him surge… https://t.co/v54WQl7NFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor Newsome  is intirely wrong  and just wants to keep the drugs  coming into california so the elites  can ke… https://t.co/fHtVEJF0yO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCodyHills @IrrationalHawk A loss, &amp; no tourney better equate to firing a coach]]></document><document><![CDATA[TX veteran raises over $4,000 for Afghan family: https://t.co/UjuCdy0WPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Comply If you don't fight the police, you will not die. It's simple folks, and it's the law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgegotjokes @mastodron @RABAGOOOO So y’all calling me an asshole. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the ref had trouble figuring out which of the four offside players was involved? #dipshit #TOTARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_waleedshahid @SenFeinstein @sunrisemvmt @AOC @SenMarkey I’m more disgusted by yet another adult using children as… https://t.co/lMPy6jJSKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crowez45 @ShaneGoldmacher Not sure that is accurate. Remember, there are amazing humans who never even went to college. 😉👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCPSKY students! We have your back in this important work. Be bold, #payattention and rewrite #Louisville’s story… https://t.co/7YXDvX4Hod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunord @mexicoworldcup OK lets look at the #s;only 23 players from the 4 rounds of the #MLS not so SupeDraft made… https://t.co/8f1UScSnId]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn Oakman was a guaranteed first round pick and had a bright career ahead of him but bitches like her are out he… https://t.co/vPiFzxaw5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiemccaffrey @mehdirhasan @JMooreBoston @cartoonnetwork @FoxNews Also, Fox is not news at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Super Session IPA #2 (Amarillo) by @LawsonsFinest @ Gables University Station — https://t.co/cYcgwvPpXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all models be cutting ur hair and that’s the main reason why u be getting booked smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMMcCammack @mattc_fcs I’ve got over half of next years crop sold at that]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤🎤   Austin WSup !! Catch me Your # 1PR Hosting @sxsw this Thursday March 14th 1-9p at the FallOut Theatre.… https://t.co/Q8qKhejcDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cummingstabytha Go Fuck Yourself - Two Feet Love is a Bitch - Two Feet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory If you ask this upstanding Jeffress ... he’ll tell you Jews can’t go to heaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADL_Watch I am a documented descendant of slave owners. MY ancestors paid good money for their slaves and received… https://t.co/r7R4zxxEQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last few days of ⁦@USPharmacopeia⁩ staff thoughts on our upcoming 200th anniversary as seen in one of our Rockville… https://t.co/NzV0ydbHye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entrega de Apoyos (@ Concepción del Oro in ZAC) https://t.co/paxMUnH1Fs https://t.co/JuWppxm0e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently LIVE playing #Starbound! Come watch!    https://t.co/VTJ6ogCpvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Giannis_An34 is putting on a show for this #NBAAllstar2019 game. Hopefully they go for 200 pts! @magentacoble21 wh… https://t.co/nCGoF46YZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Won on my best bet last night. 📞 954 825 7359 before 1pm est for today's 2 NBA and CBB best bets. https://t.co/Jg7bS4V0qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie awww,,,,you are the sweetest and most loving girl on the planet earth. I love u so very much my beautiful wife.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyThomasTV @CTVNationalNews Congrats! What a time to be taking this assignment. Who knows where this roller coa… https://t.co/7RFWhYvgFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I am two point two pounds, you’re barely a hundred and twenty-five grams.” (Beat Tape Mode in session)  Yashika T5… https://t.co/34kwPC2Wo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichEisenShow @BarstoolBigCat @richeisen @PardonMyTake Also Big Cat just saw your debate with Eisen on YouTube. Yo… https://t.co/K53WIfs2CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdellag Eat!  Listen to your body!  The same way we listen when our bodies say, "That hurts, don't do that," your… https://t.co/0hmA5i7YvC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bacchaus351 @justinamash @alllibertynews Top of the morning to you laddie !]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @hollyhendrix_ @AlainaDawsonxxx @adrianachechik @anyaolsenXXX @alexgreyxxx @rejaniced @RileyReidx3… https://t.co/pzDlJSCjSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a helluva time during last 3 weeks of solid travel for work. Luckily, I'm part of a crew from all across the… https://t.co/vnH91xYCob]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because if he did, there’d be something to blame it on, other than he’s a POS.]]></document></documents></author>