<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Haven’t studied for an exam I have tomorrow yet bc I love self sabotaging lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The benefits of having an art director friend that has some free time while I’m trying to furnish my house are *amazing*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cm_quinn My cat head butts my hand if I’m not paying close enough attention and forces me to pet her that way 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know I got the sauce, you know I’m saucyyyyyyy https://t.co/kwaQpWnP60]]></document><document><![CDATA[New to real estate? Have your license and want to join a team? Looking to grow your network? If your answer is yes… https://t.co/nNEqJcSPr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithBeyda Me imagino lo que debes sentir Jaja si yo estoy contando los meses de aquí a Diciembre 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@macyyykaris I mean I was gonna go with you but then you told me it was exercise..... pass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news from Congress last night as the #EveryKidOutdoors Act passed through Congress as part of the… https://t.co/DtX3txgypp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenny #blackberry #peach #sangria #kenracolor #pulpriot #elixir #enjoyhairandskintreatmentoil #rusksensories… https://t.co/eMxtN4t6zA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevshiotelis @HembreeSprings So glad this sweet boy loves to read! He has grown by leaps and bounds this year - th… https://t.co/AZuwienCDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HotFreestyle @kodaklens The Godfather of HipHop! God bless this Man 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccioAmberly @BlairGilfillan @hotmessexpressx @heartlesslyhope @mrolivergunn @MrErnestOwens @ArianaGrande Perhaps… https://t.co/l8Wds6BvKX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthatoddharv @BeaudoinCharlie @JoeDeFacto @angenola @BlueTsuni @shashatheitch22 @PaulSaucier9 @JamesCowden8… https://t.co/neMGjD8Mnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have probably gotten fired but god it would have been a good way to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t driven the Jeep is so long I hope I still remember how to drive standard https://t.co/hUxhdPsgED]]></document><document><![CDATA[what i am really loving about being in Boston this weekend is that my hotel is hosting a furry convention! :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorBronin @HartfordDPW Are Hartford schools off for the holiday tomorrow?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs @jetrotter She also has a girls school that allegedly had abuse complaints come out!!  She’s a hypocrite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thumbs up for solar! Grow Solar - California! #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels START HERE -&gt; https://t.co/h6vRHvyCtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing @thedivakitty and I love more than getting into an air conditioned car on vacation and Kenny G is bumpin’ !… https://t.co/1gPQ3vrDfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm having so much trouble I need some help I'm loosening our home. I haven't worked since Dec. 2018. My son also h… https://t.co/Lb6kqFBdYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough game today! Proud that you never gave up! Now what will I do with my Saturdays? 🏀 @D1fuzzymuffin17 https://t.co/5FxVYGtrGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I totally agree!  I really try my best to learn the names of every 750 of my kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoTV Of course she’s leaving him.  Really.  She’s all about herself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[please dont go out yo way to let everybody know you fw this nigga 🤣🤣 whew chillayyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Think Trump is obsessing about Cohen much when his job today is to denuclearize NK? But then again, he h… https://t.co/KssfTGjSgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACog1984 Thanks Al... Happy Valentines 😃❤️🌹💜✡️💚... first thing on my grocery list 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[As close as we got... #goodeyesaustin... @ L.A. LIVE https://t.co/YUKA2CkmeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love them .....  my fellow esthetician’s mates ! _____________________________ #galdayla #losangelesmakeupartist… https://t.co/ijekEWtRT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, I gotta stop or I’ll be retweeting content all night! #LastOneIPromise #IThink]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have 4 meetings today. but i get off work early and head to auburn so i guess that’s a bonus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMotivation....Education is the most  powerful weapon which you can use to Change the World. - Nelson Mandela… https://t.co/oK5lZWH4fZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my weather reel from the semester so far- https://t.co/oc2LRQHvjZ https://t.co/TAmWeW5rrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Calls Democrats ‘Crazy,’ and Colbert Returns the Favor https://t.co/15BJ843hGG #LSSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le «NM Apollo» entre en service à Matane #JDQ #tvanouvelles #polqc https://t.co/cdEPstDY4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying @TNiepa ‘s featured talked @ChemePitt Research day! @PittEngineering https://t.co/ZZxSpJG6RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many head strikes did he have to give you to make your dumbass come up with this??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let nothing be done through strife or vainglory; but in lowliness of mind let each esteem other bette…… https://t.co/0g4WBCXW68]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brake lights on the highway give me SO much anxiety ugh I hate driving all my wrecks have ruined me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@audsabres @JeremyGregoret1 @DragonMom98 @jimmyreu81 @SabresFunStats @lno09281978 @MsAFromBK @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/NiqeXqt9Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano 1970 protest Calling the military's finest baby killers.. now the Democrates become the baby killers… https://t.co/KGYPvBht4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ay_taybay I don’t  think he wants to sit down, it’s sad. I wish for the same thing but..,.he has to call them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚Go back and re-read The Mis-Education of the Negro by Carter G. Woodson ...... then rethink your approach to success.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The trending product that I will be trying out in 72 hours is… https://t.co/84WDGSp1t7 https://t.co/RHFc13HO8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woot! More nominations for Shadow of the Tomb Raider! Am so honoured to have been part of @briandoliveira &amp;… https://t.co/oGpmp6hwji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@la_patilla Esta mujer .... tiene perdido su rebaño....😳😩.... que hace en la ONU...?   Seguir abogando por los narc… https://t.co/IegQhyBtjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their wives in the video &amp; the center of attention instead of hiring video girls. HONORABLE is the word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset reflection on my golden boy.  #thisguy #thatface #iheartbart #bartley #bart #dog #dogs #olddog #olddogs… https://t.co/3DAtfIx9jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accidentally planned four different social outings for this week and my bank account is PISSED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for fabulous conversation with fabulous women!! @linkindywomen @ The Hatch https://t.co/xjhPVBtjUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried commenting on a subreddit, and about 30 minutes later got a message saying my comment had been removed... int… https://t.co/XdVxaIO8UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah fr tho like “see that girl...that’s me you’re probably wondering how I got here..well first we have to go back… https://t.co/4ytUXrccxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalWomensDay here’s to all the women I serve along side or the ones that paved the way for women to be engine… https://t.co/6JYOViJXjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alli___J Lol there’s mudslides in Sausalito i guess that’s not funny but still]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeachCode coding unplugged. Doing some coding without a computer. https://t.co/3DEoWKfWta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COUPLECOINS i want everyone to see how hot u are when they click on my twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Loving life just brought this guy into the family! https://t.co/CyU7SKJXkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[......she corrected me by saying “you were 12” “no matter what he said, you could not consent”. #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish more #comedy bookers took into consideration how much I #grind, how hard I work to build a fan base, my tale… https://t.co/rM0yZgMBQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensé que era domingo ya iba aventar el célula por sonar a estas horas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I welcomed my students to OHville!  Love the Seusstastical fun as we celebrate all that Dr. Seuss contributes… https://t.co/UR40m1gInJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Semaphore89 @Razorsmack1 @Tiredofweirdos @SoniaK05765611 @dizzymom64 @ToniWilliams10 @MartyWatson11 @MAGAgirly… https://t.co/HfDi9hDPXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[The smell of Amy’s candles have moved into my room and I’m so here for it. All the smells with 0 fire needed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FQMule @AynW Agreed. And maybe it could work in some other land, but you know how sick we all are of folks telling… https://t.co/n2kCljOdZX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, God, and know my heart; test me and know my anxious thoughts.  See if there is any…… https://t.co/9MgGJMgVOp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bdwal359 @jameskthompson1 Where was Trumps all awareness when he was Attacking a Sitting President about his Birth… https://t.co/LvpD5K3rKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_on11 @aaron_hogan @dbc_inc @KimGriesbach @Isham_Literacy @kim_lohse4 @msyoung114 @LevineWrites @MrBaskwill… https://t.co/zrGrNHj0tW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It may be sunny, but WIU definitely has a weary cloud over its head today. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robgrav3s I’m a nurse. You’d be shocked and amazed what people do with rodents!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do it Mr. President and end the nonsense of democrats once and for all. We need to have a safe America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dylanmsmitty This M.... Fuc... has committed More Crimes then we can imagine! My God, Treason, Sexual Assault, Rap… https://t.co/0jcLfgqta3]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches sweating me now when they really need to be sweating 25 year old me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/gv84KnCUrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evicksss Whyyyy would you do that?! 😭 I can’t even look at the damn thing let alone watch the video 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win tickets to see @marenmorris with @98wsix! https://t.co/XuMgXsml0e @Think_Country]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halsey You’re amazing! I saw snl and loooved it! ♥️ and you are so great at art too? Amazing artist 👩‍🎤 🖼]]></document><document><![CDATA[being made to show up work at 6am to let a cleaning crew in the day dst kicks on is just cruel, for all parties involved 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Kindness ninjas” is now a permanent part of my classroom vocabulary! Fantastic! Thx for sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Paulie Walnuts is going to prison for a long, long, long time. All because he won't tell the truth. Who is he af… https://t.co/sOuMCB1eA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4ILorg @SamidounPP Would you let a promotional post shape your world view?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeaknOfMoody What does that stand for I’m tired of trying to figure it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonriver365 I agree. #TrumpKimSummit - historic. Never happened before before between countries. Soft diplomacy,… https://t.co/BN2RKEK6fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colby and the boys continuing to work hard! #TrustTheProcess #KeepBattling #ColbyRasberry2022 @CyFairKings… https://t.co/qHp7tyGgKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSiegRacing Congrats on your success!!  Your team is like “old school racing” that we all love.  Happy to hear… https://t.co/JbjGBi3U2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLyK76 @Jennife14860185 @cannaworldsite @_jena4n @mmatyree @Hippie_of_Love @KushingtonBear @RogueOne3One… https://t.co/m4hNgo4gUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some hilarity. #mirth #tee-hee #smile #farcical https://t.co/Bu1WjeVV4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ms_andiloveall Such an accomplishment! I hope to have published something by then - only a few more years 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMcSallyAZ you want Arizona to elect you?....start showing your softer side.  You have to connect with people an… https://t.co/9kIosHm6Xu]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s either daj or mesha that text me out the blue and tell me that they love me . them my babies fr 🤞🏽❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It almost looked like I was driving onto a movie set. Crisp, clean air! Loving my Cardiff! . . . #cardiffbythesea… https://t.co/KeucdYl77a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Armageist1 @WlLDNATURE @conquer0r91 I honestly dont get why it would be torture since most times when animals are… https://t.co/SOqe1f1ywr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reuben” &amp; friends in progress. Coming soon to a wall near you!  #wonder #wonderbread #miami #rayban #cool… https://t.co/sBh6i3KdOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I SHOULD be sleeping but instead I wrote a whole reflection on my life thus far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathyRadigan @realDonaldTrump Cohen is doing a great job of getting himself back in more legal trouble and degradi… https://t.co/5qOlDUrBqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl I’ll tell my suegros, my neighbors, the hoes I don’t like. We gotchu!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOberg @freenaynow Who is the jerk just taking a picture of this and not helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simply trying to get a boarding pass and no help from American Airlines ....would appreciate some help. Customer se… https://t.co/27V6SKj0AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt @kookdae97 What it said? In private, you turned off for me so can't talk with you the things that has to b… https://t.co/4z3umA0tar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bgiant1Bob @MSNBC For one..both she and Bill were meant to serve their country..for two it’s gonna take a qualifie… https://t.co/hlmiYzYjb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como me voy a ir a hacer la fitness, si mañana laburo DOCE HORAS, tanta bosta voy a tener en la cabeza!!!!!!!]]></document></documents></author>