<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@bumble is to thank for multiple things in my life. Including this beanie. 😉 #bumblequeenbee #bumble #queenbee 🐝 https://t.co/LchYrFBSH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace And was fired so he couldn’t get retirement]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry but She Definitely Ain't No Angel !! 😂🤣 @SYFY #ZnationFamily @USA_Network  #NetfixSaveZNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard an older gentleman say to his friend “just fake a fall and start screaming for help”🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Metro by T-Mobile &amp; Name 🆔️ on W. Chicago Ave! @nameiDapp @MetroByTMobile @FirstOrionCorp @AlmaLon30497656 https://t.co/xFW2GVClJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alklapperichATC @sarah_bowmar @bowmarnutrition My problem is I have a hard time eating just one! So yummy]]></document><document><![CDATA[... damn, forgot about that work that means no weekend Coaster trains... still, puts less pressure on today then lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with @lerentsch and @jaredtrotter and little everett! ❤️❤️ @ Muir Beach, California https://t.co/je2lAlmHF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If y’all hear a jet pass y’all house Friday that’s me....I got my taxes 🛫]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I spent less time worrying about life and actually did stuff that would better my life I would actually be successful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitrionambalfe @YouTube Oh, my @caitrionambalfe you were and ARE just stunning!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A group game of peekaboo! The parachute is one of the most fun ways we explore spatial awareness in Kindermusik! Ne… https://t.co/dVwqYnayIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention Democrats and Republicans. It was only a matter of time before the parties separated the people of the US… https://t.co/GC21Y8OHXL]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Navy Band 🎺  #usnavy #gonavy #usnavyband #navyweek #mardigras #laissezlesbonstempsrouler @ Mardi Gras Park https://t.co/maaluU9IUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dodd–Frank Wall Street Reform and Consumer Protection Act An Act... the financial stability of the United States by… https://t.co/TgqwUvh8E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelJ262 @spouez @RTI_EdWork @RTIPress @ScottKipp @tsslade @fsueducation @MollyHamm @RicharEms I’m showing them… https://t.co/niotS1q5hc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeonardPhillipM False. They may not have the votes in the Senate to win, but neither did the GOP when they want af… https://t.co/s3IrV9WwxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SongoftheDay we shouldn't need a #HallmarkHoliday To remind us to love one another but Incase you need a reminder… https://t.co/SPMgPv2JcR]]></document><document><![CDATA[me sitting in a restaurant alone waiting for my roommates to return from games on the road.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have always been a healthy eater, but these last few months I've been eating stuff out of my norm and can't shake… https://t.co/gq3NqEzUl4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjoelpimentel @CNCOmusic #PretendCNCO #pretendCNCO  listening from california! 🥰 https://t.co/4Wzn0dOIzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of hearing the blame game and the self-blame game. This team sucks because everyone is too stubborn to mo… https://t.co/zmhbM0vK82]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than a tropical drink to beat the #winterblues. Join us and enjoy $5 Drinks and Appetizers, from 5-7… https://t.co/wslUHQkylC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahJazz17 @AwlesAntonov @Edwardonatav1 @AnnaCAAlves17 Good morning Sarah 🌷🌷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JordanPotrzeba One question - how many of our Ss have actually seen an Indiana Jones movie ?? 😉😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dannyacosta5 should’ve not blocked me on ig and stopped sharing location with me... sorry😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flannelbean Is that also where you stroke the devils pods, work the USB, and swallow the smonk because if u are I… https://t.co/QXLZbFugm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has been a very difficult day on LSE. Terribly sorry to hear the news of another serious incident. Working to… https://t.co/y8OxbAFuTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Friends, Our MANTRAS AND MALLAS is quickly approaching!  March 21st at Glazed Over in Ocean City. If you have… https://t.co/rKFmeLizdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada Well imagine how rough it is for young black men incarcerated for years with minor offenses! They d… https://t.co/BOjWeBgxab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advocating for our patients at the Grassroots - MNA Nurses Night at the General Assembly @Miki__Goodwin @JHUNursing https://t.co/Gr8ym3BVvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Maher Mocks Red State Voters, Says Rich and Educated Live in Blue States https://t.co/Xiy6VQwKwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[“call him up” “i can’t i don’t have his number” “how can you not have your mans number?!”  tbh idk i just snapchat him sorry bree 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is comic. One for the high school English teachers out there... #funniness #giggle #smile #hilarious https://t.co/gJxIoKz8xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoodGodAbove And I could have never released the greatest cure ever that will effect everyone on the planet (th… https://t.co/Gm4mr9zkZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a chilly 42 in #Alpine. Thankfully, I got #NBC7 Drone Ranger to keep me warm. Very grateful to see the sun shi… https://t.co/729jTcqC22]]></document><document><![CDATA[Edinboro ‘23... Hamdiallah for 4 more years of doing what I love to do. As for fordson, thank you for the endless s… https://t.co/ShXJtPWIWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm home and watching local news because I am who I am. Hi WI- @fox11news and @WFRVLocal5. 👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHillfl looking pretty sweaty there.  And when you can only defend your repeal of #gunsense reform in FLA by ca… https://t.co/wxAUyyQdft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannieWurz @carlywatters She is brilliant, awesome that you’re using her resources to your advantage!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a great amount of Civil Unrest in these United States https://t.co/XGo5YGyY6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @kmele So medias have already changed their way of reporting, covered a fake story, without daring ra… https://t.co/9f34JtW5nH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whose next,  your child, wife,husband...father...mother..grandparents...just not right putting illegals above our s… https://t.co/PGJGHeXfhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erxnxshley i’m typically watching between 5-10 shows all at once tbh. also usually reading about that many books shrug]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should mortify all Christians.  Hillsong needs to address this… Or they will start losing people left and righ… https://t.co/94qNGaITFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charityhelman @edtechteam Thank you so much! I think it turned out pretty good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shayw182 @ChannonRose Literally!  People get so butthurt!  Literally this is what I told my husband last night I w… https://t.co/zqibIhRZxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[this movie is so cute, it makes me want to live in 80's new york. https://t.co/XIIOHRLT64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember at Salida middle school where of you got caught with a logo on your shit that was bigger than the size of… https://t.co/tFA289Vx98]]></document><document><![CDATA[America needs STRICT voter reform &amp; voter ID at every polling place before #2020.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATLBravesGirl12 @Acuna13Matata I have used those pens for going on 10 years. I bit the hurt and bought a whole box… https://t.co/glJ9mP8RAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricardodequerol @AnaCarbajosa Me quedo sin habla Ricardo, excelente tweet🙏 #FactsMatter No conocía la historia del… https://t.co/aWm1BTLDA4]]></document><document><![CDATA[how am i s’posed to go to bed early n wake up well rested for my adult job when there’s stan twitter that goes all night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@this_girl_rach I have never had one sober. I might need to change that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend told me yesterday that I was a walking encyclopedia and I love that compliment so much even though I know I’m so far from it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samstrouud Smart!!! I rarely get coffee there so I didn’t know ab that 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell me why I work at a 5 star steakhouse and my ass gets McDonald's for dinner after work instead of getting food at work 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us never forget the time a French-Canadian man in Montreal was very confused when I told him Americans do not t… https://t.co/2JclkkD3to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameANew @WPXIScott @JenniferTomazic @kamenta @WPXITraffic @KDKAHeather @AmyWadas @WPXIMelanie @WPXIShelley Happy Birthday!! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caffeine                              Anxiety                                      🤜🤛… https://t.co/L7RXlmGrLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grantstern @ScottMStedman Patriotic. Smart. Sensible. Basically decent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassSather Once you graduate it just becomes -itis cuz your body hurts, bills are fast approaching, and everyone t… https://t.co/uEOXgpefwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am livid! A known, beloved #DisabilityRightsAdvocate is gone, essentially because her #HealthInsurance killed her… https://t.co/d8MpeiUVcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas brothers need to stop teasing us and drop their song already I’ve waited too long for this]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in my life I’ve injured myself badly enough that I’m not permitted to rungor a while. But as I h… https://t.co/qwNAqz4Y6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays @SebGorka Mr Pres - you recently mentioned- about coming down the escalator and  you announced you… https://t.co/0E6KPMuUKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaN_anon @SputterOnline @davidmweissman @BarackObama @vj44 @JohnBrennan Lol no]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a-lot of my heartbreak is a direct result of my upbringing in the church. I remember an Apostle looked at m… https://t.co/bLsaee8y4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry, Sorry, Sorry, Sorry, Sorry (the Canadian version) #FailedBoardGames]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSportsInc @celtics @Rachel__Nichols @espn She doesn’t ask tough questions. But I also think of players reaction… https://t.co/FR9FycJxNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@korgankenzie Update: Target has nothing I want and everything I want at the same time, I still have nothing to wear and am hungry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoooMoooFive I agree.  However , I do think some of them want to more than the others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my people! Way to promote school spirit @Talons23!! I’m one proud President 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m forced to order more signs - that’s a good sign 👌 The Charleston Spring Real Estate Market is 🔥🔥🔥 #springmarket… https://t.co/LweIG5jOsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know Mei Mei’s offers cookie classes?  We make cookies, learn about ingredients and how they change our coo… https://t.co/vruW4FVmMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: I will be doing this through the entire month of March and April. Spread the word! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I’m at the bank trying to pick up the Chinese yuan I ordered but...they can’t figure out their system so I can… https://t.co/YuHSdscyWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veterans Way &amp; Ventura Blvd. #Camarillo with @NelsonBussRE https://t.co/gxDwiHvp45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandaEnsing That movie ruined my life and I’ve watched it like 20 times. I can’t and shan’t stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good design #foldable #shopping #bag #korea #Japan #exhibition #advertisement #gift #madeinchina export to many for… https://t.co/FKDdYMbZR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My age is 44 😘 To all my female friends from 40 years and up... most of us are going through the next phase of our… https://t.co/jDO3makNq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @TheDemCoalition Why would any of these men have their pic taken with her because they all Frequent he… https://t.co/047wvIbhcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let Go Of Your Past  | Life Changing Motivational Video Compilation https://t.co/UFnDM0Fky4 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethMacFarlane Started watching The Orville yesterday on Hulu. Complete binged it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muadglib @MatthewWolfff @lehimesa @TheSWPrincess @1Jedi_Rey @Clara_Resists @NatCookResists @JynErso_Patriot… https://t.co/30W4CjGXIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY 19th BIRTHDAY to my bestest friend in the whole world😍😍 i love you SO much and hope you have the absolute bes… https://t.co/vFbBbtTdb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Momma said I ain’t shit but when the cops picked me up I ain’t say shit 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caromarkey @BSC_Gym @TB12sports @HealthworksFit Such sad news 😔 Wherever you go next, you can use my pre-made prog… https://t.co/NvsrkJctpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmoyer3 @ALT_uscis Let’s all trick him into watching  #ActiveMeasures so he’ll start believing Putin hacked the 20… https://t.co/XXwzq30Cci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@20ThatGuy @RealJamesWoods Its getting close.  The same idiots who are saying it was terrible if Trump conspired wi… https://t.co/F7UAvbGs1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomekLaszok Hahahahaha I’m soooo happy to see you here honey. Thank you 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lengacherjaylen @swartz32_andrew I’m cracking up 🤣🤣🤣 on the bright side: that’s 30 slides of notes that you could… https://t.co/cE0RPfEXp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[$VYST beautiful day!  MACD on Daily is starting to turn up, we are right there at the Golden Cross.  Look out ABOVE- DO DD TONIGHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottaxe You and me both. Once I get over my bronchitis, my bootie is back in the gym 5 days a week. Turning 49 th… https://t.co/If1PWr7MXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @leahmcelrath You can’t be literally examining who likes her tweets? That’s ridiculous. Now, if there is a… https://t.co/6Vr2DxAaaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomSteyer @realDonaldTrump I would love to see you investigated.  I bet that you have many " financial crimes" in your portfolio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikiMarieDawn @ConcealedJess @MsKateNewsome @Naddy37 So sorry to hear.  I remember you telling me how fond you were of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darraghforpitt Pix on bio was taken by in Kiev, Ukraine by curator of a museum show in which my work was shown, bu… https://t.co/hMjSLb7BlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndrew_lawrence Of course he is. I truly hope hannity goes down with Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Flames live in NYC 3-2-19 #inflames #inflamesband #nyc #livemusic #swedishmetalband @ PlayStation Theater https://t.co/0TQADkFeDK]]></document></documents></author>