<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tnicole211 You should be used to this by now. Academy customer service did that for you 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im barely seeing this but it my heart happy love my dad 🥰 https://t.co/1Dmj8xXIzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fancy_spancy_22 @g_peeps24 @SenSanders Because of the cost of living driven up by CEOs so they can satisfy their b… https://t.co/yv7ztzPvFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One who is faithful in a very little is also faithful in much, and one who is dishonest in a very little is also d… https://t.co/hQ0vailhj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me!! When I went from cousin to PRIMA! 😂  @chalsivette76  @yaaaatusabes]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang funny. bathroom decor,  funny bathroom art, kids bathroom #hilarity #tee-hee #grin #cute https://t.co/WIBiWeURr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I feel the fantasy it is my reality..... 📸 yiannistoumazisofficial @ Santa Monica, California https://t.co/ajlhempWYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is outrageous. Events like this normalize this administration. By attending you are mocking all Americans.… https://t.co/ngoiGg9GV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Category is: Bowie in Rubber #dragevolution @ LUSH https://t.co/HlwKi7xXDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Saturday to get outside 🌞 #yeahthatgreenville #greenvillezoo🦍🦁🐆🐏 #helovedthegiraffes🦒🦒🦒 #lovethemjtfglb💙💜… https://t.co/6MoDGxJnzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t call urself a freak until you’ve shattered a wine glass over ya mans face while slapping him lmfao https://t.co/yVf8e5o2oR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m crying because @JeffreeStar is gonna be in sac and I had no clue! 😭😭😭😭😭😭 I would die to meet him but it’s to la… https://t.co/ou4gSpSNZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaddDena I am honored for your mention. You are someone we all admire for who you are as a friend and the healthca… https://t.co/etwrvvbZu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s okay to eat fish cuz they don’t have annnnny feeeelings 🎵 https://t.co/mipry1C2L2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day!  #SingleAndLovinIt #ValentinesDay @ Murfreesboro, Tennessee https://t.co/tkTQp65TTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[My second best scrapbook @ The University of Texas at Arlington https://t.co/ghord8PqJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory This once again proves the low IQ of many Republicans.  If he loved his family he would not have done it.… https://t.co/BlxwDTmW4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always Want Me Do Something  .But When Teresa  Want Something  Niggas Deaf Or Dont Care And Have Attitudes .Fuck Out My Face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir The friendliest, best  program airline! Awesome! #iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cousins!!! I’m so mad and so confused! But I’m glad we’re here ❤️ #unofficialReadPodcastfans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I never fully edited my age and for the past week in Twitter land, I've been 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I copied my friend @dhunt116 for my new Tweeter handle. Your royalty check is in the mail. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just binge #TheUmbrellaAcademy in under a day? Yes I did and now I wanna read the comics!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Experienced Staff Accountant" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types… https://t.co/V5jWNaFn47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selene_017 If the ever reunite, it’s fucking over with I will get meet and greet, EVERYTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Les familles sont souvent en détresse quand ils réalisent qu’ils vont perdre leur proche. Les rencontrer et souvent… https://t.co/gmc4xsXgkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joyride01 @SenyoraMaris Thank u miss joy sa new time slot!   #POPSSSS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a week now I have to go back to my normal schedule which means I’m separated from Evan and honestly could get… https://t.co/bYKmixqWRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@volrob33 @DollyVol Technically it was fun in our small town, too, but only because we didnt lose power and almost  everybody owned a 4x4.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark found the perfect shoot location for a couple spring segments @jwhittalTWN and I will be working on! Thanks… https://t.co/G3T20PkrYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but it irks me so much when i call someone and they text me like “you called?” If I wanted to text about… https://t.co/MpwR6ZaHv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendOfLisa1 she need to lock him up by himself so he can reflect how hard his head is 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeeAnneLocken hello beauty. Habenyou ever used "As nervous as a cat in a room full of rocking chairs"  Or  Happy a… https://t.co/g6dLmYxICB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Audrey Hepburn, always lovely. I much prefer current setting for diamond as opposed to the one she is wearing in ph… https://t.co/C2abdb3SKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love being in Olympia, extra love talking about ChildStrive. #supportearlylearning #eceap https://t.co/N21TaNCCq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Has she ever worked a real job for any length of time? Or has she surmounted a huge college debt she wa… https://t.co/6e3PmIs0Xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are your weekend box office numbers: 🎞📺📽  @WGME   https://t.co/BzYLBaVxQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@embraceFACTS @shepherd_kt @Lee_in_Iowa @immcouncil @AILANational @cliniclegal @P4HR Have they complained of anythi… https://t.co/lUYgAcP6xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canynhikr1 Curious- is that in NW Iowa?  I’m from Sibley in Osceola county &amp; have never heard of a convention center.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like 2008 @Timbo12107 and I can’t keep petting my own head. 💇🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/531HMr7YLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[So...last night T and I drove home from Raleigh forgetting to pick up my car from work. Tonight, we did it again… https://t.co/Go2hDbZX9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Let’s hope @AmyMcGrathKY topples his seat and brings some integrity back 🙏💪🏼🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi can't remember shit! In her mind, it's called #SelectiveTruth]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCREAMING HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY GIRL @mariah_carterr !! LOVE YOU FOREVER AND ALWAYS, SO GLAD WE ARE CLIMBING LIFE TO… https://t.co/OVD0OX8hp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I thought I was about to make it through without crying but BOY WAS I WRONG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this fucking real?!?! 8 days before my birthday? I sing this in the shower literally every day. I’m also so gull… https://t.co/q0aoB454Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sick af at school and when I went to the nurse they were trynna send me home but they had to call my dad for it… https://t.co/BLLsWnp4vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew McCabe says the Justice Department discussed removing Trump from office  https://t.co/MmOukLZ7FC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sleep im looking forward to once i get back home to my bed is the only thing keeping me going rn 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the fun and games my feet ended up looking like lil sausages... #Feet on 🔥 #Ankles looking like #Cankles 😑😩… https://t.co/wViHNA7S5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz says billions in assets tied to 'El Chapo' should fund the border wall https://t.co/dOeDEQdArM via… https://t.co/QrasYOAH1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[**** jaw dropping. I don’t know what it is but I friggin love/obsessed with this palette and it ain’t a prestige br… https://t.co/goaAQWoCjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the seniors represented National Louis University as well! @NLU_Wheeling  @RojasWHSAVID @WheelingHS_AVID https://t.co/pST1bIFoVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherneyAmharaTV He’s on the show? Now K have to watch, lol I love him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC, A magical place you haven't been to before--or do you remember?https://t.co/YQDAZUCuz4 https://t.co/DBeRqYlHRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wtffiles @heckyessica No.  The PAC will reimburse her for 20 because socialism😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyalFamily @TheDukeOfYork Talk about blessed HRH you are 59 and you have both of your parents in good health to c… https://t.co/NlZE9cKyEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentfaiyaz soooooo I think you should do a show in SD. Please and thanks ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attended #schittscreekupcloseandpersonal as Stevie Budds last night with my bud camalittle in Boston.  LOVED that j… https://t.co/UqqeUTbcLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheriff’s deputy just told us the suspect is on the ground with an officer on top of him @wncn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnCamAudiences In line for American Ninja Warrior!! Can't wait for this awesome experience!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendrickdk @SenSchumer I don’t really know what the problem is because I’m not privy to that information, all I do… https://t.co/ybxT7p2Kdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning to everyone except me - the girl who just accidentally shaved off her scab in the shower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_moanner It hurts to watch Kelsey talk with her awkward smile lmao I’m so mean but really they could’ve picked mor… https://t.co/LFn9zNhngl]]></document><document><![CDATA[three knee deep playing s&amp;f is so cool. i am so glad they’ve seem to become the go-to “band from florida”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winning the Fight for Financial Freedom - 5 Biblical points - Keep Good Records, Plan Your Spending... want more? C… https://t.co/bytJ6sxjRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzRivers90 @IjoeRanger They are.  Millions of women go on dates with strangers around the world with the expecta… https://t.co/O5pQmIYS89]]></document><document><![CDATA[The card I get in the mail when Madison finally goes to prison for tax fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is on their way to Admitted Students Day? We’re axe-cited to meet you!! #GetAxeCited #Future49ers #UNCC23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrendaRicards Ok yes, that's what I was saying too except meaner. 😂 This is a much  better approach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Last night at the Oscars would have been a good place to have picked up most up your child moleste… https://t.co/iZn5KUkub9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raniwasacyborg @Andr6wMale So do the wedding as the reception and just not feed anyone? My wedding was kinda like… https://t.co/ueYqXbxsVC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jim_hollifield @Never2Late2 @realDonaldTrump He spent he entire campaign doing all he could to lose and his idiot… https://t.co/Lk2U94OmYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle As usual, Joe Biden has no backbone, will try to govern based on opinion and lease resistance. We ne… https://t.co/VimSPlRhzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost let my most territorial dog loose because I thought there was a burglar 😂😂 I feel so stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms. Glover is teaching today! #sherocks @ctetigers #gettingherCDA https://t.co/fkEzd4Jgdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick_rica @ClockworkHamma @laurieee2 @flower525 @DonnaFins @SteveDunfee @bethreamer @mattfoster2010 @jarackas… https://t.co/6e1OmLtUfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go KM wrestling team!  Academic Gold!  Getting it down both on and off the mat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollyisntdumb i agree with this (if youre referring to captain marvel) but i guess its one step in the right direc… https://t.co/hMdBw8RXVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago police officer shot   Preliminary information:   Police were executing a warrant at 2738 W. Potomac. An off… https://t.co/X7Pky8yG9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nukegirl82 @secupp THAT! What you just said, right there... https://t.co/9ItFViQVya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Personalized learning: flexible, empowering, tailored, mastery-based #schoologyCONNECT @Schoology @Doc_Kristine… https://t.co/PlefSBijJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 College Football Camps across the nation.   (Per: @Coach1Tyme)  Camps: https://t.co/EWNvR0RyLA https://t.co/gc1AT9RojQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @Grubhub person said “You must really like @tacobell” as they delivered it for the X time this month.  Listen, I… https://t.co/YHBDYYS1BS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrellanaValarie They have it there. Both sound good, my mouth is watering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s snowing in #Baltimore and it’s sticking! #BeOnWJZ @wjz https://t.co/DFEKd5DrsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E3dmond @gypsynurse30 @nosleeptilbed @robrousseau @IvankaTrump Or less.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet is for you punk losers almost killing my son last Friday and I have no shame letting the HPD know who it… https://t.co/EnaVGsg7Kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmon4ever @SuperEliteTexan I'm saying stop posting her on my page!! I don't want her hashtaging I don't want her a… https://t.co/cR8ycVwvTv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for having me! I’m forever in awe of the great work being done by BE THE ONE. Such an inspiring group of stu… https://t.co/hEyIXYP1V7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aeswds this nigga really ditching me and the boys for his new friend cube man. The fuck bro https://t.co/54YYoabxfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jodyvance @PhilipRucker This is what con men do. It’s always a shell game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKCharnley Indiana Jones and the Temple Of Doom https://t.co/2dkMSnbmh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carl_arredondo @WWLTV Love you Carl..my family and I will definitely miss you and we will keep you in our prayers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow, sleet and freezing rain yesterday as we celebrated life and those who stand tall amidst the challenge of Canc… https://t.co/kOEqafD6n4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy crafternoon everyone! Sitting in the sun and playing with sequins! #sparkly #cactus #vacation #craft @ Gilber… https://t.co/9N4eVd3KqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Guardian contacted both Kushner and Leviev for comment, but they did not immediately respond.  The pursuit of P… https://t.co/phaB2rp6SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmilingJackRoss I am not talking about existing within the current system. I am pointing out how fragile that system is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation @PascoSheriff @PascoSheriff we will certainly miss the great department on @OfficialLivePD hope you come back #lovepasco]]></document><document><![CDATA[Try to do something positive everyday , you never know whose life you might impact.]]></document></documents></author>