<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Did a work thing today #WreckEm #TexasTech #texasTechBasketball @ United Supermarkets Arena https://t.co/JFdMKx8L1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @LaurenOfThornes, @JNovz , and @Discombobul8te7 Thank you for inviting me into your communities through Courtney… https://t.co/3v7z6KdUHI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lee: "If they truly do what they say they're going to do -- to go out and listen to the experts -- then they will h… https://t.co/ofx7bTnNlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depends on the situation tbh. If I’m chillin then cold but if I just got done doing something then room temp so I c… https://t.co/4Zm97g8YDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomPerez You idiot. You didn’t act upon the “facts.” You acted on a false narrative.  You are an embarrassment!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPRverlee See @greeleyschools thought ahead on this one. Spring Break started today. https://t.co/rCe4vZXj4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulianMack105 Me reading this tweet notification on my iPhone. https://t.co/uhWI7bQIcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allison_fuisz @CanGeoEdu @_Sara_Black @XelaEpop @MAEEChaput @OAGEEOntarioGeo @littlephz Looks really frozen!  I wa… https://t.co/jXzE7cn3FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christinafriel_ I have to ask does this make finding gloves that for correctly hard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefereeHalsey Totally agree. I’ve sat through a lot of ref training and that was not a handball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful to join 29 organizations working to enable new immigrants for success at the Council of Newcomer Organiza… https://t.co/c8pUNYKlsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Egotistical billionaire rulers, am I right https://t.co/IvwF4PT8Gb @dezeen]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AshWednesday service in the sanctuary tonight. @ Westminster Presbyterian Church https://t.co/pDRRyzcsNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkempcpa He is not going to miss Presidents’ Day weekend down here 🌴 though weather sucked today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @realDonaldTrump I will lay 100-to-1 odds that this isn’t going to be a pro bono case.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homemade bacon. Thank you Dale Tabbert, very delicious!  . . #bacon #baconmakeseverythingbetter… https://t.co/fhWUGtADQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigRed_STL Despite a Browns fan Charley Johnson one of my favorites. Close attachment to both football and baseball Cardinals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The area could have a few matchups in the quarterfinals today. Which one looks the most intriguing if they happen. @Huskermat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC is an absolutely obtuse individual . She needs to be out just like @SenSanders . Career politians that take el… https://t.co/GKoYzC4Ofk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtamorse7 @680TheFan @Grand_Golf @MizunoGolfNA Did not see Kimbrel at Grand Cypress, but I was looking...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Instead of reparations, how about a Class action lawsuit and let’s see how the supreme court rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjz1600 @PeterETyrrell @IlhanMN Support our sister https://t.co/WtPyI6xZg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliaponders Is this why people think I'm a smart ass https://t.co/2b7j2j0x7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Education4Libs @dogfighter31 @JussieSmollett is the perfect example of a person being their own enemy he is unbeli… https://t.co/ol1CdNZ6k1]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/6/19 #TodaysOracle #ElBaile 😉 #LoteriaDeLaMuerte 💖 #DanceYourAssOff https://t.co/9YYUN8ZZJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So tough watching @HailStateWBK with @CoachVic_MSU, Johnnie Harris, Lashes.....even Mary Ann Baker ....still consid… https://t.co/qtT4XxkKFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shuaros There’s a chabura on the upper west side that learns and tries to live his teachings. DM for deets]]></document><document><![CDATA[14:17 1st: Hayden Hintemeyer fires a backhand that chases Kaufman and it’s 3-0 TJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j3effcSTP @happifydesign @danademaster @awillis @MikeBikeMason @joshnorthsouth @AarneClimate A $0.20 hike is not e… https://t.co/8sQomMugMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBorstein I love you in The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel and have been a fan of yours since Mad TV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir What about the three-gate changes? The $30 bag charge? And, the worst overall customer service experience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapnKeto It’s about the same as here; the only exception is in the summer where it is much hotter.  Unfortunately… https://t.co/Hd4ZiOq9HX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kanakagirlie2 But I am a people person I love everyone as long as we all treat each other with respect and kindness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crystameekins @murph_ii Definitely Dom Bc I’m not a four roses guy! Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CouchmenDBC @TheBlueStars @laterhayter @rockon_stone @scvanguard @CarolinaCrown @Bluecoats @TheCadets @MusicCityDC… https://t.co/flyYuXv2TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @AOC @RepAOC signs tell the truth. It is the prologue to a sad destructive epilogue. Nothing u can say or magi… https://t.co/rtHTub8Xow]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/0lsJC2DhHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its 4am and i’ve decided to name my hedgie pinecone finally its lame but i like it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning views from this 11th floor SW corner 2bed/2bth Regents Park home!$524,900 Open House Saturday2-4#newportre… https://t.co/OuzD554Gm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t have a titty in my mouth in the next 2 hours and 53 minutes I might burn down a hallmark store]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOK #KILLJOYS  #TV #PILOT #SCRIPT - #AaronAshmore - #LukeMacFarlane - #HannahJohnKamen on #Ebay   https://t.co/PDb9NmTrN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stickNblades @gmc_mccarthy @TheMLSchoonover @NHL I looked at the rules for the a penalty shot and nothing says if… https://t.co/09bykVu7lZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Gecko Juice by @Rhinegeist @ MyZoomZoom — https://t.co/JKDWQDulsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisw_14 Drew asked me if I wanted to go, but I haven’t been feeling right. I plan to go to one soon. Dudes eating.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwellman21 @SamsonEffect @Underculture1 @AOC Have you heard of triage? It’s where the Canadian government decides if you’re worthy to live]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odon, Indiana tonight at the community center. Coming in strong. Ready to tear the roof off the center. Odon isnt g… https://t.co/p0x5DEd5nL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lightening rod of lights. LA approaching dusk, cloudy March evening with light spots of rain. #losangeles… https://t.co/MxIOYzozhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bloody Joe Thorton gets the Hattrick versus old team the @Bruins goes up 5 to 4 in the third with great emotion cou… https://t.co/MKuv4D0dRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀CLASS B1 FINAL | #1 @BHSScores vs #2 Midlakes - @SecVGBasketball   Midlakes 10 - Batavia 6 - | 3:33 1Q  • Midlakes… https://t.co/qiS9xr5WBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshgroban @sesamestreet This role fits you extremely well! Spreading joy and making kids happy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump Southern border: 1,954 miles Existing barrier: 654 miles As of January,  0 miles o… https://t.co/giQg6QAnYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BestBuy @nxtom I wonder if @BestBuyCanada is ready to board the hype train too??]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hollywood Walk of Fame in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/DVQF9Gsfz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Norman_Locke Not me.. went from a blue collar job great money, to getting injured, forced into white collar work w… https://t.co/AoXECre6tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got to see jeff Dunham amazing show🤩🤩🤩🤩 @ Canadian Tire Centre https://t.co/Mcp6PUedI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[today i heard someone refer to egg yolks as “egg yellows”  me: https://t.co/f5mPwkElsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant decide if I should go to an adult establishment and have adult potent beverages or stay home and play video ga… https://t.co/WIH4cEPlZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@25yearsofvtm Liege, lord and lackey: it got me to look at backgrounds and institutions in a different light. Helped me be less basic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turbotax says they would give me a code and they said to dm them lol 1 day later they still don’t reply 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's meal! - Homemade Gluten Free Lasagna - Baked Kale - Roasted Green Beans - Homemade Garlic Rolls - Corn on… https://t.co/XQPDgmBx48]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bluejays have yet to make it official but Clay Buchholz has arrived and has a locker set up with his name plate on… https://t.co/8nII1kwzkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rusty_pharris @MSNBC I made a throw away comment that was obviously meant to be funny, and you told me not to vote… https://t.co/Hc9UixPQXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baetog_ Can they just fuze goyf and guide. Hmmmm what to call it .......]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the guy that says he's got all the evidence. He's never shown anybody any evidence. Then he said that Moell… https://t.co/b3DYCs3GqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loneliness has been my worst enemy these past couple years but I made it this far so that means something]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @charliekirk11 and @DonaldJTrumpJr (who retweeted, and thus endorsed, this idiocy):  The hearing was reschedul… https://t.co/nQN6j6ezWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladybugspicnic Carling is nearly 30 KMs of road that I thankfully manage to avoid on #ottbike. It doesn’t matter w… https://t.co/Z9cOvDmv1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorted digraphs with one of my students today and he got stuck on “throne” (he kept wanting to put it with Ch for c… https://t.co/qCPPYIjCbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmm this guy isn’t far from having the entire SEC covered. #CantLose #RollDawgGatorCocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said hum inside it. Gosh y’all be tryna appropriate black culture &amp; don’t even know the words. https://t.co/Zxk1fYDcHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brian31769 @dbongino @realDonaldTrump I’m still waiting... How did they collude ? So ridiculous... the whole thing… https://t.co/S4EHFn2vZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Profs are really making us buy 100$ books only to assign us 20 pages of readings :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xmarkx93 @merri_kushman @zedsdead @ZedsDeadFamily That’s good fucking ink]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump No he was not he was hiding in some College like Yale or Harvard when Vietnam was g… https://t.co/qhextmnWbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[whew stan twitter is WILD tonight…a whole ass murder mystery being investigated on the TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE OWNER AND INCORPORATION ARE LEGALLY MARRIED WITH LAW AND CONSTITUTION. PRETTY NICE. TH… https://t.co/BivUXWBqes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRaiderSports @SeanMcNeil22 Sean come join the good guys and be a part of #4:1!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your feeling sad, stop and take a deep breath and breath and start to think in your mind everything will be okay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An amazing story about really awesome people, in 4 acts. https://t.co/ViWqCpjnOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cboehm @fitzcamel Normal people don’t all understand in the news biz there are entirely different people than thos… https://t.co/b098W5dCOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sammysgranny @djrothkopf Yes, yes we are. We've faced challenges to our democracy in the past (Civil War and the G… https://t.co/pOZXRUg5KL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradrobinson8 @HawksBearsCubs I missed that part. Either way I don’t feel like Chicago media has slanted this one… https://t.co/u98ceLuUo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo Great reverence Donald Trump..yours truly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshualaporte @TugboatMcPuppy Your hubs gotta get with the drivin-around-massholes program! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bendiciones para mí hija adorada en West Side, New York https://t.co/n2TebkPkgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrockBJones I second the motion... wait, that didn’t come out right...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the @AmericaEast men's basketball match-ups are set: 8. @BlackBearsMBB at 1. @UVMmbb ... 7. @BinghamtonMBB… https://t.co/8G4V1GpAgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loganboomie @teemaction @liloozdeehurt @Whataburger @clandon95 @suga_mamta @snickerhorse @aaliyahyah_ @zosco18… https://t.co/aSeuBXH9KP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamline adds another and the Norse are held scoreless in their half. Norse trail 2-1 after 3 innings]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a good night with @Paulinaajim at my favorite hangout @ Khartoum https://t.co/K7cPjpsILG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final performance of Bye Bye Birdie.  Are you here?  I am! (@ Sunnyvale Community Center Theatre in Sunnyvale, CA w… https://t.co/ll7Smrr29m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFTompkins His classmates created amazing space-saving furniture but he smoked weed through class and only came up… https://t.co/ljxVRGhaM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Megs_ISU @KDahlsten @mdahlsten Why isn't it surprising that you enjoy sneaky wine-chugging?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder why? 🤔  “He doesn't have a birth certificate, or if he does, there's something on that certificate that is… https://t.co/GSxmzuE1ZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parkeg1 @marcddaffner @AOC Half the people in @AOC’s area pay no taxes, live in shambles, crime, drugs, and total… https://t.co/HWNdiqqoEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Tavares might wanna do himself a favor and miss the team plane. “Welcomed back” my ass pal. Hope u packed ur pjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is good in Fort Lauderdale. @ Fort Lauderdale Beach https://t.co/QKm1nR1ib3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetanalea Happy Birthday, love! I hope it’s amazing! Enjoy your special day! Much love! And to many, many more!!! #TurnUp 🎂🍰🍾🥂🍹🍷🥃🍺🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oregon_girl3 @daniellec7699 @JoeBiden @CynthiaNixon Oh, and Go Dawgs! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DzDownUnder @toddmonroe6 @ckolacia @kc10sooner @tarheelmark @PatrickKiser1 @NorahODonnell @ScottPelley @60Minutes… https://t.co/Ivdy8NafF6]]></document></documents></author>