<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@burtdesigns @ Omni Hotel at The Battery Atlanta https://t.co/tirXvHwIFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 out of 10 probably have bruises and a concussion but that was FUN @_bluntsnblondes @Subtronics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I'm baaack! Knocked off for 11 hours and 57 mins. One tweet asked what message I would send to trump. The m… https://t.co/b9CK1r14vD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Google male or female?  Female, because it doesn't let you finish a sentence before making a suggestion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMatlow And hipsters can also clean their sidewalk if they can afford 1,5M homes then shovel and salt their fri… https://t.co/XfjalRC7fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooo they use to really throw Steve Austin beers in the middle of matches and he would really catch em 🤣😂🤣 you ev… https://t.co/z8gXeFO07G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Helenhs @Kris_Sacrebleu It’s disgusting that so many people have fake cheese at the ready. Also, why is this even a thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still stuck on the fact that someone who SHOT THE PRESIDENT is out of jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya’ll really out here trying to reduce the wages for 16-22 year olds? https://t.co/gp6QLRC4zC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @itmediasentinel @FoxNews @Nestle @DuluthTradingCo @Disney @OfficeMax @officedepot @UniversalPics… https://t.co/VVcOxahwhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[These guys were super cool to talk to..  ##America##Marines https://t.co/Bp8XRTMDGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I basically had a 1 hour and a half class about empathy and civility at @LudiaGames  I really love that they… https://t.co/363MJY7ffM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@analuciafavela @SofiaOrtizS No neta si que coraje a nadie le da risa más que a ti loser]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZebulonKing @Dave_Eby Well done Zeb and everyone who worked on this. Allowing SLAPPs hurt a lot of people in our c… https://t.co/E2lqP2pwKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so glad I have my little cousin with me rn, it’s keeping me together tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que lastima General. La solución es aceptar que la causa raíz de problema está en el sistema y no en las personas.… https://t.co/c9DqSPIoDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bachelorette weekend was a winter wonderland 🐱 . . . . . #wisconsin #lake #country #winter #white #meowied… https://t.co/L7mCrSvEve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delete this shit. U trippin. U here for a reason. Life hard but u strong Sissy. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM GLAD SOMEONE IS OUT HERE ASKING THE REAL QUESTIONS! ITS BEEN 17 YEARS, THAT BOY STILL AINT COME DOWN FOR DINNER!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched the live feed.  Hats off to @hamzgiron and @NewQNSDemocrats for hosting an informative discussion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanukCrazy Oh that was heart breaking! That is a shame I love horses 🐴 and that was wrong it was just a baby!!😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DenofGeekUS @americangodsus @AmGodsRoom @AmericanGodsPod @American_GodsUK @MrRickyWhittle @neilhimself… https://t.co/FnuKkfgYz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Maine Emergency Management Agency says a colder and snowier than average winter combined with a deep snowpack p… https://t.co/Oo0IT2b80u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you were not on the logic puzzle team in ellementary school and it really shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAY 4: I have accepted a challenge from @jkeister to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews. Ea… https://t.co/nXvebyS4jR]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you choose to see the good in others you end up finding the good in yourself. Happy Sunday ❤😊 https://t.co/LWZyxAZ3fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A word of warning: we expect offensive language in Michael Cohen’s testimony,” says @NPR correspondent. — new historic quote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pray my child loves volleyball bc it’s the only sport I loved with all my heart and I sucked too much to keep goi… https://t.co/xgoUszSbJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[A *much* better explanation of public law issues in SNC Lavalin case than the one I tried to give you… https://t.co/6x3531o48G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demiurge_33 @MusingsOfDeimos @counterchekist @SpeakerPelosi Just got the popcorn...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My dreams and goals are coming into reality how they will get done is NOT my business it's God’s business”.  -… https://t.co/Vh6Z0nIq5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#POstables @TarpeoDesiree @feebs1907 @NydiaRaquel25 @Glenda68336051 @j9e9n9n9 @Laulauthelau @RobinACollier1 @kgvm… https://t.co/dGUkn1YuuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudakevychFCPS This is exactly what I’m seeing in K-2 classrooms at Butterfly Ridge!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when I seen posts like “getting rid of my dog because my s/o doesn’t like him” when I dead ass would look at… https://t.co/KeANiUNAcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Have followed you for awhile without the expectation of a follow back.  And Hillary was right about it all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voilà un très petit format qui chatouille en masse en arrière des molaires. - Drinking  The Bramble by… https://t.co/s110LBDSTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deathpigeon @ellle_em @2020Bernard No, but we can hound them until they improve or we convince enough people to vo… https://t.co/6uWh46Gwcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessB368 @ArianaGrande she has been it’s been on her story for a few weeks now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_mikawa_ I wish there was an unlike button like there is on Facebook here]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s time for a new phone because my bill for 3 phones is more than a car payment🙃 bye bye sprint]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at TD Bank US? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and informa… https://t.co/e9eqWqjieP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes exactly! I have gone through some things! I have survived and I'm here to tell you it gets better. God is the k… https://t.co/cf3WUTHfnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also pretending my wedding diet doesnt exist for the next 12 hours because mama needs her some Busch light tonight. 🍻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@octobella69 @SUBWAY @Eat24 What happened to "the customer is always right?" 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankBigelowCA Please help #California lead the way Co-Sponsor and help pass #AB388 and make a one time $10 millio… https://t.co/bTHQAv7qA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Jose City Council passed the #Digital Inclusion Fund, a public-private #partnership initiative which brings… https://t.co/5tHNLKV6Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHICH ONE IS YOUR FAVOURITE???? . #banglez #wemakejewelry #designerjewelry #jewellery #madeincanada #preciousstones… https://t.co/rt0Zj3qXBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm going to sue for them using my dog's picture without permission. (JK, I totally bought it.) https://t.co/KTLJbptS60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to support this Cambodian-American film! A beautiful story that covered 3 decades and explored love, music,… https://t.co/3BSthkLgB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper have so much chemistry I feel like I shouldn’t be watching them.  😮#Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Relationships turn around lives” @nytdavidbrooks #SXSWEDU #SXSWEDU2019 #txed #mondaythoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are you seriously trying to take on women? Because if you are you are by far the most stupid man i… https://t.co/IahfLaa39h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanMillerMath @ArchNY_Schools @BXNEEBSchools @MurthaEileen @Sara_Shea72 @oshea_marie Thanks @SusanMillerMath - l… https://t.co/dG4GBtWrO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_hdogg What’s the scoop on the Express this weekend? Who they playing and when? #1Fan #BeenThereSinceDay1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving it 🥰 @tristanrogers and @MauriceBenard are killing it love watching them working together Sonny has to work… https://t.co/4lsKVbaPdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your next Tesla, GM, Toyota - that’s 52k lbs rolled automotive steel I’m standing by w/ Keith Hoey @burlingtoncofc… https://t.co/To2QUo3WPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to stop making fun of this guy I just wanna hug him and kiss him on his forehead why are y’all so mean.… https://t.co/V1gwVpFPj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cirrus1701 @realBradStaggs @DocThompsonShow @TheCartelMatt Techno priest!! https://t.co/LRv3cB3oYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@velljones_4 Ion know why y’all think I would lie about some videos 🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Mininno #125 match Drexel VS Cal Baptist Saturday, February 16, 2019 https://t.co/OWwCnpXPWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This afternoon was the first rehearsal of #JPEPantherSingers and #JPEToneDef together!!  We had a great day!… https://t.co/HaSwR9hBb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to shut the laptop and let God speak. #life #entrepreneurlife #prayfirstthendecide #palmsup 💙🙏🏻🌟💙🙏🏻🌟💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow Dereliction of duty. You didn’t mention One WORD of McConnell refusing the release of information about Rus… https://t.co/804iDe2wYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of him 😭❤️ he’s going to be a great surgeon 👨‍⚕️ https://t.co/p7bOqWVUQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If he is speaking I will be boycotting. Fireworks or not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillWeirCNN Oh Bill, I am truly so sorry for your loss and the loss to many.  Sending you sincere blessings and to… https://t.co/VrY55srbzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Wow it takes a very strong person to blow the whistle in this situation I appreciate your service to… https://t.co/2CnnI7GKf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PrinceLiamPayne Is A Gentleman For Sticking Up For @KylieJenner !!! I Don't Understand Why Haters Would Bully Such… https://t.co/DzkR1xHxma]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m lucky   Pics by Nancy Crampton @ 92nd Street Y https://t.co/H9k3wE48ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another VT ski trip done!!! So much fun with so many people making so many memories!!! #vermont #vermontskiing… https://t.co/66OVFd4SAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s more on the new pharmacy in #Taftville #Norwich #NutmegPharmacies https://t.co/KkpeKPKsqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[All love &amp; truth here❤   I Am Classic Grooming @ Cafe Mochi https://t.co/B97XbBcRjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rduffy756 Since you yourself turned it political claiming we don’t need a wall. We do need a wall and we do need o… https://t.co/7wKsXMO2JM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Darling Family - Jesus Saves  #NowPlaying on  Final Fight Bible Radio ,  https://t.co/cQASaMMxWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@johnpavlovitz An opportunity for balance in the midst of this terror, lies within this piece.]]></document><document><![CDATA[live your happily ever after, even if it’s not the one you originally created. you’re allowed to change lanes. draw… https://t.co/u96vNZxY5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best day of the year. Happy Mardi Gras, y’all! 💜💚💛 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/N4JYKYs45f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing movie. Great acting. Important story. Wish I'd put up my prediction! https://t.co/mZhdbqr1Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MossbraeHotel You are only 4 hours from Central Oregon.  My Bachelor is in Bend. 35 minutes from me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer     Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gift… https://t.co/urtzHM5DZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel good about Bernie’s strong support of Omar. It was better than it would have been last time. Cuz he’s made h… https://t.co/NcMArJo4Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[is anyone else like not playing this bc i can't keep up so i'll watch y'all succeed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory @lovepeoplejo Of course. Coats isn’t a brown nose trump shill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece by @Popehat . He knows of what he speaks. I highly recommend reading it.    https://t.co/5sWCKrAahU]]></document><document><![CDATA[To EVERYONE who voted for Trump! Coming from someone who is disabled, DOES THIS MAKE YOU PROUD??!! 🗽🇺🇸🗽🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@domenicdefalcoo Nothing tastes sweeter than Hershey chocolate. Congrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Bellas when you think you have no time to keep up a beauty routine, try these simple tips that will g… https://t.co/66JlE3v2sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wroetoshaw @MorgzHudson I saw that on YouTube the pause Challenge it was soooooooo funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OyyyeeeCorito86 Hooligans! 😂😂😂  That's why I'm not crazy about the upper level or even suites. I love being down where all the crazy is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys with dropped trucks are annoying asf when they are trying to show off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mephistolesnc When she said but people get to take their babies. https://t.co/rgXc78UkxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freeme0215 @KW70099382 @PMCaminero @agamanimukherj1 Oh wow I want it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apologygrrrl mortaaa se bem q tds as nossas tias sao bolsominion ne, menos sua tia nice ORGULHO DESSA MULHER]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had mine a little over 6 months and I agree. It’s a dream machine. #teslamodel3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya tengo sueñito!!!!😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴!!! Mis amigos #Twitteros# sueñen con los 👼👼👼👼👼 👼👼 😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@POTUS at National Association of AG: “Today we are joined together to reaffirm and strengthen the vital partnersh… https://t.co/Qk3Y271V4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clegleiter Our district uses Apptegy Thrillshare which allows you to post on your district website, Facebook and T… https://t.co/ouNwdyvfuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you emma!! love you so much and so glad we got so close💓 thanks for all the homework in pre calc, u da best!… https://t.co/ZV66arQmbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovEvers Are you nuts? Give license to people living here illegally?? Here's my plan. Soon as they apply for a lic… https://t.co/qRVet75NUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 7507 La Paz Boulevard # 207 #BocaRaton #FL  #realestate https://t.co/mWo7s33pr2]]></document></documents></author>