<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@shaneisland Deleted out of shame... inclusion riders are far more important than Winona riders]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews Sort of like a horse . . . going through life with blinders on !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badflower @BadflowerFam @BadflowerJoey I really am happy that you like it. It's your words, but they're written on my heart. 😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just found out today that every Louisiana Lawyer character I’ve ever done on stage is in fact a spot-on impressio… https://t.co/EBBF4hTaD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Voorhees Township, New Jersey https://t.co/KmzgIEA4L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindz_berry Shhhh, of course, I'll happily go again... https://t.co/5QYatdus4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself He bestest comic/fantasy/fiction ( Allan Moore, George R R Martin ) creators have beards. Sometimes the grislier the better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time has come. It's #DAYTONA500 Media Day. I'll be providing coverage here and on @MotorsportsTrib throughout the day from Daytona.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You as always @cavanfitzgerald and @pepakoren @sjbarracuda #SJBarracuda #SJSharks https://t.co/sSI3OmWTFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Garcia @JakeGarcia14 far side! Throwing darts! https://t.co/RUewhLc0Ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most likely the drop from knee height. Dropped it from shoulder height for 40 years. Old habits are hard to break.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 And are now trying to institute those same failed policies in their newly adopted states by propping… https://t.co/jC1kW3nFc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m running for Selectman ( @VoteJustinEvans ) and if you want to run for office in Whitman this is the first step.… https://t.co/nRAqdTOGH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erossin48 @shannonrwatts A lot comes from Mexico and can't get across the border because of trump's tariffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I do apologize in advance if the amount of streams between now and PAX East drop significantly. I wanna be able… https://t.co/KvRimBdZmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackGlattacker nailed it and is your 2019 Mr. DHS! #prouddad https://t.co/AbxOS0trHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost We believe this proudly you baby killing trash. https://t.co/9sLAyk3QWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Tobin Drive anywhere in our great city and not spot 20 to 50 Tesla's... They use the roads every bit as much… https://t.co/RIfaFj8lKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralN42 @TwitterMoments @mehdirhasan U didnt see how USA began on ANY NEWS 3/5.  I got fake news. Most valuable… https://t.co/1ZevlyyQcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never seen it be this slow and we still have half a month to go before it gets busy]]></document><document><![CDATA[To write the rules and then know them is entirely different from applying them on a day to day basis on our tours. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Table Time in the $50,000 GTD $150 With $100 Rebuys  https://t.co/35lx2RZkeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buccigross any tracking updates on order #8203? Website hasn’t updated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuggets are 39-18, which is probably they’re best 57 games in a while, 8-2 in their last 10 games, 25-4 at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words Could Never Describe Nor Express My Overjoyment Of Seeing How Much My Beloved Lady Gaga Shined The Past Coupl… https://t.co/45vqM9W18u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appointment + shopping + work tomorrow.   Night. https://t.co/i1YBCSdPQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is some guy with a lanyard retrieving every foul ball fans get, even kids.  What kind of cheap shit is this?  #GoBeavs]]></document><document><![CDATA[alexisrael’s self portraits at his studio @ Mid-City, Los Angeles https://t.co/0xKodCqYlQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdamby23 I am 100% open to cutting Eli. I just think if he’s going to stay (which he probably is) he might as well… https://t.co/odWHX7qT4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody keep saying Cardi verse on thottiana is trash when the original rapper verse is what? Okay then. https://t.co/dPF6AzRJ9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Party 🎉 Tonight elevate with Me 3/7 @Letzgitit at #apexsocialclub Nightclub Lets Git It inside #palms Thursday Marc… https://t.co/YBFBJV06Lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Billie Kay is literally the entire WWE Universe in the way she’s talking to Sam Roberts   #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyKingSpitfire I think this is something you might enjoy. Uncle Ruckus Lives! And by hearing this radio interview… https://t.co/BAt8pWg2O9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just two miles from home and... well... those #DMV potholes.   You can probably guess the rest of the story from th… https://t.co/A4IMuuxpBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harajuku333 Hundreds of joke routines over the years, Sarcasm is tricky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlisidro @realDonaldTrump @AmbJohnBolton Nadie en este país, a excepción de .@Diego_Arria, conoce mejor a los am… https://t.co/KhHxVy21gE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanPOmaha @washingtonpost If my name was mentioned in a $250 million lawsuit complaint as many times as… https://t.co/9YJ3oGX4Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyschmade @szyzy Whoa that’s intense. Nothing was nearly that organized at our fellowship when I was that age. Of… https://t.co/cKdYTFcsA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have bought zero #corn today, with no phone calls.    Been there, done that prices still.    decreasing length,… https://t.co/37BkSjb6No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarleyKeiner @bwc When life hands you lemons (i.e. Air France cuisine)...]]></document><document><![CDATA[...example: algorithms that get people upset = more engagement/activity, but at what cost to humanity? Tribalism. D… https://t.co/Mv7PC0Rma7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston's best kept secret. The YWCA-hotel140, National registered building, convenient to all Copley Square has to… https://t.co/Ym96Ez9uGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can my #furryfandom friends and furries community to help #Shallow to go no. 1 on #BillboardHot100 ? We need their… https://t.co/EaBLHzC6Rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spent an hour and a half going HAM on this driveway...and the walkway...and the sidewalk...and the curb...and… https://t.co/xKs0d8RYtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suddenly stan Kacey’s music, surprisingly I’m impressed how she convey a story in her song]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1stBratt We aren't a UNITED STATES. ....We are a DIVIDED STATES OF AMERICA ! It's hard to find anything that bring… https://t.co/f8QuVKmkDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CameronDayton For me, it’ll always be the Chippendales skit w/Patrick Swayze (another gone way too soon). ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puzzleshifter Still, I think encouraging the discussion so the general public becomes familiar with the idea and d… https://t.co/tmLqwQPtm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No smoke detector in the history of time has ever started chirping for a new battery during non-sleep hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbtabhan @politvidchannel As a teenager during the 80s I worked at a grocery store and we were explicitly trained… https://t.co/R3CZcc2Hmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So 4/5 were angry/serious/straight face, but 100%happy and goofy!! We cook at 1:15 tomorrow!! #prostartkansas… https://t.co/pJQ4h8JVyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[this movie is otherwise pretty nice so far. first movie i've seen in ages where i don't want to kick Jeremy Renner's ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal background checks: Something everyone should support, but, we all know that this guy is a roadblock.  Yes… https://t.co/vqmR7G2Tv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Edurodriguezg Buenos días, saludos cordiales Eduardo, siento mucha tristeza por lo ocurrido ayer, al final el bien… https://t.co/B6PoJbOWLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bien maciza cantando canciones en inglés y lm, aaaaah pero a la hora de pedir comida, o ir al súper, o algo aquí, m… https://t.co/9ResDxGRP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[61st Grammy Awards at the Staples Centre February 2019. #grammys2019  #staplescenter @ JW Marriott Los Angeles L.A.… https://t.co/G9fnKhz9nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Tim’s celebration of life was great. Definitely gonna miss this big guy but thankful for all the memories I hav… https://t.co/YpGCfnpJvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loather And because there's 20% less meth in the customer base, compared to the Skeezy Vons on Main Street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNEE Que Cuba ratona los jóvenes cubanos que obligan a ir a Venezuela  que no quieren a ir pero  Son obligado par… https://t.co/iOmq7vw0qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t see Georgia once. Auburn had the most of anyone. Seems about right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frongbak That I’m unsure of. But for a 28th round pick I’ll take a chance as a 7th or 8th starter depending on my roster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN It's highly likely to sun will come up that day. Is #PresidentBoneSpurs gonna take credit for that too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DWFreer @katieshowblog @hostelworld Sadly they get away with it. @easyJet has done something similar recently and… https://t.co/pQiF6quZ06]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was talking to my friend about this recently but why is it as soon as women in the black community get money they… https://t.co/VvxGo6Y1c1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radioterryford Bruno almost willed the team to victory in spite of Turg, but Cowans didn’t get the memo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johniadarola @AOC Improving credit bureau systems and how statistics are used in identifying trust worthiness to b… https://t.co/5oN5g1sVuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Well_Damn_Jesse Exactly! think about it. people do anything for fame n fortune these days]]></document><document><![CDATA[UBC faculty should be deeply disturbed that UBC's administration is proposing to gut the faculty's ability to have… https://t.co/4TGtYVnHpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlogedyBlogBlog when I think of El Niño I think of this https://t.co/049FKc8TUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryBuh I feel like one special I would love in the future from BFSC is a DS3 "What Happened!?" Post-mortem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomaszwania They should re-air your season so more people can fall in love with @bbuk a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former NCC foes battling it out in the “Largest and Finest High School Fieldhouse in the World.” #HoosierHysteria @… https://t.co/AiQpdAMjDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully I'm not the only person who thinks @joerogan should do a podcast with @EckhartTolle. #JRE… https://t.co/DK94OTB9b7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday February 15 - Morning News:      Will ‘basic income’ become the California norm? Stockton starts $500 no-str… https://t.co/DPOcCOu7UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@physedreview @rich_wiles @BigTennPhysEd School is closed for us already. Snow coming in at 5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancyterhune @MollyJongFast Nope, didn't need to think about that. https://t.co/aV2eEqNU9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKUS411 @CNN You can listen, I have zero doubts he molested little boys, WAY to many have accused over the decades… https://t.co/Uwt5TvHOn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chih_somh @KweenPhotos @muluneh237 @Blackdotmandy @4eeevverrrrnaan Exactly! I told my boys the wedding process is… https://t.co/6tccszPua5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly just gimme a bag of kettle cooked Lays salt and vinnys and a gourmet signature soup from Raley’s and I’ll be on my way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gilgamesh30 Chija no manda nada, todo el crudo es para pagar deudas. India y Rusia no comprarán nada, por las sanciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be real, if this had been a white, gay man faking an attack, it’d be “Ok, he’s mentally ill” but bc its a POC… https://t.co/6tOcfKJHBF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slim_mirokujin @randolf828 @Surisskeptic @Lead1225 If I die, I want my beliefs shared to my friends and family. If… https://t.co/gqgXYBtfbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RigelRobinson No sir we have more then enough market rate. Go look at ABAG numbers. We also don't need luxary hotels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @JackPosobiec @OANN Well @AOC look on the bright side the person who took this photo cpight your best side 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modelerr Did you watch the second clip? there is a second reason, keeps interrupting the others too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how you can just treat the person who works so hard for your family; who devotes their life to y… https://t.co/rkoreknkcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUUUUDE I FINALLY GET TO SEE THE STARTING LINE. Like whaaattt the fuck?! Drive thru records nostalgia!! @TheStartingLine #warped25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics @cnnbrk It won’t be# long until her next words -  are you going to give her another pass?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kx30 @ChrisChasePnV @rickdaynyc @yourbriefrelief @ModelViews @MenAndUnderwear @DamnHotBod @SpectacularBody… https://t.co/4W1CMA5cvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entertainment executive Heather Parry leaves Live Nation after allegations of bullying: A prominent executive has l… https://t.co/cV1ZpTQl6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @DHSgov We’ve been doing this for years before Trump and none of you said a word; nothing less than al… https://t.co/e9XppO3Ggl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrystalEatonBi1 @MacgregorRucker @mjgranger1 @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Read about Eisenhower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Boone County Public Library Main in Burlington, KY https://t.co/NjOdQujtKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonnslingdog Very welcome. Honestly, bike riding on camera would make me nervous and being in a pool all that time… https://t.co/lvIBY70wOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a look at what @TexasTech is asking lawmakers for—with one of the newly appointed regents and the Pres. of the… https://t.co/gmBkTd7CYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbgarza el clásico no es tema hasta que termine el juego de concachampions, no le sabes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamodell @salopwolf @CivMilAir @jonostrower @AirbusintheUK @nikijoel Amazing @adamodell but the Butterfly was mor… https://t.co/Hiflox9SIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both the heather grey and gold “axes” pullover hoodies drop tomorrow🙌🏻. Noon CST 3/8/19 #ironandinkfitness… https://t.co/mVkVd0DiUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@venuslvnda @NinodaFilipino IM NOT EVEN SLIPPIN IM AT HOME FUCK IS U TALM BOUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewT61830774 @LogoTV @EllenPage @TheEllenShow Which of Jesus’s message or life’s work have I skewed?  You paint… https://t.co/x0NRKlzDVw]]></document></documents></author>