<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[For everyone who is saying @rickybobbybabyy is being rude or whatever for what he said. Ik for a fact Half of you g… https://t.co/dzvSrI22Vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luis_MCMLXVII @elcoya1977 No son lunchacos o como se escriba... si son machetes !! Que vayan a cortar el pasto al costado de las vías !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily @Rickbluewave140 🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻🎻 #LockThemAllUp  #CrimeFamily https://t.co/LxIQd4oqOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry Mr. President we got your back we love you we want to go on 2020 again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me counting the amount of money i’ll need to take out for law school despite scholarship money https://t.co/0TutDuDLd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miguelon_toro @sariscabal @maantoniasantos @mluciaramirez @IvanDuque Lo primero que necesita hacer es leer el libr… https://t.co/pPcC8br6xE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg That is insane! That means that any criminal or nut can carry a gun!! I’m glad that I don’t live i… https://t.co/dIM2ZTT0YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngoraBoys @TreasuryMog @AmbassacatRB @BizimkiTR Thank you, boys, and thank you to your mum also. We miss him very… https://t.co/yiUoAXa8td]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehornick My personal opinion is that Gordon's coaching style was too complex for a young roster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was taken right after @marwingf9 threw out Mitch Moreland at home to preserve a 2-1 lead in B3 of game 4 of th… https://t.co/QpoI6TyTvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Apple Music has a replay button I’m switching bc i need to listen to replay my fav song 2749374 times...]]></document><document><![CDATA[good god i really have reached an all time low for the stunt i just pulled 😂😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random dude at the gas station: “Aye, girl. What’s up with you? What you doin tonight?”  Me: “I have a boyfriend”… https://t.co/B2pD51fsda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dante closed on an IPBB “1000” BOOM 💥 @BirminghamDMDR @anthonyetuggle @mrscorporate @TonySmith4Sales https://t.co/QUM55KBPen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett I love your voice.  Also don’t pay attention to people that don’t believe your case.  Keep doing th… https://t.co/8hzcoxN5mC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition | Punish coward who poured acid over  dog, threw him out of moving car! https://t.co/zXI4Ij0TvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland  Yeah I want those Bexar County Jail Problems Fixed AND telling a Narcissist "NO" should never have go… https://t.co/K0FRvP3Xzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m back from Colorado and needed a little sparkle, so today I chose Plump and shimmer Peach Rose’ :)… https://t.co/fNWIFpiBkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRES TRUMP WASNT REJECTED BY CONGRESS!  FACTS ARE CONGRESS COULDN'T SHIT and GET OFF THE POT!! THAT MEANS GREEN LIG… https://t.co/ZfGrneORoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have an elementary aged child in Union County?  Come see me today at the PDC [600 Brewer Drive in Monroe] be… https://t.co/RP2wLefy8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking @h_lanee if his hair looks ok- #missessissy😢#trustsheropinion https://t.co/Or4e7rpBJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3Conservative @brithume Sorry I don't try to argue with people like you, you're not worthy of my time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande  Jan Drake Bakke  @007hotmail  Feb 14  ""Enter the light" Radio show" hosted by Sacred Embers on Thur… https://t.co/cM33OTuCbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[and y’all really thought he was finna do time for this nigga ?  I woulda snitched too shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come out and support the wrestling team Saturday!⚡️🤼‍♂️⚡️  Wrestling starts at 10am 💪🏼  Sect. Tournament: Div. I -… https://t.co/1HxQbcX6hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farm Yard Wrap and creator Ryan #hyemarket @ Hye Market https://t.co/AjyTea4iAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dorothy clicked her heels and she was home 😉 #GoBeavs https://t.co/vIMi1AfaHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[being ona brace probably annoying asf 😭 just knowing some big shit just placed on your ankle and the fact that u ca… https://t.co/UtXlIBQyRh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. Lok @charmaine_lok presenting the NEAT (WavelinQ device) study data - check out the significantly lower thrombo… https://t.co/mBg3u1r4Mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Forrest Gump has a far greater moral, ethical, and mental capacity than you. If you… https://t.co/kEljarniwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamShatner @opry If talking fast can be considered “singing”, than I’m sure the public will accept anything. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[No woman should have to sacrifice her career or life goals to be with someone. That shouldn’t be a woman thing - th… https://t.co/09usd60gAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all i seriously cannot stand Cheetos. I only eat the flaming hot ones and my child is obsessed with Cheetos and i just can’t deal 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[« Disgrâce », « inacceptable » : des actes racistes en LNAH suscitent l'indignation https://t.co/SFuCjsJeNR #desimbeciles #mtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElbaklySami @PucciaPatrizia @Viviane6677 @angela681417 @enriqueiglesias @TereOrt51687394 @janaplauen @ZoyaDayala… https://t.co/V2vGoSiwTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los jugadores del Barça haciendo el homenaje perfecto a Valverde por su renovación. #DeTraca @frac1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFidds @MisterVegas1957 @msw_sports @BParry19 I think they are just worried about the attendance issue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonMWaller @mistiedawn77 @cjiglar @j_bekiri I mean, @cjiglar has an English degree, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just made rent by selling my old clothes at buffalo god is truly shining down on me today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to the @thecatempire’s new album before we see them March 1st.  My hub walks in and says, “It’s a Cat Emp… https://t.co/Q9IJFDehta]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEAUTIFUL words that totally ring TRUE...no matter your sport or your school!!!  These memories DO last a lifetime!… https://t.co/IYsJRflkLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO good! Nasu Dengaku - Miso Glazed Eggplant https://t.co/acMVzEGxa2 via @misspickledplum]]></document><document><![CDATA[so is the carpool karaoke airing when the show does bc sis.... i have to sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bunch of kids on the beach made a pit to bury stingless jellyfish. When they ran down the beach to collect more,… https://t.co/gHy2b2VSrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood because I’ve never been so tired in my life https://t.co/UatbB124yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluelivesmtr @del_dalton So very sad..  Prayers being sent to his family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to new song mixes. Ziggy doesn’t seem impressed 🤷‍♀️ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/HIbwIW8mA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @JoeBiden @realDonaldTrump @VP Hold @POTUS to those standards why don't you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must see! This nurse just nailed it!! Shame on every one of us if we allow this! I dare you to watch this!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see fellow Missourian @EagleEdMartin at @CPAC.  Ed, thanks for photobombing my new show! 😉 #CPAC #CPAC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sharonstrong Can you solve it?  Happy Valentines Day! https://t.co/9xlOfIZbR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is reality. And the decisions involved belong to the parents, not the government, and not third parties who wi… https://t.co/3npWLh6jnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[The obvious answer is to secure our borders against all who would bring evil  Or discord.]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damn they know now we were just going to kill everyone here on the planet, said the main alien agenda man. Cr… https://t.co/luz7gleTM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Watch #Islam infiltration. 🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏⭐️⭐️⭐️ #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE  #LauraLoomer in Minnesota big problems, give… https://t.co/nJAx2jTNo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @LaurenUnderwood It was started under Clinton..and Obama CONTINUED the " kids in cages"!  Plenty of p… https://t.co/WqehIHMm7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobLopez_BSD @Stop_Trump20 Jordan is playing along with his role, defined as a Republican.  He can do no different… https://t.co/RoW9bOeg75]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI - @Sara_Brosious @kfhunt2 @micheleacurcio @jackielongan @GuyerElaine @KateFahnestock @JenniferHervada… https://t.co/o0FZVOfWyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios @maggieNYT The Real @FBI Housewives of Virginia donated to Sponge Bob Square Pantsuit's 2016 Presidential campaign,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im 35 years old today. This day last year I was so depressed and sad I started using after stopping for 7 months. H… https://t.co/eeXdJmiGdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaetaSusan @RandPaul You senators are misreading the voters. We back our president. We back his policies. We want… https://t.co/ZZq2AJUOF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love when non-comics ask if comedy is going well because honestly? No i do it for free and usually i'm not funny.… https://t.co/ihBwcBGcAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this book and wish I could go to any of these events! If you’re in any of these cities when @LizzyMason21 is… https://t.co/omWJWlDuYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruin my hair-&gt; cut it all off-&gt; convince myself I’m going to grow it out and I won’t let this happen again-&gt;cycle repeats]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 My Favorite Mistake by @SherylCrow on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/2LrXxF2w9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, today a teacher swerved in the parking spot I was about to park in. (So RUDE) SO tomorrow after class I’m goi… https://t.co/Mjxw99c8MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's Catharsis Manifesto, a giant doodle that I'll probably never finished. I work on it when I have my booth set… https://t.co/eDbRfR4gTC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsWelzenbach @DavidGeurin I’m under the impression you believe this is a quiz… Instead of an opportunity for dial… https://t.co/G7g80FmVYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the season finale of the bachelor, I love @demi_burnett #twins https://t.co/u68xovrtNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith I beg of you to release Dogma on a streaming service, or re-release the DVD. My favorite movie and… https://t.co/NEVb91rfmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePhang Even InfoWars came out and apologized for spreading the Seth Rich lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madelinewcopel1 @Naninani51 @AMike4761 I will never lose my faith just my patience 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to kick Tasha and Hannah to the curb and chase that limo..... #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Medicare for all” isn’t a goddamned policy. It’s a platitude. And it’s a shitty one at that. We done need another… https://t.co/rzd39XDNTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kasey Musgrave looking extremely floaty #OscarsRedCarpet https://t.co/Vv8BlCL3OM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm loving my chocolate #plantbased protein shakes brought french vanilla today...can't wait to try it before bed🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then he swerved and cut a car off to get right next to me at a stop light and scream at scared-ass-almost-died-Tyle… https://t.co/6Ni7YuK2FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh airport bars how i miss you...learned about a guy who had a pet alligator when he lived in Texas (“because you c… https://t.co/WNpaBBgWMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Must read: #TheCaseForTrump. #Tatiana is at bookstore in her #TysonsCorner mall #Virginia. https://t.co/YamAV79DS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr You have the spine of a jellyfish and no honor or integrity. You stand behind the man who is the most… https://t.co/xl2iLkLVh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh no! Why does this make me so sad?!  #GoodnightOppy #OpportunityRover]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vía @ricardolodice  Embajadora Venezolana Maria Teresa Belandria en Brasil 🇧🇷 (@matebe): “Debemos confiar en que se… https://t.co/bYqquiBC7R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@casalindi Oh I can’t imagine having asthma on top of everything else. I have a Dr Appointment tomorrow just to che… https://t.co/IePL6JYfAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo I’m guessing @danabrams word of the night is shenanigans.. ? 😂#LivePD #LivePDNation https://t.co/srlbXs7JHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE TAKE ACTION NOW &amp; Speak UP for Exploited #Greyhounds Caged and Bled Repeatedly for Cash‼️👎🏻😱👎🏻‼️… https://t.co/dAIc6wBy98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Shape Corp. team! See our latest #Manufacturing job openings, including "CNC Technician", via the link in our bio. #GrandHaven, MI]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the person who texted me and I never replied. My bad fam  I don't text unknown numbers no more. I deleted that shit quick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally own SO MANY @42NerdtasticPl lip sheers, I never thought I'd finish one, but I did!!!  Goodbye, sedition… https://t.co/LGvAgC7try]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XUCryptKeeper @fccincinnati A true fan would have flown to Seattle for the opener!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not going to act like I live a healthy lifestyle just because I’m veg but I’m also not going to gloss over the… https://t.co/Up27Phcq0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[biggest pet peeve: people getting on the elevator to go up or down ONE floor. take your lazy ass to the stairs jeez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Вован # Волгоградский @27gfh57,Gervasio Xavier soares 2 RT @gervasio_xavier, わみ @321minney, 3286… https://t.co/8E5UW0xAZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EkbMary @MerriweatherSun @sharon_elle @ElizabethPand11 @SonyaBaker2 @MustangRehab @eschaz12 @CyntWhite… https://t.co/3WbipEJFZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@himanshuPSingh @Poseidon34Live @NaomiKyle I know, I know. A woman’s opinion means nothing. I should just fall in l… https://t.co/LUASQQ44BC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, except Tierra or whatever her name is, is not relevant to anyone, no one, nada, zip, zero. She needs to crawl… https://t.co/7B9FZa3SsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[SINGLE LEG CIRCLE | An exercise which helps mobilize the hip joint whilst challenging core and pelvic stability. On… https://t.co/nOFHq64KhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m personally offended every Sunday morning when @Apple decides to remind me I spend too much time on my phone. Can you not?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CEASAR rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Po Village #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea  A shy boy. He enjoys being wit… https://t.co/vFgVpH06VI]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i tell someone i bought my next plane ticket and they say “wow i wish i had your money” but they smoke a pack… https://t.co/OZPZlDQEzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattiMurin @ArmchairExpPod with Dax Shepard and Monica Padman. It’s a crazy-good mix of actors/comedians and autho… https://t.co/F4pbvNJBbx]]></document></documents></author>