<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@teejayIs I have the same thing.. Don't look as cute tho..  Didn't  post.   Lolz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday boy brunch!!  Happy Birthday Andy..... @ Sweet Afton https://t.co/fFjIXzQQ6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onejoey @David_Shorr @chris_steller lol. I mean it’s like their 7th best album, but...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you  make plans face to face and then randomly back, screwing over the people(friends) they originally had plans… https://t.co/dZvAattaUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to make new Twitter where all messages must follow the format, “I don’t know man, i sell X for a living.… https://t.co/6yHJZJqpGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was bound to happen eventually. Me, Ted Lieu and Ken Starr all agree on a matter of a law.   There is nothing le… https://t.co/92Efg5fUQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Response is easy to formulate but tough to implement. Traitors to this country must die or be deported, investigati… https://t.co/J4kPu5Yrmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mac said f—k all of y’all that hated that we didn’t trade for Brown!! I’m trying to protect my quarterback!!!!😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bradhowe07 @Coach_Addae That hit against VT is one of my all time favorites. I am glad he is back in Morgantown. https://t.co/xDn9ivre7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmbJohnBolton @CNNSotu “Attention On Deck” to John Bolton, National Security Adviser. Sir you took an oath to serv… https://t.co/8Wv6NVoCwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailybible_app Mark 11:24 Therefore I tell you, whatever you ask for in prayer, believe that you have received it, https://t.co/ZmNtzfusLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC U would think that 1 of these major news outlets would just come forward and report real collision ...Collusio… https://t.co/5PlgPPKfBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytopinion Williamson is getting paid this year. He asked Kansas for money but Duke out bid them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilibellmia @Patriot988 Drama queen looking for attention, what a disgrace. 🤣😈🤣🙉🤣🙉🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Kiwanis of SE Volusia for all that you do to support our students. And for throwing a great “Strike-It-R… https://t.co/S78TwOV90Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[One might view the current culture wars and problems with the mainstream media as the painful symptoms of a transit… https://t.co/nXFYSoUDAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC He is a Black Man defending his alleged illegal misbehavior, against charges brought by state/local government… https://t.co/HJi6uxwUON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like 0% of my tweets are about reality tv anymore channel 5 really ended me 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyTonyTone007 @Benaskren He definitely has a Big Strong Chin! A wrestlers heart and mind. Getting a belt isn’t s… https://t.co/eA6lZiox5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que perramente estresante la gente que tarda años en un cajero. O sea, no tiene ninguna ciencia usarlo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaoz989 @albertoreyes84 @MarceloM12 @GarethBale11 @Benzema @isco_alarcon @ToniKroos @raphaelvarane Y sí vamos a es… https://t.co/tZNHRE3O3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @GOP @votevets 🌴😎☮️ #Thanks @kershaw_sharon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damage, and destruction of property is antithetical to the concept of liberty.  I’m guilty of feeling happiness fro… https://t.co/coOZex3zI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neta este pinche tráfico de monterrey me ha quitado como 3 años de vida https://t.co/8rQgEeEeEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to be smart here’s what you do  Watch a lot of ted talks  Listen to joe rogan  Read a lot of books  Only hang… https://t.co/fk0LCFUvFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a business and you don’t don’t pick up your phone - you’re dead to me... unless you sell chicken wings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hemantmehta If anything, your fake God is punishing America with Trump for Americans being so stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the internet. Perception is reality. Research, monitor, be diligent, be involved. https://t.co/dEOVvt382H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShepherd2013 Yes!  That is the motivation, curiosity and desire to serve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDiNardo "There's going to be a little rain. Bear with me" Me: https://t.co/8zctT49QZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVGMike @SimonTVG Funny!  I said the same about this one yesterday.   https://t.co/Hgsk1bb18i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting films like Argento's "Deep Red" and Del Toro's "Pans Labyrinth" in that janky fucking drawer truly pains me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot_Musket The suicide was recorded? Send that to the police, pronto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I don’t hear back about a writing packet I like to fantasize that they at least printed it out and threw it in… https://t.co/vvhSYvKO9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haivanjoe Usted está correcto mi distinguido compañero @haivanjoe Pero!!! No es lo mismo decir tengo 2 millones de… https://t.co/61XaHw3C0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some barriers to entry for sellers on https://t.co/AVv9cuDmTj but sellers don't have to pay, is it a plat… https://t.co/mPzq2N1t8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you put into your body is just as vital to how you train your body! Hydration is a HUGE part of that! #H2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re getting the band back together!!! By special arrangement with the Humane Society,  Scott Thompson’s RESCUE AN… https://t.co/R1cnoNtkZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Ned calls timeout  with 9 seconds left... We're still tied  at 34. #BigCountryPreps https://t.co/K57cPHGDTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Project Soren 3.0 by @brewery4two4 @ Podcast Detroit Studios — https://t.co/DPJqjQpX8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what happened, or if this is related to the recently murdered neighbor. Ann Arbor has almost zero lo… https://t.co/6T6nlXUWRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @ChuckWendig @rez512 I meditate to regain my mana, before casting Lvl. 8 Chuck of the Infinite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamsambee SAM! You're the reason I started to give a shit again, and to #StayWoke on issues I was to privleged to… https://t.co/Er00gCgzCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forbidden Kingdom Fest this weekend with gang 🏰@diontimmermusic excisionofficial @dubloadz @adventuredub @ Boca Rat… https://t.co/mraqVSwg8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Twitter now you’re stopping reply’s to my opinions and tweets,what’s your problem guys?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arthurstacy @XavierFiles I like Greko and they specialize in comics printing. Pretty affordable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Epitome of America doesn’t work for All Americans as the Republicans make sure many Americans can’t eve… https://t.co/ke483I9Tht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con 20 años en la #LMB, el oaxaqueño Jaime Brena es el cuarto mejor bateador en la historia del circuito veraniego… https://t.co/YMryYLFmuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hype man @peterpham brings his A-game to #SXSW and it was a sight to behold. Wonderful to see you! #SXSW2019… https://t.co/HXWkDWx9TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drdrew the thing with Leann that comes to mind is this:  Are we dealing with a megalomaniac?  We see this in so ma… https://t.co/NE0oXiVYFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballdadto2 @culver_lamb The reason he will be the #1 pick in the next draft.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSScottWhite So, you realize Adam, Chris, and Heath were basically trolling you the whole broadcast, right?!… https://t.co/pC0Z77um2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brewerhm @_AndyJacks @brijslater @SteeleThoughts @DrJStephensVP @burgessdave @mr_Alsheimer @NowakRo @DHEPrincipal @matthew_arend 🙏🏼❤️💯🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also happy birthday to @roysalazar361 glad you drink beer now, but this is a classic 🤣 have a good one bro, see you… https://t.co/Rb8e1wwQQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our picks for the final weekend of the Pac-12 schedule: https://t.co/EeP3YUrJRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rglock17 @EvanRMitchell @georgewrighster Catch a few more passes and all of that is even better. Nothing is that s… https://t.co/U01s2Mdpiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds like you need a day off. Stream one here! https://t.co/8188M33LLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[my back has been itching me for the past like, 30 minutes and idk if i’m allergic to something or what. but whateve… https://t.co/6Yw8HMCggz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterAlek For business I would say google meet. Works really well and I can generate a meeting link instantly and… https://t.co/TVWEW2FkiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered for a chance to go to the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame 2019 Induction Ceremony! https://t.co/Y96IWqb2JM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a great time connecting with good friends and by far one of my favorite conference each year. @Sureify… https://t.co/3idjobvWNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really preferred the Buffalo Marriott Airport when it had the Houlihans in the lobby. #MACtion https://t.co/1OAasI4Uzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coaching is the last thing I’m worried about with this team. The roster is not good. The guys signed around Lebron… https://t.co/GxvzTY7FZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas that drive pick up trucks think they own the road or something. They drive so aggressively. I’d slap the shi… https://t.co/6notcTU5Ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[New RCMS Instagram account. Please follow our adventures. 👍🏽 https://t.co/c0e5U8Kt6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abgracee @shannonj2309 We have more than enough love to go around ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters @JalenandJacoby - @JalenRose was right to wait on this one @djacoby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw the @InvictaFights announcement on the 8-fighter tournaments. That’s so dope. #wmma #mma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow @HeyHeyItsConrad is gonna be doing a podcast with @JRsBBQ as heard on @MattKoonTE   Two of my favorite people t… https://t.co/yl3ILYCPaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t STAND a “hUh?” Motherfucker like u heard what the fuck i said dude u just didn’t wanna listen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Popa_molly_bish @camick27 @db6strings @finebaum @KySportsRadio @CFBPlayoff There’s a lot of difference in an Aggie and a UCF Knight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepPaulTonko @NRDems Curious sir if your going to recognize this nations children as our most prized resource? And… https://t.co/tYG8nzEL7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at us. You can’t stop us jamarmccoy1 #losangeles #hollywood #beverlyhills #manhattan #newyork #newyorknewyork… https://t.co/OjlCLFOP8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigpappa040 It is very interesting! It's awful haha! Plus only costs 30p at home. I forget that must be some peopl… https://t.co/J9gvjhGGz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @journalsentinel @patrickdmarley What an ass we are done as a nation I feel sorry for my children… https://t.co/RAH076ayte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frjohnhollowell @moritz_221 @BishopStika @EWTN @FoxNews https://t.co/pV1RY4q6rQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great opportunity to hear all of these incredibly influential people speak in honor of… https://t.co/ZFAyoafz02]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamryn_kristine @dpaigeeb Y’all better be nice to whoever decides to slum it with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I want to swipe right on someone’s profile just to meet their dog. #swipeleft]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging here in my living room and it’s just so obvious Stephen A Smith just shouts random things to receive undese… https://t.co/5EKdzKl7AV]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay @YOUTUBE SEE HERES THE THING I DIDNT SPECIFICALLY CUT ALL MY COLORADO VIDEOS TO FIT THE SONG I WANT FOR YOU TO COPYRIGHT PUSSY ASS B]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you need to get MOS for a story and people actually take the time to talk to you:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fue un pedo saludar de beso a las que traían sombrero ayer en el festival de la carne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Heels4life99 @ryansatin I did. Where does it say anything about Disco working for Impact?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I find out @kimpetras has a new single out that I haven’t heard yet https://t.co/kTvil1VH7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are insanely insecure on this app lol. You can absolutely like pictures of other people, I like my friends p… https://t.co/NEhjvuWp0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@downey @SophiaKris @goodnewsmag @wesleyancov They definitely flew in alternates on their own dime from Africa to m… https://t.co/x6EquwdMIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Running out of tweets, or is this a Greatest Hits week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickgillespie @JussieSmollett I wish that were true, but the silence and avoidance of the useful idiots, like… https://t.co/nga1E8p5v2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raviolifreak Feedback sandwich. Talk about a positive, then what she can work on, then another positive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren I’m launching a non-partisan website that gives the avg citizen transparency on where their tax $$ goes… https://t.co/GpbOen0Iy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yonceuphoria Legit reading these all with my mouth wide open. Like whaaaaaaaaaaat.   I understand having different… https://t.co/XT8kWbwbvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little girls and I on our way to the #springdance for #cotillion. I am very proud of the young women that y'all… https://t.co/5rYZQEd1Hg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 well mr big Chest take care you will never have a fan base like the Steelers nation hopefully you will be a g… https://t.co/AeOERNsNuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well thanks to @mbabs21 for getting me to try Cauliflower Rice.. I’m eating it with chicken... 🤞🤞 because I’m letti… https://t.co/uZqUp8rCCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett needs to see a good performance of his fake hoax crime.  #Smollett #SmolletHoax #JussieSmollett… https://t.co/LSMEP1VmcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 Sea of Sorrow or Dam That River. Or actually anything from SAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 12 This is America (woo, ayy) Don't catch you slippin' up (woo, woo, don't catch you slippin', now) Don't catch… https://t.co/re8XnVr1QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerFernando MP Horsefeathers turns parliamentary committee hearing into Marx Brothers farcical romp into absurdity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweat and recovery! Too many people sweat and don’t know how to recover with the proper fuel, so they never see any… https://t.co/nrCPIpAkss]]></document></documents></author>