<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce Well we know who CONTROLS the MEDIA,BILLIONAIRE  MOGULS that give a s...t ABOUT reporting TRUES. Al… https://t.co/H2CCcMrifQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone who has repeatedly picked up a deck's worth of cards like these, I've found the realest one. 💯 https://t.co/3FZ46284W1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a few hours at a coffee shop ahead of you and you forget your Apple Pencil. #oops]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SiaWalker led her 5/6 grade girls team to a championship this evening in the #SierraNevadaBasketball league. After… https://t.co/9tTATnVZyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Just makes me sick. Trump needs to go. He doesn’t care about all the things are really important to us. It’s his ego.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And one day you wake up and decide you no longer want to live the unhappy life you have been. So you make changes t… https://t.co/B7LtbUDMXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe that no matter what happens now, there's no winners. Money will always win out in this battle, but God wi… https://t.co/4PsXq3OqYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeatackAADA #seatckdreamers @Jomurphy1414 @Pharrell #VBAmazing @BeachSupe]]></document><document><![CDATA[*telling @morgndnn how much I have in my urban basket*  Morgan: “says: doesn’t have any idea what you want for birt… https://t.co/fcuxMBjxec]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two interviews tomorrow, a midterm and a 6 page paper on logistics strategies :) #imfine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonG40210896 @Mary60053440 @ashionegallery @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @Kitty_Goncalves @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep… https://t.co/l3lopFbeak]]></document><document><![CDATA[The longer I live, the more I realize- I don't want to live a single moment of my life apart from Jesus. I can't. I… https://t.co/am6xKqlaE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crafting at the @thebeehiveatl with an intimate, relaxed Hive. Great way to start a Sunday! Thx Becca for being a g… https://t.co/rki59k80NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a restaurant says “our award winning team” I always wonder what kind of awards they have won cause that’s neve… https://t.co/Rw6TGgV3kP]]></document><document><![CDATA[my conclusions after 3 chapters of Queens Shadow is the handmaidens are a kpop group and naboo is a dystopia thank… https://t.co/eHdXSY0WV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I'm so proud of my boys Repost by pop2000tour with (get_repost)... Sold out show tonight at thecowannashville… https://t.co/xPVE8PtcVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Kara and I promised @anarchymartinez we would see him the next time he came to Ohio.  We kept that promise.… https://t.co/0NHLqr8V6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤗he back to speak how and what's he doing and how is his health going and when he will be back.😊true champion is co… https://t.co/mhmgxL221M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said no candy dammit , nun num num @ Bridgewater, Kissimmee, Florida https://t.co/46YlxRKnun]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wife said she didn’t want a divorce. I dunno. If you have an affair with the dude who kidnaped and molested you… https://t.co/TEHY0pPstr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Michael Cohen Michael Cohen       Michael Cohen Michael Cohen   Michael Cohen Michael Cohen  Micha… https://t.co/1NvNeh3Rv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[weekend in seattle w/ my main squeezzz🥰  #girlstrip #wesocute https://t.co/gPPMS6a6fl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helena gets a steal and Caden Pierce lays it up at the other end. Huskies lead 8-2 early. Timeout Russell County wi… https://t.co/RQk6ZC7OHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayliesorrel And your mom should have swallowed you , are we done here ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I come across this baby pig on my Instagram feed and I look at Braden and passionately say LETS GET A PIG!! (we… https://t.co/XpZ6b60laf]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥 P E L I G R O S A 🔥 by @jbalvin @wisinyyandel  Latinas power representando! 💃🏽: - Thalía Ayala 🇵🇾 @thaliaayaladij… https://t.co/FOziu4cdgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheena_655321 @Madonna @KubrickRussell @OffBalanceLibra @CrystalBeebe3 @MEDUSAS_BROTHER @pcjuk1 @JamesTConleyII… https://t.co/Z2zT94qxVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women's Day #IWD2019 #BalanceforBetter  @JulieONeillWCPO https://t.co/roSwa3B71U https://t.co/5JxUrT18iC]]></document><document><![CDATA[To everyone who says that the founding fathers would hate trigger warnings and safe spaces, please remember that on… https://t.co/xJmzXyvRYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DemiWuforTrump @BreitbartNews I would enjoy and love seeing more of her clothing choices.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rutland slips past Spaulding, 3-2 https://t.co/FYwMpTF1Em via @rutlandherald #vthshockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are such a divided state. Tonight while watching #The2000s I’m reflected on the Obama election and Tea Party mov… https://t.co/gW8o82suzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroadwayGirlNYC @BUILDseriesNYC @joelgrey @FiddlerNYC I got my ticket for this! Very excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Easier said than done. Maybe you are trying to be a doctor, it is looked down upon to do you’re sciences at a cc bc… https://t.co/PZ621zUfIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please go away forever. Your disdain for 50% of America is unbecoming. #MAGA #PresidentsDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL IM SCARED LIKE I ACTUALLY MEET SAM AND COLBY TOMORROW IT DOESNT FEEL REAL AT ALL AKDKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kepa &amp; Sarri in the unemployment line tomorrow https://t.co/vLzRz7OVLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andibeth012 @SandraK93322487 @mialleixa34 @sachikoko @mmjoymm_StP @VictoriaVogt5 @ckdusky @_Cristian_Vlad_… https://t.co/LH7gUDO79M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notbrandy LMAO thanks boo 😂💕 and it’s called Alcatraz Escape Room Games! It’s in Tempe and the room we specificall… https://t.co/KI698bDBVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down 16.3 pounds! #reallywantahamburger #healthierme #14poundstogo #profilebysanfordknoxville @ Knoxville, Tennessee https://t.co/LJXAceGkQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get how people have time to shower and shave when you’re always hustling and having mental breakdowns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden you are an embarrassment to my country. You caused so many problems for my country. Thank god for @realDonaldTrump #MAGA2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@LanceUlanoff: At least they died together. #SXSW #scooterhell https://t.co/bUe5T3oMaT” #truth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStuedler Deliberate, R’s have been promoting white nationalist bs on Fox for years.  Chump upped the ante]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time one of my coworkers asks me how I am and I say "good" I can practically hear my life's narrator going "b… https://t.co/GaONCa5HUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT I think she is pretty much clueless and speaks for no one sir. We already established she is not rep… https://t.co/4Altq9UlL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCutsinger Hi Paul!  Would like to bring an Alexa hackathon to San Antonio.   Can we schedule a chat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it weird I still have the ring my bd got me even though we not together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break a leg @CCTheaterBC at OAP and Marie Antoinette. AhhCC 💙🐾🎭 @cycreekhs @ambyclink @contrerascchs https://t.co/LFk2JZkf20]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Aunque continentes o océanos nos separen, nada nunca podrá separar nuestra amistad.” Te quiero un chingo querida a… https://t.co/P4GnDV3eSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Molly should be playing the part of Nana in the next Peter Pan!  Don’t you agree??? #PeterPan #molly… https://t.co/V4EATjJe7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[A winter’s grip. Held together with yarn and hope. I roast my regrets on flame And summon a new page. Rough skin fr… https://t.co/PAdppBhR7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaxMan4L @primantibros Have fun and be safe! They have that whole Smiley Face Killer show on Oxygen so don’t go al… https://t.co/emNexnymZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this root growth, this happened in one week! This #Orchid from the #Oncidium alliance is forever trying t… https://t.co/BsfHkXoa4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came all the way to NYC to run into my #uofsc colleague. #developmentlife She’s working. Clearly, I’m not.… https://t.co/XiQuznu9zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Musical film director Stanley Donen has died at 94, Chicago Tribune reports  https://t.co/GOLLQjrP9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[She done been fished. #movie #AMC #reaction #LiveTweet #spoiler #Alita https://t.co/D602ohySWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days you just need a mother-daughter day!!! https://t.co/yRBEK3H42N]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wishyouwerehere so you could feel these #lush #velvet #navy #fabricsamples for my #happyclient #tracymetrodesigns… https://t.co/w3qAGqSSPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoovesandpawse @RandPaul All sides...rand? I think not. You are irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jordanhasty Don’t be mad because some people get scared easily. I’d be doing the same thing. And probably would w… https://t.co/v7AiH0nSQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Octopus is "opətə" and elephant is "epətə", what even are any of us doing here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa Blessed? Your baby was murdered. How blessed is that? #SherinMathews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @shannonrwatts "I'm done with your childishness?"😂  OMG!!!! What are you...her mother?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1CatShepherd Oops - sorry! Just read that it's her first lamb ever. Congratulations, Ebony! You are already a great mom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cekieran who, knowingly or not, have generally worked hard to keep them under-developed and unenlightened in the n… https://t.co/eSP1iPZ2yE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaSirkin Taking a year off. 😉. Living vicariously through Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nadie es perfecto, pero si puedes estar con una persona que trabaje día con día para que la relación sea bonita, fe… https://t.co/1UQlbzvLaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoicePremiere y’all are crazy but I love it needed a good Laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes the fuck I will and have before , waiting on ONE very special MAN .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was in pack all day and apparently the real reason is that I have health issues so they didn’t wanna risk keeping… https://t.co/c78V0sK2cC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Love_To_Breathe is an amazing woman.... beautiful inside and out!  So inspiring. NEVER stops fighting. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEALTeamBrigade @David_Boreanaz @jaimeboreanaz Looking 👀 good, 👍🏻 handsome!!! 💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 72, a teacher's quest to never retire finds her best student in a 11-year-old girl with stunted growth https://t.co/zmOG012L1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[and extortion by police and military officers against Rohingya, and the placement of Rohingya into locked refugee c… https://t.co/NHXrymUgwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Do you ever read what the American people are saying to you? Take a moment to scroll down or does… https://t.co/ikxUcj6RFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BressieDiana @KamalaHarris If you think this innocent victim is not worth “the resources” you are on the evil side]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double header for me tonight with some playoff girls basketball @AMVgirlsbball vs. @TrojansGHoops and… https://t.co/QuFwwuHbla]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you want to learn more about #regulatory science in #oncology after FDA_ASCOFellowsDay, apply for the 8 wk… https://t.co/UQpgiJWf5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a higher salary.  Seeking 2 people to fake kick my ass.   #goals #showmethemoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday blues #bassethound #bassethoundsofinstagram #mondayblues @ Greenfield, Indiana https://t.co/B5vo7lbY5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[F is for Flag #lyspolestudio #polealphabet @ Ly's Pole Studio https://t.co/t38ME1QAvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somethings in the air forsure with the way these kids are acting today. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waynestate @waynestatealum curious on why you’re scamming alumni who are trying to apply for graduate school by MA… https://t.co/M5TopKtLMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[💚 #TBT | | 2004 💚 #BeYourOwn #BodyGoals #HealthIsWealth #EatToLive  🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱🌱 #super #model #mood… https://t.co/7s1q5uv7n9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was looking back at Nancy Pelosi January 2009 speech, she was a great speaker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the new “Homer” award-recognition wall @ HD Pro #3261!  Had to make sure there was a prime spot for that… https://t.co/fDnWyQMIkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents should file class action@lawsuits against the colleges who violate their children’s rights ofvfree speech .… https://t.co/6YsK11nopZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ARMYPEDIA QR codes are just 2 blocks away from my apartment 😳😳I use this subway station every day. How couldn’t I… https://t.co/EJ2LOK5GOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE HAS HIS HANDS ALL OVER THESE KIDS...RUMORS IN WH SAYS HE LIKES YOUNG PAGES WORKING THERE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tantas calificaciones y condenas no sirven p nada. El pueblo d Venezuela no se cura ni alimenta de lamentos; es nec… https://t.co/FoRVotFuHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here at the @MicrosoftStore with @VolunteerBGCHOU #tweens diving in to @MSMakeCode @Minecraft https://t.co/dIwQ7YUxyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iHeartRadio @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves @Harry_Styles @KaceyMusgraves #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyways :) can you guys go watch my new upload because a girl struggled to get this uploaded. Thank you ❤️ https://t.co/A49X5rNLYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MardyKing1 I think it is! Someone told me they remembered that it was! So many boats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mercantilism  The economic doctrine prevailing from the 16th to the 18th centuries is commonly called mercantilism.… https://t.co/GkU4U3Fhyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever Read Someone's Posts And/Or Comments And Just Roll Your Eyes And Think "Oh, Shuuut Uuuuupp" Because You Know H… https://t.co/oCA00x6AWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be part of @ATCouncil member @AmcomSolutions dinner with @RingCentral promoting digital communications for… https://t.co/pbL5Q9muRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamritu @DrMarthaGulati @DrQuinnCapers4 @fitmslax @pulsecardiac @bes502 @becballa @VietHeartPA @heartdoc45… https://t.co/b1R76sVplS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith  Thought I'd share this with you❤  “THE LATEST EDITION TO THE GREEN JELLO PUNK ROCK PUPPET FAMILY I… https://t.co/HkPU7oYPZR]]></document></documents></author>