<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kittykushman626 Well I admit they picked good content so at least they have good taste in videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN: Trump falsely claims Manafort judge declared there was 'no collusion' with Russia. https://t.co/qKk6TDQG96  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Gully Boy”!!! #gullyboy #india #ourstupidreactions #laemmletheaters @ Laemmle Town Center 5 https://t.co/0wthUBaL71]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacketsInsider My wife always seat belted our old toy poodle, Finnigan, on car rides. And don’t get me started on… https://t.co/uwUOVaBQ9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TEVAchrisk @BryanBoock Not my place to tell.  I just know who quits teva and why.  No results.  It’s nothing new.… https://t.co/Y7t55ojbzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushJohnNabors if you name your guys outing for Valentine’s Day you’re guaranteed to be single forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC AS A JEWISH LAWYER MIKE COHEN IS A SAINT IN MY BOOK,, MAYBE  A NATIONAL HERO BEFORE ITS ALL OVER ,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to be American. We must keep of working against the misguided Bernie supporters who want to ruin our great… https://t.co/uXYCuzXdnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews @Lamotrigine4Me @PinkNews Sure but that's not even the point in the first place. It's "what good can we… https://t.co/5DsBgP6q8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#A1427today#EMSlife (@ Virginia Beach FD Station #3 in Virginia Beach, VA) https://t.co/Lc5VmpcNCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You little fuckhead! I hope you are impeached or a recall election is held to pull you out of public life. Why don’… https://t.co/KstWvVXB2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ti-  what do you think we can do to change the minds of people? C- I fight a paper war every day.  I write and make… https://t.co/6ymQA8ly66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @realDonaldTrump for defending innocent, defenseless children. May God have mercy on the souls of those w… https://t.co/tzbJXNZv6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I have a peppermint? You can have a peppermint. Thank you my breath stinks. You're welcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A perfect Friday song for a Wannabe dictator. https://t.co/M08COB9jGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesante entrevista antes de la final 2011 y la época dorada de Tigres, @Faitelson_ESPN con Don Robert discutien… https://t.co/GIfNSikBCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preckwinkle had better polish to get to her points sooner. Lightfoot had a few answers that were borderline platitu… https://t.co/CjlqvNXXN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indyman08 @ChallengeOvrld @shboogies @DayDaVonne_ @MTV_AMANDAG yea fuck that guy bullshit , maybe people are like… https://t.co/v0R0RMvVSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t do the DEMs job. She’ll be made a martyr. Make them live with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @RogerJDavis1 on becoming chair of the Program in Molecular Medicine at UMMS! Such a strong department with amazing faculty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever you’re eating with your girl &amp; she’s on her period , that’s no longer your food it’s hers.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JabberJaw28 @ItzvMoney @Luck7jack8te @VinceGonzalezz @espn @LeVeonBell Subway also said eat fresh while putting th… https://t.co/8Y2uwvER0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I give all of me,love with each breath I take. When I feel ,I feel with my whole body and soul. Theres nothing I wo… https://t.co/Alk5WgQHhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedSoxRedShoes @b52hbuff @Joe_Rohde I can't, and I have wasted the majority of my forty two years on one bit of nonsense or another.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paper #47 - fascinating paper that points to the near enough unspoken problem with peripheral co-stimulation during… https://t.co/8AGzKqUxWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 Kabay pa nga malinong kag maayo ang kahimtangan sa sulod sang Jerusalem kag sa mabakod nga mga parte sini.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 9 - Toronto Star Morning Headlines:    Doug Ford missed 11 of 18 question periods following the Tave… https://t.co/1yLXnRhmpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to get a donut... A chocolate twist! Who makes the best donuts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[(@ Café Boulud - @cafeboulud_pb in Palm Beach, FL) https://t.co/5jmk67NPhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #marchbreakroadwarriors had a better showing in the 2nd half of the 🏀doubleheader. The #Milwaukee #Bucks droppe… https://t.co/04Vrm0vgSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell Steve Avery - quality veteran pickup...@MatthewSDunnEsq @and]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLW30 @snacks There are many, many people down there who are still fighting there war, either consciously or subconsciously. Sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on the brink of becoming a “morning person”. PST to EST, waking up on 6 hours of sleep, and I feel pretty good. So far...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #TeamFlash on @TheTylt—’The Flash’ is my favorite CW superhero show https://t.co/bDl7hjCqS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actsimpsonian @drinkwhiskey71 @JustinVerlander Agreed the sevice time is a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only reason I follow @AOC is to witness this #trainwreck fly off the tracks.    When’s @RealJamesWoods going to be on the ballet??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably for her safety so the right wing nut jobs don’t get to her.   Also look at you taking a picture of her get… https://t.co/oy03ZjWjPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Seen at #SXSWedu: Love the logo—an anchor designed by a student in transition. Art is a powerful expression of s… https://t.co/TzPf2hN6dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNickAdams @BeBeZaharaBenet @priscillabus @TheBiancaDelRio https://t.co/4u3oPaUZJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMichaelKay Don is like the Beatles when they buried Paul “Don buried Sydney”]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen. this may be the funniest tweet i’ve ever tweeted. it’s quality content.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We going to blame the goalies if we lose this one too? @JeremyWGR @BuffaloSabres @BrianWGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSIHockeyguy Yeah, don’t want to really buy boxes. Also, remember I drive a smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have immediate need for Sr developer and a Sr QA Test Engineer! C# SQL Server stack and Python 🐍 at @AccruentLLC… https://t.co/U3QOsaqLXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@todoDSGSoficial @pablitolescano @cesarcandia1985 @nachitoo_carp @urielsierra76 @dsgssanty @RamidsgsRamiro Hacen envíos a mexico?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was having a great day/life with girls, but the ex-President posting about u, wins forever! 🔵😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smfehir I'd love to comment butt two suspensions in a row @#$%&amp;*()]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the simple fact that I payed bills with last weeks check and forgot to pay myself first. This weeks check I’ll… https://t.co/cmOOgdvXGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteHegseth Lol let’s limit the federal money these stupid states rake in from the blue progressive states and see… https://t.co/kxZCStOIim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howie Roseman on Jason Peters "He's not a normal human being.  He's a freak of nature. He's a first ballot Hall of… https://t.co/5fTVHLAtoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mathematical modeling with real world situations is different than other mathematical activity.  It’s worth highlig… https://t.co/5qrkpPk7PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Future of Software Development https://t.co/LabD3C5mJn via @chadfowler]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand how people only take carry ons for trips... Can you teach me your ways? I’m too indecisive to pack limited 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[And so the journey begins 💖💍 @ Fernandina Beach, Florida https://t.co/7uIqG5HfD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itschrisblt @isaiasrosale_ Nigga what? ...Hayward is literally the heart of the bay 🤦🏿‍♂️😂😂 how y’all from over here n not kno that ?🤧🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel You pathetic pussy fool, if he wasn’t busted innocent people were going to get accused for his lying a… https://t.co/rAZQb969lm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LJSLaw You would have to have things to knock over for no apparent reason, other than, 'just to piss you off'. https://t.co/TvU1tirPJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GameOverGreggy Lack of this has brought legitimate sorrow into my life. It’s something we should all strive for, a… https://t.co/OeOviqo7Po]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissacain1 @pattonoswalt Funny, I’ve seen Gen Xers as benefiting from Boomer policy and a general apathy towards issues in general.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PostOpinions @harrylitman BOSTON MEDIA STARTED AMERICA. HELLO? I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1… https://t.co/8cLDMrM9yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisgregoire10 Have a burger at Burger Bar Crescent for me! Merci Louis]]></document><document><![CDATA[While there’s merits to free 4 year college, but in no way does it solve the student loan crisis. The crisis is wit… https://t.co/IC225s6GVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ki kòb nap tann pou’n peye lekòl pititann? @SamuelSimonis, @HerbyTheCeo edem souple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Life's all about second chances right? Back to our original gate with a new plane, hopefully departing shortly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you’re going through Hell, keep going.” - Winston Churchill, SSR Grade]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump .              Trump trusts Kim Jong Un                  Trump believes Putin               Trump… https://t.co/x2RfRpwbN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleNReed @MarvelStudios @WolverSteve @corrupt_cosplay @20CenturyFoxUK @XMenMovies @XMenMoviesUK Awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'ai exactement le même âge que Bianca Gervais. Le segment #100Watts avec @MACoallier et Bibi me fait rendre compte… https://t.co/zkTidRQxwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoniekZibi @lewy_official To nie koniec...zdazy jeszcze postrzelac zanim pojdzie do Realu...]]></document><document><![CDATA[No question.  Trout is the greatest ball player on this planet right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And once again...my bad luck strikes again. Why am I plaigued with bad luck? Why is everything I touch so complicated?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethSharp35 @allsweaty @markmartin @roushfenway @Valvoline @cegday @imqualifying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikethemiz Wanted to let you know that there seems to be a profile out there perpetrating to be your mother. https://t.co/zRnmmkI1FR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roane County Classic, 2nd place, 3-1 for this weekend, not bad. We have some work to do, but we are getting better! https://t.co/8KAqiS3Evc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 4th Valentine’s together and they keep getting better every year!! Love you Nicole 😍🔥 @ Auburn, Alabama https://t.co/oK71eezAw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBlondeLab Daphne says..., well, not quite yet, but she will. https://t.co/77W4XTHfOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbrog Please check out my blogs at https://t.co/A7jkdmWdnx.  Also, DM me #dok]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best #HipHop playlists on Spotify ! Has music all the way from then 90s to Now and everything in between… https://t.co/qvP5FTQJEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman taught me how to have a good time #internstionslwomensday @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/3KnnxLQK0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UndeadAngel1987 @DoveChad1138 You should read up on the effect of sugar on the brain. https://t.co/7zSABQR4Z6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawn over the National Gallery #dawn #sunrise xt2 #fujixt2 #coldmorning @ National Gallery of Canada https://t.co/uXxiTK6F8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badababa From the very beginning of this country we had federalists and other parties fighting each other, there w… https://t.co/2q7KGjjmA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bourbon Barrel Quad by @Boulevard_Beer @ WaLshington D.C. — https://t.co/T2JZiszGk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from the twins! Amelia and Grayson are stoked! @ Smyrna, Georgia https://t.co/kCZM5JEG3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished the 6 mile race of the miler series with a PR!!! Under 10 minutes per mile.. #indymilers… https://t.co/hevQzDeIzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treywood51 The worst basketball game ever made https://t.co/9TOyDYWFMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melanie_korach When you lead with kindness. The universe awakens new pathways to spiritual enlightenment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Japanese internment was wrong. Why do some of our leaders still try to justify it?: Today, the vast majority of thi… https://t.co/e2urlonySX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport He'll be signing bibles in Mississippi within a fortnight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have to tell us to dress warmly to avoid frostbite &amp; hypothermia MAYBE we shouldn’t be walking to class 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdvanceHumanism @Lily_Bell82 @neithskye @kenserlore96 @WalterGeorge6 @BeccaMarshall12 @skullmonkey7735… https://t.co/L1OEkxb3kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggonzales24 @410JMoney @FootyHipstat @JuMosq It could be, but 5 wins is not a crazy amount of wins. The jags won 5… https://t.co/1vNsxvgAGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump Did you go to hockey camp in Russia? Looks like @DonCheadle got your jersey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else having problems with a MacBook and getUserMedia() on @firefox 65? Successfully capturing the stream,… https://t.co/TL5kRX3ReU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want a jacket like the one @USAmbIsrael is wearing - I would settle for a job working for him at the… https://t.co/XCfgQikgFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[After each round of BP, it's #handstime with heimbuch44 #alwayssomethingtoworkon #nodaysoff @ Saint Charles, Illino… https://t.co/VVAKXNnY2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday was one of the worst days ever but yet I still found Mora than one reason to smile and laugh and Robert made… https://t.co/sN1tnOoTGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 4th and 5th Remembrance....the three before ill, sick, die..... #MarALardass @HouseGOP @SenateMajLdr… https://t.co/COSBFqWBaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: With a couple hours left until poolapalooza, still time to read all about @PIAADistrictXI Swimming 🏊 Champio… https://t.co/JAII3qzvre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Octbers Very Own w/ @StephManescu  #cenzol #losangeles #tgif @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/RONuevkE9t]]></document></documents></author>