<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Good Morning😁 *https://t.co/s88lSmxaKS 👣*eStore Open (24) hours💄 @ Blackshear, Georgia https://t.co/H8hpQgiMM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[These past two days have been so insane in such a good way. My life keeps taking such amazing turns and I cannot wa… https://t.co/0mFNRzxuul]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Oheb Shalom Congregation in South Orange, NJ https://t.co/BNtjZFuq3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Cemar Lo bueno es que ya va a iniciar el beis y ya no lo voy a pelar jajaja ok no]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poshjerkins_ Four loko is more of a nutritional balance just saying...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rustic Wedding in Shawville - Jesse and Krystal  https://t.co/6v2p9FVTk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That?s some laughter right there. Great idea for persuasive writing, Mo Willems has a great website too with lots o… https://t.co/2hCF1MgreC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katlyns2012 I said that about my car too and ate Taco Bell .. now there’s cheese stuck to my seat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has made such huge growth in writing. We couldn’t help but do a victory dance! @SpringRunSTEAM… https://t.co/BRw7JdoZuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police said Hemphill was following a car driven by Brown, Greenlee was the passenger. They said Brown brake checked… https://t.co/X3ae6k17is]]></document><document><![CDATA[They say they've temporarily named it "Braverson," and are hoping to find it's home.   @WGME   https://t.co/6G3CrkLXUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posted withrepost • borderkindness HELP NEEDED NOW! The majority 343/560 of refugees headed to Mexicali are women,… https://t.co/zoHFAparMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[National as temperatures will be low tomorrow night when you leave practice please dress for the weather - no wet t… https://t.co/MCViRARcTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love this team here, or there. I would love this team anywhere! @OutleyE #lunchhourisanhour… https://t.co/Qc3AWuS8vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's celebrate Deku's win with an episode of #MyHeroAcademia on #Toonami PLUS ULTRA!!🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[The image of bare trees can be very soothing. Just as soothing as trees with buds in the spring, lush green in the… https://t.co/i9N6z0fKjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Art to TECH @GinaStartupArt #contemporaryart #artists #showyourwork #abstractart #mixedmedia #artoftheday… https://t.co/f4uXSUWeTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EyeoftheStormZ I can’t emotionally, go there with Colbert. But he needs to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists Have u ever bought a car?  U get a better deal if u walk away.. they always call u back with better offer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today starting at 8am donations get a 50% boost!! Check out my classroom on @DonorsChoose! . https://t.co/7vH7id80dH @Angiebush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarySalcedo Good luck! I know you will be great!! Sending lots of good energy your way! https://t.co/KKcQm7lfXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to meet you @Mmorganofnc, and congrats on your admittance to the #SCOTUS Bar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dropout podcast is amazingly good. I don’t generally take joy in the downfall of others (Trump and crew excepte… https://t.co/3PhpW71dqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of the new Galaxy S10 is the camera. #TMobileTuesdays + #contest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henryrodgersdc @DailyCaller Gotta ban the network that won't give you the questions ahead of time, right. Democrat… https://t.co/giNEwnr3sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thing is, his dad wanted us to burn it cause he was tired of looking at her shit in his house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re all Targets 🎯 now because of some idiot that thinks he’s all big and bad because he’s a cop 🚓 but that wasn… https://t.co/uomLfUYdiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstichweh @WorlowDennis @RepMarkMeadows https://t.co/qttPJsu4Au I’m pretty sure these are not fake. Please view it… https://t.co/ayjEp4xHSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GloriousApricot @StephenKing In case you didn't know "It" was fiction and Trump is our insane and scarey reality!… https://t.co/EUJPOXsRf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all just a heads up I will be live tweeting the oscars tomorrow so put me on mute if you haven’t already ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaftTheatre I tried...no funtionality...now what do you suggest?  Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevePerryMusic It would be great if you did hang in the studio with me. I think the next time I see your limo I'l… https://t.co/eP4h07SWj4]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF MSM!? Kim Jong Un evicts the press from hotel: https://t.co/YacN88H27t What happens when the press isn't free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoorSquid @steviejlfc2008 @JuuszyJosh @MrFilmkritik And yeah Illinois is broke and we’re not perfect but neither i… https://t.co/b4cxAgd5Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe @Nien_Nunb @phillamarr @SamuelLJackson https://t.co/p2l5JTt9bJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, crew!! Since I missed Minecraft Monday, would y’all be interested in an extended afternoon stream on Thursday… https://t.co/uNOZybMia0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeasonneRose @Scott479 @ben_techpro @Cameron_Gray @TMZ @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @SpeakerPelosi @AOC… https://t.co/dj1CTK7CxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymusicfriend My face most mornings resembles a bulldog. Thanks, Morty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TuesdayThoughts Try  listening you may learn something new. https://t.co/ND0lNfgTro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC someone has to scream louder then trump today and block him out! I say you anchor nude all day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Well they might realize the truth, this emergency has been created by you! Where are the children?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SNLDREAMS @KellyannePolls Bullshit.  He stood there while Phillips tried to intimidate him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PR Summit (@ KTVK 3TV, KASW CW6, https://t.co/t5QI8ZClhr in Phoenix, AZ) https://t.co/jIS8Gl4cOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Spotlite #Music I released a new song, "Ex Factor", my username is buttapecan757, please download Spotlite app and… https://t.co/l9SHEeMVgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m working on a drawing and I added the palm tree from cold in la to it and it turned out better than I expected😳 https://t.co/5WYhVOiHOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheClassyHippie is living #lowwaste #noclutter - Find out how in this @CharlotteFive story https://t.co/v96HiYNNBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Selwood85 @cajegroup I think it might be a seagull. They swipe your food if you aren’t looking and poo on you even… https://t.co/hES5M9DvHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corinna_cohn @HRC @stonewalluk They are listening - they just don’t agree.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me talking to my American friends and then a west African friend shows up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[whoever’s idea it was to schedule a mandatory meeting this morning at 8:45 and then have me working till 2am is fucking psycho 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuslimIQ @sjyellehS @mkraju I’m screaming-loudly (is that redundant?). This is painful. Thank u for calling this o… https://t.co/nCtfGrE0HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentMTiberi @churchofstacey Yes!   We alternated between pizza Friday and Pagach Friday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I played the “I can take a 5 min nap before getting up for my 8 am” game and ended up sleeping through the whole thing...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine my disappointment when I got to work and realized it’s only Wednesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson This has to end. How dare these bullies think they can yell and intimate anyone for supporting our Pr… https://t.co/07Gn4dGe3R]]></document><document><![CDATA[harold and the purple crayon was the most creative show of all time. that’s all thanks for tuning in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper @RJellyman @CoronadoBrewing @JonMontag @lhtetrick @Jagoff33 @cellmavin @scottydog57 @blofmitten… https://t.co/rlox4C4SK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr It requires no effort to make any Trump, or any Trump supporter “look bad” that’s who you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stall in front of Bowman is empty, right? So there’s no reason for him to pit like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[$495 round trip tickets to Thailand. Who the fuuuuck is coming with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjolinor @RealSaavedra I do not know the man personally, so I cannot speak to his medical background.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Plus Karma is a mother F@#$ when your notfrom therebut you trying2 become something you not I like… https://t.co/y4Xgxunyjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieFire @LRPow79 @nicole_staal Having never been through one or been granted to special clearance to attend one… https://t.co/1O9WLeucsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliatijerina Jajajaj yo vi el “get well”, apenas empieza lo sabroso de la movie en esa parte 😍😍😍 pd. Amo a phil tmb ajajaja 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MerrillLynch No way was I going to wait until 70 to retire. SS just wants you to work until you die. Then they don… https://t.co/fc7Mrnucwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[HR 1 #ForThePeople is a transformational piece of legislation for our democracy. It has is passed in the House: https://t.co/ZNGrmtplVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir @VrobyG Customer service said my bag would be checked over to my new connecting flight so I don’t tech… https://t.co/Fo8X7J0MWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[MIDO Eyewear Show!!! One day in Milan！🥳 We are here:Hall 7 C02 https://t.co/zLFenP9V9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was upset and Sam put on my favorite song just to make me happy even though he hates it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg @RuPaul @RuPaulsDragRace how weird is it that I want you to follow me back so every thursday we can DM ea… https://t.co/bkDjbEEfLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sparks joy!  I am still working on the first category of my KonMarie journey.  I listened to the audiobook and… https://t.co/wslXPpyFVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathbernier @ieVincentDemers donc il faut harmoniser le mode de rénunération ... tous les intervenants à salaire?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bike trail looked like this today, the sidewalks have same amount of snow but are grey with sand that got kicke… https://t.co/LCjkLF5Wxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#texasstatecapitol #austintexas with #mydaughter #anjimirandacatalla #photocredit #mysoninlaw #godwincatalla… https://t.co/Cryg3DNmHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Foursquare (@ Weather Up for Foursquare's 10th Anniversary Party in Austin, TX) https://t.co/6UqnpJK6dX]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate ordering products from ny based companies that don’t have storefronts because they neverrrrrr ship from in s… https://t.co/WcEdebLwji]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you normalize the conversation around FMLA to care, it will help all people see the value of time off during people’s lifecycle.” #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gwenda honestly I am not saying I have POWERS but I might have an “unobtanium fairy” 🧚‍♀️ (it’s amazing how full r… https://t.co/rnKEyd6891]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit with my Niece &amp; Nephew...love u miss you guys. @ Huntington Beach, California https://t.co/0WwFMJCiIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlekzPacheco @7eleven Hahahahah oh my god that’s so crazy how ignorant of me to assume everyone has been to 7-Eleven 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Crist nailed it -- things you NEVER hear people saying at the airport. 🤣 #destinationweddingphotographer… https://t.co/PdKYKLGNS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shut up, shut up, shut up.  Idiot doesn't even come close to a description of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes Has anyone used these wonderful paper straws??  You must drink fast before it collapses!!  These straws… https://t.co/CNgSEuhaOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le entregué una carta a mi novio y cuando la leyó se puso a llorar, no supe que hacer. Lo amo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anothe towering development not yet topped off. #newdevelopmentnyc #residentialconstruction  #nycrealestateagent @… https://t.co/ItvAnsNZbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They don't have to look hard to find your dirty deeds! You old liar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twins Getting his autograph in 1987 when they played the Oakland A’s. ❤️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHochheiser @gary_houchens Is there one model that is better for all kids? No. But there r plenty of children… https://t.co/Yqnn3FMLJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing is where is he drawing the funds from? California would be one. And any disaster fund. His wall cost grow… https://t.co/4rUXvt0xyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_QuettaCannonYo @avskrys I’m never commenting on another post on here again 🤦🏻‍♀️😂 &amp; thank you! Lesson is learned! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seungseungs The microphone birthday gift seemed like an excellent fic prompt...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris i got an email that you were going to ne here in Miami. i had really believed in you. The cheapist ti… https://t.co/ztAdX6a4Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ex_ZACH_ly @CarlzMossberg Um rewind your statement— YOU ARE NOT KEEPING THIS UNTIL RACE DAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[El sector obrero recibe al Presidente @lopezobrador_ con una añeja y justa lucha.  Los trabajadores tenemos una alt… https://t.co/lxqR2SNtrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8gUH4BbBHN #OneOfAKind #Designer #ArtToWear #Jewelry 941-313-1760 Available in #Sarasota #Florida… https://t.co/n2jPfeatBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nofalloff @seanhannity No. Wearing a shirt does not disrespect the national anthem. I just pointed out how leftist… https://t.co/NPlcPvpKWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got a double whammy today and I’m SO excited!! Two papers from our lab are ‘in press’ for the book series, Me… https://t.co/H2Ii4j9Qx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[To dance is to be out of yourself. Larger, more beautiful, more powerful… This is power, it is glory on earth and i… https://t.co/feHlmu1oVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlamaria97 @ashheeeeeee we had some conversations about this 😂 literally makes no sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @BostonLogan International Airport in Boston, MA https://t.co/ym6HSaRgJZ]]></document></documents></author>