<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Lakers Home Game #31 Playoff push, let’s go!!! #LakeShow #Lakers #LakersSTM #NBA https://t.co/NCW2TSbi8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning on @WJCLNews - I’m sharing how you can say your final goodbyes to Beaufort County teen, Malik Spencer.… https://t.co/NVxB4C9AO9]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches be having a shit load of hw and end up doing everything else instead of doing their hw. I'm bitches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone calls you out for manipulating a quote and you turn into an teenager running an anon account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We 💕 our bi-monthly quotes in the teachers’ lounge. Thanks to @MsBarbour_SEES and Ms. Tilitsky for keeping us motiv… https://t.co/1gnJAAuHfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Murderstorm117 @davidscottjaffe Vita’s major flaw is L2/L3/R2/L3 being mapped to rear touchpad, making most games that use them awkward af.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDziadulewicz James thank you for the follow. I am honored. Now following you MAGA 🇺🇸🔥✅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Theisen's in Dubuque, IA https://t.co/3HDsIveSSR https://t.co/U96BsXXsPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starlounging @IndivisibleNet @goldendebbie I think you can bet on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarWarsJedinyt You have an amazing room. I ran out of space my stuff is in boxes. Have some in glass cases like m… https://t.co/Es1FGagJQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jezza doesn’t quite get the concept of being sick. For the last hour she’s been placing toys next to my head and pulling back the bedsheets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#battle #Assyria #elam #tiltuba #relief #britishmusuem #2700 #years #old  #tvwriting #screenwriting #amediting… https://t.co/Gemjg809fM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like the one person I want to be alone with. hates that idea. I feel like I miss someone, who can go without… https://t.co/EBZkkk8MHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KnockKnockMyDadsDreamforMe #DanielBeaty  #literacymatters #imagesmatter #marchisreadingmonth https://t.co/NyRyvQFQly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyCWaldon @Haudricourt Labor of love and I would have gave anything to be one of those guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7: I have accepted a challenge from @HFtrack_field to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no review… https://t.co/KBlaVRIsv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s all I do is take heads baby 😈👍🏿💰💰💰💰💰 @PUBG @PUBGpartners @PUBG_Support @ESLPUBG @PUBGMOBILE @PUBGEsports… https://t.co/xihDExvh6E]]></document><document><![CDATA[After super storm Sandy, NYC billed FEMA for damaged vehicles. Many of those vehicles were inoperable long before S… https://t.co/Dm7zgoGCT8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And such as do wickedly against the covenant shall he corrupt by flatteries: but the people that do know their God… https://t.co/j9KNujpxqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KMLE1079, any chance you can play @KipMooreMusic new single “The Bull” today. https://t.co/2RqoLMbOBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romani 8:5-8  Conferenza Episcopale Italiana    5 Quelli infatti che vivono secondo la carne, pensano alle cose del… https://t.co/50f9uB3ulq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smalltownandrew @PGutierrez630 @SenWarren Sounds like total BS,I would say he is a one cent  ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill “DOJ and DHS were separating parents and children at the border pursuant to the Administration’s new polic… https://t.co/8cCU1WSXvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiglyCnsrvatari @RAVerBruggen @ronanfitz22 @HMBroughMD @Quillette I’m a little more favorable. It’s a serious atte… https://t.co/Y5kNIanHMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abisexy1212 @qtzu1 Definitely beautiful! Defiantly perfection she defiantly is!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harry1T6 @KurtSchlichter @EllenPage no, her activism for HER cause knows no bounds. She will not own a mistake in its wake...sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current view from Ernst &amp; Young in Times Square. @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/sASVbwBKtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul And of course all of the corruption is just over the top #govtshutdown #replacecongressAI2030 #CORRUPTION… https://t.co/sznDQeupMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stacy9Allie Personally, I’m a fan of a traditional English breakfast and a pint of bitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity McCabe isn’t the only tat that should be prosecuted, But who will do it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is it ok for some dudes to be openly gay but, others are banished to hell if they speak on it? It’s because Chi… https://t.co/zH2iCOxOvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerrellMapes @ChefStefaniak Cause those are the two that i feel like I don't know what would happen, plus I would… https://t.co/ZP07mz37DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love when the hellhounds in our household GO TO WAR when the doorbell rings. 👂🏼🐺 https://t.co/FxYf0z9hTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shalomshuli Wow that would annoy the fuck out of me if I had to put up with that shit every commute home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepNotion2 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Disgusting disgusting behavior and stupidity. https://t.co/CogPIwzIcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Service Project at 2am, why not? #MoonlightMadness https://t.co/3yPzWRqCZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously Ray Perry needs help executing his duties.  Maybe the county commission could reallocate some of that hel… https://t.co/fwvb8DEh43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenwlee Nice!!! I will be just missing you. Going to Disney tomorrow and then flying out on Monday. Enjoy! Came fo… https://t.co/lLPJwhIEwf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevfromideal Something that has been talked about for along time. It’s real now. This is fixing to be a fun run!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smitjeff @haltom_david @ColoradoGirl2A @AOC I'll take your word for it.  I went to a STEM University. Can hardly w… https://t.co/OuKXiXhaAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my newest favorites are from @KevinOGarrett and @JamesTWmusic 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love wins.   And now abideth faith, hope, charity, these three; but the greatest of these is charity. 1 Corinthi… https://t.co/nY6JAU2L8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see all the @Bharper3407 jerseys down in DC this year #natitude]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySaturday @MsAbigailMac @KissaSins @Iamcassbanks @xaidrafoxx @KarlaKush420 @ArianaMariexxx @XNicoleAnistonX… https://t.co/n5dFgoC122]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone here able to give me singing lessons? If so, here are my terms...  1.) I refuse to pay for them.  2.) Under… https://t.co/OPBDPntXJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pinero_SCN Lol they don’t mention his dives ever, they’ll deflect that too. Felt so sorry for Emery yesterday. Tha… https://t.co/JwFp8CeDAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindamyers56 @JGardenofEden I couldn't remember if they were on probation for hookergate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[so aside from spongebob at the palace, summer is the only bway theatre with the marquee of a prior show still up 😔 https://t.co/FmNPtBfvLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaydee_tweets Them ugly ass wildly done brows vs perfectly blended brows. When a fill-in is needed lol. Haven't mastered the weave yet lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[While I am enjoying @RamboDonkeyKongas Beta, Ryan Hurst will always be Chick Hogan from Bates Motel to me... #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get nasty with the lifting... gonna get swoller than a mother fucker. Nobody anymore to please except myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever pays more than 140$/oz is retarded lol I can get 26-28% thc bud for 90-120$. And most bud around here is about 15-20%.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In these days #Yosemite NP is the background of a show that comes once in a year: water become fire! So my memories… https://t.co/2BQaVpzE6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Perry, 'Beverly Hills, 90210' and 'Riverdale' Star, Dies at 52 From Massive Stroke, R.I.E.P, Bro. Luke Perry.… https://t.co/N0YEXnvYIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow y’all really bout to watch 6 yard y option routes for 16 weeks again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi This note is LEgal. GATHER for All debts public And privAte TENDER REDNET GATHER REHTAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet @Senators When you can’t get actual people to come to your games...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the Waffle House experience I deserve lmao shawty came up here swingin lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markieee_doe I’m on season 7 currently for the second time: forgot how good season 7 was .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubitz @adamdberry That’s fair. I was just going to add that I assume he lives in the Dominican in the off-se… https://t.co/0L09HKxGHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 2weeks away - Mark lays it all bare ... including O'Bama, Macabe, Rosenstein and the Leakers Mark Levin Audio… https://t.co/6C44VT4pIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corporation behind Dash lays off senior staff as bear market grip tightens via @i_woodford https://t.co/zE0KLFV1yJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sincereBS @IHaveVanished @PattyArquette Thank you for pointing it out ! https://t.co/ec4wXJ3BBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all the snow we gotten in Seattle the last two weeks, United finally celebrating Valentine’s Day with cupcake… https://t.co/8KmEH4kWjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewschueler being all trichromatic - - - - - - -Strangers / @drewschueler  - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -… https://t.co/hgzj7G1f3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malucorona @aguilarcamin @fmartinmoreno No te enredes. Solo contéstame si los bots en redes sociales votan en elec… https://t.co/uRUEhXnFto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlondeScientist Absolute worst..... and a close second is the stationary bike]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no worse way to start my day than Bernie all over my timeline. 😡 Why won’t he go away and knit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[From left:  gregsanchez_4 All time rushing leader Chilhowie football; Bo Dawg, King...period....King; Ty Dawg, All… https://t.co/1NyhzwwuR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Skateland by @columbusbrewing @ On Tap Grille &amp; Bar - Medina — https://t.co/QQGutfvf8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AXSTVConcerts @cheaptrick "Live at Budokan". The 1st record I ever bought with my own $]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AcademyAwards2019 @TheAcademy can’t wait to visit the new museum! #Oscars⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[My top 7 cereals: 1. Cinnamon Toast Crunch 2. Honey Nut Cheerios 3. Reese’s Puffs 4. Cocoa Pebbles 5. Fruit Loops 6… https://t.co/3TeRUQdhmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My entire life is an Adam Sandler movie.   (*Spoken while at TopGolf.)  #OutOfContextAshley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwoodardcp @OrenIShiKiddo @HelenSpade4 The article says the illegals confronted the man, are you Another corporate… https://t.co/NKm0tb0pKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corymorton @AOC Pittsburgh or Austin: pick a side (as the old @StephenAtHome would have said)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCarlsonShow @PurpleForTheWin Well I am gonna take Steussie, Randall, Christy, Dixon and Stringer since that wa… https://t.co/SRaXojuPn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PFOSixers He's playing better than that other guy he sucks so bad right now I can't even remember his name lol it'… https://t.co/uDbd8Bvp8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s one jingle that is forever etched into my mind and that’s nickelodeon’s theme song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou 💯 YES! @MSNBCge @Morning_Joe @CNN @FoxNews all have blood on their hands for helping this #scumbaginchief get elected.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Venezuela_mia_1 @fernando_bum Muchas veces el pasado es mejor que el presente! Ahora, estoy de acuerdo la concienc… https://t.co/pYYNCpsaye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting down to the release of #MakeEmJump documentary w/@rod_strickland Feb. 27th exclusively on our #MyTeams App. https://t.co/tN463tnBGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one bite the dust🇺🇸🙏 @ Los Alamitos Race On The Base https://t.co/v6cJyrYMQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is so stupid but I still love my bughead boyfriend @JasDeStefano 😻😻 https://t.co/Nsh8xPjp44]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @Amtrak Cascades train arrived 10 min early allowing me to connect with the 6:30 @wsferries sailing to Bainbridg… https://t.co/KCNFaSFqcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t write a decent action sequence with unpainted nails.  #screenwriting #writingtips #WritingCommunity… https://t.co/jJ3GI26gg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wo0ski Exactly. The same man who worked with Ray Charles scored the film version of The Wiz and did Thriller and B… https://t.co/mUo8hOJcpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maria94748694 @Asmaa54084716 What a pretty face in your pussy.  Lucky you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Alex Baldwin is great. Get Trump that piece of Fecal Matter out of our White House! https://t.co/jDHOi9IJoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@b1rky Maybe but I doubt it. Baptiste doesn't really scream Grundstrom replacement for me and I don't think they ev… https://t.co/cGMB7g0i9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although we only met a couple of times, he always kept up with me through social media and my writing. Rick was a h… https://t.co/7CPYivWC1b]]></document><document><![CDATA[What good is all the money  If it doesn’t buy time  And what good is being famous  If I’m never on your mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t remember when I completely stopped caring about the oscars. Maybe when March of the Penguins won best doc,… https://t.co/mtU97buXej]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it's time /#youknow  #orlandostate #Cannabis https://t.co/OkO8UQFJ6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Within #capitalism, temptation is ubiquitous, almost given as the only possible option. Within the space infinite p… https://t.co/wCubd35XJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[👍👍👍🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 #FakeTrumpEmergency  #FakeNationalEmergency  #FakeEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Game Day! First game of the 2019 season is finally here! Get out to All City and support your Varsity Angels!… https://t.co/iQ7prFxhMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Razer, I love your products and have traveled all around the world with them.. can you plz tell me why/fix my… https://t.co/Kz1eqKSIdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night.. What a memorable night. @djjasonweiss was absolutley sensational and it was a pleasure to meet s… https://t.co/JlKW54rBS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @realDonaldTrump This is what happens when a bright, but poorly educated, young person is suddenly given… https://t.co/zO1dk8K3gI]]></document></documents></author>