<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So apparently I can’t sign into my own IG account. Don’t know WTF is going on. This is like the second time this we… https://t.co/gi5XW9vXt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyManMyMelo @OnlyInBOS @grovehall Agree! And thank you for the clarification.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningExp Ohhhhhh my gawd.  There would be no restraint on my part hulking out on her. I would GLADLY serve a lil… https://t.co/5HoTc00sDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunrise #sanfrancisco #vintage #architecture #design #retro #sky #blue #hotel #california #wanderlust #deviaje… https://t.co/0YMPJDUeIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyquillisDllwd @LSUbradford @JordyCulotta Baw, That was some good good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squirrelfromMS @markch5519 @finebaum @joelklatt @FredFromPlano @JohnHayes730 you state the obvious about your fami… https://t.co/3TOMnGGKqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/vR3VM2xqXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue line from O’Hare to downtown Chicago $5 and I paid at the turnstile with my watch! (They take Apple Pay) easie… https://t.co/KPovKDMi1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyashaJunior @EshuOcuboro Give them the Lauryn Hill answer. "Whenever my chakra is in alignment"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teri_A_Adams @Zigmanfreud @soccermomTEX Talking about..great. If it doesn't happen, people look like a gossip girl… https://t.co/sL9cZ76iye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews You cannot be the only one speaking these https://t.co/M9wNjInTWD need a choir of like minded Reps and Dem… https://t.co/eZEy5gKHva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BerkeleyDrB Looking Good @BerkeleyDrB Thanks for all your work and efforts on behalf of the children]]></document><document><![CDATA[PG, Charles, St Mary’s &amp; Anne Arundel counties are all closed tomorrow........sooooooooo 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN ALL LA FEMALE COMICS UPSET .@StormyDaniels FOR DOING STANDUP..Want to get even? Come to my house and get into… https://t.co/1U4hbmkvGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great now the Russians have a Kamikaze UAV. @us_sams https://t.co/mUi30qAnSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@popesaintvictor I just finished the first episode of season 2, about the presidential election. That ending, in the subway. 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see so many friends at the @equalityfl gala. What more could I ask for on a Saturday night 😊🏳️‍🌈!… https://t.co/lvWiobSFnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[7am. Winter storm warning in full effect. Kids are hunkered down. Worried roads might be too dry. It’s almost cold… https://t.co/d8Y1HGEQTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBJunkies I predict he will step down and his son take over the ownership of the team. Which, to be honest, actual… https://t.co/9zd2IsZXS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I will not be watching nor supportive of an unfair sporting event so as a word of advice to all wom… https://t.co/oJNDPuxkFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂 yo when I’m with my niggas if ANYTHING bad happens we all say this 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Sabres⁠ ⁠ lines vs #LeafsForever⁠ ⁠:  Skinner - Eichel - Reinhart  Sheary - Rodrigues - Okposo  Wilson - Mittelsta… https://t.co/glbp4Hv1QE]]></document><document><![CDATA[💥INFECTED DEAD BOOKS-INTL Links 🌎https://t.co/qRIA63fi5C… 🌎https://t.co/IC2Xc0yayU…  99c 🌎https://t.co/XGmUhu1KpX…… https://t.co/ns7xkJEpUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vince_wiz @vividiaz1126 1) This country doesn't really understand the history of animosity Latinos have had toward… https://t.co/AQX1EpH9BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rich continue to get richer as we fight over who can be the most politically correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennesseeWaster @RonToye @ForgottenXIV @UnderdogBT @keith_mattingly @marchimark @Rialisms @FUNimation Position wit… https://t.co/WiVyXTuMcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActualGod Without understanding the whole child, I guess you could say they’re just celebrating phenotypical expre… https://t.co/TzqUDaKq2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pandemrbs well right now most of them are designed to take water, flood and hold it during large storm events- the… https://t.co/U8uubmOw13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming back home from SoCal sucks every damn time. Lowkey wanna move 🌤🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristela9 He was built like an 11 year old and sounded like a reject from Jersey Boys...I think they caught on onc… https://t.co/fkdQgmuvFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile #CantHide 45s true colors, a lighter shade of bad! as he’s the worst POTUS ever on policy both for… https://t.co/nztqovtM9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha.... yes it is a #NationalWomensDay theme ride.  #spinning #peloton #FitnessMotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAL___ @JoeBuddenPod @JoeBudden @thisisrory @parksmusic where does Five Guys fries fall into all this? https://t.co/fcNjMjxIKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fingertips (@_MartinWeiss knows what I'm talking about). After game 2 my SD card was full so video cut but the 3rd… https://t.co/7bpvvaKKa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santa Fe Public Schools has won its Education Technology Note special election.  17,024 for, 11,971 against Renewed… https://t.co/fHavFyBPo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerCraigSmith Get a Harley. 25 minutes from the Valley to Marina del Rey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early concepts for the design of a grocery in-store branch for a bank in the southwestern US. - #branchdesign… https://t.co/UBkCON9kVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of #CoachSpeak is not textbook material.  Which makes it all the more awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Conscience4 @BillKristol @tedcruz It's all hog wash, he's complicit with Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gibsonguitar Anywhere there’s an amp, a pick, a stool, a strap, or air]]></document><document><![CDATA[California is know for these amazing tall #trees. 🌴 Sometimes you just gotta look up to see them or at least head t… https://t.co/yXoQKvp4er]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haywood Highsmith played D2 for Danny Sancomb at Wheeling Jesuit. Has terrific shot to be NBA Driller one day. Don’… https://t.co/COvggcrYZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kydizzel As a Mass resident, I’m not really thrilled about Weld running, but he’s rather centrist in his mindset on some things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@indigoonearth @Theresa49439710 @FightTheNewWO @BusyElves @realDonaldTrump Ain’t no way we should accept something… https://t.co/uUAK0jLbyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets go TI!  teamillinoisaaa @2018tigu19 @ MB Ice Arena https://t.co/HitQeJwPJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are you waiting for ?  Just put the cards on the table .you will win]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheekymonky73 @TuckerCarlson Why is anyone who disagrees with your idols a "liberal"? And why are you defending a… https://t.co/d8VtWZNdxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulrdietrich @craigcalcaterra Yeah, if my team hired a cricket player as an advisor I wouldn't be very happy. I t… https://t.co/OkX9WFJ7oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone who knows me knows I would give the shirt off my back to anyone who deserves it. @ Corpus Christi, Texas https://t.co/yrsGB1s0Yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sckit Yeah they get picky if you can't see where your are putting things for some reason lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not quite a defensive highlight for the #txstars. https://t.co/JGtlemsEIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @StatGuyGreg &amp; @Rosenbergradio are we getting a Cheap Heat Live show Mania week?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For me, the takeaway is that Howard Schultz is at a -44 net approval rating among Democrats.  I'm no pro, but I thi… https://t.co/VzOwNFIhP0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When editing and things you’re combining work perfectly together https://t.co/oFPmEiNlki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBirdBattleBorn @Complex hello i also don’t understand nuances of labor force data and I’m a fan of hip hop perhaps we can be frands?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escándalo . . . . . #scandal #escandalo #nadaigual #goals❤️ #likeforfollow #trapstornadores #instavideo feproductio… https://t.co/b3gXIJI25S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge approves lawsuit aimed at halting $500 million Obama museum and library https://t.co/G9QiDcJaIu via… https://t.co/Km9i2OC92Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weight Loss isn’t all it’s cracked up to be, people have started sitting next to me on the bus again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowww_P @kelnplay @dtime850 @TadariusHall yall boys got all the money 🤒]]></document><document><![CDATA[• King of The Trill Pt. 2 • . Asking all my hip hop heads, what’s your favorite song with a Bun B feature? (Leave a… https://t.co/3CXWMoZY2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHowardIII @AdamParkhomenko How does a mamasan “founder” of a brothel chain that she no longer runs end up wit… https://t.co/Nly0hWkDRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JVandercar @paulsperry_ At least until their indictments are unsealed. McConnell is the gasbag I want to see go do… https://t.co/i8JEFgrxvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AvengersNoRoadHome 4 @Marvel how’s tricks, #Nyx? #ZeusEraGothGirl has a story to tell &amp; that ain’t #Bulfinch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress Well you think  a system responsible for the deaths 260 million will work this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#believeandbestrong @ Kernersville, North Carolina https://t.co/pnIWfZorAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @berracahband @lagaviota521 @obrienmaggie17 @pppdreams @DUPONTBLUES @LuckycharmMw @helen19242686… https://t.co/tXFVu70Q2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperFlexDude @_DynastyMind @_JamesTheBrain @amazehayes_ @BleedGoldandRed @SuperFlexJunkie @TheBauerClub @RyanMc23… https://t.co/T9Mmgnm4Gs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #Oscars and have @QueenWillRock songs running on a loop in my head. #WeAreTheChampions #BohemianRhapsody… https://t.co/XIe4vlgwm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTeaz89 @Dee_Beautiful_1 He was acting. He's scared and now he wants a pass because he sang for us for 30 years?… https://t.co/kQ146cWLZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠🏧🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/Sia5XLZEd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trucker_mfc @philkillerlain @FMCSA @USDOT @USDOTFHWA @SecElaineChao @RepBrianBabin @collinpeterson @GregForMontana… https://t.co/HfajiOryKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinzieosborn @Josie_Hannah you guys don’t give me enough credit apparently. 🤷🏼‍♀️ #alwaysthemom]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 21, 2019. On this day of #BlackHistoryMonth aka #AfroLatinoHistoryMonth I offer up Arturo Alfonso Schombur… https://t.co/hTPKsS2DUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya just come to Twitter to be mad at random ass people   Reconsider your life choices please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRogie @MAJTOURE @AppleNews Need you in Virginia - Norfolk, Portsmouth, Hampton, and Newport News.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crazy. 24 for a high on Tuesday and 78 today. No where else but the panhandle of Texas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFCBarstool I know you guys blog about goofy shit most of the time, but I think you could have a serious chance at… https://t.co/eWqvnvVhHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[HB 1 on Joint Transportation Committee and HB 3 on State Port Authority’s authority to issue bonds pursuant to reve… https://t.co/YBXDMoltBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamek97531 @w_stobba @RadioGdansk Szable i kilofy w dlon-POlszewika Gon,Gon,Gon...!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FizzySodaWave @Shellanin If this song greets me after dying, I’ll know all hope has been lost and that I’ve entered hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shathiHoneymony @BWGovernment I just woke up and my eyes ca't see good yest but I THINK I kind of understand what… https://t.co/ICpXcbwON3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only have I not seen my kids in 3.5 and 4.5 months, I CAN’T see them unless I suddenly can afford $100/ an hour… https://t.co/RNQ1UiapYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[En Rep. Dominicana una persona que se destaca, se maneja de manera correcta, cumple con sus deberes como ciudadano… https://t.co/cocRymxDhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissLizz you could rock a sinead o'connor hairdo and still be hot. don't listen to the haters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartchm having some trouble logging in to the site from desktop and mobile. Are there any issues on your end or… https://t.co/AhxH7xqGxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: @PlanetFitness Day 50 #PFfitnesscontest https://t.co/JVw7lzsi1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RravenM @LouisSkondon Really, even without the polls for which people who voted for  Trump said they wouldn't, thu… https://t.co/wRpmXSLU6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte loves to cuddle!  But she also loves to keep up with her brothers and sisters!    Come see this beautiful… https://t.co/gqPEXwrUoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still say unc turns the ball over way to much to be considered a favorite to win the whole thing. Just don’t value the ball enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabineResists @TrinityResists That would be disrespecting his NRA donors if he did. Remember that once in office,… https://t.co/Wh7LJCuO5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eelowan @TheKagneiKing Why do you keep asking questions that you know all the answers too! Fuck You , the mirror a… https://t.co/79UlvQ1JAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump History will remember and be as kind to Trump enablers as History has been kind to… https://t.co/r9bodCpWNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisamurkowski @fema Fund the wall. Protecting America should be your TOP priority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SainAsylum What do you want them to do, take on the NFL head to head?? I am old enough to remember that the USFL h… https://t.co/sS3P6D6JXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royals  Charlie Lau said that there were hitters who had more talent than George Brett,  but Brett out worked them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mlle Mickaëlle Michel @MickaelleMichel and #5 Lavinia Rose ready for race 1 today at Hippodrome de Cagnes-sur-Mer… https://t.co/fXbAYgDU6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Spooner and Erik Gudbranson, the only two ‘92 Ottawa boys to make the NHL, are now on the same team. Cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to leading the music with my students this morning in our 1030 worship service. #aliveyouthfbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davekindigit David what does it take for you to redo my 71 mustang? TKS love your work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again to Jordan at the @Starbucks in @Target, Monroe LA. I fumbled the Cherry Mocha Frappuccino that my wife… https://t.co/x3vjkY0SKU]]></document></documents></author>