<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Went on a random trip to #hearstcastle today. What a stunningly gorgeous day for a really fun adventure. Highly rec… https://t.co/M15GR6K1it]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter just started working at Longhorn Steaks ❤️ https://t.co/JbZujS150Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please Share Follow  Thank You Very Much For Your Interest, In Documents Posted Truth.  #Breaking #America #Macon… https://t.co/HnFxCvmZnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jheil @mmckinnon @SHO_TheCircus I LOVE the show. It gives such an in-depth perspective of today's news. Thank you.… https://t.co/UVrh11rVLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @J_Renaissance Regional Conference at Lakeland Community College with these AWESOME groups of 9th Grade Stud… https://t.co/vpZzqh3aQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great time making kid friendly chili in our Jr. chef class. It was my first time buying groceries from… https://t.co/wXdPgyyt7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took a nap on my lunch break and it was the best decision ever 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest hurdle for parents is finding accessible child care so that parents are able to work or go to school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMessiah29 @TwistNHook This is what Twist does to people. We're all helpless before him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueJacketsNHL Thank you.  Thank you. Thank you!  High intensity game.  Was fun to watch you get that dub over the… https://t.co/nl6U7TDpHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson Exactly. Why does this keep happening? MSM, come on. You’ve got to be better than this. Children are… https://t.co/1J4mlAHmqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryanmexmart @Kaepernick7 @DjToneDef Use it to choke yourself with!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galentine’s Day with My Interesting Lady Friends! @ Broadway Playhouse https://t.co/wXEsp62L2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you say learning??? Thank you LeAnn for coming back to help us learn how to chunk, chew, check change!… https://t.co/XCsXyZ1C02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Reality #ReleaseTheVisas #saveh2b #@realDonaldTrump @SecNielsen @SecretaryAcosta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HokaHeyyy Like and of course it’s a pit mix in Tallahassee chock full of problems - I’m looking at you PARVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay guess I was right 🤷‍♀️ men think they can come at your neck but then they’ll apologize and act like they didn’t come at you. K. Lol no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite person and my favorite food? Sign me up #DBBwithMyBetterHalf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantashman Funny my last name is Tashman. Wonder if we’re related somehow. Not a common last name. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrible view for a morning jog ;). Time to learn more about wastewater management @SCEC2019 😍💧#wastewater #water… https://t.co/X7fvHkls4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I have a crush on someone who doesn’t rave but like a boy about to convert 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CinnyyBuhnn Can you make bomb French toast? Teach me girl lol 😭 I can live without pancakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is this shocking? Get your heads out of your arses! #TheResistance SHOCK REPORT: #Trump AIDES PUSHED… https://t.co/wbwvvRJr5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate no one, no matter how much they’ve wronged you. Love humbly, not matter how wealthy you become. Think positive… https://t.co/Zao3Y5xE3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[A large percentage of the homeless population suffer from a mental illness and that in itself causes issues within… https://t.co/R3xVaVHnf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChantaCombs @RunningNoleFan @OutofConTxts That’s cool. I just thought you hated cottage cheese because of the colo… https://t.co/SxY5Y11wo1]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 30Ave waited for 12 min, countdown clock said train is coming, then delayed, now 8 min. WTF?]]></document><document><![CDATA[tour day #10 the town of Mesilla where Billy The Kid was tried and sentenced to hang. also some cool graffiti. and… https://t.co/H5s0bMQY8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wanna shower but you don’t feel like getting up yet but then your roommate gets in the shower&lt;&lt;&lt; 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[More pictures tomorrow, but, for now, Bravo to this talented team and another fantastic @emulsionpop!… https://t.co/WwMNYacaHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Kingofthepillowmountain #onlydog @ Port Saint Lucie, Florida https://t.co/rPxxRDfDcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre boobs jugs pre 3rd kid and Facebook aka MySpace yo https://t.co/tKObGXERbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom and daughter playing a spelling game on the @MBTA #orangeline is a great way to start the day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I was complaining of the hot ass weather this past weekend while I was at the pool....??????? YEAAHHH… https://t.co/NMRw7CdH4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last post on this look I d k why but this just didn’t make the cut for my insta  Lips prom night mixed with black s… https://t.co/LuWm7BP3XG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @Mr_BarryWard to post 7 covers of books I love--no explanations--no review--just the… https://t.co/ZUCSw4RBtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On anniversary of horrific shooting, Manatee students reflect on year after Parkland, reports @Gsabella with… https://t.co/0E1c0mlU5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenConniee 😭😭 ima fuck around and go back, I’m giving these hoes a try and we will see. I do miss them tho 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justice is not being hand down like it should bet,the question is why. Could it be that someone got to the judge?]]></document><document><![CDATA[EWA high school Public Speaking students reading Dr. Seuss books to our EWAwesome elementary students.… https://t.co/SObxKPrNYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just throwing it out there, can you fuck your cousin’s cousin?? Or is it wrong?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My resolution this year is being open, honest, authentic and vulnerable in my own skin. Here I am with nothing on m… https://t.co/PdAMfwgpEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s something about receiving 6 no caller ID calls in a row at 3:15 AM that has me on edge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacyPSmith22 @lacrossemom5 @NARAL BTW.... that is a great video, I watched it awhile ago. Thank you for posting i… https://t.co/HHfEXk0V5I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristieEverette Lamaoooooo 🤣 i can’t with you but the accuracy.... i be trying not to think everyone that voted fo… https://t.co/i8UOscxZxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m on some got money shit and some get money shit. You wouldn’t understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sunny63166636 @mikeleffingwell I think he’s actually in an ice hut on the lake fishing for walleye. 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The energy and what you can do collectively is ginormous.” 🙌🏼 @ErinBrockovich at #expowest!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is bitter sweet as it's my last day at Comcast Business. It's been an amazing journey but it's time to take a… https://t.co/IDdS2Gl9Mr]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎂Con Sue Photography and Design🍰   🍦Like our photos...Follow our IG 🎂  🍰This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 💖… https://t.co/17mz8TGXEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaileyGoogles23 I wanted to make sure before mentioning that she’s currently waiting to give birth 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate that people use social media as a negative platform. Words hurt. Be kind.  #thinkbeforeyoutweet https://t.co/1X7Bdrn7i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[No other show will top Breaking Bad. That show is a masterpiece, and now they’re making a movie about Jesse and his… https://t.co/HDTD3niDlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #Cold y’all! #brrr lol @ Downtown San Antonio https://t.co/Lia9F04JbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilitaryRosary @johnpmooney @hboulware Bingo. Why don’t people get this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSiriano @BravoTV Can you have a show just of amazing people wearing your gowns? No one else matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A path to defeat Parkinson’s? UCSF team cracks molecular lock to target treatment https://t.co/4Cn9xFQfzs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimikry_ @Restrantek @Cygnusx112 Isn't the standard yellow crane there? Not sure what vehicle they use. Shrug.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNewYork Lmfaooo that is the most New York thing I've ever seen even more than pizza rat deadass!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryknews @imbozimo Also, you, Ryan Chan, and my sister Amy are all at Disneyland today. I challenge you to meet u… https://t.co/KOrtL0tqCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDisneyBlog Magic Kingdom. So many great memories there. Plus I'm a huge kid at ❤❤. Next is DAK. Just love the a… https://t.co/FjmsDwtRlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAW360 @ThomasKlineMD Got me almost a year ago. Thanks for standing by us Dr. Kline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday currently feeling that I’m leaving tomorrow.. https://t.co/N0YMnlDAzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grlsbeersports @kyledatrainer Perennial is great BTW sorry I did not attend maybe next time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ramón Agüero Coach en PNL. Teléf. +584167639203. Forjarse, Purificarse y Brillar…Visión Sin Límites.… https://t.co/mzZIgk5jmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newyork #centralpark #taxi #yellowtaxi #blackandwhite @ New York https://t.co/gp8CghTjkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 1328 Shell Lane #Clayton #CA  #realestate https://t.co/kquL9Dy01M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did I wait so long to watch this clip 😂😂 the meme is 10x funnier now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been doing a great job with leaving y’all niggas exactly where you had me fucked at ✌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have gloves on and my fingers physically burn @zackgreenwx I’m super super over this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse He's a druggie, that's been established.  After No Korea debacle, he looked like a deflated balloon.… https://t.co/Ii6cjrcmQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the more crazy right wing bullshit you guys throw at us (soon to be former) centrists, the more left leaning we… https://t.co/4fLpw6P9eT]]></document><document><![CDATA[No explanation needed!!!!!! #cheflarry #cheflife #foodplug #lillielues #4thstreet https://t.co/BtP3CeR08j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following a terrific debut, @aafAPOLLOS LB Terence Garvin (@T_Garvin28 ) has been named the league's Defensive Play… https://t.co/2LHSLreGE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a wrap for my favorite holiday and the best weekend of the year. Sad to leave, but ready for lent. Happy Mar… https://t.co/EP1UlzgS8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[War Eagle water polo crushed it with 2 wins tonight against Cy Woods and College Park @OakRidgeUpdates… https://t.co/QLuyCZOlxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo um I tried throwing my vans outside to see if they would land right .... and um my dumbass threw it wrong and… https://t.co/mSFswrJh0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Karp group scoop of the week! #KarpRealEstateGroup #NorthShore properties #RealEstateExperts #Chicago #LoganSquare… https://t.co/sbOm04HOjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where was the advance negotiating team a president always sends before a summit? They would have known what Kim's d… https://t.co/jwSknc4QWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of really itching to get some new strings on my violin and start playing again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi I hurt my wrist so badly that I can’t even open my contact case how did I manage to do this and not remember how]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gacupdating Oh wait this isn’t the actual GAC page. But I am so sorry about your dog/ fur baby. I have 3 dogs and… https://t.co/2ZW0aZhh4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg...now that’s better than any pop tart I’ve had! @castor_gran homemade pastry. Visit them and all the other rest… https://t.co/YA3aY7XiO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone pls send my mans some good luck thoughts, vibes, prayers, or whatever else today and tomorrow while takes the bar 🙏🏼😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexandriahovis @magentajeep @Missey_96 For some reason they didn’t pop up the first time lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna just delete all my social media. I mean, what’s the point? All it does now is make me feel bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlejandraMerli1 @RealJamesWoods The press does not care about a house not burning]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you are becoming a backend engineer and like it. #php #dev 🤷🏽‍♀️🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #CelebrateAbortionProviders because they have to put up with bs “ parades” that only harass women.… https://t.co/dKDubJInfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottdharvey @bonaevolentatis @MENA_Conflict @SkyNetDirector Those are clearly a men’s tactical schmedium.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PgGomez10 Espérate que entres a la facultad y todos absolutamente TODOS te pidan que les hagas tacooos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saturdayvibes #bigplanstoday🐋🐬🐟🦈🐠🦑 #letsgetthisdaystarted #coffeeismyfriendtoday☕️❤️ @ Taylors, South Carolina https://t.co/xT9wYlqXYf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am seriously devastated that I seem to have lost the last Valentine gift from my dad (from 2011). #RIPDad #MyFirstandLastValentine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #Tuesday #5amwritersclub Let's be productive today and #write our little hearts out. Or, if you're like me, b… https://t.co/W6M965dpmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shecanncannabis @Shuk_It_Trebek @ChimeraGenetics @AlexTheChemist @AnandiaLabs @trikomes @BeardedGreenly @DabGooLay… https://t.co/7CPcuMGb5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelScumPixie @TheSWPrincess @HouseDemocrats Please allocate funds and insist on a secure election in 2020 by req… https://t.co/DEau9dYW0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeap! I’m with all the action baby so @ me or slide in my DM ‼️ if you not gone do that then stfu facts]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Got this 😎😎 #hustleon #Analytics #B2B #BelieveInYourself #rockyobiz https://t.co/GRYT4zaHvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vote #bapnotes #sacramento #supportlocal #jazz #livemusic #sammies #boombap @SacNewsReview https://t.co/9iwN5AHzOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please! If you reside in Denton and have any thoughts positive or negative on the new ways to recycle please DM me… https://t.co/diY2yKKxJZ]]></document></documents></author>