<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.  @CISAgov makes #IT &amp; #Cyber centerpieces of National Emergency Comms Plan - https://t.co/YweOAiN2oh via @Nextgov]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cough once in the middle of the night and my mom wakes up paranoid that I’m smoking in my room]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to reggae as I study brings back memories from summer 😇 can’t wait for those sunny beach days!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCoronell @Univision @jorgeramosnews @NicolasMaduro Así lo hagan. Nada se gana cuando se habla y se actúa de esa m… https://t.co/fpJ17Lk38I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@regardlyss @ArianaGrande Omg you’re amazing I just looked it up and it hasn’t said anything about it changing dates]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I know that if I checked Twitter @bigunclepooh had already tweeted about the earthquake? Guy has a 6th sense for that 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Brace yourself, it all goes down tonight”💪🏼⚡️ • [🎥: aweavmx on Instagram] https://t.co/EUr22QJmpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother of a Louisiana high school student arrested after posting video of two students fighting to social media.… https://t.co/NJyidWENad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Monday, Feb 25 @ 8 PM Eastern, CNN will host a Bernie Sanders town hall. Glad to see the corporate media givin… https://t.co/GlrKGuWUXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz Cumpleaños 🎂 #5 a mi sobrinita querida. #AriannaBehm esta llena de sorpresas, aquí en esta foto con su Papi,… https://t.co/OcPVcbdPFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fernand77190 .... 😅 antojos peligroso, nunca imagine que llegáramos a tanto. 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yo_Ashbo Oh shoot I thought I was the only one late to the party my bad. But yes I’m distraught! But confused beca… https://t.co/a5PUYT8FY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day – 74 Pics #mirth #lol #smirk #comic https://t.co/IT6OHTQXw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leslie_Lopezzz @brandon67196027 We will! Hopefully getting him within the next hour! We are so ready to be back home and show Mav! ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfdubiner I appreciate the tag but leave me out of your Dylan Kelly shipping. That’s just pouring salt on the woun… https://t.co/pu91zeKGTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyWrestling @JustinThomas97 @RamboDonkeyKong Yes. That’s it 👏🏾👏🏾He died in prison taking on like 4 guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 810 Oak Grove Road #96 #Concord #CA  #realestate https://t.co/ZNY75oNzVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to make this a Twitter rant but he’s also just one of those professors who makes you feel comfortable in your s… https://t.co/oponGOYYUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer Oh really! Maybe you have amnesia. You act as if the PCs are lily white. Famous for blowing things to… https://t.co/01vf6gE77W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets He's tone deaf on women's issues and race issues.  He knew of Russia's attacks on Hillary and on the… https://t.co/NDXJ8u40FI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IWILLREJOICEINTHELORDILLTAKEJOYINTHEGODOFMYSALVATION🙏🏼♥️☦️☝🏽☮️ #FAITHFILLEDFRIDAY💥👩‍⚕️🌅💯  #MUCHLOVE♥️❤️💖💞💟 @ Angol… https://t.co/9fElKoSwrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Assistant Route Service Sales Representative (4 day workweek) https://t.co/QodKPUEywy #cintasjobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[ima be real real real real real real honest. I got some real real real real real real problems.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @nytimes @realDonaldTrump @BreitbartNews https://t.co/53MnQLxoTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[bc who doesn’t love baby goats @ Highlands County, Florida https://t.co/oQLSc2T4bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the restaurants on seamless that update their minimum order for delivery $60+ when it’s a blizzard. I… https://t.co/NuZGRKbYZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieFarber @AndrewScheer @NDP If scheer doesn't deal with this dolt. Then he will wear the mantle of hate into the election]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday again and again to my boo @rashauna_alyse! Tonight was so beautiful 😍 and so lit 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to spend the day learning at #trendigitalsf https://t.co/CBPY5V9Mqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[La morra es 0 agraciada y no es x ser mala pero es la vrd Y TODAVIA tiene mierda en el cerebro, no ps ni como ayudarte]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insert in depth conversation currently taking place over Cassie’s heart and what’s best for both parties.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValerieBaxter76 @ImabitcSumtimes @FoxNews  That's why I don't watch any award show! Also the View should be taken off the air!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody: Courtney at a party: 👁       👁                                          🥛       👃🏻        ✋🏻     🏐    🥛🥛… https://t.co/Z9j9AkKnd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grgbkr37 @shortlady42  Val just had to share this upbeat quote to help us fight radical zombies. 😂😂 🌴😎🌴  🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlaCaRapid Hay directeur non soxla naniou la ba si kanam !! Bayil lolou !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!!!! Some people just don't care about others only themselves when its convenient for them!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For some reason my station did not show #YR today. Does anyone know why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I let my little sister cut my hair into a lob with kitchen scissors in my moms bathroom. That was a dark time for e… https://t.co/tMRaPkrlE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so shocked and saddened by the sudden passing of #LukePerry. What a loss for our world. Sending lots of love to his family and friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey just put your sweet lips on my lips, we should just kiss like real people do]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also: “supposedly” not “supposably” “especially” not “expecially” “I saw” not “I seen” https://t.co/jtDUzTWJFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I learned a thing or two in criminal justice it's don't get in trouble with the law! https://t.co/ihGfdRcMrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Questions have been raised about whether I know of direct evidence that Mr. Trump or his campaign colluded with Ru… https://t.co/KijZvJebUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robshealofty @AnnaSimile @SeanCLofty @emmalizrader Better get on it old man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianmele Hey, at least you didn’t break an ankle, right? Just don’t miss work because my mornings are never the… https://t.co/rrYSChvHhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay #igquiltfest ‼️ Here’s my Quilt room. If I was making any $$ I’d probably call it a #studio. 😜 One of my favor… https://t.co/aRTTy9Ll9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dog #sandwich #dogsofinstagram @ Caliente Tropics Resort https://t.co/kFd7cTqfBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted the challenge from @MsAngelaGriffin to post the covers of books I ❤️. No explanations, no review, j… https://t.co/9uJz9XTTBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biobellrocks @BrelandSteward @kriscoop80 You're darn right he is and that is okay! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an emotional game!  Fantastic job gentlemen. @WCSTUCO @ChrismanBears https://t.co/RKlT8ZNkpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's pretty shitty that I had someone lie to me about having a family emergency so they couldn't attend my shower b… https://t.co/bzq73gmH8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my sisters &amp; friends don’t do this when I get married I’m gonna riot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Norway Deals a Blow to an Oil Industry That's Quickly Losing Friends https://t.co/6lQG3swfrw via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tweet got 2 likes but the Facebook post got nearly 8,000 reactions, a cosmopolitan article and an official stat… https://t.co/RuxMl8Bh1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pizza 🍕 for dinner 🍽 along with Sweet Mango 🥭 Habanero Chicken 🍗 Wings. (@ The Hambly Residence in San Jose, CA)… https://t.co/ypvRh2OU84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next stop: the popular #PitBossBBQ yes, the brisket is yummy but you gotta try the smoked wings and these tasty, cr… https://t.co/Xex9Sh0kpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[the DJ channeled Timmy Regisford tonight and it inspired me. Shelter was for the dancers 👯‍♀️ #LATings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoundationWohl was in restricted status up until about 10 minutes ago, at which time I was able to see the message… https://t.co/knYO8nCNY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[i know valentine’s day is long gone but i’m still looking for love...👞❤️ https://t.co/qMycnZ1oX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian @KKWFRAGRANCE y’all sending out false hopes and spam emails ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope y’all have a great Thursday and a wonderful weekend! It’s supposed to be 83 here Saturday! https://t.co/8hplDpREMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like newborn babies, crave pure spiritual milk, so that by it you may grow up in your salvation, https://t.co/G5bOAOEI13]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s closer than it appears, reach and continue reaching until everything is in your hands. It’s worth it!!   #IMIN… https://t.co/MmmbQiV5Rw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlicityDreams Apparently the FBI thought the leather jackets were part of the GA suit and confiscated them. 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauraWest Time is flying by &amp; realized it’s next weekend! Yay!! Long time coming😁😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippeReines @JoyAnnReid I missed you? Damn it. I never miss your appearances.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Axxess Diamond Sponsor  #Cazton Software Developers Conference #MVPMix https://t.co/9n4OVLgxr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLawrence @OversightDems LMAO wow a convicted liar and forged is accused of being liar, how dare they accuse suc… https://t.co/KozG5CzR5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard the name Bertha and I had a flashback to the many Bertha Bus rides I had to endure. #Scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a first generation college student from poverty, student loans covered living expenses even though college was p… https://t.co/i40NjKhNbE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no quieria regresar pero bueno estoy en NJ 🙃😞 https://t.co/PIKajKBre6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy This woman is trash and I will never know why she was invited back. I do not watch the program simply because of her]]></document><document><![CDATA[home from work 💕😭 a lil tired inwanna clean but i kight have to do it later i’m feeling sleepy 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are blessed to experience Taylor’s positivity. She also has an amazing sister Stef who loves her and pushes her… https://t.co/AApWyKtARD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linda_lindylou @RepJoeKennedy The senate has no more power than the house. The three branches are equal in power.… https://t.co/8fN1RKG2kM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@equitymatters77 @markusgarvey @cspanwj @alaynatreene @axios @JonathanTamari @PhillyInquirer Comey refused to tell… https://t.co/v1tDacZt2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great remix of a great beer! - Drinking a Christmas Bomb! by @Prairieales @ Doubledecker  — https://t.co/aDw2gIjL1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staying in tonight? Check out my friend @spencerlocke I’m her new Netflix movie!  Bound to be great with her in the… https://t.co/jx9PvOPWgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moniquetoolegit @amairany_mcc @RollingLoud No dead ass 😂😂😂 this expensive ass trip . Will be worth it tho !]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Peeking Peak”  #pentax @PENTAXIAN #pnw @WTA_hikers #dirtyharryspeak #SoNorthwest #washington #cascades #snoqualmie… https://t.co/ZVIc1JTDBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Big Congratulations and best wishes for a wonderful life full of love and laughter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bvbsoldier1714 @rceracreations @blackveilbrides @andyblack @ccbvb @JinxxBVB @JakePittsBVB @AshleyPurdy Looks aweso… https://t.co/4nrd3R9awk]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Oregon man who survived five nights stranded in the wilderness in deep snow with only Taco Bell sauce packets fo… https://t.co/4eTzP3ffV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squeevening Yep. $65 dollar check. And I was already having a bad day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodfellas is the issue since I prefer to be Asia and they make it an issue if you are Iridh, you can't be made eve… https://t.co/qzfVnoh0rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s some facts and it’s some situational statements in those last 3 tweets.. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[His words are so silly though as I am always proud of a kid who has survived so much by age 20 -losing a Dad to bra… https://t.co/hLOhqkHvoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at I-805 &amp; I-5 &amp; 405 North »Los Angeles bound! in San Diego, CA https://t.co/TdZTYLUj4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got my purple shampoo in my eye and it hurts worse than anything I’ve ever experienced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Anything lost can be found again, except for time wasted. A vision without action is merely a dream. It’s the acti… https://t.co/JZhuRxmSCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presidential Primaries to Feature New Debate Format, @NLIHC Works to Keep #AffordableHousing on the Agenda https://t.co/JLcBLkfaI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachASharp Congratulations Queenie! Continue to work hard now so that you can play hard later @trinjayy💪🏽🏀⚔💙❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC - I have a love-hate relationship with you. Late winter, all I want to do is flee your noisy, dirty, crowded as… https://t.co/UUA4uVSXVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[H18THBD Mary Ann‼️🎉💚👏🙌💜It’s Mary Ann-Fest today‼️ #makingpeoplesmile #beyondepic #shes18 #18thbirthday… https://t.co/3szTkNVc1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #slowandsteadywinstherace #morningmotivation #positivevibes #positivethinking #positivevibesonly… https://t.co/B0nQ9NtDjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshhBedford Do I want one with a window to watch my toast? Idk https://t.co/YWelwSrGZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaysenTSpencer Thank you! Excited about the opportunity and working alongside some great leaders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust in the LORD with all your heart and do not lean  on your own understanding. https://t.co/t5FKiWwCzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just out of curiosity: What is the point of the popcorn button on microwaves? Follow up question: Is there any micr… https://t.co/3Tz6Je9KsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant believe some ppl still believe that others are "doing better than them" bc of posting "happy" pics on social… https://t.co/4dYwvIvS0P]]></document></documents></author>