<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TampaPD oh, officers.  I told New Jersey state police just before I made a wrong turn so Angel's had to build me a… https://t.co/WxzlotscqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 It’s going down a dangerous road that the next democratic president can do with gun violence or clim… https://t.co/ZztxtCUBVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cgoody98 @Bassettthejet @YazeedAbdelhaq @jetsfan24x7 I already framed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEJARE ESTO POR AQUÍ Y ME MARCHARÉ LENTAMENTE  A 😴😴😴🌎🌍🌏 .!!!!!!!  SUBIÓ MAYWETHER 🥊🥊🥊🥊🥊🥊🥊🥊🎤🎤🎤🎬🎼🎹🎤 @papasecreto 📡📡📡📡… https://t.co/oOnMPq78KW]]></document><document><![CDATA[John 11:25-26 (CSB) 25 Jesus said to her, "I am the resurrection and the life. The one who believes in me, even if… https://t.co/0wvHGQYZyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioMocciaNMSU @KTSMtv @SusyKTSM @PistolPetes1888 @NMStateAggies https://t.co/3jVE7bqnQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elspeth_f @runnersworld Wrong. I’ve owned many pit bulls, none were aggressive. Don’t make statements based on con… https://t.co/6U0djJ5T1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjstaebler @heidi_weigand 65 and 56 throughout. 56 &gt;&gt; 11. Not sure what 56 means.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FriarGal Great minds! It trips me out hearing his name being called by @Mudcat55 and @DonOrsillo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you Mama. She never taught me how to live without her. ❤❤❤ @ Gwinnett County, Georgia https://t.co/BZm8Vxh7p7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leedership I believe #trust building begins with #intention.  If I seek to create trusting relationships instinct… https://t.co/toguQs2Qq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 28th can’t get here fast enough. I’m ready to see that Borderlands trailer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanNormanJosh #WhatIf 🤔 you had me at #curiosity 🧐⚡️🔥 🙌🏽👏🙏🏽! #leadupchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fla_panthersnhl A fraction of a taco for a fraction of an effort on the ice. It fits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimkiely Hi Jim, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy       Kind… https://t.co/NCc7o8UAHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hsimon62 No thanks, underachiever who’s injured more often than not. We have to get bigger at wide receiver. We al… https://t.co/ubSXigBt1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two K's for Liebelt, 15 Golden Eagles have been rung up on the day.  We go to B8, maybe Garth can get the bats goin… https://t.co/3pmErhmaBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmknox @AiG Yea, I'm wondering why, if we take the Creation narrative literally, @AiG didn't bring up the Hebre… https://t.co/1RSmzHlBU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TeriGRight ,,, It’s about time you get your hands dirty, what’s it feel like doing an honest days work ,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nonpolar water balloons pop when sprayed with nonpolar #limonene from an orange peel. However, the polar helium-qua… https://t.co/vKRDzaQNoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We need some fresh meat for you to tear up in the debates, embarrass with the size of your rally's… https://t.co/uHzhrCc6Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcTague3 Good Night.. hope you have a better day tomorrow.❤️❤️❤️ https://t.co/bg3sLQMFvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When are instagram and twitter going to do the right thing and let you play music on your profile like MySpace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexcrudolph one thing i deeply rue about this whole affair is that it gives netflix a chance to appear populist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes and the media is spinning it as a sweetheart deal result of Trump’s tax reform. We are told that we must elect… https://t.co/vk0OHtX9nG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBucsFan He is deserving of being brought back and the Bucs should honor his contract, much like a player should… https://t.co/pWf8UJl1AY]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Harden is probable for tonight's game against the Hawks, Mike D'Antoni just said.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing God’s work. #AGFA #AmericanGenreFilmArchive  #AlamoCon #SomethingWeird #BleedingSkull @filmarchive somethingw… https://t.co/SrdY2hJSHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods What a joke , you are irrelevant so start acting like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dherbert8 Then the kid is a moron. If I’m his coach, he’s not allowed back on the mound until he stops being stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulaski County phone lines are down.  This includes the Detention facility, Sheriff Office and other county offices… https://t.co/zdYL0zeK4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle aged man eats at McDonald’s. @ McDonald's https://t.co/3qtx60r07j]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who care about my opinion on these things, I support @CabanForQueens for Queens County District Attorney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you go see @HamiltonMusical and don’t take a selfie, did it really happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AFilmThatDidntGoToOscars Burning is one of the very best films from 2018. An extremely well-acted and well-shot my… https://t.co/s9nrhSbMUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobileHelp It definitely came with some optimizations, the UI/UX has some changes that took me a second to learn though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeNews media missing the real story again. Not Robert Kraft. It’s Daniel R. Young still getting after it just sh… https://t.co/qrUh8rl3Db]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The global expansion continues to lose momentum. Growth outcomes  could be weaker still if downside risks material… https://t.co/eaaQvETDEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@West221B He has a new spirit within him. “Depart from evil, and do good; and dwell for evermore” (Psalms 37:27).]]></document><document><![CDATA[1.Jordan gets absolutely mugged in several of these.  2. Players don’t have to think twice about anything like this… https://t.co/m3IlngUAgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can go all day, don’t ducking tempt me. Libertarians are the most ignorant of all the right leaning ideologies. T… https://t.co/ZPuZFhSyia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was the last day of just one sticker on my step- tomorrow I graduate from the climb phase!! I committed, I’m… https://t.co/lBglQj4oBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Trace Element: Peach/Apricot by @Ologybrewing at @ologybrewing — https://t.co/kvmtzCc2rE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boondock for the close!  @TheCigarAffair @BlackLabelCigar https://t.co/Y3qgYJQka2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When they realize what they missed... it’ll be too late. ☁️ #RespectTheProcess]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is about the greatest thing I’ve ever seen. I just watched this episode on my TiVo and I’m still laughing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even wrap my head around the fact that somebody designed the Honda Ridgeline and people thought it was a go… https://t.co/eF6cw5YqQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@professorduckID Hi Professor Duck - this guy was in our pond today. What is he? Thanks in advance! 😃👍🏼🦆 https://t.co/9lGsQ7ljfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please read and feel free to share. #SharkFinSoup . My next Campbell's Soup Can offering in honor of my love for sh… https://t.co/ixYr4whBbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kimberly Marie crossed 10K. Time 00:50:55, pace 07:59 min/mile, est. finish 10:36 am https://t.co/FT1GS3Li42 #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, please do. That corrupt bastard! I bet @DrJillStein will welcome this news as well! 😁 Let's hope this moves for… https://t.co/9mPnNhdDWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewbartolini @bobcohen_ardent When we look back at 09/10 I think we’re “celebrating” that we’re still here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even like anything discreetly since Twitter wants to put it on the timeline. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas Always two steps ahead cognitively when it comes to college basketball rule changes ,non-changes and the unintended consequences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep it real - Keep it real real  . . . . . . . . . . #Facebook #Instagram #Twitter #Linkedin #Netflicks #Tinder… https://t.co/JrSb2gTKGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yorobertaa That thing is probably still orbiting the baggage claim conveyer. No one’s claiming it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when people advocate for a guy that can barely keep up in today’s game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadlyxaiden You’ve been in a drought for as long as dinosaurs been roaming 😂. I don’t see anything but fake grass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Young_Lark36 Chief Keef: MAN MY MOMMA USED TO WHIP ME... NOW I CAN BUY HER ASS ANYTHING   Me: https://t.co/PEwoQXdGS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKenzieElemVic @sd61schools @SD61Inclusion @TillicumTBirds @GMSMavericks @TeacherSunnyJun So proud of this incred… https://t.co/5MDOkRpRkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euqubud Mark Reynolds is Blind is unforgettable. For pure joy, I picked up "The Soul of Baseball" by @JPosnanski o… https://t.co/yilrfVXEX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB10ThePhenom @theblaze This is what happens when a male is not good enough to beat other males in a sport but nee… https://t.co/iBntM8xWvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not complaining about calls today after United beat PSG but damn tough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😭what will we do for dinner?! We'll be counting down the day @apexcfa  #whattoeat #ChickfilA #wearegoingtostarve… https://t.co/QS5qbi8Rog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kath2cats You are back to unproductive garbled phrases of unimportance. Shall I move on? Or do you want to talk ASD ignited by MMR vaccine?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATKGirlfriends @emilywillisxoxo I love it when @emilywillisxoxo is being a bad girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great piece by Adam highlighting the close playoff races in the G-League. With the Clippers loss late last night to… https://t.co/tcGBiMKZ93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlynnjohnson72 Visibly every time. Gathering with 20+ Seminarians at times to eat always provides a powerful witne… https://t.co/ef5PrROmRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[25)THIS is SHOW business. You must show what you do! That means getting off the couch and going outside to a theate… https://t.co/w59REPIhk2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is especially relevant after this last season where Kelce was battling a knee injury all year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_MarianaSartori @BroCarrington ah com certeza deve ser muito bonito lá, eu só fui para a Daintree lá na Austrália,… https://t.co/2jCwWPSzFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@legndofphoenix This is like a Star Trek away team meeting another Space God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Your a despicable person who plays plantation politics. Shame on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership: City of South Miami becomes nation's first municipality to endorse https://t.co/9jVkmX8hN6 to put a… https://t.co/5ETIpgAYsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ll « find » it right after they plant it.  I hope someone is filming their « search »!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Eagles and C Jason Kelce have agreed to terms on a one-year contract extension through 2021.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goal Everyone on this thread is tripping naming these european teams. South american team's supporters will litera… https://t.co/wQUL8v2yKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landon I know you miss that southern weather man....COME TO TAMPA W TODD BOWLES AND BRUCE ARIANS!!!! Win a ring]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorPless1 I see you are at it again.  lol congrats my man.  So exciting to see your ride.  Remain humble and th… https://t.co/eMqHv6ybJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾: Habersham adds a run with a grounder to left field. They score one more with a bases loaded walk before clearing… https://t.co/XClT0gFSPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I wouldn’t do to get Olivia Coleman and Frances Mcdormand in a movie together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real villain here is whoever scheduled this for 10 AM #boskone #scifi @ Westin Boston Waterfront Hotel https://t.co/8fzv7iOY12]]></document><document><![CDATA[5498-5450 Clinton St 5498-5450 Clinton St, Los Angeles, CA 90004 https://t.co/8PVrUR3mYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrodriguezVen @LulaOficial Bruta y animal no eres otra la policía d Brasil práctica y entrena en Estados Unidos no… https://t.co/oC2Fbkljuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Miss Pelosi is just way under the bridge and she is defending a Muslim over Israel and the Jews one excuse aft… https://t.co/997RF8G325]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only I would get a Friday off and do absolutely nothing at all https://t.co/tMbiWTUKUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[De #BHP20 10/Mar/19  Números 32  Dios promueve la solidaridad y la equidad entre los hermanos.  #rpsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirchBarksBack @RioSlade Have you contacted the hospital's social worker?]]></document><document><![CDATA[looks like InDot did the league minimum of pot holes on the Eastside of Indy,  they filled in 4 holes on Ritter at… https://t.co/X3xLvvZXZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz A fine analogy. It is certainly #tomsteyer ‘s approach. #foolsfakesandfrauds]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re actually right; they are wrong.  Waitressing is infinitely more noble and honorable than being in Congress.… https://t.co/AOvl6rG4jU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Watergate scandal was like Shakespeare—a drama that built to a satisfying climax. The Russia story is more lik… https://t.co/CAe7H4CfMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's official. Patrick Lew Band is now legally copyrighted and trademarked and protected by the Federal government… https://t.co/vuBcg3aPYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndresVelasqz QUE DIISDADO SE MIRE EN EL ESPEJO DEL CHAPO!!! ESE VA SER SU FUTURO !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorMullins__ He is not going to care because he is going to feel like the luckiest guy in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[A History of Censorship: Richard Felton Outcalt and The Yellow Kid | Comic Book Legal Defense Fund https://t.co/5BqF1Lsw9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scherlis It’s below average, as you say. I’m sure he could score in that range. But it’s not an indication of grea… https://t.co/vj9ctMY5A0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kenzie on #loveyourpetday #rezdog #rescue #aawl Straight Outta Globe @ Val Vista Lakes, Gilbert, Arizona https://t.co/151VlX1kMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road  was "washed out" on Sun. I made it past there, but my car was  sitting  on a very precarious angle. I drive a… https://t.co/gjBatUyHJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: taco bell breakfast is WAY better than McDonalds breakfast]]></document></documents></author>