<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Have you a NIGHT Asia Durr! 47 pts. with 11 three-pointers!?!? GO AHEAD!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's interesting on this AB trade. We are getting no confirmation from no one on ESPN. One of the most plugged in… https://t.co/4nIKSE6W6m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lmj09671870 @JohnCornyn @WSJopinion Also, the FBI and Dept of Justice don’t get to decide who is elected. They ref… https://t.co/zZYrnNkpXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough loss for the #STLBlues this afternoon.   But one thing that I can bring home with me is that San Jose Sharks… https://t.co/byelpjXqZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are only two hard things in Computer Science: cache invalidation and naming things. (Phil Karlton)... Not anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tuan87416358 There is no “Motley Fool” view. Every writer, stockpicker, podcaster is asked to give their best analysis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the latest batch of #Detroit metro show announcements  https://t.co/KRSO6YBiIj  @DTEEnergyMusic… https://t.co/Uxs2KSfKu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @Headspace does not understand timezones and travel... And now my streak has reset to zero. That really messed with my Zen 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJordanDraper do you know of a place that will stock this and ship to the US?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWS_MountHolly @nynjpaweather @phillywx 2.9 inches of snow in Jennersville, PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This👇👇 quote is so deep!!  As educators we have to confront our students and model for them what success looks like… https://t.co/iBGhaMZZR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeltdownWRIF @101wrif Love bites judas priest and crazy little thing called love Queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: my mom’s condition is temporarily stable. She has a little more time, and we have the basics of her affairs… https://t.co/wF5f1Zq5SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TroyAle52891286 @CissyGebets MSM will continue to divide America with their double standard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrellb_24 In 1980 we came back from 20 down and near Montgomery and they went and trashed the dressing room (rig… https://t.co/PEM8d8mJM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a local Colorado beer. - Drinking a Spaceman Double IPA by @BoulderBeerCo @ Acres Green  — https://t.co/FFp0bvsSxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USC_Track_Field @espn @Mike_Norman22 ES(EC)PN Way to go, Trojan! #FightOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @HillaryClinton How much did you get paid for that tweet, bro!! You’ve been outed! Give it up !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nobel Committee just revealed that Trump’s nomination for the Nobel Peace Prize was forged - https://t.co/kPVlRwX4yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este Sabado En caferubio @MonchyCapricho1 @djjosephloveras 11:30 PM. en Cafe Rubio Restaurant https://t.co/k6s6HknYuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that gets angry when someone calls me about something that could have easily been communicated in a text or email?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itsnotmemario1 @ChrisLoesch Does nothing more than speak to the endpoint of every "flavor" of socialism......despotism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattEhalt @Buster_ESPN I know how under paid you fellas are. Go ahead and strike, see how the fans react this time… https://t.co/q9YfHgC8ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahAJean I grew up in Appleton. We always thought there wasn’t anything worthwhile in Oshkosh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sumcan__ All You Wanted was a great song tbh the whole Spirit Room album was good]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnShortJxS Seems to me that everyone on the Oilers after 97, Drai, Klefbom and maybe Larsson should be for sale.… https://t.co/c5DaoTR5Ke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/RpB6PfhFXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett I tell you what, Donnie. I'll encourage him to apologize when you and those millio… https://t.co/DWyiFFC7sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[plant-based meals could be coming to every hospital in the state of New York! A new bill was just passed in the Sta… https://t.co/XsqCLPkulN]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you can’t handle being drunk and i have to take care of you because you’re too fucked up you don’t need to be dr… https://t.co/1VZWnzRaZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crunchyroll you said you had two dubs coming that I’m very curious about. Any update on ReZero and Twin Star Exorc… https://t.co/jkoCX6tfpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyHu This Larry Moore happy birthday today Kelly HU God bless you and prosper you and favor you and cause you t… https://t.co/9Y24GuW1H1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalSports No only player with grit on this team, would just make us softer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose @realDonaldT. I would've never have thought she was born Wayback win maybe that's why she looks so old look at the picture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winniesun Hmm...let me see.🤔 Alarm went off at 5:45, did some things here before I drove about 30 miles (1 way) to… https://t.co/hP22Ve7h4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if I’m being loosely monitored.  Anyway, if anyone has any good follow up interactions I should perform, I am all ears.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t travel with me if you’re broke. I’m trynna go to museums, go on adventures and eat gourmet/ authentic foods.… https://t.co/JIis3bAeqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson BTW when is Fox lowering the cone of silence over the Tucker scandal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 14 - Morning Report:     Affordable housing plans in the Heights crumble;       Texas ranked numb… https://t.co/gYsOaY2mtK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people want to take away all the fun out of life. They make those balloons out of something special now so tha… https://t.co/vd1zhnR3FV]]></document><document><![CDATA[IGNORANCE FALLING AAWAY IN REAL TIME. FEDERAL GOVERNMENT RETARDED AS STATES LEGALIZE GANJA!! PAST MIDPOINT AND ONLY… https://t.co/pfgIbmuqYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Edurodriguezg Buenos días Eduardo, felíz y bendecido viernes y fin de semana largo.. saludos cordiales desde Orlando FL...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eboland11 Who cares really. Just waive him already, he’s completely irrelevant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my best friend from jr high is married  my elementary school crush is engaged   2+ of my friends from high school h… https://t.co/oH7RczDj0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanpierpont @stephenjudkins I hope not too many get confused as to the (non-binding) resolution vs. (binding) law distinction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisavenegass @puerto_ricano @hernanVVX This how you know that Ruben and Hernan can’t defend an argument if the fi… https://t.co/etadqqPqre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moolaa as in money money money monayy @reaDonaldTrump it's his entrance music https://t.co/OuNScUPBiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ballislife The reaction from the Nets bench is PRICELESS. Watch on the very last replay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoreAura No veo la contradicción. A la luz de los acontecimientos posteriores, mi consejo era el correcto. Y para… https://t.co/MRbqzZ5GSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harperite1 @robertbenzie @EvanLSolomon @AndrewScheer @JustinTrudeau @liberal_party @CPC_HQ @fordnation Who did the… https://t.co/3wIKA1sRSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraychik--"CBS’s Lara Logan on Media Bias: ‘Unless You Seek Out Breitbart,’ You Won’t See the ‘Other Side’"… https://t.co/NJap94K3Hu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willwilkinson @politicalmath @ernietedeschi @asymmetricinfo @perez_sherna I agree there’s no verse that says “Unbo… https://t.co/YEEEtw4bPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomcliffordcfc Now it seems Marina follow Sarri according to the Mirror, if true that would make the job more attr… https://t.co/RJQ1nvl2CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murallaverde @AbrahmGR @Andres_Mg4 Tu quieras al negro almiron. Yo pensé y pienso que era el indicado. https://t.co/jxD6xLvZUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHITE PEOPLE GOOGLE SHIT LIKE "WHY ARE THE CRIPS UPSET WITH THE BLOODS?".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 21 - Fox News First Morning Headlines:    Jussie Smollett now facing felony criminal charges;… https://t.co/AjDHZMWkKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[SÓLO GANAMOS CON PAPÁ, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/FWY5r7gOZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left using anti-Trump playbook against Brazil's new conservative president https://t.co/MH8MQE8fiA via @washtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im not ready for another week of school , need it to be spring break already 😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellotraincat But it sounds like they never would have cut the character if Homecoming didn’t use Ned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: California's independent redistricting rules could offer some hope for Republicans: California gov… https://t.co/jZXma9ezJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neal_katyal Personally, I don't trust Barr, and I think that Trump would go to great measures to shut down the inv… https://t.co/DBmRXOGSP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MannyMachado to the #Padres...  Memo to #Yankees fans;  MOVE ON; get on board..   Good luck to him; in #SD.😂😂  #Yankees #PinstripePride]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wardak province of Afghanistan @ Bedford, Massachusetts https://t.co/NF2IxgEaOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merengue166 Gracias pisha. I’ll give it a shot. Miss you cabron, te me cuidas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMNchiefsfan yo....he slept with one of his future teammate's wife...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yawaramin @reasonml I see, any idea why they did it with the -&gt; in bucklescript? Just to be more similar to JS?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMile305 Ohh ok I'm coming back down and I'm not coming alone ill have a load in my pants]]></document><document><![CDATA[Action at the Diamond in the Rough Camp at #Edisonhighschool on 3/10/2019 #ditr #rjpsports #raymondjoycephotography… https://t.co/vrLALjpDtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJackFrank @MDaware @BrowofJustice @blikethecheese @DrSandman11 No one does. But I know better than to keep defen… https://t.co/5UXPo11Ssi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Talent Pipeline. Cogs in the Wheel. Choose your metaphor carefully, or your metaphor chews you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actor Jussie Smollett has Trump Derangement Syndrome. https://t.co/yV64pA1xpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a grass fed/finished cow raised with love and care by my sister and brother-in-law. She let me get close en… https://t.co/jmGX6OCqAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plus I realized the value of ppe’s. Guess which hand got close to the forge #respectfire https://t.co/ksPCHP94CP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to open up a Breakfast and lunch diner because these people act like they can’t cook breakfast food]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just controlling the things in my life I have some say over. That’s it. The way I treat people and the way I he… https://t.co/uEhSdsULEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImmerRange @paleselan I judge candidates based in the celebrities that like then #hrc2020 #plsno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debwrightjones @DeplorableKel2 😡🧞‍♀️😡the only way to destroy America is from within]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@reenaninan hands to her colleague @TanyaRivero for the latest world news on #CBSN tonight at 7pm ET from New York… https://t.co/N1V713MP93]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fersch_4 @eduard0ushito @FOXSportsMX Pues el chiste se cuenta solo fer , me extraña de ti que le prestes atención… https://t.co/d0F2EGwhK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Copper Hills punches their ticket to the @UHSAAinfo 6A championship game with a 51-34 win over Lone Peak... will fa… https://t.co/7rDGPgarlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_Borders Wouldn't be shocked it Long isn't there in the 3rd after his combine #'s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaoMobFanSquad @yousparkypants @WrestlingInc Heard ppl say jojo mite be pregnant that’s why she hadn’t been on tv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FGR_SV Y el Sr. Cristiani.  Para cuando.  Dice mi abuelita ...@FGR_SV    @USEmbassySV]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of them are Disgusting Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Benghazi Stand Down Order Obama Clinton’s Stand Down Order Ki… https://t.co/M0jWGOWuxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[S San Gabriel Blvd &amp; E Valley Blvd San Gabriel, CA 91776 https://t.co/vRqeqky5VV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZoiePalmer @dark_matterTV I still rave about how well you dis as AnnDroid.... Omg, girl..... You freaking ROCK! I… https://t.co/nkZDjgcd31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@As_TomasRoncero @Cristiano @diarioas Estamos??? Pero tú ni a la petanca juegas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Chr 16: 9. “For the eyes of the LORD run to and fro throughout the whole earth, to give strong support to those w… https://t.co/mBuY2XIfnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesleywalker Contact the church where your membership is and ask to be removed.  Done and done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Franklin: overcast clouds, 21°F 57% humidity, wind 3mph, pressure 1023mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews No even strapped down.  I would figure out how to suffocate myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Ellijay #GA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/D6L4umXAaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop comparing yourself to strangers on social media. Become their friend IRL and pick up healthy habits and lifest… https://t.co/suMAoOs4El]]></document><document><![CDATA[He who dwells in the shelter of the Most High Will abide in the shadow of the Almighty. Psalms 9… https://t.co/i76IyGGnz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those unaware. Pat's is in Philadelphia. They are widely credited as the creator of the cheesesteak. They start… https://t.co/ZfP0oxa24q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRSPipBoy2008 I agree with BoRhap winning three of it's awards.  The fact it won Film Editing is LAUGHABLE to me.… https://t.co/m9PriJ6b9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you think I should make #PhotogMills a twitter account🙋‍♀️ https://t.co/ZvSY7sTXVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @MAGA96825 And @realDonaldTrump #LiarInChief pretends he's 6'3".  Here #DirtyDon stands next to… https://t.co/NrVAhw3KsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryGulman Started a showcase at coffeeshop I work at back in November. Been successful so far and has helped me t… https://t.co/5FrQf2euYK]]></document></documents></author>