<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CNN Oh honey that’s nothing compared to what some people eat here in the US at a buffet restaurant 😯😋😅 https://t.co/ok0L6k7jfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working my last weekend at the bullseye and getting a little teary eyed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are we pretending #PeacockMask is anyone other than @donnyosmond?!? #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1- The amazing teachers I had growing up in @BanderaISD Mrs. Robinson, Mrs. Richardson, Mrs. Traweek, Mrs. Harb… https://t.co/qExJ7N3FZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that my family and actual friends all know that yes I have strong and often times unpopular thoughts/views/o… https://t.co/hKI7esiVt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to meet Governor Lee. Looking forward to the opportunities created for students pursuing CTE paths of st… https://t.co/J9XW67WFrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElleWibble @TeahCartel @whyknotmeagain2 @ResistBaby @Back_dafucup @Pacoluismonta9a @TalkToMeForReal… https://t.co/mMfASjwKZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[honestly a friendship break up is worse. yesterday we were laughing our butts off, and today is unfriending on snap and deleted pics :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yummy stuffed marinated mushrooms from raw Fresno @ Galleria - Downtown https://t.co/fw8ALs6CxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WUG_Crew thanks 🙏❤️❤️❤️ I just read something and I changed my mind about everything please thanks 🙏❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[sonnn usps warehouse paying $16/hr bitchhhhhhh I’m tryna get innat mf💸💸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan This could be your stupidest tweet yet, Gym.  Nah, you &amp; Trump have no bottom.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying “Sorry” after plagiarizing authors doesn’t make everything ok. The damage has been done. Remember, if you pl… https://t.co/rPKijbajFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maleik_watkins That’s why I’m gonna help you prepare for her https://t.co/NzIOs4taS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anaknandes @giovaniulisses E a vontade de ir correndo até lá??? Só que fica a 1h e meia da minha faculdade, daí ti… https://t.co/CLa4RlAmsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tecomendozareal @Ruben_Esponda Yo creo que no, son el uno para el otro n.n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCR750 Mi opinión, es una entrevista aburrida, insípida, poco interesante y el conductor con comentarios inapropia… https://t.co/iYqrTt1imm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strong Women Are Alone, but Aren't Lonely - WomenWorking https://t.co/VUODfHrw95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGAVoter I’d say she is done when she disrespects her Speaker Pelosi.  She sure has some nerve!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 2 for 1 Broadway special with the incredible @JeremyMJordan at #TownHallNYC! @SethRudetsky  @TownHallNYC #LIZNYC https://t.co/wNWaRr4NWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[VANISHING DOVER: A Follow-Up https://t.co/lSuGIbI8GR https://t.co/M1987dadf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[good luck to my fav haynes boys #HMD 😉 @Hunter_Haynes10 @Connor_Haynes05]]></document><document><![CDATA[😉 😉 😉 #happyvalentinesday #happyvalentinesday2019 @ Northside Village, Houston https://t.co/stz9dgv2ko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just preordered my #HanginTough30 cd. Can't wait to meet @NKOTB in May &amp; have @DonnieWahlberg sign it! #Blockhead #Mixtapetour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michocollins @DonaldTrump_Is @realDonaldTrump He’s a fucking idiot 😜😜😜😜😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EileenJONeill @WEForg Thank you, @EileenJONeill, for joining us and sharing all the great things that @WEForg is d… https://t.co/voxofiDepz]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Iowa City, IA job and click to apply: Staff Nurse (Anesthesia) - https://t.co/JNW7ei8eNo #PatientCare #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aplicación de extensiones de 22" con microring.  No te arriesgues y ven con los profesiones   Salon TRY NOW  Te inv… https://t.co/xPiB8rZVEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NFLCombine : les quarts-arrière de la cuvée 2019 sont prêts à faire leurs preuves (@SCadoretteJDQ) #JDQ #NFL https://t.co/WPeGNbY1bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for hilarity . . .  This is exactly the kind of sarcastic comment I would want to say but wouldn't fo… https://t.co/r8NHWKlljV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Same goal, Same outcome . Both tried to segregate our country. https://t.co/qxy1w9dBNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uriestragedies @SAM_CHAMS @JakeChams @brendonurie @urielectric_16 @lusttrj @trvdcmistakes @dnptruce @XGoldenUrie… https://t.co/ChQrZhAwKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a vlog coming to my YouTube channel on Sunday. 😝 I’m probably going to make it into 2 parts because my friend… https://t.co/UwznZjVD0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be in NY,NY representing #daughtersbeyondincarceration y’all coming 💁🏽‍♀️ #reform #endlifesentences… https://t.co/FQXXT7bK8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I fucking hate pictures” sorry not sorry you’re too cute for me not to 🥰 https://t.co/TVRwFOd0X5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews @AnnCoulter If you don't like it run for Predifent #AnnCoulter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT This is a humanitarian crisis of epic scale! Anyone? What can we do? @UNHumanRights @UN @hrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a @LIFX lightbulb for the first time. I feel like I have my life together now because I can turn my lamp on with Siri 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_OmarShoots I literally have 3 guitar hero controllers in my trunk for a Wii and I’m about to find a way to make t… https://t.co/51oaBiBd7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to eric &amp; nick for helping me with my music theory hw right now 😪💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrestonMcMurry Love it! I appreciate the diagram of the homeless path taken. Glad your bp is normal and healthy de… https://t.co/i5Q6V5aLd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please don’t try and explain no stupid shit to me. Please stop trying to confuse me with literal bullshit. PLEASE!… https://t.co/TUH08TZhUd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ironic: losing your umbrella and scheduling your #hair appointment on the rainiest day of the week. Let’s take a mo… https://t.co/TP0rs2M4Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a nice time hanging out at the #beach . It is so wonderful that even thru #LakeJackson and sand, we can conn… https://t.co/xuurYSCiVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjrich_ @joslinschultz Wolf Trap Animal Rescue!!! Elsie was the best choice I made and her bestie is from there as… https://t.co/c3iM96i1aF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @PlanetFitness in Lawrence, KS https://t.co/MmuAulKAKq https://t.co/OOhQ9rbNqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allisonlanza girl you gotta come get your Girl Scout cookies before I eat them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm in the running of getting my own @meetsomnox #win #sleeprobot #somnox https://t.co/3npXkwH9gp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @SenSanders Why don’t you guys lecture Republicans.  You know it amazes me who you guys have on the sh… https://t.co/0qoBMKS3UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[On @GeneralHospital looking forward to the episode when Ava @MauraWest finds out that Ryan, not Franco, killed kiki… https://t.co/co2xzsYbhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have your cake and eat it too. 🎂 🍰 🧁   . . . #bostonchef #bostonfood #bostonfoodie #yougottaeatthis… https://t.co/XA6102wUsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawncampbell5 @gloomcookie0898 @KyleRichards @LisaVanderpump Right with you Team LVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mclaraf @SKK_Anthophila They help students see patterns in the answers they got wrong and if they scored below a 7… https://t.co/40Fqs4Ea8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna need some artists to drop songs cause I’m getting tired of hearing the same shit😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Practiced another Teacher Leader Institute CFU in class today! This is just one of many amazing responses!… https://t.co/lzk8fyfK5N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cromwell Bridge Road Park &amp; Ride - @mdsha in Towson, MD https://t.co/xWVeWB7WYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve been walking around for 30 mins and we can’t find our ride.. oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zoos celebrate Valentine's Day with a playful pun-off 💗 🐢  https://t.co/9ltXb9WEZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie_fluffybun @fluffybasil @MoetBlindCat @Cleo_sMommy @Tonithecat32 @nesjloch @LittleMaineCoon @TobiasandJasper… https://t.co/Yb3l0SCmeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaker Pelosi, I have no interest whatsoever in Trump’s tax returns. I am very interested in seeing yours. Any pol… https://t.co/WKsOYOzwFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWErickson I sure hope taxpayers are intelligent enough to know that vegetables, especially beans, cauliflower and… https://t.co/Y7TPtgOnji]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm listening to my showtunes playlist and Im Not That Girl came on and I just realized that For Good is playing in… https://t.co/pfUhtIR3cC]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oyQbVKQJXF @cnn @msnbc @ Maddow @catalyst pharma.  This needs focus - another greedy pharma co that ta… https://t.co/Q41zIgWlT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MengTriniti @pjn112 That’s wtf I’m talking about https://t.co/4tVmUplAb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important considerations here! ⬇️ @renita_williams @DeppeParrish @KellyMcCoig @suegb1031 @NNPSESL @nnpsstem… https://t.co/fH5ZERFZBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Carson warned Lynne Patton that her appearance at Cohen hearing wouldn't go over well https://t.co/zPLB9QSmyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runningevolve @catydidski We gotta work on our boomerangs... although I do love the OG one! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #spartanraces for this year! I'm the only one standing in my way. Time to make this happen!   #iamaspartan… https://t.co/4XXEz39n6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything is finally coming together for me but like I’m struggling so hard with which direction to go for my career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Adrian playfully argue with his mom and sister is the funniest shit ever 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[im really out here putting my literal mind,body,and soul into a person but they still can’t see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrushingOnSaban You know what.....you should try it. 🤔 I’m working from home today - I’m going to get get back under my covers shortly...😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m tired of all this porn on my tl when i’m tryna be a wholesome child of god.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh this is wonderful: Kitbull | Pixar SparkShorts https://t.co/Mn19nGaVoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not even halfway through this and I’m amazed at how much I have learned.  And how history repeats itself. In on… https://t.co/N01ZYi0lgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amendez0921 men’s sweats r comfier than women’s sweats for some rude reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird She lied. She told America she would be leaving after the 1st of the year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m having a slumber party 🤷🏾‍♀️ but y’all 🆖’s ain’t about to spend the night https://t.co/Pb4lwMQC7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are in control of how you react towards what life throws at you. You just gotta learn to make the best out of any situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[then adopt and save the kids who weren’t aborted and got thrown into the foster system]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dumb decisions I’ve made in the past 24 hours: -went on Twitter at 11:45 pm bc I told myself I’d only look for five… https://t.co/FwAE2aXhKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great evening!! @ MAE Be ranch quarter horses https://t.co/5umtbrnNiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Cost Accountant - https://t.co/WsLoawKWPB #Finance #Melbourne, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have lived in Minnesota my whole life (for real, I live three miles from the hospital I was born in) and never on… https://t.co/ijqzZgdHwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope you woke up and felt:  LOVED  BEAUTIFUL  JOY CONFIDENT PEACE FREE  CHOSEN  the best part about it, none of t… https://t.co/XOEKR0fpaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Mr. Peabody's Coal Train Done Hauled It Away..is a verse in the song titled #Paradise by #JohnPrine. Th… https://t.co/3wDyMfCN8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a damn good thing my neighborhood is prettt chill because uh. One of my fiancé’s friend left his keys in his m… https://t.co/k90vFbGDL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baldacci - Cheated Death (Ft. Classik) (Prod by Red Drum) (With Lyrics O... https://t.co/dHsuGsFy8K via @YouTube. O… https://t.co/jpIX5ovwQd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you help our team reach our fundraising goal? My son and many other "littles" benefit from this great… https://t.co/uSjkF5SLhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stichomancery Reylo became the ultimate comfort zone, dressed up as somehow dangerous instead of the definition of… https://t.co/CNheal4ODF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get. In. Formation. #FormationFridays with me, #DJPK at #hitopsla Come check our the new lighting that gives it a s… https://t.co/1he6AMf42y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just trying to communicate with the Kardashian family. Chris &amp; I are the same age but like her she nor I look our age.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenningtonsays @RealMattCouch Wow my Daughter who is addicted to drugs is in jail till 7/20 no house arrest for he… https://t.co/IDcNMxZZDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phil_Lewis_ WTF????  Not since 1965!!!!  How are all these people lost in the mid-20th Century!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotPennsy @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @newtgingrich @tedcruz @RandPaul @senatemajldr Re elect President Trump  Tru… https://t.co/CXkGOrWHzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[No saben cuánto valoro que al día siguiente después de una peda, no tenga cruda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you think we’re talking enough about how Jersey Boys opened with Tituss Burgess rapping in French]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets to see @mulaney in NYC next month is the best Valentines gift I could’ve ever asked for ❤️ @realwillbry #youdabest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you been turned down for a SBA loan call my dear friend Joyce she will help you her number is (508) 864-1181 t… https://t.co/R1HxZM1U7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yallll I really don’t like weed... like omg it’s makes me feel so uncomfortable. My friend tricked me into taking a… https://t.co/nTkRktYTAO]]></document></documents></author>