<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'd have more respect for BdB if he'd published this before he conspired with his nemesis to subvert oversight of t… https://t.co/fNTr36vNCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tzarimas @Juanita_Phillip @michaelcollins Hmmmm I guess the honest answer is yes, occasionally but absolutely in c… https://t.co/Pw8ZYIgVqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this week's @miamiherald Business Monday #CEO Roundtable, we were asked: What was the most significant change to… https://t.co/qokVjTpQwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanJulie With Foles on his way out that should be good enough to win the east! @realTIMKEARNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akiestar Just fill me in on the secrets today.  ;)  My tickets were booked last night,  so maybe next time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[110 votes in and y'all are pretty optimistic. I like it. #Phillies #HarperWatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgementScythe I like the Gotg films.  But why cant the movie be the movie and 616 be it self.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babysitter for the night means noi is picking up these kids in the morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice work, @FOXSports on trolling @BobBowlsby during a live interview at the Big 12 wrestling tournament https://t.co/khno0HqWHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[16/ Without nuclear power in the mix the fossil fuel industry will continue to have us by the coattails. We hamstri… https://t.co/NeGl2ixAJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittyoutwest Yoooo what y’all on later? And that last pic brought back so many memories 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please welcome to the stage... @meg_townsend!!!!!!!   We’ll be doing double duty on the @GLAAD account tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lorena accepts the risk post deposit meets in Columbia during dans hiring]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one thing I hate about the American justice system is we aren't allowed to torture people. This kid needs to be… https://t.co/smOc8wMvSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parrotheads everywhere are laughing at Spartacus.    https://t.co/qFd1ZIsJxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all talk about being bosses and doing boss shit. But none of y’all really be on the boss ass shit my ppl… https://t.co/pNJRkUnNnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found the unicorn!!! Great beer!! Thank you hespelerbrewing #IPA #lcbo #GreatBeer #Local @ Guelph, Ontario https://t.co/Ba4wlvYO3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBlankenshipWSB , I think your antics are fantastic! Thank you for the vid. #KeepDoingYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday @ Vintage Vinyl - St. Louis https://t.co/IgzGH1n7oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I stood outside, a man in his 20s pushed a woman, also in her 20s, out of the hospital and tried to help her int… https://t.co/I8dxzFxsdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoonHoops leading mars 32-18 at halftime! Let’s goooooo tigers!!! @WPIAL_Insider @WPIALBasketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say yes. He will do something. No one is ever untouchable but I’d guess he doesn’t move Vaakanainen, certai… https://t.co/6foEUOWH25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabo de cenar como si no hubiera mañana, jaja pero tenía mucha hambre!! 😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can fix shit by giving it time or talking about it https://t.co/Cs4ID5C0Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told the #rnc @senate_gops and @housegop fundraising goons to stop calling me 2 years ago... I sure did donate… https://t.co/P5gEzfIAWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joeinblack For sure. It’s as if some intelligent being created Earth for a specific purpose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @McDonalds - your new donut sticks are great. But I like them better when they’re called mini churros.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lineups for tonight's game between #UCF and Ball State. Tom Cheshareck gets the start for his Knights debut. This w… https://t.co/HKFhIpcElG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tzuyu is making this:  蛋餅 Dan Bing Taiwanese Egg Crépe Roll)  #김쯔위가돌아왔다 #KimTzuyuReturns https://t.co/eA4ty2Egda]]></document><document><![CDATA[me &amp; my fav scarf @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/8LAqHKx9HO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMac_1023 @TeamChevy @markmartin @timlynn_13 @lbowman7190 @JRMotorsports Winning for JRM before it was cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the first person to with from home using a computer. Very cool. Great thread too. Buy Clive’s book: you’l… https://t.co/Ww1jpKs7ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLifshatz So many games in CBB the last 7 days have had the most bizzare lines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueDaddyIssues I mean this sounds very lovely to do but we live far apart so I mean yeah I think you trying to fu… https://t.co/CyzBuAFxGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be careful with Apple maps, they will send you on leases you don’t need to be on them ranchers get mad🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why they always be loving them polar bear body ass white girls? It has GOT to end]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he paid them with a check? Is this a test?  https://t.co/6wCBIqHaQc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCrom foles, very poor play n philly? Wat? Dude won philly a SB. Bridgewater cant stay healthy. Give me the SB MVP QB everytime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To me impeachment is meaningless unless we have the votes in the Senate to convict. If Pelosi waits for the Mueller… https://t.co/jhWW5ONPTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewDay @CNN @jimsciutto Sometimes reporters add to the controversy with their statements and questions. Would it b… https://t.co/cK9DXjmzx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@papayasamurai29 @LeftAction Truth and untruth are totally different! Fox tells the truth and that is why they are… https://t.co/QZEH6OM3on]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I feel about having to tell someone in Los Angeles that I’m an actor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Politicizing federal disaster assistance is toxic, hurtful and destructive. All my best wishes go to the people of… https://t.co/CdDgjDw6VO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The press is not the enemy of the people. The press is not the enemy of the people. The press is not the enemy of t… https://t.co/kZBdMZx3fA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsRetroRalph Accidentally mail your switch to me with the next painting I buy 🙏🏾😆😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet again, Holy Spirit confirms His promise to my heart, when almost a full decade have come and gone. Yet, I still… https://t.co/a0gQc0DAWY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helichrysium09 @RTinRZ @7WhoSayS7 @BeardedAtHeart @GregLogan1 You need to sit down here. Green Book is a movie fil… https://t.co/vYOA30utDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Carter. West Carter. 3OTs. Love it! Wish I coulda been there! 62nd District games are off the charts man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLTVSupport how can I tell if the preds game with be blacked out for me tonight?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMorning: Drive as if every child on the street were you own. #schoolzone #HISDPD https://t.co/O8qX3LmbJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to the cabinet to grab a couple excederin for a headache but I wasn’t paying attention and accidentally took s… https://t.co/sR0Gu7RpoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erichgrimske1 I bet your moms is happy as hell!!! Tell ya brotha congrats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mattwheresdabat 16 years and still love her like I did at the beginning...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t remember the last time I spent an entire day at home playing video games and just relaxing. I really needed… https://t.co/2ELb7sDxjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bitcoin #Bottom Doesn’t Matter, Last Time General Population Can Afford Entire #BTC https://t.co/eWRMOA16J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukegraboyes @acaseofthegolf1 Bingo. Thanks for playing Luke. Sometimes a tweet can have simple and impactful mean… https://t.co/UP2w2tIBjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drillermiller2 @MattGaudy And the fact that King James was a Freemason, homosexual and he made his Anglican Church… https://t.co/UwsLpxdysy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This one of the biggest troll tweets I’ve ever seen 😂  You really tryna have Twitter folk completely lose it with t… https://t.co/aA5EOEXv2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiderofWolves Yeah, Freaked Out And Started Pushing Buttons, Turned The Phone Upside Down And It Hung Up (Lucky Feature On My Phone).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDGolfMedia One of the things we’ve struggled to find is something accurate and affordable. The @FlightScopeGolf M… https://t.co/RNVfFW9qOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearsMilitia David Blough - QB - Purdue. A replacement for Tyler Bray and ultimately for Chase Daniel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be ok guys I promise. I got this!! 💪🏻 I’m stronger than EVER! My work ethic and my health prove it. Actions sp… https://t.co/MpAnSEa9fj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#moto #racing weather ? #FACK #frozen #desert @IndeMotorsports @champ_school @dainese dainesenyc robinjeans… https://t.co/zVG0mPvpUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BlueJacketsNHL Do you really think it is a good idea to play #BabyShark in the arena, when the team is embassi… https://t.co/HKTewdsrEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to Matt, B, and Clay; along with the other @PAC_Athletics honorees.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @KamalaHarris She doesn’t say to all. I assume they would have to apply and then be vetted and the “… https://t.co/l0DBuzaIxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaultman @colton @CassieRandolph I read online he does 🤩 she's my fave too I just had to know if she was goin… https://t.co/ldaeitUgX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls always act like they ready to leave they cheating man but dont guys like me if we get played we out the same night]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s why it had to go. Just For Men Jett Black for the win!  But imagine that ‘stache on this OL body cruising ar… https://t.co/LOUJfCpipf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakebockoven @MarksVoice @LannyZeppelin @miss_linseylynn Question, can I grow my hair out too? https://t.co/7NfX3Vf00T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @SenateDems https://t.co/t0U4nyCdiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN measles shots kill 100x more people than the measles themselves! ZERO U.S. Measles Deaths in 10 Years, but Ove… https://t.co/cmDy7ER0Vf]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then the trolling started: “How about a PU (national championship) banner sale? What? Can’t find any ...?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, Washington is aiming and firing its war and political weapons over the world, it is not bad to be aimed at fo… https://t.co/OOAXZqwwts]]></document><document><![CDATA[BITCH ABOUT FUCKING TIME I AM READY TO SEE AND PROVE THAT RUBY STILL LIVES !!!!! @seewhatsnext]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bluegirl_3 @RealMuckmaker There is no such thing as a hot dog unless it's Vienna.B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Treasonous tiny hands Drumpf said Kim didn’t know about Otto until later, was that like the way he didn’t kn… https://t.co/sUvP2yFuEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@musclebearben Also, maybe you could try again… This time without pants? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickRiccardi Phillies fans will hate this contract in three years, if that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow!!! @briarcliffhoops going to the Elite 8 for the 3rd time in 4 years after a huge win over 1 seed WV Tech!! Con… https://t.co/RpT3TW829k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about trial ethics from the pros at @atlantabar #litigation breakfast. There is a duty to research witness… https://t.co/LC2ugwnWTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackburn3Buddy Amen Brother. Thanks for the daily inspiration, and hope]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauramahler When I graduated in ‘88, there were more women than men. When I started practicing, I heard a lot of t… https://t.co/s4xsqSiqtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n8turphotochick @AwardsDarwin No, bow line is a type of knot that won't close the loop when the end is pulled, unlike a slip knot or noose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dale_gribbs @JackPosobiec BOSTON media 1 English king 0.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1USA H… https://t.co/J9f2bUZ628]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moneymetalcakes @BSJimmy @JunksRadio @EBJunkies @GlassJoeJP @drabtshirt Maybe not mine but there’s a fetish for wo… https://t.co/NZUnDplhho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @kobebryant when are you gonna do a detail episode on @KingJames defense...asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper’s speed,  Cook’s size, Crab’s red zone clutch factor and a rookie contract to grow with JG and DC  #4 is loo… https://t.co/5EHlQa9sGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul You need to do the right thing!! Stop throwing the Constitution out there! Who else is respecting the Con… https://t.co/RSCM3HsrnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Maybe if they weren't gonna get paid for he rest of their life they would go home and get a job after a c… https://t.co/j7xlAmi6ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vampire Weekend’s new song “Harmony Hall” is stupendous! Which is just expected of them, now. Such an astute band w… https://t.co/VIP7m7yVYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metspolice @UniWatch just ran a post that included a pic or two of the all orange uniforms that one mlb team (Astr… https://t.co/dkRspSIZXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep the faith Neelam! P 👍🏼 #SaveDaredevil #DaredevilSeason3 #Theo #Foggy #Brothers #NelsonsMeats #MakeItHalpin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalkHawk501 And also should probably spend sometime in your local correctional facility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetOnJimmy Was on Acosta AGS (+270) really have to think Guz for the poor handles there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be shy. Score a job like "React Native Developer" at Robert Half Technology by asking for referrals. It's a g… https://t.co/CrrPMTa5po]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cannot hang out with alanna or priscilla if i want a good night sleep... IT IS 4 am how https://t.co/9Oy7LdWm2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Hunter. It wasn’t the route he wanted to go but he battled back to take 3rd to qualified for the nation… https://t.co/6cWIfMRgdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTorontoSun @MousseauJim 42,000 grams of carfentanil 50 odd pistils ammo rifles no nothing to see here ! That's… https://t.co/LnkweSfzgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[White Americans really need to look up the words racist and racism before they comment on shit.]]></document></documents></author>