<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This Thursday! Our Spring Fling! Bring your besties! Sip, shop, and maybe win! 5-8  #womenhelpingwomen #newreach… https://t.co/Ifu1mLTa9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ninjacosmetix Awesome Products - check them out @ Massachusetts https://t.co/lp8T692cTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BottleBreacher @Pixxydoodle @dega_boy_87 @CMANGO @DannyLeBlanc24 @spyderrider63 @rottzillasgirl @McGuireSuzette… https://t.co/QcbB3SCwsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl and her brisket. ❤️ We went on a BBQ crawl in Lockhart, Texas. We hit up Smitty’s, Black’s, and Kreuz. Our r… https://t.co/pKVTuoQ4Zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthanasiaTrian1 @NancySimonds1 @mymtbrain @mary_markssngr @ErinConrad2 @sqrlb8 @DebsterPA1 @CamillaIversen4… https://t.co/Y6ejE7CkCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenWUNDERful It is the BEST &amp; she is so much FUN!!!  To know her is to love her.  To have her as a friend is a blessing!!! 💖💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[But imagine when we all change our icons to their moment in 206 😭 https://t.co/gyPkrRa6pL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris You should be FURIOUS at this #MORON @JussieSmollett for trying to further divide our country! This s… https://t.co/LSqibRIOAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fishtender2 @moose1773 @CastronovoShow @PaulCastronovo Why STP lol!!😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyescapist @emmaladyrose @ClaireEFallon @2BlkGirls1Rose I understand! I actually listened to @bythebookpod while… https://t.co/g3FYAuS1Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FurKidMom Mom gets her out right away.  Down to the dumpster.   Iz thinks peeps think da snow gonna cover it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a woman and a teacher, I think it is vital that we support each other and not blame victims of sexual harassment… https://t.co/V4dsJhCcye]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I’m really fucked up about my bitch lying to me lol like wtf I would’ve never though 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dogsnjelly @HofiusKISD Thanks so much Jennifer! It has been a great year at Hofius!Thanks so much for thinking of me.💗Miss you tons!]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is SOOOO frustrating to try to resolve issues or have a talk w someone w the intention of getting to a better pl… https://t.co/n5CGPTZ0A7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaina I try soooooo hard not to be negative on social media, BUT I just can’t hold this one.... the whole fam… https://t.co/7ITZ6q7bAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein , @BetsyDeVos (and her ‘adoption agencies’, @realDonaldTrump , roger stone, @PaulManafort , @ICEgov… https://t.co/gAuVTi1WxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder and just where do we the citizens start not the politician as they are just in it for re- election the Repu… https://t.co/sX2SLY5kGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[ทวิตนี้อยู่บ้านทิฟฟานี่  LIPS ON LIPS TOMORROW #TiffanyYoung #BestSoloBreakout #iHeartAwards @tiffanyyoung]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who don’t like in n out fries are just used to over-processed potato mess like McDonald’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marrapaz este BR só me supreende! Que CARALHA o Procon tem a ver com isto?350 aviões do tipo no mundo voando,2 caem… https://t.co/N1PdDNwHmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning radio at I ❤️ Radio in Jacksonville, Florida promoting the Laughs For The Troops comedy show tonight helpin… https://t.co/247QK9KEkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merlin had a blast walking in the #Krewe des #Cheins #dog #parade yesterday! This sweet boy is available for… https://t.co/N6saRE78aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet dreams everyone! See you a half hour early tomorrow! That’s right! We’re starting at 4:00am on @WAVY_News 10… https://t.co/bFxdzc7aj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first in a dynamite series of stills from our shoot last weekend where @NEscalation captures my deep love affai… https://t.co/qNiYiInM74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to find someone to go with me to cardi is so damn hard when the concert is Friday🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inthewhale Seriously?? EVERY. TIME. Maybe I just need to switch my @Bandsintown settings to not tweet every time I… https://t.co/wPHuL3COi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kattescobar I’ll look into thank you. I need new shows cause I’m watching criminal minds all over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1woodardkay @mariajacomel @joey_lynn_10 @Chelmaree24 @lyndsey_downs7 You guys are no fun lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want for my birthday is a new body pillow ,so my sleep is amazing 😴🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RootsIowa Anxiously awaiting your opening! #craftbeer #iowabeer #brewmoines]]></document><document><![CDATA[ODEIO q joguem as coisas na cara se vai fazer pra falar dps nem faça entao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaBloom Did you ever see the photo shoot with MJ and Bill Weber ? Please take a look. I believe the boys, and I… https://t.co/d5Rov7h08Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reseaucitadelle @jguaido @Stanleylucas01 @michaelcdeibert @Almagro_OEA2015 @AmbJohnBolton @USEmbassyHaiti… https://t.co/EN2hOINzoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByAndrewWagner I like him with Brian Anderson during March Madness #blessed #againstTheCrowd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence We're glad you're alive too.  Praying for a successful surgery and for a quick healing of your body.  God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Purilly Dude cmon I haven’t finished reading the manga yet, how you gonna post spoilers like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[5/5 One test revealed enlarged #lymph #nodes in Mom’s chest, but further #testing for #cancer is too invasive for… https://t.co/DrJFrYrxjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oatmeal can be good but...top tier breakfast food? I know u fckin lyin 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd This is so true. I was shocked when I heard. Not that I want anyone to have to do hard time but really this is not justice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amspectator @LoufromCT Only if we turn on the TV and pay attention and agree. I disagree with his BS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SWITCH! 🔁#30daystoalign ⭐️How to BE a magnetic creator Tip #10 ⭐️ 10/30: SWITCH your self-talk to positive self-tal… https://t.co/62dQOuXMOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters We the people do support it! We are trying to understand what it's going to take for Dem's to get… https://t.co/caRhRyv8rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too funny!  And so true. #mirth #snicker #grin #absurd https://t.co/1a0Njx8KOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing how excited daisy was to see me this morning makes me never wanna leave her again😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday #sexysaturdays Repost from scuba.steph Trapped in the dark Slammed all the locks Death call… https://t.co/mGk6QoYvIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing Zoeys little face looking out the back door on the security cameras always warms my heart https://t.co/UoJFXbLtvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow how ironic @aaas @_SciComm #AAAS2019 #AAASmtg opening plenary encourages scientists to work more with industry… https://t.co/LOy633lLoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenryTContreras We should change our practices in hospitals, nursing homes, and hospices. Pets ARE the best medici… https://t.co/d0n4zcurJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a job in the high desert is hard af 😭 I’ve applied to 5 places and I got rejected from all of them. I don’t… https://t.co/u8Vz86Zi19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theartofebm Yes! I believe critical thinking is one of the most important, if not THE most important, things to be taught in PA school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen Star Wars (all of them); Die Hard (all of them); Avatar; Avengers (all of them); basical… https://t.co/uu9a9uQ9Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support I need help regarding an unauthorized transaction from you guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan O muses on the corporate money and advice dictating how teachers and schools must change while our children b… https://t.co/Zu4urlF6yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Major Telecom Disruption: What's That Mean For You? @unified_team https://t.co/UUxL3G4hb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna hold your hand...🖐🏻😻 @ Somers Point, New Jersey https://t.co/bJtjBO4KTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassanmccan @HonestLeYo @_lightbrigght_ @DearSpecialK OK someone is blocked It looks like you are indulging me Che… https://t.co/xfEqG4uCC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenrofe I wonder if they noticed that I was pretending to read a magazine but never turned a page.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Museum Archive (dedicated to Edward Steichen's Delphiniums, MOMA 1936), 2014 @ PERFUMARIE https://t.co/5YaHF6RZRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So one of my best friends doesn’t like Thai food and my fucking feelings are hurt about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urmaker69 You and Mrs urmaker mean the world to me. Just wanted you to know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Cook @Elizabeth_Cook #elizabethcook thehitonecafe #hitonecafe #nolacountyradio #nolacounty @ Hi Tone https://t.co/X7HfBLEYdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ughhh I’ve got a first date tonight and I’m about to cancel it just because I HATE first dates]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fras99 I don't doubt her math, just his fidelity. #CheaterInChief that's why she can't be too surprised about #Stormy or #KarenMacDougal]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I space out reading a text at a traffic light, a courtesy honk is still in order.  Some peeps might need better anger outlets????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Royal_Realness @slimpickens2916 Babies arrive when you least expect it. Girls are typically 1 week early and boys… https://t.co/BZ20Ha52Hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[9. And finally, here’s a picturesque view from Roscoe West. The TCNJ and Ewing communities are collaborative and su… https://t.co/Wy3IHtlAE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HolmanHenry @lloydbassII @ScoobydaDog @ODonnellKarl @micky18010 @RGatone @FactsSupport @Erekose_On_MaM @TManitowoc… https://t.co/TMLoyqx5cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do girls have a revolving door of boyfriends? I can’t even go on more than one date before I find something tha… https://t.co/qJPUUzHnEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not my character’s job to explain black culture to white people via @angiecthomas Author of #OnTheComeUp https://t.co/jVKYWRv6Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel! (@ Century Orleans 18 for Captain Marvel in Disney Digital 3D in Las Vegas, NV) https://t.co/9XhTaybwuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask him if has Committed Treason in Russian &amp; wait for response No Collusion]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever someone says “isn’t your brother in the army” I make to correct them and say he’s in the MARINES 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[At JoCo Public Policy Breakfast #2. Today’s #ksleg panelists: Senators Bollier and Skubal, Reps. Lynn, Ruiz, Warren. https://t.co/l62pYcUvOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotTodayEric @InsurgencyNQ Why lie. I like to fuck lol and im a very busy girl at times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thevanisher This guy’s patient and deliberative and incisive and I think I love him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay_riddle @flc Lol. Why is he even on twitter if he’s just blocking everyone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The feeling when you see someone reading your article in print will never get old 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I loved #captainmarvel ! Favorite “back story” movie to date, was entertained the whole time and welcomed an… https://t.co/LKS4FEYRcg]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you that followed my epic fish stories, Morgan Fishman turns 2 today. Still can’t believe he was the k… https://t.co/l39P7iq6xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are scientists sharing our data with North Carolina State University  #CitizenScience We dissected our frogs and… https://t.co/uS0Oqc3AWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hollywoodhend Always praying for you TH. Is the concussion problem getting better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dare to #design the future today.   • #uxdesign #ui #xd #ux https://t.co/Z8FwjL7mqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @tomemmer St. Louis Park, MN. I have family there we are working on getting more votes! https://t.co/yUUtHbljMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are unable to attend but would still like to donate or walk with us on April 28th at @SoldierField please cl… https://t.co/EU35mBjuf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacLeodLisa  @lornecoe Instead of dismantling the OAP, let’s work 2gether 2make it sustainable for all 100% with s… https://t.co/8gJEfjTCS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this girl! Today’s pre-yoga run was actually 2 miles plus .55 miles of walking.   She ran 1 mile non-st… https://t.co/OMOGzmZyb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Coast darlings!! Ticket link in bio!! Drama, mystery, magic, and love... this play has it all ✨ @ Solana Beach… https://t.co/VXqraEDahZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Filmatelist Yeah, Editing - whew!, that's a winner!  Haven't looked at SA in detail, but  bet that if I did.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Yet the gop, here in America is trying, state by state, to dismantle marriage equality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge frm  @MartinMiddleELA to post 7 covers of 📚I ❤️: no explanations, no reviews-just the cov… https://t.co/pU5SV2xvIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrWhoTimenspace My top three favorites from the classic era are... 1) Pyramids Of Mars 2) Genesis Of the Daleks 3)… https://t.co/dp8Sh28buS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t get to study abroad to San Ramón, Costa Rica this summer to study Community Health &amp; Development I’m gonna be pissed🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lwhea96619 And I was thinking while listening too bad he's not getting played here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the paint is drying, getting the workout room back into shape... #timetogetbackatit]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many things I wanna tweet and so many tweets I wanna read. Not enough hours in the day. Manic Monday for sure bu… https://t.co/EYZP8OWlFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vivskivs I’m considering giving up all beverages except water and giving up social media for Lent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Even more shocking is you pretending babies matter to you. https://t.co/TYPfRiACid]]></document><document><![CDATA[U should try and watch it it is on Netflix and it is a 80s movie if u seen 16 candles and the breakfast club u will… https://t.co/7acA7uQnkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *Gets hair done.* *Two days later.* Me to boyfriend: What do you think of my hair? Boyfriend: Uhh, honestly bab… https://t.co/rLkFd43AyH]]></document></documents></author>