<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@medpepper @moinanderson @LauraMalorzo @stevie76 @neighlouder @ewannaC @AlwaysChica @A_Badassunicorn @Miss_Lulu1… https://t.co/Dou5umH9TT]]></document><document><![CDATA[We continue to fight for the exposure of this league so that the amazing athletes who are apart of it can attain wh… https://t.co/5sMF7n802M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLueCrew @people That’s to bad. I was really hoping this would work out for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*just ate a 45 minute lunch with jayd at work*  2 minutes later after being back on my unit .... @jayd_brooke calls… https://t.co/qmmFyaOFL1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cambia el “no puedo” por “no quiero” y responsabilízate por tu vida. https://t.co/c61YtQRsg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, you can never go wrong with watching @zachsang1 interviews. 🎶🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want a donut but not from Krispy Kreme or dunkin. I want one from the Asian shops in California 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n_isie i wish everyone could just agree to stop using offensive language, symbols, etc and just be nice to one another]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FINISHED the #DC #rockandrollhalfmarathon 🏃🏻‍♀️ unofficial time 2:03 (so damn close) a full 17 minutes better tha… https://t.co/EOcebZU9sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Wednesday night right??? Tomorrow is another workday right?!!? I’m seeing all kinds of leather skirts and pant… https://t.co/44esoyJKB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marknolte Just saw one by Coralville Kohl's that is big enough to swallow a smart car 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @realDonaldTrump @WSJopinion i knew that was an unreasonable and expensive undertaking. I think it was… https://t.co/MHiW74qDjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBHS Boys Basketball Senior Night 2019 - what a great group of young men! 💙🏀🖤 #gojags @HBHSathletics  @BradleyHS… https://t.co/FhHoec1aTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah you are a liar, manufacurer of Trump facts and an overall piece of work. This behavior is a reflection of you… https://t.co/fOH03jmGA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACMawards @thejuic3man Where is @travistoy ? He's the best! @rascalflatts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PNWTransit The whole outfit is tragic. I don’t even know who they are!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a feeling you were hiding something...I still have faith in your motives! @ChrisMcNally_ @hallmarkchannel @WCTH_TV #Hearites]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I have is hampers of dirty #conniemotion cast offs to do &amp; #alexa is not helping @ Hollywood https://t.co/veQWFzk5qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister Ryan unfortunately this is exactly what Trump wants. He wants to divide and conquer the US. The sad… https://t.co/upT4wAmpXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedmatrix My deepest condolences to Luke Perry's family.  I'm sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobpockrass I loved the group qualifying!I'm might be the minority though🏁🏁🏁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhambrick63 @Shann_ME @wingsforp No idea.  She also puts paper towels between her tortillas.  I don't question it… https://t.co/BBgrtmYXE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Body art photoshoot with qigong flow . .  I love seeing the tranquility when you introducing someone to their natur… https://t.co/HqzijEqDBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @RCDSB two of your grads just happened to be on this years @LaurentianRelay committee at @LaurentianU… https://t.co/GERLc4AXCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moms really came through with the beef patty/coco bread/kola champagne combo for me at work today 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen to that!! Right here is one of those strong women in this world 💪🏼 💞😘✝️🇺🇸 I have been the One in ny family to… https://t.co/jMMblqDezU]]></document><document><![CDATA[First #lightning game of the season 🙌🏒⚡️ #GoBolts https://t.co/Iu9h783Bvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[whether it is a loving community or otherwise. If the man was taken out of the village to be healed and then warned… https://t.co/6ffO7m9IA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarcissistTarg1 Ignoring them is one of the hardest things. It does work, though. I have one who has been stalking me for over 25 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 @scooter36460 @BreitbartNews Kamala, since your family were big Slave owners, have you paid them yet. Probably not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @RepClayHiggins You, sir, are a total fool and a giant POS💩! You made yourself look totally stupid with… https://t.co/BQF8LOZOBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of my oldest friends!!!! Have an awesome day Ky, love ya ❤️ https://t.co/NKHxZSMmEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[About last night....Hands down, some of the best food I’ve ever eaten. omsabor prepare to be stalked (in a non-cree… https://t.co/CEl0BIZSFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke_Matsago made me cry over these last two @NBCChicagoMed episodes. Now, I'm catching up on @NBCChicagoFire and… https://t.co/yKk5xXEo92]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlin_rolli That’s why I can’t decide if I should attempt to do them myself or just pay someone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[A7: Social media is definitely a highlight reel. We always have to keep in mind that the daily routines of life are… https://t.co/jTyM9w6JWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady If it was Mad Dog 20/20 leave the girl alone. It's a right of passage, bitches. https://t.co/DWGOno4OPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[These entrepreneurs were ready for a busy marketplace today. In partnership with Jr Achievement BC, these students… https://t.co/0myR4GESKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino Been there, done that! Deliverance territory....scary...😳😰😱💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bringbackfear @NYounker @12nighthorror @Dismay00 @crashpalace @MikeysDead @PromoteHorror @MsChaunceyKR @MrHorror… https://t.co/S9seUCXrSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magee333 @SideHustleWino @VinoSocialNancy @jillianne_gray @RedWineCats @suziday123 @DivaVinophile @GrnLakeGirl… https://t.co/ZYltjZzTsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 5203 Brownlee Lane #Spring #TX  #realestate https://t.co/xvT9vpO3xp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a bath for Midna (@ Fast 5 Express Carwash in Norwalk, CA) https://t.co/ISFoUoomdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosieIsTired @the_bernie_bro It’s called “code-switching” and it’s incredibly useful in modern-day vernacular and… https://t.co/MTeZykizfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never forget this time when I was wearing a crop top and I saw this girl I followed on Twitter at MJC and she… https://t.co/P0HYz3ogEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my morning here! Got some great ideas to take back to @oso_new_tech but most importantly got to talk to a kin… https://t.co/Lp0PyNy6LS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acnewsitics @youroutervoice Sick sick sick. You know their parents don’t care or they would not be talking like this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess you can say we enjoyed our first #mardigras. @TaylorSarallo and I got a little competitive.... https://t.co/q2lzYio5XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[8th wonder of the world: my roommates spilling a pot of beans on the floor &amp; just letting it crust over...on 2 separate occasions 🤯👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I 100% think Boras is capable of competing with himself over this. He’s advertised Harper like no other client of h… https://t.co/kgpIiHuXWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aleksandraedits I hope you feel better soon!  P.S. A+ alt text—you nailed it. 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[😕 Leaving SoCal. (@ John Wayne Airport - @johnwayneair in Santa Ana, CA) https://t.co/giX9d3k5nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to get back down to 120 pounds and stay there. https://t.co/znS5PzcY1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoRedbone @JayandSteve @Shareaholic She's the pole( I'm sorry, that was bad, but it was the 1st thing that popped… https://t.co/dtLPEFOima]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunnies and sandals ☀️ ________  Figure No. 57 9 x 12 Acrylic and gold leaf on fine art paper, unframed Available,… https://t.co/YrOFxAAHRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraK93322487 Poor baby. Now she can get the treatment and care she needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a ass pic right next to a bunch of math notes and my heart stopped when I almost sent my ass in groupme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Oh dear hear comes another hoax.. I wouldn’t kiss her if I were a man... ick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Es330David @FrankDangelo23 @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton @BarackObama https://t.co/Qjkh61zUUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penguins if you blow this game....I will reach through this phone to slap the shit out of you....#LetsGoPens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tammy Enright started the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! https://t.co/SqXzwldzZP #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Valentine’s Day but it’s also been a year since the Stoneman Douglas shooting. RIP to all the beautiful souls… https://t.co/nccEkhjZFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to cut my coffee intake to one a week at the start of 2019 and it looks like I may have to cut it complet… https://t.co/U6srrdJQBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Jack_Septic_Eye have you drink regular coke before??? Tell me why did you like this orange Vanilla Coke? https://t.co/BXAJpaEnBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring training with the parentals! @ Tempe Diablo Stadium https://t.co/zMQ2grv4tE]]></document><document><![CDATA[just curious how to @J_Raaae15 gets on my laptop Bc I’ve never gave her the password &amp; I always forget it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicgarza09 @janettorres77 first of all, y’all didn’t have to do me like that 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gonna be how my friends are when I get my pet snake and lizard 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou to all who care enough about #humanity , about #freedom , about #Venezuela #FueraMaduro #FueraCuba… https://t.co/NQT6JQPMiR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy buenos días mis tiernos e inspirados twitteros 🙌🏻nuevo día #Martes vivamos siempre agradecidos. Algunas veces p… https://t.co/G5zKyJwxIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's sad but DemocRATS dont care they only want the power n control of America. Because they don't care about Ameri… https://t.co/fIOVo1md77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david3hart3 @david_andreatta Don’t feel sorry for him, this is all programmed from start to finish. He’s been perf… https://t.co/0pBilPZT5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so proud on this special birthday of my daughter jenweiss1984  of your 10 year sober birthday You have worked… https://t.co/1TMN4gFrk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaRiaCat @Jim_Jordan You haven't got an argument and you started this with insulting representative Jordan. You'r… https://t.co/Xz5wvF1ptG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcushjohnson If he can't protect or defend blacks in his own state how in the he'll can he do anything for us al… https://t.co/kKZlYbUovP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you find Cohen's testimony credible and or truthful #CohenTestimony #Resistance #resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is anyone surprised Jeff Sessions is a racist? Coretta Scott King told us that years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When there’s a winter storm warning for Pulaski starting Wednesday morning but you leave for Tampa and its 80 degre… https://t.co/rYsYF1TXvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place spawned from an Instagram filter. @ Broken Coconut https://t.co/hdDjmmDizG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rwmead OMG I WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHO PLAYED HIM Now The Loud House and Kim Possible have something else in common lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big congrats from @pennpci and all of your friends in Philly.....this really is our modern day pharma ‘Philly Speci… https://t.co/SVUUbPWNVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's their lost, not yours. #WednesdayMorning #WednesdayWisdom #WednesdayMotivation #WednesdayThoughts #GetUpDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katieppierce Just finished Deaf Republic by @ilya_poet, and this collection is hauntingly beautiful. I can’t recommend it enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #ShameOnYou You have no sense of decency and bring the discourse in the country to such a low leve… https://t.co/yWjfnM5E10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar We are sorry for all the loss of life. Why should we lose too when we arent abusing. Its not a one wa… https://t.co/qCyaRvFPQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[não liguem pro meu óculos, sem ele eu não enxergo. Só queria mostrar meu snow man e dizer que não quero tentar mais… https://t.co/nwqpH5d1MU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti Plus the guy tampered with a witness then and lied to the FBI through the cooperation. Judge can't… https://t.co/12nBP8pgPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s talk about that garage   . . . . . #realestateinvestor #buyahouse #realestate #realestateagent #myws #realtor… https://t.co/U5P5mRNuJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EHunterWrites I’m so jealous. This is what’s happening in my neck of the woods 😭😭 https://t.co/gtKTs277y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dax_x98 I just lost my 32 y/o daughter out of the blue a few weeks ago. Sometimes there is no reason, but you do N… https://t.co/KzAcz4KvJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arne Star you are unattractive old man Id never stalk.  You are the one who thought @shondarhimes was going to make… https://t.co/xU7mgWOI1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Natural History Museum of Utah - @nhmu in Salt Lake City, UT https://t.co/307m9FOaCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[alina and i are at the nail salon and there’s two yeeyee dudes on a bro date getting a pedicure. we STAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADmomof3 I can't watch Hannity.  He is just a broken record droning on and on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WeatherForTheWeekAhead #Weathercloud #WeatherForecast @NY1weather 4:14 am  video Grant City, Staten Island so it’s… https://t.co/pLy7bF55AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 18th Annual Sebago Lake Rotary Club Ice Fishing Derby has people from all over New England hoping to catch reco… https://t.co/zHpqiAHz9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[A regime change are you kidding me @tv7israelnews @osiyo_tv a regime change what next name will it be ?? Shloth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists Totally agree with you! Little Hitler has got to go one way or another!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harry_fosters Yes as do they all!!!   She looks pretty pampered and content!!!!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twoducks thanks for always sharing your knowledge... a valuable resource, esp 4 a 1st yr TAB teacher. 💚… https://t.co/aVOWub3KKE]]></document></documents></author>