<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@boston25 @Gillette @GilletteStadium "FOXBOROUGH STADIUM" 🚫Gillette 🚫Kraft  The New England Patriots franchise repr… https://t.co/RbluxM9d2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBIGAME @ABREG_1 Today’s my birthday and this would be a great thing for my son and I to win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s great to see a Councilperson holding regular meetings in the district to address pressing constituent issues,… https://t.co/aQZJ5HRSNj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s especially wrong if the husband gives no good reason for the wife to leave! That’s just oppressive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember the #SteeleDossier document that launched 2+ years of #RussiaCollusionIllusion? With intense partisan hatr… https://t.co/3yk1BW3sDF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get that #SquadWin with all 8 of the #ApexLegends … #achievementhunter #XboxOneS #BattleRoyale… https://t.co/bm0cHOsekd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daylight Savings has my body confused... usually in bed an hour ago but I’m not tired at all 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@igetponies lol probably so.. so do you think Corey Goode is a disinfo agent or real whistleblower?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@commiebobbie @SOTMead @RayPatterson100 @amber_athey @benshapiro Comatose, it's not too late. U have the chance to… https://t.co/w0r9NXAoVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @benshapiro I was stoked to take my kids but have changed our plans after seeing the @brielarson this… https://t.co/emXMfzcVLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Right is not mad or angry but the left is unfortunately unhinged.  Rabid in there DTS and hate has them imbalan… https://t.co/RWBzdDP71s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresidencialVen @NicolasMaduro ES PRESO QUE VIENE PARA EL IMPERIO YANKEES HIJOPUTA DICTADOR ASESINO NARCOTRAFICANT… https://t.co/QyXwNkLbEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @Arbys likes this, it will prove that they're officially better than @Wendys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Toy Story Mania! - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/DyRxkAPoQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[El placer mío estimado master, la grandeza es el resultado de la calidad y algo inevitable para personas de consist… https://t.co/aH1FKe0jlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercyGa29061222 Thank you for following me! I am very excited to connect with you on topics such as writing, blogg… https://t.co/i7hbfRp4R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunset #FirstAlertWX @MikeFirstAlert @weatherchannel awesome sunset this evening!! So cool to watch the sky change… https://t.co/s18jNigJKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are on @instagram, follow The Threegles for nothing but #JoeyJamieAndJulie content. https://t.co/xdC5Wjxx7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following up on yesterday’s #CrossingStreams...  Hot take: the Netflix hit “You” is popular, but as a show it’s pre… https://t.co/tyxe79OmeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of the @Riverside_MS team for coming together and competing today @VEXRobotics #VEXIQ competition.… https://t.co/DWhugOcKK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lying in bed thinking about that kid on #48hours tonight and how he's like that murderer in Bath, NY, in 1993, and… https://t.co/EMUt7UAtfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoooo!! @MilesBridges I’m loving that Larry Johnson throwback, not to mention THAT dunk! #NBADunkContest #BuzzCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoeMoton Now go and get John Ross and draft a defense with the first 4 picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodman Announces Retirement After 22 Years of Leading America’s Largest State Medical Society https://t.co/hlnAtjjVHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 5 on Notre Dame looks like an absolute geetwad in those short shorts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaraFawn Good night my dream woman. Dream about my tongue between your sexy thighs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanManning_DP @bryandwvu Cue all the salty replies from the softest fan base in college football]]></document><document><![CDATA[If people only knew how long it takes to shoot one tiny scene in a film. 🕚🕘  #HomecomingMovie 🎥🎬 (@ Be Electric Stu… https://t.co/ZiWCFT7mtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You mean like @POTUS is treating Kim of NK? Or China? Or Russia?  Seems like it might work. Praise God.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was trying to watch some thought provoking science fiction movies on Netflix but the alcohol always makes me go back to @trailerparkboys]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love doritos #flaminghotdoritos plus @ampenergy #gamefuel #chargedberryblast taste like #cottoncandy 🤤 @ Barton, Ve… https://t.co/Hp1SMWpDeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Street views shot on Kodak Ektachrome- • • • • • • • • • • #atlantecollective #urbanandstreet #spicollective… https://t.co/ZPCuWBArU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sean_Brace @Ruin2day @ChipReiderson @PHL_Influencer @FOX29philly Video confirmation. https://t.co/brik0zvyt2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RGGonzales1 Very, very real. You never leave the field. And it goes well beyond the relationships you make, good a… https://t.co/Fx1vpVtz6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WiiVik81 Happy BIRTHDAY to you! You coming to the show??? I’m sure we can come up with a FLOCK gift of sorts! 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJackFrank @Lmj09671870 @answerallman @Rschooley Fuck god with a tetanus-laced nail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonsterEnergy #MonsterTrucksRacingMonsterDancing needs you 2 construct what I see can be constructed as a… https://t.co/IhXz8drLXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this interview, Bradley Cooper describes, even after 3 straight years of back to back to back Best Actor Oscar n… https://t.co/Sbepkjzi0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CloneNic Um, I loved the 2016 Ghostbusters and highly value your social media content. I think the person that tol… https://t.co/ECqvPX8jTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennesota How you gonna be a radio guy and block people that listen to the show your on?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson  glad I spent $800 to be so disrespected...I’ve seen you 7 times now...you’re in STL MISSOURI...NOT… https://t.co/I10cVvygpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work tomorrow going to suck cause the time goes an award forward at 2 and I wake up at 3 so my alarm going to go of once it hits 2 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Model3Owners @Tesla I paid $11,300 (CAD) for both EAP and FSD in Jan 2017.  I’m already an early access program me… https://t.co/OXGXClr9dT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep fighting, @EqualityVA:  “In #Virginia, it is still legal to discriminate against LGBTQ persons. Presently,… https://t.co/TlSb7NkuOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeremy_K_Iwase Bruh you have no idea how upset i am. I can’t not hear it now 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiriamPatrick Our pen pals from Spain provided some good love poems in Spanish for us to read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss @AlexCro99199112 Then you....are a clueless....unaware moron...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough game for us, but I had a blast as the color analyst for the #Illini game today! Brian Barnhart is a true pro… https://t.co/B3VzC9xnsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump *Ian McDiarmid Voice*  Do not fear, Lord Trump. McCabe will pay for his insolence. Like all of the… https://t.co/zCEyXXuwqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderfully thoughtful and passionate talk by @norahterrault at this year’s #MetaECHO2017 . Prepare to be inspired… https://t.co/Y1NiNAF52u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just cause u delete tweets don’t mean you’re right just means you don’t have the proper evidence to argue 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshghz @Nig_Con @NSchneiderAZ13 @TheJaredMonroe @DeptofDefense Are you suggesting he's a Republican?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @Bharper3407 make a decision already. YOU are holding up the line at the grocery store. #FreeAgents]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really confused by the NBA’s “northwest” division.  Geographically @trailblazers are the only team who are act… https://t.co/JD51ZKzdXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimoneAttles @DatingAround If you want something cringe worthy next time I see you on hinge I’m gonna shoot my shot]]></document><document><![CDATA[No es exagerado lo que expresa esta persona y que muchos callan, pues es del dominio público,  como el Pte… https://t.co/YoVvbDRYol]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a mood 😂 I’m almost 20 years old and have been alone since day one 😭 and I’ll probably die that way too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome answers. Let’s make sure we do this when these come up.  #teachpos]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LukeMae after defeating #Duke last night #UNCvsDUKE #UNC #DUKE #SENIORNIGHT https://t.co/GyOv1FQIQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somespecialguy Haha, well, I guess I'll have to start following you so I can try to be in consideration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariahRockNC9 Pit Bull, Blue Belle, resting her wary bones in front of our fire. https://t.co/FS5zNjyhxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's take your hair to the next level! 843-302-1342 #raymercerdoeshair #charlestonsc #ilovehair #love #westashley… https://t.co/E8mVo6RqQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You heard GOOSSEN say he trained MOLINA and had him fighting as a pressure fighter, not trying to be selective and… https://t.co/JByhVB4s7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready to Spring FORWARD THIS SUNDAY MORNING 2:00A.M. which will b Saturday night n2 Sunday morning!!! https://t.co/F6xW42hzof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxingAddiction @Ronjohn217 @Bl8knstuff @Im_gr8nss @SibbieBoxing @boxing_fan88 @TheKidIrv24 @UnkhanciousAmir… https://t.co/tFCAjZaA1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[fun groomsmen photo - wedding  (shame his jacket is too big) #funniness #chuckle #grin #merry https://t.co/lejjbYpSS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The workout is done. Time to head back to the old apartment. 9pm is a good time. It's not very crowded now at Fitness 19.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No slugging around or resentment today we get stuff done and be productive like adults!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A meal of the day: chicken, stuffed with chopped garlic chives basted with olive &amp; sesame oil @ Paris, Tennessee https://t.co/d1SsZV1Jua]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 Stories From Women About Life in the Military https://t.co/TUQa297r8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisdollar09 @DanHuntFCD @3rdDegreeNet Certainly no fault of Cristian with a whopping 4 goals across two seasons.… https://t.co/RrAIpnC7sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since then I only really judge women on my impression of their ability to evade or combat predators in the wild. Bo… https://t.co/sFt3CLLE46]]></document><document><![CDATA[City Commissioners hearing testimony on Jeff Davis Monument in Brownsville. I wish this many people would show up t… https://t.co/Qz3l5chmPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this ⁦@octavosystems⁩ #OSD3358 based #EPAPER badge at #SCaLE17x  https://t.co/nGJVqxYGx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[This card, below. Is faster than 99 Calvin Johnson. https://t.co/gUpH5IuuKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti when did you find about R Kelly'https://t.co/m2J5HHZ0nJ TRAFFICKING and RICO STATUTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerJosef3 @froquedm I figured that you were still sobbing over Bauers and needed your "me time"]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge congratulations to Sophie, Heath and Zion for winning there respected divisions this weekend at the BGF Juni… https://t.co/R340t2imJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@destineybleu 😍😍😍 love them, would you ever consider offering the shorts in different lengths, well shorter lengths specifically?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpOrBust2020 @Chris_A10_USA @SpeakerPelosi #ThirdInLine  to becoming #POTUS  😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dude in front of me in comp sci is watching CoD:WaW zombies gameplay, and the game is over 10 years old lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We don’t need reductions,” Conrad says. “We need expansions.” @WDRBNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Can I have a Large 10 Pc mild wi..  WingStop:  You’re Name!!!! https://t.co/joKnmk5Bo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieJBartlett “I went down yesterday to Piraeus with Glaucon the son of Ariston...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone supporting not only @thedojoofcomedy but me as well. Balancing all this has been quite a feat, b… https://t.co/xOIdiHs051]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at the pictures of both of these women I see one beautiful black lady and a fat ugly white pig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmccabe_parish @parishbaseball @BSublet @coachgrubbs22 @parishepiscopal @3Rsports1 Well done boys! @MarucciDugout @MarucciSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the teachers will say it’s for the kids, insane. Let them pay into the broke pension and see their face when th… https://t.co/bllfOlN1y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clayton_walczuk @BranchRecruits @RecruitGeorgia Upcoming senior offensive guard @BranchAthletics hang cleaning 300lbs😳😳 CO 2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ainsleyearhardt @FoxNews @foxandfriends Thank God for Godly Women who step up to help little girls grow into Godly Women themselves !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DanHicken didn’t you say on our pre-race show McDowell was 2000 to 1 odds to win? 👀 #Daytona500]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Bernie Sanders is a fool and a buffoon! He always was and will always be!🇺🇸🇮🇱 Those that favor him are tho… https://t.co/yze5WpGNl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nos vemos este sábado en la Asamblea de ganaderos del VY https://t.co/AgqVGBjWbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing the game. Ice Hockey in Harlem has impact beyond rink https://t.co/YlHkFSzj3n via @NHLdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Slow Rye'd by @eagleparkbc at @EagleParkBeer — https://t.co/apTHGhQcBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh Lord! Now the President’s haters are criticizing him for signing Bibles in Alabama! God, in what else they’re go… https://t.co/dzw725o58j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopDogg @CropKingSeed @BigPercyRMM Calvin you was just like n Hallandale and didn’t HMU😊 Midnite]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a White Van by @solemnoathbeer at @bulldogalehouse — https://t.co/Krjs6l2Ofz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I let the insecurities win, then I won’t see the beauty in any personal growth. #TuesdayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Half Shell, New Orleans, Louisiana  #nola #neworleans #nawlins #louisiana #signage #neon #neonsignage… https://t.co/ETVQ7zLblY]]></document></documents></author>