<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[You know what I do when people express the freedoms I chose to defend? Beat the shit out of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New @PlayOverwatch lore from @LEGO_Group #OverwatchLego! Reinhardt is actually piloting a mech!!  (Just kidding - N… https://t.co/wYRLuXK8CQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CupcakKe_rapper Shit, Elizabeth, I'm so sorry for you. You ain't got time for racism. We love you. 🏳️‍🌈🏳️‍🌈🇨🇦]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some laughter. It's so shiny...I must murder it. #funniness #laugh #grin #comic https://t.co/Lk9yDIpwOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't think of anything profound to say this morning. Everything sounds trite and untrue when compared to the abs… https://t.co/uAETvsDGJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear I desire only money and power and presentable employees provide me with neither- Shere Kahn]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first person that i see wearing shorts on campus today is getting shipped to Antarctica bc THEY DO NOT BELONG IN TEXAS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_shutterr @chrisdelia You said the fastest sport, which it's not.  not out of 5 most popular, and hockey is probab… https://t.co/4ykdrEeOze]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 EVENTS ONE WEEKEND! We got our pool tournament this Friday and our resume workshop Sunday be there or be square!… https://t.co/0XWDh0PHoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wood, which has lived, and been cut down with an ax of gold, has the living divinity #CAA2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IronCobra هههههههه كلنا هذا الرجل، انا لبست لبسة لن انساها تالت يوم ليا في البلد، اجرنا بيت و فرشناه و تمام قوم رح… https://t.co/zCF56VlYfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I figured it out. Someone has to fuck the Kent state gun girl’s mom and not call her again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As the Superintendent of Glen Ellyn District 41, I am so proud of our early childhood programs and the positive imp… https://t.co/UdKNROviJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired and my entire left side hurts.   These very last minute parties that are put together and being expected… https://t.co/4KjhA2DZeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmichaelDave 👍🏼 to his “fastest Team in NBA History is an “endorsement” but I understand...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerkettPE @DrJoeDeutsch So now you need to keep me updated bc we are Ubering to the Amtrak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest! https://t.co/wxZR2JkWzi   I only says that twice!😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah the problem is when the dude don’t do that and the female is still entertaining the other dude, nothing wrong w… https://t.co/wYt060nYet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimMandelaro @DIRECTV @GetSpectrum I’m going to YouTube TV after hockey.   I’m tired of paying Spectrum]]></document><document><![CDATA[In celebration of Women’s History Month we’re highlighting some awesome books about strong women. Let’s get started… https://t.co/Vx40PtOFeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #FortWorth, TX? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Forklift Oper… https://t.co/HLwMwuhkXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great info. Check @jennycohn1 and @MarilynRMarks1 for tons more information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contributions are what have been driving this movement!  You help makes it so we can change the law! @ Bismarck, No… https://t.co/nUJs0NkU5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chelsea vs. Chrissy Metz Who wins this fight for the BBW Championship? Comment your pick. https://t.co/LH7R0WqZrH… https://t.co/MFL6TfqgRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you believe that there are really people who think gerard way is a cishet man...... i have to laugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start STEALING TWEETS because there’s nothing left in this tiny brain https://t.co/Eq7lGQq2v2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double standards are crazy man... saw a dude get kicked in the face by a chick while everyone watched and said noth… https://t.co/5BN8ac7yof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, those Margarita Kir Royales were good, but it’s time to get serious. After all, it’s #ValentinesDay!… https://t.co/fyyyEDKFKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non-#NASCAR question... So my pastor and I had a discussion about falling on ice yesterday. Is it better to allow y… https://t.co/4ijw3gPRYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandyinSeaLA @Sulliview I watch it only when trunk has a new scandal just in hope they finally have seen the light… https://t.co/cKETJ01bSh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these job sites look like they haven't been updated since the 90s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmackau If this robot were Lassie running to get help for you because you'd fallen down a well, you'd apprecia… https://t.co/wvbaJBXlhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierrasparrow @PodSuperstition has a private detective, a cop, and a barkeep looking for a missing girl in a stran… https://t.co/BV5sWNYFJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto gee, do you think he has inside information? is the wall gonna stop that? and by the way jim, whats up… https://t.co/y0RsmRcRjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[people being loud asf need to CALM TF DOWN it is 10:37 am on a saturday in a first year dorm we tryina SLEEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeirFoxcoon @MrCheeseGaming Make it your own!!! How many tails did you hug? I need to know these things]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots is happening w/ @AmplifySF next month!! Stay tuned 😎 https://t.co/8IqAdNwu4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump History will show you pass the least number of legislation of any in recent history. Do your homework.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goshenprincipal You can just put this in polar coordinates in your significant other’s TI 84. It will last as long… https://t.co/cajN9WnHBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love all of the movement happening in the @NHL these days. Exciting time of the year! #LeagueShakeUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pulled off a double singles win at the BDO Port City Open in Maine USA  Not my best stuff, but starting to find tha… https://t.co/WBIR0EdmLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was about 11, the song Life is a Highway was popular, and there was a group of kids I knew that really liked… https://t.co/ipi6Bq1eIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any NHL or minor league team coming into the area needs approval of Dolan because he owns are rights - minor hockey… https://t.co/B3K9dwoc3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @Finchyjoan Terri, @emmycarragher Mags, Mom, Shirley, Nan, MomMom, Mare, Kathy ... all the power to you!  Thanks… https://t.co/QSO2iMsNrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte Now isn't Chuck @SenSchumer just one Duckey New Yorker...they (NewYorkers) are all the same ...note Ch… https://t.co/DRNEFaYFS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Nice lie Trump.Saying his actual name would have saved time and words.Just admit that you are a mo… https://t.co/H8l9vfpVS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clutch free throws by D'Mitrik Trice. We're headed to overtime. #Badgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause it’s not believable   There’s video proof and real marriage license of R Kelly abusing underage girls.   Ever… https://t.co/kBf5tV2y0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[La persona anónima o no que hable mal de algún diputado sea del partido que sea, @VoluntadPopular @partidoUNT… https://t.co/hzAlJsayLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if Blackstreet could collect royalties from every white girl who still thinks that “No Diggity” is their entrance song in 2019.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hellllll yesssss "Pokémon Sword and Shield announced for the Nintendo Switch"  https://t.co/fungQg17oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F17sa @Herald_Reports @305local @NouriHamzeh 🤣🤣🤣 they all look like Mr. Potato Head]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, brother Blow eloquently teaches and expresses the truth in regards to liberal racism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pourquoitorrie @AnnetteReid24 I can't hate her she is aging way to well for me to hate her. Is it me or is she get… https://t.co/wAppvOPVPo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brady_minich @ryziegirl She doesn’t use twitter but yeah.. the kid went viral on his bday a year after that dunk happened 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I’ll be able to do BLFC this year O.O gotta find a room now 🦊🦊 I’ve wanted to go for so long, can’t waittt 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLB @GEICO Not in that park. He can’t break 40 HR in Camden and Yankee stadium half the year. #Overpaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀👟Too long for Twitter, so here’s a take on why #ZionsShoe could be a blessing for both Zion and Nike, from a PR st… https://t.co/6RmP0ISs7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Of course we do the economy is booming ,gdp way up ,tax cuts and the slashing of regulations helpi… https://t.co/AtrjUt50Ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurghBoy412 @MandyConnell Dude...you blindly support Democrats who want to tell you what kind of car you are allow… https://t.co/b9yuvFg1JU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now let's play a game of what if What if Vince would've hired @EBischoff in WWE you all seen his audition tape Say… https://t.co/5a9uxpGvdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also for the record it’s not that i was complimented its that being complimented and stuck in a car with someone fo… https://t.co/m2ufN4Uz3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why even discuss the "unhappy with salary" motive. That's fake news from a lying faker. We all know the real motive… https://t.co/6emSViwm7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my recollection, there’s no good deed or act performed by my being which validates your beautiful love for me.… https://t.co/jB0zX1sThp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@54sensaicrone @WhiteHouse I didn't vote for the guy, and I don't like his moral character or some of his policies.… https://t.co/9Ji4DSYcI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[La @F1 es una vitrina que engalana a #Mexico 🇲🇽 genera empleos, trae turismo, da una buena imagen del país, deja di… https://t.co/TVXPvXds8V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the K9 officers generally take control of the situations that they are called in or arrive on? Just curious #K9s… https://t.co/sGOaSUzwqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jody Wilson-Raybould just completely indicted PM Trudeau, the Privy Council Clerk, Gerry Butts, Katie Telford, Ben… https://t.co/nV60Suydes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twincitiestomd @tKCyclone @jared_leeper I’d like it in hoops. Creighton would be in the Big Ten over Nebraska in no time 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noah_w3 @matttttyb There’s one in the corner of my bedroom at @The_Fratican628 if you wanna go break in the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Ben_Baby. Well deserved. I think that day we spent freezing at the #TCU spring game clinched it for you. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC THE REPUBLICAN PARTY IS FOR THE RICH CEOS FOR WALL STREET AND THE BIG CORPORATIONS LIKE BIG PHARMA AND INSUR… https://t.co/iiGnODFGcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smokin that 🔥🔥wit @Donell_Lewis ....we out here fuccin it up https://t.co/vaDZqKdSyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachmanANjax You've got football on your mind- that's why you said September instead of February- can't blame ya b… https://t.co/gYahEAMy8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto This old hag is BAT 💩crazy! Not only will President Trump run for re-election, if you thought 2016 w… https://t.co/EZ7TtYvrF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched @deadpoolmovie last night. It’s still the greatest romance film of all time. #ValentinesDay2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICuRaRook @WSOP @ACR_POKER @raiseyouredge @WSOPCzar @PokerNews @PocketFives @depaulo_ryan @Wretchy The bottom line… https://t.co/gIo1ZXBAOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ummm, no, this was a repair job, not a new wall. No new wall sections have been put up, not one foot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildSoCali @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Wow, what a dirtbag https://t.co/p5PGlI3IYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s goin on today why did everyone at work wanna fight me???? I just don’t understand I’m literally so nice that… https://t.co/jJQXkn8Aks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnskrb @NormanChad That part is true...but the true difference between a tourney and a cash game is you shouldn'… https://t.co/lf6qqRUQIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[improved version of ash wednesday in which my people walk around with bloody pentagrams smeared on our foreheads]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @MurphysPubClift karaoke speakers are only rated for a 15,000sqft space at full volume. And this dude has them… https://t.co/AEf1QmXkT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charromty @MaoCavazos Amistad es amigo. Los amo 😘😘😘 https://t.co/NXZtjusEWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took another look at Chiefs 2019 schedule. Home schedule will feature these QBs:  Andrew Luck Deshaun Watson Philli… https://t.co/xnOfWP4nz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take my family to work day at @CheckersHockey with my wife and her sister. Sis got a camera lesson. https://t.co/rIrWnzjU76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliaHakes @saraanixx I feel so much,,, strength using it. I’m a 0.7 boi so this is thicc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakoppel @GOPChairwoman @trumps_feed @realDonaldTrump Guess u know from experience.  There are lots of that that g… https://t.co/f2YPUJI9ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CIBC in Mississauga, Ontario w/ @jay_aleks @texacanno @agmengage https://t.co/XzS9Q4cd9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Python Script Sends Each Speaker Its Own Sound File via @hackaday https://t.co/5CxIVYhjr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYS 3A WCD | FINAL: Timberline 57, Stadium 53. Final FT to clinch the win for the Blazers. #wabkbscores https://t.co/RHBN2XJ3u4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 48: Just because you can’t see it yet doesn’t mean it isn’t there for you to have. You just have to want it ree… https://t.co/32FRwMD2Ld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegeneracionMx Pueden hacer las conferencias pero no es fácil mantenerlas vivas durante un periodo largo si no tie… https://t.co/D8m6U7RPvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super zoomed my cat Lincoln. #🐱 #cats #cat #zoom #filter #pet #lincolnthecat #meow #kitty @ Area 51 Groom Lake https://t.co/WprIhCbuHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtkrpm Every time someone hacks a computer system, they leave an electronic fingerprint which, after analysis, can be located.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 4020 NW 90th Ave # 4020 #Sunrise #FL https://t.co/NpiyNMthET #realestate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the best music to workout to is anything by Jefferson Starship because I hate their music so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not a car person, I've never liked them. So I'm so excited in a few weeks I'll have a new SUV again 🙌 then my p… https://t.co/vOxztMyE4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troubles are temporary. Glory and celebration are eternal. https://t.co/ADrCjqhWK9 via @CrossTheBridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done @Mr_Sandlot the #crapcardfest game continues. https://t.co/ZLt25WFaZ0]]></document></documents></author>