<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@FWBHS_Band 🎶🎶 So much appreciation to our Superintendent for the support!!@mdchambers25]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing what makes you unhappy is just as important as knowing what makes you happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y ya van cuatro... Cuatro meses del amor más especial y puro que he conocido nunca. No dejas de sorprendernos día a… https://t.co/ECkeIjt1z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔪My Bloody Valentine Collab🔪 💋 Krista Martinez FB:  Kristalinn MUA IG:  kristalinn_mua  💋 LAURA BUNTING  FB:  Laura… https://t.co/jitBHjdm5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope these criminals are detained soon. Going around putting down our Prez with lies is tiring for us all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I woke up this morning expecting to cry almost all day. Awesome. It’s been such a crazy day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest That is weird!! I didn't even say anything bad at all. Ugh, twitter lol. I'm so thankful to be in t… https://t.co/C89CfPBHPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Scott, the #Emergeny is #children do not have enough food to eat.  My #grandsons and many children need more foo… https://t.co/kpfJFQpZ7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreiAndrei63 @marienassar_ 🐾 🐈  Gorgeous cat &amp; beautiful coloring!!!  🐈 🐾  Hope you had a wonderful weekend!!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmcintire You forgot the disabled. He ignored ADA by screaming at an engineer for trying to install Braille in… https://t.co/tmsS6lAeZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilyGorcenski @PRAEyesRight I remember Kessler was a proud boy chapter leader up until June 2017 when McInnes wan… https://t.co/gKPEut2UqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelFairman @billymflynn @KateMansi You know Chad drove me crazy with his arrogance during the Abigail/Gabi sto… https://t.co/dPLpLPSqWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denise_kandra @Titan775 @Yascha_Mounk I guess you don't think Trump swindled anyone out of any money despite numer… https://t.co/GEZCWrKmBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw Gloria: A Life last nigt. Such an inspiring evening and well executed telling of her story and the story of a m… https://t.co/h2P6u5kRCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonPaulson Omg Madison—History repeats itself...it’s 2019 and you ARE still a backup girlfriend.  CONGRATS! 🎉🎈🎊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came to visit for the weekend &amp; see the parade in his home town! ❤️ https://t.co/5iyrO5ghp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreyDeLisle Ok I see you girl #Comedy #BrilliantChick #HeyIKnowHer sorta lol https://t.co/9djSpjh1Qq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hall_hh at @OU_MGymnastics grinding away! Your #1 fans, @ShelbyElise95 &amp; I, were rooting for ya! ☝🏼… https://t.co/49wBPGCjNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watch for the first time last night, I don't know if I can handle the encore version. This is movie is beautiful!… https://t.co/93BMBJlyW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m really glad I grew out of my emo phase.  Me after accidentally binging the entire season of… https://t.co/MVHZFmtqJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent some time in hospital, lost enough work hours to being sick...not sure how I'm going to get rent paid this mo… https://t.co/I4VzgyXHRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CstampGames #21bday 🎉🎈 in #vegas 🎲🎲 TY glacecakesatx for another amazing cake #slotmachine 🎂 @ Luxor Hotel and Cas… https://t.co/QZCwPpWoxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job to Coach Annie and Lindsay. Congrats tigers🐯👍@Ridley_College @RidleyAthletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[more fictions &amp; #mysteries.  open noonish to 7 today thru saturday, 371 cotton ave. #downtownmacon.  #books… https://t.co/JZqXFnz1F6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JC7U @shookster1000 @TwitterMoments Chill https://t.co/PFbPRRXqRU via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianneLchan It really is great for fiction. And the editors give nice rejections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizagnnnn Technically, charters are public and receive state aid, so they have the same requirements. Private sch… https://t.co/QR1vKoi5Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have had not one single day off during spring break. I’ve graded from morning to night every day—including weeken… https://t.co/SrOZy4kyHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ranchera71 Awww omg Rest In Peace.   pretty cat sorry for your loss I know it’s hard.💐🙏 u get through this hard time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brewerytravels @Green_Tree_Brew @ephoustonbill @SommBeer @scottydog57 @JonMontag @excitedtofeast @IowaBeerBlog… https://t.co/mLQgTfbQQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cómo cuando en el domo care ya dijeron los invitados... Y no está incluido Río Roma 😒🙄 https://t.co/wDP6JLffEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that's cool, dreaming of giving me some free jewelry? https://t.co/yZJ4H7InwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifeofjai ❤️👍🙏 thank you all for your advocacy. The kids will win. Keep going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely had the best company I could ask for. I haven’t laughed as hard as I did during this trip in a WHILE… https://t.co/DD4xIWEQSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that my account went from a Joshua dun stan account To A Murdoc Niccals stan account  To A  Alex Turner stan… https://t.co/roC9f2YQyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are exalted for a little while, but are gone and brought low; they are taken out of the way as all other, and… https://t.co/CzcuJbAIiP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn @tedcruz @RepKayGranger @realDonaldTrump   You are responsible for  This outrage! You need to return th… https://t.co/MU8pBXs1lI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter @GOP Too much bible thumping, blind allegiance and memorization. Not enough critical thinking.   Tax t… https://t.co/H58ujYupAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ppablovelasco Por fiiin mi momento de brillaaaaaarr :): https://t.co/ugkrDfg2yd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya know when your pet is eating something and you say “hey what’s in your mouth??!” and then they just look at you… https://t.co/Br4UQvo1AJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's American Cup Day so I braved some unplowed streets for too many donuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the long weekend crushing mountains, IPAs and so much cheese. ⛷🍺🧀 Till next time, Vermont! 😘 @ Vermont https://t.co/SGVsuQ2Z1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICE is not racist they are just doing their job.  To arrest illegal immigrants no matter what their race is.  They… https://t.co/Y7oZJLjB0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[See yinz guyzes at 9pm at @arcadecomedy . The incredible @richtalarico will be sharing some true stories and then w… https://t.co/DaZQyGWFm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@couleurblinde don't worry babe I have never really seen a mountain either...more like big hills! @ProjectRunway… https://t.co/jsKV1Ii8ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought you was tough though. We carry choppers on our necks call it cut throat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children are our future. Why would we expect someone else's child to do this and not our own ? I forgot we won't ha… https://t.co/MlRF6r4aO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[te dejan como las de rancho¡!¡! 🤪🤣😂🤣😂🤪🤣😂🤣 #Facts @ San Jose, California https://t.co/e24yGzdpjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s times where I wish I was short but then again, I like being tall]]></document><document><![CDATA[that their African roots represent for them becuz white people, amazingling, taught them to hate themselves and Afr… https://t.co/VgxihkLlRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to go to sleep 💤 🤩 #MyPillow @ Our Humble Abode https://t.co/3Cb44k9Lj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The CONSTANT COVER-UP.  It’s how the malignant narcissist has lived his life. I actually have a part of me that fee… https://t.co/go5W95Hxmh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @CaribbeanCamera for the feature on #sashastoltzpublicity Client @MrJaneandFinch https://t.co/WviMLYJEuj… https://t.co/ozu9Otf8AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @MalcolmNance Lindsey KNOWS. He is just doing his trump pirouettes. See him spin? See him dance? S… https://t.co/w8aSggwTq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Than they are traitors as well. Limbaugh: Some in the GOP Still Want to “Get Rid of Donald Trump” – The Mad Patriots https://t.co/7aWrzu1BBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and get ‘em! #GirlScoutCookies for sale at Casey’s Diner, 13 Plaistow Road, Plaistow, NH today until 1:00 pm.… https://t.co/nQjNjl47Ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success isn’t a final destination, there’s always room for growth. •⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ Failure doesn’t mean the end, there’s… https://t.co/8EV3fJVXWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are so brainwashed or just completely prejudiced to believe that HE cares about Anyone or Anything other than h… https://t.co/Rwz5Qvryum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Megan and I made a pact last night to always spend valentines together, even if we’re no longer single.... it’s off… https://t.co/DMJA9mUDhL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from Southwest Philadelphia - the calm before an even bigger snowstorm. That whoosh sound off to the r… https://t.co/e0zNeQVRsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colton Lookin better on a surfboard than in an etiquette class for sure 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[im all in your way, and you walk on side of me 🤔... sis gave me the upmost respect. 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ African American History and Culture Museum https://t.co/OPJTfHHgU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Indoctrination? I’ve been doing it wrong!! I’ve been teaching critical thinking, respecting opinion… https://t.co/Gziyu79AJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaylyTVOficial1  aquí va el link que Arreaza está reunido con Bachelette https://t.co/doFK9WdCA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newcomer shebs_12_ making her debut at the #probluesjam at @thecountrynash with johngalloguitars and Glenn Jones on… https://t.co/Cket4kr1oQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vinny_Varvaro @UNCLEVINNIESCC @Twitter @News12NJ @amazonfiretv We need you as our “how to still watch @News12NJ if… https://t.co/XCUC4QqRpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This winter is the wettest on record for the contiguous United States https://t.co/noG972Ikln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sundays are for long runs. #SundayRunday #GetShitDone #triathlon #triathlete #swim #bike #run #grit #DoTheWork #GSD… https://t.co/BhSZMIsfML]]></document><document><![CDATA[They came, they were amazing, they’re gone...until next year!! ❤️ this annual collaboration! Thx Ms Calvo!… https://t.co/wukazqtDsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman This is the swamp we really need to stop. Making money on the tax payer backs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your hermanas are matching so you recreate a Sears photoshoot in your living room. #anythingforsalinas @AOC wo… https://t.co/sMwPngbuH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch for a hot second (splits my 4th bell into two). I spend most of it checking make up work (‘check your spellin… https://t.co/mYQHeL8ux2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you followed my Instastories today you already know I made homemade pierogi today. It was the first time ever, a… https://t.co/tT8MRqoKG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm starting a thread of things my grandma says because she says everything on her mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I continue to be amazed that her skin must be thicker than that of a rinocerous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Shocked and disappointed. That's how I felt when President Trump said in his State of the Union ad… https://t.co/9DaZEzhOn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@republiconyos @BenjaminG302 @1zenbitch @Stuffits1 @RMConservative @realDonaldTrump Hey but Obamacare was supposed… https://t.co/doiT50dqhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FHosseiny @cc_mhcc @elanaludman @GillianMulvale @drpselby @GBrimacombe @1CharlesPeter @FWKNOO 💯!]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/zR5melbS54 https://t.co/XsftH9ejEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#philadelphia #city #travel #wanderlust @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/3H5rtbzXS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha that’s why I only have her on fb .. and I don’t post on there haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@villages__ @MatDunlap @MillJeffer What a track guys. So beautiful! Oh and @MatDunlap does it again! Love the design.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/ Why can’t abortions just be “the price we pay for our freedom”?  #abortion #abortionrights #choice #prochoice… https://t.co/2pDj1omyEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leonard from the show @DatingAround is the best! Also New York seems like its on a whole different planet when it c… https://t.co/OccJsTmjrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forgettin from where I came and no matter where I’m headed, I promise to stay the same💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21ufopilots @realDonaldTrump No I'm shooting dope up in the bathroom at church today :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SneakyJoeWGR What would you say is overpaying? I mean this is just a report and you’re already criticizing the Bills.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiancaJoanie Yeah, idk if u can call what I am doing "yoga," but generally yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[away. I will NEVER call that IDIOT my President and I will vote for whomever the Democratic party nominates!  And h… https://t.co/Gy6b4HhtWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter mocks Donald Trump Jr. for retweet saying Cohen is telling the truth https://t.co/PYNpJkI4IK via @SFGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD end of watch 3/5/2019 midland Texas https://t.co/5M138x2nTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassenachSJ @Writer_DG @lea_robbie @hal12362 @AngusAngels @OutlanderHome @FRGRQueensgirl1 @SilverxVideos… https://t.co/R78NZM4FPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stand with Oakland teachers. Sending you support from across the bridge! #OUSDstrike #UniteforOaklandKids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckyWTGoodHair Missy did a lot of the production. And . . . . They don’t make dem beats like they used to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u livin' ur best life on a Wednesday and you want e'rybody to know #metroadventures #dc #itsnevera dullday @ W… https://t.co/x47fqX6SzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[PINS! They have a jk and TXT one! More to come!!  https://t.co/d2RKqkxiDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K9Rebbel That intersection is like what I have up the street but there are Arrows one for left turn green arrow an… https://t.co/ZnJqzAskp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. #Mawnin’ Love yous! 😘🥰❤️‼️.. @ Jacksonville, Florida https://t.co/k6VHsnoKgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raggapegs @realDonaldTrump Bet they will be replacing staff there soon, Barr will take care of chump.]]></document></documents></author>