<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BrianKupferer @DavisDavis37 @Steve_Irvin @abc15 Where the fuck did that come from? They don't have nuclear weapons… https://t.co/pH0o7wXeqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a haunted mansion pen that has a coffin case and I have never felt so complete in my life. I’m also ready to move in now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 mins standing between me and leaving working to go see @MorganCWallen AAAHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kandi You just have to remember she's in a better place and God got https://t.co/gcHza0inAr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is offsets album cover an actual photo or did he photoshop them kids on there lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enlaycock @hobaird @HoCoHowie cargo pants. don’t insult the man, matthew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always knew I disliked someone and today it was verified the moment he said “men are superior to women and always will be”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Theres an artist lecture on campus tonight and it’s a required thing for people in most art classes. I’m super exci… https://t.co/gWO1V6j4ao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajitsinghpundir @Jungle_View @better_delhincr @MengiKuldip @PNRATHOD1 @nirajntsh @AmreshwarS @25rubybaruah… https://t.co/lIOgGOJ7Kd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm on a controlled subtance and just got over a weeklong fever/virus so I'm just emptying the bowels of my mind right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjhinnant @CSpearsEDU @mikeaustinwest @ValeriaBrownEdu @PhilEchols @RdngTeach Us when we meet? 😂 #danceparty]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cozy #cozyhome #cozyhomedecor #elena_zimina_evnewportbeach #luxuryrealtoroc #babycooper1 #l4l #likeforlikes… https://t.co/oOhhTm99WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol some girl really just messaged me saying i don’t know how to rave since I’ve only been in the scene for 3 years… https://t.co/M67FUAH6RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today started p rough but I got to see @youngthegiant and Noah posted this soo, we’re good. We’re good good. https://t.co/5xZNfiglNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[10/10 recommend buying yourself a Valentine’s Day present. I do it every February and ever other month and am now i… https://t.co/u9As7pVA1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dehparadox Me hubiera gustado la parte donde está lloviendo y le dice a su amigo que no lo quiere volver a ver jamás.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went on a date tonight and my ring somehow flew right off my finger and I lost it. If that isn’t a sign that I sh… https://t.co/izn2vi6r8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spirit airline planes really be the taxis of the sky - smelly, a hot mess express, and obnoxiously yellow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Advil I am a single female. I have 4 towels and four hand towels. I hate HATE hate wash cloths, so I refuse to get… https://t.co/ZV51aAh316]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a smoothie consisting of avocado, banana + milk and it cost me $11..... please tell me how this makes sense 🤔😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brijslater Haha thanks Slater! It took the kids a bit to realize it was actually me talking in the video 😂😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerellrushin_ Just get on YouTube and you’ll be fine 😂 it’s super easy once you get the hang of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow guys, I woke up and ya know what? It’s RAINING again 🙃 I guess we only needed a two day break from this MONTH long rain 🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flick’s first snow! She was very cautious and thinks it’s very strange!✨🐶❄️🧡✨ @ Cameron Park, California https://t.co/zBZJAozAEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow dude. And you are proud of this? Why don’t you post a pic of your entire face so everyone can see what a bully… https://t.co/EU6CgCy5k8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PollyNaviaux Toothpain can be awful but depression and anxiety are much worse. Glad you are doing better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[70% OF HUMAN DISEASES ARISE FROM AN UNHEALTHY GASTROINTESTINAL (GI) TRACT . GET IRON GUT - WITH PROBIOTICS AND VITA… https://t.co/m6piAWnDu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrawlAmerica @THEJeepMafia @Jeep_Familys @Thejeepboss @MaryUnderwood9 @gavelar @4skullkrushers @toxicoffroad… https://t.co/FGbvBs8cJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally had some clothes professionally tailored and learned a valuable lesson: being short is expensive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher WHY ARE YOU SHOUTING!  My goodness, get some help.  I bet some women are super happy about viagra.  Some wome… https://t.co/qmO0ZAzMmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How embarrassing would it be to be breaking up with your s/o every other week...that’s something else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to a @PBS station near you! Super cool @fancynancynyc @prinniedidit]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t tell me Silky isn’t a Leo or Aries. Capricorn my ass #DragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuciferSPN13 @JulesHu863 @JannyLutz @AngelinaEdangel @aborddelimpala @demon_heart_spn @anitakearney65… https://t.co/mujAuTQOkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheViewFromLL2 True, I have plenty of those. Need to switch. And I have this too! https://t.co/SeW0ZcHwQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[in the kitchen watching kitchen nightmares gordon ramsay has turned me into a major food critic lol https://t.co/8f4YyLZZbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastofDons @KHOU @houstonpolice Police didn’t say, just that they tried to pull him over but he took off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #FrontDoorFriday! Let’s all stare at this beautiful entry. Such a unique design yet so simple. I’ve been cons… https://t.co/FQKn2oaAsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these is not like the other @ Denver Milk Market https://t.co/PpX73b64u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[she was diagnosed w lyme disease late term and faced physical ramifications because of it 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[ppl worship mumble rappers but hate on Mike stud and i just don’t understand ?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop MommaT, please keep me in your prayers. My challenges have reached an all-time high point and coping… https://t.co/ZzwRPH6vD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Blessed Tuesday Everyone! @ Edgy Girl Fitness Studio https://t.co/9Ge2WEF6Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles u are so amazing with your makeup 💄 congrats on your palette it looks great and I am following u on Twitter and YouTube ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The U.S.-Venezuela Aid Convoy Story Is Clearly Bogus, but No One Wants to Say It https://t.co/5odX8oT1Bq via @commondreams]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making everyone feel welcome takes more than putting an “EVERYONE IS WELCOME HERE” sign in your front yard]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cbp8Cindy @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz @joneill55… https://t.co/7y7vW36qIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched these go from having nothing, working their ass off to become a group in a TV reality show #No_Mercy,… https://t.co/bx721ObtjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@penguins Go get those crappy Flyers &amp; their scary AF mascot boys!  #LetsGoPens #GrittysGross]]></document><document><![CDATA[More often than not.. I dress for occasion, not bothering with the weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Trump supporters who have daughters and granddaughters... This is what you have condemned them to. You can all… https://t.co/SkmbqDzHso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump You must stop bashing your party the Dems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenstksC I use to watch THE MONKEYS myself and a Facebook Friend of mine had worked for him..🙁. May God Take Him To His Home..🙁💒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@good_going @mommamia1217 That's not even "American cheese", it's yellow... It's not cheese at all to be honest. Re… https://t.co/x17wjcDFON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiderVerse First congrats! ...but compelled to point out that just as PeterB has emotional reaction to MJ, per ba… https://t.co/P54llFlkNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can't buy happiness but you can buy coffee and that's kind of the same thing!” ☕️ 💤 • • • • week 10 of 52 week… https://t.co/5GljkFfzDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weekend with Granny &amp; Pa 🛥⚓️ @HudsonsSeafood https://t.co/gcb6iPoZKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Clark, “ Consumers want to hear the story! The real story!”Ont CornFed is a 3 star product and 5 star story!! T… https://t.co/xyrey8bIY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tessa Thompson in Chanel is just grab the black table cloth and the tacky rec center garland decorations and DIY a… https://t.co/BI31kJjKcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huawei takes on Samsung with its $2,600 foldable phone @CNN https://t.co/SobFoFimZ3 @samuelcnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I went to this and now have the same amount of information as I did before, which is next to nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[we played this note game at work where we pass everyone’s card and write anonymous compliments for the person we ge… https://t.co/OldmGqT1oF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HugTerrie @JamesRenee92 @escapedmatrix Until it happens in their community]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered what 1400+ students playing together sound like? This was the final song from Orchestra Fest… https://t.co/Jti5fRKY6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGno2trump Rs use every chance 2 speak 2 witness 2--instead--attack Dems 4 govt spending/Trump's failure 2 balanc… https://t.co/PKPHFo93Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m supposed to he hella hydrated today to get a scan of my kidneys so I have to pee really damn bad and they’re ru… https://t.co/LfUK5R44ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_sonia_irene Oh wait, if a squirrel went first, Jack would be all in!👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pixxydoodle @4judyblue @18RowdyNation @Nascar_Girl1990 @spyderrider63 @njfarmerwife @Hailey_Lynn93 @mustag_girl71… https://t.co/nA2HXL5z7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart breaks a little everytime i realize i’ll never see that boy again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo @AROD What a beautiful moment!  Thbanks for sharing your love with the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National @barbie Day, to the doll who has raised generations of woman to be strong and independent. She was a… https://t.co/dgmjzbfCoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @GetSpectrum my Internet is down for the third time this week!  You absolutely do not deserve to charge me $60.… https://t.co/22phXDujsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we just skip the rest of this winter/spring crap and get right to baseball season?? Please?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $25 Skype Gift Card Offer  Win $25 Skype Gift Card Offer By Your Email Id Submit,  Click Here:… https://t.co/sdp18Y0Dt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJeanSorohan @TarynDeVere Yes. This too. And also victim blaming happens outside the gender paradigm. It is a phe… https://t.co/8dkMAf9H48]]></document><document><![CDATA[idc if i slept till 2 in the afternoon but if i haven’t had my coffee, don’t speak to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Board Games!  I got pole position in Formula De and never lost the lead. My car was in fairly good shape, too. The… https://t.co/dv1Jj5YiDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes hard to remember when days are tough and trying, but something I’ve always believed about children.… https://t.co/CpHkQCuxp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boozychef @_drazzari @jflorez @tylerwinery @GailBenzler @wineNweather @DemiCassiani @jillianne_gray @rr_pirate… https://t.co/83W9JQOKhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbmoone @AbdulfatahBashr @AdamNiclasen @AliRaja_MD @AmyAvanzino @AnnaQuicke @Anu_roy @ARPearson2 @AwakenToGod… https://t.co/b3tXRlLtjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BookClub success! So grateful for the #ChemistryTeachers who helped me understand #radium and brought their… https://t.co/1XjkEgn2bL]]></document><document><![CDATA[don't ever trust someone. they can turn out to be hypocrites! be careful!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get as much rest as I can. My family is trying to discourage me from going to Waco tomorrow to meet the n… https://t.co/erRXvqHNCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My child just had an anti-Bernie ad pop up on @YouTube - it said “Don’t be a Bernie Buster - protect Medicaid” So..… https://t.co/kK85DukPyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Merry Xmas to me in February.  They don’t throw these from floats and I AINT, yes AINT,  about to wait until LATER… https://t.co/FZB8CsHHLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rorbot @BarbraStreisand Oh and it was “Hollywood elitism”. Apparently you have trouble reading too 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The yearling was the name of the painting. #CrosswordMysteries @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott @hallmarkmovie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy   You deserve beauty and everything amazing in life!  #Parkland #GunViolence #guns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention by @charlieputh and Lonely Eyes by @ChrisYoungMusic is the exact combination of my feelings rn. 🍷 #toomuchredwine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Once CO. We were crossing a 'dry' creek bed and we HEARD it coming. We got back to high ground just in… https://t.co/6q3m5IYofh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I went out on a date with my wife to Old Spaghetti Factory. This is one of the best meals to eat when ea… https://t.co/xDroqzxiCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of healing that happens when you are surrounded by good energy is AMAZING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @Cbp8Cindy @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz @joneill55 @FionaMorgan79 @Starofthesea007… https://t.co/9Wrsw6RxaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StLouisBlues Can you pick up my parents along the way? They are stuck in the #blizzard and we have tickets for tonight!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danielbkof2 Christianity has colonized and pillaged in the name of their batshit crazy imaginary god. Yet they wan… https://t.co/1MnU7DeO2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt BEVERY, saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK's Team from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea (Win Puppies) BEVERY is now… https://t.co/8nO1a9fElN]]></document><document><![CDATA[-No creo que te acabes la sincronizada de la 12 -a 🥚 que siiiii                                                -… https://t.co/Vrx2XdKxPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechrisbarron Thank goodness for the kitties. My 3 are running madly up and down the stairs right now. Here is th… https://t.co/esJ5iXB55f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best husband on Real Housewives franchise is @joegorga by far!  He is freaking hilarious and I love the love he and… https://t.co/qW8XT0i06M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanLairdMD I had a doctor say to me and bless him for it, “the benefits outweigh the risk of addiction. The risk o… https://t.co/z0ph9emcox]]></document></documents></author>