<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MPRnews The documentary on housing restrictions in Minnesota against African Americans sounds very interesting, ne… https://t.co/NVqCKRtbEe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFPK Thanks.  Can Alexa find it? (When I pull your link up on my iPhone, it doesn’t let me flip it to Alexa) Ah, technology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dlloyd69 Other two would have 17footers. DJ’s ......you would never be allowed in the same ocean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlight of day 1 at @SloanSportsConf had to be meeting The Truth, @paulpierce34 https://t.co/dlBkCTd6uv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao I hope feminist don’t attack me but she finna go to college n get dat WORK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday (kinda) @THOTSOFADRIAN   Hope all is well back home boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingJames Lol! Love for your ego? You bail on your team with time left on the clock, not in the huddle when plays… https://t.co/qF1dBD1skO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieBJewellery @Tpopularfront He's not the UK's favourite Jewish writer by a long, long way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was asked to work with ruff ryders and do street promo. I told my bro i ain’t doing that shit for them niggas. Co… https://t.co/1PRSG8A53L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chimmiechoo @PattyArquette @splcenter Blah blah.... it was bullshit. It's almost always bullshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie @dc_mma quit fighting bums and make it right...fight @stipemiocic or @JonnyBones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive up to CT to pay a visit to Nick in action. Think I’m gonna stay a while @ Trumbull Mall https://t.co/RvH9LaxZVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spencer just ran his fastest lap of the day on lap 18 tires. “That felt like a whole new truck right there.” - Spencer  #Atlanta200 PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanPham70 The whole bull fighting thing is not cool at all, this is definitely another level of gross and pure de… https://t.co/bUQJaqWL7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone said I should watch YOU on @netflix so I’m eating my pizza and doing just that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebkrier @ne0liberal @causalinf @erinhengel On link between discrimination and occupational choice. Extension to m… https://t.co/MYH5HtcLvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful day to #rest #relax &amp; #restring ! https://t.co/MvBZELQ5O2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @vulture quit it with the paywalls on your articles. You’re losing readers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWBone24 @AP Don’t forget 5-5 in their last 10 games (including a loss to West Virginia) and losing two key player… https://t.co/AnXxSs0NAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you need a public speaker for  upcoming events? Please consider Lawrence Hamm 973 801-0001 #Speaker… https://t.co/fdwn0k3bLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieDurdaWPLG @WPLGLocal10 Gooood morning Julie :) Outfit looks great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Atlantasportguy Trailer for Season 8 looks incredible - it’s gonna be pure madness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoodDeath is it strange that I think you have the most soothing voice? I could listen to you talk all day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Denise_Masino I loved your new boots btw,it goes all the way up your thighs😘😍and you'll need some flat boots in Co… https://t.co/hx5rgSDjx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear what’s happening...for 20 yrs the board of the teacher’s retirement system oversaw a system that wen… https://t.co/k0h0xm3uSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller 3 of my favorite words!!!!!         Hornswoggled          Bamboozled            Hoodwinked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hog Wild Saloon to be demolished https://t.co/AdtEonFaev via @TimesNewsOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 3 signs of old age.  Loss of memory, and I forgot the other two !]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKC police chief denounces constitutional carry law https://t.co/a5SJajUDZn via @newsok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey so if anyone has a copy of Deadly Creatures for the Wii, please dm me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Delta What's going on at SNA? No one to check us in? We have been waiting for close to an hour?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmac708 My favorite is I don't think he did it at all.  The Green Mile  and also  Away from the things of man,… https://t.co/sM2qhBZTYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go_jos_go Mais ça demande une grande discipline, tout le monde pense que je me la coule douce. Si il saurait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone wishes for something. 1 million views here we come. 60k more views and then it's time to get the next view… https://t.co/IxS7t5zWqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaitlynlaken I wanna suck those sexy nipples while your on top fucking me!!😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notthefakeSVP It's midnight Eastern and I'm Ron Burgundy? https://t.co/UdN3VIlZhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Redemption &amp; Recovery Restoration Ministries, Inc. https://t.co/xZffJbi2WO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hippie_of_Love @_jena4n @EmeraldZoo @franic420 @Cogitatorium @pitcow77 @Michael57645022 @realmedicineMI… https://t.co/PK2tYiM5io]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acappo4 @garywilliamsGC @damonhackGC @GolfAdvisor @GolfChannel @GCMorningDrive @APinv @APBayHill @linksoul A run of great days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snotrocket40 It might not be tickets but we have been talking about doing something for season ticket members arou… https://t.co/1EVt9lCoim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardacarbo @StephenHandwerk @AGJeffLandry @BlakeMiguezLA @SenJohnKennedy @JohnSchroderLA @LouisianaGov Am I rig… https://t.co/m6pDFiWU0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored that @gideon_pond can host our monthly Sol Latino Affinity Mentoring group. @BurnsvilleHS @veroramos_MN… https://t.co/I04IEV6YY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetSpectrum thanks for sending me a faulty modem, cancelling my appointment to have it fixed and setting a new app… https://t.co/ra2xgfJq1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the pressure is on, great #Leaders are at their best. Whatever is inside them comes to the surface. #BeGreat today! #Maxwell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APompliano @mdudas I don’t care if it’s a side project or that you don’t benefit, I don’t see how you can develop… https://t.co/0bzU5qWapb]]></document><document><![CDATA[One advantage to freezing temperatures...dog poo is easier to shovel. #LoveWinter #Cold 💩 🐕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byr_ne I saw the results of one analysis that gave the exact age of who would like the plan. Me thinks he was wron… https://t.co/8E1AxuS72n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Well ya can’t blame a dad for trying to save his daughter. She should be returned and prosecuted and then… https://t.co/PtVlY9Zk38]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just completed selecting the art for the Cary Gallery of Artists "Small Treasures" exhibition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlsCallMeGator Education yourself. https://t.co/6CVMl51YCK https://t.co/1ZQZ8Ej7EE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hes_triggatrey Lol is there something wrong with the suburbs of Georgia? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolfMonthly @piersmorgan "I would take @piersmorgan down to Times Square in New York and keep him there for an hou… https://t.co/XSKOkGtfAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it takes all the power in love and heart , but activate the King too nail Johnaane Cochran]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACE À TRUMP. Le Mexique se tient debout; pas le Canada!  Sans l'élimination des tarifs sur l'acier et l'aluminium,… https://t.co/iibH3hydkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrittanyxoxo Brittany you are mesmerizing naked, dressed or any other way. People love you no matter what you w… https://t.co/eexoTKs2y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@23_yanks @SportingKC @MattDoyle76 @Arsenal Dont you enjoy watching your prospect goalies going at it week in and w… https://t.co/9YJI60Kn6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christopherado Agreed though I don’t cover much betting strategy in my class. I don’t want to be accused of teaching a class on gambling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArnoldHSchultz1 @TomiLahren @halfpint1556 Just kidding it Was a Joke !! You Actually thinking that i will be a Drag Queen ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ça pas de sens. C’est encore plus frustant de se faire remettre la réglementation sur le nez quand tu vois ça en pl… https://t.co/68ZcQXKE1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[•?• An awesome desk made from pennies... great for a counter, floor, you decide!... #comedy #lol #smile #comic https://t.co/AbB7KXa9DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just stayed up with @sysdemes, @blind5pider and a few other people on my discord laughing at feet memes till 3 am. This is a perfect night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @CBSThisMorning @GayleKing Jocelyn has become a predator and groomer,I don't if you knew Azriel tried… https://t.co/MRnNlHaWr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is difficult to imagine the damage of the Obama administration. When Trump said I’m going to drain the swamp, no… https://t.co/nzzrvASxGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yetanothertwink Yes, absolutely meant original tweet. Yours was spot on and factual! :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricIsGuitarted No kids for me and that’s looking like it probably won’t change. So my family name is dying off. I… https://t.co/SatHgT3hgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtJacobsxxx @Frankr0d @ItsLawPort @WillStoneXXX @micahmartinezx1 @RCandDigger @jayxaustin @DillonDiaz11… https://t.co/aEnB45WXik]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Always remember your foundation is the Gospel!” - @JacobSimmons13 #2Timothy @747cbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday March 5 - Fox News First Morning Headlines:     Democrats launch wide-reaching new probe on Trump;     Ocas… https://t.co/JK8NMWsovf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pregnancy_Video @SpyroKush Come on man I’m just tryin to scroll through Twitter in peace before bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_meslin Those 70s towers continued to dominate the intersection when I moved there as a young planning student in… https://t.co/ML3LXKgblK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbrearley_mike Get used to it. The Liberal Networks and ad companies are too afraid of the backlash if they don’t… https://t.co/3xUS0X8zY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissKimShell @MoneyBadgerFC @Field_Farms Do the math with me Kim! $3,000,000,00 / 104,000,000,000lbs meat = ~$.02l… https://t.co/TUfIxasLfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working #SaturdayMorning but no complaints with this view from dtown @StPeteFL waterfront. Starting line of… https://t.co/31IL5Hm9kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WY7AA @jim9251 @NWSGJT Was decent on I-80 until Happy Jack. Roads dry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @ClaireDellaney, we should have a parade!! ... wait, scratch that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[# just see it  @luchsasaras @Fernand31004793 @austinmalestonr @AustinLuchasar2 @Valerie_Perez @ImDanaDeLorenzo… https://t.co/gZ2toJe5wX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjeong What about Vermont, Delaware, Rhode Island etc?   Tiny Blue States never get mentioned in this discussion for some reason...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slimshaady_ The fact that I’m still in college and write my notes with both sides of the notebook open just goes t… https://t.co/ISluQu5ByM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque @medical91 You are either part of the gun violence problem or a part of the gun violence solution. Gr… https://t.co/Iimwe1ddm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#new #trap #music #out #now #check me out on Instagram GTink$ - #too #drunk #need #coffee - #tags #not #billgates… https://t.co/qmWmL7E51X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry @tbonesbaseball fans we got in after 2am last night and have moved the #Steakhouse from @baseballhall to 1:30… https://t.co/yxSDr6NCUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took the British Navy 198 years to fully adopt the well-documented science behind citrus fruits as a measure to… https://t.co/E75bpdeXkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greenhousenyt @SenTedCruz @realDonaldTrump @HoustonChron Don’t be so gullible  https://t.co/oFBMQPn3jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to play with Asuka @NikkiCrossWWE @WWE @WWEUniverseHHH https://t.co/6FXRvxbSvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben And Jerry's Founder On Why Bernie Is The People's Choice https://t.co/8raNDNtqW5 @justicedems @BernieSanders… https://t.co/xfzqWALlgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danjuneau @Danielelorain @lesleychestrman @liseravary @projetmontreal The reasons behind vacant shops on commercia… https://t.co/IlDe905Kow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryQuad Yeah I'll wait until firm confirmation of this. I struggle to see how Switch would manage this game… https://t.co/EB4CBQl0p4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KennDavid1 Hope your having  a great week been busy here. New video's  tomorrow  hope to see ya there my Friend✌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas! Y’all ever look at a female and just knew she stunk! #maybeitsjustme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! 🌸 The next Primal Strength workshop is in 7 days! Come wake up your inner BEAST. Send me a DM if you'… https://t.co/PfROkuh19m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of my job I can’t publicly post my opinions of the #Cohen hearing BUT I will say that you should be paying… https://t.co/J6TozI3amz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Texas A&amp;M Law hiring Assistant Dean for Graduate Programs: Salary Range of $90,000 - $135,000 https://t.co/612YgRIPcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayyyyyeeee!!! We have a show tonight and every Friday night 10:45pm @drafthousedc #ComeAndSee #washingtondc #DMV… https://t.co/dxG3hNAyC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess though is much of that 54% still wants to see the party move left either on economics *or* identity politi… https://t.co/xJGKVaXG6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[With only a few hours left to our unofficial poll, we are asking you: ▫️ Was this bathroom signage (at San Francisc… https://t.co/oyDtfZb6AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awards Season Makes Beauty Aficionados See Gold... 24 Karat Gold Facial that is 🏆  With the granddaddy of all award… https://t.co/wl7edwRmtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLBNetworkRadio @JimBowdenGM @Bharper3407 Missing a Bat &amp; Balls!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People truly do have different tolerance levels to temperature. I'm in shorts while the rest of this Popeyes chicke… https://t.co/T6UHxHu1Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL I stopped watching as soon as the spoiled THAT Major character death. Its pointless to go see this movie 😂 For… https://t.co/pVD7JTL1Db]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI - Just doubled the length (from 1 hr to 2 hr) of my psychologist/therapist appointment tomorrow - gonna be hard… https://t.co/NtEuQNyEps]]></document></documents></author>