<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[saddened by the news of #AlexTrebek hoping and praying you will survive and successfully fight off #Jeopardy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trainers, #GOsnapshot is now live for level 5 Trainers on Android devices! Level 5 will be the minimum level for Tr… https://t.co/lEiAk6cF5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJWittz heedless of who you select it’s these master hands you’ll be catchin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @DonaldJTrumpJr Jim Jordan still let a bunch of young men be molested]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marijuanagolf Hey! Think we can get Trump, on board!!?? https://t.co/mySeizQGGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janetlynne211 @Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/73w23evqB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making sure to have a couple extra chicken cutlets this weekend bc of this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tryna be on WorldStar, n*ggas out of pocket I’m tryna be a world star, n*ggas out of options]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard about Alex Trebek.... you got this my guy! Keep the faith and fight with vigor! You’re in my prayers!… https://t.co/pL2ipfsO1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of these exhibits at #expowest2019 #expowest are from Tradeshowguy Exhibits. So glad to have them as partners!… https://t.co/tZfhq5T9qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[To work in the professional  end of the cafe like doctors, you'll be the finest in their company,  professor like a… https://t.co/dcIDpvvPq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok..lol I am 85.7% heterosexual, 100% homosexual, which places me in the bisexual quadrant. https://t.co/jPPod3Kl3g via @idr_labs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/iCqSN8U6DV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaddowBlog He works very hard to stay that ignorant! He would have to in order to be as ignorant as he is!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamilleKennerly @HarpTwins about too get back on the road lol 🙏🤓💪💜🤘🖖🙏💍💍💍 https://t.co/FZa5aRh894]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look behind the scenes...this is the printout I line edited as part of the 3rd round of revisions for this short… https://t.co/xSK9DH8FXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etaylor14 @wangchung3205 Love the initiative lol I can never justify spending more than $25 on flowers because it’… https://t.co/0rAlLbAmk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QrOlrNYbRH @deanbrody thank you for doing real country!! Found you on @Spotify by accident and I’m glad I did]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vcjate80 Same thing in Maine. Storm tonight into tomorrow and another one on Sunday...sigh 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day everybody. May your hearts be full of chocolate samplers and your rims have zero percent unem… https://t.co/58Od036haZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foone None of these folks ever read the Evil Overlord List.  You need to have a 12-year-old on staff at all times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Rowaan Actually reading the release about them puts me much more at ease. I'm confident there is a TV deal coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kupton813 @aplacecalledjer Lmfao technically speaking I was -4 but that’s besides the point I watched it a lot. Th… https://t.co/QQ1u3npHCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cordicon @Richard74195773 @RealTT2020 @codeofvets One Veteran At a Time! SemperFi, Aim High✌️😎✝️🙏🇺🇸.… https://t.co/zNQiEbmFMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mari_OS22 man i be sleepin thru all of them but now that i’m awake i still can’t feel it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@splitfire71 @AndPacing I would give ya 25 for her if you had proof of when she went green]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BirdPerplexed @SjwSpiderman @AbacusMike May I?   “And that’s why we must...”  “BUILD”  “THAT”  ”WALL”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derek Jeter had 98 errors in his 1st 2 minor league seasons. ⚾  Peyton Manning had 43 INT's in his 1st 2 seasons. 🏈… https://t.co/75AKmKgPuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeciliaVega @ThisWeekABC @jonkarl @MarthaRaddatz @GStephanopoulos One of the most beautiful woman on the news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barak_Shapiro I see you’re leaving WCPO - I wish you the very best. You’re a great meteorologist. Enjoy more time with your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The wicked shall be turned into hell, and all the nations that forget God.” (Psalm 9:17)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @Elaine_Greek @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren… https://t.co/36JVyV71En]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Penn State President Spanier's Request For Appeal Denied https://t.co/EGmKXSCCb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @jimtatti and @TSN_LouisB , not only was Bob Knuckle the GM of the Hamilton Skyhawks , he also wrote the team s… https://t.co/tbFaZ666SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lezbag @KJRushing @RonWyden @RonWyden already has #PAVEACT  ready to go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Closa112 @jaredtsteele That's really awesome of you to show your independence man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels like @JoeBiden’s in, maybe early April. Family’s with him; polls solid (for now!). Big field divides foes. He… https://t.co/4tBNuRbwCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOTCTickets @rex_rexchapman @KYChamJoe I'd say he never knew it happened, which is good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What can you say.... @StaySickGRAVER Vs @TremontCZW was violence beyond violence and something that has to be seen… https://t.co/BEjf9hiDYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are my 3 favorite trackers. @joshuagates  @SamanthaBrown @RickSteves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NineUnder_63 @IndyStarSports @nbairdjc Well the statement was factually incorrect. You can win them all. It has been done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSoundTigers @isles_24_7 No reason he should not be on Islanders with barzal they would be great]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well my morning is off to a rolling start, it's a Friday though so let's make it one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boo ♾ 🐍 Tavares. He made a business decision. He has to live with it. He strung out both team and fan alike. He’s j… https://t.co/VAzxsK0bvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK settle in because I have a @netflix  customer service #FAIL example for you - important for learning on how to d… https://t.co/fbTFAKxuaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was good but not great. Started a little slow but picked up speed in the 2nd half. Brie Larson was t… https://t.co/gJhDYXxISA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sexypontiff Tried to run a bar I heard while the case was awaiting appeal. Ended up costin Wayne like 300k]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only concern is can I wear one regular cowboy boot to match this boot or should I just mismatch and wear regular vans!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's that time of day again. #runners #FridayMotivation https://t.co/8HvzX6BHdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchuckJH @WaltsFrzenHead I don’t know. I’d tune in to see Darth go bonkers in the canteen https://t.co/lj9NUY4io7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyGird @SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump There are a bunch that don’t have a conscience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collegiate Nationals in full force at Ohio University! 2 platforms. Over 100 Lifters and 20+ schools represented!… https://t.co/LC5xCFIFnY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck To My Boy @rbenavidez_20 and @LittleRockBSB on opening day! #Trojans #CCKID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SithLordAR Also why is Boston trash, Id really rather not play them in second rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So jazzed to use my new toy! @ Lakewood, New Jersey https://t.co/UjF3c5bk28]]></document><document><![CDATA[1966 Porsche 910 Restoration Project https://t.co/9c1y6Tf0ae via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it just me, or sirperry on Instagram got a fit literally for “everyday” ? 😦]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting Ready for Sunday 2/24 for @runDisney Princess Half Marathon! Catch me at @WaltDisneyWorld #princesshalf… https://t.co/yYMQzMmK4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kiarasweet16 @RealWeddingBoss #ilvillaggionj #bilingualmc #sweet16 #djentertainment @ Il Villaggio https://t.co/JXM0i9R36b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/EXdSVcrKI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenericUserX2 @MiriseScott @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump We agree on most of this. A meth head is not going to g… https://t.co/GX8Sndc0HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internal clock must be set for daylight savings already, don’t need to be up ‘till 6. Only took 4 decades to adjust… https://t.co/mrwPvKub8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciaranfaloona You know what, I'd have to say that I do and I really appreciate it  Thou you never see posts of me… https://t.co/wrjFBKqy5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much orange stuff???? Just imagine Trump as a stand-up comedian!👍 He's a funny guy with his own brand of stick… https://t.co/Is2r7fG2TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Luponic Distortion IPA Series: No 012 by @FirestoneWalker @ Extreme Pizza — https://t.co/Yt0BaKn6uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oliviahnguyen there's a burgundy/wine red sequined strapless flare bottomed jumpsuit at my local Express that driv… https://t.co/YruRSSYWoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reacción A 365 De Katy Perry Y Zedd | Carlos Portillo https://t.co/BygDXGYmFL vía @YouTube #365ALLTHETIME https://t.co/4kvFQVmmun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO you really need to run for Congress,  I believe that   the @GOP could really need you to shake the… https://t.co/ozsFAEJfMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still just shocked at the fact that we gave up Mack for 4 picks 😂 and only 2 of them were 1sts. Then we had to give… https://t.co/XFcdlLP3Fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am the least athletically gifted person to grace this earth, i can’t play any of the sports balls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REI I just found this and it's EXACTLY what I've been wanting to purchase. But, red is the only thing left in an X… https://t.co/2JTyUa9UFh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YonhapNews It is not worth it you did while the American press was excluded from the dinner, it doesn't look like… https://t.co/hDrgIur8s7]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao what did trump say to man that he begins rapid rebuilding of the banned nuke launch sites dead bruh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esa es la presentación de la noche @ladygaga.  Yo le voy a Star is Born como mejor película (otra vez)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GREATMEMORIES #GREATTIMES #THEBESTOFTHEBEST #ICONIC . @ Icon Entertainment Branding &amp; Marketing, Inc. https://t.co/XOrBbRBnQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else want @Bharper3407 To sign a 1 year contract so we can do this again next year? #STLCards #springtraining #mlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaPotrykus @AlanModracek @RadioFreeTom I don’t apologize for being a #Centrist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bajaweddingphotographer #mexicoweddingphotographer #bajaphotographer #ensenadawedding @ Las Rosas Hotel &amp; Spa https://t.co/SFxIQXBTvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone who knows a lot more about lifting than I do.. can you explain why people deadlift, squat, etc without shoe… https://t.co/IA2N0jjwNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boeheim is coaching vs Duke Saturday night. Confirmed via Matt Norlander.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who I ran into at 4 in the morning. And now with wi-fi! https://t.co/R7ODnGndSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t let me in concrete with timbs... buy a table.. let me in.. if that isn’t white privilege idk what is..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTube @YTCreators @TeamYouTube @Google  Hey, I am not Mexican, Hispanic, Korean, Russian, Indian, or Arabic. I d… https://t.co/D5a1xfPzU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamedina8 @RunNGun8 @Teacherman1986 @CoachCahill I agree that’s what it ends up being. But that’s not what many felt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops.  Lost your skates...moves like Jagger @ Apex Ice Arena https://t.co/T971lmThh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[But yeah those of us who said it was weird how pro-Russia Trump was before he got elected were crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAO MY MIND RN EVEN THO MY PROJECT IS NOT FINISHED AND DUE IN 8 HOURS 🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialPDPNig @officialKolaO It is time to rise up against APC. Nobody fear like Nigerian soldier.If them hear sm… https://t.co/DAtsAOQA8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to mention free trade, small government &amp; economic freedom. Also extinct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[25 RAINBOW 🌈 UNICORN 🦄 COLORS! FUNK YEAH! #hailthehairking #hairextensions #illinoishairextensions #hairking… https://t.co/OqyvEbCNJU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hold Up, a song by The Boogie Man S.O.S. on Spotify https://t.co/d58BuBuhdr @ Muzic Empire "You Hear It, Now Believ… https://t.co/14FPUUFOHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natural net long positions have decreased since early November. Prices peaked in late November and have fallen seas… https://t.co/2gFlD18CV1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancelled culture prevents growth. Someone’s going to bring up I punched a dude in the face in high school like I h… https://t.co/CakFFy83ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SugaCaneRoxie @twickydicky @TheEconomist Here’s a reminder of life before we joined the EU.  https://t.co/HYoh7dafc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Go hard after trump’s grown children, they are not teens, no backlash here they are co conspiracies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standing outside the Alalderwood# after a great meal, I was slowly putting on my rain jacket as I noticed an elderl… https://t.co/EwjBxRmj7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mazour1975 @EdKrassen @PressSec @realDonaldTrump Are you really admitting publicly on the Internet that you are ac… https://t.co/aSayV7kjCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will NEVER ask someone why they dont like me, FUCK YOU &amp; your reasons😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpindell1 @kimmiechem2 @taylorbright Probably be pushing the Caddy before that happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlvgjockey Habrá gente q cree q se lanzo? Cuando en toca al animal con la izquierda hace un extraño y lo lanza, ad… https://t.co/7iahUKnT2b]]></document></documents></author>