<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@erby913 @Ask_Spectrum Pay this man!! And fix my internet right now or pay my cell phone data plan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez couldn't believe this tactic used by lobbyists. https://t.co/6yktzCMg54 # via @HuffPostPol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Check this out 👉#save money 💵 #live better #no contracts #worldwide 🌎 #this is catching on #HUGE https://t.co/pOK4drrkQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxJuuce @Ask_Spectrum Yep. They were a real piece of work and that’s why I’m leaving @GetSpectrum]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you stroke that hole and can feel every muscle. I always enjoy @SirSwallow1 🍑💦💦]]></document><document><![CDATA[All homes should have solar and wind energy within ten years. Creating 3 million new jobs. Made in the USA. Creatin… https://t.co/EIPDECagmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realGolfchat #GolfChat Evening all from very snowy &amp; cold 🇨🇦 A1 - Phil back in the winners circle. #ATTProAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you come to show a home but the owner forgot to put the dog in its kennel..... #realtorproblems @ San Antonio,… https://t.co/CDnqZuzrwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's astonishing how many people were ready to enter this damn store on the dot of 8am on sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AydenMekus She's a very lucky Mom! She has a Great Son!! 😎👍 https://t.co/V0SGzNuHl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a feel of what life behind the camera is like.  #producer #setlife🎥 #producerslife @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/gXdBHW4YPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice place (@ Rose Theatre Brampton - @rosetheatrebram in Brampton, ON) https://t.co/LSTSbW7EuM https://t.co/Tq4xbCp45P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BriannaWu My first PC was also a compaq born around the same time as yours. Could possibly have been the same mode… https://t.co/rfsGJ1QPwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minnesota (2-10) vs Washington (8-4) happening now as the Seattle Baseball Showcase's final game with a first pitch… https://t.co/tCe6Zwn70Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaneCook how do I go  about getting you for voice over work for my upcoming tv show that’s coming to amazon prime.… https://t.co/FeJaBQSsRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽🖕🏽… https://t.co/XFJMGRQbnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st rodeo concert of the season. Gotta love free tickets #HLSR #rodeohouston #houstonrodeo #rodeoseason #rodeo2019… https://t.co/JWx4cryiww]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few favorite photos from tonight’s win over Creighton! #LetsGoX https://t.co/u5SRsNbWmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking with my mentor today and giving him some excuses and looking for sympathy, he tells me “ if it’s controllab… https://t.co/Jhtfwxj1cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnyWatkins @IlhanMN I will give you my address and you can come here and tell me to shut the fuck up.  Fucking moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring Paul Rudolph’s Walker’s Guest House in Sarasota, Florida. Designed by one of America’s leading midcentury… https://t.co/taKZXJGpWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else tired of being called “tribal” by people rabidly committed to a single candidate on the left. I’m const… https://t.co/BC5G5fBieH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bill would have exempted Colorado-based SMBs from this extremely onerous destination sourcing law. Nearly a do… https://t.co/ZLjP4Y1cmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great read for anyone interested in the amount of money that the government puts in for golf courses https://t.co/cuzAw46OxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[College wrestling Eight UNC Pembroke wrestlers, including 184-pounder Brandon Sloop (Carson) will compete iin the D… https://t.co/WZr7IjmAo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/cFdrLIZZuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was an eight run first inning for Georgia. Riley King had two doubles. Aaron Schunk had a two run homerun. #umlvsuga #GradySports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_SKG_1983 @krassenstein 🎶 Give me three steps, give me three steps Mueller, give me three steps toward the door...🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Large crowd already gathered, waiting to get inside meeting chamber... @WPLGLocal10 #Runcie https://t.co/UnpyjqFUo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great afternoon connecting with colleagues from Indonesia! I had the opportunity to speak at @UCIrvine today… https://t.co/gsJC2kmdGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS! My wife caught the beads you threw right after your open! #righton #thumbsup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last weekend I got to visit these furry lil guys at the @DukeLemurCenter. It was too cold for the lemurs to be outs… https://t.co/pTYBSHJ8nK]]></document><document><![CDATA[She pass 40. When Khia was talking shit about her always covering her neck, she gotta be a old bitch 😭🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shit u not being a virgin is the best thing that has ever happened to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[May not have a Valentine’s but I’ll be running up a check 🤷🏻‍♀️ @ Hooters https://t.co/9qYmoJeR9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatAmandaC Bubba is such a capable driver.  2019 is the Year of Bubba!  I have every confidence that he will win today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading back to practice a day after a very long tournament. The legs feel 100 pounds a piece but otherwise good! Let’s Go! @gammapickleball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fbhw it's a bummer as a Landing leftover to not being able to listen to you on your website https://t.co/Bv85QZbjFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Sioux! - Drinking a Laughing Lab by @BristolBrewing @ Colorado Springs World Arena  — https://t.co/i2ERxITiL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any prosecutor who couldn’t convict anyone even trump with all the evidence already shown on several counts should… https://t.co/uqblmr3STj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hadas_Gold We need this kind of person to run for elected offices. Well done! #lovewins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Twain:  “Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely o… https://t.co/bF68x5dYQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sillywithsad Now you’re talking. Nothing like being construction to take your mind off things. When it’s all said… https://t.co/cvai7bhCYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought I was gonna go to sleep at 2 and it just magically became 3...oops lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Askren will be the UFC welterweight champion by the end of 2019. #UFC235 #FUNKY #WRESTLERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Heller Bock by @marchfirstbrew @ Bockfest — https://t.co/fIFQXy8Wz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight it goes down again clubsecrets vip lounge TurnUp Thursday's Karaoke Edition promises to be a great night So… https://t.co/sUxOtPJ9vq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaleej40 God gives his toughest battles to his strongest warriors. I'm not the best at giving advice, but I will s… https://t.co/Y3yOrK3WKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: suggesting that a romantic evening together could include throwing cheese on her face like those babies o… https://t.co/ZQAmtj4CaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommaUnfiltered Any given state has the worst drivers, and the best pizzas, I've discovered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MitchEiven @thehill It is disorienting that we live in an era where people who lost an election will stop at nothi… https://t.co/8FgmfwfPId]]></document><document><![CDATA[No I did not watch any of these Surviving (insert singer’s) documentaries. Most I’ve heard already or seen the clip… https://t.co/gRinsdhsCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks my 5 year Twitterversary. I’m so grateful I get to work for this company and with so many amazing, insp… https://t.co/UcwYIcZo5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirKingBruce @unclemike21 If he was coming off an injury, maybe. But he was a Pro Bowler. Gonna use that to his fu… https://t.co/1EdnyjgQ0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLGreenberg @MattHayesCFB Alternatively, you all could wise up and not challenge me. 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_botanis Is that Johnny Socko's Flying Robot I see?  Oh, following you is an easy decision then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas really be mad they at the same exact place they was a year ago and your not. Salty niggas make me nervous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterKozodoy Great article... often times I have to unplug the world to write...or even outline the crucial items… https://t.co/w5wgTdzMI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maxine the Corgi is my favorite starlet. #corgi #movieposter #horror https://t.co/LfPG02hLck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dalton leads off the fourth with a double that wakes the crowd up some. He advances to third after a flyout by Calilao. #Gators]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always a pleasure watching you ladies,  thanks for the love! @EvolutionDance   #saturday #night #carousel #glendale… https://t.co/YYLo0kwBb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wasn’t sure it was possible for me to like MAS more.   Now I see them watching soccer.     😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to share one of my favorite music videos and this is my favorite dance. From Christian Psychic, Angel… https://t.co/JaebzevRMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@serguht @AndrewYangVFA @PatrickCaseyIE This is what happens when organisms/cultures collide &amp; compete.  https://t.co/hxpiluTRHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoastalOtter @VillalobosE @Iwori07 @ConsultaPara @PartidoMorenaMx @PRI_Nacional @AccionNacional @VicenteFoxQue… https://t.co/qXaYESqL60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyslist @wendycarrillo Congratulations, Assemblymember Carrillo! I knew you would win! Sending you my support from AD43!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fortunately not sore from yesterday’s race, so knocked out another 20 mile Sunday long run on the treadmill at 7,00… https://t.co/VkDBpujTKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brain power off the charts w/ two Olson's on staff 💹📈⬆️ 💆🏼‍♂️ @CoachLukeOlson  💆🏼‍♂️ @CoachGrantOlson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_Coffin @Pontifex How many retired Popes can we handle? https://t.co/xJURjGUvUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2brothersoutdoo We have a long growing season here. I'm taking a chance putting it in before Easter, but I won't b… https://t.co/zyXkIBN2Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[USC gets to take more jump steps than the NBA does. They just pick the ball up and start running. Also, their fans… https://t.co/gJiWAGRdKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[OOOOHHHHH WEEEEEE! @Iam_AjSparks a straight/block steal, runs up the floor, dishes to @AirBeasley5 who hammers home… https://t.co/jOKz6VspPX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long couple days dealing with life. But getting back to normal today. #Sweat #GymTherapy #GoldsGym #BackToNormalcy https://t.co/0GtJSE118Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not kidding in the least. I’m going to end up pretty drunk today/tonight but if at any point you need a friend… https://t.co/P0YdlKmRsy]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNA DE LAS MAYORES INJUSTICIAS DE LA HISTORIA DE ESTE PREMIO ES QUE GLENN ICONO CLOSE SIGA SIN TENER SU ESTATUILLA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebo High, Sub State CHAMPIONS! @ Wabaunsee Sr High https://t.co/2m5BQMwRA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be proud of being stupid! The Democratic Racist Dixiecrats of the south are now the GOP Racist of today. They… https://t.co/i4FkGoYk3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adouglas_0298 the air is literally suffocating me 😞  it’s a wet moldy blanket]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glock__Lesnar Being up late making jokes so you can sleep through all the bullshit  tomorrow &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexa, play Cold As Ice by @foreignermusic. . . . . #Arkansas #Razorbacks #woopig #wps #gohogs #softball… https://t.co/bAs89u94Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[White House Memo: The War That Wasn’t: Trump Claims Obama Was Ready to Strike North Korea https://t.co/noJvNjCUod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smoothturn2 @horsechappy Woah woah woah, listen. I am allergic to chalk and maybe @heavydutyhal too! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up at 7, should I get up?  Woke up at 9, definitely time to get up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nena7119 Gracias que linda siempre Edith, ya sabes cómo soy, mis tuits y cómo soy en persona, oye necesitamos otro… https://t.co/N6qivULspZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder whenever he received opportunities his rookie year.   https://t.co/Wb0LKkGxdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[She wants to leave her footprints on the Highest of Seven Hills! Tomorrow, vote Kyra D. Freeman as your 113th Miss… https://t.co/8x033gxI56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great episode of the Disruptive podcast! So aligned with what we do at Crescendo re: Profit w/ Purrpose.… https://t.co/AN8PNMelrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Wifebrag post #579: gmnicola likes trying new things and is really enjoying pour paint projects. As awesome as the… https://t.co/yKftIIPEbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[History will remember you and those who stood with you. I am proud to say I voted for @JohnKasich in the 2016 GOP p… https://t.co/bWAA5cPJ8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenCarfagno Hi Weather Bunny Jenny.  How the heck are ya?  Didn’t see you yesterday on the ole tv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlvaroUribeVel Tal cual su gobierno nos acostumbró, importándoles un PEPINO la constitución y  leyes en un estado… https://t.co/T13mdpkXJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow I’ve never seen How to Train Your Dragon 2, and my heart just can’t take it...]]></document><document><![CDATA[my whole leg from the hip down has been in a TON of pain today and i'm just gonna take a tylenol and probably walk around for hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warchant37 @Big3Rollup @Snoop_Minnis @kcampdesign @bgedits1 We mentioned them both by name when giving examples.… https://t.co/LKx9PYHnBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher From the beginning when needle and thread were used to sew hides together to make clothes !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HailsAlexandra Yay! Let me know when you’re home and we’ll plan something!]]></document><document><![CDATA[all i remember from last night is that i was in a crowded car and was drunkenly talking of peeing my pants. ended u… https://t.co/tYfqQQVohz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zacshipley I know you've got work and family, but any chance you've seen CM yet? I'm really curious to know your thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 1 of the @YouVersion plan 'Encountering God In The Jewish Feast Of Weeks'. Check it out here: https://t.co/bWKyWzl02B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JIMrichards1010 I might have jumped 3 ft high, swore under my breath something like, this better be f29383ing impo… https://t.co/Gp8Mep5Lep]]></document></documents></author>