<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We are still figuring it out...it takes a team of doctors to manage and heal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[📣 OPEN THIS SUNDAY! 📣Contemporary townhouse located on Stanley Ave near popular Beverly Grove and West Hollywood ne… https://t.co/V6iWVqQbmV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_palardy Take a bow Matthew, your 2015 season on JV was the inspiration behind that workout to make sure the d… https://t.co/x9OdROfuXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would be great to see and meet more Chicago law students this next week - the students whose eyes are open to thing… https://t.co/lEQ6Nbe2Wo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeachersareReaders - by supporting their own children love of reading and learning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chapo_chris @p0is0n0uz_ White people cheat with family so nobody be finding out lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Shut you hole HRC!!!! You are a crook madam!!! #LockHerUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever feel like you reached your goals but havent really.  That's how i feel.  I know there is more just need to fig… https://t.co/LDKZM8riuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you thought it was cold last night, you’re right. We had a low of minus 6 degrees this morning! The snow is stil… https://t.co/5PkN4L1hkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scott_boulware @ANDY_CEE_ @Brwilson14SHR @DerrickQLewis @CraigSagerJr Fox just happens to spew the most bullshit i… https://t.co/0WNkdsE8Is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealtblake Lol this is probably one of those fake packages Amazon sends out to try and catch a driver stealing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playoff Hockey: Trenton leads Woodhaven 3-1 at the end of the first period. https://t.co/nO08JystAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[TY for sharing this @JonathanMTurk. I earned my A.A. from my @MDCollege &amp; can attest to your brief. #comm_colleges]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bvrrd @Dstepp0218 @Heynow01258131 @arielhelwani LOL. Easy to bet from behind your keyboard. STFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juslaswek @llaurenhenry_ @bottledfleet Heck no. I’m an Aries and I’ve never gotten emotional and loud like that. W… https://t.co/d6NdK634MM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian it certainly seems that you are an obsessed Democrap!!  Grow up snd accept the fact that Donald J Trump is ou… https://t.co/6CLft7NzrG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need an English Bible with a better word translation for “you” plural. KJV had “thee” and “ye” which was helpful… https://t.co/Rhh9u7MF4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not rooting for #ManU. But I'm definitely rooting against the Reds #ManULiv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CelticFC Pish pish pish!! Be proud to run a league that can’t compare! #poorcunts #howseurope 😲😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sasquatch Stout by @flagstaffbeer at @flagstaffbeer — https://t.co/8hSNlkGZEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatHarty You actually probably could have gone a different direction there with that burn, and I thank you for tha… https://t.co/sXLyTTOMgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, and if Obama didn’t get our guns taken away, it’s not going to happen any time soon. Let’s get over that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why so serious? #tbt @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/tnSduTgL8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rogers on demand = @Netflix 2012.  Actually no, Netflix has always been better. @RogersHelps #Rogers]]></document><document><![CDATA[CON RAZÓN CARAJO AHORA LOS ABOGADOS SON MATONES ESPERAMOS LE RETIREN SU LICENCIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iiSimeonSound @sblpodcast on Twitter and Instagram  https://t.co/HTphxXakzP  Spotify -https://t.co/TkH7RuoFTC  iHe… https://t.co/lLvLkdem9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grindin 💪🏼  Comp Deadlift 1x3 RPE8 285✅  Comp Deadlift 3x10 215  #24hourfitness #relentless #bodybuilding… https://t.co/L2tLjFXadu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@batpoet Thanks! We still have 3 to see but we're on pace to finish right before the awards.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lbt3um I’m sure Curtis was thrilled. The zealot racism was palpable. Like the guy who hassled the Native American… https://t.co/skfg7mHuRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would rather skip my first transfer and walk in the rain than wait for you clowns to show up😭 @sfmta_muni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamnJazAgain I mean I’m not counting because I’m not bothered by interracial couples but I see enough of both. Wha… https://t.co/xuPw9yI5G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to shop for new clothes, I'm starting to not fit in the cloths I got 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait till we see @Johnnywalkermma vs @JonnyBones one day! #IronSharpensIron #OnlyAMatterOfTime]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be honest, this is me: so many churches I attend turn Lent into a six-week long funeral.  I'm not saying I am do… https://t.co/N7rPOjraAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitbit #ezpz #mondaymorning #morningwalk #beforesunrise @ Orange Park, Florida https://t.co/K5cEpnC0zf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Earl_DaSquirrel @camdanos77 She can identify however she wants she doesn’t need to have a dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sandy45_2020 @realDonaldTrump The same people were silent when Obama sent Iran $150 Billion without congress appro… https://t.co/0JqrO7O4LU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom There is no defending Crooked Donald Trump. What’s truly appalling is the Republicans know he’s a cro… https://t.co/zd7wpnmgc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairohbk @AnthonyD_Angelo @Naty_SWZ @JZerojak Sigue asi y trabaja duro por el Mod ❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuntFiber Wherever they’re going I feel no compelling reason to go there..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_KissMyBot We need that money...if he refuses to return it then block all other grants for this state]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephendunkel @BillOReilly Swedish Economist Schools Sanders On The Ravages Of Socialism  https://t.co/Lrg3Vp9rJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jelynchjr bro don’t feel alone, I spent too much money on new tubberware this week, I’ve never been happier #washed 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out on a snowshoe and found this to the west of the house. #cummington @ A &amp; D's Place https://t.co/2pVEhJXeL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week I took challenges for my #OneHourSong including lyrics about @DPitz82, marimbas, ocarinas playing hemiola… https://t.co/EDNaSQ3j0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shore ties it, 1-1, for the Ducks, shorthanded. Nice pass by Manson sets up the 2-on-2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timtrefts Being a motivator is bad for the grumpy man image that I'm known for. So I had to squeeze a bunch of positivity into one tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fire Station 66 Clark County in Las Vegas, NV https://t.co/5AZf7PPfWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muppetfrenzy I guess that means we're teaching her but, and I did go to school to be a teacher.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m out here drink contaminated water and all y’all got to say is “alert” 😂😂😂💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL Do you believe Murray will go round 1?  5’8/9” has got to scare a lot of GMs picking a 1st round QB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twisted Flowers. Made from #mylar #artfromtrash ##sculpture #origami #ish #upcycle #upcycledart from nutrigrain bar… https://t.co/d4K1vIXtAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRedacted @politico This isn’t meant to be a shot at Harris just a reminder that before you make a inflammatory s… https://t.co/a72kbiwVmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infoparadox Thanks John, it’s a first articulation of this work, so I appreciate your kind words. #WorkingOutLoud https://t.co/fSSDdipDwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zzzweber @WBBM780Traffic Like mom used to say "Dont step on the third rail." 😁😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reverie13 @DonaldJTrumpJr Personal attacks are a sign of immaturity and of losing the argument]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loriellenew here’s my late Happy Valentines to you kiddo ❤️ hope you have a good laugh: Melania's Rules | Real Tim… https://t.co/6s40QJB9oL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EchezabalJuan Entonces te defines como un estupido inepto fracasado, solo lee historia y donde se ha implantado el… https://t.co/5Pu03JNmBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a little too much sun at yesterday’s game but things could always be worse... https://t.co/e0DmqPSgLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been preparing for this @MeekMill concert in LA for months....now I can’t go due to work...ohhhh the bitter sw… https://t.co/QpqGmtJtFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogersHelps hey is there an outage in the Thornhill area? Back from dinner and still no internet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to love the 7 ?’s the gas pump asks when it’s negative 14 out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mari_vargo @TODAYshow I agree with you, but you know Hoda is a SHE, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[100%  Paying athletes something more than schollie won’t change what’s going on (contrary to popular belief)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Balboa course needs to be shut down, xeriscaped with native vegetation, and turned into walk/bike trails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it’s been pointed out to me that I wear my @shovelsandrope hat a lot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great things take some time DON’T GIVE UP. 💥   #waterfall #nature #naturelovers #waterways #zen #calmingsounds… https://t.co/0G6MtIyOxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[California Wine Country Road Trip: Sonoma to Santa Barbara in Two Weeks  https://t.co/Ed8C0VpETg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama tried very hard to tear this nation down. Obama still Sucks and will forever be know as.............. https://t.co/ftps060WUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanover_amin @angela_pitts @TravionScott I’m a longtime Georgia fan and originally from NJ.  Congratulations young… https://t.co/3l6TuqgeLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be a Wildcat! KSU Big XII Champions! #EMAW #KStateMBB https://t.co/mjQYjJxytq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen... snow is on the ground. It’s cold outside, real cold. In fact, cold enough to cancel school. One more day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had my annual check up at the dermatologist’s office and a follow up for the pre-cancer spot she removed on my fo… https://t.co/kUZdOJnRR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronHughesMMA @Mraposo_ regimentstrikingcoach DRILL DRILL DRILL!!! March 16th, AMMO!!! #TeamNewEnglandMMA… https://t.co/5O7BfeZnLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notjessagain @DavidCornDC @AOC Doesn't change a thing. Everyone wants to be relevant and he tweeted a bullshit lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is NOT the outward show that counts, BUT the INWARD CONDITION of the heart. Salvation IS of the heart. An outwar… https://t.co/4UlJEDsP2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to work from home with your kid being home sick is damn near impossible to be truly productive. - Losing my mind over here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pninapf @haimfrid אישה יוצא בשאלה לא חרדי שתומך בחילל שבת ובהגייז וברפרמי]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaybayeeee Na I feel you on that 😂 but I normally hit it twice and my craving just fades away]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NolanHeffernan @GoBearcatsMBB You’re not kidding.  We were sloppy but the refs were insane.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning Raman &amp; Friends #PhDlife #microfibers #microplastics https://t.co/vgIOp9gIpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ClydesRides @webbellas777 @TimHammer11 @CaliRN619 @4x_Clubchamp @ImabitcSumtimes @realfrankberry @briantopping66… https://t.co/p2SVhqJ5mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s excited to see part 2 tomorrow of my banging good time with @micahmartinezx1   Subscribe😈Like🐷Retweet🍑… https://t.co/iZ64n3ELjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Don't have to get on your Grind if you Stay on IT!!!  ATL ROLLING..#TRAPNPAINT #BIGLITTLE #LEARVISIONCLOTHING… https://t.co/0MGxPVdotc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFigen I’ve already done it. It was quite a rush! 😂  And that’s only one of the rides they have at the top of th… https://t.co/7bAeBk9gqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleMoyer6 @smarxist_ @rob_sheridan The one characteristic I’ve noticed that Republicans have in common is the ina… https://t.co/XXQZCI7vi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJLang70 Please tell me this doesn’t mean the end of talking with TJ? Gonna miss you, man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The murder of 14-year-old Emmett Till based on a LIE by a racist flaunting power whites enjoyed over their non-whit… https://t.co/ceiqhHf9nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aamyjade_ Then don’t it is another stupid attack on the Estate. People sicken me with their forced agendas and pol… https://t.co/B79QkDAHAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapnCornelius Your buddy CBJ beat writer Portzline on my flight to Chicago this afternoon. Think he’ll be intervie… https://t.co/zFNnO48rXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_molotov @pocketmnky I fell into the same trap of playing every time I was tired and then just eventually gave… https://t.co/Zs66EV5QxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When #3 said “bring a title back to DC, uh, Philly” @FPSantangelo @masnKolko @NavyYardNats @DTally15 Should say whe… https://t.co/FvHCQl9a6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mullyhaugh Bryant is hurt an awful lot. The @CubsInsider would be smart to let this situation play out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoalieHistory @NHLBlackhawks That was back when Chicago's crease was a revolving door.  What's Adam Munro been up… https://t.co/6BgFcOvN7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotMyNameWhoU @porterairlines I've heard. We were in NYC last march, we did Air Canada (do not really recommend) b… https://t.co/fcbpEofj0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome day today, started season 2 of Game of Thrones with @MortarChelle , ready to knock a lot of that out… https://t.co/k2qBf7u7Li]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL!  Still trying to think you are #relevant ?  You were at best, in your prime, a B-lister.  No one likes you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teaps @nickdaddariooo @TMcGuirl @IzzoJustin @ImNotRobGudgeon Nah just fined almost a million dollars 😂😂😂what a moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marv_Time13 @NotoriousNJV Thanks for being part of the ST JOHN'S family. it's not over let's see this team do a ru… https://t.co/UcrTsj9U3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which leads me to Amazon to make sure Oakley has all the warm snow clothes &amp; snow shoes and I have no shame.]]></document></documents></author>