<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Day 109: Estimating sums and differences with rounding! #medfieldps #wheelockians https://t.co/opVNT85YOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela isn't yours #Maduro!  Go away now yells singer #MiguelBose during the #VenezuelaAidLive concert in… https://t.co/TqdYvqnnfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So can we start normalizing dick pics again then cause we tired of having to tell yall “i forgot i parked in the fi… https://t.co/lTL0kOVP3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nbell3 @jimsciutto Really deep state? Did you bump your head? The President got a foreign power to help him get el… https://t.co/ewYK2Dxygj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharlesPreston FIFTEEN! wow what a way to look back. Many unpaid... I'm probably forgetting a couple!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryBonds you should come be a part of the @tigers this season. With @MiguelCabrera and Skip Leyland we could def… https://t.co/Zk7diAVymW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you, Stacy Abrams, take that big fat mouth of yours and condemn Gov. Northram &amp; the Lt. Gov.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re just mad I wouldn’t kiss you because your breath smells like 8 cans of shark shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heidibickham1 it was ab you and a few other couples i know ngl. i still love you tho. i’m just tired of seeing all… https://t.co/ZghJpKOkvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog This moron couldn’t take responsibility for ANYTHING THAT HE HAS DONE WRONG.  However, I believe… https://t.co/CY1FKqmnYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I spoke at the League of Women’s voters fundraiser.  I shared my story about how I became an activist, an… https://t.co/LYchFqcoA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Good God, could we PLEASE get an adult as president!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[waiting for my bf at the gym, bout to take a nap. maybe if he doesn’t find my car I don’t have to go in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching that 70s show and saw jenna Fisher using her client number 7 voice @jennafischer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katepmcandrew @butcherbox @Imperfectfruit @reads_delivery Send me all your referral codes so you get all the thing… https://t.co/fXk5gsNxAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dobriksbutera @dobrikbait NO FUCKSKSNDJWNNFJSJD FOMG LITwrally A DISLEXIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[there is a clown convention going on at the Sheraton we’re staying at tonight and i am TERRIFIED THIS IS HONESTLY ONE OF MY WORST NIGHTMARES]]></document><document><![CDATA[Superb take on the Hanoi Summit outcome and how to move forward, by Bob Gallucci in @38NorthNK. A must read. https://t.co/52Oz9cUsqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still the coolest summer camp option by far #diseasedetective @CDCgov https://t.co/hfFP5FcCeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[A proposed charter school in East Liberty won an appeal fight against #Pittsburgh Public Schools, which rejected it… https://t.co/TgYVnHXAGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwoWITpodcast @girlygeeksocial @rockchick322004 One 👏🏼 of 👏🏼 my 👏🏼 favs 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys, I knew he would go after the 1st Amendment shortly after going after the 25th. I just didn't think it would be so soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Her hate began the destruction of the Democratic party and her power. Thanks for the hate and all y… https://t.co/jJt9WlvfeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtray420_ I think I’m just immune to their bullshit after dealin w/ one for so long lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Faith, hope and love! Happy Valentine's Day! Remember to love!!! @ Rochester, New York https://t.co/dOatPdzXS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Tweeps!  I woke up inspired today... I’m trying to create a music video using mainly still photos w a… https://t.co/jeYWTOkWPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @redheadjen21 @ActingSecDef We spend it fighting wars all over the world--18 years in Afghanistan!  --… https://t.co/AJz0m21kcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ez4u2say_Janis @robreiner No need....Pelosi has lost control and her party is divided. They will lose in 2020 to Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u see me out in a hoodie with my glasses on and no makeup tonight, mind your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need a sugar daddy cuz this broke bitch shit ain’t working out how i need it to 🙂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My intoxicated self told this guy last night that he looked nice and he just looked at me like I was crazy. Not. Ev… https://t.co/XWoeoc4xG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTomsriver @carriesheffield @LaraLeaTrump @AccuracyInMedia @IamJohnBurnett @FNC_Ladies_Rule @StevenBrill… https://t.co/mUwc2I09LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Room 13 is full of amazing artists. It was fun to see two of our artists have their pieces chosen for a display at… https://t.co/0iDpGJva7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so happy that after almost 20 yrs of living i’ve finally found genuine loving ppl that i can actually trust n count on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFilmkritik @cryborg Holy shite.  The whole thing was an intentional distraction.  EVERYTHING he does is a lie an… https://t.co/9rzCk8Q5zX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there any question who started the original fire at the cabin with Ciara now? #Days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XoSweetGirlXoX She’s awesome I love Carrie Underwood she rocks people Need to get over there self’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a huge project I’m directing this weekend and I need quite a few extras to pull off the final scene.  It wil… https://t.co/uGnubQMnqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_NoiseWaterMD @Jason_Paul3 @farris_april Bullet coffee, beef jerky, Reese’s peanut butter cups, energy drinks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an endless supply of black silicon tunnels bc I keep losing mine in my sleep 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐴Like our photos...Follow our IG🐎  🏇These photos were taken by me!🐴 🏇Photography by: Connie Wheeler 🐎@WheelerConnie… https://t.co/ML0yvGC43J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody just got knifed and Lord healed his arm on the way up!   MIRACLE TIME!!!!   Hang in there!!!!   Jesus is d… https://t.co/JTLX2stdC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything was quiet and peaceful until Steve mentioned the word WALK!!  Bonnie goes #crazy #crazydog #walk… https://t.co/7ykoTdyFbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snus_kin Is this a screengrab from #HeavyWeights when the campers are on their way to #CampHope? https://t.co/3Kfwtoybmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 No forgiveness  for what he did. He needs to go straight to jail. He divided our nation even more with… https://t.co/sI82Nrkm5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for letting me tag along, mercymcauleyart and French Club!  Today we went to see "Paris 1900: City of Entert… https://t.co/wUwXHBjils]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a t-shirt that says: “please don’t talk to me about politics” Some days I need it more than others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattiafeltri Facile parlare adesso, ma chi è stato il primo a dire che l’Europa non ci dava i soldi per aggiustare… https://t.co/oJ2CW2mDPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me compre el mejor exfoliante de la vida y me pone muy triste por que cuando se acabe se que no lo encontraré mas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@likrayado @rosyalanis mi querida amiga FELIZ DÍA DE LA AMISTAD te quiero preciosa ❤️💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW: Whistleblowers sounded alarms about plan backed by Trump advisers to transfer sensitive nuclear technology to… https://t.co/0D32CE2XqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cofe6370 Oh this makes my day! Thank you, Blue. So grateful to be connected. :-) 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ . So, saying you feel peckish means you need a cock?!  Good grief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hopeb4change @Top_Sergeant @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse You r stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Client: do you remember me? We talked about @JenniferNettles last time.   Me: Psshhh I talk about her to everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por esa misma razón no lo quería en mi vida, le doy un chance, UNO y la cagó tan brutal...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then it’s good to sit down and take a look out beyond - away from all of the noise, the stress and me… https://t.co/shkXFhYQ6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love to chuckle. It ALL begin with something just like this!  Hahaha!   Best Pregnancy Announcement Ideas...… https://t.co/A0Qntd6uz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was my first experience with the flu and if I never have it again that’ll be just fine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have heard about/seen the new FedEx SameDay Bot, how do you feel about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wavebird_ I go to restaurants by myself all the time. It’s great! 🙂  I get a lot of pitied reactions from people o… https://t.co/Yb2ZSdgozH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callme_raymond is in LA y’all! If he were to do a pop up show just anywhere I’d be there forsure! 😭😆 LA YOU NEED T… https://t.co/pTrnW9PTgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 3 little beggars ...those faces!! #yorkielover  #yorkiemomma  #whocouldsaynotothatface😍❤️ @ Jo Linda's Hideaw… https://t.co/gNDTwBtuEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning #Mlotters! I hope it's a great day!  #Mlottersnation  #Tunesday https://t.co/xYHXKign0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[prof_parker I am so proud to be your mom. 💚 You stepped out of your comfort zone and nailed this task! You represen… https://t.co/vFBgS4drEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ordered my valentine’s gifs for drive up pick up at target. God is good cause I don’t want to get out of my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[A win in Texas!! “The evidence has shown in a hearing before this Court there is no widespread voter fraud.”… https://t.co/vBULcu8get]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 3:1-2 (KJV)  Now the serpent was more subtil than any beast of the field which the LORD God had made. And h… https://t.co/gIGbxzkuJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite place ! The gym ❤️ #girlswholift #anericanbarbell #healthylifestyle #supzilla #supzillapickerington @ A… https://t.co/0ymcpu67Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fritzycarls If you were sexually abused by a pedo you would never forget it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @WABGTV6 and @DIRECTV y’all need to figure this contract 💩 out ASAP! Not getting my local channels it’s making… https://t.co/iyOVRF6Fa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamm_lester @MorpheBrushes @jamescharles 🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈🌈 love when influencers show they care!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinakardash and this is totally out of love and unbiased as possible . ( I grew up in the church but decided it wasn’t for me ) .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciate your concern, but I think you should treat a disabled person with the respect they deserve.  3/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLozanoA Ha de pensar que es como lo reprobaban en su mediocre carrera]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorneliusTanks2 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump Voting machines are not hacked, rather corrupt!  These politicians ar… https://t.co/dUDNpADBAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a rare weekend work day for some training, it’s going to be a long day..... 🤔 hmmm maybe a mid day nap?? Then… https://t.co/HURInyoOuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an AMAZING weekend!!!  ✅ Beautiful visit to alpagas.chelsea (stay tuned for some exciting news...🦙🧘‍♀️🙏🏻)  ✅ L… https://t.co/50gSa4OXKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking advantage of the traffic jam. 😳 @ Parkchester, Bronx https://t.co/Q295dZJi5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adamiington Mel B is not an ARTIST! The Performance was a thing of BEAUTY and will long be remembered and immortal… https://t.co/oXco6LcxoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden Great, but are you ready to implement universal single payer healthcare? Because that is the only issue that matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hey Huntsville is really close to Nashville” he says.  She replies, “I’m only going if there is good seats.” Two d… https://t.co/ZkCKhUW97O]]></document><document><![CDATA[custom printed washi tape,50rolls/design  #CustomerService #customgift #DIY https://t.co/ESLjNDplBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mercedes_adams @AnitaB_org @ghc @MobileCTC Omigosh! Keep us updated! I can't think of a better presenter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UN_Spokesperson @antonioguterres I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back wa… https://t.co/EssE4mrQcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look ma, no legs 🤪 @ Holland Fit Body Boot Camp https://t.co/h1ijuVuczS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Founders really need to understand that investors don’t want to hear that everything is perfect; they want to hear the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Galentine’s Day, @ZaraLouU  Zara is an absolute delight. Her blog explores the vast and exciting beauty world… https://t.co/D6ofufAgOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got goosebumps listening to Shelf by the Jonas Brothers. Am i good?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, we review for our unit 5 thermal energy test. Periods 1,3,5 - be sure your study guide is complete to partic… https://t.co/XYavfa2aJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daanielleryan Then you’re a no for me  (I don’t mean one word of that, I’m just trying to stand my ground &amp; be sa$$y)]]></document><document><![CDATA[the snow passes clouds push north followed by the sun   #haiku #weather #Snow #iphoneography https://t.co/k5ZQDssN3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Square building highlighting #livingcoral on aqua blue. @ New York, New York https://t.co/Ji4nQZt53H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram, Facebook, Twitter and Snapchat : Stop celebrities promoting toxic diet products on social media - Sign t… https://t.co/KwPpYUfrNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[O VERDADEIRO Belenenses está na distrital. Não destruam o futebol Português...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere in the 130 credit hours I have (I wish I was kidding), I’ve taken enough classes to earn an Associate of… https://t.co/K5CxNkG6At]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr When pd goes on strike is when I will be proud of pd in California let these dummydem’s deal with k… https://t.co/njnKG5BPBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/8rQrSRFqs0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dangit, we’re headed into the World Series of Bowling here shortly, Norm Duke is freaking about to be among an all… https://t.co/mAODYFpTSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your girl just got approved for an apartment and it’s move in ready..I am picking up the pieces little by little]]></document></documents></author>