<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PhilMickelson How/why did they reset everyones scores?  Never heard of that, but thinking about using next time im out in the rain😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Osiecki24 @HistoryOfFights @Hanson_Brothers Don’t forget about Used Cars and Blazing Saddles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[But @GovBillWeld is serious. The only question is who in @realDonaldTrump’s rigged @GOP primaries will vote for him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin how can they sit there and not say trump is a liar. Tell that cracker you can laugh at whatever you… https://t.co/VosnvkY63t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always love collaborating with @TheDoubleclicks! Can’t wait for you all to hear this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How a Young Girl's Death in 2000 Gave Birth to an Urban Legend https://t.co/Obe5cH9AfD via @vice]]></document><document><![CDATA[2007 #Subaru Forester S $7400. 125k miles https://t.co/z2dJiuseFa https://t.co/Y7tEouRRDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaplinez70 I understand bros, but there are other ways he can be punished. This is big match and he needs is best… https://t.co/EoHQjerDbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Catering Facility in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/lrHBZY3ft9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So imma try to push out four videos this week since last week was a fail 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you give your thoughts on ‘The Cosmological Constant Problem’ (aka ‘Vacuum Catastrophe’) It seems to be as ... https://t.co/ANsLpiOPR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ssnyder1835 T hats a pretty big statement!! You've written some pretty dark, AMAZING things!! I'm very surprised y… https://t.co/vsV1KJ3LKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Printed retraction of earlier post today that caused a major market reaction!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to burst out laughing it off. The GQ Guide to Naming Your Baby... and good laugh that helps avoid bogan names!… https://t.co/5KgB8FNjEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr The real headlines will occur when they begin playing contact sports like field hockey and basketball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @highbrow_nobrow Spoken like a true republican douche bag from florida]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RHONDA_USA @jackmurphylive They’re called men, I think. Or “males”.  Not sure what sperm generators are called...*… https://t.co/Oxtx8CZWMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manuelucab @Petrypsique Yo intenté algo similar. La respuesta no fue para nada lo que esperaba]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to go on a road trip and not come back until I ran out of money...walked to the end of the driveway and back. So exciting 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of warmer times on this rainy, winter day... #californiadreaming #missingsummer #whyisitsocold #winter @ S… https://t.co/NsRenenPwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drill - Coach Martin Chuck explaining you SHOULD NOT try to keep your head down. @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/agmyXKiA7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @realDonaldTrump Dictinaries definition of Socialism.    Theory or system of social organization that advo… https://t.co/eeq9lyPCTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes i really wish i could invite my brother over and we can eat the savemart super sub or get to work on sque… https://t.co/Kiu6dlzK4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zwift - NYC - Everything Bagel Course 40K Olympic (KOM Arch) #wezwiftny #strava #zwift #gozwift #rideon… https://t.co/bFCyQI1555]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashaBanksWWE never said she was better than Melina or any other woman from the previous eras because she knows without them there's no her]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me feel good about myself and follow me on Spotify. Thanks! https://t.co/t8KyKxsWIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The apartment complex where I stayed for a few years in the early 80s had a major fire early this morning.  I think… https://t.co/GhhAuV5CCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not mad at Amendola. He's nearing the end of his career. After taking paycuts with the #pats if someone wants to pa… https://t.co/kPaE1VksRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of love I have for @awonderland grows more and more each day!!! I live for your music and I can’t get ov… https://t.co/qeqnIAVa17]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm here to HELP you, because I ❤️ what I do, Let's Get You Moving!!! CONSISTENCY BEGETS SUCCESS   #realestate… https://t.co/WeOvXB3bWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we’ve been waiting for a new content platform and it seems like this could be it. The concepts seem great b… https://t.co/ljcOycb8me]]></document><document><![CDATA[No shit! Lincoln arrested some congressional Democrats he felt were trying to subvert him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErhaborFona @prometheus_team @nwasorderick @Obhenimen @eL0TECH @greatuniben @xigmaofficial You clearly don't under… https://t.co/GIEuZhOvOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@30andAlone @McJesse FINE!! Chips Ahoy have pure crack in them so of course I have an irrational love of the little… https://t.co/ArWG8irG5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnitaAma6 Love The guitars in your picture🤘 What's the story of them if you don't mind me asking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Ghosts In the Sky by @4quartersbrew @ The Deep End — https://t.co/WGago7fcbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we drill down on the importance of loving yourself. It's critical to your success and the core of your being.… https://t.co/XHs2DQLDJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a home studio can be cost efficient but for me there are too many distractions. Wish I had an office nearby… https://t.co/ywuoGieeH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRyanDale If you did, you’d have context. I get where you’re coming from based on the simple tweet.   We’d have… https://t.co/gBkiKMaoit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalOccupier @edwinwhysun @lydia_kou And yet life spans are greater in cities than suburbs. People get more exercis… https://t.co/EJFd11NcSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZaltzCricket Doh! This Bugler can't make it to PDX tonight from the coast. Free for breakfast at the beach, Andy?… https://t.co/pmPASeKS0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrible news from SE tonight. We lived closer to Cairo than Tallahassee our first 5 years at FSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t beat FM radio after midnight. 100% bangers only #KellyClarkson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwaynecobb @GOP @DonaldJTrumpJr @HouseGOP @realDonaldTrump @SenateGOP @JohnRoberts_CJ @RepMattGaetz @senatemajldr… https://t.co/qUtlsIGc4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HA_HA_HE_HU @fetusfilets @levic26 Y’all just wanna do anything to ruin an innocent mans career]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t been this excited about heavy rain and thunder/ lighting. Hope it lasts all night, that shits so soothing and relaxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WTF what do you mean no one is accusing you of crimes,  many people are accusing you of crimes you… https://t.co/yt53Qvsf6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sounds a lot like Facebook in the United States that blocks content from Conservative voices and ignores anti-… https://t.co/oRTFa14Zeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfloraHD @Natude1_asds @JoeZuniga1 @timgbauer20 @EmgeJim https://t.co/ZrjlzQE35B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk And I bet you spent yours working didn't you...  Make it up to yourself, go to the bar tonight and find y… https://t.co/ABsbZNviFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Haigh @philconsalvo Could have played in China... he’s on record as saying even if the rule wasn’t there he… https://t.co/dafJ3zRdNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoe tosses should now be mandatory and must be thrown at maximum trajectory into the stands. Fans will get to keep… https://t.co/2vAyLyhLrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/rXKpUlyogC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@byronjr23 @JohnLundRadio I bet the golf course knows the caddy and would have contact info #gofundme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freedomsmokeles You would certainly hope so Glenn - especially because we will all know about it if any choose not to do so!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Vikings as weird as this may sound should look tobextend Kyle sloter! I still feel like he has a very bright fu… https://t.co/ULV3j9JV6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StickToPizza In other, more accurate headlines: "MyPillow CEO makes one of the strongest cases for Atheism since the turn of the century."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyAlpha why haven’t you hit up @nobatechnology he makes awesome videos and he’s a teacher 🤟🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinDuska @KurtLarsonCPL This is so stupid, it has ne agreeing with this guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you sit here and listen to somebody smack their food like this???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTodd3000 @kel_robbins I know I sound extreme, I literally gag when I eat them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been gone for 18 months.. What are songs I need to hear? What are movies I need to see?  Comment yo 👇🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cazij @FionaMorgan79 @suziday123 @jflorez @MUC_Airport @Cbp8Cindy @JackConnie @magee333 @ja2cook @CaraMiaSG… https://t.co/7UIPr3KRwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_reno @C_Robbins_ Pretty sure @erikschlitt was talking about this the other day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Storm Spotter talk. At the North Central Kansas Technical College in Beloit. Tuesday March 5th from 6:30-8:30pm. Ho… https://t.co/UTwAc0DUdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee with Real Estate Investors at Starbucks #meetup #okcrei #realestate  https://t.co/YAKpDtpD7F @ Starbucks https://t.co/rC4XI6P7HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drifter12552121 @LizTorralba3 @Franklin_Graham @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @BGEA @SamaritansPurse Actually, we know th… https://t.co/FvyMVRtGK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t think you need to communicate better i think you need to find something better to talk about]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianaSkinner_ @maciijoness It bewilders me that you’re trying to insult someone by their looks while your tweets… https://t.co/hB6oDk35Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peachygawgagirl @richdollaz @JoeBudden I’m out here arguing for both of y’all lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Only thing you should apologize for is spelling it “Angelinos” instead of “Angelenos”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexWardVox Finally have a thing to focus on! Besides the whole world!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobPratte https://t.co/r8h6gjjOK8 @PittsburghPG @PGSportsNow @Dollar_Bank @WRIGHTAUTOGROUP https://t.co/WSCVVFWghj https://t.co/sJreDUDob9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The Lord replied to Moses, “I will indeed do what you have asked, for I look favorably on you, and I know you by n… https://t.co/Cr00sjiFlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orpy44 @steph93065 @Ilhan ..she’s a fool, tracy..thinks “impeachment” means removal.. #maga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sola_Veritas @Goodbye_Jesus @ovjocm @mikemaz57 @crazydoctorlady I’m down with that. 100 years seems excessive. My… https://t.co/Q6zqrQFKar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VapeTheBud Never too much information. The more the better. Thank you for such a helpful and thorough reply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Antoinetteeeee mannnn if you play for the seahawks omg im starting you on madden every fucking time]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cars #california #garagelatino #petersenmuseum #orangecounty #photography #instagram #photo #clasic #classiccars… https://t.co/i0Wgkm3aqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night in the lab finishing up a run!  #HealersNotDealers #HempHeals #KNOWYOURCBD #NotJustCBD #ENDPAINNOTLIVES… https://t.co/Wf4FuQkMFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you don’t think it can happen here....watch https://t.co/dXIAklAL1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders Buenos días! Quería que se desayunasen con este tweet del senador Americano y Socialista, Bernie Sander… https://t.co/c6itNFlGl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perverted_creep I have an old picture that looks almost EXACTLY like this, and it’s tripping me out, lemme go find it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metrolink  Today is an especially good day to leave the car at home and take metrolink]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barrett has been invited on a football recruitment visit to Georgia Tech! That’s pretty cool thebarrettwooden ! @ Q… https://t.co/vjMnLCvWZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I can’t believe they paid him this much. Harper is about to get paaiiiiiiid from the Phillies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to take a deep, cool breath of this beautifully crisp morning we're experiencing in the valley today. This need… https://t.co/Tl1eueRGlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday, Tuesday,  &amp; Wednesday, (2/25 - 2/27/19). @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/tXg0eDINju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kissing you thru the phone Ari... I bet your lips taste like bubble gum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epeterd916 @AV_SardonicWaif @VeroniqueSemtex @historybythpint @IAMISjp @heartsabustin @El__Bohemio @IOurpatio… https://t.co/S8R3mcyhBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I reached full adulthood when my only requirement when picking bras/underwear is what is the most comfortable option?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nate_Poppe I bet it’s this they’re not too fond of https://t.co/yk8ISnmg4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Popcorn in hand. It’s movie time! #CaptainMarvel #Avengers #MCU #Marvel @ Century at Tanforan https://t.co/cG9irzYyOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horsemandon @deltaracing Sal's $1 late dd  R9. 3 R10. 2,4,5,9 $4 good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LennartHerrera Si, pero esa llave no fueron los mismo de las otras 2 ... O l diferencia fue que tigres no era el atlas ni Morelia ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[If so, I would like to speak to Jermaine Dupri, who made us believe it was real and verses were recorded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoankaSW @ZbigniewHoldys @wybierz_TERAZ @RyszardPetru @Schmidt_PL @adamkadziela Oddal Polske Zydom.Psia lojalnosc dla wlascicieli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys who try to start snap streaks with other guys are OC suspect 🙅🏽‍♂️🧢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janiobi A hot priest???? That was my number 1 fantasy growing up in catholic school lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimiuorio @JoseCanseco I’d fork over some cash to watch @JoseCanseco beat the heck out of A-Fraud!!]]></document></documents></author>