<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[How about a nice bipartisan project: Expose and remove influence of Saudi Arabia Lobby. Begin with heariings, come… https://t.co/udFmR1MgYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because my parents taught me that I could accomplish anything!   #InternationalWomensDay #ThrowBack #preschool… https://t.co/MCGGEjp2Ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliraneymusic @DearEvanHansen @Mirvish Amazing! I want to see this so badly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyTammyBruce @foxandfriends @ainsleyearhardt @SteveDoocy @kilmeade Having my coffee warchonf https://t.co/qvC1HH2N2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[This!!! Why Earpers fight for #WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing fulfill your commitment to Get our cast and crew ba… https://t.co/ObJRVaOdYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Global brands like @Nike have an incredible opportunity and responsibility to change the common societal dialogue a… https://t.co/RO9ctH8GPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s some selfies which is the only quality content I can really provide https://t.co/MAsNsFy6p1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peek-a-boo bridge at sunset. #wahi #washingtonheights #gwbridge #sunset #sunsetnyc #nyc @ Hudson Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/IL2dy5HMAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHibberd @GameOfThrones anything (any"one") that has Arya THAT terrified...? freaks me out!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have that gif of Minhyuk dumping a bottle of water into a champagne flute?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valeeriaahh @loveesydneyy_ Bitch 😂😂😂 i literally said word before u so HA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some days I need a little motivation from @garyvee or @SpartanUpPod other days I reach for @SuperSoulSunday or… https://t.co/T1m0A8cy2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish we did. Sheer has nothing to offer except criticism. This is all much a do about NOTHING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate thinking about the future too much, because I’m not where I want to be, or with who I thought I’d be. It’s j… https://t.co/FnHO07SXAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well my Monday is great. Woke up to my car not starting. How’s your Monday goin?🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally Counting Down the Days So Far Toda Vía Me Faltan 3 months 25 days and 3 hours Waiting A Bit Impatiently J… https://t.co/Bm9zlysC5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really hope she does this! One of my amputee friends has, "I can still kick your ass with one leg," on her remain… https://t.co/bl3azuKxjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teagan https://t.co/7hjYeRP2kP via @YouTube @NBCTheVoice she is amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally have the best job in the world &amp; my heart is so full wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Every single one of them that we’re a party to that should be expelled. These are the people who are representing “the people”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djcarl937's freestyle mix this Wednesday only on the Empowered Houred powered by @thisisqueendom on the station th… https://t.co/9OKBTt605i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEG_NARCISSIST @torontopaper1 “Meghan Markle's facialist, Nichola Joss,”?? Guessing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope will be my bestfriend for life man, I can see us now causing trouble while we’re like 70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmckinnon @algore @SHO_TheCircus I enjoyed this interview very much. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Educate. Celebrate. Inspire💕.. #IWD2019 #WomenInSportsCBC  📸: @mike_cowley @cbcsports @ CBC Toronto https://t.co/xu8NCkfsrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylethegreat33 your rising is how you come off to people. my rising is in cancer as well. basically we come off as… https://t.co/tiX9yFlYo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckenrickreads Only and ugly were the tricky ones we really had to break down and discuss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katheyandpaul @ChrisPantani @PBR @davidsburgers @EdPalma5 @chadberger @TeamCooperTire @abbinow @cowboylifestyle… https://t.co/Ns2nHhOD6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ambermfreeman @lisa_carrasco2 @LauraSheffiel20 Data drives instruction at Murnin Elementary!! Way to go!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexgraysf @Twitter I BETTER SEE YOU IN ATL THAT'S NOT A THREAT IT JUST SOUNDS LIKE ONE BECAUSE OF ALL CAPS BUT OK SEE U SOON.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are unique and so is what I have called you to do. I know this concerns you, and it has even caused you to subm… https://t.co/r4obagw5Wj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It only takes one person to make your day and put a smile on your face , so hope you have a fabulous day today beautiful people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cllrainslie John makes promises every election year then breaks them just as easily.  He cut ribbons in Malvern la… https://t.co/S9yUBqkPAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evidence against Smollett is piling up. What a grand Hoax. If guilty, this millionaire Hollywood brat should be mad… https://t.co/YiCIN6obDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The O’Jays perform at Hardrock Stadium during Jazz in the Garden in Miami Gardens on Sunday March 10, 2019. Jennife… https://t.co/bIYnTRi30u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flexxin out now!!! #wakeup #music #hiphop #rap #memphis @ Memphis, Tennessee https://t.co/Etsj1K21IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lconicMinogue This place had so much shit girl. My cart was up to $50 and I had to narrow that shit back down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo excited to share that Territory will be hosting a fellow this summer. It's a 3-month paid fellowship, to do do… https://t.co/3o57JBrQsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jshadowhunter Many blame her for the GOATS meta in OWL and high level play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump Mr Fitton, are you blind and deaf or just stupid???  The evidence is mounting almost da… https://t.co/u7ekUAS0Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have this bad habit of brushing my teeth before getting into bed and then I eat in bed before I fall asleep 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No national emergency is getting in the way of a round of golf!! Priorities people desbudesheim lulybean ReneeS1983]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Beautiful Corpse by Christi Daugherty #bookreview #tarheelreader #thrbeautifulcorpse @cj_daugherty @minotaurbooks… https://t.co/wTBXYJpvaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Papá: “Ya viste que los atunes son pura soya???” Yo: “Si no manches, mal p2” Papá: “Naaambe, pinché gente valen men… https://t.co/USsISOGaKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArmyVet5 The sad part is how duped I was prior to racists crawling out of the woodwork. I had know clue the hate that USA beholds]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:45am  Early morning.... pulling up.... @ Life Time Athletic - Syosset https://t.co/RTMXrdBhZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone who has been to lost lands and has camped, pls dm me I have questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nourishment for body and soul from Mrs. Congrady! @DOC_CHS_Ajax @DOCthinkPINK @DurhamCatholic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk The Democrats are bunch of fools and they don’t even care!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawneeMS1 students Skyping with the Johnson Nkosi Memorial Primary School in #Uganda this morning! Our weekly… https://t.co/EH9kJQDT9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeoneMack3 @BwoodBucs @Ma_Martinez69 @BrazosportISD @delgadong94 @Seidlitz_Ed Nooooo way would you be a bother.  K… https://t.co/81bbtGChXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanVermazen @saikatc @ltthompso @AOC Thank you!! AOC is already a crook and a liar. Nice going people who voted… https://t.co/iLltVx2Tzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winstonbassett This made me laugh out loud!! 🦖 https://t.co/FFjSgESSE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[M2 | Rochard makes the Blazers go three up, three down  Strouth will lead us off   (🦃 0, 🐲 0)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kacey Musgraves singing Como La Flor!!! Love it!!! Today is the anniversary of Selena’s last concert at the Houston… https://t.co/TzeITVcpJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haleighbroucher If you plan out the what ifs over and over again you will be prepared. This is what security taugh… https://t.co/WdsUzquQii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnyrrahJ Wahahaha buti tlga malaki memory mg phone ko momsh! Hahaha puro marnigo na nga eh 😂  #MarNigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC He is not defending him, because Mr. Kraft has not defended tRump in alot of things..... #NotThatCloseAnymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my students wrote me this...#whyiteach #teachersofinstagram #teacherlife @ Berryville Elementary School https://t.co/w3mwRCAzSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Price talks about her career on @IFSAdotnet side meeting at @forestsdialogue week https://t.co/oSNpLHxRPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[No offense but you wouldn't make very good road kill. It was probably that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to figure a way to get all this home to Orlando?!?!?  🐄🥛🐮🧀 🍦 #tillamook  #tillamookcheesefactory  #keto… https://t.co/ctT1bJNVSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForeverLogical @marcorubio @CNNEE Not just that but won’t be tough on Russia 🇷🇺 and Putin for elections medaling b… https://t.co/wd7d7mkoA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning and Have a blessed day!😊 @ Georgetown, Kentucky https://t.co/uq2ivT27sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @lauferlaw Unless they are completely stupid, like Trump, who gives himself away every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, h*gh as fuck, eating a biscuit with jam at a party https://t.co/6CQEt0Udme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of these GES Kinders for their detail, labeling, illustrations, and sentences to show their understanding of… https://t.co/oIQVSgMYyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The servant #leader engine: yesterday, today and tomorrow. #ACHECongress2019 thx LInda Knodel @KPShare @ACHEConnect… https://t.co/3ruJQqJMRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna be wrapped around someone in bed and give them endless kisses. Life would be great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Bernie Sanders may be close to announcing a presidential run. https://t.co/5DO4nqyyOI via @HuffPostPol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys. Guys. Guys. Bill Clinton was in the same building as me today and I didn’t know it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Good night Eric!  Thank you for your support of one great man!  Doug Davidson. Can't wait...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yankeecannuck @PinkSparkleYums @steve45220 @dennisdiclaudio @MugabeJonathan @nypost Aw calling you names? Like how… https://t.co/hBBaejKNEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good evening my friends. I hope you had a Magnificent Monday. It's been a long day. I was wide awake at 5. At least… https://t.co/sviW6oddnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Sunday brunch!! See ya at Manuel’s!! #sxsw2019 @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/RYNSINMbr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Lady of Water Cathy Bailey delivering her presentation in perfect rhyme at #ELGLInspire is #NextLevel https://t.co/YJIJAtwZLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a notification that there was motion at my front door from my Ring app. Casper, is that you? #ghost #spirit… https://t.co/dSgZrBckXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassanmccan @HonestLeYo @_lightbrigght_ @DearSpecialK You didn't there is just more of them than we thought. All d… https://t.co/IO8HDHn8r2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alicia’s Free Kick that tied the game with seconds left! ❤️#7 @aliciaanne08 https://t.co/uydxmyZIOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lol.  Snl has made fun of presidents for decades.  You just are the only one with such a fragile e… https://t.co/C53jL8Eumr]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Valentine would be so proud of me for finishing this whole box of chocolate covered strawberries within two epi… https://t.co/BtW4nHZCgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff A crisis that doesn’t exist?????  Have you heard about the caravans coming our way???  We are being invaded you idiot!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockcandypod @thecountdownpc I dunno, something about music and movies. Just make it happen already. https://t.co/BnqUwkd0gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OnThisDay 25 years ago, rock band Soundgarden released their 4th studio album, "Superunknown". #Superunknown25… https://t.co/qRpbzD7ch8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saragoldrickrab @AOC Reasoning this well at 9yo means that at 18yo this young person will be a force to reckon wit… https://t.co/QinJbNgTr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Academy Awards Party &amp; Red Carpet!  #academyawards #actresslife🎬 #redcarpet @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/BTo1dVXedq]]></document><document><![CDATA[the episode of friends where joey learns hot cross buns on the recorder gives me ptsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yelnats_eel Oh thanks! Disappointed to miss some decent matches tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start pleading with people to stop saying "Patty" instead of "Paddy"! #itspaddynotpatty… https://t.co/Y2pBDL9ohb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCal_Kopites @LFC @Senorgrubbys @ortelius @Messina217 @KerrySomewhere @TheRedWay1892 @The_Schumanator @USA_KOP Br… https://t.co/kPbhDutziU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TessFowler We had so much fun just watching him pick our new supplies. All he ever wants to do is draw and I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet Cameron 5 weeks today. @ Meridian, Colorado https://t.co/fVyXk9jRhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benpo19 The game was in Toronto so I’m guessing he didn’t think it was safe to leave the country]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilGuzman41 @realDonaldTrump SHUT UP YOU ANTI-AMERICAN WHO THINKS KILLING BABIES IS OK. MAYBE YOUR MOTHER SHOULD HAVE ABORTED YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early for the first day at my new job!!! Headed to West Palm Beach for a meeting and back on Friday. ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #Realtor is always the answer when it comes to finding my dream home ✔️🏠]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Joe Biden. I want the absolute BEST we can put forward. Watching/ listening to all. Confident our best will… https://t.co/HhR9EPQTsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our government has one main and most important job - NATIONAL SECURITY.  So why does our NATIONAL SECURITY continue… https://t.co/9dnmNoUtAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is ab how most of my convos go w most men... god take me out of alabama but keep me tf away from ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@He_DruNkAhH3ll I saw Dame lose his whole starting line up and his 6th and 7th man and still make the playoffs the next year. In the West]]></document></documents></author>