<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Damn I spelt ALL DAY TODAY and I’m about to go back to bed #sickpeopleproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s MARCH! Time to celebrate #womenshistorymonth and my favorite holiday #stpatricksday in the colemanms546 media… https://t.co/JFPDziPLgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wanita1 I still cant believe they called the cops. Its not like he was smoking some huge blunt. He told them, and… https://t.co/nRFXswDitI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two weeks ago I got to experience this incredible sunset and full moonrise over Yosemite Valley. It was one of the… https://t.co/eU4Q0GrkOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#zumbastrong #strongbyzumba #GK5X_FITNESS_PROGRAM #instagood #youtuber #influencer #influencerswanted… https://t.co/BbajHFnMr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KotzLindy @leeleeb50 @REDDOG73829268 It’s so interesting that millionaires and billionaires think that just becaus… https://t.co/ysgpfcZfiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished walking 2.31 miles in 1h:49m:01s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/559eaMkPFg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaniaKhalek @facebook @IntheNow_tweet @CNN Our Constitution is being ripped apart! It's frightening!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casually throws out that my birthdays in three days for my sister*cough cough*]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cam Johnson’s response to the best part of playing with Kenny Williams  “You want him on your team. You would hate… https://t.co/CvTzG10UCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAY TUNED AND TURN YOUR NOTIFICATIONS ON!!!   DON' MISS THE FIRST EVER ALL BOUCE MUSIC FESTIVAL   💃🏾💃🏾#BounceHouse… https://t.co/2HrMs04n7u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Variety Of course just bury your head in the sand like every other person this is ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t believe everything u hear. Understand many of the thinks u hear come from someone who has an agenda. U should… https://t.co/4Agzx9aHqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted! WOVEN RUG #LdnOnt  https://t.co/vPH3qrxnwc Get the app from the Play Store https://t.co/LIp5kvzmOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flowerpathTae I know right? I wasn’t expecting this at all! Can’t wait! But now I have to decide where I’m going to travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hurt but a bitch ain’t gonna show it....JK MOMMMMMMMMM YOU WONT BELIEVE,,,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascalWhiteXXX Already did today. Lol I can’t help my muscles when I’m orgasming 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CasaReal @worldjurist @MAECgob @justiciagob @EmbEspPortugal @Congreso_Es @Senadoesp Vaya espanto de monarquía]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camiloatala Que orgullo ver a los amigos tan exitosos ! Felicidades familia !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Diego Public Library - Mira Mesa - @sdpubliclibrary in San Diego, CA https://t.co/krzWwrGOeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHO is here?  WE have the right to know!    The only way to get people to go through a port of entry is to block al… https://t.co/4v14PDf1TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today consisted of cleaning/clearing my magickal tools by letting them soak in pink himilayan salt for a bit ... Pe… https://t.co/gSwkM9L6Sg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NATA_SAAC And even then. Always, always introduce your self:  first and last name. #StayHumble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHempiricist @Noahpinion Sure it is. It states it  Whereas the Senate/House recognizes that a new national, soci… https://t.co/ltQZZGoMVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ex-Roger Stone Aide Andrew Miller Loses His Challenge of Robert Mueller's Authority https://t.co/ujVbQalNaf via @lawcrimenews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary me and twitter look at that https://t.co/rvLVvpDGEv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaisyGamble19 @CNN You can be entitled to your opinion but don't harass others about it - especially not when they… https://t.co/GcFSTAI2ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySimonds1 @hpeder @AthanasiaTrian1 @WilmaChelius @Martina82403124 @MakkOlga @brownie_mac @JEACARD… https://t.co/k0LIjRsYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch ya on the flipside! #nofilter #vacation #nola #wheresthebar @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/xtssrPbxo3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simple mindset hack....every time I hit a mental wall or life is really challenging and I want to throw in the towe… https://t.co/0LtYE3hCu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRyanSupreme @pewpewpew I drove on the QEW two Sunday mornings in a row when they hadn’t even been touched. It w… https://t.co/wgiHpMU9HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been one month. Glad I got to start my birthday week with my family and felt our two angels presence at dinner… https://t.co/7MZNXRWXRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I SAY T.   U ALREADY DID THE DAMNNN THING THEY SUPPRESSING WHATS ALREADY BEEN DONE. DONE..WHY I DON'T GET..IS… https://t.co/LM50ipZh4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcsupasta1984 @TeamSpaceIL @ILAerospaceIAI @ILSpaceAgency @most_il I like the cookie cutter effect. Takes a big cookie cutter . Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rita Moreno has influenced me to add a new goal to my stack of ‘em: I’m going to be a hot old lady(:]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coffee was ok. It rained this morning but it wasn’t super cold. Hey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blog stuff...pre-employment tasks to complete for a new job (yay!)...clean messy apt (boo!)...read awesome blog pos… https://t.co/xA2eLx5N9K]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you happen to take any of my jokes/status' seriously, that's on you, my dude. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sobrang ganda ng voice recorder ng Google Pixel 3 XL. Ang HD ng podcast namin every episode. Huhu. Thanks @madebygoogle]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve never waisted 6+ hours watching YouTube videos about #rawrocks and #gemstone then you clearly don’t have… https://t.co/QTV0OkYFdP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I get a notification, it’s a celebratory slight twerk that happens!! From sales and posts!   #happydance… https://t.co/7In2AIQyNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kayetothebeats @MattsRoadTrip @TouringTastebud @hooter_pettus @thdivewhisperer @ant_kneee @thelinetrek… https://t.co/dr83KFER4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichOnOWN @Oprah @oprahmagazine @GayleKing I’ve had to cut a few people recently who were smiling with me while th… https://t.co/0pibMjX5zE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadresGeekster @Padre_PoohBear @leisurefriar @Mudcat55 But you know Geekster we love you 😘😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m at the pool for a birthday party, and I’ve already seen three men wearing glasses in the pool. And they’re soak… https://t.co/1nDRWxxtQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thephotoist @lloydus2215137 Just make sure to recite the 12 steps while sipping. Cheers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer And he said it in an interview. Think about it. You don't have to be brilliant to hide the real reason… https://t.co/KaF4fVtkcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi doesn't get a free pass.  No more "Democrat Privilege".  You want to end the hate Nancy, shut your l… https://t.co/BL1GkCwr56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police say 83-year-old Judith Morin of York died after being transported to Portsmouth Hospital.  Investigators say… https://t.co/Q57r8kzEe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJoftheOri @BeautyBind @Bravewriting Rotfl.... me too! 😅😅😅😅 https://t.co/xHYsSmlyst]]></document><document><![CDATA[The teacher is a racist traitor to her Country. She should leave this country. Venezuela might be a better fit for… https://t.co/7jGfQTFkeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeriG72859565 Tired of winning?  What has Trump won?  The title of having sex with a porn star to the president of… https://t.co/LSNzT8MQeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[New drinking game, everytime Clint throws his phone like a spoiled toddler, take a shot! 🥃 @LuvAfterLockup #LoveAfterLockup @WEtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordan__kimball I follow you so you can follow me back. No worries 💁🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[so proud and honored to have watched this night with my own eyes!!! thank you for a great four years and happy seni… https://t.co/OxoRqzs1ta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soulasylum on @YouTube last night was too good!! Great night! #drinks #mylove #goodmusic and now we’re late for work!! #whatreyougonnado]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitches can’t even spell but wanna skip class to get food...(i’m bitches)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@year_progress @McKennaEcon @scopatz that means at least 262.47mi for @RunTheEdge #RTY2019! We’re rocking it as a team- 393mi done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen Especially when it’s a really yummy crust! #foodieissues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mackel_smore Oml nooooooo 🤦🏼‍♀️🤦🏼‍♀️😭 I cannot believe I didn't see that before. I HATE TYPOS IN MY TWEETS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My honey made me my fav (shrimp scampi) and bought wine and my favorite chips😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our baseball team is amazing, both on and off the field!  From Mr Kaneland, to college scholarships, to raising sch… https://t.co/JkJeQyZH1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Disaster and destruction comes when one thinks of himself more importantly or highly than he ought… https://t.co/bZvToC0id7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scornpaul @realjeffdixon10 @antmountains @thalsted @SenSanders We can give them the means.  A decent wage and access to education.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMNwithDaveLee @Vikings @AdrianPeterson Considering we have always been a has been town, yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WebMD Now that is cool, I’m going to try that . But is it cold water . Warm  water or hot ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrumFromNorwich @chrissy_goss @Boxmenot @TsuDhoNimh @Melissa62263619 @TakeThatCDC @EmmaGPaley @AlexMurdoch7… https://t.co/U4L4f0Xd3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 #ImpeachmentCountdown began with @JohnWDean testimony.We expected an outpouring of new evidence revea… https://t.co/0LhBrvnnl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow! Desoto vs Skyline! 7:00pm  Colleyville Heritage High School @kendallbrown__  #NewEra https://t.co/6BCyGbh3gw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss being on the @cruisenorwegian #norwegianescape Even a little rain shower couldn’t ruin relaxing on my balcon… https://t.co/UwdvCbhcUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally stopped puking around 10 PM last night. Now I'm just tired and dehydrated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of ‘partly cloudy’.  Today was stellar ✨🙏🏼 #texas #gulfcoast #earlyspring #grateful @ Galveston County, Tex… https://t.co/2a56WZevMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JMVivancoHRW Que no se vera como política, sino como cómplice de estos asesinos.. y narcos ...vaya a estudiar más… https://t.co/8jBIZuy2id]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cock and the bot 🐔🤖.... then there’s Caitlyn 🙄❣️ https://t.co/yYWdS1nUrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s have a terrific new month. Welcome March! 🌿❤️🏡✨🍾🦋🍀🌺💫🙏🏻 @ Yorkville, Illinois https://t.co/R15YwnUsTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obsessed with is very casual version of @KateMerrill laying in a snow pile. Happy 15th anniversary at @wbz Kate, yo… https://t.co/lWhtP6eQ7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Watershedd Love Tim Tams..Especially the chocolate mint ones...My favorite😋😎😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Obviously you’re not that interested “ “don’t chase”... first of all can I wash my ass FUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidcicilline @BarackObama Every Day!!! Hell, I miss Bush! At least we knew he wasn't selling out out country to the Russians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do I move past the  heartbreak and allow the next person in although I’m so guarded from the last. #evolutionoflove]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnewin10 That's kind of you. I feel recognized already, and am thrilled to see @reappropriate's contributions amplified in this way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Nicole! The @qualtrics team has built some amazing innovations - my job was easy to show it all off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up a home office soon. I wanna get a podcast really soon. Idc if I have zero subscribers. I’m just gonna be happy I did it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Talking about the Jonas brothers reuniting 😂 I just can’t with Stephanie https://t.co/0p2L6IADGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Poggy_16 Yes maam! We went to the domain during the day on a Sunday and it was fun af lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at all that money you got. Please donate some of it to my invention and I'll reveal what I'm making https://t.co/46XTSKHhLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome back Tuesday!! I lost my motivation for a bit, With all the curveballs life keeps throwing me...Ashley help… https://t.co/b9qO0XpXA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[In other words, any healthy relationship (or one in pursuit of health) should involve talking through and working o… https://t.co/0WxYBmrgeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@so_claudia09 Dedicated parents as well as the presenter 👌🏽👏🏼 @so_claudia09]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Alexandria: clear sky, 45°F 17% humidity, wind 25mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mando knew I was having a bad today so he surprised me with a bear and a rose🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[В местной газете статья про то, как в парках убивают оленей, потому как их очень много и они съели все, что могли.… https://t.co/yUO5MEmu89]]></document><document><![CDATA[⭐⭐⭐Look at these VOC superstars!!! Paula with 5, Heath with 1, Tamy with 1, and Randy with 2 mentions last week!!!… https://t.co/0G0go5plTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[First, let me congratulate you! In 2014, Nature had an Impact Factor of 41.456, which means it's highly influential… https://t.co/hh5pqDMbr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Girl Scouts are Go-getters, Innovators, Risk-takers and leaders.” Feeling inspired at the Women of Distinction lun… https://t.co/SO3d6kKK3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moto practicing his “place”  #germanshepherd #germanshepherdsofimstagram #boardandtrain #motoman… https://t.co/2ZGavhTqjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shouts to @Letang_58 for buying me a Big Mac today!! #bigmacattack #pittsburghpenguins #lgp #hockey @penguins https://t.co/aL21mYmrHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueEyedRy I wanted to go, but tickets were sold out by the time I found out about it. I’m never in the know, on time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Pence deserves every awkward moment he is handed as he goes about the world making anyone who encounter… https://t.co/97hPEPzcvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! ❤️💕❣️💘❤️ #happyvalentinesday2019 @ Woodstock, Georgia https://t.co/JDiFb4QA75]]></document></documents></author>