<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@kacsandy5 @mehdirhasan So sorry @LtStevenRogers ... How embarrassing for you!  🤭🤭🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦶✨A big shout-out to my amigo Ruben Palacios aka murked. Your vision’s been and will always be golden✨🦶#la #ucla… https://t.co/ooKnQ1sG6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate that eunice doesnt have a twitter becus i stay having to send the links to mine citlally’s and eunice’s groupchat &gt;:(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pttynn Oh yeah it was Tito’s 😂 &amp; actually you should’ve made @AlysssaMitchell do it- she’s the one who filled it up! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill_magnussen @jbwhite777 @1228erin @CasperkErickson @SemaCiel0101 @loveGoldenHeart @Nayalla334nd @TathamSmith… https://t.co/ugg8tAud7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[You thought you had a break down? Nahh... God said that was your breakthrough! 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad is THAT petty. he hid our favorite girl scout cookies from me https://t.co/62Wggl6fw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ehernandez 😂 You are a trooper. Drive safely tonight. I know you have to be absolutely exhausted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys really are the needy ones nowadays lmaoooo y’all asking for the MOST]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Rangers Caps game is giving me life #sundaymorninghockey #WSHvsNYR https://t.co/jp3l82xjQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriteNThrive @peiferlabunc @jenheemstra I did. I'm not seeing any that suggest that the person's age was an issue.… https://t.co/BpioQlJ4rL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolo_quintero It was the greatest experience ever, I can’t wait to be back👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of my favorite memory’s are the moments in between the plans we made. Thanks for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating A Day of Peace at BES  by working together as good teammates while using fractions to cooperatively bui… https://t.co/F9eoeNMKnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#robertmapplethorpe #philipglass #robertwilson #guggenheim à Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum https://t.co/iGY4Qg4IHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoaferNed @JonahNRO Where did you find the socks?  We have a Yorkie Shih Tzu mix that is constantly licking his fe… https://t.co/Z0zDZ86VnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold when I’m not doing anything. Room temp when I’m working out. And hot when I want hot chocolate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, more #foodporn but that is how I am rolling. Plus, I am a huge #foodie so #yass! • Greek shrimp with tomatoes… https://t.co/nc3kSJrJ8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since then there has been even more great work in Civil War-era politics. Just a few examples include @aipsmith The… https://t.co/InG53mPsc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanezuda @newerikanew @vanessaafs @Isneu4 @brunocovas @joicehasselmann @belagil Então, né? Eu e você somos privile… https://t.co/iCh8o5l3Ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all women are like this but it’s sad that there are some that do this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrovstreetIJU @VNugs_ If you weren’t here for FAN4LIFE we don’t want you https://t.co/Jcs1YoOSEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beggr12 @PNemiroff It’s Perri!   Maybe she’ll be in the pre-show for the next set of shorts too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @UMChurch Stay out of our church.  People are hurting.  I’m well aware of your homophobia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a headline where it says an actor died after suffering a cardiac arrest, well, duh, different causes but that is how we all die,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook memories bring back such great memories🥰  Miss y’all...@alana_bracken @bobbynahill! https://t.co/45aKDeZaQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to catch today’s shower show? You can only see it right here! https://t.co/ekwAUD7QNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are dropping a very special weekend edition of the🎙PODCAST today !! You asked and we are answering on today’s ep… https://t.co/biXlXU7tR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYUDocs What can everyday people do to help prevent their bones from becoming weak?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was just boutta take these braids down tonight too so I can get em re done. But this is all the message I need to… https://t.co/2tcP4oORQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom I've never understood why he didn't. I think it was hubris at the thought anyone or anything helped him win the election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDoochMan @TheKidsABC I was watching this show but missed the last few weeks. I will have to see if I can catch… https://t.co/M6CWNwypsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch @foxandfriends @FoxNews Thank you God, for, Judicial Watch!!!❤️🇺🇸🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s someone with every opportunity afforded him in life complaining instead of taking advantage of the resources… https://t.co/57N6FExOFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDailyShow @MuellerSheWrote @realDonaldTrump’s fat ass could never pull off a tan suit. Obama rocked it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[when waiting in line and the uber was more lit than the actual event smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living with @mercyfuldm is like living with an angel.  An angel who LITERALLY hands you delicious cakes 😍 https://t.co/BLSGYCik50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobBrinson1 @4boysnanny @KathaleenHarpe9 @msnicole1124 @Patti_Sc60 @DDW7369 @Aimee23569269 @frankferacious… https://t.co/5XFIpXm75w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 44002 W LEOLA CT #Hollywood #MD  #realestate https://t.co/XOi5pFUP6h  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PucciaPatrizia @ElbaklySami @enriqueiglesias @Viviane6677 @roberta_lanzoni @zetakaty @janaplauen @TereOrt51687394… https://t.co/51wjtMkELG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OffToWork #5am-12pm #RunningToTheMoney @ Atlantic City International Airport https://t.co/LJo4r3ISvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to the For Emma, forever ago album on repeat all night while it’s snowy and like -1° out is tradition ❄️🌲☁️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been F off on social media all damn day only accomplished a few things I lost my to do list]]></document><document><![CDATA[point of view / Halloween cute idea to do for art or for a creative writing... #mirth #chuckle #smile #humorous https://t.co/woxfghmYw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always so humbled when I receive a review of my work and the client takes the time😌. It reminds me that I still lov… https://t.co/VzarvvHCj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophomore year I pretend like everything was okay but nothing was okay or going the way I wanted everything makes sense now]]></document><document><![CDATA[#vincentvangogh said, “I never get tired of the blue sky.” This definitely rings true in #pnwlife 💚 #nofilter… https://t.co/b1U3hiDPNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Positive-Constructive-Criticism You know.... just like as an adult when you have your job evaluations! Not Everythi… https://t.co/1o1TzVoJJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[having an anxiety attack while bartending might be one of the worst experiences of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[according to this radio show my mom ALWYAS listens to robots are taking over the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to stop forgetting that I have my nipples pierced because I almost accidentally get them caught/rip t… https://t.co/hCqwlcrym2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think it’s weird for a girl to message the ex-girlfriend of the guys she is talking to to ask about their re… https://t.co/1NWRxT7byf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today boss man is going to chew me up because of what happened over the weekend 😭 but I’m ready lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of people are like “I miss Obama because he would never *insert something he totally supported during his pre… https://t.co/NfueJpUFOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRIMALDATA @tlwry @steph93065 @KamalaHarris When you pay less in taxes, you get less back. It’s simple math. Small group? You’re nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco to expunge over 9,300 marijuana-related convictions  https://t.co/ZpM94xBSiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dios te bendiga, hermano. Aplaudo tú valentía. Le pido a Dios que proteja a tu familia y a todos los que dejaste en… https://t.co/vWCCrhLFuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we go out to eat and we don’t share each other’s plates.. let’s not do this again. #commitmentissues #withfood #itsmenotyou #dating101]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus @LisaMoraitis1 @highbrow_nobrow I’m shocked! Do you mean Jared Kushner is corrupt? Everyone in the Wh… https://t.co/YEtxjx32aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Babs has that quality as well,she is polarizing you can't stop looking at her,watch her and Kristiferson ,it's a st… https://t.co/uPayH5fBXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m not the only one who hates Bellaire and all the idiot drivers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Pick for International Women's Day? Jane Fonda.   https://t.co/bSxQAG2WUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patriot_Musket @mchastain81 @SShackford Cause chocolate obviously always wins out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccatmpt @AkronWineGuru @Cbp8Cindy @FionaMorgan79 @cowineco @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @joneill55 @suziday123… https://t.co/yH80eEeTUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you believe my galpal @laylasusie took that photo on the back wall and all of the others?! So proud of your met… https://t.co/1KPHNdAH6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hank_tower @jleland_ @BridgetABC11 Bullshit it’s been s doozie love fest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, I try not to hate myself at all, but I never regret buying books at @GreenAppleBooks (or @gabsunset or any ot… https://t.co/M1B6GBp4Rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a morning! Celebrating our super ⭐️ readers. #esl 🌏📚❤️ https://t.co/0BMBlwEOrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prnirvana @righty64 @RamblingPariah @atrupar 1. K I wasn't going to dignify this with a response, because one out-… https://t.co/B9jySq7CvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy your weekend 💋 sc ogkellydivine 👀 LINKS IN BIO 😈 @ Wilmington, Delaware https://t.co/1ukejrMWge]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Optional second sentence, ‘Is your chair comfortable and have you got your favorite pen, the one that makes your notes look so nice?’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good argument for @netflix to @TheAcademy especially with the women/ overtly male white criticism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this helps for transitioning from Seurat v2 to v3 https://t.co/sPmzJfLjle #rstats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dude it was funny - gets funnier with each tweet you do. I hope when you go to prision that they a… https://t.co/XGoT646RxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strive2bGreat Gracias! Same to you! I’m very inspired by your quotes and I certainly make it a point to apply it to my everyday living! 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing weekend, that I spent with students from @_HamptonU .  It was our pleasure to introduce you to… https://t.co/DfRggwfQCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are your plans for Spring Break?! #360Blue #EmeraldCoast #30A #SpringBreak2019 ##vacationmode]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corigamm Hahaha!!! It’s so funny... we have been to Cheersport 1 time and that is my least favorite comp, even tho… https://t.co/NBJgpIIQdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YurntNee Lol you really told me, you single mama products are hilarious, keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Universal Orlando Announces Opening Date for New Ride at The Wizarding World of Harry Potter | LoveFLTravel https://t.co/FxjbEyky12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir thanks for being the absolute worst airline! Every time i take you guys you ruin my vacation!! But now… https://t.co/CrGvsX13iJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emergencies Power Act - Mark Levin https://t.co/7r74wK4JZI via @YouTube. Must listen]]></document><document><![CDATA[When me and @cbrookecox have “girls night” it’s always The girls and Dallas 😂 let’s see what happens tomorrow for girls night 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[humor right? #funniness #tee-hee #smile #hilarious https://t.co/nBZDp82S07]]></document><document><![CDATA[what the hell am I doin, if I don’t leave soon I’m gonna ruin my bad reputation 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing you a fabulous Saturday morning.  Enjoy your coffee! #wishing #fabulous #saturday #morning #coffee… https://t.co/Dy3d9gMsH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selenaalenaa_ @ashleyviictoria let’s get a family tattoo. ahoet or a yoshi.. you’re not down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“OLD ARCADI”  Is location two and it also serves as the headquarters for the Brotherhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so hungry all I’ve had today is animal crackers..water.. and applesauce. 😩🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamedayMediaInc These parents forgets who picks their nursing home. While you embarrassed your child for a laugh.… https://t.co/2yX9K187Ol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ideal man? Oh I’d say he’s noble, optimistic, cares about climate change and immigration, has a cute lil lisp an… https://t.co/E7pRnptEy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stillinnocent13 @lindsheartstayx @rebekahswiftie @sweetx0love25 @newromaticalexa @swiftsupergirl @eastsidedivebar… https://t.co/s0vaCFGaUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love sharing my birthday with #InternationWomensDay Today I’m inspired by the grace, courage and unbotheredness of… https://t.co/DMwQAHDa7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $60 Spotify Gift Card Offer    Enter Your Email Id And Complete A Simple Sign Up To Win $60 Spotify Gift C… https://t.co/KaRG9kQpIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting into the St Patrick's decorating spirit! I have discovered battery powered lights, I can put them every whe… https://t.co/D1Hjyh2Io6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donna Riggs REALTOR at Coldwell Banker Seacoast Advantage 910-340-0224 https://t.co/2oCupvR3Xd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in tonight @nbcsandiego 5pm for Politically Speaking with @Alex_Presha with guests @sergededina and @honghd https://t.co/Kzf0j5VMsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InterimLeader @joncoopertweets So he loses his business to make a point about something he's wrong about. OK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WITN @EngelWX #Domestic Violence Survivor Speaks! https://t.co/NSgJ8oUOA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevens6129 @realJoseLazcano @AnnaBrosche @lennycurry I wouldn’t know since he hasn’t said anything thing publicly… https://t.co/rkySr3yxrx]]></document></documents></author>