<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MrSilverScott @MrDrewScott @PropertyBrother @hgtv Loved the kitchen 👌👌👌😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coco2010coco23 Hi, we have vast experience in mobile app development and would be happy to assist you in building… https://t.co/kge0mGkPuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiltownBucky @jsorgi This is kind of cool. @Bucks @MarquetteMBB https://t.co/PHa7P9RsbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fahadma45457790 @danielyhalom @marinavibu609g @akomama_tm @AAvallones @LivePDJacob @Romanof_Martins @PatGrant7777… https://t.co/HmzqHoEG7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol tonight’s shift wasn’t so bad when my Indian alumni 👩🏻‍🎓 🎯@xo_senia_xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[i learned that the less sleep i get the more awake i am in the morning and that’s kinda frustrating]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been following this post specifically and it makes me so happy a business boomed quick!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone else randomly reminisced on a scent and it takes you all the way to elementary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DancinLionheart I kept thinking the same thing when I was taking screen shots of them! Too funny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u let ur partner take control of ur life, ur in a toxic relationship. Long term friends shouldn't be replaced ca… https://t.co/MyuefXH9RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great food and cocktails @idlehourquincy   but I'm in love with their bathroom! #prince @ Idle Hour https://t.co/VTlCX24ApM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooh. With the new Screaming Frog update, it can now crawl your structured data. This should be quite helpful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod His son threw him under the bus so no suprise. Funny how the R's are really quiet about election fraud right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndh313 all I want is some code somewhere free of bad hacks and syntax errors that uses Git to share oh, wouldn’t it be lovely...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REVASHELF #love the way this #LivingInPlace movement is now #mainstream #interiordesign! #clipp design is just… https://t.co/Z6Bpt6iqQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kateplusno8 “Don’t wanna text anyone, chat tomorrow....maybe then I’ll be more willing to deal with people.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently my dog enjoys to sit on my “back lap” 😉😂😂😂💋 @ New Haven County, Connecticut https://t.co/9EXbpnVXc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kind of girl!!! Came out to play on swingset, but we are #rockhounding instead!!!  . . . . . . #oilbeelievers… https://t.co/k5mPVd83df]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP Learn how to conduct partisan https://t.co/wGD7mDdTT1 has been scheduled when POTUS is doing a great job… https://t.co/aZHh6OoTAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_nizzzle @hailezzz__ @sarahcimring Omg how did you get this video of me!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dustin3v Ew go move into a trailer what the fuck is wrong with you I’m so concerned get your head checked]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @LitVentures to post covers of 7 (children’s) books I LOVE: no explanations,no rev… https://t.co/gRZjl26vTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you for your Tweet, President Trump. Please Expedite My Charter to The White House for The H… https://t.co/ldMjP78WDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 2nd Birthday to my Sweet Paisley Drew! Aunt Nat and Z love you more than you will ever know! I hope you have… https://t.co/wzUanIEBAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are in control... * * Whoa. So many of you reached out to me about my last transformation picture. That you did… https://t.co/nZbBYuD4Fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized there’s no school tomorrow. Meaning my house will be total chaos for about 9 hours straight 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get your point and agree with the criticism....but can you clean up your language a bit?]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow i love @norvina1 even more now bc she smokes how is this POSSSIBLEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonesy1313 @penguins @WBSPenguins Sully said him and Ruhwedel are longer term. Just hope no one else gets injured or they are in trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying out the infared sauna @Cloud9floatspa today! #gifted https://t.co/F4lX79R0y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TashaAdamski Let me rephrase that, do i gotta walk around LA and take pics of these bikes? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulaannev @ahmedhankir I wasnt told my dad was dying when it happened or I would have gone to st. Louis, mo and s… https://t.co/9oYrGjG9zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Covington Catholic teen and his parents sue the Washington Post  https://t.co/lxSh4CxMGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Wallflower in El Paso, TX https://t.co/vKLqxud3Gh https://t.co/B6eqvGsfFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTVToronto @TracyTongCTV ....... and didn’t look remorseful at all.  😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennakelleytv @VGuzman_TV @AndrewNepsundTV Tbt to when Jenna popped up at the start of my weather. @jennakelleytv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought about writing about all of the women who inspire me. The women who hold me up. The women who fix my crown… https://t.co/u9Kg2Owkdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REALJohnAtlas Amazing story, great athlete, and very inspiring! Keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this Antique coffee table for $95 on OfferUp https://t.co/dmyfBEkLS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekMYoung @mattdpearce @mgerrydoyle @Popehat Doesn’t the...U.S. flag have to have, let’s see, gold fringe on it for this to be valid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carl's alive!  And has both his eyes!  #twd @ Camarillo, California https://t.co/RU4ORYNtcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“CHOCOLATE GALAXYYYYYYYYYYYY” @desusnice @THEKIDMERO @SHODesusAndMero https://t.co/wAgyWxHEjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaClinton Agreed- and you were one to champion The current child in the White House as being off limits as well!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMAZlNGNATURE I'm gonna love him and hold him and name him squeaky. 🤗💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[J and I got drunk and danced to country music with the dogs in the kitchen last night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhannahjones Even worse, he was proud of the land and mentioned that the enslaved people were “sad” when they were… https://t.co/rsmXqeBdgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I need this today. I’m not going to lie today’s workout is going to be a first and I’m more sure how I’… https://t.co/Cs9jDPgNhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got the lil’ Beamer back home but drisee says he’s ready to let her go 😭 #bmw #2002 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/yPltInHj8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[This young man is the son of a good friend and friends with my son. He has worked incredibly hard and helped an unb… https://t.co/PftMYFC1jA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well played, Brex 👏🏼Also... you should get a @Twitter account. #fyrefestival @netflix @hulu https://t.co/s3qC15XiqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Abernethy Laurels - @abernethylaurel in Newton, NC https://t.co/4Z9VNPArO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now are these best friends again ??? @tv7israelnews @IDF @netanyahu ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel horrible.  Do you guys have any suggestions for body aches.  I need relief]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard in #apseminar just now:  "Guys, I just found the coolest article with all kinds if interactive maps" ❤️ t… https://t.co/qz7clFjdxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta say I loved the #oscars opening number is it prescient.... #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[driving in PA is like:  ❄️ |         ||        |      _________________       |  🚘  ||        |     |       ROAD… https://t.co/poPAQ3vn9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechAppar Drove it at 1pm.  You would have thought traffic would be somewhat moving along]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great session from @bethrihtar Thanks for sharing your knowledge and your positive energy. @AIMSNetwork… https://t.co/uaQyAI4Kci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amber_athey @ThePatriot006 @CNN CNN employs the most unprofessional group of journalists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another reason to head to #Springarama at the Aud. The official donut of Norfolk County @TheApplePlaceNC… https://t.co/X6D1xTHzx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCorleyMath @Gnrazngrl @iteachmathAll Was just going to suggest Desmos!  Marble slides is magic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday to the best mom in the world. Momma you are the strongest, most beautiful, kind heart… https://t.co/ToZJLuBH44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Designer71L @freedunni @thehill Because they have already dug tunnels, no wall can stop a tunnel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Starbucks at LGA airport has to be the worst and slowest I ever been too. How is it possible you have 6 people… https://t.co/xDgYxxej07]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband  hes my life  he knows I don't  lie to people  soo u believe  them go to that person  scope  not my scop… https://t.co/8Y1fy7wFID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally seeing the stars. 🥰@EarthandClouds @ThePhotoHour @StormHour @AMHQ @weatherchannel @JimCantore @JenCarfagno… https://t.co/NPlmkWanfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day!!💪🏻 #wecandoit #internationalwomensday @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/GMfMAP97sd]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Grand Forks scores on the power play to up lead to 2-0 over Bulldogs at 14:04 of 1st period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karin_robbers @bulkbiker @billybunnysmate @lowcarbGP The more you say no to high sugar high carb the easier it becomes #yes2meat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned off fan for audio! @BedBathBeyond #steamer @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/82n651L4oS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @diplo and @johnmayer  Do you ever find yourself posting photos with yourself in the same outfit???  Because h… https://t.co/XcxD9UZGbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then what advantage has the Jew? Or what is the value of circumcision? https://t.co/0P5WT1xgav]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when the predicted snowfall ends up being anticlimactic and yet we still get a snow day. Grateful for an add… https://t.co/EO09REHfEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think he should be able to do that if he can make a house in the wild.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting cut short and lunch cancelled...does this mean they have to send these tshirts to Africa? #TrumpKimSummit… https://t.co/0gqBq0AHPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshlyeKyle Girl I just watched his video I have 1 opinion his channel is starting to lose a lot of subs and hes butt hurt as hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geminiman82 I cannot begin to imagine what D is going through. As if being ill on top of everything isn’t a slap i… https://t.co/bwM1to5qt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megcatherine20 Are people just making decisions based off of jokes? Wow - what amazing evidence you have!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just  sending some positive positive thoughts your way.👍🏽📚🌹 @LakeWill611  @bfreeskeewee  @DOEChancellor… https://t.co/KVteUi1AG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had a dream that a nigga built a mini plane out of science fair project poster board, then broke it trying t… https://t.co/CeQdgybM3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every woman’s dream closet!!!! ❤️ Lic: 01894317 #skyriserealestategroup #skyrise #skyriserealestate #closet… https://t.co/BbTsvvJNeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me cooking supper*  Me: supper is almost done, then I have tomorrow supper in the crockpot  Cody: you trying to get a ring or something? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Congress to support immigrants with Temporary Protected Status (TPS) https://t.co/xOXdDyKOuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkronWineGuru @CaththeWineLady @thatsVeryKari @Dracaenawines @joneill55 @Julianna_glass @ccatmpt @cowineco… https://t.co/dW7l5VRntf]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the tests for faithfulness in the last days is love for and confidence in Revelation and Daniel ... indeed a… https://t.co/JfZNVe9Qs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay so just ordered my waist trainer and I’m really excited. I really see a future with change coming my way 😭!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MikePompeo asegura que los #EstadosUnidos han entregado más de 100 millones de dólares en ayuda humanitaria, retir… https://t.co/66VIWdCQTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassandra Silk (@CassandraSilk) is now advertising in Atlanta! https://t.co/yZ86HbPD3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw a cop with a sniper facing some apartment complex, was asked to turn around, went into the store, came out an… https://t.co/eizpvuCrXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, health care shouldn’t be just for people who can afford it. Blocking care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/9fV1FP7Lli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamGuynes Actually I’m against any American citizen that’s turns their back on this country to go and join for… https://t.co/ekWUgJvsaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurenLovelie I know I’m just overwhelmed. I know things will be hectic at first and then things will settle down. It’s just been crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFizzlio @FoxxyAsFuq @zamasumeatyabs @vicmignogna BOOOOO!!! GET OFF THE STAGE!!! BOOOOO!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curlyygirlly @netflix P.s. my apt is Wednesday at 3:45 , hopefully she gives me more cookies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of @AleynaCorona calling every now and then for directions on how to make arroz con leche! I still call… https://t.co/M5d79xoIHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Papa_paigey @titsoutayy @kamdaddyz @camillewehr Lmao three hours ago I change my insta and you tweet about but gla… https://t.co/FLN1a5W0ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janwithay @funder @garz2656 I think she might be playing it right with Stone - making sure nothing she does can ge… https://t.co/TqiCXTHveV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary (only because twitter told me) https://t.co/aMuaFT0nEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coltonbeau @tdf512 @BrycenNFL @fly01275 @PatriotsSBLIII Are you really that ignorant to believe that delflated foo… https://t.co/0Pi9u5TEaE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s the tea 🍵 sis, you will not have personal space within the subway system or the commuter line so please don’… https://t.co/PrNGDj21Aa]]></document></documents></author>