<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@BrdCmpbll Brad, Terrible to hear. Too young. You gave him much to be proud of. Thoughts and prayers to you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nephie @DVC_99 @jlmomrn Come on Steph, keep up with current trends!! 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnyzgurl We always called them "potracks" because of the noise they make.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP’s silence on ALL that is Trump is deafening. Are the spineless, or just hell bent on destroying democracy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SacksandF @ChampionTwitch That's because all the good players are on Xbox....lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My timehops from the past 3 years were sappy love posts... and then I come across this. Yes Jess, this is exactly w… https://t.co/6MLdlQN5Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoHapy828 teaching 4th graders how basic coding works using a concrete and fun learning experience with cups Ss ha… https://t.co/wIVLCjzgyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes @CalvinKlein Great Job On The Elvis Tribute!👍👍👏👏 Rocking The CZkS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast @yashar I freaking love asparagus all garliced up and broiled]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlissaBjerkhoel If my "man cold" isn't excuse to call in sick to work, then your "chipped fingernail" isn't an exc… https://t.co/HHI0YpwBjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano U really need to get a life your so ignorant https://t.co/9z9V3Zr1qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Copperking1982 @BrendenMaclaren @fbx_IceDogs That was pretty obvious !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaBoots @jetrotter Fantastic this should be shown on every channel every hour and on every radio station this is… https://t.co/axYZhmjZ1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyOuriel Hope you are well, great to meet you. Our factory are clean air specialists over 12 years, we provides… https://t.co/3N4ZYolnXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingpinbb21 Happy for you! Happy for your boys and all the kids who were lucky enough to have you coach them. Congrats &amp; cheers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN @RealJayWilliams Nowadays it only matters what happens in playoffs not regular season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something good did come from annett winning this weekend. https://t.co/xzPOoEfeOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satan’s Evil Butchers Pelosi Feinstein Harris Cory Booger’s cryin Chuck Clinton’s Obama’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick McCusker would love to show you the #listing at 9101 Atlantic #Wildwood #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/CYAerBZ6Jt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nate_mccomb @28delayslater @elonmusk @Tesla But say it right because the SEC is listening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theMagdalenRose What if he says something like, "Jordan Peterson is a fascist."]]></document><document><![CDATA[New: @GM CEO @mtbarra says all @Cadillac models will offer Super Cruise by 2022. This is more detailed timeline tha… https://t.co/oDmR1kcL3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMarturano Me and Tony Dockz had ta take care of somethin @Pont_of_Gold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiebruddah @CarefreeEdition Most of the announcers are former players from clubs like arsenal, United, Liverpool… https://t.co/HzZAB7S9FQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill Simmons on MSG denying that James Dolan is trying to sell the Knicks: “All I said was he’s courting offers, an… https://t.co/CcAsBagCwn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy Dios me dio la oportunidad de celebrar un año más de vida con la bendición de contar con salud y muchos afectos… https://t.co/tXPSQCQc1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJHartman At times they do. The question is, why don’t they look that way all the time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkLorando @RichardAWebster @emilymlane @NOLAnews Louisiana’s criminal justice system is truly horrible on so man… https://t.co/0hDCXKB3ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRiggsWDRB A friendly reminder:  WATCH OUT for people suddenly swerving to avoid potholes! A guy almost hit me whi… https://t.co/wheewDNx6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RTREYR1 @garbitchh @DakotaLameHumor @iAmFrankON @CTZNCorinthian @AmePotato @Victor_ighoo @BlvckAsh_ @tmylmiley… https://t.co/DdyGu0S5qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My success is as equal as every being's, just bc you can't see it, my actions for my plan will always speak for me...https://t.co/xdOO5cELcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Home_Halfway @BTuckertime @melissaFTW I do hate infanticide and socialism so might be some truth in this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GentStateOfMind I hve no interest in weak men, or men who can’t pick their battles. Like to lose a fight, ehhhh… https://t.co/Zx5ErzCPsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyHitch @DTich16 @ClayTravis I’m not taking up for Wade. I’m pointing out that there is room for them to make th… https://t.co/SIR9OKhxxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @VikingInFL @EPA Trump always picks the worst swamp monsters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DARK_COKO Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea female month and the Turkish government is throwing a big party . Should have sent the DemoRat Liberals and Soc… https://t.co/y2Bqu5vCaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hersheeyss Idk but if you’ve ever been to Fat Tuesday’s they make really good slushie drinks 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashlyandersonxx I think it's harder u get hit on by how many guys everyday and there fans too so how I'm I going to be any  different]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi it’s 2019 if you’re still using the word “epic” to describe something please check yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kroeger @HOMAGE @hornets @KembaWalker @MilesBridges Thought I recognized you in the team store yesterday! I should've spoken to you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This society is upside-down. The white collar crime gets rewarded, while the have-nots doesn't!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t think it was possible but #WWE writing somehow got even lazier. #WWECHAMBER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports Good for him. He’d never get the full credit if he won, and humiliated if he lost. Enough of this g… https://t.co/6cd0QzPC0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Fox employing this Racist and dangerous Race Baiter? Who ever he works for it’s time to do what’s right His inte… https://t.co/P0kIpwqXi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to work for me tomorrow? Guaranteed that you’ll lose your soul. Raise of hands?? 🙋🏼‍♂️🙋🏼‍♀️🙋🏿‍♀️🙋🏿‍♂️🙋🏽‍♂️🙋🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m surprised Kyle Guy made it on first team, but he certainly deserved it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel good and I’m about to take the best nap ever. But will I make it to my 2 o’clock? 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamXMen on @TyltEnt—can't wait for the X-Men to join the MCU https://t.co/SqXWhg1JRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reivers21 @FieldYates You listed two linebackers and a corner. Those positions are more valuable than Safety. What… https://t.co/zgD49UnBAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkgrlpoet Congrats, Angel. That’s amazing. 👏🏿👏🏿👏🏿👏🏿👏🏿👏🏿👏🏿  My grandfather taught me; “It’s not what you have that… https://t.co/urs7x7FPTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barks and Brews... - Drinking a Lavish by @NewProvinceBrew at @newprovincebrew  — https://t.co/GWlxgANW5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: How could anyone think Paul Manafort lived an ‘otherwise blameless’ life?: As a convicted tax chea… https://t.co/mvuJY3G48T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @bedevilme666 @EricLevis4 @1776KAG @gator4kb18 @KevinMFerrara @NahBabyNah @Libphobic @1776_eye… https://t.co/wePFgfpc1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Heimlich, contratación pitcher zurdo de los Tecolotes de N.L. levanta ampula y polémica. Probablemente sea blo… https://t.co/HDnCU20dZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere, someday, somehow DJT's gonna commit an impeachable offense.  Must we wait for the Senate to flip?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 43 #100DaysOfCode  Day 10 #JavaScript30  NO VIDEO CLIP TODAY, UNFORTUNATELY!! Mainly Backend today. Worked with… https://t.co/ZwRxr1YNM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out @plugxtalk for the @trickAIO group buy! https://t.co/JsfBm2QT58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStarDC4L @XFLDallas @ConceptLeagues @ConceptLeagues is creative with their designs, but I thought they did bet… https://t.co/ygNdbaEABx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered this @ICENINEKILLS #sweepstakes on #tunespeak.  Follow the link to enter and help me earn entries. https://t.co/Q25a83gxkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hjayoh @melamparo @engadget Damn man....even almost 2 years out of school, Elam with the old guy jokes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MON 3/11/19:Pt4: Musn't For-HO-get Walkin Insane Asylum  Wia'$ Harleygwen's&amp;crazytony kgs Neighbor-HO-od'$  OF INFORMERS WATCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me listening to @iamcardib bars in “Thotiana” #Thotiana #remix https://t.co/ZAc3l4OtSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@womensmarch @JennMgg Don’t you dare pretend to be a woman Jenn!  They don’t make enough yard bags for you to be wi… https://t.co/4rg1fRx4cf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a video of your first performance of this amazing song.. thank you for sharing this with Portland first ❤️… https://t.co/1JdnBkbZhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dr_MatteoGalli @wawinaApr Hello! May I kiss you? Oh...I’m sorry...did I offend you? I’ll just sit here quietly...]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The thing that wouldn’t leave”  She like that old Saturday Night live comedy skit. Please run we could all use a r… https://t.co/bdryCthBCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeopardy Great msg Mr Trebek. I applaud your courage. May I recommend a cancer clinic we used in AZ called Envita.… https://t.co/xF8H9E8Q0m]]></document><document><![CDATA[bundle up !!  #DC #layersonlayers #itsfreezingoutside #brrrrr @ The District Hotel https://t.co/6N9SDFD04U]]></document><document><![CDATA[where’s the after party in dallas? i’m tryna throw up my life too #stayongame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Someone needs to stop these dictator type of behavior. You can't let this pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett's 'Empire' scenes cut after attack controversy https://t.co/1MWPJhGcpr via @pagesix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your job is not to judge. Your job is not to figure out if someone deserves something. Your job is to lift the fall… https://t.co/C4dxDhg1s1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:18 in the morning and the first thought that’s in my head is how I cannot believe how happy I am. Overwhelme… https://t.co/LQjsIr1U8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#steak #pornfood en Best Western Cumbres Inn Cd. Cuauhtémoc https://t.co/1gomIPz9PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelword9 @feesage Definitely beautiful! The both of you defiantly are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joliehaitian79 Hell Zendall I wish I wish they would bring AMC back!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre que estoy deprimido intento recordar cosas buena que hice y no recuerdo nada 😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇦🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss akatharinav The White RACE Australian BLONDES👑🇦🇺 Women Are The MOST Beaut… https://t.co/AlZcrzPxwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#edgeofdesire #johnmayer #guitar #acoustic #vocals #j45 #gibson #latenightlosangeles #latenight #california… https://t.co/0nPSnZC3pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This also misses how much of this data is anonomyzed. In almost all cases you have to load any personal data into p… https://t.co/RoK00acQ4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 degrees tomorrow at 6am, you’ll need to dress warm! #EugeneOregon https://t.co/O18l7PZeux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phelpsbecca @lexi4prez No but you'd be mad that this person was a mental health worker. She told me once she clock… https://t.co/OUnuq6vwOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[UGLY game last nite no 2 ways about it BUT... WINNING PROGRAMS find a way... Biggest stats of the nite -… https://t.co/V9h9rHQSph]]></document><document><![CDATA[This posting by @Ilhan is laghable at best! This hate america joke has no place in Congress,  much less in the fore… https://t.co/vpIJjLnKUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real life sometimes can provide the best material for the most hilariously funny monologues. Current events in the… https://t.co/ADqLi5OMPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotSpamIpromise [stranded drivers nervously try to avoid eye contact with each other]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCTakato Good news sir! You gonna do a marathon?? https://t.co/MmNHgB31rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@War_Sloth @OldTakesExposed @hcom34 @YahooForde Old Takes is a Gators fan. Can’t expect much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big management change for @WBUR, @mbebinger reports. https://t.co/H2iqTvuhNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElectionBabe @Polit_eurOpines @civicdesign @aztammyp @DenverElections @dominionvoting Better video in this great t… https://t.co/OjQhCa1m3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[El tiempo no puede volver atrás; pero las memorias SI! #TuRecuerdoHoy #UnaGranEmocionSenti #UnRinconcitoDeMiCorazon… https://t.co/AZyAh7g1Y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaBaer @BoozAllen @truthstreetart @CFCoworking @CapitalFactory @CFDefense Otherwise known as the SR-71 Blackbi… https://t.co/ZidKWDDQWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBatard_Reddit @gregcote Hahahahahahahaha. Amazing. I didn’t get it for like 40 seconds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PanamaJack_757 @_AbrilYMayo @_Just1me_ @Pharrell Yeaaa yeaaa. Whatever https://t.co/xO4lDVFEho]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all honesty, i liked Suicide Squad, it was a decent popcorn film.  However no one really stood out for me so im… https://t.co/4B9rXQCI86]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌬Chanel No.786 *If you know what i mean ... #LasVegas #Nevada @ Delano Las Vegas https://t.co/1G3PUfIIh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tactical_review For the record I carry everywhere and have guns strategically placed throughout the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[@writers_desire Better try to snag a slice before Erza swallows it all in one bite! 😊😋😁😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monte Carlo, Principado de Monaco, Sur de Francia, Mar Mediterraneo. https://t.co/xE22NpMofG]]></document></documents></author>