<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@iamcardib And ten times stronger than the 6’3 (right), 243 pound (right again😂) orange bastard president. https://t.co/IcNSUkKoud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZeeeKyle @bareknucklefc @MMAFighting @RowdyBec @FiteTV @SusanCingari @ChristineFerea Like I said I respect them al… https://t.co/gQsQODtpH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a MAJOR project at work today.  I have no idea how it’s going to turn out... but I’m super excited.  Stay tu… https://t.co/UBYVAZZWOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all Chevelle, Three Days Grace, and Breaking Benjamin are touring together this year and I gotta go so I can pretend I’m 14 again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total love, gratitude, and reverence for this sacred space. I often think of the incredible courage embodied by the… https://t.co/noL7hvsW4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a scam that I have to work all day today (On my off day) &amp; can’t be with my boo. BUT I GUESSSSSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janasea21 I follow back !! VIP on #TeamMAGA #BackTheBlue #SaveTheBabies #KAG2020  #MAGAVET   It's follow for follow friends !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mfr always think I’m cutting his ass off cuz I’d rather take a breaks than argue or waste my time complaining. I]]></document><document><![CDATA[March Madness prices have been posted. Visit https://t.co/L0H5ChDh68 to book.   #dmvbraids #dmvhairstylist #dchair… https://t.co/u1E8wP3xD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some behind the scenes magic: “Soooo one of our engineering alumni won an Oscar for techies what are we doing with… https://t.co/y1zFFOxf8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was hoping to celebrate my next birthday this spring, but Iowa basketball may be the death of me before then. #HookEmHawkeyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deedee_1962 It gets worse every day. My heart is breaking. So very sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love working at a long term care facility  *one of my residents looks upset so I go over there* Me: -“Is everythi… https://t.co/cU2VwNHmCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath She knew something was going on before I did.  She's now a sweet, elderly 16 year old who we treasure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Washington Post: Ruined crops, salty soil: How rising seas are poisoning North Carolina’s farmland.… https://t.co/jssUWIH74v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffworldJosh It's already better than lord of the rings lol already had two battle episodes that are the best on television]]></document><document><![CDATA[3am thoughts...  (My dog comes back inside after going potty) Me: “Is it me or does it smell like updog in here?” (… https://t.co/guUYC1OaE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ga3power It breaks my heart that you’ve experienced this so close to you and your family but I know that because o… https://t.co/Rfk7VyTHCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u want something done it’s better doing it ur damn self bc when u rely on ppl and shit doesn’t get done who’s th… https://t.co/konQbuHRdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait for rosarito &amp; to drink my sorrows away n leave them there! #NewBeginnings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carmen38004447 @TheView @sunny Both Sunny and Meghan are pro-life. Recently Congress voted “No” on a bill and Megh… https://t.co/4lbbXG32Bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're #talking to a friend and she starts #screaming and #struggling hangup and call 911 #Lifetime #SickOfIt 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChooseLove86 It'll take a while. take the time, just try not to let it overwhelm you.  Its truly like losing a dea… https://t.co/U3fVxMwgI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRAYANTIWOOD It’s all love @BRAYANTIWOOD and I appreciate your authentic self don’t ever lose that!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I saw #JordynWoods posted an Instagram live https://t.co/uXWomWbBbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[For if that first covenant had been faultless, then should no place have been sought for the second. https://t.co/YLNYw8bHd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. Olympic Cyclist Kelly Catlin Dead by Suicide at 23 https://t.co/FzDDqc3JeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet spring dreams *♡ @ Libby Patterson Organics https://t.co/tTmUQNaJmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarruRachelH4 @RedHottDevil @ArianaGrande You should do a cover at the tower farm😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mmm #IronBeer. #latergram #Cuban #pop @ Versailles Cuban Food https://t.co/xXetyvf9LO]]></document><document><![CDATA[PERFORMING ARTS MOSAIC • Hittin the step with my #solesisters as we close out the OPEN STAGE show last year at… https://t.co/KBvTTDVEzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyxglass I have several people who are down for me to tie them up but I wanna make sure I know what I’m doing b… https://t.co/Jst1U6KqOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckyysara ::rewinding TiVo since I’m in East Coast:: 😂 Totally just caught #Diggle sleeping. @david_ramsey was that improved?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the mechanic/realtor episode of Nathan for you and holy FUCKING shit I’ve NEVER laughed so hard in my entire god damn life]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a job where I don’t work weekend because u can tell you it’s gonna be a rough morning after]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_campingfamily @algonquinoutfit You are going to like the topic next week. Set your alarm! #WeGetOutside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLZambrana @UpOsmond @donnyosmond @FIDMMuseum Wonderful news! Thank you for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have never had this much road rage when there’s weather in Vegas. JUST DRIVE. #icannot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Boomerang... she was wrong af for going over Marcus house without having her toe nails done 🤣 lmaooooo smdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBSchroeder I hear there is research (I honestly don't remember source so I could be mistaken) coming down the… https://t.co/AmRfwZ7kV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[cheer has honestly been one of the best parts of my life and I can’t believe tonight is my last home game 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how @indelibleev acts when @steph_biasi and I comment on her posts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeslieRiccio @leslielehner @mr_pdayala @KellamCounselor @KFerrell03 @KimDWhitfield @TheresaHolloran Fresh start th… https://t.co/4XQtMavURy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oghaz001 @andyvitale Thanks for the feedback! Not sure when we’ll be back but I hope it’s soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @tomigoldnet Their fragile egos are on display and they absolutely cannot tolerate anyone who challen… https://t.co/yzrGgDNNUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how me, Karissa and Gabby all decided we were going to watch the bachelor this season, now all we do is talk… https://t.co/9e8bDWRtEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s 2 am  who the FRICK thought it was okay to set off 200+ fire alarms in my apartment complex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sentantiq It also has to do with journalism, reference books and non-fiction. It’s preparing for real world writing situations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hater against the President of the united STATES need to be arrested for hate crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beatty nevada is such a weird place likes it's a town of 1000 in the middle of the desert but yet it has 8 Tesla chargers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hareematifkhan @hareematifkhan do you have any recommendations for something to share with parents who are opposed… https://t.co/LkYp2ftdts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lindapearl2 I can record as well but it still picks up ratings.. frustrating..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StinaLeicht Oh, I get it. I'm - gasp - single, and a state worker, so I get a lot of the looking-down thing. But I… https://t.co/oBcxICcBAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than 1 in 5 men in the U.S. are offered any paid paternity leave, and most dads who do have it don’t believe t… https://t.co/UMRaBxZlqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Zentangle ® -inspired illustration is from this week's post, in which you can read at this link:… https://t.co/B2BKclnero]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mali is making great progress on #womenshealth and #girlshealth   #HealthCareForAll #developingworld… https://t.co/JQ9dY5Kwge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory This is so sickening!! Fire all of them!!! He’s picking up trash!!! At his home!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin @SenDuckworth @RepLipinski this policy should be put into law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazed and inspired by the women of the 1940s who built the USS Midway and all those who served and continue to ser… https://t.co/ejvACrM7Oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇… https://t.co/VnkZTVQng8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tadyak Idk how our friendship will ever??? Recover??? From this??? I’m???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime I wake up before 7am I get seriously sad about it and all I can think about is the next time I get to sleep 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shurmur talks about the strides he and Gettleman have made from first year to second with the Giants: “We have a mu… https://t.co/xIeXFcthqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch now: Victims and families of Danforth shooting to call for gun violence action in 1st public remarks https://t.co/CJoxNjcJNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: Knowing my students and giving each of them the support and encouragement they need. Finding ways to challenge… https://t.co/y2Pcsfn8Sn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lownsbery @IU13IMS @zimmermank What would we do without you, @IU13IMS??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crime scene investigator talks about the safety on Jones' gun. @WPTV #NoumanRajatrial]]></document><document><![CDATA[So blessed the day we brought this good boy home #nationalloveyourpetday @kcpetproject @ Platte City, Missouri https://t.co/XCG09Vdql8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Locked my keys in my car again.... Mercury is definitely in retrograde 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sobrevivientes 🌿 #sobrevivientes #enterradaennieve #winter #wintermood❄️ #wintermagic #snowinfebruary… https://t.co/1yTlEMfQbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wormbound @SarahPalinUSA I know the truth . You are the one with blinders on . How many presidents said lower taxe… https://t.co/WgIRjzy3jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't promo your man on Choices as your avatar, are you really even dating??? 👺😹😼🕵🏿‍♀️ https://t.co/firSpkrGCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I agree 100% now let's kick their ass out of Congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieChrisley Great for you!! I've lost 160 lbs...so glad to have finished that journey..now on to the next. https://t.co/AaEBJaOjPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told y’all today was the today‼️💍I am so proud of this team, the early mornings and late nights in the gym all pa… https://t.co/sLD4sX0lEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The periodic table is 150 years old this week - The history of science https://t.co/RZHgIOWlmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know my son is old school Army: we are going to #BTSxMETLIFE and he wants to hear Suga rap Dream Money. His inn… https://t.co/YolAUuZMuF]]></document><document><![CDATA[its one thing to see a fly ass person, but a fly ass family?? whole different flex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hinata has always been fun to cosplay, but I also want to give Sakura a go. Maybe this year I'll finally do it! Who… https://t.co/qhpuolj11r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matchy matchy with my @puravidabrac #ruthsnailart #notd 🌼🥰 https://t.co/0gMpS7pmR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexi5983 Maybe, but I'd either be 6th or I could have been in 5th at Derfelt. I was class of 2003.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a woman and mother defending expressing her biggest fears. We need more people like her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The integrity of the upright guides them, but the unfaithful are destroyed by their duplicity. https://t.co/rGftEChRJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Tyler Perry is really madea but I swear when I watch one of his movies, he really makes you believe that Mad… https://t.co/1YHeQDze7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[In love with San Antonio (@ Ocho Lounge - @hotelhavana in San Antonio, TX) https://t.co/F6qPPjdXuL https://t.co/8aANWslUrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY AMAZING SEXY, INTELLIGENT GIRLFRIEND!! @lizzieyeager]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another alumni doing great things on the field.  Wtg @Si_Grin8 . We are #scfproud @SCFManatees @SCFBaseball… https://t.co/71zGG1Ac3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope, the calm for my soul. @ La Paz, Baja California Sur https://t.co/oMBK7pS3Ec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao I spent about $700 on a dress I wore just once and get this I didn’t even have a date 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This old guy just drove up beside me and honked to tell me my tags are expired. Mind your business SNITCH]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Mexico national soccer team  2. LA Chargers  3. Real Madrid 4. Phoenix Suns 5. Lebron James  6. Morelia  7. LA G… https://t.co/LE4t0gQLMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[FACT: over $44 million Americans with #studentloandebt @almapact #startuppitch #MITfintech]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game night turned into a sleepover. Still stuck in harcourt. Full on survival mode has begun 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[white people are so stupid who goes to the gas station to smoke a CIGARETTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. We need to listen to the voices of indigenous, black and other students of colour. What are the micro aggression… https://t.co/wE0fxCMF9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@addy_pez @RCSD @OfficialLivePD @LivePDNation @Sean_C_Larkin @danabrams @TomMorrisJr1 @WomenPatrol Congratulations I am so happy for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met a twin 🔥✨👯‍♂️👊🏻👊🏻 . . . . Thanks _tsunamijenn_ !! #kacchan #kacchancosplayer #bakugou #bakugoukatsuki… https://t.co/tQiB6QpoOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing donut and coffee. @ Asheboro, North Carolina https://t.co/eaDalp9uSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you go to Olive Garden in your fat pants but by the end they’re just pants #breadsticks https://t.co/5ZFkWSJ1Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st birthday to this beaut 👑🖤 swipe thru to see the cutest photobomb ever. @ Some Random Parking Lot https://t.co/ZQV2iNe8SG]]></document></documents></author>