<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[See our latest #RichmondHill, GA #Healthcare job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Pharmacy Technician at CVS Health]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for fun ♥️ my tribe 🤪 #mytribe @ Timonium, Maryland https://t.co/Rw0xbNyYQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KmetkoG @TweetNathanRich @GrowingupinSCN @AftermathFdn @Clear2Insanity Oh! And lest l forget l am here if you need… https://t.co/vmlMOH3DIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my sister REALLY got 80+ likes on a tweet because she commented on how ron is gonna flip out because sammi got enga… https://t.co/UkeZvoM5WD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Why should we give a fuck what this @GrahamLedger says?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizpeek @Jim_Jordan Money Money Money!!! He got off with just 3 yrs and will be out in 2 1/2 yrs I think he got a stellar deal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProseGarden_HJ I did and wow!!! Yeah... &amp; I'm so confused  too. How? When? Why???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick break to apply #coconutoil after shower 💋 @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/RYAH1Skw0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @JoaquinCastrotx I would have a lot more faith in you if you would be honest in all your dealings with the pub… https://t.co/OGasshGQmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kickstarter for the LOZ anthology is still going strong! Get your copy here! https://t.co/YXDVcpA8ec @LoZAnthology… https://t.co/vuHkLHWqjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want friends that drag me down &amp; talk about bitches all day 😴 Too old for that 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History February 19th 1905 - The cloth cutters of Ludlow Street Photographer Jacob Riis took this photo in… https://t.co/rKzj0n70Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thai princess issues apology after running for prime minister  https://t.co/qmIxzyiiSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veggie bed + morrisfamilyfarms chuck roast = 🤤 @ Morris Family Farms https://t.co/jftRSnrLNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I have a massive migraine right now, thankfully I’ve been good up until today I suffer from migraines and shit i… https://t.co/NSXWkLVU0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniversalORL If yall wanna rehire me for summer id appreciate it. Already applied.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Cosmetologist #hairstylist #licensedstylist #haircreator #stylist #hairdresser #beautyparlor #craftyAF #DMVStylist… https://t.co/bl3oyErdGa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally getting around to watching #CriticalRole's first campaign after trying a few times and not liking it. Third… https://t.co/zis4cqQ46y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making new stuff!! I live spring so much!  it's just around the corner! Yay!! ☀️💜 Just check out my shop it's liste… https://t.co/jpq6fmCszO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥✨ Come as you are ✨🔥        Available for purchase!             Follow my insta:       @goodasgoldashtrays https://t.co/3lLz0XaQo8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use #CharlieThePenguin to help us keep track of what’s going through our bank accounts.  They’ve given me tips on… https://t.co/uIeFO4zciL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blackvalleyfilm @foodevomovie @asbg @Moviemill @kiss1077 Aw...my home space! I’m so pleased to see this movie maki… https://t.co/UyMfGlnyHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final gathering of  @LimestoneDSB K-8 Ts engaging in Indigenous Ed + Turtle Island doc; asking thoughtful questions… https://t.co/GbWa2qBhfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBryanOnline These guys will see you one Thursday! Their 9th birthday and THEY. ARE. CLUELESS. https://t.co/MzgvFifBYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomCostantino @SethMacFarlane @planetary_union @ScottGrimes Did Scott take the helmet home? It is kinda badass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Banshi131 @PLenkov @H50_Writers Yeah..I know I was screaming at TV..how about you tell RACHEL to do right by Danny lol🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraFlowersE @amy_nusbaum This is amazing! I admire your immediate action in helping provide students with food.… https://t.co/qVnqRV7tKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaulGuereca @LDarioAG Supongo que llegará a las 6 de la mañana, y como placa de trailer. 💔☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nope that does not cut it. Franci Neely needs to be charged. @HarrisCountyDAO @FBIHouston @FBITexas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be sorry I screamed this late at night when I saw the mouse come out again but there are neighbors full-on… https://t.co/leDf1VJWYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/M7r8DVFS90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epawawx @NWS_MountHolly I know there is a sound explanation but wouldn't it be great to have the wind in the summe… https://t.co/Bt9h00rJp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All school buses in Wellington Dufferin are cancelled today. Erin PS is open. Please be safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody Wow! What a idiot! Cannot believes that is what they see. I watched the same thing and did not interpret that at all.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now... WTF is Duke... his “death” is a false memory’s! And is her age correct now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[i keep having dreams with @timheidecker and i don’t know what it means 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who would have thought me being a smart ass would get me here 😂😂 Everything happens for a reason 😍 https://t.co/KoSUX9yzZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My students had been begging me to make elephant toothpaste all year... Finally made it happen! #elephanttoothpaste… https://t.co/iJ0MkxJaVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats agree with all idiocy. Why ? So the criminals can walk right in, and vote for them. Look at all the Socia… https://t.co/4NSNQRcvWx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#earthquake is trending because of a 3.5 earthquake? C'mon L.A. We'd handled worse. Go back to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist @Powersource36 By pretending that trump never ran for president, and the Russians never put him into office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend posted this. #snagged #facebookposts #karoke #karokenight #journey #dontstopbelieving @ Aurora, Colorado https://t.co/1TyYYhED3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes it's just a, "break into an abandoned house" kind of day. https://t.co/BoMTX9KXwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza If this Loony toon sat on her hands she couldn’t babble....😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customize your home office 🔙🔛🔝 . Furniture World 🌍 Delray Beach, FL CUSTOM INTERIOR &amp; EXTERIOR FURNISHINGS . .… https://t.co/XXYZ7TDlNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this place to have my cat neutered and these 2 dogs were being all lovey dovey and I can only think that “Spayna… https://t.co/oH6j5E5nKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women’s Herstory Month! #womenrise @sdmesacollege @DeniseRog @RanmaliRanmali https://t.co/sCJ107VqNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a lot of feels about this. Yes she's badass, but this level of passion  means stress that manifests as high… https://t.co/irlsZvHQVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vic_treaty Us trying to do physics hw on the board and then realizing those markers dry as hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good day to appreciate all the women in my life, but also recommit to driving progress - as Jodie Foster said, “n… https://t.co/YrcIlP2aaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t been to work in two weeks b/c of midterms and going to AZ. Going in for one shift this week b/c leaving for Hawaii 😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tacobell @TacoBellTeam I’ve ordered from you via grubhub twice and every time I get my order, something wrong :( j… https://t.co/Aa1Xr2xLEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need a little push in life. No matter what your goals be, and how important they be to you, it is dif… https://t.co/ri2RU3xLai]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw Spike Lee in this picture at the Oscars and i was thinking how sad it is when a former popular celebrity… https://t.co/oqHy5B2Rce]]></document><document><![CDATA[you’re looking at the newest t-ball player on the block! 🧢⚾️ I don’t know who was more excited for this day to come… https://t.co/7OaNBBhKht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even tho it’s extremely dangerous, walking back to our dorm with @lauraedillion at 1:30 in the morning has to be one of my favorite things]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 1412 DESTINI Lane #Southport #FL  #realestate https://t.co/YFv6ntCOGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WolfCraig74 @1COACH_CARTER @BDawsonWrites 😳  If real, it shows what a scumbag he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn mosquito bit me. It flew away but I caught it with my bare hands &amp; killed it. I am a savage.... &amp; also itchy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrabChuck WOW! 4660 packed down and ready for our customers! Great job Dawn and Steven! @RonitaHW @DawnMcSorley84… https://t.co/G4NeB7jzoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveKaval @chrisgiles01 I'm headed to Tokyo to watch our #Athletics in person. Any A's sponsored get togethers or… https://t.co/emcAqsQKIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pw739 @SonOfGodAndMan dont rub your rod on her then.. I mean your "friend" shouldn't. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote this yesterday. Tetris will be the last franchise standing on earth and also this game is v good. #Tetris99]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel the same. I feel so sorry for those people and their lame as lives that they have to do all that 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at a bar tonight eating with friends and the hot bartender put my tab under cutie and omg my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[NC-09:  An elections board cover-up of DEM shenanigans in Robeson? https://t.co/cMi4UJtwI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorhou Hi, Talyor. Are you still in Houston? I'd like to talk to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebugg82714 You are the one that clearly has no idea what they are talking about.  Saying ALL makeup contains a… https://t.co/DtB2hSvsiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike gave me my birthday present a day early....Elton John @TheGarden Yayyyy! I am so excited!]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so glad i met such amazing people in Reno. Love my little squad ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graciefell @SamWeisband Thank you 😊 @graciefell @SamWeisband  thank you 😊 very nice of y’all for following me please 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @politico_z Alex Jones should be locked up, in a high security mental institution, key thrown away.… https://t.co/cu1WTqGko5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I even bother responding to ESPN’s tweets, there will always be that one fuckin’ guy who won’t let you have… https://t.co/9MRMr4DjgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Five Definitive Reasons Trump Has Already Won On The Border Wall! https://t.co/XOytQj3Oi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary ........oh https://t.co/kBN40JMiKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to ALL my Lovies!! Sometimes the only way I see myself is in a photo. 🤨🤪💋💋 dress and shoes fr… https://t.co/0V6cEz9spM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Animals... throw them in jail.  This bull Sh.. started in the 60s and many looked away... mistake]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this time tomorrow I will be readying my workshop @ramalotusyoga in #Ottawa! Creativity and Yoga face your shado… https://t.co/GfLxuLc9tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callistawolf For those of us that had eye surgery and shouldn’t cry, what does he say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenth #halfmarathon is in the books. This one was a hot beast but I’m so proud of everyone who kicked ass and conqu… https://t.co/OoqD4g3aGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ksauer51 First meal of the day (regardless of time) is breakfast sorry I don’t make the rules]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beauti in consciousness... #staywoke @ Meagan Mitchell salon https://t.co/sfgPdnXsfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending lots of Valentines wishes &amp; lots of loves 💌❤️😘🌹🧸🎈 @TeamHowe05 @naeemaothman4 @WolverSteve @WolfMoon84… https://t.co/VRGNn4Hd5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love loving and being loved by this man. ❤️ What a wonderful first vacation together. https://t.co/18cL85Az9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy mustache 😂😂😂 great shadows! Need to get my #lilbro back to Wrigley this summer. #EverybodyIn https://t.co/kjPigoMcha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Dude. You might just want to stay off social media today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my all time FAVORITE video on the Internet ever lmao. It makes me laugh sooooo much 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 5280  County Road 320 #Rockdale #TX  #realestate https://t.co/QSkxUaUmYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA Why has it taken 2years to determine this??  What are we doing about it??  #]]></document><document><![CDATA[i deserve to have money sent to me like all the time and attention okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so lost, I’m barely here. I wish I could explain myself, but words escape me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too late @mattgaetz We all read it and it was only after your @SpeakerPelosi admonished YOU that you pulled it down… https://t.co/SFyqB4okEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[De verdad no saben la falta que me hace una hamburguesa tulueña bien recubierta de quesito y con salsa de piña 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill John Dean, for one.   Plus which, if the administration is fueled by lies, who close to it HASN'T been tainted?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum How gorgeous!  Your nails, your bag!  Hope your evening was wonderful 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will I ever learn that scheduling appointments on Monday mornings while on the overnight is a bad idea?  *stares ou… https://t.co/oE1PAk8WVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I overthinking? Over analyzing? Paranoid? Letting my insecurities get the best of me again? 😓 feels like all of the above.]]></document><document><![CDATA[but rly tho #teampink #pinksociety #lgbt #LGBTQoftwitter #gaygirls #PinkItForward https://t.co/m8gCmrMVhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snubs @JohnBarrowman Yes he is incredible!! He will even go over the time limits if necessary to make sure that ea… https://t.co/xcjF2ClC5X]]></document></documents></author>