<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[In between #weddings and #events we are regularly treated to the many gifts of nature. Cool air, warm #sunshine and… https://t.co/zH9RdcAdgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Evans helping Regina King was 🥰 *swoon* #Oscars https://t.co/PvAtx7qvb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not about to put up with the same stuff I put up with last year, it’s just not gonna happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie dog photo bombing Brogen’s photo shoot 😂                                    #brogen #dogsofinstagram… https://t.co/v5oyYaCa0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump You all remain in my daily prayers for protection and continued success]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaylaraOwl @Geechie4Kamala @chrisdameanor19 Why does a pharmacist think he is a doctor? He is not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From our prayers today @ASCpas @MKinman @UMChurch #FaithfullyLGBT @episcopalchurch https://t.co/cSe1Bx7NWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mugyeman @realDonaldTrump @Varneyco Not from here.  You have NO idea.  It's not the only solution, but is one that… https://t.co/RQ6vJbYEQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flower_boho Loved watching him growing up.and he was a heck of a actor. He will be missed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamlegend1623 The processed cheese is what sticks.. the good stuff doesnt stick to skin.. #expertcheesetosserhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gearing up for Free Comic Book Day with #DCInk and #DCZoom! #underthemoon #catwoman #teentitans #raven… https://t.co/GKsxJPeORY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieMaikit1 How you feel about him taking $$ from military families who are living in slums for his wall?  $$ th… https://t.co/5MsuBXwXy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyPN Si no han visto sus antiguas fotos en Twitter no sabrán que la chama es exhibicionista. Ella es feliz así]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my #LivePd going between the #StadiumSeries since my whole gangs there’s ! Even 2 little guys 1st hockey games… https://t.co/Qlq5POeE4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[My good work is either ignored or taken advantage of. Despite being the best at counting in and out tills and makin… https://t.co/Vioexh52fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnieRadke Devil, What Up Earth, Destiny, and/or Fair Weather Fans .. #mixtape need these on #spotify @Spotify]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioParis Alien!!! Oh, and I love WarGames too, but maybe that’s a different thread.🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@headius The driver was very nice when she finally arrived at my hotel although she kept telling me the roads (pave… https://t.co/x4bpZ5O0xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting rid of a wait list by ending the services, doesn’t solve any problems. It makes more problems, that will co… https://t.co/nCcYDCOKCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter I love you and you deserve the best 💕 loved seeing you last night like always 🤗🥰 https://t.co/U5WRvgihOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family is so important......so hard today.  Keep in touch with your loved ones! #family #love #ripunclewayne❤️ @ Cl… https://t.co/GfEoOFg8cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaddyGurks @unclebizzy4 @Lesley_NOPE John is professional and he tells the story. He is not salty. That makes his stuff readable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freaking excited at this point. Main structure of the body is build plus legs ready to be transfered to Eva foam. J… https://t.co/0M1zpXaYUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Our system needs to evolve a bit here, I have shared the same advice only to find people blocked at t… https://t.co/fSuYsOCefP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch When will our Justice system do something about it ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d be genuinely interested in discussing potential solutions to the issue of transgender women in sports. DM’s are open]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catch me singing my heart out to all the wrong lyrics at these next concerts  #BLACKPINK #STRAYKIDS https://t.co/e2xWC5PrDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Errriee So sorry I'm late getting back to you sweetie. I had to go back on them. I have seasonal depression when t… https://t.co/cAnBX6QoSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Hourly Restaurant Assistant Manager - https://t.co/zKIQOpo4dx #Restaurant #Owensboro, KY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some personal favorites listed #Esquirrou Sheep milk imported by Savencia USA  #ClothboundCheddar by… https://t.co/1aBKLQdbyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when I predicted (jinxed) Parra getting the wooden spoon after their first trial last year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@narendramodi Stop the condemnation and ensure a befitting reply is given immediately, no more terrorist attacks in… https://t.co/APmEBsSiO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for the next meeting of Orlando NOW.  https://t.co/DKu9L9Y70m https://t.co/xmjfrJY4XD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those in the area, please keep an eye out for her. https://t.co/uDsTzHvqrq  ( Sent from FCN )]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I think about on a daily basis:   1. what should I do with my life after I graduate   2. will I make enough… https://t.co/JgB50A427w]]></document><document><![CDATA['Rage Daily News' Keeps It 100 About White Privilege https://t.co/2biAVkUk0n via @blacknerdprblms]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItsSundaysBest Sunday Morning Blessings Worldwide #GodUp @ Washington, District of Columbia https://t.co/lvek3F4obN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annelise_c26 woke me up in a panic thinking we had to work something today and our shift was from 7-10am so we’re… https://t.co/PI0gAZBxjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pid_gov and #bryanharlan you should be ashamed, but we all know you aren’t because you are cowardly, immoral fools.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenKiraa Deadass!!! Really tryna come for this girl like don’t get me wrong she’s fucked up too but she is DEFF… https://t.co/CYqBwUX7MY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel MARK MEADOWS should be Cirque du Soleil tarred feathered &amp; RUN OUT of office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 spots left for our travel blogger happy hour today after #wtfest19! Hope you can join us!!… https://t.co/0IQX3Tmr4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[And THIS my friends is why the GOP is afraid of @AOC    While the GOP used their time to grandstand, she asked ques… https://t.co/cD93G0k1Nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PumpRulesOGs Wow. No one provoked him at all. Being disinvited is embarrassing and emasculating. He could have han… https://t.co/pVORTreBek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland “I think Bob Mueller's an American hero … even though he came from an, arguably, privileged background… https://t.co/p86n7mJXY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMitchellMD @RepDonBeyer @HouseDemocrats She's recovering until the end of the month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@expectopaolita You’re welcome! and we can use it towards @artetriste too 😝🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jax is a lil worried about Grammys feeding style 🤣🤣 #thatfacetho #jaxonoliver #marchbaby #almost1… https://t.co/NdmoFO0NUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSalesforce It is early here,  they moved out instance on SF this morning so I am just validating. 4 am came fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s YOUR story? #saylavie #maudegrahamjewelry #jewelry #madewithlove @ Plainview, New York https://t.co/qrZtRU96he]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ The regret reveals itself in other ways even if one is not aware.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought it was unique. How many people get engaged in a Haunted Museum]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianMcGloin1 @iff_or I can’t spell that either! But I am just generally bad at spelling.   I thought I could say… https://t.co/jmTK7nF8xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SdeWeger Yes, it happens. That's why we just had a bishops synod on child abuse.  But not all those accused are gu… https://t.co/Et5cwifyV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the @SisterhoodExt Success Summit with Elena 😀 photosbyelenaandjim   📸📷🎬📽🎥📸📷🎬📽🎥📸📷🎬📽    -  #womeninmedia… https://t.co/qCFAyBI6Ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerseymikes Hi we drove about 15 miles to get JM in Hoover AL tonight with the email BOGO free sub coupon. They ar… https://t.co/ISABkNIxih]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PadresUK hey man, late night tweet here, early tweet there. But, how did you become a padre fan? Being a guy who d… https://t.co/w8p1DdpWUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[walking straight into the weekend✨ • • • • #universalstudios #islandsofadventure #universalorlando… https://t.co/lxy1b0ijTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any tweet or drawing I do and gets 1 or 2 likes and possibly a retweet XDDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedmatrix This is a sin. A black spot on America's Heart. If we don't help our neighbors across our nation the… https://t.co/lVg7zCQJnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t take her long to be on the take. Crooked Hillary 40 years ago. This is how it starts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ With GOD All Is Possible Loving Bud "Specially-Abled" Son Trisomy Miracle https://t.co/N2U0v1IZ87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavensRantz Jackie was in the position of Tres kids Her parents did it not her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bilks @rodadams46 Until the Muslims cut your head off because you are a Jew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All set up and ready to read! Join us this morning at 10 am @BPL_inthecity Downtown branch #NoDragonsForTea If you… https://t.co/kwkPFRbNH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@idasanchez716 @tomboyranfan Well I’m here at the San Antonio Rodeo and whose music do u think they are playing?… https://t.co/f3GgHDZS2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IllinoisCivics thanks for your work to bring civics back! EVERY. SINGLE. DAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evan_fit @MichaelAvenatti Just saw that video you mentioned.  They were definitely buying a red hat.  But JS isnt… https://t.co/jutRJVvete]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JuanitaNetflix about peach's rig You gotta whole world up in here, a whole world #truckerjackie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brown City was offer to get a flick with us, but declined. Unfortunate. Congrats to Sandusky, Harbor Beach, and Bro… https://t.co/RoOsWmN0io]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I wasn’t a horrible person and late to literally everything. But I am. That’s me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsktoMandrake @RalitoDigital Pero no habia crisis humanitaria segun Delcy la fea]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #RT Featuring our @KPSanBernardino TAVRs heroes in honor of the last day of February Heart Health Month... Drs. D… https://t.co/1w68gc3UeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mujerdelvino Si ya conozco ese vino y esta un buen precio con la posibilidad de el envío Si lo compro. De lo contrario No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zanarkand4ever @babytwosteps i did this a few months ago and everyone said I was gonna die but I drank it and vodk… https://t.co/ijpXIyL3v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lumpy88 @ehj5010 @Lovatsis14 @J_Stizzy1124 @jachobe Can I get “Spot the Penguins fan for 500,” Alex? 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jumping on super late - hola everyone! I’m Aida and my book, #TheMoonWithin came out 2 days ago! It’s about an 11 y… https://t.co/eDnQnFxEuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Omni Community Credit Union in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/xHLgAscxEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Accounting job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Staff Accountant a… https://t.co/1havQqlff7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section 8A West Championship at REA in Thief River Falls. Ada-Borup West vs Fertile-Beltrami  7:45 - tip off https://t.co/cfzzCvC2Mn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro You will be a stunning bride. Congratulations to you and the lucky man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when someone asks me about places to go in Austin and if I live there  🤠yeeeehaw 🤠 I live in Miami but… https://t.co/dzJ8EiG4kS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to everyone except #MyArchNemi who I really hope will take some sober inventory of their life today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just want to come out and reveal that im a fake and i never stanned the jonas brothers ,,, so i feel nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @gloria18513108 gonna be the trash state but it's there choice]]></document><document><![CDATA[You were great... won't forget you... always a glowing talent in everything you did❤️😭📽📺📻📜 https://t.co/addfDaaxc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone get this kid on the phone... after Saturdays performance he can teach UK a thing or 2 about shooting 3’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonmatheson it's not your responsibility to positive-up anyone's day. You have a right to criticize whatever you… https://t.co/xaPU6SsWpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate working a 4 hr shift and then working over 9 hours the next day and making the same amout of money in tips. Such a waste of a day 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodsaPox We are all Sinner's and if you are perfect you probably won't live long because God works through ordinar… https://t.co/ohgVrX1Oxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agentausten09 Lol, not for me. The hairier the better. 😁 I get that though. I shed enough hair from my head to clo… https://t.co/PT1hU3IEtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next brewery @fernsonbrewing with devang1944 @ Sioux Falls, South Dakota https://t.co/CC0KIKCO1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoboldtVanessa @BoyGeorge Muchos Gracias 🙏🏼💓 only love for the Boy 🌈🎩♥️🌟✨!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actordougjones @startrekcbs @StarTrekNetflix @CBSAllAccess @SpaceChannel @CraveCanada This news makes my happy heart Squee!! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know why my child is awake at 3am 😴 “mommy I have to go potty” “mommy drink” “mommy I hungry”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Chinese New Year event of 2019 🎉 #fortune #health #happiness #feast #yearofthepig @ Good Kitchen Restaurant https://t.co/gfl0qqqVFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF YOU DONT HAVE BANDS UR BROKE KAYLA SO BASICALLY YEAH LOL ARE YOU UGLY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Tony starks calls bucky the manchurian candidate in civil war... https://t.co/iJKdWhJjfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierrerosellini @martinerande La battre à plate couture aux élection = la réponse À moins que déjà noyér dans son fiel!....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@helenbmarrow You should submit an editorial comment, or, better yet, write an op-ed about this. Re-framing her arg… https://t.co/i8bE33vBMO]]></document></documents></author>