<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Straub American Lager by @StraubBeer @ Dinger's — https://t.co/oK14IYOlHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEAN_MARINE @SharylAttkisson @SharNeal @ShannonBream @JudgeJeanine @marklevinshow @MarkSteynOnline Jussie Smollett… https://t.co/tzQauz5nAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#weaponsOfMassDestruction if they were lying about those, did the fabricate the truth in 2001?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP Pence either has the onset of dementia, or he simply loves kissing the butt of #AgentOrange #Enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always get invited to happy hour with my team and I know I should go but I’m not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else remember that before he was terminated without retirement pay, Andrew McCabe threatened to "Take d… https://t.co/cXTdeZ2uoi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next furnace is just going to be all my workstations plugged into the vents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikSolheim Also consumes a boatload of space while roasting birds that fly near. Shift to Tesla’s patent 685,957… https://t.co/xs5YEcLB9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tradingwell Ahh timing, the thing that turns winning into losing. This is something seasoned bulls &amp; bears can agree upon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InsteadOfSheepICount criminal indictments, convictions and guilty pleas surrounding the tRump crime syndicate #LockThemUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynthiaNixon @JoeBiden @mikepence As a gay man, I was not offended by this. In fact was more offended by… https://t.co/oqUy1OdhP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyAdami  I need you to stay bearish.  If you capitulate to non bearish the sh@t is going to hit the fan and I will have to sell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukieLang That does sound frustrating. But I validate your idea, and now it is time to let that disappointment go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@true_pundit Ernie Chambers is the Nebraska State Legislatures court jester.  The only reason he is in his chair is… https://t.co/jgYkyt3sDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT @maggieNYT They’re not overstatements or mis- characterizations, they’re flat out lies. Stop sugar coating his bull💩.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nobilta_miseria @GianlucaVasto C'avete l'ossessione per il PD. Ma una volta tanto una responsabilità ve la prender… https://t.co/0IFBd8OI7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhxKen Clint certainly got it right: OBAMA is One Big Ass Mistake America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miketarasow @Jensnh87 Not at all they have a gender to all media does. Did you know there are five companies in Am… https://t.co/HPL3nMRp20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callcody1 @Conjacerio @TSN_Sports @TSNHockey @TSNBobMcKenzie I spent some time at the rink hey skippy https://t.co/mfLMrZ1015]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto ya es de locos y el tarado de @MartinVizcarraC se llena el hocico con la lucha contra la corrupción y la impun… https://t.co/qy8J9KB4Ds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racism Like This Is Taught. And Can't Be Ignored. https://t.co/cdDhsXZfFB via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demo Continues at BVUUF.   Click here to visit updates at the Building Committee Blog:  https://t.co/mWumZbYVZw https://t.co/URgVgrkED3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean I pulled his auto out of Bowman draft so hey, let’s keep it up eh lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at MARTA - Indian Creek Station - @martaservice in Stone Mountain, GA https://t.co/110jROj4pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The colors and patterns of Santa Fe @ Santa Fe, New Mexico https://t.co/jX7B4d1gjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@igz The moment he comes I desperately try to skip forward. I can’t take him anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[They ended ABC portion of Combine asking who stood out. Louis Riddick went Dwayne Haskins. McShay and Kiper went Pa… https://t.co/5oNvwSeqFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently found out you can send gifs via email and my world has drastically changed. Sad, but true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second day of corporate headshots today. Electric company yesterday, country club today: https://t.co/KzqUXW2mqM https://t.co/A8Qd4vHLdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was hard to make out some of the numbers, but if @LoriSchmidt’s binoculars are true, the first-team offensive li… https://t.co/ilCqW2MRU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraGay @kelleydixon The silver lining of this shitstorm cloud is the majority of us know how terrible a significa… https://t.co/3E3y0qESGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokerRat1 Thanks.  I can tell you this.  It'll be easier to lose the weight than face my wife if I end up losing the bet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else is hype about this 60 degree weather for Oklahoma this weekend 👋🏼🙋🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitansSouthwest @walterfootball @TitansReport No problem man. I started it lol. Thought it would be best to have a… https://t.co/dhxSAH4Vfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGrims503 @chrystalized94 @adamcbest Talk to me when this disgusting mess is all over. This administration is the… https://t.co/Byrl59ayT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you had a nice Presidents' Day! God Bless America. https://t.co/qKhUusaXZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you do after you spend the whole weekend with teenagers? You take your kids sledding! Love these guys.… https://t.co/jMliUneQ79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 Fitz says you’re going about this the wrong way. You say Pouncey doesn’t like being called a kid but just ink… https://t.co/DrxF9T7xr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missed bachelor party Friday and amazing brunch yesterday thanks to this damn cold, but today I feel better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever course you decide upon, there's always someone to tell you that you're wrong. There are always difficultie… https://t.co/5mgFdYv3xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@disneydenise73 @thecjpearson Often well-to-do young people, feel guilty over their good fortune, and the need to c… https://t.co/N94hroClfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 18 I identified as Independent, but my parents were Republican so leaned kinda conservative. At 35, I think all… https://t.co/aFAjvcOUCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like all these folding phones that no one asked for is taking away from cool tech like DeX by Samsung. One d… https://t.co/GStsWdGcJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have to agree with sentiment that Luque would have lost without the finish @espnmma #UFCPheonix]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What is something you love that society tells us is not valuable, intelligent or cultured? If the question had bee… https://t.co/1llEuwn5o4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eight seconds to go, @FBAlions up 64-61 and will be at the line when post resumes. One and one situation @NDN_PrepZone @nphssports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent editorial shoot of actor @NatePotvin for BitMap magazine. Photo taken with fujifilm_xseries cameras and… https://t.co/ynzbTGoeLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now this is all starting to make sense. Good grief. Brexit divides Europe and creates a permeate tax haven]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queen_Geiana He ain’t even ask or put it in quotations, just used my shit no credit no nothing 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure I had to read this like 3 times during undergrad and WHEW yet I’m also pretty sure this is the firs… https://t.co/e5bY2NtOMD]]></document><document><![CDATA['Unicorn' Tarantula Wears a Weird Horn on Its Back https://t.co/71Ii8qPXWZ via @LiveScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LA_Banker @laura_nelson Tempted, but it’s LA so you’re totally not going]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends: wanna do something next weekend?  Me after hearing the Jonas Brother’s are finally getting back togethe… https://t.co/dAOLZVrTzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tipstrum1 FWIW, #cigarettes are much more addictive than #ecigs. Moreover, recent data shows #vapor products are v… https://t.co/VWqXBoYBQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @SaraCarterDC @realDonaldTrump @MichaelCohen212 @POTUS And the demon-crats in their desperation and… https://t.co/kNert7cSkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BebeNeuwirth Gwen Verdin in The Sound of Music or Fiorello!  Ummmm, I don’t think so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crozzlow latest work....“Jean-Michel’s Gilded Safe Word” 36x24. Everything but the kitchen sink and gesso on canvas… https://t.co/3fS2jGMiYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VontesRealm No shade ... but they really releasing this? 😂😂😂😂💀 https://t.co/oSA2obdyY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[For history buffs this is of the Spartacus Movement in Post WW1  in Germany, it was a Marxist revolutionary movemen… https://t.co/UEOWi9G7aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite Wilma Vote! @RealErinGray @MeTV @Gil_Gerard #BuckRogers #TheFlintstones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ARmastrangelo @ARmastrangelo Probably true of Bronx women who actually live there, and not the ones who just show up for photo ops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thirsty_Pilgrim @bartlebeer @HartfordBrewer I think that’s a fair question. For most competitions (not that they/t… https://t.co/NWJFjAsIl3]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're drink comes with a straw, you ordered the wrong drink --@Diddy]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6 we’re supporting @_universalsigh ! Buy tickets-&gt; https://t.co/pNJFyA7hHb https://t.co/1GSc0jcVd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why on earth or heaven or at the Victoria’s Secret fashion Show would you ever wanna “Angel Invest”!? #ch2 #cs183vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛬 (@ San Francisco International Airport - @flysfo in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/E3QDgKXGbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[REMEMBER to the PEOPLE: The CONSTITUTION is to protect the PEOPLE from BIG GOVERNMENT Abuses in Washington DC! Thei… https://t.co/2PlZYjMbpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So.... I just got to @flySFO six hours early thinking I could get into the @AskAmex Centurion Lounge from Terminal… https://t.co/WSLB8u0cxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Hollywood, they're good at making up stories. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/FyLmkbBvT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStuedler It is all about polls and money. Values? Principles? Not so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pamforrest3 @Steph56Renee Jim. I wouldn't say you were involved in this sex scandal at Ohio State. Unless of cours… https://t.co/CwxH8ZTWEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Come on down” For some great RVs at some Unbelievable Deals Today at the North Carolina RV Dealers Association Sho… https://t.co/Oh865J8DZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellos, mi motor, mi motivación, mi luz ....... Uds las razón de mi lucha diaria. Mis hijos.  Dios bendiga cada día… https://t.co/qnscevr3bZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve literally tried everything to find pleasing sex. And it all ends the same...everyone thinking it was mind blowing sex except for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @__lawson22__  on the win tonight!! Still love my Panthers 🐾 but best of luck to you the rest of yo… https://t.co/0fSQzdlAK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day One: One on One w/ ncbutterfly17  Ab Work.  Music provided by Lissen Band 5-19-07 Tacoma Station #Strength… https://t.co/NM8PvLHK5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[QUESTIONS ARE GOING THROUGH MY MIND.  🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️🤦🏾‍♂️  GOOD NIGHT. 😴 😴😴😴  This photo of me and the expression… https://t.co/jD6BQH578u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrCeezy No but he should have. He was snubbed back in 2012, 2013 &amp; I'll leave it at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Timeout OC South Plains College leads 74-73 with 50.5 seconds remaining.  Wranglers with the ball. 13 second left on the shot clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DelmGordon I really want to say Future just because of his impact but idk man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerrForce1 @HigginsEats Here is another one for you.. https://t.co/uKpskcGTdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump He didn't say that.  He said he doesn't have a book deal. So that m… https://t.co/iowR2JTeLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHWministries 2/2 My Lord condemns lying, bullying, adultery, cheating, law breaking, siding with dictators. How about YOUR GOD?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@earangu @ibepacheco Intervencion Militar PERO EXTRANJERA YA, la FANB es EL PROBLEMA - Basta de Jalarles Bolas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiazCanelB Compartir con el pueblo humilde? Que compartisteis?Tus marisco y filetes,tus mansiones y tus viajes? Tu… https://t.co/TuN0sAl3gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You don’t have to be a Social Worker but you need to know one!” @saragoldrickrab @AchieveTheDream #ATD_DREAM #socialwork #socialworkers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chibikuma83 Last year was my first time also! The voice is still there.  Shes finding her way again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian All the Kardashian’s stole peoples men but your mad when it’s done to you ☕️ 🐸]]></document><document><![CDATA[You feeling OK?  Perhaps you need a full psychiatric evaluation. Throw in a CAT scan of the brain while you’re at i… https://t.co/eDzCqc1Ar4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/fAw29mIO08]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people text me saying “call me” and literally want nothing at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii 4 years plus he’ll additional sentencing next week. Trump’s campaign manager is going to prison. All y… https://t.co/vjmRorR8mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to take this moment to remind everyone that @GovBillWeld is launching a primary challenge to the shill pic… https://t.co/lxCarSExxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see you trying to make a point but that ain’t the case lol. We talking personality and lifestyle traits. Not cons… https://t.co/Q4M44PTcyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Definitely some top level sleuthing toward winning the war on drugs here:]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Haller Post in Seattle, WA https://t.co/BzN6SR3or2 https://t.co/LJ8UJwWHap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wayno_70 @Lexus No, they were already there. This behind a strip mall, quite certain they were done at night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirchilly Where i work its plenty Dominican women getting money with good hobs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just inspires me and I'm sure all of you to eat more beef farts or no farts. This is a Soros hack for sure or… https://t.co/L4eh1Me8JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@307x He’ll make your jaw drop and then make you kick a wall. Seems like a great guy and I’m sure he’s okay with mi… https://t.co/NE0z26ESoh]]></document></documents></author>