<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Icepickdanza @GameOverGreggy @andrearene If you get the gold or ultimate edition (comes with the year 1 season pas… https://t.co/KruvUUPWCv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tercer avance de @Radio_Zocalo #Noticias. Feligreses asistentes a la Catedral Mártires de Cristo Rey de @DiocesisPN… https://t.co/6bVV2b7Nib]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice changes with this simple drill. Getting away from bad contact to solid contact.  https://t.co/lKZxErDrAa @ Dee… https://t.co/mSn0j89Ak5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a shitty pillow .  I will never support a Trump supporter !!#MYPILLOW @realMikeLindell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how much money you can dealing guns over sea's. War is inevitable... what side you on? The money side]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Meph @Sixdiceskills Relatedly Dok, will just have to run Morathi as a counter to the Gristlegore general who do… https://t.co/tGwbJv6GOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's just RIDICULOUS! @NBA will apologize to the @hornets but it's too late. The ref was within 5 FEET  of… https://t.co/yJG24BWZnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssgslack @Jason @justinkan Cause they (the rich people) just don’t a shit about anybody unless it affects their “b… https://t.co/yvX4yq89jb]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are here for another hour. Find me at this table and I will buy you a beer. @Uleletampa @VisitTampaBay… https://t.co/k8soeSu5XE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Levy4_PreSident @JPGroves @MrLastChantz @KarenTrujillolc Thanks Coach much appreciated!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 1 - The Hive:    Elizabeth Warren’s Rookie Mistake Foreshadows a 2020 Money War;      Wall Street Bets… https://t.co/zbt0XVzyUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Valentine's Day, love is spelled I-H-O-P. @ IHOP https://t.co/H8kqvGAsFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys district basketball Madison 42 Hudson 11 at the half. @lenaweesports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KidCudi I really want to enjoy your song, but that fucking rising up and drone in the background is really killing… https://t.co/ZHXc9kwTNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Image detail for -Western wedding by Your Inner Song | Pretty Little Weddings https://t.co/C3bG7XrSDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flexing that you hang out with girls and pre game? Damn bro save some for the rest of us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast in the Classroom is changing lives for @JCPSTWEETS students!! We couldn’t do it without support from… https://t.co/e9JruVb3UF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't  have this nascar app you need to download it.  Schedule Racecenter Standings Fantasy League Every thi… https://t.co/hh8M0xuTaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[FOR THE 6TH TIME! IT’S DAYS OF THUNDER ALL OVER AGAIN!!! @sadieastanley @seangiambrone1 @Ciarawilsonxo @ErikaTham… https://t.co/iNU0beamC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s a damn shame that Sanchez is our highest paid player and De Gea isn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaReefKnockOut MJ was sitting on it too, left hand was almost touching the floor, AI still shook him just hard eno… https://t.co/glRA38UHhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this online and immediately had to buy it! It's gonna be cold in AZ for the spring training games next weeken… https://t.co/vBMlMb17un]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get up and get it this money... It doesn't care, it doesn't wait, it's only there for those who put in the… https://t.co/cGKzUWISFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisgarcian @JPAlvarezGuedea @AbboudOropez @SocCivilMx @ferbelaunzaran @beltrandelrio @FelipeCalderon… https://t.co/3QRxltmcLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidMeleroEF Kids always surprise me with their creativity. A challenge like this could really get students excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I really want to go to class rn I’m about to be a minute late is it worth the effort?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how much @Microsoft intentionally causes Chrome to slow my laptop to a crawl, I'll never use Edge. Seriously, just give it a rest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A massive thanks to @wilkespharm and @stottletron13 for helping to bring Erin to NEPA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration He’s Uber wealthy. He’s not yet fixed Chicago. Illinois needs more uneducated unemployed? Another stupid liberal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_johnson412 You have to try chikn in Oakland we just opened a few weeks ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom @djrothkopf @dandrezner Don’t forget all of the regressive taxes middle and working class folks pay (… https://t.co/vOKFG3dfFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t put me in a group message cause I’ll fuck around and start blowing it up just texting random shit 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these couples are going to wake up to all these paragraphs tomorrow morning and I’m going to wake up with my ph… https://t.co/tIRoxDQIvd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a simple request @SGcrimlaw. We have psychiatrists ready. Let her contact her family. #JoycelynSavage #RKelly… https://t.co/8r2EnImikL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mac Dalena #WideReceiver #2020 at the @uaallamerica #underarmour #uaallamerica in chilly #Folsom #rjpsports… https://t.co/m71SZ3kLqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamSlauter I think I’ve got Matty-Ice. Just have to hold on long enough for him to choke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jocelynnmassiel you and your little clique turn out to be fake, you all really tricked me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanchyAlmonte @juan_sanchez01 @JoseGomezFrias JAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The return of the Ashi 180mm Swedish stainless petty. Big petties make an awesome line knife, just long enough for… https://t.co/zaHZT869QU]]></document><document><![CDATA[so my inactive YouTube channel that I only use to watch videos has been terminated!!?!! @Youtube @Fwiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just for some reason wanted to squash beef that didn’t need to be. i’m on the “if we end badly fuck you” energy.… https://t.co/TjdbcqtaTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven @GOPLeader president trump admitted he fired comey to stop the investigation of russian interferenc… https://t.co/vYTvXIV0c0]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they lost their house behind that shit, too. And had to downsize  then save up and move back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now Putin is trending, so I guess we know who's behind Cobain's renanimation/campaign funding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job for #FGCU men’s golf on the tournament win and @NaplesHS graduate @chasebigham on his ninth place perform… https://t.co/lF6NZ2gaE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze The real question we should be asking is how Colorado allowed this in the first place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A healthy UNC Squad is the best team in the ACC year, bar none. More depth/shooters than Duke. More talent than UVA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe Donald Trump’s ‘Maximalist’ approach as outlined by @mikeallen —big approach to things because Donald… https://t.co/i0lW9WgQ3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s literally dying and I’m like oh look, another guy in underwear 🤷🏽‍♂️   -yea he’s attractive but it’s not… https://t.co/AuMLJXOkDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenDaddyNinja @JasonIsbell Would love to hear Jason's take on this. And I agree, hearing DA, DT or JI on slide is as close as we get]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea she did both characters. That's crazy and she is awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then she proceeded to tell me I’m probably not covering myself up which is how I got the flu?¿?¿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PennyMuetzel Hard to fit a wife, two kids and a dog in a 125 sq ft studio]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle with me for a bit. #funniness #tee-hee #smile #clever https://t.co/c3bEa1wiIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just not even going to bother getting on Instagram/Snapchat today lmao ❤️🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[На меня в инстаграме подписалась "Помощник депутата". Жаль не написала какого депутата. https://t.co/ehjJ6v3vl1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEYTNC3Senerey If my surgery goes well , I will be speaking to parents at Our Lady of Guadalupe Church on Thursday night about this topic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @tyler_devereaux - notice the meme game is strong as Godzirra wishes Kitten Happy Birthday 🎈I hope y… https://t.co/GNB13wSwSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @yourmumspants @PCribbett @mikenedie @tklforgiven @KotobaruSanSama @Heliocoptero @PittsburghTodd… https://t.co/mYMwxhKwcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a pic I got of @MilesBridges last year where he dunked so hard that he exercised demons out of the poor dude. https://t.co/MlTEKrrXtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobEstesPGA @rpcannon313 @CologuardGolf Ryan: you’ll love playing w @BobEstesPGA On Tour, we used to pay just to p… https://t.co/3P2b02t8bA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dewdrop42 @RcsSports Oh man such and such playing with us, he wasn’t at practice because he got real bad sunburn a… https://t.co/aABhHGukZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the left is allowed to throw the racism card and rewrite history unchallenged, this is the inevitable result]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProspectJesus @MLBMovingAvg Doubt Oakland really cares about pitchers because they get injured so often they rarel… https://t.co/6ZdCr4FRYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlanetTyrus @drdrew @KatTimpf I humbly apologize if i have offended anyone but this is a National Emergency… https://t.co/vOUm5igDur]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘You got 2 minutes to order’  Industry people: ‘Oh then no thanks’  Other people: ‘Lets do 12 wings, sauces on the side with fries and tots’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convos with 3 year olds! #deklenryan @ Bluffdale, Utah https://t.co/8rvzpdiE4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenSani_1958 @ElginCharles @YeshaCallahan @HBO @Channel4 Typical and obvious more like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This antenna works pretty well on my Yaesu HT. Even inside a building I can hit repeaters within a 35 miles away. https://t.co/RtLsgCrFDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the @Spotify app would let me send a nice message to users who created playlists, to let them know their pla… https://t.co/MCSkRpBgNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just nominated @briewhitexxx for 2019 @XBIZ Cam Awards presented by @MyFreeCams! #xbizmiami https://t.co/0VPy2JzyIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeannineSabuncu lmao aight my fault you jus might be right for once you know what you talm bout 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a funny little world in which form letters from HR for TT positions try to acknowledge the emotional labor of… https://t.co/QOnf2zFaWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Deep Fractures’: Veteran New York Times columnist explains how bitter divisions in the US could create a 4-party s… https://t.co/b2mcnEWEAC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este gol debió ser narrado por Óscar Cadena y ganador en bonos del ahorro nacional en Sopa de vídeos si fueran los 90s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one year when February felt like summer. I enjoyed hiking in Palisades Park, wearing shorts and a t-shirt. This… https://t.co/38w3cjxH6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to sleep after a 3 hour drive home at 3am and i cant sleep cuz my ears are ringing. Had the speakers boosted to max to keep me up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next bout is defending champ Landon Foor (46-0) of Fred T Foard vs. Alberto Vargas- Perez (50-4) from Lexington for 2A 182 title]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Western Glow by @casa_agria @ Chez Buchon — https://t.co/zZI9agYzUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pierre_lemieux And here's another wrinkle -- https://t.co/mplXVpg6mo  Different? A little, but still shows how gov… https://t.co/yqFV3An1RX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bob_woolsey We have a lot of those insane infrastructure design fails here too. It’s a big reason for the whole ‘c… https://t.co/c6V5xpQLYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation   Get @JeffBezos on the phone.  Now.  #topoli #onpoli #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaBig90 @SirDaveyBoy It was a battle to say the least. Miss ya Byerly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aqua174 No matter how thirsty Jordyn was/is, if Tristan didn’t engage it then her family wouldn’t have broken up.… https://t.co/C1wrGrj1RY]]></document><document><![CDATA[$NVDA heavy I see profit taking and selling today on a Friday. All depends on the market but key level is 158]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horgan and his sidekick needs to go, our province is suffering because they don’t want anything to start that might… https://t.co/new452XgZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsmehannah_b @getfeedback Have you checked out our local friends @TINYpulse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronmortgageguy Been looking at SDF homes downtown Toronto recently and anything listed near $1m is going for 250-400k over asking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colin_dunlap I'm not sure AB plays more than a handful of games for the Raiders. There are suspensions coming. And… https://t.co/GW5VWO5iJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @KrisKatJam @realDonaldTrump Sorry Alec— grow up— your children will be embarrassed by you someday]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does global warming work? Indiana seems to be ignoring it. ITS FREEZING HERE 6 MONTHS/YEAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@David_Gergen @jimsciutto @CNNnewsroom My guess David is they still haven’t found their spines and continue to be c… https://t.co/28SHa3GXAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Pharmacy Technician Lead Instructor - https://t.co/TcZ8QdmVZ1 #Healthcare #Denver, CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the past few years, being vulnerable and transparent about my own #MentalHealth experiences have changed my li… https://t.co/xwfmliqD9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber hasn't hit profitability tho?? It's revenue has nothing to do with the bottom line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[While Southern Baptists speak of “God’s person” chosen “for such a time as this” to describe its leaders, that lang… https://t.co/16upn5TR8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pPqRnv7oK7 Despite missing the last few weeks with a knee injury, Duke's Zion Williamson has been name… https://t.co/W2ftbJFnCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CincyCurse_ 1. Producing NBA ready players 2. Winning regular season 3. Generating school revenue 4. Developing co… https://t.co/32dPy23tDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is literally rappin bout it a fuckin hell of a lot more recently and his music release and features is pointing… https://t.co/1fh9MFthFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PunkDaGod @gooseyhoops I could hear my roommate shouting from the other room 😂]]></document></documents></author>