<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@houstonpolice Better arrested than the homeowner shooting them ! It’s Texas after-all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First kashoggi now this. @realDonaldTrump you are a nothing but a money grabber all u care about is trump hotels in… https://t.co/vufnDv2Tz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nabe2019 #ESCregion20 #southsideisd #sa4duallanguage •new America belongs to everyone !” Supt. of Miami-Cade publi… https://t.co/vze7fyA9tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbz What a great guy! He had no fear, and just chased the guy! 👏👊🏼Stil good people out there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surprise birthday party for uncle pulled off successfully. 😁 (at @SaltrockKitchen in Sedona, AZ) https://t.co/k8ev9bvlBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry I can’t, I have plans with my dog 🐶 💕 @ South Fayette https://t.co/x43uduuyZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m still up by 7, I’m just going to stay up because if I fall asleep I’m going to over sleep and miss class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You seem very pleased with yourself the way you are treating the president of Unite… https://t.co/QqQbYRzJEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[You take family photos/shitty senior photos and u had the audacity to look at my shit then dm talking about u do bu… https://t.co/t0iUVg58qn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @City_Perch Kitchen + Bar in North Bethesda, MD https://t.co/yGfmu1Qkq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[just had a mental breakdown on the phone to my mom in the middle of the day! love that for me! 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg @SonySquareNYC I will live vicariously through everyone’s posts! What an awesome day! Have a blast everyone ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoelPaine @Ice_Spike I'm so sorry about your neighbor!  Ouchie!!!  Can't imagine those temps...or the ice😳  I won'… https://t.co/LxNBw8yCQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndurham32 @AlexGSoderstrom @Myan_Patel @whitemarshth But did she get booed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The gorgeous Julie. #campPatrick @ Papago Golf Course https://t.co/FKyKpSKB5Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs Pelosi, what a disappointment you turned out to be. Omar HATES Jewish and white people and doess not belong in  Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gailcarriger Read the article, wish our teachers did more linked projects like this when I was in school. This is amazing]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to share that I’m managing @yanquiloca’s campaign for St. Anthony-New Brighton School Board! Thanks for… https://t.co/IsEAfd3RpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lola's Trailer Park in Fort Worth, TX, US, TX https://t.co/r01CdFIAxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasHeaney6 @DineshDSouza @TheTattooedProf Your ugly snobbishness, Mr. DSousa, sadly reveals your true (lack of)… https://t.co/h9zchlj1P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Police Beat Up 19Yr Old #Black Girl In Mistaken Identity Case Of Course They Claim She Attacked Them I Wonder How… https://t.co/xcF2CBapJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexisxarce I mean I still suck at managing my money lmao it’s all gone by the end of the week 😭😂🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to announce a new chapter ... first day on the @WeAreCisco team. Badge official. 💁🏻‍♀️ #WeAreCisco https://t.co/TMBpn60htG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts Jaysus I hope it made him sterile. If you’re too stupid to flick the thumb safety, you don’t deserve to breed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! We are always learning about influential and inspirational women around us and tha… https://t.co/1RMt5lGxVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Geeeeeezz.... I don’t know what’s worse, looking at your phone all the time on a lunch date. Or your bible. Or both...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@draywharton @Amy_Siskind @bulldoghill The REPUBLICANS have swept it under their rugs, but that's ok because "WHAT'… https://t.co/F9Dcz9nbX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[if it werent' for funniness . . .  LOVE with child's footprints....great gift idea for Mother's Day or Father's Day… https://t.co/7b040rgP6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @amyklobuchar Well, Davis, it was gross. And hinted at unhingedness. We already know Trump is both of those things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassynae28 @ThePeriGirls @RealtyGoddess @JsScope @blakeshuskermom @NexJuice @blaine_48 @AllanJMac288… https://t.co/0ijOLq6Qm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t keep dancing with the devil and wondering why you are still in hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shall we take a gander at @Bigticket_sc’s line? https://t.co/hP6aNM0jof]]></document><document><![CDATA[While you are in Vietnam @realDonaldTrump your “fixer” @MichaelCohen212 is writing American history. You are a disg… https://t.co/vPRZWTUwpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomingoOsorio15 Te faltó la más importante. "Y ahora tengo para ahorrar" . Abra su cuenta mañana mismo, y se acord… https://t.co/Ff3KWCI18f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preston Hollow Open House Today @ 4300 Park Lane, Dallas TX 75220! 2-4 pm https://t.co/x6vTeBsU4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt STELLA rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from Chestnut #DogMeat #Farm and the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea  A qu… https://t.co/WnyqCfcPxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to start the annual #CMUPitt forum at 4130 Posvar Hall. All are welcome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[7thgradeseason @Morgantay11 @StephenCurry30 #11 @girlsbasketball #fortheloveofthegame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejonas The Jonas girls are awesome too! When you tour please come to Nashville &amp; bring @rcschwartzman… https://t.co/p5lLgeaXsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blackdotmandy @mackpoppa_ She would’ve got her ass beat on her wedding day]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best shoot @redbulletin ! Thank you. Let’s do another adventure?? Take a look behind-the-scenes at our cover sh… https://t.co/qyixRPwhQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xx_kiarra literally i found like maybe like 3 dewy/glowy foundations. the rest were bb creams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchotzHM Very clever ... actually, I celebrated at my home sweet home by allowing my head to find my pillow. 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD NIGHT All PATRIOTS, GOD BLESS ALL OF YOU.!! From, VIRGIINIA L ROSS 😹😂👆💕💓💜💥👒🐶🐈🌹🌹🌞🌝⛄❄🌈 https://t.co/xBSpoNHVXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at BAYADA? We're hiring in #StateCollege, PA! Click for details: https://t.co/jC7YSDs7op #Clerical]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkline56 @rosered2020 @hoppinmama5 @trumpshappygirl @GeanineC @Jetsta812 @WandaWomanHere @Thom_Thom9 @mary_patriot… https://t.co/fJDCjfF5Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @MEDIATIONS99 @seanhannity This is where Dibls should direct his attention she is the Soros poster child of the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is flat out gut wrenching! These are INNOCENT life's being massacred!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 36 of Stay in Touch is up https://t.co/ZilYXBoCk5 Slam! The image is by… https://t.co/Khtno6y2Tl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now playing on Starfire's Country Music w/Trisha at Night Wave Radio (https://t.co/OI5xIMNO2M) @nightwaveradio1 Tri… https://t.co/gW5N5oP7iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity is good for the soul. FREE Editing Checklist for Young Writers ~ C for Capital Letters ~ U for Understand… https://t.co/OECUpZgm6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUCH a good article. And very much along the lines of what I work to teach through Reframe It! services .... 💥💥💥… https://t.co/lIlnn76MzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PASUSA65 @ECHOtheCALL @SoWoke2018 Unwanted touching? Teacher has no legal right to call this boy out,and embarrass… https://t.co/JG56ZgS8yU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its really hard for me to ge tour of bed in the morning, but also really hard for me to sleep at night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A stranger (5 mutual friends) adds me on Facebook, then messages me asking if I will post a promotional post on my… https://t.co/ee63kJPSSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[DUI? Suspended license? No License? Multiple tickets? SR22? NO PROBLEM!! Call today (951)657-3000 #sr22 #Dui… https://t.co/bhwQhZmCqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to chuckle. #mirth #tee-hee #smile #amusing https://t.co/GkARBjK2Iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebeccaballhaus @GStephanopoulos But who cares what Nadler thinks.. he is another #TDS sufferer wearing 24k gold t… https://t.co/LYUrLBTVIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bobby_Dunlap @abnormalmarisa @mtrench So jealous, wish I wasn’t already seeing Casey that night 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You check that bitch or I check that bitch and you don’t want me to check her ass.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ireland0828 @pannlewis44 @joylynbest @birdieglad @graceslick77 @khwalz @LoordyMarie @ChkUOut @GivensLois… https://t.co/TR90dV3lmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who qualifies and how do NYorkers apply for affordable housing like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The condition of contention is inseparable from the employer/employee relation.  Every employer would receive more… https://t.co/6f9NQNkx98]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's their future and their planet.  I'm ashamed to admit it, but I know I'll be leaving the planet to them in a mu… https://t.co/GLeq1aPLVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brand new terminal, but no permanent #SouthWest boarding numbers?! Interesting... (@ Terminal B Gates 40-59 in New… https://t.co/KCoaZ8DWni]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @iGiveYouMoore @nerdette @taynadua @AngelaCYang 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 amazing panel. More of this next year please @sxsw… https://t.co/2xieXjiSvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#booksfortrade #arcsfortrade DISO ADSOM/Vicious arcs. https://t.co/8vxoHgRoUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Planning a real quick trip to Asheville. I have New Belgium and Burial on my list. What's a good third option? #CraftBeer #Asheville]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HartwellTonya @TexasTechSB @jess_hartwell9 But girl it sure was hard!!! 🥶🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine Day far away from my half but with great people @Think2019 #ibm #arrowecs #AmericanDream https://t.co/uw8tHUMUvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using their majority in the House, Democrats are intending to go beyond the efforts of special counsel Robert Muell… https://t.co/x3Aj0rdnZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoopalong61 My husband and I had to pay an extra $3000 in taxes this year. No increase in income. Fortunately, we… https://t.co/Rqo3FjD7tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saddee2 @YandR_CBS @joshgriffith59 @anthonymorina #YR #FreeLilyAshby #LaneArmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 69 topic on @breakfastclubam is crazy, all these boys saying they won’t snitch lying like a mf 47 Yearrrrrrrss… https://t.co/rNtRZos8Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 Things You Should Not Say to Your Teenage Daughter  https://t.co/MB0s72bC6e  From Discover on Google]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up with 101 temp again. This is so weird. I am not sick at all except a fever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rulo_atorres @MexicoSocial_ Ya le quitaron presupuesto para muchas investigaciones]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened... (my sons are 6 and 3!) #lifeinthearts #theworldisastage #parenthood https://t.co/PQoGvLMwAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of bruises my body endured from this weekend... never again lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SineSavard Un autre boss qui met pas ces culottes,encore la fautes aux employés Luisa Longo, présidente des Intermarchés Lagoria]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelsdear Also tell the one that he is a natural blonde, that one day he is going to be somebody, and the bad thin… https://t.co/vCdy26nW1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally convinced my mom to get out them hospital waiting room chairs and to come home and get some sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyft offers free rides to Black Historical Society in wake of Senate refusing to honor Kaepernick… https://t.co/OxQOK0nkm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shiroiusagi_ Ohh that’s for sharing that! I didn’t know you could earn cookies with the app, although I would’ve a… https://t.co/yhcmvi4pvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[An utter sobering moment of the insanity we live in. Stephen Colbert runs through a list of absolutely bonkers thin… https://t.co/K4kzPQJjTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women’s Day with my @DellEMC colleagues! #balanceforbetter #iwork4dell https://t.co/5wLcV7ROMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real are you kidding this people need to step out of what they’re doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like Headshot Day at the office to make you feel your very best about yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a wonderful morning with @mackphillips ❤ Loved getting to know  her! #sonoranliving #sedonafilmfestival #abc15… https://t.co/k2C7qefHqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRJOHNSONAUTHOR @EarthandClouds @EarthandClouds2 Thank you, John! 😊☀️✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tart_manchester I think he can beat Trump. And he has led a life of service to our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick trip home to @TheOttawaValley for #InternationalWomensDay  My mom's birthday is Mar. 21 (and mine's Mar. 24… https://t.co/Mftx7Z3Cg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼🥁🎺CONGRATULATIONS Tiger Pride Band!!! Great Job!! We are Proud of you!!! 🎸🎹🎷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmilieTaman Yes intended as deflection from the issue in front of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been really disappointed with the weed in the H lately like I miss SA so much now 😞😞 its not the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Just live your life, doing important things for those of us who cannot. You are a special person. Never marry… https://t.co/PbdZ3KylKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattYurgelun @letswinpc Also helpful to examine family history as a whole- pancreatic cancer might be part of larg… https://t.co/jkiv3IfvMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defend the Titan Staff dominance, 6-3 record! 🏀🏀🏀 @lswcoachwells @teachHumphreys @mrthistory @mshortino13 @GradLsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[. . . critics, as if they were personally discovering fire, wrote of Hugo that "Scorsese has made a film about film… https://t.co/dhxvNZ7Uyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Using children for any political agenda, even ones I agree with, leaves a bad taste in my mouth. I’m… https://t.co/9ThEDWm55M]]></document></documents></author>