<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[El problema es de las comisiones mediadoras que le siguen el juego  a la dictadura. Estos no son más que unos títer… https://t.co/QkRG03oe4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somanyshrimp @1ofakindT @NateG1520 @ech0astral @toooooort https://t.co/wedmL1W3xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atri_93 54% of the assumed drivers to these consumption trends are trash 🤾‍♂️🗑.  Big implication is these market l… https://t.co/vAcLzVEdx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Collier banks in a floater and Grandview leads 6-4 with 3:38 in the first   Bobcats on a 6-0 run]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to @wwe ring announcer @ItsJoseann #HappyBirthdayJoJo @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/359Mlxollm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinsonjoel124 @NRA @RepDougCollins They were promised freedom for fighting but received Nothing in most cases.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to commission @USSTulsa! The ceremony is underway in San Fransisco, head over to @KJRH2HD on Facebook to… https://t.co/3JYh0CVuGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will go down as one of my favorite #SJSharks memories of all time.   https://t.co/CXO1c6y5Pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresidentTrump_ Is Becoming Communist! This µjust be Stopped! My President!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DieHigh633 @ManUtd This reminds of the time I bought a Tony Tchani Crew jersey from China and it was a Ghana Jersey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late Morning Walk. Before bed. @ Cornerstone Park https://t.co/HMiNsiF34Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo I did a thing from back home #CentralAmericanTwitter #FernandoLlort 🇸🇻 https://t.co/XDXfMZm1AU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #valentines ! Treat someone to this delicious Mediterranean spread! 😀 I don't normally eat much meat, so I ha… https://t.co/Q7A3aN6vUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good back and forth game with lots of intensity and was even treated to extra hockey with overtime and a shootout w… https://t.co/CipwftJrEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corine Rodriguez crossed 20K. Time 02:32:01, pace 14:32 min/mile, est. finish 12:24 pm https://t.co/ASN8DeN88i #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ERyan74090140 @DamienL @DanCarrier11 @washingtonpost Socialism is not an economic system. It is a social system. T… https://t.co/t6NG6xbo4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers to @Kirill_CoreBTS on six great years at @CoreBTS !   Proud to have you as a friend and teammate! #1Core https://t.co/BeUxyL3pXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strategygurl @axios He doesn’t believe in many of their policies yet he votes with them 99% of the time? Seems lik… https://t.co/McONrny3Ng]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dustin Johnson DTL Driver @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/3TjUUd6R7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando vives que si se puede cruzar en paso cebra sin miedo a que te atropellen, utilizar las direccionales y girar… https://t.co/Fpmcfjy23N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining Howe, Richard, and the other greats on God’s lineup. Thx for the memories and gifts to this great 🏒 game. R… https://t.co/OpGwiEIHnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/Z7JbvTi5tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than 15 minutes until the start of South Webster and Eastern Brown! First of three Division III Sectional Fina… https://t.co/fsSmlh29sk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your listeners can do their own research on this @brianwiqo 1) do a search on highest and lowest paying college deg… https://t.co/qBv0WBcUV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyantist d3 by a mile. I was prepared to say something like "aren't the diagonals on this graph functionally ident… https://t.co/SCOMdZktgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN With constant push back and naysaying in the press and 7 rate hikes.,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @MMwiley204 Ask him why the rich people from Canada come here for medical care. They don’t have to st… https://t.co/Ln79eN6M2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevolivee @zzari_ Yeah that heavy shit will buss ya head and have ya gut poking 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHeiman Let's see how many arm injuries this mound change contributes to. Very bad idea. Think there will be a few walks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @OutOfRegister @RealTT2020 @McguireScotty @cindy_nurse @TWITMO_INMATE @JETH0MASCUOUS @ImabitcSumtimes… https://t.co/piEoXScgWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special thanks to @Google for the Childish intro. #PureMagic https://t.co/oQ2obpiw6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of you, your teammates, and your coaches, @cbecker_32  Have a blast on Championship Saturday! https://t.co/s6bjUGR7Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[College basketball just can’t get out of its own way with this. These rules are absurd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snickers flavored coffee creamer by @Coffeemate is a game changer. Enhance your mornings. Cheers! ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s it like to not have a job? Asking for me cause that must be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Calling people who own guns zealots doesn’t help. This coming from a progressive Combat Marine Veter… https://t.co/VzrS3Y0eGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC if you believe in God, you know he doesn’t sleep right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday: Kids eat free and get half price tequila shots   #Vegas https://t.co/zyi7xrmSC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast at @FriezeArtFair LA on the @ParamountPics lot! #FriezeArtFair https://t.co/2lNrQzih7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eternal Return... - Song: We - Mac Miller Feat. CeeLo Green @ Whitby, Ontario https://t.co/5DaE7f24UM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Waste your $10/hr gas money just to see President Trump!?!🤷🏻‍♂️🤔🤔 Brain, I think you… https://t.co/ZbOv2VlT77]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youfit @dianaaaa_c Tweet how long you’ve been looking into it and how Channel 8 is waiting in the wings to descend… https://t.co/Vk11AD1Xjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I was speaking to the man who had just … won the election for the presidency and who might have done so with the a… https://t.co/a2ubXz2Zm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monteagle Mountain has faster Verizon LTE than my Comcast at home. 🆒 https://t.co/bUqOkUWgY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up in the 80s, I get it. But, an #Olympic sport, #breakdancing is not!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had that Kaitlin Bennett gun girl blocked for more than a year but now that she’s known as the girl who shit h… https://t.co/LzHbYGYytx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn't a fan of his but I did like most of his music. 👀 CHILE ME TOO! 😂 #LeavingNeverland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ken_republican @PatrioticCindy @hirschA8720 @SenGillibrand @FoxNews Where in the Bible does it say is alright to kill babies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@0123trump @markscocco @NikkiHaley Russia stole documents from Dem HQ.   Roger Stone leaked them to Wikileaks and l… https://t.co/f3IW410m8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:45.9°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pelosi is seeking legislation which will force the President and VP to release their tax returns.  So will Pelosi,… https://t.co/ctRKWNXVLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a weak man who picks on strong women So you would feel right at home with the Republicans in office So live the… https://t.co/IHI1htsqiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried Corn Nuts as a new snack - something different for a change.   ⭐️⭐️ | Flavor is there, but lacking. Too crunc… https://t.co/iyuDuV1W4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alabama | Disabled Alabama veteran's body found in trash bags https://t.co/8BCliNU5WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeff07557443 happy Valentines ❤️and thanks for the fallow!! https://t.co/vm7pfrsudA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comic book friends and fellow comic book podcasters! Doing some research. What are the most common questions you've… https://t.co/TiqLJcjHrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s pretty cool that my brother thought I was good enough at this stuff to ask for help. https://t.co/xu6c8xaPjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s week 8, should I tell my professor that he’s been pronouncing my name wrong all along or just leave it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudraMayPhoto The Eevee nest was a good idea 😊✨ https://t.co/csAHcCJeLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Americans should listen to Angela Merkel about the U.S. heading down a dark path: To the editor: Columnist Doyle Mc… https://t.co/YYM8Nbgkbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever thankful for these people. @ Niagara College Canada https://t.co/MEo0HaFzkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening day #LAFC, and our view for the entire season. https://t.co/ubyFiVaPjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been up since 5:30 and haven’t been able to fall back asleep, should I wake bae up cause I’m bored lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSoulbrother I, for one, NEVER listen to the show. I just love following SBK clueless rants on twitter. The mind… https://t.co/MVAhmhcqdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeCarlisTerry @DaleJr My wife (a former Redskinette) drove a milk truck looong ago and delivered to Sonny!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#seaturtle awareness education #seaturtletrackers #newsmyrnabeach #florida #volusiacounty @ New Smyrna Beach, Flori… https://t.co/TRPqncRXvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally,                                                     I don’t need my eyes to see]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introducing E. Patrick Johnson earlier, @salamishah explainsd how Audre Lorde’s work inspired this year’s #MTW19, “… https://t.co/9S1HsL6mKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregLogan1 Amen!  Worst case they are adding picks 17, 27 and 32 at this point AND Muuuuusa to the roster next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Muslim? An illegal alien? Came in with the caravan? we need a wall around all our borders!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blueneck600 @MeltdownWRIF @Jason_hartless His Dad is a friend of mine, this was in '17 at the 1st Wings game in Si… https://t.co/wekJd7dxjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Seahawks Russell Wilson to the #GiantsChat proves a slow news day https://t.co/XqNbqAIVQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mviser They STILL think Russians did it! 😂  Yet they all conspired with the FBI to Spy On Trump. #SpyGate]]></document><document><![CDATA[So......what exactly is wrong with Socialism? Seems to work for lots of countries. Do most Americans even understan… https://t.co/ja8JyIc9gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowie doesn't gets enough credit as one of the progenitors of heavy metal.  Lots of the album "The Man Who Sold the… https://t.co/FI6B0SbzSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @netflix,  Please give us #WynonnaEarp Season 3!  Pass it on! (Copy + paste + quote RT. Don’t just RT.)… https://t.co/XR0kKrvHFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maniscalco_carl It was a stretch ;-). Nick Woodman actually credits UCSD as the birth place of the GoPro.  Back wh… https://t.co/e8nHFCQiqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[People watch the first 4 episodes of game of thrones and call it trash :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for everything you have done over the past 3 years for the Cleveland browns and their fans @darthBoCa 🏈🏈… https://t.co/Z4KnOv6lKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tornadosis06 @okaatta Two all time great directors who had a penchant for filming leading ladies in beautifully unconventional ways]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can break down @Broncos fans into 2 groups after the #Flacco trade:  Those that realize the ship is sinking and… https://t.co/VqLO7gE8rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladder Cap #commercial #realestate #finance co. $LADR Makes 52-Week High Feb 21 @equitiesinc wish we could claim re… https://t.co/k7liuZaBdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwyaneWade FEBRUARY 27th back-to-back years with Game Winning shots. #OneLastDance  #HeatCulture https://t.co/1WPi9pMyem]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 Dance Tape Out Now !!!!! @amarucloud Stop playing with them !!! https://t.co/O92ZlaIugi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukehorseman getting some work in before the start of the spring season! @ Evolution Athletics https://t.co/AL9WURVZKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thankyou  Mr.President for all you do!! Today you r making history in Vietnam, and the left is doi… https://t.co/y5aTO761aX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX @IlhanMN Remember when you signed this pledge for civility. We all expected more from you, Dan. We s… https://t.co/ttbGjA4t4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good stop time of head where you can look at the time why you here depends upon a time you a bear]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitting with world famous choreographer Eddie Torres and his Mambo Kings Orchestra! (@ The Copacabana in New York,… https://t.co/gV22FN7Y1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CBellRacing is hot in Hot-Lanta as my boy @NoahGragson finishes in the Top 10. Time for the Wild West Truck Race… https://t.co/B1roHlAPrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_Bert32 i think they’re a good team, but even with him there are teams i like better just bc of the leadership th… https://t.co/eo1Qafpc2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hughes2Society Defiant One's was like a manual for me while i wrote/recorded my most recent record. Dr Dre, Tupac,… https://t.co/gXw2t6F63N]]></document><document><![CDATA[2K19 AGAINST TRASH TALKER CHUCK , (HE SAID IM TRASH) https://t.co/cvuVjYDN1f via @YouTube.   WHO NEXT 💯💯💯❗️👀🤫… https://t.co/M6MWwF4kMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegreatgazzi No goof. Talking about the prospects we’ve been growing for years. Cease, moncada, Robert, Collins,… https://t.co/8GWcQ7Op4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Odio a todos los que andan de peda el día de hoy porque yo estoy en mi casa estudiando para mi examen del lunes de… https://t.co/0wfXGoVEBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @serg208marti I MISS YOU!! They say things get easier with time but not this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLRaider @pillagingpod @AB84 https://t.co/lh0oKrcq9P 🍻make sure you subscribe :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How will L.A. replace three gas plants that Mayor Eric Garcetti plans to shut down?: Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcett… https://t.co/pb6XD5Zqhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RGoltsch @Marriott @TownePlace FWIW, I called the hotel numerous times to get the front desk to answer. They didn’… https://t.co/AeSrXNCEbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2014FloridaTOY OMG....is it okay that I’m totally geeking out from getting a shoutout from you?! Thank you so much… https://t.co/nB2udAmSBq]]></document></documents></author>