<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[An enormous part of my heart and my life.... Lourdes. Looking forward to this film. #Lourdes #lourdeslefilm… https://t.co/jtPvMD67ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Coach Vogt, Jess, Marina &amp; Emily!!! Way to represent the program! 🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teach your daughters less about fitting into glass slippers and more about shattering glass ceilings 💗💆🏼‍♀️💆🏻‍♀️… https://t.co/ob92gF9W6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pipers multi sport &amp; 1st yr Piper wrestler LeJames White is going to state!!! Congrats to you and let’s get that 3rd place medal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's wrong with encouraging the artistic side of children?  I remember everything I learned in art, music, and gy… https://t.co/B6iFoCidAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to have so many brilliant and dedicated #NCISD educators learning writing strategies with us this morning!… https://t.co/iVvgaL2mLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lowegrls @imwtclothing @AidenHatfield @MindCharity It’s used to be called Irvine meadows  in so cal. The weenies roast w Kevin n bean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seize your moments of happiness! IDLC Turn your phone off for an entire day. https://t.co/vbU0xBsVoa via @valuescom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump proposes $845 billion Medicare cut.  Trump proposes $845 billion Medicare cut.  Trump proposes $845 billion M… https://t.co/CfJGSPu7ZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's from an article she wrote for the paper. Isn't that so beautiful?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenTracy13 @brianstelter @CNN You want to have an intelligent conversation?  Do I need to quote and post the cou… https://t.co/aWW6RudRIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt CONOR saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea  CONOR currently is fostered in… https://t.co/qJiFdqLQVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewjdowd what word accurately describes what the GOP calls "socialism" in America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestleMania @WWE @BeckyLynchWWE @MsCharlotteWWE @RondaRousey Like we didn't know that was coming after @VinceMcMahon suspended Becky.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowshoe-ing... or trying to (@ Beaver Lake in Montréal, QC w/ @joemasilotti) https://t.co/aoNVwqhXX1 https://t.co/eiaCRGSHPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberrrrs Ya shit fuckkkin hurts lol my skin became so raw i was like omggg haha]]></document><document><![CDATA['I think the thing to do is enjoy the ride while you're on it' - Johnny Depp   Disclaimer :: Not my car 😂  #winter… https://t.co/wvXGXGwu1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[White makes right, didn't you know? Why aren't the police confiscating that arsenal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No firearms allowed?! Excuse me, not according to the First Amendment.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fries I just had at this @FiveGuys were the best I've had anywhere in months. Only wish they had a veggie burger in… https://t.co/iIhKXteykE]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re at University Park early vote site!  #jaxpol #ilovejax @ University Park Branch Public Library https://t.co/Yt35kzcdEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotQuiteLindsay Thank you. Yeah it was the first one I was prescribed when I was diagnosed. It ruined my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t fuck with me only when you wanna fuck with me . It’s either here or you gone, no in between 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s her trade in stock. She’ll be on any platform that gives her visibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I’m still in shock that freaking @DanAndShay walked in to my store last night 🤩😍😭🥰 like holy shit they’re 1 of… https://t.co/mMJKJYOUoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse @RusevBUL @WWEAleister What is the matter Rusev?  Let the new kid beat you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supplies are purchased! This will be my 3rd mural using @behrpaint !! Let the #painting begin!! #MuralProject… https://t.co/YdEG0VAe6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really cool absolutely and completely accidental...ART. Found / created by Priscilla Batzell Expressionist Art Stud… https://t.co/mDpisIjJ2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[february ends next week &amp; it feels like we just started this month wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby like... wtf i fucking miss you @nolifeari I’m proud of you everyday! Sending positive love and happiness your way beloved. 💓💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped by to say Hi👋🏻 #StPatricksDayParade2019🍀 #TheMoores💙 #OneWorkingOneNot🤷🏻‍♀️ https://t.co/Ji30wRP9ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[$VYST may have quick chance in am to nab sone .13s.  We shd ..have ended near .16 w all the eod huge buys. 147 to m… https://t.co/a6Vnal0GuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have to go out either! It IS beautiful. Our cat is befuddled. What does your doggie think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RAW I guess they want us to forget Eddie Guerrero beat Brock for the WWE Championship]]></document><document><![CDATA[this chick said “that hick ass down syndrome baby you’re about to have” HAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very sad to hear about the passing of Luke Perry.  I have many memories of my brother, sister and I watching our… https://t.co/RBoPNH6ftj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with DC's Finest! FBI National Academy Session #275 @DPDMoore @ChiefHallDPD @DallasPD https://t.co/NLKvea6ChK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe @desusnice and @THEKIDMERO did read my book!  They just announced that the @BodegaBoys are endorsing… https://t.co/14FsOjTtE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God we are not a part of England and the men who sacrificed their lives to make it happen.  Both sides are wr… https://t.co/rnd1ePE7mf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much for your help in hour products #mzdivanailz #bhcosmetics I could have done all by self. @ Windsor, O… https://t.co/MutNl6ngse]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/cR0dBijca8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praying hubbys car doesn't cost too much.  It's at the shop, for inspection and a repair.  Going to try for a cheap… https://t.co/J2ky48hUO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went cyber, dyed my hair and got my cartilage pierced, all in the first three months of 2019. what is happening a… https://t.co/WNZYJJCPvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this and love our #ConnectedDC video! Thanks to @tricomb2b for having the vision to do something so cool that… https://t.co/d6AXnX1Cdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I say thriving, look, I'm a proud mother I know but in recent weeks:  - my non-speaking son, I get kids I don'… https://t.co/CnxyMuFoLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattdamon_ Satellite Address where High Ups found Girl in what became The Tent of MyBedroom beingTortured byIndivi… https://t.co/n0Abey5Niv]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPD dispatch tells me this crash involves 3 cars and the driver of one car has been transported to Community East.… https://t.co/2JQTVjtPAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary Ann Lisanti calls black people in district "n*****"s. Where's the protest?? Where's the media? I didn't hear a… https://t.co/hhsq5H5gPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[my butthole after eating 3 bags of takis, a mangoneada, &amp; 2 elotes https://t.co/52JyjkdQEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LM_TDTSS @NISDConnally @MichaelaHarlow5 @bearden_julie @mrscassiefern Hope you saved me one!! I'll be there tomorrow! 😬🙃🤪❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[gotta lottaa luv for tha homies🖤 @ Illinois State University https://t.co/KkRrZTrqnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickHamrock @HeyRatty Welcome to 2002 everyone https://t.co/gX2NBbQwf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaaweather Can’t wait to get back to DFW today! Been visiting Chicago! How do they live here!? Too cold for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@822Tribe @PrincipalTribe Wow!  Thanks!!  Still at work - hoping not to be late to the chat again this week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manager is rude and has no customer service.  Talking about a customer who has a guest ion with other employees #no… https://t.co/8EVBKToobF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NICOLESKYES any updates on Kali. Is he doing better or has the vet said anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to all of the learning!  Thanks for being here @pernilleripp]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 3 course meal I’m having is making me feel like a Queen rn no lieee LOL never experienced this before. I love… https://t.co/is1eLiKYt3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wheeler’s EPA Keeps Brain-Damaging Chlorpyrifos In Food, for now... https://t.co/7d3XXdvWzA via @earthjustice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdySmol @Aztecauno @Azteca @anettemicheltv Es lo que pasa cuando baratean, pero las 'talentos' también podrían ten… https://t.co/dlZ1QgXJQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASKING FOR A FRIEND: Where can I get fresh Irish soda bread in CT?? 🍞Help a sister out ☺️ https://t.co/6a52ptQHqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ciaracalvert22 @SwordMya @_Maddie_Barr if i lost an argument to underclassmen at your age i’d be embarrassed for weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[* Injecting toxins is no different than ingesting toxins. * Because one vaccine is safe, two, four, eight vaccines… https://t.co/SvxwzgPUx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toppel_ELD @SIOPModel @Powells @carlota_holder @jessbell79 @CBTennyson @emilyfranESL @Jechev @AllyteacherELLs Love that place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Valac666 @JeannaMarie32 @JaneColes2 @SharonG40210896 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @jeanine_new @Mary60053440… https://t.co/Ss66wI91XG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterPendley @conwaychitty I thought about that right after I tweeted it. It’s ok I drowned my sorrows last night… https://t.co/HWbn9DVxaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou to all who care enough about #humanity , about #freedom , about #Venezuela #FueraMaduro #EnoughIsEnough… https://t.co/YMUEvauq2E]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many cans of sparkling water does it take before you have a problem?.... Asking for a friend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkCallMeAL It is so depressing that we have so many uneducated people in this country who are being led around by… https://t.co/b3dnSGh9HG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello #MarchMadness!  What a game! Proud of our athletes, coaches, student section, and fans!  #BigRedNation  Next… https://t.co/pQ7A2aeHy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn3 Saluki softball. Appreciate the commentating- but it would be nice for you to keep updated with lineup changes for butler as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brothersosborne I have more than 1. It’s a bit creepy https://t.co/UFZvzfII1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you were ´pro’life´you´d be expanding Medicaid and saving thousands of lives in Missouri every year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Guide For The Top 10 Skincare Products For Your Skin | SKINN Cosmetics https://t.co/giRXp5Bdbz via @HSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of a personal pronoun that shows possession. Which one are you thinking of now? https://t.co/XdTrcDH71Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amarillo_isdCTE @AmarilloISD  we have amazing things happening! Our students our college career military ready. We… https://t.co/Ag0lUDjrUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@its_mirielle It definitely doesn’t make what he did ok. What I’m saying is is if he’s apologized and they’ve gone… https://t.co/JHr8qCcEgw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepStateExpose Oh really? The good Lord doesn’t think so. 🇺🇸🇮🇱🙏⭐️⭐️⭐️ #WWG1WGAWORLDWIDE God bless our President D… https://t.co/gPJeyn2863]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miloramone @ThatEricAlper I don't think it got the credit it deserved 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s really cold here in Kansas City. 4° rn feels like -8°. I got the heat on 75° in my hotel room, I’m under the c… https://t.co/BiqOlZny07]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning to you beautiful, energetic, badass ladies  💕🐾 Don’t let perfect get in the way of progress today 🙌🏼 S… https://t.co/En3GRaJINy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am about the @HaloTopCreamery and #TheBachelor crossover. But I only like the Nick part because he’s making fun o… https://t.co/RuagwziMur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrslevin11 I love that you wrote this! I had the same feelings this morning! The snow was beautiful but I wasn’t i… https://t.co/8nLMZ6J4ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaubtu Hi, there’s a big error on one of @Slate ‘s articles. No one has corrected it yet so I figured I’d try to… https://t.co/gRKXsIx9Cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is my honor student, please help her to get her goal! #gofundme #donate Global Leadership Adventures https://t.co/PA1srasdaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Akuma_no_Kanton @roccozilla @BernieSanders Here you go,  Trump accomplishments: 1 criminal justice reform 2 policy… https://t.co/fsi0BuIkC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HDGregC @mespo2013 @ajsmama118 @1258ASDS @DebazzDeb @mike_seifert80 @BelmontePaul Congrats Andrea! 🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I hate when people message you on social media and say “call me” , the time you took to do all that you could’ve actually called me🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDeanCain @HatchingChange @ComConLiverpool You two were always my favorites. Good too see you together again even if it is for Comic-Con]]></document><document><![CDATA[FRIENDS themed wedding shower cake for today. I love the couch, but I think my favorite part is the lobster!… https://t.co/2FbtOguCoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay, since it's March 8th, my goal is to put away all my winter decor and replace with spring decor. Maybe this wi… https://t.co/ci2uPOV40s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJ_2_FL @mollyday15 @realDonaldTrump The hard truth is Democrats are trying to destroy Americans...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids going from dislike to love math... all because of a great teacher-facilitator. Thanks Cicely for making a diff… https://t.co/WkQxVZh4yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The perfect product for you @twitterlessSaraPaclat #glutendetection @johndchisholm https://t.co/XC9JsJJmWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me just completely bored with your negative shit, realizing you hold grudges like it's life support and you're dyin… https://t.co/6aymKbLUhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to do this for me. I need to constantly remind myself that prioritizing my well being is not selfish, but a part of growth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He would not let me catch my breath but would overwhelm me with misery. https://t.co/qml4TVEPm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump He's trying to run this country! He hasn't done anything wrong! You guys are just… https://t.co/tsUDaGBAzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda crazy how everyone is talking about AB?? His name is Mr. Big Chest now please respect that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Jacey Hammond (Hammy) @jacehammy2 for retweeting my poem! Happy day!💕💚💜🌻 https://t.co/QNKRcjirzV]]></document></documents></author>