<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Check out our #listing in #Avalon #NJ  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/OTBepf9zXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this talk about taking K Murray #1 is BS. I bet the AZ @AZCardinals trade out of 1 and get picks. Rosen is just… https://t.co/AlwiYwXot5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Jimmy Avila v. 1212 Grant Realty LLC, BASICS, Lorraine Coleman Federal Court Docket No. https://t.co/vgS9uvEJQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost lost it on this kid... lil nigga is the most annoying kid I’ve ever met.. no bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #SWSX and 1:45 am in Austin, TX, and @dens' @SwarmApp hypertrending is telling me that lots of people are at h… https://t.co/7PzuGjCEEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Monte Cristo... Superb... @ The Cheesecake Factory https://t.co/8wqamQf68P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernalJatleen @pam_brundige @american2084 @JCoker13 @lc1_summit @Kewlbearhelloki @RuleChicago @CIAnderson3… https://t.co/6jXttmUQ1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysterysolver3 @RealJamesWoods Don’t come. Problem solved. If they do want to come to our country. Then come the right way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pilar66429233 Pues a ser feliz Pilar , buenos días y feliz miércoles saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@towardfulllife @srissundaram @MDT_Cardiac @EPinnovation Also 3 tines engaged, RV threshold 0.5 V @ 0.24 ms. Not to… https://t.co/6BGSnZeFBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bklynfinest1477 your avi makes me wanna like you! Have a good day fal!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexregala should have been first man. if that movie did literally nothing else great, the audio shit was bonkers across the board]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spookyxbrat I literally slept through the entire presale and STILL got one. Tell me Irish luck isn’t real]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck Trump! Do you feel you are getting somewhat mentally exhausting with all this "trump shit"? Here's a 12 minute… https://t.co/AbwDS2VIe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dxisyleonor @evansatlaw I had time for this fool right quick...  I can feed a troll every now and then... these Ch… https://t.co/cg80CzkmO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always be that true blue Duke fan that will y’all even after a loss. Unlike y’all so called Tar Heel fans th… https://t.co/3KWs2jVBSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Wanderland IPA by @etherealbrewing at @paxtons_grill — https://t.co/S8lpFMyyGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright y’all...I’m done recording my podcast. Time to kick up my feat, have a drink, and watch some @NASCAR! #NASCAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinawinabobina @OC86370976 @KamalaHarris No i been paving with 400 degree asphalt since i was 15 and no there not… https://t.co/QPMsmjkHlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JameelHassan_ @YesItsMe_JP What is the name of the documentary? And when will it be released because I am all abou… https://t.co/Qwq13Lhxyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my wife. 25 years she still loves me. She wrote me a poem that only love could dictate. She never ceases to amaze me. I love her so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JesusChrist #Jesus #Christ #worship #praise #praiseandworship #HisAnointedCC #HACC #together #WaldorfMD #church… https://t.co/fhCEpPL5Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @AOC Cortez is likely a racist. People who call others racist without overwhelming evidence are likel… https://t.co/R3HH5CCq2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawsonElia @MorganCWallen Y’all better do one of these for me https://t.co/xpPOldsjxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about going back on the Gold Standard? Then tell our China Friends, sorry that system is Bankrupt. Does not Isr… https://t.co/ZLeok89MOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doobox Nice, simple website, too. Effectively does the job it needs to. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we commit to courage, to truly overcoming whatever stands on the way of what we want, we prove something to ou… https://t.co/Dn8gLUESOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@detnewsRodBeard The Pistons have looked good during this soft part of the schedule.....keep it up in the playoffs that are coming up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely shredding 🥁💥 @ Johnson City, Tennessee https://t.co/s8ohnuXxpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannon0318 @YouTube I listen to the song again ...... great show ....but now I sit with a knife in my left hand ......😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swinging through the end of my weekend, in truly fun concert style. https://t.co/zU3dNyBF4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pappapit1234 @floydbama @realDonaldTrump About red states......ask California &amp; Puerto Rico]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper Now ask what we would like for our dying word to be?  “Yep, I Have Been Waiting For This Moment All o… https://t.co/GG9Ohu5LFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first tweet in a series of tweets on the #StrongDollar thesis (for now anyway, #Reflation, &amp;… https://t.co/1kH12Eh2nZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the face of someone who loves                           ~~raving~~ https://t.co/2QiaNnLbun]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the catfishing going on now, I'm actually insulted nobody has tried to be me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddschnitt @DonaldJTrumpJr Unlike you Don, the cat won’t be Indicted soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shmcminn @bridgetbhc @DonaldJTrumpJr She didn't include that phrase for those people who understand how a Glock works.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@col1015 Wait yeah, that’s what I have. I can’t take a pic though lol it’s an 8 and red]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I'm assuming some angry white man just ran over all the trash cans and hit a car driving wrecklessly in Cambridg… https://t.co/iUJ2Puqeef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tbaytransit, the 2 crosstown just skipped the weekend loop for stops 1484 AND 1773? WTF? #ThunderBay #Service]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we deviate from available processes we damage the rule of law. With Trump we are damaging the rule of law by a… https://t.co/bd2xrj6FZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fuckin weak pogba’s 3rd missed pen in the prem this season. Took the hat trick away from lukaku as well. What a game tho sheesh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 February are her lips so inviting Silk hair as short as her fuse She's is damaged, she's been misused🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudeCosta_ @wesrucker247 Sounds like folks I sit in front of at Neyland 👨🏼‍🦳👩🏼‍🦳😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what makes you get out more now? C- I love to give away magnets of my art and stickers with contact information… https://t.co/6wiaZLItUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Independent It’s hard to fathom that ANYONE believed this story from the onset.  It was a polar vortex in Chicago… https://t.co/TfAusgikiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you notice how none of your sycophants asked questions of substance about the allegations? Not… https://t.co/KJ9HCtmZBm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffgerstmann @DanRyckert With your affinity for Super Mario Maker and the sequel coming in June, any chance we ca… https://t.co/sdzT4PjziD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmichaelswx How come this website says Helena has its second coldest and first snowiest February ever?  What site… https://t.co/cJWQkkuGqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[And here I thought today would be a good day. Unfortunately @FantasticPods weekly podcast only lasted for half of m… https://t.co/Z0iCts7lts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@witp_blog @Travel_Couple_ Disneyland is my favorite after only one trip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wearelostkings Lol.  Yeah I’m out on that.  My fave tweet was someone said they watched the doc with their kids in bed.  Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine how we the people who pay taxes feel with this disaster of a presidency......]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is another cold-ass morning. I am camped out directly in front of my tower heater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShesMJacksonBad Um if you recall she's the one that said if she'd knew about or ever caught him she'd hang him from a tree so...🤷🏿‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember my dad being confused when I wouldn't ask to play more on teams where I only filled a niche role, and I… https://t.co/35Q9fUmF96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DuncanMRF @Jcamps30 Picks is the rumor. Would be nice to swing Miller but not likely]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to be involved in my kids education more than just sending them off to school, I wanna know what my kid… https://t.co/z9SYXXIA2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spurs Game with Jamer! #gospursgo @ AT&amp;T Center https://t.co/7sn7u59gpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler Workers owning the means of production is communism. It doesn’t work. Sounds great but always a failu… https://t.co/w4kcTcOilf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A quick one from last night.. Here's the Death Run at Corner Cut in a pretty kickass ride called the Rammerhead.… https://t.co/C8GyGYvLGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helpful philosophy as you stare at the stack of non-fiction books in your office!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to #SXSW ! If you're coming to or interested in our workshop, "Producing Live Performance in #VR," check… https://t.co/qIs0UNUxF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethDavisHoops Really need to keep these clowns off the floor after games!  Somebody is going to do something stup… https://t.co/6TOkG00Fqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Quantico Amtrak/VRE Station in Quantico, VA https://t.co/jL5E7I2EFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cities across the country are looking to start a program @SafeHealthyLou is already using to reduce violent crime i… https://t.co/VJL5fj54aa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero felicitar y agradecer el servicio excelente que me brindo en ZOFEMAT Ayuntamieto Hmo la Sra Juanita Núñez en… https://t.co/HRfAgBfedo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobbyldowling I had the 15" to try and it was nice. Standby time was atrocious, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun in class reignites the passion we have lost the passion for learning in our schools. Loss of passion is a natio… https://t.co/qQUMmrZhHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning My Beautiful America And Wonderful President Trump, God will be by your side and guide you with your t… https://t.co/My6GmnqF9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Apple will be including CanCon in the upcoming Video subscription service based on this job posting   Bu… https://t.co/60b1fTxCeB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great FacultyFocus this morning @AHS_Alabama ! Looking at student data, QuickWrites @AVID4College strategies and th… https://t.co/9D0GgGt7ky]]></document><document><![CDATA[A line from @TheCWSupergirl, said by Alex Danvers about her new Government appointed supervisor: "If she gets any m… https://t.co/9rejghYXaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatEnquirer @TheSun I can't believe you missed this story last year. I'm also reposting this because it's really f… https://t.co/dNJneRa3Wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANeal16 Lol an eye opening realization. Imagine 4 months of that. How long you got?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SiddonsDan @LadyRedWave @realDonaldTrump I know that fat, slob Michael Moore said he'd leave the US. Don't know if… https://t.co/RDJCbgluxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please look at the pictures. They’re “screenshots” with pertinent information   2nd request:   can you combine the… https://t.co/jiWv8RAACS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You and my boy @SticksMcFall6 won't let up on this Kenny! #Rays #BlueJays]]></document><document><![CDATA[A week from now I’ll be in Jamaica. I know you don’t care, but I’ll still let you know every chance I can, because I’ll be in Jamaica....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz You keep proving over and over how unfit you are to be in congress and how unfit you are to be in the HUMAN RACE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been awhile since I've seen the Stones River this high. Seeing it from the top of J Percy Priest dam was wild. https://t.co/XwQ6EnL4zG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh CRAP! Is Linda #SourAssCamelNuts, still alive? Thought she drowned in a tub full of pig blood! @lsarsour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up➡️ Showered ➡️ Got to class late➡️ Learned that a robot can take my job away from me➡️Notes for History ➡️Lu… https://t.co/95u0hH6Hju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yay_yee Stfu            Mind your business, opponent / journey man guys needs the $. He’s there to to fight, get p… https://t.co/6YW4i6zPHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good to have Dr. Lajos Pusztai @muschollings talking about #Immunotherapy, #breastcancer and Charleston history! https://t.co/vk70ISV2ZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust Quotes | Trust Quotes Pictures, Images, Graphics,Glitters, Photos - Page 10 #mirth #chuckle #grin #cute https://t.co/nGWgASoTDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWxNYC @Meteor_Mike @JGodynick @judah47 @NEWeatherWx @BobbiStorm @WeatherEric @_NEweather @LensReality @PaulPiorek… https://t.co/AITxli3GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music always brings me back to reality though. Tonight it was @gjonesbass latest album]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just back from lovely #Norway!  They say there that there is no such thing as bad weather; just bad clothing.  Than… https://t.co/2suUbS9TLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Played whistling Straights and The Links At Spanish Bay today with my son. Want to bet who has a better swing?… https://t.co/IbC5sUdJFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Alleman from #HuntOil on  Real Time Drilling with TIBCO analytics -  live IoT data in Spotfire X to analyze b… https://t.co/CcR8cbWTza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinFrankish @SenecaMedia @SenecaCollege @femwriter @GOtransitBR How so?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xSlyyblue Kudos to your girlfriend! I’m very happy the show makes you happy. It’s incredibly gratifying. Thank you… https://t.co/CeYuwVXsFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your favorite president isn’t one of the Roosevelt’s you’re wrong, and to fuck yourslef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engaged crowd of citizens last at a Form Based Code lecture.  This event was part of the community education in the… https://t.co/6T2g6ZIVDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett Sending you Love, Light And Prayers! ❤️🙏🏾❤️ Oh and kisses too! 💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Did you forget that only a couple of months ago you couldn’t afford an apartment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReutersBiz Eddie Lambert is a Complete FRAUD .. and in my opinion .. a Thief ! .... wouldn’t surprise me if this t… https://t.co/JXAjBXBtP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chloechristoph8 @climer6699 @sjohn691 @MichaelChazell2 @happyandme Good morning sweetie 😊😊😊]]></document></documents></author>