<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day at work was fun because a cute yellow lab named Maple stopped by for a short visit. Maple is one of… https://t.co/6WGlZ5gAr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Dining Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/wFRB0L5gMc]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT Y'ALL!  LEGGO!  Food is bomb, drinks get the job done and the music is unbelievable!   Last week was cray!… https://t.co/pl9KYhH3Gq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orangetheory Fitness Astoria in Astoria, NY https://t.co/kenytgqNKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want pressed juicer so bad. I mean I guess I could get it shipped but who wants to wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be rough. But, I know my dad would do everything he could for me. We’re gonn have a bunch of restl… https://t.co/rXkRarPppT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Alerts: Nancy Pelosi is threatening legal action over YOUR WALL. Let's make a statement. All gifts in the nex… https://t.co/dMFPydppe1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobofinch @MolCZet @feloneouscat @DindiOhh @CloudContact @BevDiane @jeffreyparrisne @blaclmere @funder Ok I’ll be… https://t.co/wgHoJIv6xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm right  (Disclaimer: I don't actually know if I'm right, this interpretation of All Might is based on very sligh… https://t.co/NmBwhxBpaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristalramirezn just had a massive nightmare and now my head’s pounding like mad 😓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @DavidJUrban @KirstenPowers @amandacarpenter @JamalSimmons @TheLeadCNN What a moronic comment.  Really.… https://t.co/UnWOt6NWtJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacetelelive Hello Space Telescope Live, I missed you, where've you been? Prof. Sand needs you to make your very… https://t.co/yQfEat8157]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhc07_ wow she was so sweet and classy. did not put you down AT ALL. and did not judge whatsoever. such an angel 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anybody else have days where they feel more insecure than the others ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had the choice to save a dog or person - I'd save the dog because oops I just didn't want to and people ain't shit so lol 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can’t believe sis said Yara Shahidi had “Eurocentric features” with that nose and those lips. Y’all really say whatever lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Do you think Cleo had blond hair with brown roots?  Asking for Lady Clairol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: “Estoy muy deprimida🙇🏻‍♀️ ya nunca voa salir 😔” Also me: “¿What qué hay un partyson loco? Orita llego en putiza 🏃🏻‍♀️💨”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news. I have a 50 acre farm in my backyard that I don't want turned into a housing subdivision. He grows soyb… https://t.co/cTFZLlOWae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memphisweather1 What was it in 2010? Wasn’t that the last time we had flooding like this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naptime &amp; Pretty Woman. A Saturday with residual sniffles never looked so good from the couch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young men provide an astonishing 52% of all marrow donations. Join Now @  https://www. https://t.co/zYGFwsKr3k… https://t.co/4Nh4TZouza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaykinney What are YOU doing to get ready for tonight’s bachelor? I’m grabbing my passport because I have a feelin… https://t.co/K3Z65cJGOg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indy airport just paged passenger Penfield Jensen. Just in case you need character ideas for your next novel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👉 @laurenperini inspires me with her amazing work ethic and growth mindset. Happy birthday and happy… https://t.co/4LmC10q6kI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still debating whether getting my bf nerf guns for Valentine’s Day was a good idea 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my professor for playing yoga music while we was taking our midterm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSpadine @hawaiibobb @MikiMiyazaki13 @alkhateeb @aboalfof73 @ATheriver @SK8sandhu @srinualme @cc_chicco… https://t.co/elrYGcuYBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ihachey @Polluxe Des millenariaux supportant mal la critique....Ayoye la défense!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yodaquoter @thomaskaine5 @MjaneMarshall Same here! I'm with you. Always have been a lib, getting more liberal as I… https://t.co/8LhxhABShx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The small fragment of U.K. folks that will have a problem, would have a problem with anything this Duchess does tha… https://t.co/gNxDYcVz8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mookyluv3 @ShanRussell72 Well I’m proud to be an American where at least I know were really really really really really really smart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This literally makes me sick / angry how can you treat children like this and make them hate everyday life?¿]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOING TO RT THIS FOR GOODLUCK y este año me dejen ir de viaje con mi novio 🤞🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaveyDaniel Very inspirational boost for editors out there. Like myself I dont have confidence in the edits I mak… https://t.co/xKDpDVrnJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump How cruel and unusual you are. You should have respect for our President Trump th… https://t.co/UsDXLBQw8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to get so offended by things and constantly feel like I have to explain myself. I’m honestly so proud of how… https://t.co/qvBvN3FVMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨The Expansiveness of Life - in all of it’s Forms and Beauty - can feel mind-boggling!✨ . This is one of my favorit… https://t.co/fy6oKsMlXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arbnrngr @ASimplePatriot @RandPaul And if you don't think their criminals within the law then you have been fooled… https://t.co/MOvplSKjHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was for Cassie all the way on the bachelor, but knowing what I know it’s sad she made it this far when other girl… https://t.co/2fLrEiku7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard a group of young girls playing the ‘Penis’ game, is it strange that I wanted to join in? I’ll say it louder because I am an adult]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monica152712 @SouthLoopES @jackielsaenz Beautiful ladies! Way to go! Mother-Daughter Teams 🙌🏻 #THEDISTRICT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iTunes Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% Free in the Link Below 👇   C… https://t.co/lbJy6ddxNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro how in the hell could Travis cheat on @KylieJenner  men don’t know what they take for granted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I grow up I want to be wonder woman because I want to save people My 4 year old daughter on… https://t.co/LMQ5p0HjL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I’ve produced fashion shows , fashion festivals , styled entire events, short films , written and spoken on ma… https://t.co/8rvjJd0UZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GatlinburgTennessee #goodmorning #nofilter #smokeymountains #weekendvacay https://t.co/9aaWcISfIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here listening to Lauren huffing &amp; puffing while gulping water as she eats her carrots. Brings back lots of memories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[wireless headphones dying in the middle of a workout is definitely worse than heartbreak]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve seen @The_Infotainers do this trick at least 40 times. Today was the first time I’ve seen him give away the $2… https://t.co/Yd0lHvP18p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delaneyrozich I’m not optimistic at this point, he’s in so much trouble!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all my great clients! This year has been wonderful so far! #january #realestate #coldwellbankerburnet… https://t.co/Qg9k4kNBwQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeidiTown I think my little guy agrees. He is bonding with his bunny😻 https://t.co/sHWHRuf8sG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mercury retrograde for a scorpio isn’t getting to me yet !!!!    I feel so powerful and I love this time honestly March is Great for me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will punch you dead in the voice box please do not even try it with me today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scheana I want to say I feel u have the realest heart of everyone on Vanderpump Rules. U want acceptance, forgiven… https://t.co/zzzSXJjGHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year plan an out-of-country trip ✈️ :: I feel that we work really hard and with that, we should treat ourselv… https://t.co/9KzU1FROxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being friends with doctors is all fun and games until you wanna call them dumb but you cant because they’re prolly smarter than you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarletM1926 @RAICESTEXAS Show for trump; wonder if money to Mexico was promised]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always working on the Best Version of myself 💢  🏋🏽‍♀️🖤🏋🏽‍♀️🖤🏋🏽‍♀️🖤🏋🏽‍♀️🖤🏋🏽‍♀️🖤 Let us design your next training… https://t.co/GnB3JgrNxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally no one: quentin tarantino writing a movie:https://t.co/wzT7TRnNyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump As a bishop, if this is even true, you should be discouraging hate speech… https://t.co/rPZ60KJtiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillingEve @BBCAMERICA Miss Eve is coming... 20biteen indeed https://t.co/cZFgJF0GxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Transamerica Problem is resolved. After 4 phone calls I was able to log in to my father in law account and get wha… https://t.co/hR0o4FilKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtDisneyAgain @WDWNT I meant all hail @WDWToday. But whatever. Hail both. Still watching the two of you. https://t.co/GgdTDF16cT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nails n brows done .. Now hair n I'll feel normal again 💯😀 @ Regal Nails https://t.co/yPu19o8UFf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbgMCrovato @RomuloGuardia No saben hacerlo, son incapaces de construir nada bueno.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me intriga eso de que las bombas lacrimógenos pasan al lado de Colombia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven't left the house, - I'm ready for this day to be over 😭 #tired #iwanttosleep @ Douglasville, Georgia https://t.co/33J1XkVsKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask any student in a grade where the TNReady SS test has been “cancelled” or “suspended” for the last several years… https://t.co/HFKdi98PLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the enterprising attitude of startup company, misogood —the family recently launched their company and are al… https://t.co/7EjUAHsnli]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, I’m the happiest and healthiest I’ve been in years &amp; it feels amazing. Never underestimate the power of prayer people!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[german shepherd puppy funnies | Dog Pictures: Funny Dog Memes #funniness #giggle #smirk #jolly https://t.co/YkCFbUlhty]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TRAFFICALERT: From 9am to 3pm, 131st St will be closed between Allisonville Rd and Fawnsbrook Dr In Fishers for st… https://t.co/1i3SOQGrce]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd rather die than give it away to someone who THINKS they can get it when they want, how they want it. Go shoot in the gym solo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unetvhn que mediocre ese Cesar Silva, demostró lo q es la izquierda de Chávez, gente agresiva, violenta, intoleran… https://t.co/JSyxrQJBkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[All proceeds from the golf tournament will benefit the #RobesonCounty #HumaneSociety 🐶🐱⛳️    MORE INFO &gt; &gt;… https://t.co/ndvNgo2c9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bendito @ruleiro me ha dado el termino perfecto para zafarme del trabajo cuando no quiero ir 😅#Poderoso #HomeOffice https://t.co/HBbaj3feok]]></document><document><![CDATA[and with that, goodnight. to all my swmrs fans, please have an amazing day. if youre not a swmrs fan, have an amazi… https://t.co/KOOFSPUlAB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marvelwonderkat @marieluciesecr1 @moonhight2020 @mojosusan @mystealthXflies @WadeAndersonPT @Commandtechno… https://t.co/9nubNgKxKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mte_detroiter Expose the RHINOS / TRANSPUBLICANS https://t.co/8RfAuTZHkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a love and hate relationship when I have to work both jobs and especially if I have school lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RahelCNBC @CBSPhilly @CNBC Congratulations ❣️ You will be missed. So glad I can still watch you. You are a great A… https://t.co/EFjaFVfbMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twin_blue_eyes @SarahPalinUSA @NaturegirlRaine And when you don't believe in God and live right God will take you… https://t.co/WfIW0uGu9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyStateU I hope I make the list to see Hamilton #InTheRoomWithBrownandHamilton]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time i go on IG i see @AsToldBy_TYE  in somebody comments 😂😂😩🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rose Gold obsessed 💖✨  In Love with my @KLASSE_14 Rose Gold mesh watch 😍  Use my code Dimple_harika to get 12%  dis… https://t.co/27QKYfZFDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going to be a great morning at Bethel!  #weloveourworld @ Bethel Assembly of God https://t.co/O0BLafSj3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a voucher on a set with #LukePerry.  He knows his craft on a set.  Hope he is OK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum Put a photo of @TuckerCarlson next to the word “odious” in the dictionary. No further definition necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devislaskar Thanks, Devi! In the meanwhile, I saw your book on the TIME best of Feb list!!!!!!! ❤️📚🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Corruption is corruption whenever it happens and by whom. The key fact is that YOU ARE COMPROMISED… https://t.co/4LITpJ75TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh my co-passenger just got dropped off at my old cross street. I now despise her more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izcastillo Hopefully she embraces the never stop learning mantra...she’s great for the up and coming class of American pro tennis]]></document><document><![CDATA[saw all these great animals at the zoo today!!! My fave is the last one 😩 @ Nashville Zoo https://t.co/BmN8jDTCud]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤗I know it’s really early BUT I’m just so excited🤗  tonight I was generously offered help to fund my trip to Nation… https://t.co/xJqJIayWdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellow Californians who have filed their taxes how's it working out for you? My husband and I have to pay lots of m… https://t.co/IDqf8NUTaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @tarynrebecca for sending me an early copy of @LoriGottlieb1’s MAYBE YOU SHOULD TALK TO SOMEONE. Not only am… https://t.co/cDQl5OfNAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lancer Park needs a recycling, having to take my shit all the way to campus is annoying 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi guys. I’m not one to tweet things like this, but my dad had to go to the ER today. He’ll be in the hospital for… https://t.co/cbkyZ68FnZ]]></document></documents></author>