<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@KHGlasgow @Carolinamidwife @TheRealBSKay @SuigenerisJones @thistallawkgirl https://t.co/Mjgflz7lfA still brings tears]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayHockeyNBCS Saw this picture from past nights game. does the team save every puck for anyone who scores or is th… https://t.co/qOAnwf57xe]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% true. Unfortunately people end relationships etc.. because they think or have different beliefs. JFK said it b… https://t.co/HUKlsSwPaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[📹: Back to back buckets for @BrendonRedford in the fourth quarter. We are headed to overtime! https://t.co/zpyooj335K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Truth2Dj Bird is a habitual retweeter... And NEVER modifies his reply to line UPON REQUEST  HE still drags ppl int… https://t.co/RFWwtz4Zd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#repost Your salary is the bribe they pay you to forget your dreams.#dreams The man who is swimming against the str… https://t.co/cKoODXmjjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the @LRMarathon from the tower with over 12,000 registered🏃🏿‍♂️🏃🏃🏽! #UniteLR https://t.co/ejHA3XALC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have little problem observing a scene by myself. The environment usually does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joaquimhs @MyVMUG @vmugpr Safe travels #sadeeqi https://t.co/Kw08MzhCpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl Anniversary of one of the greatest days of the 21st century. Scumbag is burning in hell, waiting for you and Jacob to join him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Nation that feeling when pax across the Nation are sending pics of new gear rolling in... https://t.co/CsGdkta3uD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vephriel @PancakeMix85 @Warcraft @Blizzard_Ent @WarcraftDevs https://t.co/DyCEU6exsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMouchette @freshmanjourney @MonsterJam @MBStadium Very loud - thankfully RoRo hooked him up with some headgear 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should California insure itself against spending too much on fighting wildfires?: This would be a first for Califor… https://t.co/tK4x0Rcq8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ICIJorg @manda1219 @JustinTrudeau @cafreeland @CIPO_Canada @hrw @UNHumanRights #TheGlobalCallToAction #WarOnDrugs… https://t.co/bZvySbz29y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 It certainly would be a grand contest between a guy that deliberately puts his foot in his mouth and… https://t.co/H8vdTXTYzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIYL: A less creepy Ryan Adams, Kasey Musgraves’s husband. And good music.  https://t.co/qiQr0ej2Rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my four years at KQ2, @CichColt_wx has truly been one of the best people to work with. I will miss you, friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck @metallica This is true metal!!! https://t.co/kMFKbimtQx @deathangel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsatk If nothing else just because other scripts are equally valid, why should Koreans program in Latin alphabet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickPacilio @ThackreyWine Might need to make a stop there this weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8_Bit_Bobby Due process is your day in court. You aren’t entitled to “preemptive” due process.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great. Well done @TMobileArena @MGMResortsIntl &amp; @GoldenKnights]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndehlin Very much enjoyed that episode, both from a family history and a personal perspective. Don shared a lot… https://t.co/FOKQ94A09q]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the heck happened to his voice? He sounds he has a bad Jamaican accent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA UN DEMÓCRATA DE MANOS FIRME, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/vXKV88DOg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Massachusetts, we should be in the business of expanding access to the ballot. Young people are hungry to engage… https://t.co/x6muFPacIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenSeanFord I just figured out that a certain someone will be turning the big 3-0, this year.  Oh, my.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#carttest in action “will this be on your Home Card” #WePassed @JWentovich @richard_bielawa https://t.co/qS5MufFqZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freddy Krueger , Jason Voorhees, and Michael Meyers were all just really big introverts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH. MY. GOD. Literally one of the best shows ever. I can't even begin to thank everyone for comin out to support me… https://t.co/SV4bbIUeV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sapper_nikki like wtf is your problem? you’re basically a midget and take up my whole bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaliRanks @IsaNahilaS @Donxila @NagUK101 @Grand7Surgeon @inlightenmg https://t.co/34oYAKb5G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewvmcneill @Jess_Halladay I believe, technically, they refer to it as maize. I know that as a native of East L… https://t.co/momx36WZ8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best friend picture #laughter #lol #smile #laughable https://t.co/LJIQL9a8es]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DaleJr when are you going to bring @MartinTruex_Jr on @DirtyMoMedia's "The Dale Jr. Download" as the guest? Yo… https://t.co/45BL3zWDTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tactical_review Ummmmm.....nope.......carried for 40 years....locked and loaded safety on and still practice drawi… https://t.co/EmOrhLcASv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ma Nigga Mad at my Diamond. She Knows Where all the Keys are. Plus Her Mama Just Like her " I Love my Grand Father… https://t.co/3rxjogxruz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Category - Things that will piss Trump off.   Answer - what is being labeled crooked ? https://t.co/40aRq2VX30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jbrackets1 Ohio State? Have you seen them play? Nada. NIT maybe. Maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iron Man, Capt. America, Thor + were great movies because they built a shared legacy over time. Captain Marvel is a… https://t.co/Rr2GdqjxJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlecCizak I’m living about half the year near Gainesville, and when I was in Tampa for @StephPostAuthor’s book eve… https://t.co/HTMzTcPLJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more to go... GPAC Championship tonight @ 7. See you there #whodem https://t.co/wCezPQYAZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickKackis @Th1Percent @MsTeamKK @Sonny33084 @VillainofVirtue @EA I want clarity Mr KACKIS. Are you a EA GAME CHAN… https://t.co/bIE608zxLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great moment indeed! @EC_Preps_SD @b_surp,@SportsOnTheSide @MAlvarez02 @patricktakk @aztecfan144 @SDPrepInsider]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upon investigation, I can’t find a very famous “Collin” with two L’s. But if you spell my name incorrectly—with one… https://t.co/5JpgByfqpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Genesis 50:20 New King James Version (NKJV)  20 But as for you, you meant evil against me; butGod meant it for good… https://t.co/BlQ40B4WyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this doesn’t get you excited for a good summer, I am not sure what else would. @Brewers https://t.co/1wTAFiFg82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleyTallent Hey Hayley!!!!!!!! How Are You My Friend? https://t.co/YxbXpoalZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Simmons can NO LONGER be called the next Lebron , mfs did it wit Andrew Wiggins. Now Zion . There’s only ☝🏾 chosen one .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me some time but I’ve finally realized, ion’ got time to chill. I don’t got time to stop, I gotta KEEP GOING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hypergeekster @regular_joe80 @jax_persists You do realize your tweet is grammatical nonsense right?? “Read the wor… https://t.co/Sl5bE6KEXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice truly one of the best portions of this show is seeing @CarsonDaly true honest joy when a contestant is… https://t.co/7tjV6wG8kg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcNATSHACK Exactly what I've been saying. There's is no way one of the most pragmatic persons in the team and mayb… https://t.co/WgBTM7mVhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary Mrs. Langille! (aka St. Diane's Day)  Twenty four exceptional years, thank you to my wife for wal… https://t.co/z8vZqvR6GB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmarpdx Took 45 minutes, wish I had 60  If we’d had an hour it would look slightly different, but this specific se… https://t.co/GFzFbBZdEc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RomanReigns with his second best promo ever to start #raw tonight.   Good to have the big dog back @WWERomanReigns #homerun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stoolpresidente biggest no brainer purchase on the live stream for the next Cincy game. Make it happen CC: @BarstoolBigCat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worst start to year for equity flows since 2008: BAML | "A $10 billion wipeout over the last week" | https://t.co/lC5hq2x3xY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lymanstoneky You’re missing one big thing: this is also insurance against the population dropping aka a loss avoid… https://t.co/ovhAqxX1yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, someone called Vets to fix the foregone Demorat Party, but the Vets threw up their hands in disgust, and said… https://t.co/YxpkZgWZpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inauguran Carnaval Cultural Guaymas 2019 https://t.co/Tlm0fKdUZC @SaraDessens @Saravallesara @mrodriguez1567]]></document><document><![CDATA[As expected, showers have developed and will brush parts of Las Vegas through early afternoon. I'll be on @KTNV in… https://t.co/ifpn0g8dLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy Seconded. I feel like it's often shorthand for, "I don't feel like I have to justify my apathy toward… https://t.co/fxaOO2VP31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk how many times I’ve seen some shit go down at @McDonalds, there’s something in y’all fake ass food that’s making everyone crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltimateNCFan @solerKing247 @PelicansNBA #trumpcard https://t.co/9CSs3Jfye3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpatricksmith @briankoppelman @AdamCarollaShow talk about billions - chinese internet-- yepper go sina   go weibo… https://t.co/0vASzAvCSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJHerrmannYES No both injury prone statton they will pitch 2 were not in Miami never see it here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Wednesday @SuckerFreeWes @ Chloe's Restaurant &amp; Lounge https://t.co/mwJKsbmB5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhhh... adulting is doing for yo younguns when you wouldn’t do it fo yo self. Way to go , supermom!!👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free food: the universal siren song of the engineer.  “I’m not going to go to tha... oooh cake...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[In @AnnieLowrey’s book “Give People Money”, one of the most damning examples of American wastefulness is the amount… https://t.co/JhWDjWIySd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller hope he then calls martial law and that will put a end to the dems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaDelgadoP Me encanta la selección de los paises. En cuánto necesita que se recuepere? 5, 9, 20 años, nunca ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@todpalmer I honestly thought we were going to have dogs from the telethon scratching at door while we were recording.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get it, we are all human, with human emotions. As spiritual beings we are no different. The bonus for us, is that… https://t.co/rustObC2aJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Breaking News:   Venezuela shutting sea links to Dutch Caribbean amid turmoil      Via @MiamiHerald     https://t.co/W64rkmyqZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your meaning of success? #go #question #success #journey #business @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/IcPLQZHVIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stonekettle Turd Blossom needs to crawl back under a rock. He made his money with the Bushes. Now STFU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VnzlaSoberana jaja ¿Así que tu crees que fue .@marcorubio? ¿En una operación telepática?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love the training weekends, knowledge is priceless. Thank you #superd #donniethompson #bodytempering @ West C… https://t.co/zZBWRvdoyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdgeDaDon718 @TeamThirstTrap @NJD107_ It would be so Jets to have all this money and no one out there (in terms of… https://t.co/iUCGVyK7xM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CtCathCorner @FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy But neither Peter nor Paul started the church in Rome. It was like… https://t.co/eodaK3EyrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not like policy arguments that stop at “that’s too expensive.” Budgets are about priorities. Too expensive mea… https://t.co/FrWUXm525e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkAtdisney @BShieldsWFTV The Princess Half marathoners would prefer an early morning chill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaleb_carle19 @billy_baroooo @DRoan @MDGonzales Your attendance is what it is, a given, you avg what you avg.  Tho… https://t.co/4cDtA8qr6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Second show tonight: @msdaisyoconnor at @geraldinesaustn @ Kimpton Hotel Van Zandt https://t.co/CUDW8cIPb8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 8 - The Point:    How Bill Shine (and Donald Trump) killed the White House press briefing     Via… https://t.co/LHhsyFQXUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at @SonnysBBQ  but this time in Melbourne, FL. Really good food! https://t.co/zZtisQgad9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s strap season and I have the spirit of the tiger along with Mr. Miyagi with me 👊🏻 https://t.co/SLSt9QYEa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonLeeTX18 Another liberal loon, quoting a stat that includes suicides...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSimmons Ahh, okay. The Bob Arum one came on and the new one disappeared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep so you all get to read me tweet NFL thoughts. Here we go...Mayock is proving his worth as GM of the Rai… https://t.co/ME9IxiIVhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So this happened yesterday. Dusty white supremacist tried his troll hand.... the fire of god rained on him in a hai… https://t.co/CuBWmivjC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most frustrating thing to me about tennessee’s lost today is how selfish they have become as a team they’ve tal… https://t.co/LtuM3LoDfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re looking at the first customers at Shelbyville Dunkin Donuts! Me and my boy Smackers ethan_pruitt can’t be st… https://t.co/JCPX2wGr4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of news is making it increasingly difficult for me to get excited about professional sports. Our prioriti… https://t.co/zqZIdgI1HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeskeets CJ McCollum is almost in that group. 6th season?  Same for Gobert. Both feel significantly younger than t… https://t.co/HWFJSZCjjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s funny what information ppl choose to believe in. Someone can say “you can’t succeed at XYZ” someone else will… https://t.co/iJy7EOMNjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your tweet is what I will agree with. As Rangers have done in the past, despite that rule. #PowerRangers… https://t.co/7rlzQxLRq9]]></document></documents></author>