<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JayMetalPlowBoy @woolcott_dawn @LiveMusicAgent @GA_GalSouthern @SilverSmith560 @hairnetradio1 @mauigirl2117… https://t.co/CzQUGLUYxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weberair That’s standard for me to fly in the day before to make sure I make practice in the morning on the day of… https://t.co/SrHnFCGwxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #internationalwomansday with 3 generations of women! #TGIF #beauty #skincare #strongwomen #bosslady 516… https://t.co/8XloO8H4fq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Yes! One of the most EVIL! Democrats don’t just want to kill unborn babies… https://t.co/GPqb5MqGrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachleat @Delta yeah, could do better with offline functions there - part of why looking so heavily at mix of text… https://t.co/TTWR5bgW3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Pats on the all tournament team: Emma King Maddy Boyle  Kaitlyn Wilks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lifechurch Finally getting to be back with my wife after the army has had us apart for awhile now]]></document><document><![CDATA[I witnessed Alex just suggested to Chris Harrison that he be his choice for his replacement within 3 years much to… https://t.co/OoHxEouYiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life and death, poverty and riches,  its all destined "Vida y muerte, pobreza y riqueza, todo está destinado" 616… https://t.co/cw6C44kl1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ski and snow report for steamboat ski area February 20, 2019. #Ski #Skin #SnowReport #SkiReport #SkiTownUSA… https://t.co/tw21VgfHXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another easy @AskTSA experience @JFKairport in @JFKT4 in the PreCheck line]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexander is in its 10th district final all time. Spartans have won five district titles and are trying to win a th… https://t.co/cBHbssmPVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[In kindergarten I tried out for the role of Billy Goat 1 in our class play, The Billy Goats Gruff", but instead the… https://t.co/MZvCBHVSBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patimoma56 Muy buenos días Paty y feliz feliz semana tengas tu también cuídate mucho saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ran. We saw things. We ate tacos. We drank mimosas. We talked. We smiled.  . . . .  #run #running #runners… https://t.co/w0idTfIlMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning, #5amclub #51savage @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/9nDLEAw0dr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m pretty self destructive, I fell in love with someone who doesn’t have read receipts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseKellyDC The only true statement that came from all of jussie smollett's Lies. This is MAGA country indeed!😝🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Genius Imagine sampling a serial pedophile in your new single “please me”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ariana_brooke @teruhxo “The Rock” autobiography.  Crazy ending https://t.co/rfNTMtGsoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still annoyed that Storm, motherfucking Storm’s incredible powers come from Apocalypse and aren’t just inate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to be back on the bump pain free in game action after all the hard work we put in this offseason. Now time to… https://t.co/a0cInttFpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aurelio Casillas was on a coma , imagine if next season he comes back with the long hair and no beard , that be dop… https://t.co/wH2jOV8DhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJSmith910 @mattzollerseitz It's really weird when certain big titles just get totally ahafted by a major studio.… https://t.co/sbHuTjE8U3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just starting the obstruction. What a joke. Why everyone is so worried. Lol.  Love how now they want to follow the rules.  #CohenTestimony]]></document><document><![CDATA[when something that felt so real ends up being real fake ... that shit will fuck with you foreal mentally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Orioles don’t overthink this... I plan on watching him in @shorebirds or @FrederickKeys next season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dsutherland17 @dianaklonaris Send me your financials and I’ll let you know]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, and the first great “purge” will follow that, as it has in so many states after the rise of Left wing regimes.… https://t.co/2WErOxcG46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connor's Lullaby  Link in Bio  #americana #altcountry  #music #itunes #amazonmusic #country #reverbnationartist… https://t.co/p49rWvvpld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny that Sonny Gray accuses himself of sucking during the season but now rips the #Yankees for forcing him to be… https://t.co/8vOh36BU2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA['At least I'm trying' =  'at least I'm trying to impose the full power of the federal government on my pet issues w… https://t.co/x12rk3PQS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[February, been so lonely It's been so long, since I felt you I could care less if I deserve this I won't survive the sting inflicted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iheartmindy There’s been a ton of strong female leads and a recent remake tomb raider and I see most because I lov… https://t.co/spgrToZo87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elizabethnews12 Forgot to mention that you looked so beautiful as always in that red dress yesterday My heart skip… https://t.co/d677ulKs9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[But on some real shit WATCH YOUR FUCKING KIDS ! Look how carelessly they was runnin across that street 🤦🏾‍♀️ hope t… https://t.co/zIeC4qEiep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm just a normal little piggy!!! Happy weekend!!! #pig #pork #swine #little #piggy #happy #weekend #fun #pink #mud… https://t.co/HVNE2UT9j9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddyke If you have ever watched a scoring module you instantly have an appreciation for the book keepers.  Especi… https://t.co/wdBj9XEHaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSteveCox @EmmaSegasture @thenation @johncusack @BernieSanders I did. Every cent. Paid for medical school too.… https://t.co/ZvYkA6sK5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im at 167 right now. I got lots skin but hey what do you expect when I was 300 lbs. I am lean bulking. I aint going… https://t.co/93PGcw6VQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple choice: Trump met w/Kim to: 1. Get his latest orders from Putin;  2. Deflect fiom Cohen's testimony; 3. Pu… https://t.co/DuTv9VjtzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcrouchpr @Doc_Texas 500 more attempts, 4000 more yards, almost 2 yards per attempt more, 36 more tds, I see no comparison to the belldozer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh by the way I just followed the @jonasbrothers #jonasbrothers also putting #NewMusic out! Cheers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Theological debate with a certain religion could end up with Theo having no Head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PusateriJake Wait did somebody really say this in real life, that’s so disturbing, I’m not sure i know another word to use]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAHA I just photographed a Chanel dress with a consignment price of $8,150. Don’t mind me, I’m just having a heart… https://t.co/avDzXLsTMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaKAlston Their is no joy in my heart or peace even if all sexual predators are found guilty because they are… https://t.co/rkAmE4xoXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/csG1pWhcMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Mason! State Champion! #Best1stYearEver #bebold #lakecreeklions]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 hours and 100 games of crazy 8’s later... it came down to the last game for the winner.. https://t.co/w1GpKwI33M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shameless plug for one of his business interests becuase nothing matters anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SQLProApp I've been running 1.0.413 b110413 for a while now. I'm not able to reproduce the problem at the moment.… https://t.co/2HzsZ8GFWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revmark18 Again, good words, Mark. Thank you for them. Glad to have shared part of the journey for a time in western Pennsylvania.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Summerville, SC? https://t.co/lG2shKJ7rj #Automotive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatbaldguyracin True. Said going into year tourney would be a successful season. I just hate refs in general 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT!!!! COME PARTY WITH US!  4834 Tidwell Dr. Tyler, TX https://t.co/61CE5qWy6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you!! Yes you!  Did you download my music today?? 🕶🎷🙏🏾💆🏾‍♂️———————————————————— https://t.co/hfGiHHk3NR ———————… https://t.co/DYA966VlZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te regalo una rosa la encontré en el camino no sé si está desnuda o tiene un solo vestido no, no lo sé...🌹 https://t.co/xMIbJLzjWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djlerwick He is probably only getting paid by the hot thanks to Arenado!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep in mind that when you’re praising, God is working! Count on it! @ Newport Beach, California https://t.co/6bGptvZiBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheStalwart Low tax rates = lower rate of growth of inflation in this age https://t.co/H9Fxnjcwdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love a wonderfully crafted string of  curse words better than poetry https://t.co/0mR73RbEKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTuckertime You're right, it makes zero sense. I figure it's less about their actual love of Trump and more about… https://t.co/kNy74fW3Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenSuttonISP @attproam @PebbleBeachGolf @GolfChannel Ha - too funny @BenSuttonISP! #wehaveallbeenthere #missedputts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Psych_Borg @kevfitz36 @AGrossNewsday I believe there isn't a salary cap either...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I no longer drink beer or liquor, Black Cherry White Claws are officially the move.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades amiga Carmen Jara en tus proyectos la nueva era de. Carmen Jara con tu nuevo show. Y también tu cumplea… https://t.co/feQTLAs5Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Far too many times people just complain and put down people working at the airline ticket counter when… https://t.co/6PuUA0gA9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoccerSTL @tlucas19 The federation doesn't cover any of the cost of the in person courses and the state associatio… https://t.co/0X8a65llIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustDaveXxx Tricky business - If you ride like lightning, you'll crash like thunder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas trying to flex going broke meanwhile me and girl got everything paid off  like fuck it let's go get some popeyes .. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every visit to Balthazar Bakery for a signature baguette or the bigger sub baguette is a test of will power. Oh, ho… https://t.co/BhioxUL5WC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MareChiGirl @barrybutler9 Put my snow shovel away yesterday. If it snows niw, it will melt fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mini_kyle2 @ChuckW_8 Equally smooth... will be smoother if he rushes for more than 1,000 yards this season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWInvestors Can you point me in a direction where I can look into this more? Any reading?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure if I’m happier that Leaf nation is getting smoked or Hab nation is winning ?  Go Bruins!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump @CuriousKat2017 Jeanine Pirro shut your mouth https://t.co/khntCyPQOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindenashby Are u sick? I’m getting over a #viral infection and a ear infection. Hope ur well @lindenashby. Don’t… https://t.co/qwyZlT2Nh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bytownbees @FBorgal So Dinah, whose in the kitchen?  Is it John Manconi and Steve K?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLEastChampions You aren’t going to get Realmuto by trading one of the 12 guys. The Marlins were asking for 3 of t… https://t.co/mG9ViOwoZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorus77 @LarryGorkin1 @business Not exactly what he said, but there are definitely parallels. Hitler saw Germany a… https://t.co/ZOpoPdqOI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brannon_besse 69 at Hillcrest CC 17y/o hole in one on 12! Oh by the way 1979]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am ready to RIP these 2 teeth that are bad out of my face and push forward I'm tired of this headache &gt;.&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Telling Myself Ion Need Nothing From The Mall But Soon As I Get There It’s Over With 🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling out into the void, unsure of the legitimacy of my feelings, afraid of the specifics, but more afraid of the status quo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proviniendo el informe de un grupo presidido por un tránsfuga trotskista como Tuesta soldevilla no existe mucha con… https://t.co/zqWFrGHCRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sari-  stories C- one day doing homework in the front of a class the teacher asked me why I did?  I asked who had t… https://t.co/9zwbaz4pE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenWolfe Throw back a few more of those BOTOX MARTINIS Jeanine!!!! 🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸🍸 https://t.co/4tOI3rviZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basic structure is tiny ridges on an undulating surface, which gives a waider view angle for the iridescent color t… https://t.co/o4sZMTyRaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure Rusty did a great job! 👍🏻  Always love seeing our teams getting out into the community! #Path2Pro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customers use what they know to figure out what they don’t understand @aprildunford #conex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPRweather Highs just below freezing in mid March is considered spring? That’s still considerably below average. A… https://t.co/2VpauFpaoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué bonito Monterrey ❤️⛰️👑❤️ #monterrey en Monterrey, Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/l7t3ASA0JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/18/19 [Q] Warren Approves Using 25th Amendment https://t.co/droxYN8gom via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did it!  I got the Corvette!!!!   Videos to come! Thank you Linda Konrad for showing up as I purchased it!  Whooo… https://t.co/0fUayl38tn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MusingsByGritXO Come on Biotch come get some https://t.co/PhUzQRnRcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farm certifications need to suppourt farmers communicating with the market! At @CertifiedbyAGW we are focused on co… https://t.co/IaRpDdLALO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:51.3°F WchillLow:39.0°F Wind:7 mph Dir:SSE Baro:Falling quickly Rain2day:0.20in Hum:91% UV:0.0 @ 04:30 02/24/19 #weath]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a No Diggnity by @pigeonhillbrew @ Trouble Bar — https://t.co/YuYu4FZSLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lblee58 @SamanthaBusch @ToyotaRacing @KBMteam @JoeGibbsRacing @DavidWilsonTRD @jackirvingjr @TylerTRD @AndyJGraves… https://t.co/SRsacx8paH]]></document></documents></author>