<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JulieReichwein1 @gatewaypundit PAKISTAN??? R U KIDDING ME? R U NOT AN AMERICAN COMPANY? WHY NOT SANCTION PAKISTAN FOR  RIDICULOUSNESS .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am literally going to cry locked out of my brothers house IN THE FREEZING COLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I had a teacher who looked like Professor Kukui, I might have actually liked going to school #pokemonsunandmoon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wallpapermag The horizontal lightening bolt shaped roof is interesting. Not keen on ranch style homes but this one… https://t.co/mmrk7yizg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabían que hay una composición en honor a mi universidad llamada "De la mora al amor" y las partituras tienen la fo… https://t.co/XEawJmsgSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaKaySkyla @JSOPIO @NationalSheriff @GoodNewsCops @GoodCopStories @FLSheriffs @BlueWalkPoconos @propacop… https://t.co/gyGcA4Q7qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myserenity69 I have to qualify my response:  I am very allergic to cats or I might be a cat person..  Of course, I'll never know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is the night we fall in love with @howiemandel all over again on @DealNoDealCNBC tune in 9pm ET RT hashtag… https://t.co/0TWSJDFj13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNEE Bla, Bla, Bla. pero Uds siguen en EEUU mientras un PAIS se muere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very early, though not so bright yet, on this Oklahoma morning to support @WorcsWarriors! #cheeringfromacrossthepond 💙🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone have a student ticket for tonights game that is willing to send it to me? I don’t even want a shirt i just w… https://t.co/LurvnjVyaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too many of us aren't living our dreams because we're too busy living our fears. #Facts #Mentalillness #mentalhealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Relationship is not Perfect.  However the Love we have for each other, makes up for all the small imperfections… https://t.co/3JuMEGAKX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow - @MorganLewisLaw is quite lucky to have @chaifeldblum and Sharon Masling. Thanks for all you’ve done for so ma… https://t.co/xsran9S5fu]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Citrus 2016, #OilPaint and #Acrylic on wood panel. 🍋🍊 https://t.co/Uiu6TrVFMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He has to have more money than me, that’s for sure. Because I’m not taking care of any more men!” 👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾 When she… https://t.co/mETHyyHmCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk if I'm tripping or am I really hearing cheeks clapping in the apartment under me 😒 can y'all not 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @itsBayleyWWE and @SashaBanksWWE , the #FirstWomensTagTeamChamps ever!! So exciting!!❤💙❤💙❤… https://t.co/CoZTz3Nn2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melbicoo @TheAcademy I thought they did well without a host - I was pleasantly surprised. I could have done withou… https://t.co/LvuNN7JHke]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suppose the best thing about teacher strike is I don't have to get up at 6 am.  Parents pay off, too...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanSteed Thank you for coming out supporting the team and for your awesome art!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Your boring grownup activities are taking up the whole day.” — my 9yo  Joke’s on you, kid. My boring grownup activ… https://t.co/wDdOpe0Ba2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved putting some behind-the-camera faces through RQI 2020, showing them how @archildrens and @AHALittleRock have… https://t.co/muNs2Grhfr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many tell me they struggle with healthy eating because they aren’t good in the kitchen or they dislike cooking all… https://t.co/M7upLYK7q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @FCC, can’t we maybe not give us a heart attack when we sleep or when we drive (the sound goes suddenly in all… https://t.co/gRcMINh3Xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryMur66166221 @trish_regan I read somewhere once that his right hand man is a Hezbolla terrorist, not sure how true that is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grown_upenough @inevitablyjohn1 If you have an opinion about anything you stand the chance of being blocked on here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox5dc 🙏 🙏🙏 my family gets picked.  We signed up yesterday when it opened.   keep America great again 🇺🇸❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittttneym I don’t know much about like what to look for and how to know if they were bred correctly that makes me so sad tho 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl could be standing there naked and he still has ZERO RIGHT TO TOUCH HER!   Men like this are trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it worth it for me to go to the Black Excellence Ball or do I stay in and work🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNTonight @donlemon Trump is one of the biggest liars ever up on the hill and we all know what accomplishment tha… https://t.co/4jI3liem3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously? You don't think this hearing should be held because POTUS is out of the country? Smh. And… https://t.co/JwMX8MCLRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beth0505 Hello Beth! Thank You! Today we are snowed in! I am inside and in bed!🤗 Have a great day. Me Love!💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[El cambio mental del latinoamericano para detectar communists ha comenzado, si seguimos así podemos imaginarnos a u… https://t.co/xSMVuD5Y03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcusGilbert88 I’ll miss you. You were one of the good guys. Always engaging and good to the fans. God speed my f… https://t.co/RBjmut6mQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my morning Twitter scroll lately. It’s all full of awesome album covers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shnikes, I did it and found a unicorn – a left-handed school desk! https://t.co/5QzmcTDwJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repetition of this historical dynamic causes harm to both sides by seeking to establish "femme" as a marginalized i… https://t.co/l0YzrYKGHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow it’s really too bad when your car is stuck in snow and the roads are dangerous af and your boss hangs up on you… https://t.co/sntuQXhmVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My roommate’s mom is sitting at the dining table she just walked in and I’m baked with my open grinder and piece ou… https://t.co/habisEnLZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi comida favorita en el campus de Vanderbilt es de Grins😍 #comida0302 https://t.co/aILMxXQVSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got off work and decided to have a drink here. A guy i used to talk to who supposedly never had time for me… https://t.co/leCbHp7eYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving our restocked farmhouse tables!! These don’t last long so head in and grab one.  . . #tyhdesigns… https://t.co/41IDG6WCjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/oAqU1eUygo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CallieJoy I still die every time I go through it LOL butt hurt she never replied to us tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all better listen to this mofo song!!! Domo &amp; her friend friend killed it in the video ❤💯😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan How does trump actually NOT know that unfortunately we ALWAYS hear what he says, no one else has to give an opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ItAnnoysMeWhen someone labels themselves a “craft beer snob” but always drinks craft beer from the bottle instead… https://t.co/mFARLkoAd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvelDick @CourtneyHYates @hashtagfiggy Have to say, at least on #ExtinctionIsland, they're having to earn their ke… https://t.co/74f2HTUnBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Purpose being to use ill educated  And socialist indoctrinated children to vote for the socialist Democrat party. I… https://t.co/bXmqIlmste]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling strangely down. What do you folks do for a pick me up when you’re down about #art?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willlls @Jeopardy I knew I could depend on you, Brian. https://t.co/ucNtzjw3fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so ready for vacation! I just want to get my buns toasty on the beach already!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bulldawg1987 @CouponsOfDay @PianomanSoxgame Indeed! I’ve always been an Okie. How about you? Are you a true Okie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Honored The MAGA Victim At CPAC Today—He Spoke &amp; Was A Great Young Man—Still Had His BLACKEYE!… https://t.co/nANSqzVUeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can’t you stop talking about Clinton already and look in the mirror.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great idea. #jackiehenry  #jackiehenryrealtor  #loveandletlove @ Glendale, Arizona https://t.co/UxBSkk4c7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[5. For all the caffeine lovers, take a reusable coffee cup or tumbler when you get coffee. Many places, *like starb… https://t.co/pAhW20Q6HP]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK!!  Who is ready for a PINNERTEST party!!! Mark your calendars!  Next Thursday February 28th is all about underst… https://t.co/GQM6I4QDer]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to reserve your seat for all the phenomenal events at Authors And Art! Reservations are required. Private event… https://t.co/uwBfNf3maQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fingal1962 Girl, I'm crying along with you. If it makes you feel better - you can talk to @hicusick about the firs… https://t.co/pWGXKFuQnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TONiANN_ROSE These Dean pics are me every day dealing with my migraines.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sooo easy for people to see your change in behavior towards them, but they’re  blind to THEIR behavior that ca… https://t.co/LLoykXhn2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[the dirt beneath my heels in the road obeys command to me and serves me as i go and though it helps to know you’re… https://t.co/oPd3KfD5zU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaladinCornelia @aseibal @sockeye6 @vanadiumzest @HawaiiDelilah you’re article is outdated, Cornelia. https://t.co/w1JhU4fVSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise Please comment on this law @SteveScalise @GOP HOW does it differ from your legislation? https://t.co/ZXemP1hu2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurry...change the locks since both the lying President and Vice President will be out of the country at the same t… https://t.co/ajHmEsQm2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[NC All Hazards Incident Mangement Team staff providing a mock community briefing in Maggie Valley, NC It’s only an… https://t.co/MZZ0mAMziN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I'm shaking, drinking all this coffee, these last few weeks have been exhausting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are quoting Trey Gowdy wow you are really reaching 😂🤣😂🤣😂 #LockHimUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goo goo ga ga I would like to discus this with my legal counsel thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge congratulations to my pal @jweisswolf, who coined the term #MenstrualEquality that was used on the #Oscars stage last night! 💪🏻👠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @LindseyGrahamSC I don’t want to give Graham the benefit of doubt, but maybe he’s playing a confidence game on the dotard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my newest listing in Bethesda! Complete makeover and fixer upper. Open House this Sunday from 1-4.… https://t.co/cP9PgEN99n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UtilityAutonomy @RepMcClintock @CAPolitiFact Trump's #ZeroTolerance policy is going to be under Congressional over… https://t.co/sK5T5NNRLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What did you do to taxes? I usually get a small refund, couple hundred dollars. This year, I will… https://t.co/2bmF28tH4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrocanada certainly has the money for it, but @HumeChristopher is right... The city doesn’t have the self respec… https://t.co/GrsOGtXpUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[l just really need a Mamma mia 3 like idk if Abba even has that many songs but like l really need it]]></document><document><![CDATA[CELEBRATING INTERNATIONAL WOMEN’s DAY last night with #solesister @acastrodance, ariellerosales in spirit… https://t.co/LZu3QU6Cwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao this is such a weird promoted tweet for me like I'm sure its bc I used to be a big top chef fan but also I hav… https://t.co/Uad53snjt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best Valentines Day gift I could ask for, my lineman got us power restored after two days!  It isn’t an easy jo… https://t.co/QQ6x1F7UpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me &amp; @Senaida_Treto talk about EVERYTHING😂😂😂😂 nothing is a secret in this friendship 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I am so sick of these rich privileged white men who think the law does not apply to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[dinnnnnerrrrr🐷#foodporn #foodphotography #foodie #foodgasm #foodstagram #foods @ Dixon, Illinois https://t.co/wOnueAP5eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your MCM thinks he’s the shit but he’s really just an asshole...  It’s me, I’m your MCM lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[248 phone calls later and 13 minutes of thinking I didn’t make it through — I am singing at THE BLUEBIRD CAFE in Na… https://t.co/3qjrEQjiBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop staring at the clock every day. It's time for a new career. Follow us to view jobs with titles like "Yard Team… https://t.co/EBovZwwGYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPOfriend That's absolutely not true. Video storytelling triggers emotions in an incredibly effective way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felix hates that we wake up early. He’s snoring away so loudly and glaring whenever someone turns on a light. 🐶🦴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@first_sf #choirrehearsal #happyitssunday #first_sf @ First Baptist Church of San Francisco https://t.co/gMNM9eSokX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse should not be able  ADVERTISE @realDonaldTrump family hotels! STOP using our government for financial g… https://t.co/XvLqpnbbRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost forgot to put water in my ramen. My roommates would’ve killed me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t believe for one second that Zion isn’t healthy enough to play yet. There’s something going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bro_Charlie_ @Littlleome @JudyMarie4DT @maryllewis53 @RenaCBSW @BionicPopTart @erenna_marie @PamelaJoWilson1… https://t.co/LDj5ymZJQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game 63 : #huskiesrn 8 cataractesshaw 3 06/03/19  #rouyn #shawinigan #gohuskiesgo #lhjmq à Amphithéâtre de Shawinig… https://t.co/59L0uKMmw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday My little grandson Juan when he was little. He had his 1st day in pre-k at the age of 3 years ol… https://t.co/k3ocqzTKJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[i @ my finsta in the comments of meme accounts bc i don’t have friends to @]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheldonfountain @_orionblackburn The countless times you almost killed me driving drunk from Jerry’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaMrugg1 @kushibo @realDonaldTrump that's exactly the problem - we are all waiting to "see" something - if it… https://t.co/Vioy3cvb6f]]></document></documents></author>