<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[They show allied characters obviously “feeling.” But then the crescendo STOPS settles on this vial witch of a queen… https://t.co/cDDDtYxJRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on y’all my shit different on these sides 🔥🔥🔥🔥 #PlaylistChallenge stillspudy propaganda_pat @ The Don https://t.co/TdjmpzpNvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#QuestionOfTheDay  Only ONE out of #Marvel, #DC, #StarWars, #StarTrek or some other fictional universe can be saved… https://t.co/HcWgG7mz9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[M3: Bradley 2, UNLV 0  Bolt led off the 3rd with a double and scored on an O’Brien RBI ground out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working all week long at #winterequestrianfestival very excited to start doing Comedy again real soon. I'll keep yo… https://t.co/eZC6PDEiBk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays @NickSew If people in Canada knew I see my doctor less than a day from when I think of seeing them,… https://t.co/W6r79h9jq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Les_Aker @sandangel_RN @JerylBier @allahpundit I mean, says you. I wouldn’t want to live in a banana republic. And… https://t.co/ECjDQpc9m3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@niclloyd70 @Drewschluchter1 Don’t even bother trying to talk down UM education. It is a fact that it is far superior to that of MSU.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @IowaWBB on the big win over Rutgers. On to the B1G Championship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mostrolenk I don't have any first hand knowledge.  My wife and I both started out in the help desk of IT and have… https://t.co/HTxxxEa7YX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to 1940-1960’s audio tours pushing versions of Civil War #history that omit slavery]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still need to nominate a moderate. #myopinion #Election2020 #VoteBlue2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tGXu372xM3: Jeremy Clarkson pays emotional tribute to 'important' Top Gear fan: 'I listened to him'.… https://t.co/hfg4D9HnBz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConservInNY @DavidJHarrisJr Excellent messsge this Sunday thank you here from upstate NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brie Larson es más grande que todo el hate sin sentido que le tienen a Captain Marvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom He'll be 80 by the end of his first term!  Where are the qualified younger men?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the brightness of your eyes 🙈 #cokisofc  . . . . . #love #igers #tbt #photography #photooftheday… https://t.co/vBOJqM7TAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[us gays are so oblivious it's not even funny  you could be flirting with me for months and I'd never realize I'm so sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Methodists believe we should “make disciples of the world for the transformation of the world...” But we don’t beco… https://t.co/b9ELY4fGti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PulidoAndreina @BofA_Help @Zelle @WellsFargo @JackRhysider My proof that I’ve used it in the last is here https://t.co/A3diKxFeh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish her and Ariana ain’t had beef. Just imagine both of them on a song together]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP isn’t looking for TRUTH. The GOP is only looking to PROTECT Trump!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @jumpman23 the lobster roll and pizza was fantastic. @ Michael Jordan's 23.sportcafe https://t.co/x8a9VuAHUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMARCA @JLSanchez78 @Ramon_AlvarezMM @QuiniAlvarez @Paul_Tenorio @PipiEstrada1 @raulvarelar CR7 recibió expuls… https://t.co/MvMVEJAzgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey you guys! I know a lot of people have been complaining about seeing the same ole foods in the Cafe. There’s a s… https://t.co/q1gwt6Ytch]]></document><document><![CDATA[This may sound soft as hell but i almost cried watching D Rose in person i love him]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @JillianMichaels @Tharealmouse @AmyMotta @Keegannnnn @missjudygreer @kate_abdo @komandnaya 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 43 I started reading the #Bible, it’s truly an amazing read. I’ve always envied those that understood the script… https://t.co/Klh50NNiN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all my roommate and me just send each other funny stuff all day long 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[For someone who supposedly has a lot of friends, why do I constantly feel like I have one good friend, and that per… https://t.co/CPucuCwHd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HORRORFlED @landofthe80 I had many pairs of parachute pants, the glove/socks, and a "Beat it" jacket that my mom m… https://t.co/dVT7dH9GDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaEWrestling @JobberkNocker @smarktodeath @fowl_original @FightfulWrestle @WorldOfPW Agreee wholeheartedly!👏🏽I bel… https://t.co/reYe4c1LFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iron sharpens Iron! You must sharpen your iron physically and mentally! Who you hang out with is who sharpens your… https://t.co/jQguXZmYnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone explained to the “Resistance” that Trump has been doing EVERYTHING that he was elected to do, and no mat… https://t.co/B4x27aecuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AlmostFamous1_ I was just going to start smoking weed and eating healthy lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreBos10 @Ebron85 Ya but how many honeybuns you eaten so far this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[for .2 seconds i maybe thought about getting my real estate license but i can’t even go eat with my mom without her getting a phone call.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @TKinMB I always remember my ID when I need a loaf of bread and some lunch meat. Wish others would do the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Devastating to US policy around world that all know now that Our president is a “blow hard”, worst since Carter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not crying, you’re crying!!! Way too much fun playing with the @treatvancouver crew.  I’m ready to set up a dou… https://t.co/tDMhcDkDct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleybigma that’s why you don’t mess with my army #FleetWoodMacinators  @StevieNicks @fleetwoodmac luv u guys, hmu sometime stev!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam It might surprise Rashida Tlaib to learn that millions of Americans are wondering why she should have… https://t.co/X1xBDOYaUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Racist is upset about being called a racist.   “I know black people!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamzaKK @ManUtd @Ibra_official He’s the reason they won the Europa League. He and Mkhitaryan. And Herrera placing… https://t.co/BWCIDLwxSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewski9110 @LatonyaYarbro Bro... what it sounds like you saying is: it takes one to know one. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free to speak... #ThisIsWhatISee #aNgles @ New York, New York https://t.co/ELAzi3kMg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASavageNation Easy mikey...shine stepped down to start working on Trump's  2020 campaign.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddya_torres @Ojoos_de_Bruja @islademiencanto @LcdoTrafala @boinaverdeyulin Buenos días Limbersito vda de Manni!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a team sport. The skill positions make all the flashy plays but the big boys up front dictate whether or they… https://t.co/FllBDobNVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honda Accord Sport 2.0 with the 6-speed is coming soon! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Ri… https://t.co/lqEyuLv2PH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeConti5 @JRMotorsports @iRacing @JRMotorsports  for the win. Show the what your made of @MikeConti5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaneBerrong @indfbscout #404Takeover #404theCULTURE #GoldBlooded21 💪🏼🐝🔥 https://t.co/d2meQ5m9Dz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wowgioio I dated a girl that would beg me to spank her. She got so turned on and I loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hulkster_on @CreamyButters @OpieRadio I think I took an acting class with the guy on the left back in the day. Lived in Chelsea. 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Get it done Mr president show the democrats how it’s done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the Lake High School 1st Twitter Chat https://t.co/IVZXdEThVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andddd Rami Malek wins for lip syncing in Bohemian Rhapsody. 😑😑😑😑 #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, I pray you give me the resources to bless everyone that doubts me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GitRDoneLarry @jkeenan81 @thehannahhuston @KitKat_US Put that in a blizzard and eat it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m currently playing the 7th Player on https://t.co/esb3xyKIT5. Come and join me! https://t.co/O613awShE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeymourHoops just a reminder to all Seymour fans: Your All-Sports, Owl passes and season tickets will not get you… https://t.co/zaXu0VDAnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernanGomezB @ricardomraphael OBVIO, LOS QUE SI SOMOS SOCIEDAD CIVIL NO PODEMOS ADMITIR QUE LOS MISMOS DE SIEMPRE… https://t.co/pxTm4iY1vQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SjwSpiderman @AbacusMike Now I kind of want to crowdfund an incredibly apolitical comic, too. The villain would be… https://t.co/579RpRcLZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SciFiFanFreak48 @VerseTrek @TimelordGenius I plan on watching BR this weekend before the Oscars.  I wanted to watc… https://t.co/ZawQKsGwXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesRamos63 @randomguy495 @Blaskey_S @NickNehamas @ceostroff Maybe.  Because that is the way spy’s work.  U get… https://t.co/GfLoiNEAYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a shame a sexual predator in Kent Hehr blocked me on twitter for calling him out. A real Damm shame. #cdnpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad boy! Now imagine if this was a white man and Republican the media and democrats would want him arrested prosecu… https://t.co/wRUrVlRJpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilliams86 thanks for you and the family coming through G appreciate it]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA commissioner discusses the “anxiety generation”. This is so important and applies to all of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost She just talks to her herself ... sad that the people of New York elected her .... sad .... very sad ... sh… https://t.co/QcKfF46X0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkMcCall3 Really? I’m not that special. I’ll miss you and everyone. One of these days I will be unlucky 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught a lil bullridin after his basketball game! jkb23_   #muchtooyoungtofeelthisdamnold @ El Paso County Coliseum https://t.co/GU5ulODo9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AraEdTech @MDGrose @mcarlstromDR @SueAkre @PollyASheppard @DRGuidanceDept @DeHron1 @markmotherway @MTMorrowGR To m… https://t.co/byqqyonBaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[What in the Hell are these two imbeciles doing at  a Security Conference in Munich, Germany? Must have been offered… https://t.co/3F4vhk9Uur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElisaDiStefano Hey Syke... what about @bruceaveryWRHU?  Did you forget your roots?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaroleRadziwill Can we stop generalizing all white guys. It’s kinda shitty. I’m a hard worker, provider for my 2 k… https://t.co/WSZzGTB7S3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I see here is a guy who has nothing to lose, and knows it's time for the American people to see the whole pict… https://t.co/QFheBbHu3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#filteredaf #drgrabow #wednesday #pipe #pipesmoking #tobaccopipe @ Sioux Falls, South Dakota https://t.co/7lyoWm2isq]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I do is work &amp; stay blessed !!💯🙏🏾💰 No bad vibes on my end just good energy &amp; love!!🚫🧢💪🏾🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEGENDBETS @ShotTakingTime @gabe_prewitt Somebody to send me a link to a book to buy....like I know where to start lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kentuckyweather Snow really coming down and sticking now since temp dropped to 32 degrees here in Eastern Mason Co… https://t.co/0wwhW159HV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unvaccinated Oregon Boy Is Diagnosed with Tetanus, the State's 1st Child Case in 30 Years https://t.co/xR6pdYXZfM via @LiveScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess: @Bharper3407 to the @Phillies for 10 years and $333M (with incentives adding up to $363M).  #BeBold… https://t.co/yEeIsOaKgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No person resolved to make the most of themselves, can spare time for personal contention.” #quote #quoteup  Abe Lincoln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe Nancy's tax returns would show us how she became a multi-millionaire After she got into Congress? 'Pelosi’s C… https://t.co/YSMxBlsX8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DillyDilly97 I get you. That makes sense. But I feel like in key categories he’s subpar. For me it’s a situation w… https://t.co/bE9f93uIc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just backed Collar Keeper: Simply hanging collared shirts on @Kickstarter https://t.co/o4UWyFkvp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cehryl found your music at a coffee shop yesterday and i’m in love, thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brin_bee @ThisIsMe_Suter You IG story. Wasnt tryna be weird but wanted it for her bday S/O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anasoguegbe  I arrived safely. I need your updates during Gubernatorial Election]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will Americans and Europeans stop running scared every time someone screams “anti-Semitism”? Until when will I… https://t.co/NCaMX4yCJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay that Tottenham performance was so good i started drinking. Just realized Villanova isn’t on for 3 hours. Let’s… https://t.co/M7DTjqYRc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Isn’t CPAC a machine for people with sleep apnea?  I mean, that might explain a few things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone remind him he’s “part-owner” of the Warriors? Money changes people 🙄 https://t.co/O13srUnG0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xylauraz I guess with baseball season starting I had a nightmare about the perfect game thrown against us! 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[TB siempre ha preferido sacrificar dinero por hacer espacio al tope salarial. Si se fuera, fácil serís el mejor pag… https://t.co/WgpXmW8nFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zac_delong @VCChaps @coachpatty64 @PBR_Oklahoma @baseballmachs Congratulations Big dog!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressClubCle @MarketGardenCLE @SceneSallard @CarolKovach1 @Fladung Ruthlessly and endlessly take Jackson and Budis… https://t.co/jBDyFyNuWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cecilio_Rosales what I hate more is that after spring break we only have like a week of class, then finals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Americans and American businesses, not China, are paying most of the tariffs though higher prices… https://t.co/fwR65gi5Em]]></document></documents></author>