<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@akirallen_ Oh lord I’m sorry girl.... I been on defense mode all day on this app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fly ball to left ends the threat. It's 2-0 to the bad guys. Headed to the bottom of the 3rd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inspiretowander Wales, after doing an extensive research project all about whether or not King Arthur was real! #InspireToWander]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it’s fab hair night here’s an updo I did long ago and far away in front of a painting by my talented hubby… https://t.co/7fNSfKYap5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guilhermee_g4 .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different ki… https://t.co/hHrSybpVML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnitude 1.0 #earthquake, 12.8 km NE of Death Valley Junction, CA https://t.co/1467K061tD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom told her hair stylist to give her this hair   and i had nothing to do with it, she was just excited to tell… https://t.co/t2ODs44PTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hyundai Swag brings out the kid in us all! Especially when your assistant is named....wait for it....Bentley!… https://t.co/k9gB14iWbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time of year it’s gray and gloomy almost always so I’m grateful for my small town where I can step out for a r… https://t.co/kj1UWWp6PS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get Free $25 Skype Gift Card Offer   Win $25 Skype Gift Card Offer By Your Email Id Submit,    Click Here:… https://t.co/XhUOYPU7Us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PineyElem in #STEAM lab @MonicaNikaleal 1st grade @EcoSchoolsUSA #MonarchHeroes take a break from painting w/… https://t.co/UQzfrmClaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4. I was nominated by @IanIancovell @MaryAnnMullen1 @AmyCharbonneau1 @jnbell_bell to post covers of 7 books tha… https://t.co/KRicrmMQsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ObiWanPhanobi Today gotta be the day. We need some good after all the drama this week with the two RK's and Jussie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will be holding a service of support for LGBTQ+ folk (clergy and laity) during General conference at our… https://t.co/UJynK4gI6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[If u have &gt;10k *followers* on instagram and a blue check mark by your name, #cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Wow. It’s a twitter rant fest.  Trump is seriously troubled about what’s coming. He def… https://t.co/dgCAt2ey4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @Hollandmspeech for being selected by your peers as the #spedstrong MVP! It seemed fitting for you… https://t.co/8QMrSnk9VR]]></document><document><![CDATA[6:30am. Starting my day with prepping for the first installment of my film project 📹 . . Thankful for all thats bro… https://t.co/FOCSz3Y1aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loricatus_Lupus @OriginalFunko Ah. I love cereal! Adult and kid kinds. Guess I'm 7. 😉😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter for a chance to win round trip air travel* on Southwest for yourself and guest, plus upcycled leather travel… https://t.co/FyjJzZ6CN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[That girl that never gave my music play changed all that though. Back when trap was just starting to really emerge,… https://t.co/oeSxg0e74D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattygarciaaa_ Say no more estoy lista para ti 🤩 https://t.co/IqVjDK4ld4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaPubSchools you should be ashamed of yourselves for this. He will walk in the door with his team and all the boy… https://t.co/tZVqfakJaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bedtime my body is finally tired headed into town tomorrow to get stuff for the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[This dude. Every time I sit to do laundry. Every. Time. @ Sterling, Virginia https://t.co/irn8TbY98w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't have any energy to tweet about Bernie Sanders. How are y'all even doing this. https://t.co/GJrqtlehO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuskersAZ @Huskernupe1911 @ThreeBeersLater Tropic Thunder was probably his best roll... Valkyrie was a good movie. Otherwise I don’t care]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ The Waterford at Valley Ranch Apartment Homes https://t.co/jgtUgU3UbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The E. Jones Show..  Love them.. @ Bethlehem, Pennsylvania https://t.co/l6Fe8M1ix7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It irritates me when people think that their life is harder than anyone else’s. We all got stuff that we could neve… https://t.co/EKvwBYqCMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Warbler is coming soon to #Kickstarter. ENTER TO #WIN: https://t.co/bjNYSNgCju #relax #stretch #workout… https://t.co/9GufyDiVsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCQueensPark Hydro One needs the best, most qualified CEO it can afford. It’s a utility that we all rely on in a… https://t.co/ctP2LZZgBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonMindful It was a slider and came through quick and dropped about 3” really quickly. It’s an icy mess. Be carefu… https://t.co/iIB3fWZ1fE]]></document><document><![CDATA[those who want to live a gratuitous love and the gift of self will be crucified as Jesus was. They will be persecut… https://t.co/w16j6ljNcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaytonPubPolicy @HaffaAlan The power is out at my house because a tree fell onto the power lines that run along Hi… https://t.co/b3adMO4EUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[10th Anniversary date night! bookofmormon @ The Kentucky Center for the Performing Arts https://t.co/NJcufkRjw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring the new eatalylasvegas at the Park MGM. An amazing collection of restaurants, Italian food and wine marke… https://t.co/QLTwuxi9hE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders We all think that life is so good in the Scandanavian countries  - well, they have Democratic Socialism .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a Momversation?   I admit I wasn’t prepared for how fast my son would grow from a toddler into a… https://t.co/kS7r4B3V9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mel_Edwards80 @FOX10Phoenix Haha really? I missed it because I was out shoveling. Lol. Dang it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you also "struggle with #depression?" Check out @andytheamateur's video about her experiences. Everything she sa… https://t.co/qLBS3sykB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday NaTHOTlia!!!! Love you!! Have an amazing day bbyyyyy!!! 💓💓@xnataliesworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The #census is a non partisan issue. It’s about ensuring we have the resources, infrastructure, and representation… https://t.co/CaEPplUaD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunning beauty perfect for MAC first face @mainedcm  / Maine Mendoza  #MaineForMACStudioFix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I don’t know if Harry asked this question. But this is fact: #MeghanMarkle in #NYC without #PrinceHarry two we… https://t.co/oJ2Y0wEpLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The snow is falling fast and furious today! Looks like I’ll be racing through today’s workout. 🏋️‍♀️ The main roads… https://t.co/fwVSypRxwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: Pro-Gun Man Stands Up to Pelosi with Fiery Public Statement Every American Needs To Hear - https://t.co/Bhrx035mKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow moms are so mean to other moms who literally just state their opinion ???? Like why be mean ??? Just because you disagree ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @extratv @StateDept @SecPompeo @KellyannePolls @PressSec @SarahHuckabee You were really good Sean..but… https://t.co/XhvWpCpNSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing goes harder than Queen's Liar, I McFricking lose it to that piece everytime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lis_on_Life @Bethenny @giseleofficial I agree if you love someone you love u might look but you dont touch if you… https://t.co/tXZgiinPyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just start craving a salad? And then you stop yourself like https://t.co/1XpKFqws13]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever add you to one of me @KayUnbroken and @lolastfu ft calls just know we’re gonna be together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale @EricTrump The poem of Old Ironsides, by Oliver Wendell Holmes depicts Our President! Despite what’s thro… https://t.co/h4JY03WdQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Titanic again and I will always have a negative reaction to Rose as long as I fucking live! THERE WAS ENOUGH ROOM!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sad that your own friends actually delete you just b/c you have a difference in opinion on politics. The fac… https://t.co/lD8Kg6nwZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Essex County South Mountain Park in West Orange, NJ https://t.co/4Vw2V8AQpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stop selling arms to SA.  If this were Assad we be bombing them now. @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo @johnbolt @IlhanMN… https://t.co/nG8lzQpbUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE CAN DO IT! #AlamoPHX #CaptainMarvel #drafthouse #enchantedentertainment https://t.co/4cKPkdCp6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime! Just make it warmer and next time you might get a king sized candy bar. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlie loves peanut butter so much. He knows when I’ve had some and didn’t share and he gives me this look and it breaks my heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bilingualism No Problem for Children with Down Syndrome - Language Magazine https://t.co/G7lFxMDdKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaWarfield it would be refreshing to have the option to do so and I absolutely would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel uncomfortable knowing people who are close to me talk to people who did me dirty and are obviously toxic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalehousebarn That’s the same thing @patchfarmstead said. I’ll try to find some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A glimpse into the CWP CATE Pre Conference. So many great ideas revolving around amplifying student voice..#cwp… https://t.co/4q63lBQw1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, when you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you achieve it.  - Paulo Coelho, The Alchemist https://t.co/QHfU5mdlKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an amazing group of ladies I got the chance to be a part of last year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m hype about the move I just made!! #JaeLeighBoutique #AshleighYvonne  I swear I was made for this! 💋💋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ben Kadillac-Czechoslovakia lmao @BaaileyC that’s almost as good as when Siri said “calling Ben Cattle Sex” 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnny_Radio @Isaac_Rivals @DustinStarr @TheMariaStarr I’ll be listening!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customer called and asked if they could deposit cash with the mobile app. #BankTellerProblems https://t.co/Je0PwsUSlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@estheramma @NancyKrause47 The voting process is done according to our laws.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJAEBrown This couldn’t be more true! Seeing my parents in the bleachers at my softball games meant the world to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, so, I’ve got this human growing inside me and she’s making my belly huge, so if you could actually MOVE OUT OF… https://t.co/KP3ggdFFUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello I am in search of someone to sing Bradley Cooper’s part of Shallow with me in my car as we drive around in my car. apply within DMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump Lier just like daddy both need to go before a firing squad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias to @teolol and @HomiesEmpower for hosting an evening with #janetstickmon from  @nvcollege reading from her… https://t.co/T7OpiodtCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCWalsh1 @MomSkelton @washingtonpost @KatyTurNBC Gawd and he’s a Hoosier. I’m sorry. And for Pence. So embar… https://t.co/PIZKX1YOrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to love running and now I can barely walk on incline without my back hurting :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming home from a really tiring and busy lunch shift to a dog super excited to see you is the best feeling ever.… https://t.co/WjGxl4tuAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NayhelyMclaugh1 @CorridosYBandas @juanvegao5 Fuck yes sis ya te la u knoooo😝♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be straight up w me fr cause I’ll sit there and overthink e v e r y t h i n g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we millennial  friendly?   Are your motivations sincere?  Do you have a clear purpose?  Are they welcomed to th… https://t.co/Bq92dstmXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw I get to spend IWD with my two bffs tonight. Last time me, Katy and Nicole we’re together I cried in a Wawa for… https://t.co/HiK5KhBDLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking a for a side job that pays atleast 100$ an hour, I need my car fixed ASAP 😭 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottSabolFOX8 2015 seemed a little more consistent until it got into February.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchoenstraII @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Using offensive, belittling and homophobic clip-art simply furthers th… https://t.co/8FTUh4SlLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Great technology should improve life, not distract from it.” — Julie Aranda @jul_2222 on #digitalwellbeing at… https://t.co/hAJ3o8QtLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to my first lacrosse game, was hoping it would live up to my teen wolf fantasies  It didnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Match Day Shout Out @GRgunners @ArsenalDetroit @TriangleGooners @BrewCityGunners @CuseGooners @futbolesqueAFC… https://t.co/iqSnN2V5R5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not even on the Bachelor but Colton sending Caelynn home after EVERYTHING THEY TALKED ABOUT and her being the o… https://t.co/VqNpYXzJcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to the love of my life, most beautiful human being on this planet &lt;3 imy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally me. My coworker dead reminded me today was payday 🤣 never thought I’d be here so soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pingflloyd @guyverhofstadt No I don’t see the hypocrisy since I am informed and I know what you say about tariffs… https://t.co/NpVOA3w73U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thepremierguy You sound like my mom. She tells me I don't have to speak Spanish to her. She might not speak Englis… https://t.co/4vDsZr4Sal]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said yesterday night I will skip my event today in Washington DC tonight. I was tired. I am thinking attending ev… https://t.co/tNtY2XDJGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenSilverstein1 @EliLake @MaxBlumenthal Thank you. Looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliewilsonmd @ChildrensColo Ditto! Look how far you’ve come from your first football game as a resident managing an elbow dislocation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas will have all kinds of emotional issues and act like it ain’t that deep.... um ok]]></document></documents></author>