<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Crybaby chuck looks like Mr. Withers in Bart Simpson show PURE EVIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know the less than noble beginnings, or the pain you may now face, unfaithfulness or job loss, perhaps. But… https://t.co/SbTB23akUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews ....TRUMP FOLLOWS 'FUHRER' HITLER...TELL A LIE LONG ENOUGH AND... TRUMP'S BASIS..WILL BELIEVE IT.... WELCO… https://t.co/n0w81avsRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maybesomedia @TheOfficerTatum And Americans enslaved blacks. But not Americans in the last 100 yrs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowy Saturday Mood #mood #current #snow #NYC #weekend #bed #dachshund #dachshundsofinstagram #wienerdog @ Upper Ea… https://t.co/aeq8tZ4ibI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonRMatheson @ChrisStoney This played a huge factor in my career decisions. Do I wanna leave my grandparents who… https://t.co/XHmFfIFC6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moneylionracing @Team_Penske @joeylogano @MoneyLion @DISupdates Great job Joey!!!! Get it in Atlanta!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class Schedule February 19-28  Class schedule  2.19 6:30p Insanity-Jen 2.20 7pm HULACISE-Leigh  2.21 6:30p Dub Yoga… https://t.co/Ayd7Qu2Hgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so effing sick and i decided to watch john mulaney’s standup show that’s on netflix and i can’t stop laughing. i’m in so much pain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pablohidalgo For real though, has anyone who's ever met you described you as an egomaniac?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's National #FrozenFood Day! (No, really, it is!) Stock your freezer with some yummy #GirlScoutCookies before the… https://t.co/gjXefHIYkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 augmented reality apps for the classroom #ARVRinEDU #iPadEdu #EduApps #iPadChat #iPadEd #iPadEdChat #AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤯 Not sure how I feel about this but it is definitely exciting times for @HotelTonight! @Airbnb @TechCrunch  https://t.co/ptrW6zPiw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful scrawled filefish about a mile up the intracoastal in south #Florida, must have come in with the clear oc… https://t.co/vR9QCggcl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another AMAZING book!!! Literally finished it in 2 days. Gustavo was so over me because I was literally reading dur… https://t.co/feqF1iv5SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: Richard Williams is STILL alive and kicking yes?  So I’m gonna go out on a limb and say he has SOME input… https://t.co/nC11uImePc]]></document><document><![CDATA[i say some outta pocket shit then i follow it w/ jkjk but im definitely probably not kidding]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost prodigal_sonmedia Made by image.downloader · · · · prodigal_sonmedia with @djnaim filming for… https://t.co/h4Ba9tqY0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The road to safer driving starts at @TMobile! Come by and check out why you need a #SyncUpDrive in your vehicle.… https://t.co/btRikpN9Qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsbuckenham I’m worried about @ejstallings...she is not practicing proper bus safety. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspan @GOPLeader You are idiots! There is no National Emergency! Trump is mad because the house voted not to give… https://t.co/7nbs43aoUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You are a Spartan, this is your kingdom, and it does revolve around you. That isn’t ego, it’s truth. You are here… https://t.co/kC5urQfUES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sqlmal I heavily commented my SSIS packages. Including dates and ticket #’s what the etl was doing, and why I may… https://t.co/GnQEwVEMm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask me how to get your entry @ SEPHORA inside JCPenney https://t.co/Lbek4NbWnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fucking sad that my fav ever Mac Miller had to pass 😔 forever heartbroken]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for some great music? #sundaynight #widewonderfulworldofbutter #classics #soulmusic #greatmusic… https://t.co/FD4WeBeweD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joefaz Must have been interesting. Wonder if she kept referring Mueller to another person or agency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our situation may be different, but we could see some potential damage from the upcoming storms.  Please be prepare… https://t.co/Hx9GUQiFva]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheUSASingers CA wildfires National Parks destroyed for pipelines  Flood Snow Hurricanes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 Why doesn’t these kids who are bullied fight back. We’ve seen enough of this 💩 and they don’t defend t… https://t.co/t1TiqBvfDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw memories! Can’t wait to film my next music video!   Bonne Elle - MOONSHINE https://t.co/zPoDICcAWs via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KerryNBC @NBCNews @NBCNightlyNews Is Trump going to build a northern wall too?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to investigators, Makowski is steadily improving.  His son appeared in court yesterday, March 5 for an in… https://t.co/I7VFySN6rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Get in, loser. We’re going shopping.”  #TBT #Thursday #ThrowbackThursday #Throwback #MeanGirls https://t.co/AwelCc25CS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another week another pit road 💁🏼‍♀️ #nascargoeswest @ ISM Raceway https://t.co/L0cjNM33Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[That shit needs to stop! We cannot allow mob boss trump to control this . WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yesterday, the coffee was already turned off and cold. The old man said “just warm it up in the microwave”. Whic… https://t.co/KxB1SuMf8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of wine and a game night means the end result is my roomie and I crashing on the couch after 11 pm watching #Hairspray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. .        🎤 .           🎤 .              🎤 .                 🎤 .                    🎤 .                       🎤 .… https://t.co/kNlLkesbrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ve somehow made this into an actual fun scene (like, actually kind of funny) and I’m impressed. #ElyssaWatchesFSOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColsCitySchools @Centennialstars @CentennialAD ✨Go Stars ✨ https://t.co/HOSwCUTpEj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anyone else wondering about the parrot?  Can we get a welfare check? 🦜 #LivePD https://t.co/xOY5UXt15I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkippersHuman @ewarren You must be very young. I can tell by the way you talk. I pray God helps you see the light… https://t.co/Shr5pqeKWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t wait to have kids but i can wait ya feel i wanna be the cool tia for a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a little appreciation tweet for my guy, Riff Raff. 😝 https://t.co/hIoAAfRngY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year so far has been full of big changes, I seriously couldn’t be happier ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you experiencing the symptoms of burnout? You’re heading towards burnout and here’s how you can avoid it →   https://t.co/wpiuA9ae6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarahsorres_rex And they have the AUDACITY to charge COVER??!?! I’ll never understand it]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's 3am and what am I doing.... watching the Dolan Twins on Celebrity Fear Factor!! @GraysonDolan @EthanDolan]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that he has a daughter who is this old, makes me feel so old 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥ANTIHATE RESOLUTION TEXT🔥 🔥THE HOUSE IS VOTING TODAY🔥   https://t.co/e8cEUdz8Nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath You mean like he supported Hillary?  He supported her in name only...he never really got behind her.… https://t.co/DlRCkFYqq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeZimmersEars @DelReid @TerryBdattd @Burke_William1 @lno09281978 @Pammadonna @MsAFromBK @60N861RL… https://t.co/ZOG1sXDr1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t tell you when the last time I paid to get my hair done &amp; I switch braids every 2-3 weeks 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, snowing up high anyway. Raining down low. 🤪 #T3IC #T3IC2019 https://t.co/Cv5Ic4RFnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every week I buy so many veggies thinking I'm gonna make Gordon Ramsey Michelin star meals when in reality I eat ch… https://t.co/O2Ftwop7d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[When someone tells you that it can’t be done, do it twice and take pictures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[do food delivery people not come to the door anymore? like is it expected I come outside of my dorm/house to meet you at your car?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was weird because I was texting like 10 different people and I never do that and I was getting confused 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made my whole bar watch the twilight movies yesterday and honestly? They deserve a better bartender]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did no one else immediately think Rachel Greens bridesmaid dress #Oscars2019 #rachelgreen #FashionPolice https://t.co/mcnKnB6Pdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah sex is great and all but have you ever sat and watched Bob Ross painting videos together?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lowe207 @MissZoeyGailey @SFecich @sarahdateechur @smgaillard @EMercedLearning @mlarson_nj @SteinbrinkLaura… https://t.co/SToePxQyBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Atrium Health, our patients, communities and teammates are the center of everything we do. If you are seeking an… https://t.co/i4gmqypK9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great evening with UofSC IHI Open School and SCThrive to learn how to better help our patients and connect them to… https://t.co/M8EJWVC1Pq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing better than the sound of gunshots at your apartment while standing outside!! @Regan_Dawn_]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another amazing Numotion customer!! #Numotion #mswheelchairamerica2019 #standforlife https://t.co/hsRWo5BvXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauramdempsey @nyknicks @Matteo_Marzoli @TheGarden https://t.co/ZVpOWEyyBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trublu24 @PhilomelBooks @PenguinClass @wcswmslib @wcsWMS @WCSedu @Bigdaddylattin @UTEPAthletics @VandyMBB This was… https://t.co/532GxBpE1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Los amo familia y amigos... esto también pasara.. Dios nos cuide siempre.. de su mano todo va a estar bien... fuerz… https://t.co/pWLj9UT2KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I’m watching Sabrina on Netflix - this doll look like my neighbor]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The majority of White Americans hold their wealth in home equity. They are living inside their bank accounts” @leagueofcities]]></document><document><![CDATA[Official: 11 hours plus time differential instead of 16 hours rest and shortening the race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Broussard The Lakers were the 4th seed until Xmas. Parker is a Bron and Laker hater!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m legit happy with my life. Feels nice to say that. I might be broke, but I’m happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyGirlboss Why would you ask someone out who is "in love with someone else?" Why would you want to get in the m… https://t.co/fh7S2mUggU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now there are 5 @ELSOOrg chapters! The impressive data from the jan 2019 registry @ECMO_Bob @SCCM #SCCM19 #SCCMSoMe… https://t.co/apJgMWgkSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[yearly cost of attendance at Duke is twice my mother’s annual income and basically what I make in a year now before taxes. this is madness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why snap chat wanna be playin wit me takin filters they need to tell fb to stop letting y’all go live 🤣🤣🤷🏾‍♀️I said wat I said]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leskocar @ashley_naimi @ADAlthousePhD @MaartenvSmeden @malco_barrett @edwardhkennedy @nshejazi @EpiEllie I’ve def… https://t.co/5EyqocTwxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1027KIISFM @jonasbrothers We stan the Jonas brothers harder than ever 🤩 @1027KIISFM #KIISJonasBrothers #Sweepstakes #jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see @1love_drea featured here. The #MagentaLove is real! @JohnLegere @CallieField @pscodeman @DavidCarey]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to @Chicago_Police #JussieSmollett walked into Central booking at 18th and State where detectives received him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump CC!. C'MON NOW! you must know how ridiculous that is. NONE of us wished for our PRESIDEN… https://t.co/2D1NLjIpXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nateryan @JJWatt Haha no pressure JJ, it’s not like Twitter will call you  out if you mess up. Nascar fans aren’t… https://t.co/4wLeD1PIxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone know how to fix ghost touch on iphone x because i'm about to... https://t.co/RxAvl2pifa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dasani water is a scam and I don’t care to talk to anyone who believes otherwise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué tal gentuza! y una policía muy débil que debió aplicar la fuerza a estas malcriadas y conchudas https://t.co/KGZnqoVNTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Those lights up there… they’re not like anything else in the sky but they shine the brightest.”    @Dusti_Bowling… https://t.co/h5N7jDEUso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatGrant7777 @TAASAA1756 @SjiKKQ5GxHivdqC @akomama_tm @juwadikimiyaho2 @marinavibu609g @waelkr2 @hijaze82… https://t.co/Oeo1YVBs1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[A dark cloud hangs over @sarasotaschools with this decision. “I don’t want this to be a trend that continues, that… https://t.co/sfl5Bqz6Pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrozcoRosalin @DiegoSuarezM @JohannaGiraldoG @BluRadioCo EXACTAMENTE así fué el contexto de la conversación esta m… https://t.co/fqCxxX7pyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laying the digital groundwork for #BlackHistoryMonth project by matching scripts with digital photos that will serv… https://t.co/hS4k12MokP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t get to say anything when you’ve never seen high school musical]]></document><document><![CDATA[With Trunited, you can earn an extra $500/month or more without changing the amount you already spend on shopping.… https://t.co/wZt83qmgQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men really are scum bags. How you gonna make a Valentine’s Day and anniversary video for your girl when ur texting… https://t.co/zjHZkkdNgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DanCovfefe1 Ok let’s investigate EVERY  deal the past 4 Presidents made!  Geez stop the hearing circus!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland What exactly are PREPPERs Prepping for https://t.co/rQ8hUfO4DE https://t.co/C2sWoIXiVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a beautiful (and chilly) day on the Destin Harbour with our @embarcresorts members! #embarcevents #sandestin… https://t.co/4NtdJuIQ0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitegirlsmooth @JennyMcCarthy Can't be Anita Baker she isn't old enough]]></document></documents></author>