<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ScribeUndead "Are you seriously telling me I'm not oppressed enough?!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NastyIsland Is @BlueBarronPhoto there? Then we already know what’s gonna happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_chadreynolds I still can’t get over it.  At least I have my casino trick; they can’t stop me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLE_Online A smaller shielded speaker would be nice. I used to have a couple of those.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I present my featured talk on the Art of Digital Storytelling Monday at 2:15 in the ballroom.   Join me if you are… https://t.co/y8ZGClSsR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernard provided a great spark off bench last week but no @richarlison97 is just criminal from Silva... #EFC… https://t.co/qNiFGydeLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI (and we understand if you did): How do the @Mets prepare for #SpringTraining2019 ? They go #shark fishing  https://t.co/5ilEwmv42W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @MaddowBlog It's very clear that you're full of shit MSN pushing your bullshit we don't expect anything less https://t.co/TJ3R20y0OT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish that the @NHLBruins had Shawn Thornton omg. @NHLBruins you absolutely need to sign a #Tough Guy. It’s only g… https://t.co/HQ46PwMQtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dead Man's Cell Phone presented by The Comrades 🎭 #localtheater (@ Greenhouse Theater Center - @greenhouse2257 in C… https://t.co/9bc464eQd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovingAretha Well after reconsideration we’re not sure... the block may have happened years ago 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[SNWJ: The Emotional Mess Series: The Old Town Bully   https://t.co/mK9N5BEF5f  week three in the emotional mess series]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Pollinger @JonHeyman Can be looked at as a starting point in negotiations numbers wise or can be looked at as… https://t.co/idX8ZiWC3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbyL66 I don't need suggestions. I comment on what I want and do it factually. Have a good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[You'll loose everyone. They will all move out like there doing there in New York and Virginia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[City:  Hey SNC we're a little concerned about allegation of bribery and such the feds are investigating,like, anyth… https://t.co/gMB0cPdMt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[love how all the sharks fans are being babies but earlier in the game were calling bruins fans babies for bad calls… https://t.co/QWxZspN8gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump You have to forgive Lori she's just stupid. No clue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @GTSFarmer @realDonaldTrump Between this and the "love letters" from dictators and Chen, I'm starting… https://t.co/Hz994hEa0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigpartyjoe I'm a healthcare executive in Nashville. Your writing is fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hecpara I have been there. Flew out several years ago to attend a 🏈 game. Want to get back out there soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexRileySN @ByAlexRiley @OwenHassellSN @StarNewsVarsity https://t.co/dxy1JZM4CP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goofy in the hizzy.  #goofy #gooftroop #goofymovie #disneycharacter #disneyland90snite #tomorrowland  #disneyland… https://t.co/YAMSolryTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisvirtel @joereid Leave it to the writers to finally get something right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sisterofasavage how would she know they’re mad , she must’ve asked about them 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertdryer @CorbyAmos @skymcm In our conception, to be Father is distinct from being God, because the Son is God… https://t.co/anfq9KbZws]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #EastWenatchee #WA  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/d5MJhoQ197]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pez5683 I actually like the switch online stuff. That said…I’m hoping SNES games are announced soon….]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Missandei on the throne? I miss sum? How that promo even make sense?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buat yang penasaran kenapa Minnesota bisa disebut Winterfell-nya Amerika, bisa baca-baca di sini yak 😉  https://t.co/u8efrdHLLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A convicted LIAR testifying before LIARS, doesn’t get any better than this! @DonaldJTrumpJr… https://t.co/LFFkOGBy4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plz check out my take: Geraldo Rivera: If Jussie Smollett’s attack was a hoax, victims of real hate crime will pay… https://t.co/fP6EEpQx8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutSpok32579262 @memphis_tom @USAsunrise @jhopkinswx @EdPiotrowski @SC_State_Parks @MyMyrtleBeach @HariG_IN… https://t.co/tYmwqsuhq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaroSos1 @ArthurArkush No safety can say no to 45 million guaranteed..have to take that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC7Chicago Congrats Tamron .....Children are a blessing from the Lord ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday run, 3.16 miles,  44.50 minutes, #run,#running ,#runningman ,#runningmotivation ,#runner ,#walker ,#walk ,… https://t.co/JXq0BysmZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a little bedtime video before you hit the sack tonight, but before you do, stream Shallow. #gaga #ladygaga… https://t.co/nswcBVQApr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tips for making cosplay:   1. Measure twice 2. Cut thrice 3. "Ah sh*t, I'm out of fabric."]]></document><document><![CDATA[People say that the Oscars don’t mean anything and won’t affect you. Well I just stepped in dog poop while wearing… https://t.co/WE12dsu3zL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChronAVT Over/under 28 feet for the longest 3-point attempt of the night? Not including trying to beat the buzzer at the end of a quarter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bag she really really wants ❤️ (Photo: @glamandposh) @ New York, New York https://t.co/siBeMuxGeQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was well aware she did wear Nike. Just wishing we would appreciate and highlight her achievements a bit more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BisonsCelery @news4buffalo @BuffaloBisons There's just so many things to like about this tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sigtruth @TravisRuger @realPolitiDiva @JGilliam_SEAL @realDonaldTrump Retard, the government pays for the healthca… https://t.co/ORn5pI0x8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@downwithtyranny @saikatc it used to be the john birch society was on the far right fringe when I was a kid. Now it… https://t.co/oZ5P6vog8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KannonShanmugam Remember the cardinal direction your train was going when you step off of it onto the platform, an… https://t.co/ZgaMgCtuya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow take a look at this! @panasonicusa #panasonicsl #newcamera #newlensmount @dkhauver #dkhcinema samyscinemaworks… https://t.co/hzrDGFWrjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job has made me very emotionally resilient to a lot of shit, but it hits different when it’s someone you work… https://t.co/pMrfvdVKr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrantTufto Thanks for the invite, quit hogging all the kisses for yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBS " Even if Thing's aren't Alway's Great for Us "..... https://t.co/1HId1MV84W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachChrisRich @NorthCarolinaFC @USLChampionship @OCSRaleigh Thank you Chris!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaheimFire And not to mention how long that car has been there. If it was literately parked 10 minutes the undern… https://t.co/fiYqD2g1G9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePackageJG @warriorsworld You know he stuttered cuz he know Steph for sure better than Kyrie 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got Marketing? Getting pumped for #robinsbigseminar today in Nashville! #MSP @ Hilton Garden Inn Nashville Downtown… https://t.co/mjTbh5u9Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to my watering hole to have a nice, peaceful cocktail with those I know ... and instead, have this guy standing… https://t.co/0p0TPljuTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get what ARod has done in the past..but what he’s done for baseball in the past couple of years..the insight he’s… https://t.co/pDvFXejick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hpicciotto @MarshaFosh73 So....when they are perpendicular, the result is the reflection. When not perpendicular?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top power play comes out as Crosby, Malkin, Kessel, Hornqvist + Schultz. #DKPS #Pens #Sabres]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest concern with these attacks is who they are targeting because they don’t like what they represent. Sooner… https://t.co/aSgYqUgSc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notdetails A lot of my friends are locals, some work in tech and some work in the beer/food industry but maybe I j… https://t.co/GL37cEGupM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @realDonaldTrump Lies liesnajdnmorenoutragous lies.  All you people know how to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarayJer @BernieSanders High military spending is not an excuse for letting kids die because they can’t afford insuline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG in between sleeping on the plane I started “Russian Doll”. Hilarious! Love Natasha Lyonne in her role, except for her IDE 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 @AbeCheyanne Right went to inaugural n applied for 2 positions https://t.co/SAC6t2Z5yM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was convinced going into the game (and still am) that Zion v Maye was a major advantage Duke. But Maye is a good… https://t.co/mKn6LVrtAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's going to be an incredibly fun, family-friendly event as always. Saturday, May 18th at Sunset Hill Farm County… https://t.co/12Mgvs4NdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great young man! Love how he has worked to earn this! Also, such a great job by the HC to inspire and help B… https://t.co/tnpYAXFIvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advertisers Boycott YouTube After Pedophiles Swarm Comments on Videos of Children: Google said it had deleted the a… https://t.co/FHk1qCSStt]]></document><document><![CDATA[El silencio no siempre es cobardía a veces es prudencia y otras veces inteligencia... en Sacramento, California https://t.co/5Yx8h2PiGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day PSA: pornhub premium is FREE today and while you’re down there give yourself a feel for @testescan!… https://t.co/LxYLtuWu8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unsportsmanlike conduct to the max.  Bailing on the tournament doneeeeee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5NEWSJoe @weatherdan @5NEWSGarrett @KATVToddYak my lunch.  I started my tv dinner diet Today.  I tried last year.… https://t.co/E4B9CHjyLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a leader who is full of who ignores the experts which are trained in our nation's security but follows prop… https://t.co/RcWxmu22Yp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband is out of town and I fucked up my diet really bad and gained back all the weight I lost so I might be super depressed about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Será que van a demorar lo del 9 hasta el domingo, a ver qué tal anda Valencia de nuevo por si alcanza con él, Sáez… https://t.co/BK2BYylWJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec A bigger mistake would be letting a fool like you back in.. You play the game you pay the price !!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be cool if the team cared enough not to get utterly shellacked. #rctid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @dbongino Obsessive hatred is a poison that you drink yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to head into the weekend like...😎 Super excited to tell you guys I’m headed to Minnesota for the Let’… https://t.co/X74su856oU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of riding along with Oxnard's finest yesterday #ThrowbackThursday @BDP_Christian @SPGJESS https://t.co/S1WwqAFQHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VEcholsWFTV Praying for your hometown and all hometowns in the storm path. May God encourage the able bodied to ru… https://t.co/60hGGRBpM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamestown, NY tonight Friday in the Tropicana Room!  7 and 9 pm. Tickets:  https://t.co/rgpgWXyn2v. @ntlcomedycenter https://t.co/FAz0cpmkBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day to submit a talk proposal to #heweb19. I already submitted 2 but was thinking of maybe submitting a third.… https://t.co/6POf67xbpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAgness @NBAAllStar I get that, but I'd still say they are represented. All a matter of semantics, I suppose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulDHeenan @nodqdotcom How about I give you a little taste of how they micromanage their employees you got a hair… https://t.co/lFxfcgQwcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShesMJacksonBad Fair enough. Defenders of child rapists are typically affect-proof.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roads around Fremont @OmahaWXStorms @NWSOmaha @omaha_scanner https://t.co/A3nzBMBeQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zander9899 @Target Me on the right, can't beat a good Titfer and a lardy! https://t.co/HKVNmeSdWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ60487505 @3YearLetterman @realDonaldTrump Please let us know your findings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Bloodline Nitro Blood Orange Ale by @flyingdog at @citytapcle — https://t.co/F36xUCFPP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duke, which just returned to #1 in the AP poll, starts FOUR Freshman. How come Duke doesn't have problems due to their youth? Hmmm #pcbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WEEI Coincidentally, that’s the same thing Kraft said to the prostitute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOLO!! SEASON 7!! #fortnite #fortnitememes #fortnitedance #fortnitely #fortnitelovers #fortnitebr #fortnitestreamer… https://t.co/id4fvmNMzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianBeckcom @LibertarianBlue Um, no, it is what she has said in her own words. Last year Texas Monthly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteBayshore @Luke_Sonnys_ I was nailing it Tyna Luke tried getting involved 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[They hired that group of people and all the regulars quit and it went out of business. They were annoying and weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yassymonroe Bitch you out here tweeting on the dime, how lit are you right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking sex vs gender in class tonight. It became a little tense. It’s hard to not get pissed at people who just ref… https://t.co/cCnrXLJmnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @BoeingDefense soon for some exciting news on EA-18G Growler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trashpandas New hat and Tshirt. Now, just need @MiLB season to start! Hurry up already.]]></document></documents></author>