<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@rottzillasgirl @OriginalFunko @tattoo49ers @laura24fan Thanks Rebekka!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Family Business: Successful Succession Planning  https://t.co/Spr6yZfaFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michie8 I thought the same thing. A lot of whiners amongst the people that are making it fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tampa Florida stop showing off! Enjoy your Saturday.😌 #floridapalmtrees #palmtreelife #palmtreelover… https://t.co/gdlodVuG0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Myrna Quintana working 24/7 not only with an awesome team but with good friends like family that always back me… https://t.co/kPj62tnR6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Wow what a speech !!! Nancy please say “Thank you President Trump for all your hard work” someone had to do it -you couldn’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MailOnlineVideo @CentralParkNYC @MailOnline Share away! Thank you for the credit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I really really wanted Nolan A. even though I knew it was a Pipedream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before you Ask me for this absolutely delicious simple recipe… It’s collard greens 1/2 cup vinegar. instantpotoffic… https://t.co/fsdXPOA1js]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tarastrong @HamillHimself @RealKevinConroy She may have started in the animated series but soon after entered into… https://t.co/vgF1Y3jDDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatGuy4442 The outsider is a continuation of Mr. Mercedes, finders keepers, and end of watch. Excellent, excellen… https://t.co/xzuMGQwSMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Diva's Headquarters in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/eIXQ2VKmDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABFalecbaldwin Tor Johnson from Plan 9 from Outer Space. https://t.co/l9i6sXVlo1():format(jpeg):mode_rgb():quality… https://t.co/E4QolGqYmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drump commenting on Cohen's testimony yesterday, "He lied a lot". Wow, isn't that the pot calling the kettle black?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PlayStation Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/AX4vpuBqEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy omg just saw @TODAYshow ur baby boy Benjamin is gorgeous so happy for u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mr_skeels This is awesome! What a great way to keep all students involved and motivated!]]></document><document><![CDATA[U is smart, u is important, u is loved ❤️ - Samson Marvin, 2019 https://t.co/OhGsQqdNG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanMacKayPhD @JadamJay @StephHfitness But you can’t dispute the male physiological and anatomical  changes that… https://t.co/0SREyDDlaK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC I can't wait to C U locked up along w/ all the other MAGATS!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron57407963 @420Sincity @NickCannon @MaskedSingerFOX 7 solo &amp; 3 with the Pips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinoGuz hahaha oh i forget you’re still kinda new to it. so with every comeback there are multiple music shows whe… https://t.co/PAs4N1s6MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter was in Annapolis today marching in increase funding for education..Advocacy runs on the family..so prou… https://t.co/4IlZKx7qpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModernTimesLB Well at least @SecNielsen has her designer water to quench her thirst. #ResignNielsen https://t.co/ChxjX1A2uh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Is Mexico paying for it? Because that was his promise😂. You must’ve went to trump university🤣.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those of you following the ITF, its new World Tennis Tour, and its upcoming election for president, here is a l… https://t.co/ss5LlVycLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyhawk It made my heart swell when you told her to not go toward you, but to go straight...her response was to h… https://t.co/pSV8XZ4SYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo Even if i did things like that at all, even if you didn't have an awesome wife and 3 adorable kiddos.… https://t.co/gycjntvuIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Until a young person in Port Harcourt has the exact same opportunities to learn as any of us, we haven’t achieved… https://t.co/g1cLLApYr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog wakes up at 6am everyday to come to my room just to continue sleeping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady and how about 45 getting away with bragging on grabbing women's vaGigi's. #angerierblackwomen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelmcdaniel01 Keep swinging Bub, they want be able to catch them all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyGirlBoss Hay Jr. where did you say you got your Ph.D from? Oh that's right you don't have any Ph.D's. so sit… https://t.co/MSZlWmcfXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavinmbauer remember when i got that water on the way back from AC and I had an ad for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay I need someone who bakes birthday cakes lol tag if y’all know of someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT 👇 Special additional grand prize: 10 tickets to #NevermoreFilmFest Fri-Sun @CarolinaDurham:… https://t.co/gT9ec92alJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Bren has never NEVER asked me for money. That does not make me privileged! But if there was ever day she neede… https://t.co/HHH4auQK56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntiekiva @NKOTB @DonnieWahlberg @joeymcintyre @dannywood @JonathanRKnight @jordanknight #GriffyMac is a heartbreaker!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HernandezMhaila @iammendozapau @sanya_lopez @ShyrValdez23 Dead si sanya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myths are not scientific fact — it’s depressing that this is not understood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a birthday in the shortest month of the year is a rip off I didn’t even take advantages of any free play or… https://t.co/GO36Rjnqs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t fear commitment, I fear wasting my damn time with some lame ass🤷🏼‍♀️🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all loved that training scene, now picture it with: lights to fucking see 🤯 #ShadowhuntersChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are a few days late but it turns out our First Valentine’s Day was the same day we turned 5 months old! Lachlen… https://t.co/ERUnz2pbjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Agreed! I cannot stand Miracle Whip it tastes like a combination of butter gone bad mixed with way too much sugar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had several scoops of cookie butter for breakfast and I feel great about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itscedsworld My friend is planning to retire at the @Marriott with all her points]]></document><document><![CDATA[I once went to a JoBro concert in New Orleans with my friend from Houston, then woke up at the crack of dawn the ne… https://t.co/TeRowL6oyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love surprising my girlfriend with flowers just to see how happy she gets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylieJenner  the bitch gotta go, sorry i know that’s your bff but if she really was she wouldn’t have put you in t… https://t.co/RMlhvrtBKr]]></document><document><![CDATA['Zombie deer disease' has impacted wildlife in 24 states https://t.co/mP6i0jnrdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sinned12342 Not the few I've had to deal with in the last hour....😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelieinTX @MinutaeForDays You're welcome. I totally understand and it's so very hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all all said y’all wanted cold weather well here y’all mf go so don’t complain smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radkeylimepie @DonaldJTrumpJr Oh tell us which one specifically he should worry about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicekeeler @shirky17 The design makes sense and it’s easy to locate the information you might be looking for. The… https://t.co/dKebdhxZO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very true! 😩   Study Finds 80 Percent of Female DIRECTORS Made Only One Movie in 10 Years (Exclusive) https://t.co/STPAwG0dxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched so much Midsomer Murder that there is a bird/fox screech that’s always in the nature scenes I find sup… https://t.co/yRtckQEluf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi 👋🏽! My name is Lala and I’m just a gun all around Cali girl really into food, cooking, travel, trying new things… https://t.co/6mBgBeZs0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your coworker walks by and says there’s pasta in the break room...🤦🏼‍♀️girl shut up #givemeallthecarbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey there #UMCGC19 - the Mennonites prayed for you today. We prayed for justice and inclusion. We prayed for every… https://t.co/gkpUuDQXbf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another RC120 is on its way to a customer!  #construction #faeusa #rockgrinder Learn more about RC rock cutters:… https://t.co/n7qjlOmmpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sister, Sister Star Marques Houston Engaged to Girlfriend Miya: 'I Said Yes to Loving You Forever' https://t.co/2cSYl5aZOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am very simple when it comes to nails, but I’m not paying more than $65 on a basic full set. lmfao. I understandi… https://t.co/1cQfBb6kUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cwhitesellstem @CobbSchools @STEMcobb @KSpringsLions Congratulations!😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani If she’s that limited re:the language and history,what is she doing in https://t.co/8J38CbYy9B can yo… https://t.co/twVO3w8EMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amanda is a movie that was deeply affecting and gorgeous but one that I’m gonna enjoy talking about more than I enjoyed watching it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day today.. I'm spending it picking up tree limbs from yesterday's #Oklahoma wind 💨 😩 trees are highly overrated!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dave_landman13 @MichaelJSams93 @DemolitionDan @KathyMu87484671 @shearl_d @SkyviewKevin @KamalaHarris Do you not al… https://t.co/MEfdWBOmVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews I'm watching my favorite show w/my favorite SC Senator!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚀 https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum #RickRock #dope #westcoast… https://t.co/1ZRE421L9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im an asshole! Hahahahaha  #homesafe #syke #immadick #sweetdreamssweetcheeks @ San Jacinto, California https://t.co/SLNSJMO4TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CherylWellsWAHM @ThatEricAlper My favorite song in the world! I had chosen Funeral For A Friend... but you've changed my mind 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[My angel my sweetheart my hero. Just my reason for being. My heart https://t.co/BZsyHOODXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closer To Fine At 30: The Legacy Of Indigo Girls' Spellbinding Singalong https://t.co/FWeZTqt0ZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest painting “Healing Emotions” #art #artist #contemporaryart #montreal #decorator #texture #interior #beautiful… https://t.co/ry4rNcYrpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vafordman @fox5dc Thanks! It's about 50 degrees colder here than it was when we left Hanoi! https://t.co/Tlzb1P5yAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Future "My Savages" (WSHH Premiere - Official Music Video) https://t.co/biUu0G2303 via @YouTube https://t.co/cQjdz2ybXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cricketcrocker I wasn't expecting this in my feed and I full body snorted before my brain even fully processed what I read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i do shit from the heart simply because i remember all the times i wish i had help .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading home 🏡 so extremely blessed to have been taken on such an amazing trip! 🙏🏼   #TravelDate #TravelCompanion ✨ https://t.co/2YkJhYBoDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UcResistance All sane females ask that question. These are the men who are still stuck in the days when the women… https://t.co/zrFu0xwWSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[forever on a quest for amazing bbq. this place was pretty fantastic. ➡️ all of the spots on this map are on our lis… https://t.co/vk8WwEK2Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinesbryant Hey girl hey 👋🏼👋🏼👋🏼👋🏼 come on over I have some unfinished dinner from last night too ✌🏼✌🏼 oh is this off topic??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IkaRuss6 @PrimeCreator2 @MAGAforc @JeremyRobards7 @elskemccain @hmcd123 @mona_cajun @WYATT251 @staggerlee422… https://t.co/A4EDZDeiCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason has always said some vile shit idk how he is still in this industry getting invited to high level shit - “she… https://t.co/m4jCWGSvnE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JournalismIsNotACrime ; #journalists @AP @Reuters @Bloomberg @AJCglobal @Sfchronicle @sacbee_news. @SeattleTimes… https://t.co/VrM4UldiWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulyShore I will be on that stage someday!  I’m going to be hilarious at 80! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE Went to see #FightingWithMyFamily with my wife for my birthday. Just might convert her to a wrestling… https://t.co/3iERGOmLXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realtor #acronyms #mindofarealtor #ronisterin @ Cooper City, Florida https://t.co/wXxrRibzaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GizmosCookie It ain’t never about the color/class to Me,a thief is a thief. That sucks,I wish I could catch people… https://t.co/EtwGnn6igV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bruce35dc @SonySantaMonica @corybarlog @StudstillS @Sunnysuljic4 @iamchrisjudge @mattsophos @RichardGaubert… https://t.co/bOUokaAEhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharedMotivati1 Good Morning, JuJu! Your opinions are right! There is nothing when you cannot trust the word of th… https://t.co/ETYXf6vrcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrassrootsSpeak @siano2020 Also other prisoners unless he gets sent to club https://t.co/UWU1dtyS2K virginia]]></document><document><![CDATA[#newkitchen #mirrortile #refinishedcabinetry #farmsinks @ Lake Forest, Illinois https://t.co/hil4lV0pUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Love your Per day (yesterday) ❤️#nationalloveyourpetday https://t.co/eBJa62tkqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legal Notion is getting geared up for season 2 everyone! Only on, Facebook Watch https://t.co/wDUVxOemO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[. 💛🔹️☀️🔹️💙🔹️☀️🔹️💛 You have power over your mind - not outside events. Realize this, and you will find strength. 💛🔹️… https://t.co/6j1FudrMik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how my love life turned upside down in a matter of minutes. But it’s okay, I’m not gonna be sad about it, especially not today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGWOW1 @UncontrolMarie @alluring_blue @Gisy_Angel @WolverSteve @pheltzcomics @jav5022 @bronxfanatic @ItsNotRevenge… https://t.co/m7UuFrAaU3]]></document></documents></author>