<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Reuters FACIA-L HAIRS TENdE-RForA-L  A FACETTECAFE T HiS.   A  .NoTE             ETATE THE UNITED ETATES of A--Mer… https://t.co/MTryWttVaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hustlers On The Map, In Pursuit Of The Scratch.   #mardigras #mardigras2019 #neworleans @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/NK7KLgUDMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakers. #longbeach #sunshine #bluesky #california @ Downtown Long Beach, California https://t.co/GdvlYOcIZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opuntia Microdasys Bunny Ears cactus + heat pack included in price https://t.co/yR4axEaC6X https://t.co/N9g7kurhXZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jingleangel @septheunicorn @NBCNews well you might want to hope he gets a deal done sometime cuz Seattle be one of… https://t.co/WYe1iw7txr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think about it, the common practice these days of #DayOne #DLC for #videogames is incredibly efficient - it… https://t.co/sffcmTC03i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivalaclocks @PhilCollinsFeed Love your vocal so easily understood words in all ur music.. thank You Phil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly, some people don’t remember the sacrifices made to save the world from evil and preserve the liberties we sho… https://t.co/69xSs1DFN0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found @YHSPodcast after new GB announcement &amp; have been listening weekly for last month. @splash_mommy… https://t.co/SOyLzrZdeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@narendramodi @PMOIndia To my fellow citizens   Darn   Lost connection...🎬 https://t.co/ItugxO75IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Salmos 122:6-7   Nova Versão Internacional   6 Orem pela paz de Jerusalém:     “Vivam em segurança aqueles que te a… https://t.co/lFUTqRXNjE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50F10ULE votre opinion est aussi importante que celle de la majorité des gens du milieu pour confirmer tes dires d… https://t.co/1DmrgY51pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheClothier @BankofAmerica @selectbank I'd jump from them. Cut the dead weight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[March is the treadmill month ❄️❄️ @ New Hope, Pennsylvania https://t.co/YeI9TBeiJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a strong supporter of Prop 206, you can count on me being a solid NO on HB2523!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fatbaldguyracin Fun fact: Xavier actually means “turnover machine” in Latin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Males are known to build more using their hands in the past! Not saying true now, my gals love their LEGO! I love t… https://t.co/eDrpMdIgNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesmcelweejr @cbouzy They have all been read twice and referred to the appropriate corresponding committees. You… https://t.co/ydzsEAjag2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing to see here. Just the most flagrantly corrupt administration in American history, where paying guests of th… https://t.co/JIGqqOcOCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siggyflicker @tiffany_annx3 @A1_Buckwheat @lisa6654 @chickencounter @Moe_green7 @evsmom @Tits_Deep @MCM0NA007… https://t.co/67S3GsocOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  WE will watch this space.. Rick might be right.. but if he is wrong and he is shocked.. will rick have a hear… https://t.co/4jhpiFoWgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devonte4Graham out here speaking his truth for all of us Jayhawks who have been suffering heart palpitations for a… https://t.co/mpzuVIFey7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using IVF the average net merit of calves would be $862 vs $778 using a mixture of sexed semen, conventional and be… https://t.co/tRc8aeHk4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney on Ice with the family. I have a deep connection to Disney classics, but we can erase Cars from history. Seriously. It's awful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump No.  He needs to a thorn in the DEMONCRATS side]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering if @aafp and @aafpprez would be amenable to the idea of moving the Washington chapter’s office to, say, P… https://t.co/5VFzwGmZI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aftncanada Or Reyna not being suitable to play on the wing, when in fact a natural number 10 doesn’t exist in the… https://t.co/SMBPCGIRp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest News:      It's a good thing: Martha Stewart partners with cannabis firm;       Cruz warns CPAC of 'unhinged… https://t.co/fqdv1azioT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Únete a la discusión en la Cumbre @AACSB para Latinoamérica y el Caribe el 17 de mayo en @FAEexternado en Bogotá. E… https://t.co/OC7kyIPwha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes a picture says everything. #Statechampions #basketball #Wyoming #Whsaa #fortheloveofthegame https://t.co/oTwesUuBIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surt_lab I kind of see #TheSmallMasters just smiling at us indulgently and putting our articles on their fridge wi… https://t.co/gJimmiJqnO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joe_weller_ Dude, we need to hang out together on one of our birthdays in the future. We’re the same age!!😁😁😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let prayer be your first response, not your last resort.” Joyce Meyers #closertoGod]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful Sunday here! We put out the dollar bins like last summer and the doggie water dish (and we still have a s… https://t.co/5fSHJT7JzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hurtling toward that last draft—this one’s about ready to start making the rounds. #writerslife https://t.co/h25RlXqrgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without him we are nothing.  #Godslove #lovingthelord #havefaith #Godspeople #humbleservant #blessed https://t.co/pcxzGWjEdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe we just start reporting when they tell the truth.. assume everything is a lie until then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilvinaFlorida Plus the machete would be handy as well given the government has confiscated their guns. You are ri… https://t.co/g3g6TXKbMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tumbaburross @socc_tavo Tú chaquetas solo recuerda por donde entró el espurio de Calderon a tomar posición y por d… https://t.co/kjCGu4IsRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James_Barragan Those fights with Barrera were epic. Middle of the ring trading blows. Neither one backing down. So… https://t.co/318am5jJ7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSN: thenightmare778  Mad because he lost with the three shortest players in the game in @NBA2K_MyTEAM triple threa… https://t.co/GiAOt0xQnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payless going out of business and having a huge sale. I’m bout to have so many new shoes for hella cheap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If they were not who you were taught they would be, would you still believe? • • • • • • #TimShaw #sculpture #art… https://t.co/rkEiKiiykm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go world, take something awesome and make it annoying and stupid]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you vote for the promises of the Dems, the only thing they guarantee is poverty and misery and that way they wil… https://t.co/2aeaZyE26R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UbisoftSupport I can’t log into my account because of 2 step verification the google authentication thing is very… https://t.co/KtpOEvXkho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @ZeyuRen - very interested in your work and would love to connect. Can you please follow me back so we can DM?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d drop money for an ass reduction if this was me. I know her back hurt 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the greatest tag teams ever and now they are 2019 #WWEHOF. Congratulations @RealStevieRay @BookerT5x… https://t.co/MAOQ8UTpsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grbibb Yeah I'm that weird guy who likes cold rainy days but even I've had enough!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to believe but there are only 4 more home games left in the regular season for the Bruins. 7 of their next 8 s… https://t.co/XYH6K6oiRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkZinno Are you also annoyed when flight attendants refer to a 'full and complete stop' or your phone being in t… https://t.co/So6sNVkM0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Influenza y Recomendaciones por temporada invernal #SaludSonora @SsaludSonora @Enrique_Clausen https://t.co/T5xw5Oq1j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next weekend is going to be incredible. Absolutely can’t wait to see these 4 teams compete for a title. Hope you’ll… https://t.co/Tk6kSLmO5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BeatCancer follow your mates the population is much smarter then cancer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soñé contigo y me desperté sonriendo porque recordé que te vería más tarde.  Daniel Rodríguez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nadiadaar thank you for shedding a light on the data and facts around poverty and inequality that exists in our wo… https://t.co/DNkZWytSKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch with a view!  #golfreptravels @ The Bench https://t.co/cGWD0wGfka]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Jackson: broken clouds, 34°F 90% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1024mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conocen esta otra frase colombiana?  Arrieros somos y en el camino nos encontramos. Quiere decir que vida es larga… https://t.co/qNmGXybY57]]></document><document><![CDATA[What am I doing at 2 AM? Finding this picture of Quaker Rowland Ellis’s estate in Wales that is the namesake for Br… https://t.co/NDtTQXOSYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[X-Men has the best transition of characters in any series I’ve seen... like how they switched to the young actors a… https://t.co/er3SeQVAIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pair of Double-created Cormorant #naturephotography #wildlifephotography #Lumix #birdphotography https://t.co/ywbcCqndVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand Hey Roger be prepared. Make sure you wear 5 pairs of underwear unless your into boxer shorts and s… https://t.co/bqfEneIe6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chucktodd Like everyone else who has become entangled with Trump he will regret this. This will be a permanent sta… https://t.co/6joPnoWYC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erieforage @pwrliftnerd @walker_lockard @The_RyanHoggatt @jahillegas_51 Spot on! Plan-Do-Check-Act.  I haven’t rea… https://t.co/a3276YqNzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess who WONT be #1 come Monday? The same team that literally ONLY had that one accomplishment to hold onto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forest king #TedsLittleDream  A different take of my guardian of forest. There’s just something mysterious and magi… https://t.co/xbGbWVoQQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recomienden rolitas para escuchar con una cervecita en mood tranqui... Algo así https://t.co/KEut4EPwzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephen_daly I did that too!?! In delamont with Orangefield primary school!? Maybe it was just us that had to do i… https://t.co/fgeVpnNYdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all the guys and girls who ain’t got valentines tomorrow, I might give you a strawberry https://t.co/nhTbhefsVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wanna call you babygirl and feed you chicken nuggers but you can’t act right 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatsMrNeil After this fake scandal we can see how fake news is manufactured in Canada in mainstream media pretend… https://t.co/Mm8B4qS8bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @GameStop you guys messed up on GSTV. Metro already released. Not on 2/22/19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my Guy jak.e1 to eustisskatepark For his first trip out there🛹🙏🏽👽🖖🏽🛸 👀 it‼️ 📹 filmed 1/5/19 📹 Proceed to Get L… https://t.co/RUPnp4GeOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooked beef short ribs for dinner. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/2xHWzvc4V1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evil: Oh, Benson... Dear Benson, you are so mercifully free of the ravages of intelligence. Benson: Oh, you say suc… https://t.co/P0agg8EIjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewardessChick Weird, your Lyft driver told me it smelt like ass too...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's 'Word on the WAY' is Psalm 59:16 from The New Living Translation of The Bible. It says: ...   https://t.co/DLFbZFmqr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siqueirosdavid *screams* "LOUDER NOW, LOUDER NOW."   (Please God be what you were talking about....)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElzaSeferian @hragv Using, but defined not as spoken/typed out but as being "used"]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for my forever #Valentine. I love you, @MandersPE! https://t.co/DDwOlrUfZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao aim is terrible mf missed and hit the ppl that don’t want shit from her nigga]]></document><document><![CDATA[The devil is fighting you harder because you're close to your breakthrough. Don't quit the game! God owns and contr… https://t.co/juL5KijFxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TysonFoods Bullshit. Your only goal is to extract the most profit possible (for your shareholders) from those farmers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your waiting on your ex to get back so you can leave to work ugh.  I need a night baby sitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillsmereHealth @JRNLive @JRNHeadlines A Japanese one through a PNP set up I have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw this cat on my commute today, I have no more cash and my dignity is no longer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherEric Greg from Clifton received a similar diagnosis a few months ago 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryVellequett @Automotive_News One of the best who will be sorely missed. Best wishes for the next phase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryancheets That’s the answer! None! They ALL have been nominated! https://t.co/eNiE2PVg75]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t deserve @_rone and @calebpressleyxo Barstool Travel Show: SEASON FINALE https://t.co/0iBoUvY8Ka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup, there is anti-Semitism, then there’s the “real kind” of hate we really should concern ourselves with. @EMET4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly a month from today I'll be making my annual pilgrimage to Coachella, spending the night at the Morongo Casi… https://t.co/tOtFgFh6Ak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Owes Unpaid Taxes and Faces Campaign Violations - Jail Time? - https://t.co/7BQgrn0eYR @AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PluckyChicken I don’t even know what to do with this. A lot to unpack here...as there always is with Alex Jones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennymckeeDenny @AndrewScheer @CPC_HQ The facts are, there was a racist element within that convoy and it was obvi… https://t.co/125kCXuQRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, hey park vloggers: you're impeding traffic, it isn't impeding you. If I say excuse me and cut around too, don… https://t.co/ujZojnuQpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnHilgert He is freakin awful. Send him anywhere but no ice time whatsoever!!!!!!!!!!!! The Blues need to fave t… https://t.co/2MsBpolJgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSpain Kudos to other team for continuing to pitch to her. Wow. Great feat!]]></document></documents></author>