<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Imagine how many people have been buried with money, expensive jewelry, valuable things...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nigerian superintendent Veronika Openibo demands that the training of priests be fundamentally reconsidered. "I… https://t.co/22PoNgGZgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okayisbenja @JAGIJoeShow @Xaib416 @StephMcMahon @WWE @itsBayleyWWE @SashaBanksWWE @BillieKayWWE @PeytonRoyceWWE… https://t.co/OMwDeGgjej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oberreimer @CaththeWineLady @SteenbergWines @winewankers @DemiCassiani @wineworldnews @Julianna_glass @suziday123… https://t.co/n8jvk2hane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rook is no rookie when it comes to being adorable! The 3 year old chow chow mix can be a bit on the shy side but lo… https://t.co/7HzZxuBADD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@themexicnvictor FINALLY. SOMEONE WHO UNDERSTANDS AND APPROPRIATES A GREAT DAY IN THE NATIONAL CALENDAR https://t.co/PvYbspDUiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[comedy is good medicine. Narcissist Ex: How To Co-Parent With A High-Conflict Ex, According To Experts #comedy… https://t.co/vxLf4X3sYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom, can you just give me money this year? #teens  . . This one turned 14 yesterday. Baby of the family. ❤️ Used to… https://t.co/0UB9FSZiGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trish_regan @AOC I doubt that the dem party want to put her on display in that category 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[En unos momentos más estaré con @sergiovallep en @NTelevisaSON   Hablaremos sobre la problemática de las estancias… https://t.co/cikkD3HxE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting times! Modern fragrance design is to California like wine is to Napa. Thanks @Allure_magazine and… https://t.co/4YFSnbH5Zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro It's a smoke screen...useless, toothless... what is it actually going to do?  Could you whip up resolut… https://t.co/JmjmWPfkZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSusanDavis build the wall, reach out to the families that have lost loved one’s by illegals, you know the borde… https://t.co/wkkl8Y5FtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️Good Morning Beautiful Ppl #goodvibes #goodmorning #goodmorningpost #goodmorninginstagram #goodmorningbeautiful… https://t.co/c2Ypfpy1V8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@court_morris_ Timeouts at Disneyland are super fun, too. https://t.co/yGCUv2Rgel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredithMalbone @KempsAcademy @KHS_Chiefs Tickets will be sold on his website.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mia's Brooklyn Bakery - @miabakery in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/2ywLwkFKJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peak!  Yummy smelling bath bombs!  My doors open full time on Saturday February 23rd and my Grand Opening is… https://t.co/DajKjE1IbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefOfBcrk @kirasroth I'm condescending?! You literally shut out an entire group of people saying they aren't val… https://t.co/GQdLjUJwE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydmcgee_ Happy Birthday queen lets go to Taco Bell because I’m so lit right now okay okay okay okay😃😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the point in talking if no ones really listening to what you’re saying??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamTheFro @MontanaLives me: wow thank you for this promotion  FBI bossman: so here is your new desk, and oh, this… https://t.co/H2tqJ8OvSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless you @KyleKashuv... even due to the circumstances, you confronted him respectfully.  #fixit… https://t.co/NwNPNkCu4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[he’s still little but he has my permission to wool another kids ass in self defense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauroTravieso Eso pasa en algunos bares de esos.... es parte del paseo.... ¿te gusta Ushuaia?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michellemalkin Well,  He's Dead....  As if he deserved an apology anyway 🤣😂🤣😂😂😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBQ sauce on pizza?? Ummmm... count me in! The hillbilly pizza at @waynespizza is so unique and awesome! A must try… https://t.co/VbomDPa7zm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zohie_dysert I would if u didn’t live literally across the country from me :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems @SpeakerPelosi @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer How about investigating… https://t.co/K3PK2C3uyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[just because he didn’t abuse every boy he invited into his circle doesn’t mean he didn’t abuse some. it’s like some… https://t.co/8L1fGD0yNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big crowd at the RCV Town Hall event in Concord hosted by @VoterChoiceMA, where they’re discussing my legislation,… https://t.co/CQSwy4txyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[the people at the eye doctors all seem like they are in a bad mood and I am uncomfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DawseyOncerJenn @gilesmatthey I’m going to tell you what @gilesmatthey use to say to me and I remember his words e… https://t.co/UocU2KASXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is he running as an Independent...or muddying up the Democratic  primary again?  Don't  let him get away with it.… https://t.co/CyALh8ozxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dead asf y’all niggas do the most, how is my ex gonna message me from a mutual friend of ours snap talking about if i miss them 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[freudian is that one song i skipped over too many times and i finally fell in love with it.. daniel caesar i am SOR… https://t.co/2RDWgCWCkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uber drivers really be the most interesting people when you actually talk to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[She remembered who she was and the game changed! 🙌  Happy International Women’s Day to all you AMAZING ladies out t… https://t.co/jvd75ari4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dacheteur @andylassner @joanwalsh @TuckerCarlson 🤣😂🤣😂🤣😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/xmfFrDpeJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GingerJoye I know you're gonna wanna see this.. 😁😁😁💕💕💕https://t.co/IyoVbOeIri]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋Serenaaaaaaaaa🎾🎾🎾  USA🇺🇸USA 🇺🇸USA 🇺🇸  Hope you feel better. See you next year💪  #SerenaWilliams 🇺🇸… https://t.co/Fq3ANRk9SO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Edoar1956 @patrickturner91 @kmbrlyfrs @realDonaldTrump There’s no shortage of oil or oil suppliers. If you support… https://t.co/C00ddQQkBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh yeah, Michael Cohen went to Cooley   https://t.co/mgtN9XXBbH #MichaelCohen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aninick4n6 @rafaelbryantt Omg I’m sad for us but also so glad I’m not alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @PanoramaHSD2 for fostering great leaders. @SierraHSd2 here they come. Go class of 2023! https://t.co/0GhDW4SNjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive   Let’s become The Three @ Five.         @greggutfeld @JesseBWatters @DanaPerino]]></document><document><![CDATA[And what if Alexa decides she didn't like the tone you took with her last week and decides to punish you for your "… https://t.co/K4yNVqdXrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any #gamers out there that like to watch streamers check out @sarahjosoprano on twitch: Strawb3rrypuff   She is fun… https://t.co/JhfCt8Miup]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many times do you have to tell someone not to do something before they actually stop doing it..... 🤔🤔#AskingForAFriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Paczki day!!!! #fattuesday #paczki ##lent #haveagoodday #behappy #beblessed #bethechange #realestate… https://t.co/eqJtPz9N5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courtesy of my pal overseas, Japan has peach coke! #QuestionOfTheDay Would you try it? I would definitely stick to… https://t.co/YgrhYXSblt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #BeaverDam, WI, check out this #SupplyChain job via the link in our bio: Night Shift… https://t.co/fVjbZakPyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[im always so nervous to tweet about vegans because i know they could destroy me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black will get you a handout &amp; a quick move up the chain no questions asked. Geez🙈🙈😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I tried really hard not to drink &amp; drive but I did it last Thursday” 😳 yeah I’m back at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had some messed up dreams. Looks like I’m not gonna be sleeping well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night I showed my daughter the full moon, and she kept tapping on the window saying ‘come in, come in’ and the… https://t.co/MeqPQ9uot3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champagnemammi6 We’re definitely not simping this year ! His lost 🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of the @ConsumersEnergy Foundation's support of Communities First Inc in #FlintMI -helping create a… https://t.co/UPNPL5tpdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Where is @RepMattGaetz @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows on referring @AdamSchiff &amp; staff over to the… https://t.co/xp6A7bF8xR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRam2 @bralyn01 If you think I’m bad wait til you meet Bralyn’s Mom. We all love our boys lol!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jh0anPhant0m It was dumb lit and chill and I met a new Leo dude with fire style lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do contractors wake up so early?  My kingdom for a “sleep in” morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump EXCUSE ME???? Your top people are falling..one by one.  YOU claimed that none of your people had R… https://t.co/0uEqGB5EMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@louisebrooks99 @tracey_thorn Yes, I was so disappointed. At least the season wrapped strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darth 😋 Gotta have a beverage handy tho, they dry the heck out of my mouth when I attempt to eat the entire bag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rweichselbaum @hoosierdfh @StanleyNattel @CJC_JCC @SCC_CCS @dominik_linz @Cardio_Girl @ICMtl Things may turn out O… https://t.co/YTVah3zti9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding out your pregnant when you’re only 3 weeks makes for a lonnnnnnnng ass pregnancy. 🙂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15RW15 Buna girls were in the preseason Top 5. After going (2-5) in week 1, they dropped out. Plenty of time to bounce back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Hey Lindsey. Here’s what you and I know- Trump is a festering boil on the ass of humanity, and you’re pret… https://t.co/BvYyxbk0iG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heughanthings Oh wait that was uber in Hawaii lol https://t.co/rF2OD04iZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrScottLads @MSNBC @CNN @nytimes The #Constitution grants us a right to privacy and THIS invasion of privacy from… https://t.co/tfRHh7Goov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clauersen @LDNLibraries I wanted to be a teacher and a radio DJ. It turns out that I was both before I became a librarian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachEMcCracken It’s only 8 for a few sessions. Two of my players are moving and we added the 8th just so he’d be up to speed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy valentines to the loves of my life @ShawnMendes and @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistyonpointe @UAWomen @StephenCurry30 @UnderArmour @warriors On point!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Beau1969 @swicklepus @Revitalized_Dem @CapnMAGA @BwaHh @ricklundl @cspanwj @nytimes @katierogers Godzilla may hav… https://t.co/4TyDFkzG3H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ideally I want to have a natural birth if I have children-watching these clips once would’ve scared me now I’m just… https://t.co/j6cJBDVo0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I: wore a jacket with elbow patches, helped prevent a fight from escalating to physical violence, and had Xav… https://t.co/7yUTMnsbWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would like to know how i was capable of writing two pages (front and back) worth of words in 45 min when nowadays… https://t.co/bmc4ILtYAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep praying for the two guys in Havana! They are from the middle east #brspi19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lightwood Sibling night out!! 😍😍 @EmeraudeToubia @MatthewDaddario #SaveShadowhunters #ShadowhuntersLegacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple iPad Pro (11-inch, Wi-Fi, 1TB) #giveaway #win https://t.co/ZdShYV8Z14]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a Coachella weekend 1 ticket in the Las Vegas/ Henderson area! Dm me if you or someone you know is selling one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please explain to me the new Mathew McConaughey commercial? I kinda want to  sew my eyes shut. Thank god for tv remotes now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made this tweet yesterday and I expect that deafening silence to ensure right away😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing calms me like watching nice British people fretting over jam #GBBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[While in the @CityofTampa; we had to visit The Floridian, who was awarded "The Finest Cuban Sandwich on the Planet"… https://t.co/EZlvkAe2Jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put love into the universe and it will come back to you. Adopt a dog, do what your passionate about. Put love out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bichikobalandro @MichaelJamesNCA @PaulLeeTicks And 16 speeding tickets]]></document><document><![CDATA[morning reverie.(on ice). #winter #frozen #icefield #artistseye #shimmer #february #icestorm #frozenmeadow… https://t.co/KfeYVPW6yZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marnes @rumpfshaker Your problem is you think a person can be a Trump supporter/excuser/enabler/loyalist w/o becom… https://t.co/ZiIOIp0yeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too funny &amp; oh, so true. I think the govt. also gave a big can of Bulger. Who the heck eats that nasty tasting crap?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are now free to level up your life. @ True North Mediation https://t.co/4iVg3mlXqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[47 MONTHS! SOMETHING'S SERIOUSLY WRONG WITH THE SYSTEM! A black guy carrying a small bag of weed gets more.. #TheBeat #Hardball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLoradelaCruz1 @VConner13 Miss you! One of my favorite books for our principals and for the support of… https://t.co/xYDTHU3JpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training: The Indispensable Ingredient Needed to Contain a Deadly Ebola Outbreak in a War Zone https://t.co/uWhtFyKdPX via @IMC_worldwide]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Carolemon_ @TikateeOW They have Chocolate Chip cookies, Oatmeal Raisin cookies and Snickerdoodles. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking a selfie from below my chin makes me look like a wild boar, but when I raise my phone up, I still look like a wild boar. 🐗]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants.” - @KarlLagerfeld.… https://t.co/K8gjS0HHDg]]></document></documents></author>