<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Opportunities await for those willing to act. . . . . #fitnessprofessional #personaltrainerlife #personaltrainer… https://t.co/51iwqIBrhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs That would be a heaven sent gift...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oatmeal has to advertise, uses toppings to be different. Bacon is just bacon - smells and tastes good. You want to… https://t.co/eaaQIBCeU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lefebvre_jim @leonc626LA SoCal NRAE @lefebvre_jim on fire today during @SamsungMobileUS GS10 launch #nowteamSW… https://t.co/vQpwFEBaSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Love me not” next month 🌸 #newmusic #art #indie #hiphop #love #lovemenot #la @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/ArtfkYhHQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSea1964 Losers will say anything to get 15 minutes in the spotlight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me every single day when I look at my contacts and decide I can’t be bothered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dicklawfirm Hi there, I follow Jesus &amp; now follow u cuz I like ur Bio/Tweets, so wud u pls follow me back?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrasiTunity If you search my name and the college I went to the top result is someone who murdered someone like 20 years ago lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomfgoodwin Wait, those are the FIRST CLASS seats?! Have we reached the “no one is paying for these theyre all loy… https://t.co/lZ1Ckrn28f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tscinti @baseballminutia Thanks! I love Cincinnati history. I'd be happy telling these stories for the rest of my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perspective: The devils are all united while we believers are divided in our service.]]></document><document><![CDATA[JK FACEBOOK IS LIKE EVERYONE IS FUNNIER, PRETTIER, TRENDIER AND MORE ACCOMPLISHED THAN YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayleKing Gayle please help me convince @oprah and @ww_us  tat an ALTERNATE DAY FASTING PROGRAM developed with… https://t.co/hsO3k0ZfFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you like music? Would you like to put together a playlist featuring the likes of Bill Conti, Seal, Nancy Sinatra… https://t.co/8HHR97eBvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lance Stroll (lance_stroll) and Sergio Perez (@schecoperez) with the new look for 2019.  Good luck guys.. car looks… https://t.co/h2AxH6kuxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fear not, for I am with you; be not dismayed, for I am your God; I will strengthen you, I will help you, I will uph… https://t.co/WJBL5oD5uQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[TBT: On the Set of "I Know Where Lizzy Is"  • • • #independent #film #spain #california  #hollywood #film #producer… https://t.co/gzRFnbgtL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RRRawlings Sorry, I hate seeing anyone go through a Divorce.   It’s a horrible experience.   Prayers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimrome James.  We also have a fire up our ass. Thanks  Taco Bell customers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day. Salute to all my friends who make a difference in my life each and every day aroun… https://t.co/KhaqMddJaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulwilcoxen @jaredmac26 @pdcprepsports Stating hearsay of a merger is not the same as saying a team is in a confe… https://t.co/YM72CzxMBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know any Executive Assistant's looking for a new opportunity on a dynamic and innovative team? Our Corporate Accoun… https://t.co/xyF9umyFS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smiling girl needs neutered along with at least two of her cohorts.......how did she make out in her country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webgriffintales I read the Marine Raiders series several years ago. I found out that I had a great uncle that was… https://t.co/sMvqUKk7zn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stihl1991 @EastSideDave @RoyHarter @Flutesy @biga614 @bobo103nyc @andreafromslc @CompoundAmerica @TheESDS Heeeeeey… https://t.co/k1yZDMuCBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[US asylum shift targets Spanish speakers, Latin Americans  https://t.co/HfpUTvmoAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItIsUp2AllofUS @CBSThisMorning @CBSNews @GayleKing @rkelly So, I can’t express my opinion in the court of public o… https://t.co/zYhN8Iaiyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markkprater @CJMahaney @SovereignGrace It's evidence of the same arrogance that originally thought CLC could inter… https://t.co/UQGdXRLlOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[UVa switches up the starting 5 again…going with Clark, Jerome, Hunter, Diakite and Guy tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoWHS_Flanigan My inner child is going crazy ...1 day till #Baseball2019 season 💜⚾️💛#BaseballFAMILY https://t.co/ldYYu6HByg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been a digital designer for years now — i can spot an app filter from a mile away. 🤷🏽‍♂️. You still cute tho 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Others wrote about Randy Weibel's impact on the court at Hononegah. I was more interested in writing about Weibel:… https://t.co/rHgRwhuCRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, @TuckerCarlson. It wasn't just naughty. It was horribly sexist and degrading. By all rights, you're done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rrhoover @steven_feeney @geraldine Travis became a billion at Uber by lying nonstop 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rya_meyers @C_J_Boyle @ladychryse @MacGyverCBS @lucastill @LevyTran @jamesdevoti @AlecRayme @DonPerez777… https://t.co/inMrAAJLQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact of the day: President Lyndon B. Johnson in 1966 issued a proclamation honoring father's and the role they… https://t.co/kJRlyyGjw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PAMdemonium991 Good bye Pam take care of yourself, don’t forget to check in once in awhile so we know you’re alright.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple more photos from when @acolan1006 and I intercepted a supercell t-storm near Houston, MS. Some of the best… https://t.co/k91vXcGS9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take:  Black Panther should never have even been nominated for Best Picture, so I don’t care that Green Book wo… https://t.co/InBFyXo3Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe you didn’t mention Sam Smith or Joe Pernod!   I want to seriously say a special thanks to to them a… https://t.co/jCoggGt3BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltPress   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)  https://t.co/j0aZbvB0ii… https://t.co/f6ISC5ReA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost You go for it @washingtonpost you keep up the attack on the President with skewed facts!  You will get him out eventually]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatKevinSmith @captainmarvel @MarvelStudios @TheRealStanLee @Marvel Crybaby! 😂😂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hard to believe you don't know right from wrong Lieu. The electorate should not need to teach you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunyanhilde @poedavid @Spotify @amazon @AOC @SenSanders @SenWarren @CoryBooker @KamalaHarris @amyklobuchar @SenGillibrand Like @TIDAL?]]></document><document><![CDATA[His statement was written by Lying Lannie Davis (Clinton hit man). They have something on him. I feel sorry for him… https://t.co/MUpLh9cJdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[George Peek https://t.co/5j9os8TdQn Ran across his name in a BusinessWeek article. Somewhere in your family tree? @lizpeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markpoloncarz @NYSThruway @TheBuffaloNews @TJPignataro @WGRZTraffic @news4buffalo @WKBW @NewsRadio930 @WBFO… https://t.co/Ia8Lg46UQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffBills53 @ohhmik @Pens_Lynn @JodN20 @jhartlov @WestVirgYinzer @steelrzfan2015 @EHUNTER55 @WilleMH00 @jbange831… https://t.co/W9cYd9SXqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly British Film Festival 2019: As is the case with all things, Britishness comes in varying degrees. Last month… https://t.co/Pj8U68zM8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @ZeroBlog30 @mlynnicholson @PGP_Reviews @hamwich452 @isaaccsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice way to start the evening: Villiger Selecto #heistcanteen #charlottecigarclub #villigercigar #villigerselecto https://t.co/1fbXOjg0QI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did someone say Room Service? Fresh fruit and yogurt parfait to start of this Saturday morning in Vegas.… https://t.co/6qsyOuq2hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Belgian White by @BlueMoonBrewCo at @studiomoviegril — https://t.co/vX8b1GKUko]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s tough to balance sometimes. @ Queens, New York https://t.co/eVL1StL8kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tkachuk is gonna have to call Naqvi by the time this game is over   #vegasgoldenknights]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the property owner that takes in the shorts when property taxes are astronomically increased and upkeep costs s… https://t.co/mWINQOLWdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m drifting in and out of sleep but I think the fever is breaking. I’ll check in later. Please RT that great review.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xaneonthebeat @pinwheelempire How you gon reply and then block me so I can’t even see it 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a blast to talk about X Caesars with the great @heymiller Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newsjunkie3 @mcall @JamesTaylor_com @PPLCenter Thanks for the feedback. And mostly, thanks for reading!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordDusto @tb_crypto @NotHentia @KrisAmber799 @letanimalsbe @JoshuaBomb @realUSDOE @GobAbiertoBOL @AOC Odd huh? I… https://t.co/tW2mHq6shE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCDavis01 effort at the 7:45 mark in first half set the tone!!  Please somebody send me that layout dive!!!  👀🔥🔥🔥🔥… https://t.co/a27wiHHBWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Channel 31 in Huntsville Alabama is working illegalls https://t.co/8TUsQ9zzaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Raw from last night. @WWE do not bleep with me &amp; tease that The SHIELD is coming back again. #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE that @RepMarkMeadows was called a complete racist by @RepLawrence in front of the world. Thank you! It's abo… https://t.co/wp71VoMaM9]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Questrade Why is your customer service so inept? What happened to common sense? For a service that is predominant… https://t.co/VxRObHUTzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[College of Science and Technology faculty meeting. No snack or beverage in today’s meeting. Hard to listen these pr… https://t.co/U1aGYVFXbR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yfreemark My mom gets one or two boxes a week of dog supplies for her pooch delivered. The boxes are about the siz… https://t.co/Judhvwo4kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Paddleton is a fantastic movie. So simple but so powerful. @MarkDuplass and Ray Romano killed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do the idiots keep saying the drugs come through the ports of entry, ports of entry are just where they catch s… https://t.co/wFUv8DVlmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seananmcguire @cmpriest @MandaTheGinger Did they warn you the cat would be the size of a large pony?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonBordoff @MattBakerEnergy @greg_ip @pisaniferry Hum, the truly honest thing to point out is that we will no lo… https://t.co/pjGreJ9RcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the hell go ask for Vodka on the rocks . Lol you a killer in the making]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kavmac @MathieuFleury @ottawacity @ctvottawa @CBCOttawa @OttawaCitizen @ottawasuncom Same everywhere. Saw someone… https://t.co/qeAIu6Zxlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually don’t go this route, but if you’ve been scammed through an online dating site and would be willing to tal… https://t.co/RAzy44vwAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get those miles in for the  #BostonMarathon 😉Went back to the #HokaClifton4   Now Focusing on form 🏃🏻   tha… https://t.co/xoLAIO2KxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popular opinion:  If you wear these, plz stop 🤢  Seriously, you could fuel an entire McGregor fight with the amount… https://t.co/TYIqfGeyPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrecho el poder del pana! Desde allá pisó un botón y dejo sin electricidad a Venezuela... MOLLEJA E FALSOS!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can I not stare, the way that you're glowing I am your nightmare, you don't wanna know me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve wholeheartedly decided that my future baby will be named abstinence, but everyone will call him Ab, no one will ever know]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman is a gnat.  If she ever becomes bigger than that, a cockroach, the American People will step on her like… https://t.co/NsgLCqb2xT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrokenplate Stainless steel is great because it can take a real beating and also a heavy cleaning. It’s Neitzsc… https://t.co/MQuBbQqKFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day for the Trojans in the Trojan Classic Tournament at Troy’s Sportsplex. First Pitch starts at 4:30 with :… https://t.co/TFlLa7arz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Down four at the half, in that environment, is a win. Nevada hanging around on the glass so far thanks to an 8-3 ed… https://t.co/JqtgFSKaJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHE👏🏻WASNT👏🏻READY👏🏻FOR👏🏻 THIS👏🏻SMOKE!!!! @ San Angelo, Texas https://t.co/1Iz2TjE8Pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[rainy LA gives me an excuse to bring out my fave raincoat soooo... not too mad about it 😁🌧 📸: salmabustos @ Los Ang… https://t.co/whMl9fROqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your at the airport late when the board is that empty. @ Detroit Metro Airport (DTW) https://t.co/gY76i0Ymfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Sinclair after that display at 5:40 am I will no longer watch #WSBT hello #WNDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m adjusted to working over night, now that I’m home idk what to do. I can’t sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rikleen They’re helpful for overall assessments but even something like a 2% FG and .3 blocks difference can go fr… https://t.co/kg6y94hBE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner is served... Curry Katahar with hot Roti caribbeandelightsqv cdrestaurantandbar Happy Shivaratri chris_knows… https://t.co/KoS4BpZBO3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow found myself cleaning behind the refrigerator bc I thought I smelled something bad and thought to myself ha… https://t.co/Hz54MzVlwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so cheated we wont see #KendrickLamar or #SZA perform all the stars at #Oscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[January 2018 @Wendys Employee of the Month, &amp; January 2019 @Wendys Employee of the Month. #lovemyjob https://t.co/POBRMmzofM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithSmithNBA @Hoophall @TheSteinLine @nytimes @NYTSports @ESPNNBA @NBA @NBAHistory Thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember during the Obama years when someone was being investigated every week. Neither do I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hasn’t hit me that in August I’ll finally be in kingsville, maybe after transfer Thursday it will]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes YOU are painting Dems as left-wing radicals because you are reporting news.]]></document></documents></author>