<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[From owning a New York coffee shop to opening a Vegan Burger &amp; Smoothie Bar in Zagreb https://t.co/Qlk0ZGvERI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work lunch!!!! (@ Liberty Tap Room &amp; Grill in Columbia, SC) https://t.co/B6GQg4U7Lh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mac_Pro_AM88 The fittest man in history and the NFL MVP who is arguably the best all around athlete at the most im… https://t.co/LKwnOZcYgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see what this R. Kelly interview hitting for..... got my premiere halal food here so I’m set]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait for the kool aid drinkers to cheer every time he grounds out weakly to second...which is a ridiculous amo… https://t.co/zcnrxT7t0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Cabarrus County, @philbergerjr greeting a packed house of Republicans at the County Convention. Encouraging vote… https://t.co/CnF5r8lcdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys basketball extend their lead to 13 with 4 min left in the third qtr. @cszscores @_shsstudentsect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klmr87 There was a guy one time at the tasting room so hot that I literally couldn’t speak in front of him, and I… https://t.co/J4ia20AFKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpearlman Can't help that you're too stupid to understand walls actually stop people and good guys with guns ar… https://t.co/MLzJOfpfym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Assyria15 Why do you concern yourself ab the past that you are misrepresenting? You expect me to believe you… https://t.co/uMD9VVjfEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got done explaining Medicare for all to a coworker who actually asked me to explain it. https://t.co/j4YqrXAv2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRA @RepDLesko #877877 Just text Brady to #877877 https://t.co/D9rQDyI0qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 minutes to go ... Country Day 21, Greenwood 21 #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops  @LCDSsports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsRadio930 @NYGovCuomo The guy who turned bathrooms into a hostile environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @Dirk_JDR up with the @mnwild for their gaming Tournament! Photo cred- @TDIHockey https://t.co/m1IIObRABk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCallanan @ThoroStride @Craig_Bernick I would say it’s the people who raise horses for the sales ring not th… https://t.co/1pUOgN5KTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SmartCities touch upon all aspects of the infrastructure, cybersecurity, services, citizens and visitors in cities per @LOrtona]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarettIsman @AndPacing Nice when you retire I’ll be interested in breeding to him]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what is my pet peeve ? When soccer teams have mascots of animals that are not native to the teams region. #Showerthoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arikadou @oasisoverwatch @timthetatman "make spaghetti? I don't have any noodles in my house" lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rzr #polarisrzr #rzrlife #utv #canam #utvunderground #utvlife #sidebyside #utvaddiction #canamx3 #sandrail… https://t.co/FXGT2frYxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord give me the strength to move forward, allow me to wear the armor of your grace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: The mother of the teen driver has confirmed the driver hit a fellow Lafayette student while avoiding anot… https://t.co/OffqAcYRe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Apalladino8912 @Orfeu_Negro_ @marxistfilm Puts him above average at worst without taking into account rushing. Top… https://t.co/TMfe6FJJWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Tasty IPA by @21stAmendment @ Leeswood — https://t.co/COaZUEN2aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gosh_ItsJosh24 @emmonsaggie Benefits of getting piss assed drunk by 1130 and ubering home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsiCohn @acwmc @WheelingNailers @FWKomets @BlakeSiebenaler @penguins @WBSPenguins @ECHL @JGfortwayne Wheeling… https://t.co/tBlyz4GZOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@walrus1963 @ryanjacksrytpeg @ccbasher That’s all you got? Accusing me of being Judgy? Come back with a better argument.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Franklin: clear sky, 22°F 48% humidity, wind 5mph, pressure 1029mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So was Lindsey Graham running for President? If not, your comment is lame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricJoh37288055 @Vazhog @jeffjeffries99 @Stephen57036680 @DavidHo66029379 @arkiegal411 @Kellie2727Paula @Jeff38152… https://t.co/6FKgJ0WpKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So now we've got Ivanka and the nuclear codes why not just pass it along at Disney World and let Donald duck and Mi… https://t.co/wrUtifen7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[god damn, new deafheaven track is the thrashiest they’ve ever sounded. this fucking rules.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilmingFrank @billburr Season 2 and 3 are great. You’re in for a treat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for KISS...  #rocknrollallnight @ Target Center https://t.co/c7wG8n1GJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebrittanyxoxo You are a beautiful image of a lady with the kindest personality I have seen for a long time. I salute you, cheers👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send it to us, that you light may shine brightly!!! @ Hughesville, Maryland https://t.co/REcAOnspYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[One very early #peach tree wide awake  in this #houston #texas #foodforest #backyardorchard #permaculture… https://t.co/oBIBeDVbVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monique__Luv Damn. Well hopefully everything works out..  anyway she can refund her tickets and you buy them off someone else]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's official......I'm a Northern Michigan University Wildcat 🏈 so excited to begin a new chapter in my football ca… https://t.co/sv5LbVY6MD]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE ARE NOT JUST A GYM!! WE HELP YOU WIN YOUR DAY OUTSIDE THE GYM EVERY DAY!!… https://t.co/XpKx0p14KI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family First Always! Friends is a misused word now a days, so i choose to share the rest of my career/life with Fam… https://t.co/Tpf3l1X4na]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheElishaFelix @AddyPeters Ummm I clearly still shop there since I could make that observation 🙄 balling on a budget]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day thewolvesdtla ; thanks Isaac! #ValentinesDay @ The Wolves DTLA https://t.co/WWdIlj2ef6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening Ceremonies Briarwood Little League #briarwoodlittleleague @ Santa Clara, California https://t.co/jPJwfI1Fxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my mf dawg @CarsoniHodges . One of the best days of my life !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying a Wychwood Brewery Hobgoblin Traditionally Crafted Legendary Ruby Beer 🍺  #beer #cheers #wychwood… https://t.co/q2A55iAptk]]></document><document><![CDATA[You must be gettin' after it when your sweat pool starts to resemble the #Punisher 💀💪🤣 https://t.co/FoeqRh0coT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElwoodBluez @realDonaldTrump Same here....Connecticut is becoming a third world country wanting to become SOCIALIST. Time to move out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyBrownG @momo_nv @teeenaww You should think about changing your Twitter name @momo_nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith Feel so bad for family, don’t know man when a cop tells you to stop you really should stop . It’s crazy… https://t.co/mTDBNscPXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scwills Well ya know this year just started... you can make this one a little better if you wanteddd... but then again #meh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in this Friday NBC 8pm!. Prison life gets complicated. @NBCBlacklist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of my comments about how “Bones” would change the industry are finally coming true]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaydajusa Yes you are a sexy female. But I never see you get fucked. Never. Drooling over any female i can not hav… https://t.co/4UNmKiNVwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jw1605 @HoardsDairyman @GHGGuru I agree. But, people in my neck of the woods will use yours and other's tweets of… https://t.co/vjbOYdJMVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatDStat He has been solid and consistent for many years now. One of our best open field tacklers. It would be a b… https://t.co/ahESTcC4V5]]></document><document><![CDATA[An NYPD detective was shot and killed tonight trying to prevent a robbery in a cell-phone store. Gut-wrenching and… https://t.co/5UFo8ZDufi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have I not smoked w Byron. I need to experience. Dude use to have me dead in choir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh bueno este HDP justificando que no se le hizo servicio porque no se pagaba por luz!!!! Maldita piltrafa y todo… https://t.co/MQ6gBokKsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[HeadsUp @himss peeps into population health and the emerging value based healthcare economy. Come to Philly for… https://t.co/tiKSgyXY6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter As long as the wall gets built, do you actually care about the tactics used to achieve it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak We don’t tear up the Constitution for Sandy Hook and we don’t tear it up for angel moms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PokemonGoApp you make it no fun to play the game when you pay to raid but can’t catch the boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Thursday! Coming up we have your chance to win #free breakfast from @Wendys plus our Facebook giveaway for No… https://t.co/Mz6w55T7nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrwphoto Most of the people talking trash about the man look bootleg themselves lmfao! 😂 he would take care of t… https://t.co/6r816BIHT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[3) CBP, which includes Border Patrol and customs agents, was also the target of 1,187 complaints of excessive force… https://t.co/ZhT2oY6sx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TillerWills1111 @CathrynTownsend @mskurtdemars @drmistercody @realDonaldTrump To be clear.  I am not down with mos… https://t.co/aGcP8Mojeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbrahamAlyzah @cowboys20041 @Black_is_back5 @dogthecat3 @bitterlily22 @Mharris888H @GhostOfTick @Trumpbane1969… https://t.co/4lR2mJrnhs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mo’Nique and Steve Get Real: Part 1 https://t.co/XmgzxqIcMW via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@golferinatlanta @thextra I hear you... 👍🏻 Although I am excited about Alianza Lima vs River Plate with Ray tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[I long for the day when that slip lane from Fulton to Lorain no longer exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@f3FruityPebbles @piratenation02 @Asbypirate @F3ENC @F3ChickenWang YHC let a brother down this morning in the gloom… https://t.co/k6YW98Ii7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these good looking, beautiful girls go out with these crumb bum, jerkoffs nowadays... it’s really ashame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair @annewinters @1ZackaryArthur @robtomham @JoeUgly @Momentum_Pics @TimZajaros]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rO81XFD4Qa  This song has been on my head since Friday and I love it so much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to keep votando por @calleypocheoffi en los premios Eres!!! 💜💜💜  https://t.co/GdpW9y80Ti 🤘🏻😍 https://t.co/727e5GdvdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i could hug all my friends who i love at the same time i absolutely would but my arms are not big enough :( my l… https://t.co/6LPnQBDiTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[-0,4 degrés Celsius depuis trois ans? Que va-t-on faire pour arriver à la fin du monde en 2040?  https://t.co/7AL8yLzGXf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My normal life feels like a vacation from all the vacations I’ve been taking so I think I’m doing something right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imisspoundsigns @Pillboxz @logophobe Tired, thank you, for your are a true and supportive internet friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OlStupidHeadAss @j_bellaire Well yeah. But that’s what I mean, he controlled where he went cause if it was a team… https://t.co/0JlUPO7gos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great @3M promo today at one of my distributors! Read a promo flyer and eat a Breakfast SLIDER!  Love you… https://t.co/twYWmVQphh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRivera23 @FlatgroundApp Are you looking for somewhere to play this summer ? DM me for more details on the Puerto Rico Collegiate League.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who support you. #bullfrogfit  🐸💪 @ Portsmouth, Rhode Island https://t.co/qLnif05G58]]></document><document><![CDATA[Election results in progress  Atiku won Ondo state https://t.co/1SZBn8mjY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question for #ModernAthlete “What about Curling?” @Gladwell @DavidEpstein @SloanSportsConf #SSAC19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have no respect for our military or Vets. All you are is a draft dodging chicken.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laikabird You can message me anytime youd like, though i might not beable to get to it right away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Midnight sees the light -- 4-8pm Sunday, WUBE, B105, 105.1 FM -- the Country leader in the country @B105 @Alex_B105]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 sometime soon, The House Democrats, will, get ride of Nancy Pelosi, and, will be the "House of Representatives " again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StyleLearn Thank you. I’m gonna try to do one today so I don’t worry about it later haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In whom ye also trusted, after that ye heard the word of truth, the gospel of your salvation: in whom also after t… https://t.co/a2t8wWr9XE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prattlandia Kinda funny...because Bernie started it in Monday calling Trump a racist on a radio show]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lobos shot so well from the line for the first 35 1/2 minutes. They got in the double bonus in 2H with 4:32 lef… https://t.co/tsrSYcwRNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[alllll i’m saying is the person who’s constantly making &amp; changing the rules shouldn’t be on a specific team https://t.co/OcjhORrcV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia You're one of my favorite comedians, your stand up and podcast are hilarious, and despite that this is… https://t.co/M4zshLgp8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicks think just because you had sex with them they can start acting like your girlfriend 🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar You knocked it out of the park tonight! Keep up the great work. Stay out of the trenches with Trump,… https://t.co/2y8X89bPwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaarioBrandon Underage drinking is still illegal. If you bitch, then get Congress to change the law.]]></document></documents></author>