<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@InHisGripIRest @JamieDailey5 @DaileyVincent @DarrinVincent @bluegrasslife45 Oh my gah, that's hilarious!!! 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Sisterhood Month, the chapter  is conducting an IG campaign. #PAACMomentinSisterhood.  These are photos posted… https://t.co/GNXNLyeZnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My church is a mean church.”  8 out of 9 Traits✔️✔️✔️✔️✔️✔️✔️✔️ https://t.co/DTHEGlHwpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cozzzyboyz @spacermase @Sirius7dk @TheChrisMosier @rachelvmckinnon People got hurt fighting? You dont say....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eymi_mailen @SAEED_Guide You always gain by giving love🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸🌸Thank you💗I'm touched beyond words.🌸🌺🌸🌺🌸 https://t.co/YWiVISCAjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dogs outsude going crazy at 5am, took me 20 minutes to get them in. Got out the spotlight and find they chased a ra… https://t.co/F4LKeTXxxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze I absolutely refuse to be  a wh0re. Go promote your prostitution sh*t somewhere else.  #KamalaHarris]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100PercFEDUP @kylegriffin1 @BillClinton @HillaryClinton We ALREADY Knew they Had SEX ISLAND !! Took you this Long… https://t.co/gwUFYcKTLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jake_Ansell27 @johnny_bankosh @FortniteGame I’ll play sum of that in like 5 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen A Florida judge ruled Thursday that federal prosecutors, led by a man who is now President Donald Trump'… https://t.co/EQwRyarxoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Per me marzo è giallo. Come le primule, gli ultimi mandarini, e un canarino che avevo una volta e che poi è morto e… https://t.co/J3XMaVowQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much interesting stuff in this well-written piece from @TIMEMagazine_ !  But I think it buries the lede: Poverty… https://t.co/zxwJbua8PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ending International Women’s Day and the first week of National Women’s History Month with a packed house of proud… https://t.co/682cpzFMKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BebeRexha Its just a lazy way to use the English language. Explore delicious words and delighful expressions inste… https://t.co/PbzRCMYnvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsallison @FaceTheNation @LindseyGrahamSC @margbrennan Speaking of mold in schools... ya know, walls don’t work, s… https://t.co/Bn3TGJ9Kw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soda!! Pop!!! Sugar!! (And don’t think because you are drinking diet or “no sugar” soda pop that this does not appl… https://t.co/ecEbryZtcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not a Showchoir Competition unless a group does a Michael Jackson song #MJ #Theevent]]></document><document><![CDATA[😩 the shade room posted @AriLennox. It’s over!!! No more late night shady lives. The people are watching watching now 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rj_cresswell Ughh I need this edition of Volo’s in my life and I can’t find it anywhere. Le sigh! I guess I’ll jus… https://t.co/FT3590ga0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bshsmspero You are the sweetest! Just remember I did not get here alone. I remember a very special teacher telling… https://t.co/0V3aFcD0CE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump The Russia Obama laughed at as not a threat and Hillary sold US uranium to? That Russia?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein But a poster accusing a US Democratic Senator as a Terrorist responsible for 911 doesn't.  Hmmm....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liesssss i have YET to meet a romantic stud cuz every stud I dated I was doing all the romantic shit 😂🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GovernorKayIvey Too bad you didn’t feel the same way about Puerto Rico.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WXBelk yeah i don’t want them crying again bringing up championships from a decade ago. let me hush.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheyanne woke up at 345 am and asked me if I wanted to make breakfast with her she said she couldn’t sleep cause she was hungry 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My child has Autism and it is NOT because of vaccines. Vaccinate your kid because these diseases can KILL your chil… https://t.co/Ue4cV3sVSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol I was muted from commenting in a dumb Facebook group about food bc one of the admins, a Canadian, posted about… https://t.co/ZcnssBAnjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp His cases in NY is even worse than Mueller's. Let that sink in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGS926 @Newsday Where love and charity prevails.  Instead if empathizing, there is only criticism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R3in4DL05L4G4rt @TheAvengador15 @lopezobrador_ Perdón  es difícil mantener  el teclado en español]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson Gee, you make an unsubstantiated personal attack on a member of the Democratic Caucus, and you’re so… https://t.co/sAzECbhaqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de llegar marido con facturitas en la mano. Soy feliz por unos días 😁 https://t.co/JstYIi9nGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lies. When are you all going to release the babies you’ve allowed this administration to brutally separate from the… https://t.co/KhUapVoxwi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for following me @SaintRPh . Your artwork blows my mind!!! Your commentary should be heard by everyone!!! #truth #art #artwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Pasadena Yacht &amp; Country Club https://t.co/NAbLKMrmU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread sparked fascinating discussion on free press, capitalism, and the Internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IKEAtkinson @ianxcarlos I like the idea of that. But mostly, I’m all “keep your fart dust to yourself”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBD to the best dad in the whole wide world. ❤️ https://t.co/qvS3yCgJGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyShoe0bsession Hey babydoll im wearing these hot shoes. What do u want to do im hungry im a kitty cat. And drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you know someone looking for a great #property in #Millersville?   #realestate https://t.co/FbQ51QHNXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triple D night time to get the dice rolling and Drink on.  #lilfroggie #adventure #tripled #dnd #dndndrinking… https://t.co/4RNPKINhnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasnt wearing makeup today and my friend asked if i was sick... I- https://t.co/GN0sWeQb4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petrogustavo Señor @petrogustavo, le dí mi voto de confianza en primera y segunda vuelta porque pensé que sería la… https://t.co/IlhZKcQv8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madmareseq I rode a dirty stopper for two years, she needed to be so micro managed and she wouldn’t jump anything… https://t.co/Ks2TJoftJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AgaO72 Pani Ewa najlepsze "odloty i polowania na dinozaury" ma po naftalinie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#daysminispoilers week of March 18th #dool #days  Thurs Mar 21 th @1CaseyMoss @TMegiaAI10 https://t.co/gjMKCbzauQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liam_twomey @HaytersTV @GerryCox @strollernick Thank you Liam! Much appreciated. Catch you soon 😊👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadameKarenina Oof.  I went directly from that class to a bar. (Admittedly, it was mostly to get food, but I also got a large beer.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @scottbails13 we will have to celebrate with chocolate on #OpeningDay ❤️😘🎂🎈🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMaeTay I spent the movie super angry at the gorgeous sets being filmed with a shitty fisheye lens covered in vaseline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the @stalphonsaDP chess team today! https://t.co/2UNJ74C8qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dog is annoyed with me for gently resting my feet near her face even tho it’s her fault i’m doing that because she’s hogging the couch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@petershearer on how to sense out bud to determine its quality.   https://t.co/RxfZZgjw0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XvnnyPhvntm @SageMeleney @benxhrgrvs I just feel like if she REALLY loved her daughter and wanted her family to st… https://t.co/597Hee2qmT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vgallassio @Phil_Ponterio @District31R @SIBOD31 @CWATSONHARRIS @DrClarenceWill1 @DOEChancellor Did Mr. Gallassio read this??]]></document><document><![CDATA[That funny feeling when you go to pick up your asthma meds from CVS and it’s $389 because your parents deductible r… https://t.co/Tho9AtMyKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAlexHayden Eh sleep is overrated. I’m up too. I better see an Alex Hayden appearance in the garage tomorrow. I… https://t.co/RsgpIicG7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[My take on this is who cares? When has this label helped her in anyway. I don’t see her taking up space in queer ci… https://t.co/k6yLB5OSWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabbirae21 with 20 -- YES 20 -- points in her team's last game.  Always more to come with this player. #OUDNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEGO movie the second part! (@ Hesperia Cinema 12 in Hesperia, CA) https://t.co/0ZaBNEuIQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me longer than I care to admit to realize how terrible and toxic this relationship was. I kept trying to be… https://t.co/xX6LnvoPeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elvisduran From NJ to Ohio to see @pentatonix at the Ohio State Fair 2 Summers ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all 🦈..... come join our #MCPS Team..... the MCPS Superintendent (Me!) is a proud Alum! Details below....I… https://t.co/7jNzGPoKyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chasing waterfalls.  - #sólisdefloresluna @ Brandywine Falls at Cuyahoga Valley Nat'l Park https://t.co/FEcuZvzyNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar You are the definition of self made, would’ve been more satisfying seeing you on the cover but also lo… https://t.co/kjuakhTF4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[78th Southwestern Conference 2019 💙💛🐩 Sigma Gamma Rho #PRETTYPOODLE https://t.co/MVbIyUrr50]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I don’t like the idea of songs going #1 by fans obsessively streaming. I would rather it happen organically  Me… https://t.co/mn2odAIctu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANNELAMOTT Another non FB person am I. Thanks for posting on Twitter @ANNELAMOTT Love your books, my early morning… https://t.co/FSqSiKGXl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @Emily_Stains413 to post covers of seven books I love no explanation —just a cover… https://t.co/4PiVNkVB9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamodaStallion Girl gimme dat pussy-girl gimme dat-girl gimme(x2) that ther-girl gimme dat pussy🎶🎶🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t breathe calling my parents still running. Screaming at ry to get a Uber for us to pick us up from the highway]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm really enjoying this #AustinHedges interview on @DSmithShow haha between Wil Myers apparently getting a spray t… https://t.co/GMWtzKBqs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReneeLibby2 I said the exact same thing the other day.  Yes woman, he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super LTD ed faux fur and sheared sherling collab coat pietronolita x @NourHammour #pinkasfuck #pietronolita… https://t.co/8KhG4QLrB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyblues @RevAdamHamilton 2,000 years ago women were chattel. I’m supposed to embrace that too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasminecainrock Good morning, sweet Jasmine ~have a terrific Tuesday 💕💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I told my astronomy GSI that I think the earth is flat” –@aisha_jama101]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinsonWoodrow @fieldcrestband @DavidDiehl20 @DavidJNann @wyattpauley @jaimewyattmusic @cookingmama48 @JenHeizer_… https://t.co/9ltxQkAl6d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have people in your life that require so much emotional work that you “just can’t” at certain parts of your… https://t.co/byXEBon5Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maduro announced that starting tonight, Venezuela is closing its border with Brazil, and it may do the same with Co… https://t.co/gaeCfWgZE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD LUCK, Candidates! May you all be game-day players and shine your best this week. #AdvSommExam]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey if Tampa takes Dallas to a Cup final and beats them, the Rangers have four first round picks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milo and I getting ready to sleep. Night Night. https://t.co/zDUwxNIndZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano What the fuck just happened here?  I just got on Twitter and everyone is coming for Sal? Um, a comedian… https://t.co/7V9RDQ1ICd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So i still cant believe im engaged 💍 &amp; how beautiful my ringS are 😍 .. #Stackablerings #2on #1togo #OMGGGGG 😍🤤😍… https://t.co/pZtSzzJXVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spontaneous dinner with just the 3 of us last night! I've missed this silly boy so much... there are days where I d… https://t.co/TXBmDyKFc2]]></document><document><![CDATA[this moves so smoothly and it’s such a VIBE ugh everyone listen to Rex Orange County pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetJoeLocus @K9starSarge Praying for them and ALL OF YOU precious family.  I 💙💙💙y'all🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided. Committed. Succeed. = chocolate wasted..... chocolate wasted is no joke.... but it was sooooooooo good.… https://t.co/0ot0X9eZYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever gonna tweet about this man all month!! 💜 #Bias #MinYoongi #Suga https://t.co/t9f7NcROxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RFisher59 @JuddLegum @itmediasentinel @TuckerCarlson @JennyCraig @SamsungUS @Bayer Oh, hahaha!!! Yes, it’s wrong!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethMaitlandDQB @YRInsider Yay.. You're coming back again to grace us with your presence! I wish you'd stay Beth,… https://t.co/zgV0aYU7Wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uɴɪᴠᴇʀsᴀʟ ʙʟᴇssɪɴɢs ❤️#blessingsonblessings @ Infinite Blessings https://t.co/UyqPKhEDpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[👩🏻‍🦱🦸🏻‍♀️Guys...guys...I have a hashtag now please use it #MarvelousMsLoughlin 🦸🏻‍♀️👩🏻‍🦱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taBoy_Geordi @ChontellNicole @DuckedOffOfLOVE YOOOOOO 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 i need to save this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Presumably in your case, all the groundwork was laid beforehand to prevent such an outcome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @DivaVinophile @joneill55 @jflorez @SideHustleWino @SashaEats @FionaMorgan79 @GailBenzler… https://t.co/87gQKDt2yS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@always5star @Visit_Morocco_ @FSSerengeti @TravelMindset @iexplore @SonyAlpha You’re so kind. I wish!! Any magazine… https://t.co/djGBCib0oO]]></document><document><![CDATA[this sounds so textbook and annoying and basic but its still this thing u have to explain to others]]></document></documents></author>