<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Recognizing Jeanette from the MET team for January MET associate of the month.@LaurenSmith0929 @armidalg… https://t.co/vBQXCyiMHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Court artist joanne Gervais 2019 trial sketches @ Frontenac County Court House https://t.co/Yfm1QqGvdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LtGovHochulNY What can we do to make surrogacy birth legal in NY #SURROGACY #lovewins]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand the lakers but just had to wear purple and gold again with my teammate 💜💛 @ Staples Center https://t.co/v9lpIPc9JF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dataandme @LucyStats @elizabethmatsui @jtleek Just a totally casual causal inference chat. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I ever lower my standards for a boy again will someone do me a favor and smack the shit out of me🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Banking on another snow day tomorrow which means we’re definitely going to have school]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lights are so bright but they never blind me ✨ #welcometony @ Central Park https://t.co/mU2aBRVUb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The blackness of  #NBAAllStar weekend gives me so much life!! 🙌🏽✨✨It’s really our pop culture #BlackHistoryMonth ce… https://t.co/9qgran8wto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a pic of me truly living my best life 🤩🤩 https://t.co/yvVWgbtwG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaigeChristieUK I'm constantly being told "oh I thought you were going to be such a bitch"...🤦🏻‍♀️ Do I need to be Karen? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A magical adventure around Burbank! #doublerainbow #incredibleviews #viewofglendale #viewofdowntownla #potofgold… https://t.co/eiEJ66GPNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating love at home, aka the Heart Rock Cafe 😉❤️ @ Downtown Little Rock, Arkansas https://t.co/YOS8qpOYzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handstandmom @LiveKellyRyan @NKOTB @joeymcintyre @DonnieWahlberg @dannywood @JonathanRKnight @jordanknight Honestl… https://t.co/KjLIqPskZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUNISHED 4 PROTECTING PRESENTS WHERE ARE YOUR CHILDREN? https://t.co/x9GqD3GOMg via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newhot899 @BradyJones899 @MaulerMauler @OneTrueRush CTRL + ALT + arrow keys for Jenny’s computer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uglyy_goddess GSNSHDNDHDHBCNXMXBCBSKSHDJWKKWJLNLMFAOOOOOOOOOO JAZMINE 😂😂🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the sweetest man for coming to visit me for Valentine's and dealing me being sick. @ Boulder, Colorado https://t.co/jMk6Q4GwTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday is huge now.   Bagley is ok + win Friday = all good  Opposite of either one of those things and it’s a major… https://t.co/KhlowwUFi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Probably the best election night of r country!! Just love it!! Especially to see all the pundits cry… https://t.co/uFOB0qTtsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[HARPY PROTOTYPE | 2019 | Wearable wing sculpture; Bendable Poplar, Vinyl, Stitched Pleather, Foam, Translucent Spra… https://t.co/ZQHKu7wzZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCantore Here is some video footage from the Chickamauga Dam in Chattanooga.  TVA appears to be proactive in pre… https://t.co/VtpspKwlJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of a sleeve, work in progress tattoo. #tattoo https://t.co/bZK39R5aKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside is our favorite place to be (besides dad’s side of the bed after he gets up for work at 3am). @ West Fork T… https://t.co/84XQSxVPCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Customer service bitch talmbout "let me see what flights we have for tmw morning?"   Me: Tomorrow morninggggg? Bitc… https://t.co/wCflIF5lKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unspoken New Yorker Rule #62: You must apologize to your cab driver if you’re going to Penn Station.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was gonna go to bed but I found cool whip in my freezer😂😮,it's ok I'm only 99 lbs🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[No school on Presidents Day = SLEDDING!! @ Arlington Heights, Illinois https://t.co/ZXpAeKRocE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WomenThatSoarAwards Airing in @dc_now @washingtondc today at 2 p.m. only on the @TheCW #WomensHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday reminder: No one is going to give you the education you need to overthrow them. #leapfroghacks… https://t.co/MrHTiT0ZUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't sell yourself short for those that don't see your value.  Change the perspective and go after those that see… https://t.co/Sic9GCHvil]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Surprising Cleaners You Can Find in Your Pantry https://t.co/MmGl1vcmKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no problem shouting 'SUP MOUSE I ain't finna ask for no pic son!" if I ran into @DonCheadle on a NYC or LA s… https://t.co/Jh5AS6XtKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided today that I’m not dating until 2020. Way too many things to get in order this year to bring another pers… https://t.co/MY6KrSO7W7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seattlesub320 Thank you. If I didn’t love their products so fucking much I would’ve demanded a refund months ago.… https://t.co/zDVMXU1XDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[custom prom by FumiDesigns  Now accepting new clients. Link in bio.  .  .  .  #fumidesigns #nycdesigner #nyc… https://t.co/dRdBNBhurn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GaryClarkJr @nbcsnl Great show💙 @GaryClarkjr Austin #ATX born and bred  Nurtured in the bosom of @AntonesNightclb  🎶🎸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días, mi querido. Papa ; Francisco . El Espíritu Santo, lo llene de sabiduría todos los días de su , santa v… https://t.co/8kYcOYuTUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Trump is like a working mom with twenty teenagers that hang in her at her job asking for stuff and thinki… https://t.co/4C9pcCrzR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he went on backsliding in the way of his heart. I have seen his ways... "Return, O backsliding children," says… https://t.co/Gn72JZRBHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieRi39597096 @ParryNormals I am sure they are!  Trust your intuition!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a wonderful visit at the @HashtagGallery! Beautiful and powerful works by black artists! #tdsb #blackhistorymonth #art]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislpontius @AnaMardoll Nooooo, don't let one of the worst offenders spoil all opera for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow first I love you. Second when are you going to do a Broadway show because you deserve a Tony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a @CommonCause petition: GOP Senators: REJECT Trump’s national emergency. Sign here: https://t.co/4yHFte0RYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk bout you, but seems to me that a full ride from Duke isn't cheap. Zion may not be making money but he's not pay… https://t.co/JAwiXUSQsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for coming out to read to our scholars! #SpringISDreads @ReynoldsElem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovely_haiku @Jerry_ceballos @batmaninheaven That took 6 1/2 hours? My huge ass tattoo only took 6😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does Ted really think he can take down Ben come on dude he’s on a mission to save Ciara step aside]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Hate destroys the hater, not just the hated.  To be free, you have to let go of hate.” - @JonathanSacks_]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VoteTheBern2k16 @mmpadellan @sahilkapur He was not perfect on every issue, that is true.  But he had to be realist… https://t.co/58osVG0QEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericswalwell @Rosie @HouseJudiciary Eric wants to know what we are waiting for? We are waiting for the chidren (of… https://t.co/HaKJuYOnAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The gay American don’t realize that Muslims will bring sharia law here thus ending the gayness in A… https://t.co/OCLyhI6feM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#winterwonderland in your own backyard! #winter #snow #peaceful https://t.co/eJrCSk3Mlh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Or lied about! My fear is that he’ll make up some crap about Trump, and start another firestorm! I fe… https://t.co/kjEVUoUwh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacPaschen @RogueFirstLady @Mastermind7864 😳😂😛😛😛 https://t.co/XBNzMk0ymK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so very proud to be a sponsor of Feast with the Beasts! Will we see you there?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IstandwithJessieSmollett keep your head up only god and you know the truth praying for you peace and love to you ❤❤❤❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dantej21 People need to slow down when it is snowing and this wouldn’t happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary cute https://t.co/1T5U8NB5vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more You BELIEVE in yourself,  the more other people will BELIEVE in You- @common https://t.co/5nzdjiMOvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BubbaJoeJimBob1 @busbee_deborah @mvj737 @StormyVNV @ChuckKeller14 @ashau68 @cspippin @Hell_HasCome @deepdvr1234… https://t.co/pFsN7hv7IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueMalley I don’t remember that one but I do like the one where the dog goes canoeing without his people. https://t.co/mzICnZ8Bes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesHo03148924 @JussieSmollett Lol! i don't think that it's going to happen though; i heard that his Network is r… https://t.co/6qvLUSMQ7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got into a car accident on my way to work this morning, someone ran a red light and hit me and now my car is tota… https://t.co/NGzXIFItsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[…and that’s all folks. The #MCU Netflix shows better end up on @Disney+ 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how much I want to relate to Buttercup, Bubbles is me. https://t.co/VW2wGxdHWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter the Wild Waterpark Giveaway for your chance to win a getaway to an indoor waterpark resort in the #PoconoMtns: https://t.co/y7OwtQzCPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz I would NEVER waste my vote on trump or a REPUBLICAN .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OK_Magazine No one cares. Had no idea as to who this girl was until Harry decided to date her.  She’s no one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought my best girl as my date tonight! #MamaMack #FOE❤️❤️  #SneakerSoiree #GirlsOnTheRun https://t.co/70m9B7GfTY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDRoseJr1 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @LizMacDonaldFOX @Liz_Llorente I’ve wondered who watches over DEA?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolannleif @mogaffney And do something with his hair, poor dear. A good stylist can work wonders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler  Thanks from the bottom of every true blue's heart! #GoJerryGO https://t.co/8sHXMEMQH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ashamonet @AYANNAJNAY my people ! may 14th !!! taurus szn is the best szn https://t.co/xYY1EfDIZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t want to give my NCA jacket to anyone else but my mini me Gigi!! You’re amazing and so deserved this with W… https://t.co/7Is0mIfjSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA He can keep playing if he wants to, he'll get shiny silver bracelets and ankle bracelets along with orange… https://t.co/TvzHttxG56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TS7Track3 Gorgeous, ready for it, all too well, call it what you want, enchanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched season 7 of #GameofThrones on @hulu and earned a banner from House Targaryen! #BingeTheGame with me… https://t.co/5G8rFpVw2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, you have no right to control my body or my decisions. Your gag rule keeps patients who get care… https://t.co/luXNxwzsOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speed Challenge MiniLab on the band practice field today in Integrated Science class! So thankful the weather coope… https://t.co/yjHEnfqzmS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnyrrahJ Wahahaha ay walang form kami momsh. Basta mahal ang dalawa matic na un hehe  #MarNigo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I still had pictures from my first rave I swear I’d kick my own ass for leaving the house like that at age 15 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could’ve won more but I just wasn’t feeling the matchups tonight. If anyone needs help let me know and I’ll show yo… https://t.co/aZmEC9O7Pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyday 🧡 beautiful 💛 #hmswoods @ The Red House https://t.co/TFjvVqPowp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissagorga @JuliusMichael Hair clips on fleek, I thought they were @jenatkinhair . The reunion you composed your… https://t.co/SXItwHPAV2]]></document><document><![CDATA[being apart from someone you truly love to better yourself is whole different type of emotion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollie_fishback @TaylorRitter16 @jessicalbright why is your face so fierce, you’re like 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great article if you want to understand how stupid biomass is. https://t.co/slY4aEvSgp via @voxdotcom @clf @MaryPFPI @CLFMoses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMac_1326 I always thought Protestants did not observe Lent. Turns out I was wrong, and oh yay we Methodists do bu… https://t.co/MRalDTmfMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in Aberdeen, MD? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/LFkFHkWNfr #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/09/2019 • #Art • #cottagepie 🥘 for #lunch 🍴 with #oatmealraisin #cookies 🍪 for #dessert 😋 in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻… https://t.co/s51J2U0oSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kassie, practicing her skateboarding... #SheIsASK8RGirl #BecerraFamily @ Emerald Park Estates https://t.co/Wk9S3mxU7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wait_about The person running the screening sort of muted the situation lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 Chinese  women rescued in Seattle #HumanTrafficking bust at massage parlors across the city https://t.co/S06XupXKTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 The parents need to teach their children to stand up for what they believe in. However they also need to… https://t.co/obrsYACrki]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have the right system in place things are just easier. #homeorganization #getorganized #askaprofessional… https://t.co/kcQ4aRHdHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s look up puppets, though.” -@KyMorland on YouTube at 2:30 in the morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People never tell the whole story just the bad parts. #sad https://t.co/GHHEvx9R7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s finally Friday!  #treadmillvibes #playlist #hitthegymharder  #everyday #fitlife #GOALdigger https://t.co/iATQP9BXHR]]></document></documents></author>