<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Headed into the weekend like... #shutupanddance #partymode #weekendvibes #custombranded #bars #NYC @ New York, New… https://t.co/NN9iDLywFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a beautiful family brunch with the roomies and lil bro! #SundayFunday #Lazy #Full #Brunch #foodie #food… https://t.co/kcHdzoJWDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously intelligence doesn't get someone a blue check. I was young but I don't recall Nixon being impeached.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedkavanaugh @SenFeinstein The problem Shane...was there was also NO respect by the kids OR the adults...on eit… https://t.co/j9Y2X3UgHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh; #CaptainMarvel. Not since 2005's #AeonFlux has there been a worse melange of bulls**t source material (MTV car… https://t.co/Z1YJQdtPP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Someone forget to include Eric in the poll or is he even less relev… https://t.co/476UYiCfLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh how you going to have me wait 20 mins when you have tables empty?!? Fuck Applebee’s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueKofi did the damn thing. Kofi F'n Kingston. Wow. Thank you for that. 👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👏 #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsthrowbacks @SNYtv @jwilson4real “say hi to your mom.” Pfffffffffftttttt hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! @aliciatillman talking to the @girlscouts about STEM programming for girls. Really empowering girls to go afte… https://t.co/GOlWx3hrO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alec_zamora Loll yea... usually if the first post credit super lit then the second not tht important]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your life be free from love of money but be content with what you have, for he has said, “…… https://t.co/ryODnWN2lW]]></document><document><![CDATA[That high fastball followed by that change up by German is as good as it gets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman AGREE. THE ENTIRE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION MUST BE INVESTIGATED.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to hand this country and what's left of our entire social safety net, healthcare, courts and much more to Trum… https://t.co/Dkwzub4i60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind-blowing stat from @DaveRandorf: Tyson Barrie is second only to Alex Ovechkin in PP TOI per game]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Lady &amp; Moscow Mules... @ Lake House Restaurant https://t.co/Iwb6r68hMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember like it was yesterday @USHockeycom @Olympics @olympicchannel @MERUZIONE https://t.co/Dx8DxY5c1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had forgotten how it feels like when the door smashes  your finger until this morning 😫😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuento los días para que corran a Solari Del Real Madrid. Que manera de partirle la madre a lo que construyó Zidane… https://t.co/NmjQLq3C5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/4) Example given was that Chris Archer, based on his stuff, should optimally start Mike Trout off with his slider… https://t.co/xeiyH4X1Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conservmillen Amen. Here in Austin, it looks like Thursday it’ll start being warm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My buddy @imcorinnemec made this for me like 10 years ago.  It is awesome!  I’m sure it is long gone off the wall o… https://t.co/BiUMHTvtKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost went to bed early but Premiere and Final Cut are racing each other on one Mac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen: that appears to be a sword https://t.co/8PgYI9qDVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday I lose it just a little bit more living at home with my parents]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update #3: Excellent #CSed conversations (as per usual). Many new friends. I even ventured outside and pretended to… https://t.co/3CqDGxOQNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeanandCuisine @jacqueline_xo2 I was NOT expecting that https://t.co/bkwQi7PdNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[▫️Here to improve not to impress▫️ USATF Championship this weekend. Running the 300 at 5:00 pm. Catch it on NBCSN 6… https://t.co/La2YtG4uTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewmartonik That would explain the fortress of solitude in Lake City.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oldie but a goodie! 🎥 - @thebroah @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/GlsAYMRDRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawyers use cooperating witnesses all the time but they make sure to have evidence to back up any statements made by said witness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fine Tuned by @Burgeonbeer @ The Wandering Tortoise — https://t.co/s3iVus8q2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_Jacobi Chopped up garlic and onions and rolled some sausage into meatballs and along with some vodka sauce an… https://t.co/TgJRJKQPIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paseo Santa Lucía!📸🚶🏽‍♂️ . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . #paseosantalucia #instagood #instagram #instalike… https://t.co/u215DMKjwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This GIF is 🔥 &amp; will inspire YHC as the Q is planned tonight #LostInYourBurpees]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...it is a $270, silent, 8x SFP+ 10GbE switch that sips power” MikroTik CRS309-1G-8S+IN Overview and Unboxing… https://t.co/nulOXoCZ8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Phillies need to send Herrera and a prospect to the @Indians for Kluber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PDXStephenG @theanthonyware Yeah bro. Took a hit to the immune system yesterday but I'm bouncing back today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He just wanted a little rough play... You didn't have to take it that far]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Adinkra #BiNkABI #BiteNotOneAnother --- #UsLiberty #SilverDollar https://t.co/O3b3waA3de]]></document><document><![CDATA[I posted a new song so I hope y’all like it and check it out https://t.co/9XdMJkmg3h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LinksGems @bedfordsprings That western PA golf is some kind of beautiful. Laurel Valley is in my own personal top 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DougNorrie I'm being a smartass, I know how much you love Trump, not. I seen several high ranking Dems wanna let 1… https://t.co/PPSWFWZlbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spilled my espresso all over myself god dammit catch me out here sad and depresso  ↗️ Promoted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpiniAnne @drewand1212 @An_Amish_Cyborg @PoluzziDavid @9NEWS Border guards overwhelmingly support the wall. Obama'… https://t.co/LFbvjT8uil]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the local pub puts 2 BrewDog claccics on tap...#agoodnight @NoHeath66 @BrewDogJames @BrewDogUSA… https://t.co/xu6OQvGQhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryAnnOlivas66 @catherinedoc12 @Nick_Carrillo27 @AthleticsView Absolutely! I’d do just about anything for #TheHerd love these kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mom_zoey @Ilhan Well.. I guess she missed this test too.... #Immigration #Citizen #USA https://t.co/tDccObdybQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHech What happened today to Paul Manafort was a total miscarriage of justice for the American people.   And i… https://t.co/aahq3vg518]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christoplack I remember Jumping Bomb Angels being so talented &amp; good.  Way ahead of their time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBourbonstein @TheRedFallows @GitGud315 @thecollinhill @sarcastable @Greg1313Greg @slowbeef @itsAmatiramisu… https://t.co/SSUg5bze8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crampell I should have known using that stand on Central Park South to get my eye tat done was a bad idea! Plus, t… https://t.co/w1ChWdb3bF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am going to try again and again and again...And I am going to look failure straight in the face and I am going to… https://t.co/hY4mVXc6nS]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Steez could see this he’d be smiling his ass off rn. #LongLiveSteelo]]></document><document><![CDATA[What Disney's 'Frozen' Would Look Like If It Was a Horror Movie https://t.co/uRAyDjaIJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we said with Brian earlier today, that magic pixie dust that was spread over VGK last season appears to be evapo… https://t.co/ZhJIKDEIYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This program feels like a Crockett program from 85-87. That's a good thing. #WWEChamber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FastCoDesign I love this satire! It reminds me of something…  https://t.co/VzoNuGled7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ike58Reese Hopefully @Bharper3407 is taking notes on what happens when you pass up Philly for LA #come2phillybryce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrvintageestate @AROD Bruh, I’ve been browsing twitter a lot today and this is the dumbest response I’ve seen. Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ziebasteve @FullCircleNutr1 Good thoughts. This should help. https://t.co/kBBPdatNqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericmbudd It's all fun and games until you have to build an ios app...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally some nice weather! @PackSoftball continues to be exciting to watch this year! #HomeRunMindset]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XYennial @mitchellvii @SoBeCruzGirl This case was widely covered in South Florida.   The Buzz was “the deal” was t… https://t.co/7Au344k7ES]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO PUMPED RIGHT NOW!!!!  Just sat next to the chattiest person ever on my flight!!!  YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSS https://t.co/zuPtvjX0Wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barr will not release the Mueller report Barr is just a lackey for Trump and will do his best to cover up for Trump… https://t.co/fonFe21xTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#turtletuesday tmntbox best turtle box around @ Fabulous Las Vegas https://t.co/0MZROqTPyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Patrick! Ax Thrower, #karaoke at Residuals Tavern. moviegal119 @PatrickGman @mindovermind #Birthday… https://t.co/vKNJpuicUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep.Dov Hikind,why when there is any Anti Muslim Propagandas and Attacks by the President Trump,Right Wing Republic… https://t.co/qMH0QXUIKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiriasoto Hola hermosa Katiria. Te deseo un feliz comienzo de semana laboral. Llena de bendiciones. Amor mío. https://t.co/Xj107vRaIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna learn how to play Wingspan! I'll avoid foul puns... w/@MyndaJ https://t.co/n4TfxPH1qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toonanim8r Look ion my other tweets to you, I know I've said to get back in again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, if you wear a backwards baseball cap, you’ve probably never read the Constitution.… https://t.co/LGz89Ry1xJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a S'muttonator 2016 by @smuttynosebeer @ Heritage United Pentecostal Church — https://t.co/RqTUzrUmbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Checking out one of the new @SIRIUSXM channels on my app while I'm waiting for @SXMTheHighway to finish playing Ras… https://t.co/Y2ouqVvaST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encantó participar en la producción del primer álbum de mi gran amigo @RZegundo bajo la dirección y arreglo de m… https://t.co/5VnXPxyX8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Gafford: “If it wasn’t for the crowd we wouldn’t have pulled this out. They got loud and we fed off them”]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Commute: Since I started this 30 Day Photography Challenge, it seems like I see more. I see more beauty, happ… https://t.co/9kI0e7lQHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alungstory Cause you're Canadian and the maple syrup runs in your blood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sh8wnjor7an @JustinSimp7 @THightoweriii @ATVSPoseur So why did he “choose” not to coach a game again last year. What was it for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safulgi @RobGunst Yes! I love it!  Feed me all the whining, complaining, denial, excuses!  I want it all!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano I did Alyssa.  And because I am a good very vulgar Christian, I said on her tweet to them all..."I b… https://t.co/BDXQzNPqYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrestling is a big one too lol I love y’all too. I’ll be glad to have y’all here for a few years and I just want y’… https://t.co/kPbqeydyXb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bitchimmmboolin Honey mustard wings and onion rings with honey mustard sauce 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StonyBrookMLAX crushed by Penn State, 17-4, in season opener by @bheyman99 @NewsdaySports https://t.co/9sME1DRkNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'aime Pixar Pierre 🥖 🇫🇷   #Disneyland #DisneyCaliforniaAdventure #Pixar #ABugsLife #ToyStory #Incredicoaster… https://t.co/b0yA0HOFl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the clock app icon skip 2am and jump straight to 3. Wild night over here in Palms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Likin’ the smallball from the Hogs to score the speedy @hestonkjerstad in the 5th. #OmaHogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your your beloved cast and crew fights just as hard as you for our shit show that we all love❤️ we’re more tha… https://t.co/S2MApg1MQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Leads by Example members (@ Tempe Public Market Cafe in Tempe, AZ) https://t.co/zJGDgt57Gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoradoEagles @NickyMonsPhoto @ajgreer_10 What a great moment captured. That photog has a gift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch_M They’ve gotten better over the season. Certainly can win it all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnel62 I’m pretty sure he has 10+ of those little fuckers running around, Bin Ladin was not about the condoms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain continues to fall in #HelenaAL with 0.80” so far today &amp; nearly 6” for the month! No drought here. #alwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[👨‍👩‍👧 my daughter asked me to explain ancestors... You have 2 parents, each of them has 2 parents and so on. A gene… https://t.co/9I5lJsXCGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and Grind!  Legacy Open Gym every Saturday at 7am.  607 S. Lazy Lane Clute TX https://t.co/jUdQWCUAp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be on @FullMeasureNews talking Vogtle and national security. Tune in March 17th. https://t.co/P3SeFldwAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/HXKD7UadTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several Freehold Regional high School students getting checked out by EMTs after their school bus was rest ended by… https://t.co/IofhxLp580]]></document></documents></author>