<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PharmacistReb @rubycramer @SethARichardson So did Florida and a conservative Republican beat a Democrat for a Sena… https://t.co/KLpMCKfr9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this the new convict leasing system? @southerncenter @ProjectSouth https://t.co/jR0W222YhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignByKyle Vudu or Amazon. I prefer Vudu mostly. If you have an Apple TV iTunes is hands down the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finalmente mi è successo proprio davanti alla mia faccia e non riesco proprio a nasconderlo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In progress #NativeAmerican girl . Ink on skin ( black and grey ) . Done at @DarkWStudio #chicagobesttattooartist… https://t.co/214Sqt6Lku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apollo_50th Looks so different from today's launch rooms, got to love  Technology!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shorter beard (bout an inch) or the current longer beard? 🤔 I’m struggling rn 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Until the revolution, when all will be paid according to need.   Tell your BF to enjoy his hamburger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeddyShoes will be doing yearly maintenance on its website and may experience temporary difficulties in the next f… https://t.co/mgzhGALgtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe last time seeing Z. Hope. One more year!  Still top D on the team https://t.co/GKD6Nkrolv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gluestickgirl @hobaird @IndyinDC @ThemeParker104 @AtCrescentLake @HoCoHowie @MMOMpodcast I do lots of questionable… https://t.co/G7fcoVP6Ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please acknowledge the fact that it just took me 4 and half hours to do ONE statistic assignment🤯        Wut]]></document><document><![CDATA[thelacsmusic   #TheLacs #CountryBoysParadise #CountryBoyFresh #190Proof #KeepItRedneck #RedneckRockstar… https://t.co/11be5TqGJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My trust got fucked up when I heard mfs say “on god” and dey was lyin 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having an awesome time at NACA Nationals 2019 @chrisfleming91 @RKE_Agency @NadeenManuel @joelmeyersmagic #NACA19 https://t.co/sXeAbDyGyx]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t get stuck in a snow storm, this should be great! MIA ✈️ BOS ✈️ JFK 🛌 JFK ✈️ MIA ✈️ UVF 🛌 UVF ✈️ MIA (@ M… https://t.co/FEjwv5LMUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm absolutely not worth a shit today and so fine with that... #LazyAssDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be posting another video ASAP on my YouTube channel meeting r-truth yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Project65Golf @GGolfpro To answer the higher handicaps kill the money games in the winter when everybody rolls the… https://t.co/tvpfLWMUsV]]></document><document><![CDATA[RayAnn Ortiz and I are off on our first leg to Amsterdam with a little stop in to our neighbors to the North.  Off… https://t.co/NcpYp3PBTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceMcMahon @RicFlairNatrBoy Diamonds are forever and so is @RicFlairNatrBoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul_M_Huettner @TElonians Hard for the fleet sale buyer to test drive each car.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rkelly Being aggressive doesn’t make you look anymore innocent. If they truly are lies we’d be able to see it. Act… https://t.co/7emBmFR46z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#quotesdaily #annapolis #quotestoliveby #quotes #instagram #instagood #life #lifequotes @ Annapolis, Maryland https://t.co/a9JPSti3hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just go and get it, fuck 'em if they don't love 'em https://t.co/rP1ziByaWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[1980 called, So I picked up the phone and said “Last Day of the Month, time is money” @ Yaphank, New York https://t.co/0RSff4Abz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CubsTwitter: “The Cubs should sign Bryce Harper”  Joe Maddon: “We’re not getting Bryce Harper”  #CubsTwitter: “The… https://t.co/DpzaxoV4eC]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINN BALOR RETAINS HIS INTERCONTINENTAL CHAMPIONSHIP HITTING LIO RUSH WITH THE COUP DE GRACE TO VICTORY BALOR CLUB LIVES #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clubtrillion @HOMAGE @oneshiningpod Already out of medium. Any idea when more stock will come in for that size? https://t.co/9CVxf9YgBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes @TexasGOP @SenTedCruz @GOP Watch @wisgop @SpeakerRyan cheer on police as they beat and arrest a 71-year-… https://t.co/IOSio3UUlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Atlanta; I go pick up Malik Jackson that just got cut by the Jags. They also pick up some fresh bodies for the OLine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let your engineers choose the license: A guide https://t.co/4NpCmOgqf4 via @opensourceway by @opensourcepilot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourboyQ254 I pray we hear tomorrow some other team made the AB mistake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[aaaaaaaaAAH q agusto llora uno en lo q viene siendo en el jale nomi raza?? un saludazo a mis compas q andan triston… https://t.co/o2kQP6m1FN]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/l6oUNSAEzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bakebm46 @Section6GirlsBB @WNYAthletics I could not agree more! A smooth operation! A lot of fun, and some great meals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperSmartMark @JRsBBQ @AEWrestling @WWE Stop acting like you know everything, nerd. You're absolutely clueless wh… https://t.co/73U6BY9XVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamChampion, what's causing all these rain storms? It looks like NW Georgia is going to float away. 😊😊  Good to se… https://t.co/dHhoQfbYv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the “Silhouette” shoot with ballet dancer Libby Griffith. “Silhouette” is now in its second edition of printin… https://t.co/p2lsgZUwhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SectionVI @SFHSwrestlingNY @NW_Wrestling1 @LancWrestle @CSHSVW @WN_SpartanWres @NFHS_Athletics @JacksWrestling… https://t.co/FunbF63rnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jus_paz1 congrats on an amazing season thus far and an incredible EPC playoff performance! You deserve all the shi… https://t.co/IY0CiJDNnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real life goal is to travel with Ellen just so we can hang around in airports and train stations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nuttin changed @ Cherry Hill Dodge Chrysler Jeep Ram https://t.co/ivensMqhEz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAlinaJo Doing fine Alina. Not on as much, but trying to keep my word and check in on you as much as possible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@principalvoices congratulations on your boss retaining his position.  We need strong leadership! Keep fighting for our youth Robert Runcie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[”Think Like An Owner” (Why I’m Joining @cartainc)  https://t.co/cRCZu3Hpsl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Havinga open house again Sunday 3/10/19 10am-3  come say hi!! 24560 wild calla here in Moreno valley. Come by and c… https://t.co/8Gt0hc8Chp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I broke a bone in my foot but i guess we’ll find out in a few weeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewute1 @BradenShamo One time spent an hour at winco filled my cart completely full and go to pay with my credi… https://t.co/6q1IbrXLPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never understand how people get out of something and 3 weeks later in a full blown relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mayman10 @jjaimemanrique @AOC The 4 billion number is not for a single year. You think they were moving there for 12 months?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you missed it this morning, @bethanyshondark sat down with First News on 570 to chat about the Ilhan Omar s… https://t.co/IDsOxSRA8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[All 2019 wrestling team titles are coming back to the 2️⃣0️⃣5️⃣‼️@Thompsonwrestle @McAdoryHS @MoodyBlueDevils… https://t.co/8gqb8ShE8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m over here in the jacuzzi plotting that slide’a demise… It’s going down… Or I’m going down it I don’t know @ Lif… https://t.co/rRLukTEDXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to have the U.S. Marines in to talk to our students at Ingomar and East Union  @UCSDSchools https://t.co/SwbBJaqaUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chinese are determined to have their way with Canada and Trudeau's convenient croak about following the rule of… https://t.co/CmHV1fq6XQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌿PLANT BASED HAIR COLOR🍃from biolage! New no lift technology uses hot water💦as activator! Coming soon! @ Miami Beac… https://t.co/2OQPrBGxSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX @DaleJr That is a deeply well spoken comment by Jr. Congrats to Annett]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Barberton #Ohwx Temp:24.4°F WchillLow:13.5°F Wind:3 mph Dir:NW Baro:Rising quickly Rain2day:0.00in Hum:86% UV:0.0 @ 11:00 02/18/19 #weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las hormigas son buenas, necesito ayudarlas 🐜🐜🐜🏞 #sabinashidalgo https://t.co/4Xh3I9K7lg]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re experiencing some technical difficulties... please hold... #shakycam @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/cAjlifUSAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firms like @Dentons, @TEC_FoleyHoag, @cozen_oconnor enlist former state AGs, State AG staffers, and other officials… https://t.co/2yB8n9R2m8]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you are short on flat bar, but know how to make it work 😉 https://t.co/xW7nFmOt1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be reading along with my own music at The Visual Arts Centre on Tuesday February 19th, 2019. Show is at 7PM. H… https://t.co/u0E6r9uhy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seven days into March and we all can agree that y’all gotta stop getting y’all weather forecasts from a beaver 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktomassoni1 I'm trying to figure out was he ever going to sit out due to injury even if he could play or was it al… https://t.co/51WoS2nk11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sadybeaches @SportsTalkBarry @realDonaldTrump Love Trump, but you’re 100% correct on term limits. Both sides need… https://t.co/JKObAhu2Uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pajaropolitico @lopezobrador_ SE DEBE PROCESAR Y EN SU CASO ENCARCELAR A LOS RATEROS, ES URGENTE RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielDmanx123 I'd love to see a Walker-Boyd-Barber line. You have the speed and feistiness of Walker, the vision… https://t.co/zR2VHHFmfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3)  Rain but I like snow when it keeps me from going to work fir a few days.   #SocialRoadTrip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rewire_News Christianity, by its very nature, rests upon evangelical terrorism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we've made it to San Luis Obispo, 6h30m later. More worrying is the amount of weather Northern California is… https://t.co/ardUkr0Bua]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 2019 playlist!! 95 songs added! Slim thru it and let me know!! https://t.co/xnL9yem0JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on Lot 35 Mountain View Court #Crossville #TN  #realestate https://t.co/bCePfJOy70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJoeAddabbo @JGPretlow @YUNews @CardozoLaw @MelanieLeslie5 @NickReisman Will NYS sports betting be an 11th-hour… https://t.co/MgGK1EYl7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angcould @we_r_Psymese @VAGirlsmom @806_sharon @lolamare69 @assy_zwoelfe @iveigh_girl @Duncan_n_Duncan @dustinca93… https://t.co/fi3Qngx81k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fayette Co. HS(AL) hires new football coach Bill Smith. He spent the last 4 seasons at Munford, going 28-18  making… https://t.co/EivxMFcktG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have two children on the autism spectrum, the way this mother is behaving is completely wrong and damaging! #DrPhil]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Halloffame #Dx @TripleH  @TheRealXPac  @WWERoadDogg  @RealBillyGunn My Favorite of All Time #DX My Era… https://t.co/LwmQW24QxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always happy to meet with my people @pomara_matt @deehungerford28 @mtvisme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatthewFairburn @JoeBuscaglia just want to point out vontae Davis vs McDermott in final 4 would be a travesty.  Cl… https://t.co/wXZU9mfG9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandallTime Just  make sure to find your way back to the Browns for the 2019 season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Biblical principles of leadership need to come from the whole of Scripture.  Leaders in multicultural situations h… https://t.co/yVCk2tmOTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BerniePleskoff How about this one - if Trump gets reelected, and then there is another 2 term president we'll be r… https://t.co/cEtqs18mOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 tickets for tonight’s game up for grabs for $20 if anyone wants them! Section 225 Row R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t recall playing a murderer’s row of players in any event but I *do* remember my first draft pod at my first… https://t.co/AQMqiXd0a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daviddoel @BernieSanders @IlhanMN Bravissimo, President Sanders! https://t.co/USLIAlQTyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesuSegoviano @SoyReferee Ahí se ve claramente, el tobillo va a los tacos @FerRamos26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveMcLean888 Sounds like a messy messy game. https://t.co/RI4BPpzEe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anilak_99 according to the email, 3p EST is lecture and https://t.co/t85ykzmORQ but not sure if that means live or later archived]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AprilDRyan @realDonaldTrump He doesn't know. He never knows. He is INCAPABLE of knowing anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[do you think there’s a correlation between *ncels and being r*ght w*nged?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyeatwordz great how Netflix keeps cancelling their good shows so they can invest more money into psychopath showcases. bunch of sickos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to settle this right now... @UncleChaps and @katebarstool  Shout out Group 8  Classier Snack nut...... GO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calzone night with the boys and @durand_jones new joint..... Damn Grateful... @seasickbham @plaidroom @ Alabama https://t.co/HMMALhWiVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rockies @ColtonWelker24 @reekohsuave @C_RusIn @hoff_23 @MrGrayWolf22 @carlosestevez28 @germanmarquez5… https://t.co/sPjbXbYO1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Revision is the process of life, the process of writing.” Joey Garcia — How wonderful to hear from my old friend… https://t.co/Hesis5dHKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw @JRubinBlogger Wonder what Harry Truman would say. I bet it would have something to do with an electric chair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LETgolf @heathermacgolf Once a Capable College Player and from a Family of Players. An Aunt on Two Curtis Cups....… https://t.co/Ur3YQjTry9]]></document></documents></author>