<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Harry Styles is really out there breathing and looking beautiful huh? Wow I love him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Jugar jueguitos secundariles - como éste- en Twitter. :3  4. Curiosa. Apasionada. Ñoña.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CastMemberLife I’ve got a good feeling about this https://t.co/CpOLNzT6Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Seriously... is this the reason you stopped flying nonstop EWR -MCO? https://t.co/ckus92EouY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Yahoo @WSJ @nytimes @washingtonpost when you and others will learn that Fed Chair, Congress and the WH have no… https://t.co/icx45qCfSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys cancelled a show years ago on my birthday. Not your fault. But I am so excited you're coming back to Asbur… https://t.co/dPHFFGVH4U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow will be 7 days in a row I’ve worked out &amp; ive gained 4 pounds so far!! Love this improvement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always knew that Hannah Brown was the real one here. Colton's lost, not hers. Very beautiful inside &amp; out… https://t.co/jp9hCELz0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trent_PhD My hair is going to smell like grilled teriyaki shrimp for the next several days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I dive deep? Will you come in after me? Will you share your flowers with me 💐? We’ll never knooow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol I’m twist out look like a blow out but I’m wearing it to church just like that 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAGA2ARIGHTS @AmericanThinker If President Trump loses expect them to come after every conservative and kill us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinoDelaforus @RuiterWrongFAN Hunt made a statement to ESPN about our video, saying, "I want to apologize for my a… https://t.co/a91loTbRp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GearGrinder8 @SenFeinstein Look at everyone commenting, 16, 100 20 followers.  It's all fake to make it look as if people believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeFait Thing is he knows how to lose weight hes done it before, but he isn't finding the motivation to do it again]]></document><document><![CDATA[These past few months have been nothing but blessings to me. Really is crazy to think about where I was 6 months ago and where I am now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all gotta check out this article from one of our friends on caring for those with chronic pain 👇🏽 so so good: Jes… https://t.co/C6cgHqemcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_whitlock I’m going to Austin at the end of March - need beer/restaurant reccs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤠 #Day2 ~ #Dallas ~ #TexasBbq | #TexasPlates | #SoCalRealEstate #offers | #MovieNight | 💙🖤 @ Dallas, Texas https://t.co/Hz5h4Ih7fK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor Elliott awards the Community Spirit Award to the late Robert Scatterday. “If you look closely, Scat’s fingerp… https://t.co/pItGhJCPmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teamfrench23 @pkizzire Surprising most of the penalties have come on the mens tour and not the ladies who tended t… https://t.co/3kfFuvSZVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't find a lint roller, so I wore a jacket over my sweater to hide the cat hair. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I may have someone with me who is short, about 5’0” tall with freckles with me. Wears heels, hair pulled back in a… https://t.co/OH1YXOAxvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was so nice to finally meet you in person @DynamicWebPaige! See you tomorrow at #TFDevSummit! https://t.co/eRiNKkqNXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donaldbroom @PoliticsIsDirty Love this guy. He has our backs and he is fun as hell 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@187k87k This3 look so good. Don't look hard to make. But as I think am good cook, candy has never come out well fo… https://t.co/Y1REs6art0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlights from #2019 Hot Chocolate Race! Edgy Girls turned the place out!!  #edgygirlfitness #fitover40… https://t.co/5dhYXwMk4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck the stingray that killed Steve Irwin hope you rot in hell bitch. Rip Steve Irwin we love you 💖🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m writing this mid-show so you should tune in at https://t.co/6DbJc2IeRS RIGHT NOW!  I’m talking about The Color… https://t.co/SL9dtRqDrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In this overwhelming time of government ethics violations, following @CREWcrew gives me hope.]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Emergency?  Seriously? #BorderWall #FakeTrumpEmergency #StopTheMadness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlackIceSheep @CBBloch I don't even know why he did it. I don't know whos muted me, whos shadow blocked me, and wh… https://t.co/pURhqcMTUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for coming and letting them practice! They were so excited and feel so much better about their bi… https://t.co/PRvwG7t32b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is concerned about who’s in the middle and NO ONE is talking about how joe just won Tic Tac Toe https://t.co/uyaAKBJpd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOrlandoJones It has been such a long wait!!!!! I can’t believe it’s today!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to rule this Monday?!? Frances???? Maybe later? Cool @ Independence St. NOLA https://t.co/UQX4ZjQNqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you'll go.”  Happy… https://t.co/gRoXLWRys7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@somewhatemily So what im hearing is you believe in the reptilian illuminati]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol my boyfriend always recommends shows for me to watch and i’m like eh, and then someone else will recommend the… https://t.co/RYgkErEAg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working with the school district for 6 months now and I couldn’t be happier 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I hear a Rick Steves type voice in the background? @SeattleChannel , please do something. Thank you. #MHAhearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quesadilla day!!! #quesadilla #thursday #thirstythursday #localeats #dinein #takeout #familyfriendly #pub… https://t.co/R5vgvAD5jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia watching Daddy's Canadian special Just For Laughs on Amazon Prime TV with my bf. So glad I found this.… https://t.co/dQpUSWgRnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone, have a blessed day in the Lord our God and Heavenly father! Thank you Lord!! Blessings to yo… https://t.co/5D7GkcReUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @RWPUSA I agree don't call him MI it insults people who are truely struggling. He is purposefully… https://t.co/T0Mp2ywmAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kehlani I can’t believe Ehile We Wait drops tonight. So excited. You’re a queen 🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cordiallycontgo I compltely forgot Oregon is one of, if not the last state that has attendants who will pump your… https://t.co/aSAQfvFqvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamBlackPink @ygofficialblink I hope he adds more dates. I want another in NJ. Ticketmaster added more platinum t… https://t.co/dGM0VNXx4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Democrats have not gone all in on socially! That’s more of the Republican Party’s false propaganda. If an… https://t.co/3QpxuS3rzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow or feathers? When the lint trap is MIA and the comforter comes out empty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Making! #R10CIRCLE #R10ECServices #ECEchat @ICanReadDallas https://t.co/izkwkRNOz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to be part of the first open house at the new venue @thegin_hidalgo !  Come out today to see the venue and… https://t.co/CzG6PXPxzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Lmfao you’re an idiot! We are coming for you!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of @Guiding_Light’s best. Trivia: My hubby did the original. I watched Mike Nichols weigh in outta town.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeAndDeathYT @TheAlanJohnson @wbgames @MortalKombat That’s so awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What formation even is this. #tahoe #wedding #snow @ Boreal Mountain https://t.co/RJp78XA1FJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the years of joy your acting has given me, I’m sorry and I hope you Rest In Peace and I wish peace an… https://t.co/oyn6DnEb4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does your group’s penguin shelter measure up? Today, peer evaluators will check your measurements and we’ll fin… https://t.co/Xw0gTfKdwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still marvel at the fact that Elizabeth Warren was my ex’s lecturer at Harvard Law School.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is the best  I was born in the same area My age is not an issue  I like to see you in your home   Alright]]></document><document><![CDATA[threw up in my mouth at work and I had to swallow it bc I was in front of customers lol xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiGlanville Why?  Why must you even stir the pot though?  You don’t care about either party so why even say an… https://t.co/IUYijwYlXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[College Prep #Students Visiting #Boston #University @ Boston University https://t.co/dXDs497mcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much punishment is enough? How long should any person be penalized for something that happened decades ago? #abolishtheregistry]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a fashionable pill case. If anyone wants to buy me it I’ll take it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s ‘Emergency’ Declaration Is Illegal https://t.co/afrUXoLFnX via @aclu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're playing far cry new dawn and want to have a laugh, make sure you have Gina as your gun for hire when you… https://t.co/iHLcj7WQ26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyh8nejeal @breathniari FUCK I HAVE TO UNSTAN I- https://t.co/C9oi09Ivjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take control of what I say, O LORD, and guard my lips. Psalm 141:3 (NLT)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much has changed in my life these past 4 months I’m just redirecting my energy to the things that matter most.. spiritually, mentally..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NTN24ve Ya están sacando a la familia real!! Lejos mientras más lejos mejor!! Calle calle y más calle #quenocallelacalle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mollyscarden @Sydneyalexisw @dylannivens I saw this earlier &amp; died 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianPaulStuart @MELANIATRUMP @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump Wow, pre-surg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittLeighJack @miche11e8 @FourPrivetDr @hollieoverton @ZOmygawd @TayMals @NappyThoughtz @claire_hupy I. LOVE. YOU… https://t.co/QUY0BVnckQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJellyman @BallastPoint @StoneBrewing @badhopper @zappafaye @JonMontag @lhtetrick @Jagoff33 @cellmavin… https://t.co/lfr121DM2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittytoooo @NTWOorg @stephan67212617 @ItsmeEddieC @IndependentRed4 @MuelBoy Those precious babies 😡😢😇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dd_guerrero5 Beautiful!! Let’s do it again young ladies !! Si se pudo!!! Go lady eagles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnChardRE @BilldeBlasio Interior decorating, lobster dinners, the finest tailored suits, lavish vacations... Tha… https://t.co/2xiRzChAK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jxoxpxaxt She was truly unrecognizable.  This Sam we’re seeing today is the one we all grew to love.  She’s a BOSS… https://t.co/NraW1aT9Sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me relaxing in silence while my family is at church https://t.co/PwDLrnIpgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por una mujer mas empoderada, segura de si misma, una soñadora que trabaje para sus metas, y que no se sienta derro… https://t.co/PGjQs9K9LN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for coming to read today! #WestShoreProud #HGStallions]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebrownie @knittykitty who puts out two amazing albums within 6 months of each other. her mind, i can't handle it !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[chelsea has zero leadership. a good captain would've made sure kepa went off the pitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love anything I don’t have to cook! 🍔🥤🍟 Helping @Sachse_Cheer is a ➕BONUS!  Dinner has been served!🤗 https://t.co/bBKzUSmz8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl sitting behind me at the Mavs game is talking soooo much shit about James Harden, I wanna know what that man did to her 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repairing what should od been done the first time @ Farmingville, New York https://t.co/Zw3WX4kkTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are not innocent and SDNY will prove it. https://t.co/xjrqtfEp8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaLoulouC @JeanMic71 J'ai ça aussi.. mais c'est pas de ces petites merdes que je me sers.. je trouve ça ful fif sw… https://t.co/B9mo2EOJws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoibearddeUna @sunrisemvmt So why is over populated California complaining not enough water when it was always tha… https://t.co/oPKkkoDMDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing getting me through right now is the promise of experiencing this on Saturday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did 2 years go by so fast? 😢 114 days until I see the pilots again. I can’t wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaronDavis @JohnVelkEsq @UCLAAthletics @cheezit @Pringles Yes please see the picture good me tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know the pollen count is hell right now but damn, we are so fortunate to be surrounded by all of this beauty  🌺🌸🌼… https://t.co/2xmgTZghG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ba bshalrga disha yesh cha na sha/  bonito platique palabra pueblo hoy día #purooaxaca #oaxacalifornia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynHewitson @cassia_sil @BBCTwo That is hilarious, as is the FS spoof with Ellen DeGeneres.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Primer día de rutina. Me afizzzziioo, me afizzzziiooo Dioooo!!!  #rutina #🦈 #babysharktututu en Universal Studios O… https://t.co/dQRjpplGTO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immensely proud of having led this group of educators in this work. We are the change we seek to see in the world.… https://t.co/R3RuX2KXhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Congress: Stop the sexual assault of migrant children and women under Trump. https://t.co/p5VCJPdUmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay !  I spent the morning wandering through the Hilma af Klint exhibit at the Guggenheim… https://t.co/6E5GxXb42O]]></document></documents></author>