<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@golodhros A slide theme should be used only for company marketing slides. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Pros and Cons of Roof Deicing Cables #roof #roofers #homeinspectors #Minnesota #homeinspections  https://t.co/43Z5G07lqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[My take: 1) Blame does not need to be assigned for athletic losses. 2) referees should not be the default excuse 3)… https://t.co/QdDR8V06EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tottenham were better when they had two of the best wingbacks in the world is quite the argument to make. Not sure,… https://t.co/LjFCIZDbWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doutrive a bright spot for Arizona in dark times this season. Deserves more opportunities. https://t.co/mmNQ0Hpk1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lsumab11 @briancrice @ErikAinge3 Did you hear my comment this morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wine 2 go?! Flyers V Pens Stadium Series! #nhlstadiumseries #nhlflyers @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/6ORqA0DzEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 You forgot that Farrakhan praised Omar and told her not to apologize for being anti-Jewish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever think you might like people, then actually go out again, but realize you dont like people again?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday is for the ______ . . . styling: @grnweddingshoes | ties: thetiebar x @grnweddingshoes | photog: katieprit… https://t.co/gsOMbCZ6g6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Champion_Zeus Basketball players can start their pro careers whenever they want. Under current rule, they just can't play in the NBA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NRA past, Heath Mello, Kelly DHS vote, 94 crime bill, writings when he was AOC’s age]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristiePetty10 @RandPaul 5. Trump created the “caravans” in order to manufacture support among the base.  6. Trump… https://t.co/uUQQzja9qg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Call Me Today To Find Out Why NOW Is The Best Time To Make A Move ☎️ 905-334-5883 #marketreport #realestate #remax… https://t.co/j95sjdhbiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at work yesterday and Eric says to me “you’ll know this, what happened to shakira?” I’ve known this guy two m… https://t.co/YSNpErUV2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright everyone I woke up and saw a bunch of dumb stuff on the TL, back to bed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLoganFye @EBUSoccerWi And I thought reffing in Dallas was rough this weekend....]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time change has really thrown everything off big time! This is the only time change I hate! Argh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most Of The Time Ion Even Be Wanting To Fuck I Just Be Wanting To Lay Up And Enjoy Your Presence 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched @KevinHarvick interview and the prase he gave about @JimmieJohnson .Greatness only comes every few gen… https://t.co/FMMTryXeSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ is King of Kings, and Lord of Lords!  @Oprah spreads lies, telling the masses that there are many ways… https://t.co/oTWgxInu4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeltranKo4 @fell_1970 @GraceRandolph @brielarson Yes I'm curious on your opinion too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToniSync That we humans are aweful beings and are terrible to our fellow humans. The only purpose of having power… https://t.co/bqCR3C0Ttj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alex_zee @Leah_Sottile Are there really people who believe this? It’s pretty obvious Portland has had problems for, well, forever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i really rolled up into this shady shit and took the tf over lmfao bc im excellent at acting, specifically acting t… https://t.co/HxaPyeMkhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mayor of San Francisco stopped by the russiancentersf Russian Festival today! . . . . . #russian #festival… https://t.co/A3R6syVkOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paris today Minnesota tomorrow ever day gets harder and harder to correct the organized infiltration of Somolian Mu… https://t.co/gSJDqfBJUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking in the beautiful countryside views on a rainy day. This was just east of Turlock, CA. Why was I here around… https://t.co/6bIAwb30hF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say these words every morning out loud to your self for 30 days. In Christ I am chosen, I am predestined, I am adop… https://t.co/e2AqiT9oz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am having mildly inconviencing negative thoughts about myself rn and idk what 2 do so i’ve been laying in bed wat… https://t.co/12rpmpfbZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoyCardenas7 Nah bro...I’ve never seen a character with a more punchable face https://t.co/21ddWKwyd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering where is the first half white  old new president obsme Who ) today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior @davidmweissman This makes impeachment even more important. Otherwise, my gay ass is going to have t… https://t.co/AfPIniNQe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS BUT, Repulicans refused for her to answer… https://t.co/4EMaTcX9pP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theeclarkjones Tell that to the #CancelCulture who’s gonna dig this up in 10 years and rake you over the coals]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LloydShermer’s powerful #GutenbergsPuzzle 🖤📃 on display at the @Newseum https://t.co/G9f0FmfB3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win men!! @SeattleSportsU @AbrahamDeWeese @SeattleUBase @GoSeattleU  @PhilDaMann]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimothySRoy @grumpybirdieS @TulsiGabbard Contribute to her campaign. We need her sense of reasoning in the debates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDOTDC all of the lights at the intersection of South Capitol and I Street are out again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyGallaghe10 It's hard to tell where one starts and the other ends 😊 so cute😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElizShockman @MNCompass I'll get you started:  https://t.co/06M5HKXc2I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be in bed by 10:30 but when that Netflix comes on lord knows im not sleepin till 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannsands1 @amvn90210 @IlhanMN Maine is another example! We have to wake up and take our country back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quede solo en un minuto mientras estaba en Twitter 🤦🏽‍♂️ https://t.co/7Pz6QyxZvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I have always been one to say both sides of media are changing the narrative for us all but this is nuts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @MacysBackstage in Waterbury, CT https://t.co/iB7c3R5mXE https://t.co/OEbFOqaxXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing new @TensorFlow website announced at #TFDevSummit - give us feedback and we'll continue to improve and publ… https://t.co/tbaHkXXHk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gletham @ArcGISOnline Give people access to the tool, no questions asked.  Provide basic training like others are… https://t.co/wLNTSob0RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnionBlue1789 @Indians @Browns @foxsports_1350 @wncoam @1390wnio Why/why not to #1!  Need a name for #2.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOP IS PACKED WITH AMAZING STUFF ALREADY PRICED LOWER THAN ANYWHERE AND NOW WE ARE HAVING A 50% OFF PRESIDENTS DAY… https://t.co/2C02IP67kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders already moved Democrats to the left. Why is he running again?: Is there another outsider who yanked… https://t.co/RmGreiV524]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure liar liar Ilhan Omar claims her Obama comments were distorted, then posts audio confirming controversial remar… https://t.co/RKwEkSuIAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@teainfo updates at @MathLeaders #TASMTalk: TEA now offers a two week window for online testing starting in 2019-2… https://t.co/Y3sASxMKG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀 The homies over at @TheAthleticPDX are selling a couple of my #basketball artprints that are beautifully framed.… https://t.co/aiBq4lvlAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerichards1068 @CoachAlanBishop @ElliottChapa and @BakerLBrian worked these today during the period! Kids did well! https://t.co/fwHLMRIb7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trudeau says he was 'surprised and disappointed' by Jody Wilson-Raybould’s resignation  https://t.co/fp12OKSp0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LedouxPedailles @InfinityLithium That said, I do like your graphs - thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is time to rethink your #RUN! Come visit ASICS 5th Avenue on 2/28/19 to experience innovation in motion! #asics… https://t.co/KugNX4JULR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast To Go And It's Very Good And Tasty Breakfast Served. @ Castlepark Apartment Homes https://t.co/CMKcETwoMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking like a good day to drive in the mountains!!! (@ Durkee Oregon in OR) https://t.co/hPOjB7D2qX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8tags @4TyIerHiIl Y’all wait two more weeks so I can go during my spring break 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[having a journal really works wonders on getting your thoughts out, y’all should invest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ag innovation and what @JohnDeere is doing daily to move the needle globally is transformative, relevant and is dri… https://t.co/cLKAqIFjX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChocOne0One @silverandbluesp Need somebody who knows what they’re doing on scoreboard replays- got a video screen.… https://t.co/waE4umgYzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddiebravo looks like if #Boyle from @nbcbrooklyn99 actually hit the gym to earn #Rosa's love. #Cobbservations… https://t.co/K20T1LhQGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y líbranos del mal amén en Stratford, Connecticut https://t.co/gtmYOR8zPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjab_84 @v0nd0ll0 @CBCNews @cattunneycbc That’s not relevant.  I’ve already said he was a criminal.  It’s not lega… https://t.co/FyDEMA9lY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_JustHype I’d also probably bench Shamet before Shai. His defense is worse than Shai’s offense rn. And I’m never g… https://t.co/KrhT668UVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarBombBoom13 One thing about what you said. It’s a hit that results in a brain injury. I agree it quite frankly I… https://t.co/zY8H9LOI9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Herro glides in off the Auburn turnover and now has 15 points, 2 rebounds, 2 assists, 0 turnovers. Then a crazy PJ… https://t.co/EiqU5C6JYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Eagle @yomilo @MCNocando @PlanetPremRock @VerBSisthehomie @WillieGreen1 I love this in every way]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tokyo Bay Buffet in Royal Palm Beach, FL https://t.co/xfNtfM4kUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriesMarquis @donleyp @MillerStream @RoamingMil Even if that’s the case it certainly doesn’t justify caging every… https://t.co/ZOfe4Dn0Kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Bernie but are we really going to split our party vote again? Please let’s decide on someone this upcoming e… https://t.co/gJJvkgYnsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers are 1-5 in their last 6, told y’all LeBron wasn’t playing when he told everyone he was going into playoff mode.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJetOnTNT it’s not we. Your not playing anymore. And that was a clean block and that’s the refs fault for calling it. #hater]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bethenny Abducted in Plain Sight.  It's a Documentary feature but it is bananas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summoning circle, hope this works                         🕯               🕯              🕯         🕯… https://t.co/NZnkpDbmwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @elonmusk I cannot wait for the moment when car accidents are a thing of the past.   https://t.co/5AMnV8LoAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo y’all just highkey keep making the realist music I’m highkey shoook 😱😱😱🔥🔥🔥Y’all as artists speaking the truth an… https://t.co/PWANCYE1ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Mike Trout grew up an hour from Philadelphia and was a Phillies fan, but radio people (national) said the ot… https://t.co/LhP3NP6XG3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincenzolandino I had a Realtor as a client years ago and told them exactly what to take pictures of but they mana… https://t.co/diLZuwNqcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BruceLee Was A #Beast... --- -- - #PingPong With #Nunchucks - -- --- #RIP… https://t.co/YrfJXI4iuR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not let any unwholesome talk come out of your mouths, but only what is helpful for building oth… https://t.co/xKmR36LbFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding job to all of the wonderful women in the world🌍🌎🌏🌐! Past and Present... @ Greensboro, North Carolina https://t.co/sBkq6htViQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RingerNBA Dany- she would trade her best asset to another team for an army of players and the traded asset would s… https://t.co/Xeap8Oxlek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dataspot1701d @adrelthi @TeltheTrekkie I go see them.  Some are better than others.  I am looking forward to DUMBO… https://t.co/t7SQgmCmMY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple choice, Locker - @JoeBpXp I like it! This is where I excelled in college! - @Laughlin18  God I love them… https://t.co/K4D4WR7q5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sitkarev Hi, We would be happy to assist you. See our innovative work here: https://t.co/0kK0depliy         Kindly… https://t.co/mhuW3pCXvl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politicobsessed She pulled off a surprise victory. That should have been a 2-day news cycle story, at most. Then s… https://t.co/V5hNI90Bzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mum2Autist @AutisticTitan5 @c255666a459a495 Won't be getting one either, I'm surmising! He certainly isn't worth w… https://t.co/H5H6iOPcwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimKardashian Watch the intro to Belly which YE stole this from its much more entertaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of time this must’ve took just running back and forth in a restroom astounds me]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no reason to keep this opinion a secret anymore:  Cincinnati chili is aberrant and abhorant. I admire a cit… https://t.co/Aw3vaZKkgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @NBCNews KILL YOUR NEWBORN BABY! (Vote Democrat in 2020!) https://t.co/fndgYeXgBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love dafran i know i sound like a broken record but he’s come so far and i’m so proud of him !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeekWithThat @wrytersview @pkmmpositivity @TrashCanDanpt3 @replicantpinky @AtariVision @zaku1982 @MonstMashup… https://t.co/2Jq2L4G5T2]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we make the jails our shelters and emergency rooms, this is what happens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaqi_B_2001 Collecting is the BEST thing ever, trust me. I mean as long as you're a Barbie girl! Noooooo but I have a feeling I should lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ashamed to admit this traitorous tRump MAGAt is from my hometown  #TreasonWeasle]]></document></documents></author>