<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Así llegue a la última hora nevando en casa ahora 7:20 pm  !!!!#LaTrilogiaParanormal https://t.co/pCqmkBzoZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my brother and I basically almost eat the same cereal but can’t agree on which is better so you guys tell us]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got a perfect 100 on my assessment at work today. Clearly I should’ve been a finance major 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is jolly. #comedy #snicker #grin #humorous https://t.co/l5NCVmJing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @robinlundberg @MsAmyCampbell “No one loves to run to that point of exhaustion “Obviously you are not a runn… https://t.co/A4Z0VPCR5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men aren’t shit. Even when you think you might’ve found a good one, they will prove you wrong time and time again. #DoBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you start feeling the sadness creep back into you so you sleep before it takes over good night 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went on an impromptu date tonight and it was fantastic and I’m so happy to have had such a lovely night and great conversation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaskingSnark @emrazz I wasn't talking about single vs. couples I was talking about the traditional man as provider… https://t.co/UFxa8lVef6]]></document><document><![CDATA[On President’s Day, we honor the leaders who have fought to move our country forward. I’m proud to have stood with… https://t.co/ZU80A1U0gv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherfro @quinnanya @ProgHist Really cool idea. Would love to know what you hear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Howling: Why You’re Hearing Coyotes This Month https://t.co/BJDnwRg5Vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Airport, am thinking it shouldn’t be only ACTIVE duty military that boards first. It should be all veterans… https://t.co/BZ7hF27SJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Patreon post alert!  In this entry I talk about how 2019 has gone so far as well as some upcoming work and trav… https://t.co/cZqgdWcjQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[drake: what good is all the cash if it doesn’t buy time and what good is being famous if i’m never on your mind   f… https://t.co/S6UuX0Qw0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will have live reports all morning from @rhyan_henson on the scene of the fatal fire on N. 22nd on @ksdknews dur… https://t.co/bh4YYvI6Ru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skyMadison5 @bubbagump324 I know..secretly I wish they would remain that small much longer😔😊😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted the challenge from @ShadSalem to post covers of 7 books I LOVE: no explanations, no review. Each time… https://t.co/EoepiKYf6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to check out Googles home page for some wholesome content today]]></document><document><![CDATA[The students: Get Davanta Parker back as SGA President - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/YtjnsCu7hS via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ms Higney doing th final preparations before @TreelinePDSB annual talent show! So excited 😆 https://t.co/Ag8Q8DofF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No dejes pasar esta oportunidad. Tienes hasta el 4 de marzo para solicitar ayuda financiera #FAFSA con @castudentaid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin’ around #Toronto à Museum of Illusions, Toronto Ontario https://t.co/wursmwTXff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX @notcapnamerica Wow seriously though what is wrong with people? 😮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 Peanut butter and jelly a lot healthier than martinis and hamburglers, they’re doing him a favor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Parents, educators ‘blindsided’ by potential choice school in Gig Harbor  https://t.co/wx8jaTH4EA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@extratv @KimKardashian @Mugler Maybe she got dressed in the dark and put it on backwards 🤷🏼‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesleyabravanel I support Chris Wallace for trying to get those creeps to admit the truth. FOX watchers are blinde… https://t.co/g4P9ty4g9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahTrejo @Hozier I need to listen to this - I’ve been waiting for some new tunes from him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for exploring w me today shoeymcshoester  ⛰ #pnw #explore #deceptionpass #whibleyisland #sunny #roadtrip @ D… https://t.co/JToWoR2xZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sryiwasclimbing @AriDisneyLove @spadergasm I’m aware of that but it doesn’t change the fact that it’s not a health… https://t.co/9FrIuTHw67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are California's teachers' strikes part of a coordinated 'wave'? Not exactly https://t.co/phQrOrk2bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back from 2 weeks vacation-excited about this start! Thanks! #SafariLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieHayton @DotAtomosBlog I think even Canadians can struggle with it! For me the giveaway that I’m talking to a… https://t.co/OWN1VZyX3B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarrieQ82 @LakeTribeBrew @TLHBeerSociety @NoleNurse00 @DannyAller @OutofConTxts @Greg_Tish @sweeteabourbon… https://t.co/ZQCS8ILPoX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn't  there some work you could be doing for your crumbling state! That's what you were  hired to do, not chasing… https://t.co/Jk8k9IV5tB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th Birthday to one of the best people I know!! So thankful for you and hope you have the best day ever 💕🎁🎉 @AllieRittmeyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in Chicago, and interested in gender equality in science, do come to my talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDrGina @LisaMei62 @LibertyU @realDonaldTrump's #CPAC2019 speech was so awesome!👏👏 #LoveMyPresident #MAGA🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we first reported:  #ChicagoPD charge a man who they believe was in this video, flashing a gun and threatening t… https://t.co/R29JAE0w5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is "I want you to be Happy" day.  What makes you Happy? #happy #smile #goals #reichcolorado #love… https://t.co/Fc1OdonF4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Pix3M_ Lets just say I'm worried about it happening again, and I'm glad I at least found out you didn't have me already blocked... 9_9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @dalynncosmetics with get_repost ・・・ Remember the name:  @DALYNNCosmetics - We're not going ANYWHERE…we're… https://t.co/erZP8JGaSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DARH3112 @ProjectBetterUS @IlhanMN I know Fakey SHE is an IMBECILE! ALL #AntiSemites ARE!😺MEOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t leave Joey alone with my phone.  Not because I don’t want him seeing something but because HE HIDES IT ON ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QValentine_ @ichavez96 this is going to be us when we go model in 2 weeks 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget we have a Mardi Gras Slot Tournament! Registration starts at 2:15p-4p… Qualifier round starts at 3p-5:… https://t.co/ZhzUEJyd7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait I was bleeding before I started cleaning!!! Preexisting condition. Also fuxk typing with bandaids someone fixthus]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cute guy has my heart...love you Clayton❤ @ Kill Devil Hills, North Carolina https://t.co/OVAnLGKSV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It appears that we will be able to watch the @NBCSN broadcast from our seats @GPSTPETE... But I feel really bad for… https://t.co/rLtc5gfg3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all this is ridiculous. I know I voiced my opinion but, @khloekardashian is dumb for going back to a man who chea… https://t.co/wJ2EV3U7kF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelYelliex Driving down the street - people are so rude to other drivers. They would never act that way face to… https://t.co/o9S2VfR0nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadMustelid @Katja_Thieme @NiceMangos @MishMei In the case of the murder of James Craig Anderson -- the families a… https://t.co/cGc9n4K9bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidKAllen_ Congratulations! Especially to @AimeeMPerryman. I never doubted your persistence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New tattoo! The Little Cthulhu! @ Colorado Springs, Colorado https://t.co/hz0RI3iNnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to wear these today for the GOAT @Jumpman23 #happybirthday 🐐🏀 https://t.co/0BCSCQ0TUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading by example! Henry SM at 4162 Doing The Right Thing! Thank you for keeping our customers and associates safe… https://t.co/DoOsJZ9WCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[top pics for cast? @DoveCameron and @HaileyKilgore      Universal Sets ‘Wicked’ Movie for 2021 Christmas Holidays –… https://t.co/6ILwVlrpq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night i met somebody who doesn’t believe his friend is a woman beater because the girl who accused him is appa… https://t.co/Xb4uSlVcTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the most non partisan way, Trudeau has to resign. Not even a question. If he doesn’t the liberals will suffer a humiliating large defeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[A full parking lot and lots of full tummies at the Portguese Club for @SouthEssexCC Chilifest! I was ladling for Jo… https://t.co/7YmGt61Z7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicktangorra I’m sooo freaking happy that I got to talk to you last night 😍♥️❤️❤️😍😘😘♥️❤️♥️❤️ , I love you so very… https://t.co/SQYuIOqoxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always awkward and hilarious hearing cheeks getting clapped in the room next to you or above you after midnight💀💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[📍281 Bentley Cir | $48,000,000   Please visit https://t.co/3Ymdr7Srd7 for more info  We are looking for a buyer! Pl… https://t.co/WdiEm3mVd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleCharlie50 @garthbrooks @BigLeagueImpact And then there’s still your delicious dip.  I eat it until I can’t feel anything but heat!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Viendo tus ojos puedo descifrar el universo, el viento suave, el azul del cielo al fin lo entiendo... que este mund… https://t.co/9wQYRtV272]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gchance668 That means everything!  Forever grateful for all u have done for him...cannot thank u enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[In more sad news, i had the cutest booties in my cart for a STEAL! Got busy at work, forgot about them... sold out. Life’s great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 @realDonaldTrump Why do I believe Michael Cohen over Donald Trump? Michael Cohen only lied to prot… https://t.co/RzYGbsbnFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out @globeandmail Great review on #sashastoltzpublicity Client @MrJaneandFinch https://t.co/iXyloEmbK2… https://t.co/sruWhprnjX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to stop being so negative sometimes. I can not help but overthink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But don’t let me fool y’all, i’m still crying bc i’d much rather experience life with someone by my side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t be at cheetahs tonight I am out collecting skulls with @aeonmagdalena #makeup by @iamleah corkytea… https://t.co/gLhM82CmQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be heading to the @lawnond this Saturday for weekend 2 of their special winter pop up event ☃️ Anyone want to… https://t.co/Zz2cHsoS2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet author, illustrator, artist, entrepreneur and pro wrestler richie frieman who personalized his copies of his b… https://t.co/jAMKTprYB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryMarvel And you dip it in to country gravy no questions asked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLiberty1491 @h8Wankmaggot45 bad. I have not idea what happened to the end of my tweet. Weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I don't eat red meat so you can have my hamburger, but I'll be damned if I won't be taking up arms when… https://t.co/WTAlyNoK7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Elle_Spencer_ They blamed Obama publicly &amp; grossly &amp; let themselves be paraded around by this charlatan criminal to do so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some interesting news this morning. Regardless today will be a great day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After spending an entire week with 4+ white conservative men who go to a Christian college, nobody can ever tell me… https://t.co/9cBzdbspxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnWDean It's exhausting, depressing, and puts you in a state of constant anxiety. It could be called psychological terrorism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top 10 in Points and Assist but not shoot first and he’s a foward but passing like a guard. MJ, Kobe, Kareem, Bird,… https://t.co/ja1w5hA49H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oreo cheesecake, and a glass of milk. How much will my body hate me? A lot. The answer is a lot. Am i going to regr… https://t.co/j637Imkb9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Trump bring in PNAC Iran-Contra neocon Elliot Abrams to help push a regime change coup in Venezuela within… https://t.co/OjoPfRJvMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro I was knocked tf out I wake up and I’m hungry as hell but it’s also 12:23am so I need to take my ass back to sleep lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darlinbiebss @DlVlNEGRANDE I agree, I was just using her as an example because she doesn’t have that Mariah Carey… https://t.co/ModxEkFGW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to be home with my babies!! @ Westwood North, Magnolia, Texas https://t.co/kvgcjWqXIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time to start a new adventure! I have a job interview today to work for Dior! Wish me luck! #Jobs #interview #adventure]]></document><document><![CDATA[[cont.] catherine deneuve by david bailey in uk vogue, april 1967 https://t.co/1mh3nhih6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truthtobetold9 @FeministaJones Exactly !! I’m so sick of their ignorance https://t.co/agLg51XTx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍸Curls and Cocktails🍸  Hello Hello Hello  Women, Ladies, Young Ladies, and Youth would you like to be able to curl… https://t.co/rNsTfVCpag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juic3box_g4ming @jonnybernthal You know what they say about opinions!? Yours will not change mine, so what's your purpose here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Kelly Services? We're hiring in Hershey, PA! Click for details: https://t.co/Z3os9FMSVI #KellyJobs #KellyServices]]></document><document><![CDATA[a pigeon overhead shat on me on my way to #LLiNYC2019 so it’s safe to say the auspices have been taken.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EugeniaMaryDon1 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump They could make you richer, but is the price right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenagabby @tootlelOops @marzelladeville @Skipease @LiseGervais12 @wgnamerica @OfficialDOGNews @bobbybrown719… https://t.co/RHpZCIg6cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandatriana_ @Stanlllyy Okay 1) pack of cigarettes  2) bong in my hand  3) inhaler right next to me 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @rope_shakerag for working with me earlier this year to use @nearpod in my music room 😁 Now my 5th graders u… https://t.co/i1CoCcTLYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful the most stressful part of my day will be shopping with my mom and sister! #stateholday #MondayMorning]]></document></documents></author>