<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@RoseLaoutaris &amp; I are reuniting this morning and I’m pretty pumped https://t.co/gy5oXdKELG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/8XS5T6h1rj]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's amusing. This brings back memories of my aunt. #laughter #laugh #smirk #laughable https://t.co/CKyCttISm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacred Heart gets the lead up to 35-18 with 3:17 in the second.  Jayden Stone started quietly, but he's up to 6 poi… https://t.co/BmJKCz4yoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deadl_E_Cheese The only relevance to me on any of this is the extent to which it might move the people.  What do y… https://t.co/846SJmotmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauStack I don’t like their resume right now but if they can get a couple of wins in he ACC tourney and go 3-1 o… https://t.co/Wiz6zf04m2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crosswordlita @JordanUhl @bobclendenin @TuckerCarlson He should be. She is a no good person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@splinter_news There’s so much room to build in Texas and with no state income tax it makes more sense. Why uproot… https://t.co/vE7j9wfQiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disagree. Doubt they make the trade if they don’t have some idea of Talbot’s likelihood to re-sign. So they get an… https://t.co/OvHoMnF1wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbiehowell @ralpo67 Found this one. I took this photo of him in July of 1999. https://t.co/GTVIxV0did]]></document><document><![CDATA[The coolest trio of brothers to ever exist. I still listen to their Debut Album!!! I feel slightly more whole https://t.co/W2uLbnp439]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/syiSf2skwX   #NewUpdate, #WeMakeaPartyOutOfJammin, #ComingToSanDiego, #ComingToTijuanaMexico https://t.co/r7bdzIElqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubySojourner Me too, but bc I work from 6 p to 6 a Graveyard lol.  What keeps you up ? (Coffee aside 😏)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinGarwood I think the eyesore 'historic' buildings help drive that narrative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechrisbuskirk @SebGorka To paraphrase Nancy P. , Tucker simply has a different language experience and blah, blah blah....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/5PgCrB90K8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because every woman was once a little girl. Born with a spirit to take on the world. Love her. Support her. Respect… https://t.co/c1nE9tBdzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends You sound nervous and guilty.   Just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this a show about @TheLadyBearica baby sitting children or a show where she plays a a family’s child?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m caught up on rest from my trip to @BSidesSF and @RSAConference after two back to back days of a goo… https://t.co/XztSdcaG8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seancannell @Roland_US @CES @SonyAlpha @skillshare Super cool, but super pricey for the consumer/hobbyist and casu… https://t.co/SJPHpDv88D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué lástima que la inseguridad por medio de sus líneas de presión sigan amedrentando gente y autoridades… https://t.co/KzMlTinkVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DisavowTrump20 @bannerite @IlhanMN Cong-women Omar is a symbol of t greatness of America. Our govt should embrace… https://t.co/YRyAWNOwGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOberg @elizabeth201823 Cows milk is for growing baby cows into big cows. Nothing else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pilots say with the soaring number of close calls in the skies, it's not a matter of if, but when a drone and plane… https://t.co/puqGD6PJLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WarlockSalarez @Top10Annie @DicePools @Th3Danimal @doogmcnoog https://t.co/lPZRYFTrUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Acklesevans_ @itisdxvid Jeph Loeb confirmed none of the Netflix series were cancelled due to the numbers:… https://t.co/7QzQ6VkDQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when they said a strike would be illegal for the air traffic controllers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible. A VARobbery. Terrific effort tonight from United, but they shouldn’t be advancing on that call. #MUFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @PNASNews special edition on #vaccines and #AMR is out on a nice web interface https://t.co/ENAmaKGPN1{"issue_i… https://t.co/JK0zVWoVJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Ted Cruz wants El Chapo to pay for border wall https://t.co/qiIKtpvjWi via @NBCNews.  Doesn’t surprise me that… https://t.co/jlHCn5PQKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SHistorians @WinterParkGolf The best treasure on that list is in Tallahassee 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump owes the American Taxpayer $1.4 Trillion for his giveaway , and this TERRORIST now demands another $5.7 Billi… https://t.co/wF8uHLuSko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pardon Manafort enough is enough sentence and send home I can hear Dems now President let’s him die    Know the Pre… https://t.co/lvNLbw9RuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BattleHim4Repub @Elyrya_Ylnae @TheRickWilson WARNING: SARCASM DETECTORS OFFLINE. WARNING: SARCASM DETECTORS OFFLINE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 16, and I just finished another amazing cardio workout 🏋️‍♀️ @powerhousegym rocking to the mix of @djmellstarr… https://t.co/86L1lTgZqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every workout is progress. Killer leg day with dchin501. Started with some back squats and worked our way into some… https://t.co/xxk8igMPZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hugocarvajal4f muy buena pregunta.  Seguro hay una lista grande que deberá responder. Tendrá que arrodillarse ante… https://t.co/i6N3rluOdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phelpsbecca @lexi4prez How many female teachers compared to males have you had?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buckman08 He could both be the best coach in college basketball....and be dead wrong about how he handles this issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldExposureWB @BCDenver_WBB @tomiajohnson She comes by it honestly!  Absolutely love @coachtj &amp; his family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YDynasty27 @ErinLovesNYY I agree.   I don’t  want Frazier here sitting the bench. Want him to have reg reps in AAA… https://t.co/q7dB8cL1Zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #AnthemIsAMust on @tyltsports. Honoring the military is important https://t.co/c3WqyWb8wG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess all those years of GOP lead Benghazi and Hillary Clinton email hearings were fake too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad the snow stopped but does the sunshine really have to come with -11 degrees early this morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Derbinator @ReBourneAgain they need to leave when the contract is up or asked for their realease]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this kid and his passion for art! #Bastrop #FineArts #TxEd #PorfirioSalinas https://t.co/PQWvhTjZRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflection is about taking inventory of personal successes, cataloging lessons learned from failures, evaluating yo… https://t.co/c0hBjExLYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an American im just here for fantastic curling, but I find myself rooting for Saskatchewan in the Scotties just… https://t.co/r9Wu5EHgG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson How can someone who works at a Sunglasses Hut afford an armored vehicle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickkanthony @EASPORTS_MUT @SteveAtwater27 Yeah man, he is everywhere on the field and closes in quick. 2 picks first h2h game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to everyone! 💝 From me and my Ghost Producer ❤️🌼 @ Riverside, California https://t.co/sVUGQVAn0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, look at this diversity...you have all points represented of the white male hair loss spectrum...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heeey !! NAO ! L like your sweter , yo look very nice ! Cheers from mexico 🇲🇽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mik235 @worldwise001 I think that's the case in the screenshot, yeah. If that's objectionable, I'm not sure why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He Is A Racist.  He Is A Conman. He Is A Cheat.” I knew this about him and therefore didn’t vote for nor will I support him. #wakeupsheeple]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koster_jay @realDonaldTrump @POTUS When I look back to 1973-1974, @koster_jay I can say in earnest that our curren… https://t.co/jqBl55z7lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_nicodemo @FrankLevesque09 C’est la seule chose de vraie tant qu’à moi!! 👊👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpirnia Argh, I forgot again! How is King Cake, really good? Can’t believe I’ve never had it! #FatTuesday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 11 days left in February. Hang in there, whatever your going through it gets better I promise.   This tweet is for myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savtah8 @ltmd11 @RealJamesWoods This, I knew , the word “faultiness was supposed to have been the word , not fault… https://t.co/Fq1jp4T3xZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over The "Period" bSP PFC! x2.5 ✈️  Inspired by @kuuuuki 😊😊 https://t.co/FDwBDfNgCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fraternity suspended for having pledges wear Dora the Explorer backpacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV @KamalaHarris @MrColionNoir EARNED IN LEXINGTON 1775? Fake Indians 1773? I also got fake news. Most valuable… https://t.co/zwMm33nmVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goal: Corbin Rumboli gets drury on the board with 2:08 left. Greenfield still leads 4-1. Assist by Toby Ellingwood]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost as if they get him to tweet. Just adds to the comedy. I recorded it last night and just finished watchi… https://t.co/g0qpl3ATqW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarieNews3LV @BryanNews3LV @ChloeNews3LV Look at those beautiful angels forever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TTOGIRLS2024 @TTO6thGGBB @TTOGrassroots @rljames10 @CoachBuckCarey @coach_iii @TeamTakeoverGBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreZnyc621 Cap overrated- Contenders spend well over it - OWED: OKC - 93 mil GSW - 51 mil  Gotta pay to play Z.. And that’s just a few...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennypang @elonmusk @raulv48 @bryanMackSC @Tesla At least lifetime supercharging for these guys that got jammed El… https://t.co/wfs2oiMOQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moose Box #mailbox #moose #taxidermy #blue #green #pink #photocollage #collage #art #modernart #artoftheday… https://t.co/AeRl6vwdpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaltripRam @WaltripAlumni former flute player in the @HamiltonMS_Band and @waltripramband Congratulations Joey!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny how Lebron just walks off the court before the game is over and goes straight to the locker room without shak… https://t.co/OHQTgv8s3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[OFICIAL, HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Yo… https://t.co/d36bKBu1zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulafaris Paula my deepest condolences to you and your family. You are an awesome daughter and you know your dad… https://t.co/K6h6bQf3HR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ñoñeando jajajaja 🤓  He practicado 31 palabras de Inglés (estadounidense), incluida «mixer» en solo 5 minutos con D… https://t.co/VuSI8IcxpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vypermajik @HaloOutpost Thanks!   Hopefully there will be some cool pins like it at the Post Exchange in Outpost D… https://t.co/EHEN1TuvfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffwilsontech What happened with Android to really save it as a platform is that Google was able to build a set o… https://t.co/b9UF5NKKnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoagie is really glad to see me back!! #puppy #morkie #cutie @ Washington Heights, Manhattan https://t.co/w9FslR6Slu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Distance Time @ Jeff Rouse Swim and Sport Center https://t.co/ueI4wYue1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the most satisfying things I love about San Luis Obispo...the sanctuary for these magnificent creatu… https://t.co/s6MxqxsY66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude deserved it. Bohemian Rhapsody is an elite movie. Well done sir well done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencer_young5 @Jon_DelValle15 Yeah for sure bro, teams dont realize it until it’s way too late and they are stuck big time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite all the Lakers issues and LeBron's outside projects, I still feel they'll make the playoffs, then get AD th… https://t.co/l7jF9szO1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScAr801 @Cbass83 @jphanned If Mack was resigned with the Raiders, he would have sank the franchise as they would h… https://t.co/36s8B0HNrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goku #sailormoon #dragonballz  #anime @ Mission, Texas https://t.co/6dNYiTvSAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me taking a 12 min break cause that’s how I roll. Don’t tell my manager.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having an imbalanced backswing and follow through in your stroke may be causing not only speed, but directional iss… https://t.co/gmkJ7fjI2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryandasilva1798 @PhoenixSherbroo @ArmadaBLB J’ai dit a ryan que ça l’air il a trop manger avant game 🤢 https://t.co/zaMtZ7xYw0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale You are a freaking liar. Police wouldn't let in more than LEGAL capacity. You don't know what truth is. Lock him up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geographywee Hey! That sounds great! We don’t have them in our class, but they are on campus! Thanks, Chris!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro Her comments, which have so gravely offended you, were about actions and policies, not faith or birth c… https://t.co/bva77eUjsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full review: "I underwent four lid blepharoplasty on January 31, 2019. It has only been 11 days and I am very pleas… https://t.co/q77JuJghG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SInow @JohnKruk It’s stupid money! Those kind of contracts ruin teams for many many years! Just look at the Detroit Tigers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[While this is my Friday Funny, the truth is....it actually doesn’t need to be this way! Do you have the self-care p… https://t.co/7bCgaKLigu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the other way around, I'm on my ladies side when I wake up 🤣 @AlisaMarquez21 does this make me a bitch 🤔🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @Phillies @Marlins_Man Playing in Dodger Stadium is a step above the Citi Dump! Weak fan base!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only y'all knew the joy I feel to finally ask Siri to give me the 10 day forecast (as I do everyday when I wake… https://t.co/JyMW67uRgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mirac7es @ogDaize @lts_Paco @Cruhmb She just going off on everyone at this point, no fucks given anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am saddened to hear of the death of Lee Radziwill. I got to know her during the many times she traveled with her… https://t.co/KUSsu4jUoU]]></document></documents></author>