<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[They are both female that’s rare especially the Treecko that is a 12.5% chance https://t.co/aYdOoD442d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super! Now let’s target every low voter turn out district and register voters @ScottPresler  is helping and I will,… https://t.co/ogNsNCP0yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you know certain things you just don’t feel the same vibe anymore.☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[these mothafuckas just added an hour and 45 to my shift. 😭 WHOOO ISSSS RESPONSIBLEEEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Taisha @Esther188rod  GIRLFRIEND ❤️ WHAT IS WRONG WITH MY DEMOCRATS MILWAUKEE PLEASE AWFUL THERE FOOD IS AWFU… https://t.co/X54DYRQF0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[i never thought i would be the type to sit on the same side of the booth as my man .... I’m - 😩😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday my handsome! Mommy and daddy love you so much! 🎈😘🎊🌟 https://t.co/icvSAsrD8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mcflinchy @CrankageGames He was scary af, yet you wanted to hang out with him. I don’t know what this says about me😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway My husband &amp; I love your gift with cutting through BS &amp; stating the ironic core truth. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cant even watch this game but now I'm reading on the twitterverse that Ques is down. This team = injuries SMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanKeshet Please explain this at my court date for when I punch a scooter rider who hits my dog. I support wider s… https://t.co/qOtFjvYVld]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has a plan for you! Don't feel pressured trying to fit into everyone else's plan. ~ There is one glory of the s… https://t.co/mnLO1mfhrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[to all my friends that i grew apart from, don’t forget you can still call me if you need someone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein when they come knocking at your door to arrest you is the day California is free of your kind of scum… https://t.co/OV0t9MnqQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter It’s what low IQ people do when they can’t find appropriate words to communicate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AggieBaseball @SECNetwork @TAMUHotelCC Fabulous first outing of his college career! Really enjoyed watching Jonathan Childress pitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jm_mcgrath @kinsellawarren Usually everything is done quietly, behind the scenes. Not, god forbid, in PUBLIC, like… https://t.co/uVUxC334VQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annendil @MomAutie @ellievan65 They act like they can take the money with them and buy their way into heaven]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanSinn Did he compare you to a semi-notorious college sports commentator this time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peut-on convaincre en étant méprisant? Le cas François Bégaudeau https://t.co/pF1sfLImWh via @slatefr]]></document><document><![CDATA[remember when people said i looked like them, and then i showed them a pic of the dog w a blog girl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Meghan_Trainor I love your video for your song #marryme https://t.co/28fEEQHRjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[People get so mad when you catch them doing what they're not supposed to be doing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbkotv on Facebook Democrats is threatening to leave the Party if Nancy Pelosi can't stop this relentless anti-Semitism and racism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DietCoke Thanks for getting this meteorologist through her midnight shifts clear-headed and alert! 🙌🏼🌪⛈❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachMayweather Could not ask for a better coaches and his staff leading this program and these young men!!!! Than… https://t.co/wr7tXHgvZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is important. I can’t count the number of conversations I’ve been in re: cross-sector coordination or charter… https://t.co/liYfpZERIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@killiann_ @joshuaivancic And because they tell you you have a better chance of making more money with a bachelors/… https://t.co/TyVFosBZcj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoschHomeUS our SilencePlus Super dishwasher does not go two weeks without an E24 error. We are in a small apartme… https://t.co/o7kJpbqEUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon Personally, I think  @SecNielsen should step down if she isn’t fired.  Gross incompetence. But then we… https://t.co/JkriA9cPoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF enjoying nice dinner with fam now off to Merrimack Women’s bball playoff game https://t.co/CTAuhPwAP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glam look done today on the beautiful @jessicakalmar using the @ABHcosmetics #sultry #palette! . sephora_disneyspri… https://t.co/bevFsW9Rpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @BlairImani! Still here at #SXSW2019 ? I am! Lets meet up for coffee or tea.☕️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delwichejody @Mimirocah1 @joncoopertweets Take Ibuprofen &amp; hit the gym❣️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is below a 40% approval rating.  You are a friggen disaster for this country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @TroyTrojansWBB plays at 2 pm on Saturday and WE NEED YOU THERE as well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 mins of cringe office team building starting now https://t.co/YEubD57jxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 If she had hired qualified staff who know protocol and spent time preparing this would not happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ericbryant5 @Latinlade58 @LoriinUtah @RealTT2020 @realDonaldTrump I agree! I think it was more of an attempt to ha… https://t.co/4uvlVAQiMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[a disposição que eu não tenho durante o dia, eu tenho o triplo de madrugada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body is not looking like it’s going to Hawaii in two months and I’m offended]]></document><document><![CDATA[Courage should be rewarded with something other than 5+ years in prison #RealityWinner #FreeRealityWinner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redoregongal @ColumbiaBugle Always!  She had a best seller with the book she wrote about Trump when she was supporting him, but not since]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChumelTorres Es irónico que al no ser periodista tengas un programa en HBO y otro en radiofurmula, como si fueras un periodista Imparcial.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmund_Fraud @mcfunny @Plasticdoe @Rosewind2007 @badzoot7 @KimPaddockASD @djt10 @JuliaHadley15 @SueQuez @jkellyca… https://t.co/MRFPIxGqYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Realtor Humor😂 #makeitagreatday @ LA Fitness San Antonio/Babcock &amp; Huebner https://t.co/uhKFRrKgDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great rule is to not destroy your house as would a fool. Ppl fighting for control of a home they destroy. Better… https://t.co/GFU4fTVe9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so discouraged to write this paper I’m just sitting here waiting for my phone to die so I’ll stop scrolling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalEdMom Not sure who you mean? Everyone in the thread is a parent and also works in education in some way...w… https://t.co/iXZAjYtaEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachariahBASSan @aaeisenhower @ShaneSturkie @_emmabradleyy please dear rave god]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyyroro @thdShannon @StaceyTank @LisaAdamsTHD @lgranskie @PattiSingelyn @Hamilton4138 @keeley_chet @hderich… https://t.co/yozxfXP2xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️🌱🤗😊😂 #CBDCoffee #HappyGirl #PainFree @ Rocky Mount, Virginia https://t.co/6MsHigJUv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A esquerda escandalizada pelo seu reflexo no espelho, adorei! #BolsonaroTemRazão]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing Cat’s Cradle  // funny pictures - funny photos - funny images - funny pics... #humor #laugh #smile #clever https://t.co/1se096aWNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beep beep! Outta my way, I’m on my way to @DisneylandToday 🏰🎢🎠 #Disneyland #disneylife #disneychic #arewethereyet]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess we'll have to call him Zak of all trades now. Get it? See what I did there? Yeah, this was an @AaronGoodwin… https://t.co/BZUUFAsTNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle @johneo09 @LivePDNation @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @LivePdFantasyLG Beautiful song, and both of you had a great voice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BookerTb0303 Happy birthday brother and I love you so much and I am really thankful for you being in my life and y… https://t.co/jnbCNafJ62]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #familyday2019! I'm so grateful that I was able to spend quality time with my family this weekend and we had… https://t.co/dAhdAcQ0ZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s two women having a loud ass conversation outside of my bedroom window and I’m just trying to sleep please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DMurphyOfficial @playbill Hope you had a great birthday Donna!!!! ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright alright Jonas brothers 👏🏻 sucker is on repeat this morning @jonasbrothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RestlessNews @co_rapunzel4 @RichVee1 @CitizensFedUp @Ireland0828 @Stewar1W @birdieglad @Maxeightyeight @MaxSped… https://t.co/liiut7Lc2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj The Biggest Problem in AR is a Stump Dump Fire. Seems a company took waste expensive to properly dispose o… https://t.co/dM5J8KCCCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phranqueigh Where all my servers at? 🙋🏻‍♀️ When 85% of your income comes directly from the people who berate you.… https://t.co/iOQc639CY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're a wasted vote if you don't learn to deal in fact ... Canada can't afford to lose another election to willful… https://t.co/nF5bbJFlrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abortion started out with the first weeks and for rape or health of mother which was rare. They have now taken this… https://t.co/CUeI4VUwNb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CorneliusTanks2 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump Comrade, your English needs work, even for a bot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commuting from New Braunfels to San Antonio has made me miss Austin traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grabbed Chris a few special bottles while I was at the Incline Public House last night! 💕🤗 Did you get yours yet?… https://t.co/0UJETgLEZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast Oh man, I grew up listening to Mystery Theater on RADIO (yep, I’m THAT old! 😂). Looking forward to this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you really like me or am I just there to help you pass time? Boy you’re losing me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GFanff @RaisedOnGH I wish they would bring back Jeff Weber it would be cool if she had a father to help her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the annoyance scale, hearing other people's music on the #TTC is second only to hearing the sound effects of their video games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How Filipino families go on a vacation: after 30mins of driving: bathroom/eat 1st stop: eat, after 15mins of walkin… https://t.co/BVX94SgXAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siano2020 I agree. Not the first time for our country to engage in such evil!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had to warn Aiden Morten that if he wears a denim button up and tearaway khakis to this wedding, I will no longer be his plus one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandvickScience High School Science Olympiad team placed 4th at regionals 2019....on to States! https://t.co/wMomic9DLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncusack How can you condone this? This is not an isolated incident with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bashers on $VYST have become Bullish, bouncing of the 200ma a Golden Cross approaching has that effect. I don't… https://t.co/FIHVflulmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My children are 26, 23 &amp; 17 and I have to know their where about at all times!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We keep aspirin in our house ... do you? Thanks to my colleague Dr Peter Scheufler for sharing his story so we can… https://t.co/in9FhQ0iT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went tanning today &amp; didn’t post a picture of my legs, while in the bed, I bet this is why the sororities would never want me. 😭💔😢😔😖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He will win ....and beat you OUT of the White House and right into an orange jumpsuit!!!  I hope you like orange!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 de março, dia Internacional da mulher. Hoje, pra mim, essa data adquiriu um novo significado. Estar em Nova York… https://t.co/k98wgGAeDl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had to wake up to some creepy sounds outside my apartment at 3am didn’t I? https://t.co/nNImPECMd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmkeene2 @kvmidd85 @tommortl @StephenMJeff @fed_up_pup @maryllewis53 @rudyandcobie @Richard98144666 @American2b… https://t.co/AuTSODBr9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏛Con Sue Photography and Design🏛  ☀️Like our photos...Follow our IG ☀️  🏛This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🏛… https://t.co/K4W0UyXRb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read a whole ass book (and took notes) in less than four hours. Go me. 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to dive in the creative box and discover even more about #CreatingBlue ✨💙✨🎼 @ Oakland, California https://t.co/AKEGda0XRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mandolin_Orange You’ve made my night TWO nights this year!! Thanks for being you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day🙏🏻❤️Shout out to all Of you Bad Ass Ladies and cheers to your friends who are out th… https://t.co/OYIzvAh99X]]></document><document><![CDATA[im missing europe soooo much right now:( seeing all the videos is making me sad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gaye_gallops @RodStryker TERRIBLE!!  And they complained about Gitmo and waterboarding!! They complain about illeg… https://t.co/yJPHiKqKeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[They should be members of that ski resort for life, but I guess a year is at least a thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJerryNadler @nytimes @NydiaVelazquez @SenGillibrand @SenWarren @RepMaloney @RepJeffries @RepYvetteClarke… https://t.co/DQ3bd7uQNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wildwithpants @TimDownie1 @BakingTimeClub @sweetloungeuk 😯 My birthday🎂 is August 5th, too!😊 And Tim👇🏻...🙌🏻😉 😊 https://t.co/WewE65ROq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @Tesla; fyi : summary of price reductions of certain Tesla models. Retweet. Gloria]]></document><document><![CDATA[do i have to make my bio "big titty liberal bitch" again why are we spreading the rumor again that i'm a republican… https://t.co/zE1P0YftO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can provide compassionate care of substance use disorders and work for healthy pregnancies and families without… https://t.co/jiLQClEmuO]]></document></documents></author>