<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Cook @Elizabeth_Cook #elizabethcook thehitonecafe #hitonecafe #nolacountyradio #nolacounty @ Hi Tone https://t.co/lRmxCx8qjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @QuinnXCII says “your gym membership is not a crown, you’re not so tough” I kind of feel personally attacked]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friends told me that I had two cute outfits in one night and honestly that is the kind of build up I need]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Catholic leads Central Valley 56-42 at the end of the third quarter of their WPIAL Class 4A championship game… https://t.co/e2FLqByixw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieScrofano @realtimrozon #FightforWynonna #WynonnaEarp @SYFY @IDWPublishing https://t.co/ZJZGqj1Dex]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSkolnik @Rosie what pisses me off is the news people they are so focused on this fool #45 that those in fli… https://t.co/5UyS78bmig]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Communism_Kills Where did A O C and the others come from? Great video describing the process. https://t.co/Lz2Szj95Yv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShaunaB44 As a crew member here, yes please also look up the aircraft type you fly in, cuz I get yelled at all the… https://t.co/kMwiliszEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[First ever Oklahoma sunset. Quick week here to check in on a project then San Antonio bound. Getting back into the… https://t.co/sXxiIut7Jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones | Season 8 | Official Trailer (HBO) https://t.co/lVmL180noM via @YouTube WINTER IS FINALLY HERE!!!… https://t.co/xbv7kTXpZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #weedywednesday. Can you name this weed - scientific name and all? https://t.co/KpTSnsXEgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to see one thing before @UVAMensHoops is done for the season - Jack Salt shoot a trey #UVAvsVT… https://t.co/LLYtvgXdqF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kind of experimentation builds better story writers and makes for better stories. Taking the time to tinker th… https://t.co/fScYbFyha1]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re a sweetheart and you’re intelligent and kind and funny and you manage to make me forget all my pain and sadn… https://t.co/XWpAv6mRNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know how the heck this happened or when but @LukeBryanOnline follows ME little ole ME. My mind is officiall… https://t.co/EZubJRQwiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might just take a quick trip to Cali for a long weekend pretty soon. Anybody wanna tag along so I don’t have to go by myself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@another__dad one of your ears is smaller than the other, it’s just not ideal in a partner]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok it’s time for me to find a boo who wants to stay in with me on the weekends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnfollowTrump Yes. You, the president harass us every day. President harassment indeed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I can’t go back to yesterday because I was a different person then.” -Alice @ Action Church https://t.co/6NdrHRnx4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; moderate rain temperature up 46°F -&gt; 56°F wind 6mph -&gt; 3mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahershala Ali just gave a first-class acceptance speech. Sell done, sir. #Oscars2019 #MahershalaAli]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go get something to eat but I got a good parking spot. Refuse to lose it 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you ever masturbated to my pictures I expect white roses and chocolate covered strawberries on thursday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zach_Brach other fans just need to learn how much he’s had to step up, especially at his age, that it’s normal to… https://t.co/8jjk5jQFJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LeahRymer I wish I could give u all the hugs :( I hope ur ok I’m here if u wanna talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are out and about today for #TittyTuesday come see me in my private location in #Englewood until 10pm! 720-583… https://t.co/2N7zUgF08X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rt for Greys Anatomy  Like for One Tree Hill  (Trying to prove a point🙄)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make someone smile...  #lolove #nyc #valentinesday @ Park Slope https://t.co/1PvGwRyND8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the terrific @sagaftra podcast about organizing #telenovelas with @katiebarberi and @azarpablo — hosted b… https://t.co/H9H0ZEJEOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fender4Ed @NDUMFORD_THS @DFenderOfArt Puuurfect read for you and your family.  Love the Pete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I seriously HATE B-BALL except for my @SparkyArizonaSt @ASUathletics @SunDevilHoops #remy screaming my ass off! #forkem]]></document><document><![CDATA[World View  I find I covet  #kindness  and kindness  covets me, For when I’m  kind I’m finding  it travels back  to… https://t.co/JDePlrFQU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging with my homegirls at the Twin City Kiwanis Club pancake day! #pancakeday #twincitykiwanis #dtws… https://t.co/KBljSZ0zFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgardiner_1 @SenateDems @HouseDemocrats #HandMarkedPaperBallots actually ARE the solution; at least part of it :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[#getmydrift #gotfrosted ❄️ #nothingisimpossibleifyoujustputyourmindtoit Took my run to the streets today🏃‍♀️No side… https://t.co/YwcjovYyGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s good!  Mexican people have been flowing through to America for years!  Mexican government has selfishly just… https://t.co/3r7kbp0cSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well done to the first African American woman to win this category @iamRuthECarter - note to other winners please d… https://t.co/DSMW8SFscA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If paper valentines were still a thing, I'd give mine to you ❤️ https://t.co/BAu9DgwOKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[MBB: Crazy night is about to unfold before our eyes 🔥🤪🔥 https://t.co/xUbLTQakYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[JQ is the man. His star is on the rise, but he remains down to earth and remembers even a lowly extra (basically fu… https://t.co/Le9HfIGCDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brigitte St-Pierre Leader #Tupperware à #Sherbrooke 819-238-5138  https://t.co/tk4p8gTKK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My high school crush just posted a mediocre video of him playing guitar on Facebook and man oh man did I dodge a bullet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist I, for one, enjoy reading your non political tweets too! It helps me go away and decompress for a litt… https://t.co/oGlDwBEl4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice Honestly, I can never, ever get tired of @kelly_clarkson’s outgoing personality!😆❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so stressed i’ve been on the verge of puking for the past two days i’m ready for break]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fhsvgockey Congratulations on a great season including Hockomock Champs!!  We are all very proud of you!!  ❤️🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also @MissDelainie and I are in agreement. Please no more @AcademyAwardsHD hosts. This was refreshing. #whoswithme]]></document><document><![CDATA[I retweeted something but it didn’t tweet the pic just the caption 😒 lol i had to delete the whole thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson I've boycotted DNC since they've allowed Sanders to run as a Dem and cause mayhem again! I will donate d… https://t.co/kAJtHtWKz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@back_2_fact @macabreavenue @Rockford_IL You dead ass act like you live across seas. Bye.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings  Sorry sir,  but the person you tout as one of your best friends is a racist idiot. Who brings a Black… https://t.co/u27tnGH0t4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same. I get emotional thinking about how amazing and freeing it truly was]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of MO State Wrestling:   Dominic Cahalan places 4th.  🤼‍♂️💪 @FredBeckKTVO #kvproud #moyouthwrestling @KVDailysports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Princess             Eugenie     " A True Princess "💕 A Princess of Her People .. For Her People!      England Is S… https://t.co/VtGMgmAY5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @tinyboo49 @SenFeinstein Of course they do. That’s why Dump nominated him! #Barr]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nIX4kGJUTf LET THE SONG I SING BE PLEASING TO YOU LORD JESUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[R u ever just so tired from working all you do when you’re not at work is sleep? Bc same]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snowconvallaria @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch Tom,  First of all, I love ♥️ ya’ Sweetie but this one… https://t.co/RFTy784boq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Valentine's Day.  Remind your loved ones to get their PSA checked, get a mammogram, have a screening colonosco… https://t.co/VH9J6fdWDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wise person once told me, “let people do what they wanna do, so you see what they’d rather do.” That’ll answer al… https://t.co/8ah6XSkh36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just need your best friend and some stupid snap filters to make you belly laugh so hard you both forg… https://t.co/J7VH3OZEjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Specifically can we call up that Rizzo kid to center Guch and another player for the playoffs? 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Romans 8:39 Nor height, nor depth, nor any other creature, shall be able to separate us from the love of God, which… https://t.co/RcXVwF54xx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m looking forward to this conversation! Check out this great resource if you’re a twitter chat newbie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After talking about it last week, I decided to re-read Ender's Game. This really is one of the best science fiction… https://t.co/PJiwFE3mMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @DrMarkGreen4TN Well then DO something about it take ACTION ‼️ Same old crap from Washington nothing subs… https://t.co/wA5Zcqu6bJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HTZfan @RECITpresco Merci! Je vais créer un diagramme à pictogrammes adapté au programme de la #Beebot se sont les… https://t.co/FDlBx8jsvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept the challenge from @AmberDembowski to post covers of seven books I love; no exceptions, no reviews- just t… https://t.co/h6ueUqu4v0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is always a productive process that you can’t always see. . . . #workout👍 #workingthroughpain #workoutroutine… https://t.co/ZVun29TZ4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMah26387695 She may fool those around her but, GOD knows her “heart”.  BE afraid Nancy, you can’t fool GOD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine your wife telling you she needs space after she has sex with one of your best friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same issue we need lots more Zumiez stash rewards. Too many posters and backgrounds. Rewards not moving should be t… https://t.co/R4R53VxvPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Favorite O-GUY @iamerikestrada doing pod casting ❤️😊 📸: credit from Erik's ig story ) @ Maryland https://t.co/rZv7dpVn8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimemurrgay @MsJaimeMurray Omg where are these pics from?? Also what is your Instagram ? Would love to follow you ☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[To protestors tomorrow, about @realDonaldTrump #NationalEmergency I want answers, why did no one question Obama, bo… https://t.co/wRiLwXOLtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Well written and a good reminder that getting rid of Trump still leaves us with a vocal, ignorant (scienc… https://t.co/MrjlpItUSk]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂  “Tag someone and say nothing” Share to story for a follow. @ QuikTrip https://t.co/lPfiFpQlqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReesKassen @robannan 'How to be taken seriously as a thought leader 101']]></document><document><![CDATA[When my parents ask when I’m gonna give them some grandkids   👇🏽👇🏽👇🏽👇🏽👇🏽👇🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I step away from the world for yoga, and my whole world is finally complete again! @JasonWitten makes his return to… https://t.co/Bef1q9A3lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in Columbus, GA! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Office Manager at Kelly Serv… https://t.co/cgtwmEeYaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #facialfriday! Let’s talk about dermal infusions. This amazing facial exfoliates with a diamond tip that’s cus… https://t.co/BsywesnkJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebradfordfile Jussie is now a "victim".  Somehow, I knew he'd come out smelling like a rose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for the screams and ....We won! @GRHS_Stallions https://t.co/9cDali2DJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breakoutedu doing a breakout box on The Giver #schoollibrariesrock #breakoutedu  https://t.co/9u2qYhxPs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Effondrement de toits enneigés: la ministre @AndreeLaforest rappelle aux propriétaires leur responsabilité #JDQ… https://t.co/tuRS21eoSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyJairRamos @10APG @Rayados @TigresOficial @EnnerValencia14 @eduvargas_17 Jair y si es sorpresa vamos  con todo mis tigrrs 😘🐯🐯🐯💛💙👍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @chucktodd @Jim_Jordan Remember, he’s protecting the president!🤬👎🏾⛓ Did you ask him about the #OhioState investigation?🤬👎🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t showered 🚿 since Thursday and I am not ashamed! However, now is the time. Even my cats are judging me. Ch… https://t.co/oyz99FoPu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[In waek up at 3am its 6:30 and I don't want to know nothing about it, everything still the same o ,same o boring bullshet routine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JiminEsArte Ok pero te Mando mensaje en 45 minutos, me van a llamarte de Italia por visas que abogados estan hacie… https://t.co/uyOTdLsYVN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McGuireSuzette @DISupdates @austindillon3 @WaltDisneyWorld @RCRracing @TeamChevy @CocaColaRacing @CMANGO… https://t.co/MlpQPn00HL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @AdamAuerbach to post the covers of 7 books I love (pleasure or professional) w/no e… https://t.co/B5G7ZA0X0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 50 of 365: finished watching Weightlifting Fairy Kim Bok Joo a few day ago and now I’m almost finished watching… https://t.co/HMwfTliE2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yessssssssssssss this was exactly my thought I think Kurt will have a match with my favorite wrestler forever… https://t.co/ib7MeVRTM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RippleCreekNW @VisitSanya @SouthernerSays @RoadTripsCoffee @monstervoyage @The_Jenius @HHLifestyleTrav… https://t.co/W3brKbyiyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok i like them sweats too. I wish they sold more Tommy Hilfiger stuff at the mall near me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my gosh. I LOVE this call. NO ONE is happier for Cory Schneider to finally get back in the win column than… https://t.co/Cz6mdCyw6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shari2112 @4238_449 @Dax_x98 @AlexHonnold 💯 Love the movie, I've watched a few times and the reaction is the same.… https://t.co/Qn3p5U6w51]]></document></documents></author>