<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[my sister’s boyfriend is flying me out to washington to surprise her for her birthday so i’m now the one and only m… https://t.co/XxiYxftOWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the earrings @junkstarsok when I was there last week. I bought the red ones and a pair with a cross.… https://t.co/i7IvQvhjx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 She's small, the puppies might be putting pressure on her lungs, along with everything else. If she's… https://t.co/PlKPHxpVjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaFrom970 @CNN There are many many of these. Try a little research yourself  https://t.co/I6NCYOwMgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I experienced a whole lot of firsts with the wrong people but I’m gonna appreciate all my last’s with the right per… https://t.co/aACg5Vmr5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleSparkzLFG Hoping the best for you! These days we must stand firm and be our own advocates for our health. Gl… https://t.co/41IlbGUTes]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve allowed ourselves to get caught up in a mess we didn’t create &amp; take advice from those whom have created it 🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imagewords @TheCoopCowork @MakersLV @DTSummerlin The gratitude is all on this side, my friend ❤️☕️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking to boost your happiness and well-being, loving kindness meditation could be just the practice for… https://t.co/J2C0DwCYrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Despite feeling the need to hurl my most recent meal every time I see Roger Stone, I thought this guy was… https://t.co/KvZaS6PRPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buffalowildwings @bwwings got the #💯  #💯piece  #wekilledit 🤤🤤🤤🤙🏼🤙🏼🤙🏼 #🔥 @ Buffalo Wild Wings https://t.co/ZwDa1kEMXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedRaiders_B12C @gunsupnation @vivathematadors Well now... https://t.co/0Tbcf9uH88]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es su forma de decir que nos ama y que no puede vivir sin nosotros! https://t.co/52aruk97pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaureenDe2 @SandraK93322487 @chortletown @gaviota330 @andibeth012 @KindFashionNY EVIL TEEN. Lacks normal sense of… https://t.co/H3LFxneObR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s to being up all night with a child who just didn’t want to sleep https://t.co/L686KIILkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ss worked hard today @TurnerBartelTSA preparing for @fltsa conference next week!! Leaving work now headed home to w… https://t.co/0iGpXpcZNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[The argument that it’s expensive to raise kids does not faze me. I know this. This is one of the hundreds of reason… https://t.co/0vcqUbWtoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History March 3rd 1959 Lou Costello died -  b. 1908 (Louis Francis Cristillo), American Comedian, Abbott's… https://t.co/7hUm5JTzEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning Meditation: Seven baskets.  Jesus had compassion for the crowd. He provided sustenance. And there was even… https://t.co/JZipdTmvYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump No you’re highest priority is to line your pockets and the pockets of your rich cronie… https://t.co/v6tsNQ3u0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtomicOvermind I’ve often said to folks the job of billionaires is to realize their scope and use it for good. Cha… https://t.co/fKuL2QnoRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi so I just finished Marvelous Mrs. Maisel (I know am late) and I am TORN on this ending.   But I mean I guess I’m… https://t.co/46iXySGSZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 2640 Lake Shore Drive # 2114 #RivieraBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/j6Zpt2ZJR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m helping @SCJohnson build a 9th @PlasticBank recycling center. SCJ is building 8 centers, but if we help spread… https://t.co/k672Rfu56J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpolk_22 @CoachMattRhule We’re more than fans.... we’re family!  #SicEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a touching moment! A pre-Valentine visit from my nephew #eddiemendoza to #rosemontpersonalcarehome with… https://t.co/IdNXPLV4He]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelz_dc @krassenstein @mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 @GOP I don’t think so...  We shall see tho.  I’m going to revisi… https://t.co/M4zm2Ap0E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘The blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb’   I am so blessed to know that Ezra is will not know that feeling .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine The golf simulator was purchased by BHO with taxpayer funds. POTUS upgraded it with his own funds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeLaLosaCriolla @adrianadesala @caribbeancinepr Disculpa, pero en ningún momento he dicho que solo pasa en Puerto… https://t.co/HidrtIm4oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[even if you're on the right track, you'll get run over if you just sit there 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes you can  eat all that delicious food and more, and still lose weight with the 2bmindset. Who’s made these yummy… https://t.co/BQ2aygDA7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newberryjg @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Anyone with any sense of mind can hear and see he made absolutely no sen… https://t.co/CNjsXsqnov]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am sitting in the same row as an experienced Southwest flyer and I appreciate everything she did to keep our midd… https://t.co/6TqG7xf4hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss you Obama but Happy Presidents’ Day! . . . Monday’s..... . . . #mondays #mondaysbelike #workinghard… https://t.co/aEmrN1BomN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doy gracias a cielo por tener a mi mejor amiga conmigo💖 https://t.co/RrD3Jkczrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump You're way too good for that bunch of back stabbing bitches. ALL of them are really nasty...with th… https://t.co/ae0VlXH2rM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox I mean I'm not the one marrying my cousin but go off I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MassTrialAtty @JoyceWhiteVance No !  No! The Judge should NOT BE recusing herself over this !  She did absolutely… https://t.co/p6tCGMH5ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN THE FIFTIES, AMERICA WAS BEING INVADED BY COMMUNIST AND MUSLIMS. THEY HATED AMERICA AND TRIED TO CHANGE IT.  HOO… https://t.co/qXFFWsZ79B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Most are not cheering you right now. Your decisions are selfish not for the people and only are to fulfill your own selfish agendas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if you find yourself standing alone, speak up. Even if people get mad at you, speak up. It's not our job to st… https://t.co/fK32jVxuUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleymassey90 @_WendiWright This DCS worker for 17 plus years agrees!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake and Bake ADULTS ONLY... NOW STREAMING https://t.co/V91WuvRkRJ https://t.co/UcuRTlkYFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain jack sparrow!! And his mum apparently 😂😂😂 @ Pirates of the Caribbean https://t.co/27F7TpgWsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsey_sum happy birthday 💕🤩 I hope you have the best day:))) lets make a trip to BEV soon since I couldn’t make… https://t.co/kFYoj7Gke9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely need more vacation days. But so grateful for this long weekend with some of those I love most! https://t.co/8ckZzUuOwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lookout @Google @gartner Should be great! Patrick from @Gartner_inc told me he knows DR pretty well— good discussion ahoy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDuplass @januarydearest @netflix Would Netflix TELL you if it worked?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeman_e Can we have your permission to air this pic on CBS2, with credit to you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blue hair is fun until the rain makes the dye run down your back and stains your shirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fired4smart @Humasound AKA, she is pissed we don’t care. Lol. #teamspirit 🤙🏽💫💯❤️ My agenda is to help heal the pla… https://t.co/reDVZARhiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally will figure out what life truly means when it's all left behind 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guy and I are having three different conversations though text, snap &amp; Instagram. That deserves some kind of prize. 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Excellent well done! I’m also being tired of being called crazy, hysterical or a bitch. That means I’m… https://t.co/u9B50FePZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Navy Veteran Imprisoned in Iran Was Beaten, Family Says https://t.co/6F44ydCoau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still waiting on the answer as to WHY @BarackObama was meeting with @KinJongUm in Vietnam and why the news has not… https://t.co/2P95PiPAv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DisneyWalls #ThemeParks: The Wonderful Walls of Disney: A trend that was never meant to be https://t.co/biI7jIvYvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for @CasameraStore to launch on Indiegogo. Check them out if you're someone that's into showers and stuf… https://t.co/B7DKrcSScg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, if I take the time out of my day to text or tweet you happy birthday and you don’t say thank you... don’t expect one next year]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias @HitsFm1061 @jorgelozanoh hermosos una canción. Bonito día https://t.co/P32rS5B6J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedStateLexi @BenHowe I’m so sorry. No one should ever have to go through that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDWPublishing u want to know how much I luv #WynonnaEarp I am going to WE con in June that happens 2 be the same w… https://t.co/jzjs8iPPsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detained physician puts Trump-Saudi relations back in spotlight  https://t.co/DcA29WB4QY]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️2Pac ft. Eminem &amp; Linkin Park - In The End (RIP Chester Bennington) (2019) https://t.co/HGXiBXW73S via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC We’ll you just did. Shame on you for trying to divide this country we have enough problems without you incitin… https://t.co/RaXi1wsr8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños mi estimado amigo @AlejandroOMont te deseo lo mejor de la vida! 🎊🍻🎊🍻🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[To new beginnings 🍾🥂#2019 @ Freehold Township, New Jersey https://t.co/zQVT75SWtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilartimpane @hannahboning I feel like Casey shaving her head is at least 30% holy pettiness. Or rather @johndbadley shaving her head]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh hai, it me😊honored to be running games along these amazing ladies and for an awesome cause! More DM intros to fo… https://t.co/JXF2tObI3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supppsteph @ATLUTD Me because I’ll be at the opening game https://t.co/kosj3GixGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[You never know what you might finish at a soccer game. @ Lower Woodland Park Ball Fields https://t.co/WEwifCekC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The stupidest and incoherent speech has ever been uttered by an American president. Nonsense. Just… https://t.co/hFJmGXo2xP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennkirschner2 If the cigar bar meeting is circumstantial evidence of a conspiracy against the United States, are… https://t.co/KcLzVIc9Md]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MondayMorning @samityme Ⓜ️ @bncargram @BRNRGAL @JediSkysinger @katespalding1 @JaneGrafham @Zoey4Always… https://t.co/ewOoyJ0b3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kkelseeey_ @weirdradopinons @momof2dinosaurs @xoxoelley But not me. As I’ve been horribly depressed myself multipl… https://t.co/0OvkBnGCD2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss Strawser’s homeroom is working on a 13 Colonies #Escaperoom to practice our skills. @LSPioneers @HansHerrES https://t.co/PDzLTa8LF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly out of cat food and out of food stamps until the 6th...can anyone help? https://t.co/RB4Ykd7v4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do #US #airlines fly @Boeing #737Maxs? There are at least 69 #737Max aircraft in service across @SouthwestAir,… https://t.co/c2QqQbBeQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay to women everywhere!  To the women I know that are strong, smart, fun, resilient, and… https://t.co/x3sVv8TBkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swhaye88 @MrRonHastings @RepMarkMeadows Ok, I’m willing to research both topics 🇺🇸 thanks for clarifying 🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check us out on the @MsDCLowe  Show from 10am-11am this morning! Promoting the @EpilepsySETN and its upcoming gala!… https://t.co/CohS0lL1AT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@92ZEW says @amandashires isn’t star-quality and a women’s music group doesn’t need a political agenda. No, Tony. YOU lost ME.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTFFFFF was this a real thing my schools aint even have a nurse. scrape ur knee? ice and bandaid.  headache? ice an… https://t.co/4qGltOAEDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisRValle @ZonaMegaRadioTV @azucenita @HildaMurilloS @HumbertoToledo2 @lrodriguezerazo @juan_palacioso… https://t.co/JaJSeF8WYB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I refuse to see life through anything other than #rosecoloredglasses 🌹👓💃💕 @ Angels Landing - Zion National Park https://t.co/ZPjuOhhJxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go home newspaper editors... You're Drunk! FAIL! LMAO | Sarcasm. Because beating the hell out of... #humor #laugh… https://t.co/xnk502I2Bj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thx for visiting me sissy’s 👯‍♀️ @ Vice &amp; Video https://t.co/YXHMNGQZ23]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Indianapolis International Airport - @indairport in Indianapolis, IN https://t.co/pNh1wLnoQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[COME AWAY, MY BELOVED....let everything that hath breath praise the Lord....just dropped by to throw a Jesus love b… https://t.co/qhmULx5969]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating emmas_mommy23 birthday, Happy Birthday!! 🎉🎊🎈  #friendscelebrating #goodtimes #groupphoto #sundayvibes✨… https://t.co/dCePRov4Ej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddybanany @thealf420 I was literally gonna tweet you the same thing cyanna . 😂💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Phat relaunch? i’m copping a sweatsuit &amp; a winter coat with the fur hoody. check me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedWings even goal: DeKeyser (4), de la Rose, Abdelkader at 2:22 of the 3rd, 2-1 over #Avalanche.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McGuireSuzette @poconoraceway @MonsterEnergy @bkrt29192 @4judyblue @AnthonyGreco3 Thanks so much Suzette!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kat_Travino Okay, I see so crazy Kerem had a twin so thats who fell in the Well. OMG this fool is crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently asthma attacks can last for several days?? And your rescue inhaler won’t fix it??? So you have to go to… https://t.co/cksPQl59HQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If washinton wont lead MINNESOTA will”..... wooooohooooo! I love this place! #GovTimWalz #MN #LtGovPeggyFlanagan!… https://t.co/hK9gs4oAD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am quite sure, without a shred of doubt it speaks worse for the Congress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch today was amazing! Pictured is a chicken and Mac and Cheese wrap, butternut squash soup, loaded mashed potato… https://t.co/haYv5EXF8M]]></document></documents></author>