<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m not the same happy girl I was before and it breaks my heart because I’m supposed to be the happy friend..🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I go by that sign on main that says caution overhead marquee I think of someone really tall hitting their head on it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialRezz and @elijahdaniel interacting on Twitter made my whole fucking life thank you mom and dad]]></document><document><![CDATA[“how are you and your dad doing? living there alone.” we’re doing GREAT! how’s your daughters divorce going?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are fearless and we will continue the fight till we win! Toronto feminist icon Carolyn Egan closing the United… https://t.co/fPbp3wKoWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Cortes is not correct in trying to Change America to a green State . She’s in experience in economi… https://t.co/G1peIEnfFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This scene is hilarious!  #AOMH @hallmarkchannel  @brennan_elliott https://t.co/ZJeVv4uUwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thread by @EricColumbus: "Many people say that Mueller’s report should be made public because Trump isn’t indictabl… https://t.co/pPxrjCtLJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved getting to see Bobby last night ❤️ @ Steam Bell Beer Works https://t.co/ZzV5c0H6Gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/p6lDa6h75J]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HeadshotBadge #sketches 4 @gasarakirk9 &amp; @artofyote 😊 @ Burtonsville, Maryland https://t.co/PYsQOVnD7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyBaldwin Same in Las Vegas today too! But hey climate change isn’t a thing right *sarcasm* 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[This blows my mind!! Texas has the worst mobility infrastructure! Cycling is strictly viewed as a hobby and not a v… https://t.co/tov67kHUB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verawishful1 @Defenders @crimsonfate88 @HoustonPubMedia Do you understand how migration works?  Trampled ground?!  You can’t be serious!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @FredBarnes @MittRomney Man up and say Promises Kept for #WeThePeople]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter For A Chance To Win A Cuisinart 11pc Chef’s Classic Cookware Set @dealmaxxdeals  #cuisinart https://t.co/6MhLqH8mNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing but respect and love for Kes! He’s truly amazing! @Ryan_Kesler the @AnaheimDucks are blessed to have a lead… https://t.co/HQrEdAMAAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moved my muscles with Becca! Thanks for s great class, Becca!! @sbegemann @Adamleid @AnthonyBegemann @brockportjazz]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS SO GOOD HOW AM I GONNA GO BACK TO SLEEEEEEPPPP. 😩 https://t.co/ddyHV252RP]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s absoluately nothing Gaga can’t do and I am so insanely happy for her right now ☺️😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsCPR Perhaps they should put their money toward 1) drug prevention and 2) drug rehab.  I'm not saying it would… https://t.co/mODOyNrJSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why doesnt @jimmyjohns deliever to my house when there's one 3 miles away?? 😔😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listened to @ben_courson teaching about God singing over us and then a car turns in front of me with license plate… https://t.co/6BoM4uh960]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImRellyBevis @Cheri6538 @RepDanCrenshaw Aw come on. That’s not right to say. Killing any baby is wrong. And I’m su… https://t.co/A4WLH9zlsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having fun reading words part by part #FHESfamily #lucycalkins https://t.co/XTImPPs70q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to have fun here at Disneyland while my significant other is back home. This whole place is full of memories… https://t.co/VkEmz03NsP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelinpooler ALL Americans should be outraged by  everything that’s happening with this racist Grifter. My neig… https://t.co/wo8RpuMewL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump President Trump feels that our country needs fixing to prevent all these disasters, pr… https://t.co/wz7D3i4HZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Gardner-Webb / Radford game is kind of an exciting one!  #NCAA #wherearethesecolleges]]></document><document><![CDATA[An evening for s 14-year Caribbean cask single malt, Bill Evans, and the electric fireplace. #thebalvenie14… https://t.co/E7H7oOmvM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tucson_Police Lmao, you officers are hilarious. https://t.co/4xm7Ih689Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Either a Formula One racecar driver or Wonder Woman. Possible both. It would be a nice arc ok the story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will I still lose weight if I just eat tacos everyday. Just tacossssss https://t.co/RTVjF9BCvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the new nails. #nails #thinkspring #mymklife #entrepreneur #sportsmom @ Deluxe Nail Salon https://t.co/uASVbq72Bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized something. I met @haleymossart back when she was a teen artist! One of her paintings is still hangi… https://t.co/ycGjUnuhRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickwtyler Great questions of Khanna! I hope he is wrong as I think Trump will smash Bernie in the “socialism” iss… https://t.co/4aoQAFlrFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[since knitting is supposedly the newest craze........ i would like a handwritten apology from EVERYBODY who made fu… https://t.co/BuItXaPlCl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks 3 years in a row I’ve failed the compliance trainings at work on the first 2 go arounds, but let’s be h… https://t.co/inwMV9ntAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to choose the #Caribbean Island 🌴 that is best for you.  https://t.co/b8WvMXAG49]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth is he condones White Nationalist Terrorism because it supports his agenda of fear. He also doesn’t care to hi… https://t.co/4IL2cOylOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got surprised by my work family for my bday and I cried a lot💖 #24 https://t.co/LvH6mcINox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indian nationals account for 36.9 per cent of all expat workers in Oman, followed by Bangladeshi nationals at 36.8… https://t.co/0uHxD7Y3tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winstonCovfefe @lovewrenching36 California needs that.🇺🇸 #MAGA #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockyOfficeCat @Lis_Smith @KeithPowersNYC @katie_honan @NYCCouncil @NYCACC @coryramey @MayorsAlliance @CoreyinNYC… https://t.co/spb4ACRivK]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jqlcAPykTP #friends #smile #fun #likeforlike #toptags #cute #happy #tbt #girl #fashion #followme… https://t.co/uKH1DhDa87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missingwords Pfft...there are no limitations. No need to be scared, we’re all friends here. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RooLivesAgain32 @SlenderSherbet What? You mean they just move their lips?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to the library to return our books and get a new set. #readingrainbow #pandababyfi #elifoxprince… https://t.co/yTTnJIabPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gym grind! 💪🏼 @ Anytime Fitness Murfreesboro - Medical Center Parkway https://t.co/PzhhCjPvcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My webcomic reading has two moods now:  CREATOR HOW COULD YOU? 😭  and  CREATOR HOW COULD YOU?😍  there's literally no in between mood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[please be mindful there's a reason why we're asking so many questions. It's not that we don't want to see you; it's… https://t.co/cEcZF62LMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real time and automation that the cloud tools provide allows for work life balance and an opportunity to women to b… https://t.co/O3GGbpXsH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for thinking of me when talking about dwarfism @maighlin 😂😂😂 https://t.co/QuJ8TWd6k2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sodasotta Agreed. When I visited Chicago it was freezing with wind, and it was miserable. But then it snowed and I… https://t.co/Og76Rwm7X3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohabitation is mostly hiding the food you want from the other person. Like the last homemade walnut chocolate chip cookie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[there's something about the spirit because when He moves, HE MOVES. it's crazy how it happens right in front of you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You tell em Bernie, let’s get back to the good old Depression, my parents told me it was great, Nottt!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill So close to the truth it wasn’t funny. More revolting and disappointing that we’re living through this daily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StillNotGrown @uzairxyz @deesperaado @BoofBundy @playboikadz Point me to where i said anything you just asked... i… https://t.co/McxS7B6H1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Arizona.  #mvhssoftball #2022 #SoftballLife https://t.co/LCU1dY4Ima]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoSofieFatale If I'm not mistaken, Howard Schultz. An exception from the city to build a longer drive way to his h… https://t.co/pXZvJbhHZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who me? 💁🏾‍♀️ #ootd #fashionnova #fashionblogger https://t.co/kFCJZFdvLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying this sunshine on this beautiful day! 🌞 #kelleymariechicboutique #comeonspring @ Kelley Marie chic boutique https://t.co/lUE8bYV6JN]]></document><document><![CDATA[From one Lab family to another my heart breaks for you.😪😪😪💔💔💔  Such a beautiful boy.❤❤❤Alfie, sweetheart, run happy… https://t.co/5sc3D5WgWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤯 Tater Tots &amp; Hash Browns are literally the same thing, different shapes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad you appreciate and acknowledge her greatness. Sadly, some weren't surprised by attempts to block her as Speake… https://t.co/swQ75HorQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent entretien réalisé par @jmhamburger et @DCharette43 pour @Tocqueville21]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please tell me why even at 4 in the morning I have 15 year olds hollering at me at stoplights ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch The President needs to include in his National Emergency a cleansing of… https://t.co/60Jd2Rzv8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[On what grounds were they going to remove the President, why, because he likes  cheeseburgers!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS Gonna visit the final resting place of the young soldier who took your place after daddy bo… https://t.co/prSP2Y7aY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #Accounting jobs like "Tax Preparer/Bookkeeper" at Accountemps in #Charlotte, NC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShirleyDHatfiel @DVanDaveer @RepMarkMeadows Haha! Your party can no longer recognize truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everybody...I’m going to take the time out and grieve the friendship of @keturahsoundz and I, because she is honest… https://t.co/rKPeYylRT4]]></document><document><![CDATA[La da dee la dee da,la da dee la dee da,la da dee la dee da,la da dee la dee da,la da dee la dee da,la da dee la de… https://t.co/AK8aLvdfDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love ice cream so does that mean I love revenge? #mirth #tee-hee #smirk #absurd https://t.co/NhWc0RhdWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm team Targaryen for life but not going to lie I'm all kinds of excited about Arya on the throne here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie How many times have these same fools posted pictures of Hilary or Obama w/the liberal villain du jour… https://t.co/rRbHDrLGr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out in this wind! All surrounding schools are delayed but mine. Wish me luck!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so proud I was going to go out and buy food pero mejor me dije “ahí comida aquí en la casa”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Livid2point0 Just reading that reminded me of Q’s ‘dark to light’... that may refer also to JA coming out if the s… https://t.co/5KLJpvGNmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[In January 2016, there was an incident in my family that changed my life forever. In the midst of that trauma, I qu… https://t.co/Ft9coriPBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love the show of respect between Apollo Crews and Kurt Angle for Angle’s last hometown match. #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[going live on twitch will be streaming  kingdom hearts 3 be sure too tune in  https://t.co/eJ3Kd7Oe0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linorulli Haven't made the cut for a pilgrimage yet...but I'm going to Boston!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't stop taking pictures of Lucy. I'm just still stunned I have a cat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor and I have been playing webkinz and it’s the actual best thing of my adult life https://t.co/xwXqBjRSXP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Speedway Pump would not take my Cc card unless I scan my rewards card. People were getting cards to get gas. I was… https://t.co/fV2BtqRDCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m not sure if you understand but a lot of these government regulations were put in place to keep black people do… https://t.co/w614Lz1uw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMobileConverg Well I was more commenting on how silly they looked :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've gotten to the point where if you say some stupid shit that annoys me, I'm gonna say some shit bc I'm tired of… https://t.co/V42ONawigc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quisiera que mi novio estuviera dormidito conmigo, pero esta trabajando 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fiannabradley @InsurgentDesire @AdamWagner1 What does it even mean? It doesn’t not matter where you come from, it… https://t.co/Ur7hEnPL80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did y’all hear I was 4 months pregnant! These rumors gotta be a joke 😂 but hey I’m living my best life]]></document><document><![CDATA[and the choir girls are singing hallelujah! 🤤🌮 #tacolounge #tacos #chips #salsa #enchiladas #pacifica #aguafresca… https://t.co/L1fNoQHR6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmywinter My popularity would have been severely compromised. Highly, highly uncoordinated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning!!!!! 😍😍😍Its My Favorite Part Of The Week!!! Happy Worship Wednesday!!! Today We Will Have An Early Mor… https://t.co/scc6WOClyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnitaMHairston @TamikaButler @Bici_Urbana @DanceforMyself @VeronicaODavis What about “Leaving on that Midnight Tra… https://t.co/fJS1TLDj7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a place for everything but not everything has a place. Good post. I thought the same as u when I saw that… https://t.co/oV3gpXBcT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EffseaEscobar @Protector1984 @Deleon076 @zxnga_ no wtf if you can see in any of the responses I wrote that sex isn… https://t.co/tAvGpBRxGB]]></document></documents></author>