<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@H0ustonPa @MattWalshBlog And furthermore, to say that "the man paid for the house" like the woman is just allowed… https://t.co/h466U8sgwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait until I’m 21 so I can sit alone in a bar pounding gin and tonics while annoying the bartender with my… https://t.co/BRVTDXMVXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early Birthday dinner with the fam 💛 (@ Maria's Pizza in Oregon, WI) https://t.co/sThLlGCxYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennycohn1 @Renjen10 VOTING MACHINES FOUNDED BY WHITE-COLLAR CRIMINALS.   JUST WHAT AMERICA NEEDS.    https://t.co/EthdeXBr5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao fucked up that I was stupid enough to get over when he slept w/his bm ex while we were whatever yet I send a d… https://t.co/s6PDWg9OTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday snuggles are the best! Especially on this ❄️ day...we will stay in pjs and play all day (this pic is when… https://t.co/e9Az6z1FUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Donnielover6 @birdtracs @stacie9853 @BuckeyeCuti @Katie_Elaine012 @24loves75 @tnormandeau22 @moonrayvin @jessaugie… https://t.co/03zoFQtCL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck! They have more viewers than any other news media. Over 5,000,000!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shireen_jamil I LOVE You Sis. Our conversations started about but that didn't last for a couple of hours. It has c… https://t.co/yQvl2NDmPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want some canes rn but I also want enchiladas😫 idk what to get?🤔 should I just get both?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw Tony Goldwyn (fitz on scandal) eating breakfast today and I totally lost my shit, here’s a creepy ass photo I… https://t.co/FnhgD9o59d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some girl that I keep ignoring requested $350 from me on cash app and when I asked her about it said “oh now I have… https://t.co/Y9GEY4Gf1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day Everyone #Jesuslovesyou #loveisintheair #begreatful  #bekind #loveeveryone #thankgod… https://t.co/CXtvH4h0aE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a "tip-of-the-tongue" feeling in regards to my personal direction.   I know I'll figure it out eventually, b… https://t.co/pxZGBPcw9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4: Ss without balance develop unhealthy habits. I have a few who admit to 12 hours a day of screen time and little sleep. #jusdshares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlynnJoycemarie @dmills3710 @DoingRight1 @POTUS @GenFlynn @FBI Not in Washington.  Anything the Democrats want, go… https://t.co/0XFFVzbgTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jands1118 @MattShaheen That will just bring unwanted issues....teaching to test vs student learning....and I’m sur… https://t.co/JAeua3tccx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not go in. I will not go in. I will not go in. #iwentin @ Tanger Outlets, Sevierville https://t.co/bKM2Qdm5oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneaker shopping for Johanna love these for her https://t.co/QqglUH8JsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thom_malone @RInsideTracktv @curraghrace @JohnOrmonde Sand and fibre - 9.5f uphill parallel to Old Vic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I love these? Do I hate these ? Should kennysingstheblues get these?  Should I get these ?   Things in my mind t… https://t.co/DuQaXy2inw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not reaping any health benefits but it sure feels good. #sunshineatlast☀️ #desklife @ Gatineau, Quebec https://t.co/adzMJKLpm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on my 5th day as a pescatarian!!! Lol that’s a major accomplishment for me I love meat!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you just find out you are not allow to eat Mofongo until the season is over. 😭 Happy Monday Everyone!!!  Cloth… https://t.co/eYJnUSbVDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Give it a break. You know, we all know--NO COLLUSION.  The Democrats dirty secrets about to be exposed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow, Thursday, Feb 21st from 4 to 7 pm at MVE! @ClintISD  https://t.co/UutqHwUErT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day started with my bestie dewing the DEW @ Madison Dental Group https://t.co/vPH7N1VvNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azucenau disfrutando de #SegúnEllas pero podrian poner en pantalla el cargo que ocupan tus panelistas? Gracias]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is so much kindness and love in the Twitter community. I feel such support and love leading up to an 11 hour… https://t.co/ynsv5CYCyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us as we escape winter for fun in the sun with our #MyKissimmee Twitter Party. Get travel tips to plan an idyl… https://t.co/1CsBt3xtaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this time of year! Welcoming 5 New🍊Blooded Associates to our #NewHDFam2019 #NotGonnaLose @HuntingtonHD… https://t.co/aq4f1gHa8o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@case333090 @Milk_the_cow4 @nickhiem @JoannaMWallace @DanAlyea @jzantinge2 Whatever it was, it looked like someone… https://t.co/DDo6tue1UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's wrong with Rosrmary.☹ @WCTH_TV @hallmarkchannel @hallmarkchannel #hearties  #WhenCallstheHeart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Brandon @KPRC2 I love how engaged you are to whatever she’s saying. Some of the best reporters are the greatest listeners.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this handsome dude!!  Hondo is as sweet as he is good looking!  He is headed to the vet tomorrow to get c… https://t.co/q99ZlZCiUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickyB4Prez @RealRyanWhorton I agree with you.  If the movie is about a culture or race, that culture or race shou… https://t.co/qXXqtzd1uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein Rude. Time to retire. If you can’t uplift our next generation then peace out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/CZpBSXjext]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaRush I have never been a person to get into politics and things like this but after watching so many vids fr… https://t.co/Z4WUsSA94C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the ending we wanted, but still so proud of this young team. #wildcatnation https://t.co/CX8FjG5jxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve prayed about this financial situation for months &amp; months and today He showed me that He’s been hearing me 🙌🏼 #GodsWork]]></document><document><![CDATA[did... did hozier seriously write a lyric about adam (of genesis fame) ejaculating for the first time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg my prescriptions have been in process for almost 3 hours 🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬🤬 @cvspharmacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i gotta lot of things im sad about but im trying this new thing where i don’t cry so often]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beer tasting session at your office is a great team building opportunity. Many offices in the gta are already cel… https://t.co/XWxDQTM7KT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnFPfaff @emzanotti I’d be scared if it said ‘do you want to play a game?’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nekesa @sarah_edo Hope you are well @Nekesa! Does #nairobitechweek still live on? https://t.co/SJRHgKIrqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serous but not too serious 😉... allow yourself to celebrate when you achieve one of your goals 🙌🏾❤️  . . . #hiking… https://t.co/5yULbdP7Yk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rolandtureaud @krassenstein Fought for the right to protest freedom of speech moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave Of course, we all know the Dimms are more worried about money than they are about what is good for our… https://t.co/Vrp6DzLPHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget women and children are regularly sold and bought in today’s awful sex trade]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only similarity I have with my car is that we both have panic modes]]></document><document><![CDATA[We braved I-4 for some Detroit Tigers spring training in Lakeland with Grandma. 💙🧡🐯⚾️ @ Joker Marchant Stadium https://t.co/3ChlP3RiPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’ve ever punched a hole in a wall or told your mom to shut up stay the fuck away from me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC30 That's like most Mexicans 😂😂 and I'm saying it cuz I'm Mexican. I got a few cousins that got married to each other]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I am the nicest person and people constantly be treating me like shit 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lisa723Kelly @FLOTUS @ericbolling She’s off “Be Best” - even she gets the hypocrisy - but opioids are safe 🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters @MedicVet68 I agree  i want to see what the republicans do. We will all watch them carefully]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrishDukes1 @KathyDutton16 @blondedolphin17 @army_bc @barb71 @MTumarkin @nanafrey7 @4thelilones @ThewardmomCindy… https://t.co/PpIU48APDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was stupid to believe that you were genuine, and true all those years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s, right!!! #whatmeanttobewillbe @ Saint Augustine, Florida https://t.co/cfTNScokcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m already thinking about what food to eat at the fair today. Hawaiian bbq or ribs...or both 🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Wah, wah. I can't get away with being a fucking criminal, so I'll blame it on Hillar… https://t.co/InSGnRUNoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lightening is on point but Atlanta I have arrived https://t.co/asxpPkHd09]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tha__Problem @egyptiansteven @mgoodwin_23 @NoNameGirl8686 @jerry_saviano Well, it wasn’t Beyoncé, that’s for sure 🙅🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation @McHenrySheriff That is so sad. God Bless his BLOOD FAMILY, and His BLOOD FAMILY....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mesealake lol that'll start encouraging people to actually see the movies because who would want that. You've gott… https://t.co/8EKzEwLTxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you thought the crazy was high enough, it’s amped up as we “celebrate abortion providers”.  🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenRichey7 @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You need to ask Pelosi that question]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimhaz99 @jordanbpeterson @MikhailaAleksis Offal is not required. In fact no supplements are required when eating… https://t.co/kaJgSkxYSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @WSJ @KCarliniKing Here is the history?   There were over 18 000 cases of measles in the Philippines in 20… https://t.co/0hGY5xIJv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone asks me about today's fashion choice, I will tell them I'm going for Jim from Taxi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @GallupPoll You guys just couldn’t wait to put out this poll.  And dome a favor Joe stop lecturing the… https://t.co/5OVNGc9Igx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since my friend died my dad has called be from his vacation in Hawaii twice to make sure I’ll be able to travel to… https://t.co/ZeHqQNU1EY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftAction I don't believe in either censorship or boycotts.  On either side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Esor_Fasa Esor, be careful of this tweet lest you are labeled anti-Semitic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to snicker. grumpy cat quotes | Grumpy Cat Strikes Again https://t.co/w1WdSHQtLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Cuda alum @DcotaDixon1. Was awarded the Jason Whitten Collegiate Man Of Year Award last night In Dallas… https://t.co/nnY1cZ1inF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walks by the pier with this angel baby are 10/10 💕 https://t.co/mYMk2MS7ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother.... literally got over $100 worth of la croix shipped in crates to our house lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly Stubby’s on Minor Night is scary and I CAN’T WAIT for next week 😂🎉😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone said “white girl magic”, it would be blown out of proportion as RACISM.  @Google @abc @cbs @FoxNews WHY?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle @thundacat830 @Gavin_Walmsley @deputyblanding He’s very fortunate to have met you, handsome young man‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CW_Riverdale @morbeen4444 How much longer do I have to wait till it’s in Netflix lol I’ll have to watch all the seasons again !]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Virgo and that’s why I am going through a rough life so I’m sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmAlyJ @DaveRanard24 @HillaryClinton Thank you! Boy, the ultra right wing troll fest starts in no matter what she… https://t.co/Deg4s9nz1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BklynActiveMama I could eat pizza every single day. — no heart ❤️ shaped ones here either. 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOT good at all terrible I think they should b charged when they screw up look at the shootout that just happened t… https://t.co/8C5mVTPhho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta I prefer my steak med rare and so does my dog Quinton Terrin-Chino.  AKA..Chino https://t.co/frHcd77Yvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlendaWarren15 we need these!  Read this amazing article!  Already planning where to put one in my room!  One outs… https://t.co/rP8DBg8OLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertqberry Where is she presenting this? Would love access to the slides! #iteachmath]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Boy Dannie's first season she was dressed like a prostitution whore for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenDerow @realDonaldTrump @GloriaBB2 @BillKristol @JoeNBC @jpodhoretz @NoahCRothman @NicolleDWallace @jheil… https://t.co/dm2iWcqJAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robyn_rl @realDonaldTrump @WSJ I understand and respect your view. My perspective is that hypocrisy is not the uni… https://t.co/sNJ6N6Mvkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[going to heb when ur pregnant is just as dangerous as going to heb when ur high]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bit it's all a LIE!! Every bit of this shitshow is based on LIES &amp; corruption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one can save us but ourselves. Inside the brutal war against Afghanistan's women https://t.co/0G1t8mcvDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking at masters programs makes me excited &amp; horrified all at the same time. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how Monsta X came up with our name Monbebe well I have come up with one for all the fakes out there   Faux… https://t.co/2l40uHd1II]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's get your ass home kind of cold outside. I'm am so all done way to soon with this weather.]]></document></documents></author>