<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@giantswfan Damn. A few of us are trying to go to nashville for the draft, was hoping you and the crew were going t… https://t.co/Bwp20FAUUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Lord.  Good works of Hamas is that they haven't killed all the Jews yet!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boyd County has forced 11 Ashland turnovers and there’s 5:24 to play in the first half. 28-14 Lady Lions, TO Kittens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamDjDWells Part of da streets cuz....live by da sword die by da sword....wen I was playin wit dem tools I got sho… https://t.co/5oBOSMZWjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're attending South Dakota state swimming meet @ @midcoaquatic this weekend, pay super close attention to whe… https://t.co/tMBN46ax5q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Project GROW prospecting session going down in a West Covina!  Teaching these young minds how to hunt for businesse… https://t.co/FId7d0KzRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nyjets are you guys debuting a new permanent logo or will you guys keep your current logo? Also, when new jerseys coming?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonEley_32 So is Amanda. She hasn’t celebrated anything since National Drink Wine Day on Monday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaHendersonTV Have you ever considered the works of They Might Be Giants? https://t.co/f8cljYx3Bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder Carpool Karaoke https://t.co/EK8ivvi4Ur via @YouTube.  If you don’t have love for Stevie Wonder, your… https://t.co/46ceyz1i7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Valentines Day my toddler son was in a store with his mom. He saw a Teddy bear with a heart around his neck. He… https://t.co/ChaKD18WLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tigerbill My t-shirt @TalladegaSuperS said that. Mixed reactions as to funny or not, but I enjoyed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenjimallon @imisspoundsigns @Pillboxz @GCraftyCouture @Lah_Em I mean, I think they'd be nice little get togethers… https://t.co/Xc3mh4YHw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs just heard about you from @Timcast. Shady how that bank did that to you!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be outdone @EAST_HAWKS Sophomore Kyle Seiler at the SW District Championships! https://t.co/I2lqtF73jk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I hear someone or something mention “financial freedom”, I immediately find myself acting like I did when some… https://t.co/uKreJLoUmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[In life, there are times we MUST learn to #let #go!  "Hey There Lonely Girl" -#EddieHolman]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 20th Anniversary Air Canada Centre/@ScotiabankArena  From 3-2WIN vs Montréal on Feb20 1999 @ Air Canada Centr… https://t.co/EADn6CwdfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess my idea of traveling is different cause no way I’m paying bread to look at some damn temples lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so happy to cancel @Allstate a year &amp; a half ago. #AllstateSucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my beautiful, intelligent neice Nini's birthday today. She gets straight A's in school and is incredibly k… https://t.co/tRr4MHPLwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to one of the realist @RayHill_ ☝🏽 Have a great one n we gotta get lit this weekend🤘🏽💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day! Why not give that special gift of adventure! #savinghistoryseries is the way to go. Get… https://t.co/4Mo5dGeD0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeifHemstad And you regularly spend Saturday weekends in the fall at two of these top five locations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh new commercial for Gresham Plumbing Supply Co. in Charleston!  Concept: Blackwell + Co. @ Gresham Plumbing Su… https://t.co/zG0IeMLSsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeGoodnight1 @BrandonDrumm247 I dont like it either I'm mainly classic rock 80's 90's and country like George strait and other greats]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dallas we had fun this week! Lets break records! ✊🏿🔥🔥🔥 #impactTexas #impactDallas #impact ✊🏿 @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/wy1w5hQh8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have like 3 songs on repeat I must master them before I go back to 🇵🇷]]></document><document><![CDATA[rump &amp; his Trumpanzies are going to prison! LOCK THEM UP! So. Cal. Ocean Crew! One ! https://t.co/y7l8Op8A1E https://t.co/ICcugFqtzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @realDonaldTrump @DineshDSouza @DonaldJTrumpJr @charliekirk11 @LouDobbs @TheDemocrats You can't be eve… https://t.co/BtINmxaaAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews That’s California our politicians are Nuts they do nothing for California]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here come the #Blackhawks. Jonathan Toews throws it on net where Brandon Saad is planted. Saad gets a piece of it a… https://t.co/T03NPrHLBq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lenkiefer @IntrinsicInv @ProfDowellMyers This is true, mobility of people wanting to move has been in a decline for decades.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sav01 Swing voters need more to instill confidence than do his base. Massive fascist plans with existing implement… https://t.co/k97gDuKUBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s an Delta Airlines Instagram wall at the gate waiting area in Atlanta airport.   I want off this rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dan_sauceda_ @MatthewJamesV Unpopular opinions: 1) Force your parents to get divorced and have the poorer parent c… https://t.co/DpqL8qA95J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something serious is going down...#Moriarty #guitars #comics #rockandroll #music #guitarist #guitar #LesPaul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: I was a big Rainbow Warrior fan growing up. Had a bunch of his memorabilia on a shelf in my childhood bed… https://t.co/yzAZTiDz8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2braptuedbyJC77 @MarkWarner Well, not an active agent. Maybe he’s a sleeper...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IbBK @linda25b @emilyrauhala So the Clinton foundation sucked up 5.6 billion from donours to Haiti and kept it ins… https://t.co/IA8vQRoAok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come save me @CourtneyHansen the last show I watched was #ROYL https://t.co/jULbRkvQAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindasteelehot1 All u have to do to motivate someone is walk into the place where they r. That’s motivational enou… https://t.co/D03d6pZ9WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerGroepper @Str8ballNtwoOne Boom!  Time for an @AlluvialBrewing when you are back?  No sports for my family this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lasocba @TheFlaBar @OCBA_FL @OcbaYls @HBACF Sign up done ✅ https://t.co/vPrbGlQ6aF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Free_Media_Hub @realDonaldTrump This just a poem not the law of the land! If you come to this country illegally then you are a criminal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Largest trade deficit ever, unleashed state sponsored racism not seen in 100 years, largest defect… https://t.co/GH6TKB0YpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I’m the only person that remembers the original Go-Gurt Man! https://t.co/8SHcdO5H9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMorris55 @Taxcountant I’d add “scheduling meetings without an agenda”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw #Network on #Broadway yesterday. @BryanCranston-always terrific, (Breaking Bad, LBJ)- was also great as Howard… https://t.co/4uBsxRyjPr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “we are family” talking point isn’t some hokey meme in the case of @sup_graps - it’s real.  If you took money f… https://t.co/7JSJLdLbyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFCLxwis Liverpool fans are rushing to Twitter to scream “WHAT ABOUT GERRARD!!!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Proto_Zsay Literally. Every swipe, refresh, RT. Our generation too pressed for attention to be committing crimes l… https://t.co/qqXPkvrYT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreddCNC @F3Metro @F3BabyJesus There were 17 including an FNG who did Not get left behind thanks to @Stinger_F3 an… https://t.co/F6halsK0VF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to an Apple store to ask what I could do about forgetting my screen time passcode. They were trying to help wh… https://t.co/InwDzc12g0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kendrick_bacote @mattschneidman older and injured. Seen his better days. Not sorry though. Came from being an undr… https://t.co/fqJQTBDZIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think people care. They are frustrated with what to do. We make calls, we march, but the insanity continues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattZCleveland Although, “uncomfortable” might be a better way than “left out” to put it. “Left out” makes me uncomfortable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes life has tough periods, stages, moments but we cannot allow the turbulence destroy, mock, change our inner peac… https://t.co/IY85vCziqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[40 is starting off pretty good. @ The Omni Grove Park Inn https://t.co/qBnwc0GTzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que,,,queeeee,,, saludos para toooddooosd como se siiieeennnttreerennn???? https://t.co/jfed33XFWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Typochondria Sound editor Mark Berger has been nominated for four Academy Awards. He's won each time, for "Apocaly… https://t.co/Hb7CzhdTI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: SoMa West community comes together to improve the neighborhood - San Francisco Examiner… https://t.co/FJClGN4wMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Legendary entrance by Living Legend. @tonibraxton @BraxtonFValues @TamarBraxtonHer @towandabraxton @TrinaBraxton… https://t.co/FweuEELmHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soonerleesa As long as you stay back a relatively safe distance, especially in this windy month we're in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe that was just the back way; perhaps @MelissaFinkkkk &amp; I won’t die tonight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is The Boss Burger. I've never tried it before, and I'm completely impressed. This is a solid 10/10. Thanks, c… https://t.co/Zop68MGw96]]></document><document><![CDATA[#100thdayofschool fun @ Roscoe Central School District https://t.co/6cJDaBX2ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmelli @Espngreeny We are all 50 50. Jesus isn't helping.  Be pretty bad if your health is at the whim of one person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dvel86 Probably best if you are drunk when you see my titties though...just sayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willie_t_smith @DeionSanders The Sharpe case is a stark reminder of how media will remind you that they will have… https://t.co/AopXM8qLGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marcus Mariota is going to have a breakout season coming up in 2019-2020. #TitanUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcLachlan60 @CWasylciw @MonteMcNaughton People took vacations and day trips. And then they invented the IC engine… https://t.co/1keVKmpGwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[My prayers to the people across the South, especially in Alabama.  H/T @KrzyKeeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything Has beauty, but not everyone sees it. - Confucius @ Hamilton, Ontario https://t.co/fb926TZhJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite store got this in for meeeee, yay more basebaaaallll https://t.co/L368gDikSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldofWarships Give @Femennenly a permanent stream buddy for broadcast someone like @tragicloss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebDingell knows better than to assert such nonsense. Not a single federal employee was in danger of damaging thei… https://t.co/2Mw4j6K0sB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@softly_sighing2 @carriebear421 @lullekbh @shanaonthepiano @Fab_Mommy_ @chaoticmess17 @DarkerSunrise @Love_bug1016… https://t.co/1Zow9sLLQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[True story that Congress VOTED to pass healthcare, and this wall, which FAILED to get funding from a constitutional… https://t.co/MtoS7OQZSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Because she’s an idiot. Unfortunately her vote counts as much as yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever think 💭 so far ahead 🤦🏽‍♂️ cause I been thinking 💭 forever 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@douglass_braden @andrewkongslie @danoedurass @svbgusmaker @koinzangreg Yes. We’re building some pens tailored to c… https://t.co/33cv8a95cn]]></document><document><![CDATA[However, I turned working for free or working at a net loss into the business I have today. If I’ve learned one thi… https://t.co/9hfNojACRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Achieve Anything in Life You Have to Believe that You Can. @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/hUvgBjPLCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Allenwrestling’s Trent Dooley takes the boys 138 over @PWWrestling6A’s Jacob Aragon. #txhswrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ouch. Someone did him a disservice by not playing him at safety. @CAHIRONMAN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charromty O sea la canción por sí sola es buena aunque ampoco es lo máximo. Pero Lele Pons sólo llega a cagarla. Q… https://t.co/GNQCHbeEYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCU_Tweets @RottenTomatoes It's the mcu this is what we do https://t.co/SmYvTjFxJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skepticscalpel @TomVargheseJr No. ‘Reality’ television is the antithesis of professional, compassionate, efficient behavior.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lake Conditions Message: Due to higher than expected rains received, Logan Martin Lake level could now approach 472… https://t.co/nIT0hCB5wM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevanBateman @ShawnMendes @CalvinKlein UR THE THIRD PERSON TO SEND ME DIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people list their position as "Visionary" on @LinkedIn  - that means they're unemployed, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chas_Battery beats this mascot any day of the week and twice on Sunday.  Leo the Lion!  Leo the Lion!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always pretty spiffy to have Epcot mostly to myself...now if I could only get the rides turned on! @ Epcot - W… https://t.co/iw6Wt6zbfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @Carver926 What a hack! Can we please just trun him off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean, it's the effort right? And have you ever ate tacos?   Fit(ish) Workout Shirt  #fighterwifejess #blogger… https://t.co/3SySYHVqCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have no idea what this Twitter thread is about but Constable Bob is one of the best written, best acted character… https://t.co/QkngEkkjOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much for jumping on board with this amazing charity. I’m glad you love the autographed baseball.… https://t.co/64bcar3c4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joy_Villa @realDonaldTrump Like anyone gives a shit about you, your D-list “career” or where you will be at any given moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthboundTrain @kat_sturtevant @DennisDemori @TellYourSonThis 1. You're not citing his examples, you're posting y… https://t.co/WSaG8VpKRW]]></document></documents></author>