<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MrsTyler78 @BunAndLeggings @ChaosStyled @lostmymommymind @KristinMoras @Roster192 @sweatsntopknots @honestly_mom… https://t.co/F1A4rWWP6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow runoff.. ❄❄❄❄ #water #creek #snow #runoff #creekside #mountains #river #rocks @ Mingus Mountain https://t.co/s6ubHhheW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rrrrnessa Pls do...I've been thinking about visit to London and other places (at my age, time's running short; why… https://t.co/6l6USkJc5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a picture of me and my best friend in honor of his birthday. No explanation needed. 😂  Thanks for being an a… https://t.co/NuEsafp7kR]]></document><document><![CDATA[There never be another Faction like #THESHIELD @WWERomanReigns @WWERollins #DeanAmbrose U guys inspired to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celinedion we are here!!!!!!! DREAM COME TRUE!!!!!! #celine #vegas #canicomemeetyou #dreambig https://t.co/QQYKIrxigg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught @mariashriver interview @HowardSchultz about his new book “From the Ground Up” at tonight’s @LiveTalksLA. Pr… https://t.co/Alf1P4BXOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stirgdatguy There are some black students in attendance but, who says they would be any supportive of her as the o… https://t.co/NZlFGTGsfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing this to Facebook in about 3 months, sharing it here now because it’s important   Let's talk about left wing… https://t.co/YdPvhkucgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/lwBPoBivxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jesus #love #Bible #verseoftheday #God #christian #bibleverse #inspiration #verse #grace #hope #arkansas #b #read… https://t.co/lAEj3P51sz]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Discover on Google Ocasio Cortez is such a phony. @cb55uic  @BasshamCandice https://t.co/eACi11Hdgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite thing in the world is drunk ft calls from my sister and her friend at 1am who just wanna have a dance p… https://t.co/XEeiS5FcOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[May we offer ourselves this morning to the service of others, — and do your will in all things throughout the day.… https://t.co/s0h1MvELiy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conner won’t eat his food but is acting super hungry and I’m like ???? Your food is right there. In your bowl. Like normal. Eat???]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I learned #Matchday is a very involved process that I'm not looking forward to participating in]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took Kristian to the car show last year for his birthday and he saw the @TMobileTruckPHL! ✨ He was so excited! Ha… https://t.co/9lhRdeD3Nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP @ABC @BW @WSJ @cspan @cspanwj @axios @thehill @ShepNewsTeam @foxnewspolitics @Acosta @maddow @60Minutes… https://t.co/ZjgLDUBHR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not the money I'm after. It's the freedom to live life on my own terms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyGoesDating I can so relate!  I just found your blog and I swear you’re writing about me.  LOL. We’re living pa… https://t.co/Il1lCSmjGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpuntimeCreates damn that really sucks :( have your doctors tried to help it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think he’s smart enough, patriotic enough or,most importantly,  honest enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc how many times we get into it if he call bitch I’m answering Df no matter where we at .]]></document><document><![CDATA[got your bitch in the kitchen cookin’ up the pork chops. 🌼🧡 @MichelleRincoN_  https://t.co/9OkpA74ZeE https://t.co/fPx0ZNdFyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once we understand that the story of the antebellum American, when it came to citizenship, turned on the status of… https://t.co/Q3TMUORNrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@17Kandles @miscmusing @rickspringfield @17covergirl Always a good show]]></document><document><![CDATA[#eggyadventures in #philly Great team spirit in the office. Thanks for organising #Kathryn ward_ric @eggplantio @ W… https://t.co/iHdsNozSOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEDx: Can a Blog Save Lives? https://t.co/eNAXGVQvF1  @KevinHinesStory @joelprestonsmit @PsychToday @theMHcomedian… https://t.co/2dnLNZAuSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RankoRussia What’s wrong wit New York and jersey why u wanna live so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Charlotte, NC #HR job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Compensation Consultant at Wells Fargo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker try living without animal byproducts https://t.co/JXgXNA9gxm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grown up nightmares: I dreamed last night I scratched my favorite non-stick pan 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCoachWilkins @CoachWilkins23 @OCLadyRebels @emmajohnsonn11 @MacybLittle Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many chances!! 🤦🏻‍♀️ Come on, Liverpool! #ChampionsLeague @LFC 🔴⚪️⚽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeePistol Good luck!! (btw, this is your Aunt) https://t.co/Oz6d0a84nB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SashkaCo @jsbayer @Piratemomz @BlondeTexan71 #Giveaway! We're giving away 4 New @SashkaCo Bracelets to 4 friends!… https://t.co/Jdo7WdqHuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kostas_Kokkoras @DinosPalaio @Makedni @Tshirtbandit1 @Killer_on_site @toscanamkd77 @misssjdoe @NikosChangez… https://t.co/U42KeYQ8Lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to @LindseyGrahamSC speaking at KCC @hainesforohio @JaneyMurph @Not8upSL @HamCoGOP @NEHCRC @senrobportman @la_bissmeyer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes ah dude really DONT love you he just love how YOU love him!!‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShanaVWhite Nowhere near the population of SOC I serve. I am sitting here in my discomfort, recognizing the work yet to be done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching episode of red talk table and the two episodes I watched was about depression and then forgiveness. And man that hit hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always excited to see bae, I could never get tired of his cute self 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is why the Lord says, “Turn to me now, while there is time. Give me your hearts. Come with fa… https://t.co/LkXpfSJWst]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coalición internacional ya. La quema de ayuda humanitaria, el asesinato de ciudadanos , esto es inaceptable. Estos… https://t.co/9SFqalCnVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THDKC @nyyroro @StaceyTank @LisaAdamsTHD @lgranskie @PattiSingelyn @Hamilton4138 @keeley_chet @hderich… https://t.co/dUytTb5OPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@america_sue @Venum84839107 No, I really don't think there was. They have always done spells on albums to make them… https://t.co/qd0xvl5DnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day we will have no countries and we will realize that we are all citizens of the world.  ~  Un día no tendremo… https://t.co/17n96xck7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColleenGanCook @idinamenzel That was an AMAZING Duet !!!❤Thank You Both for sharing this with us !!!❤ Love you both !!!❤😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met @hunterpence once - when I covered the Giants at the end of 2013.  @BMcClintock_BSN got me a press pass - hes… https://t.co/fTAt3s6bv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, no sh*t Sherlock.  Extraordinary deductive reasoning skills.  @cnn  Idiots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[gUySSssSs for fucks sake i just wanna see hot mulligan that’s gonna be the best show ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patfkelly What a week for you! It’s right around the time we started dating 7 years ago. If only there was an app… https://t.co/iEa77tuNob]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s national margarita day....pace your yourself accordingly!!! 😆😉😁 #nationalmargaritaday #patron @ Thomas County,… https://t.co/ne2lL9DSK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllWaltrip how funny. He needs a patch on that eye. And he wiped the smile off his face. So funny. @CoreyLaJoie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewguterl Yes. Headed there at the end of the month and can’t wait to see it. Is the @DukeU @NasherMuseum the… https://t.co/FobXiM0BJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No power..... candles taking over #crazywindy #manhattanbeach @ Powell Casa https://t.co/7RwAjuiKQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be elected to Congress or the presidency. One has to be a veteran of the US armed forces. A soldier knows the ho… https://t.co/0hgf55zJy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity I love our President Trump With Him we can keep America Great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pretty pretty princesses 👸🏽 💝 @ Timberlake, Virginia https://t.co/nOjRSuDU0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a scale of 1-10 how bad of a mom would I be if I eat the cheesecake in the fridge that Harrison doesn’t remember is in there? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our @ColumbusAcademy Vikings tonight!! Way to fight all the way to the end!! What an incredible game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full house tonight and a successful meeting with @CommackFD promoting our award winning @nationalgridus… https://t.co/wrSxELA1Oq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blakespana I feel like you should have specified that it was my first stream ever and I have no idea what I’m doin… https://t.co/KCGyTuI1wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely birthday present from my beautiful friend of 20+ years Heather heatherhandcu  Thank you for the bracelet and… https://t.co/PNJ0QjmngX]]></document><document><![CDATA[just had an @ArianaGrande moment &amp; apologized to the lady at Starbucks for her messing up my order 🥴 #sorryifisaysorrywaytoomuch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't much care for Matthews, @MSNBC. I care even less for @SteveKornacki. Please give that slot to @JoyAnnReid a… https://t.co/vp88UpXKqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoked up my girl now she's over here nodding off on my couch,  like bitch grab that blanket and just lay down 😂👽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@attilatheblond @kylegriffin1 @TimOBrien I thought that too ! He left abruptly. Why ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My exchange student is 6 foot 7 and weighs 151 lbs. Less than 5% body fat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews Say thanks to my deplorable president @realDonaldTrump  cc @PerezrobJ  #MAGA https://t.co/NvNPXYtQxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be perfect for the intro of @Oscars2019Live_ 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣👏👏🤣👏👏🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣👇👇👇👇👇👇]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuitYourselfToo @MrFudgey @blue_check_mark @FantomaSpirit @RealMissSteam @ProSouth_ @TheCognificent1 @Andywarski I… https://t.co/mtUvBvj6s3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proverbs 5:18-19 18 May your fountain be blessed, and may you rejoice in the wife of your youth. 19 A loving doe, a… https://t.co/VboxpzvN1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should’ve listened to my intuition, I’ve put myself in this position, It’s all my fault! Look in the mirror, Thin… https://t.co/mSfVMFPRlo]]></document><document><![CDATA[just in case you needed more cat twitters in your life https://t.co/CqlAuckDEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[as much as being single on valentine’s day kinda sucks, i’m really glad my friends that are in relationships are ha… https://t.co/cSGlZnESCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[you're going to chuckle. Literally laughed out loud. Loooove it. Special shoutout to a certain someone! #hilarity… https://t.co/9D7RA7ZuQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[You should be proud of your legacy. You’ve made Wisconsin proud. #OnWisconsin #Onceabadgeralwaysabadger #Bucky… https://t.co/aXRoj8CYGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between the smoking couple next to me and the Indian guy w/o deodorant in front of me I’m just gonna stuff my nose with Vick’s Vaporub]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had the energy of the toddler running laps around this @peetscoffee rn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinRoiland Aaaargh I don't even hate that I want this. #RickandMorty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_laughlin_ @mbmk7 @nick_ramsey @maggieNYT Then he should be okay when we call him President Orangeface.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing beats a good night’s sleep in my basement 😌❄️ https://t.co/Sr2487o8BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a tragedy! We need better #data &amp; #research to help prevent these unnecessary deaths. What is the… https://t.co/xo9PBRQ65q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should clarify - tax abatement for developer and raising of homestead exemption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD @MichaelBerrySho Nancy no supports him again because the black democrats are upset. Obama will be on th… https://t.co/uqpoQY7piJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sounds about right...that's why he is hellbent in investigating our President because he can't fathom anyone else n… https://t.co/oNCe1mMuuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 5:30 tonight they were flying over the premiere of captainmarvelofficial at 7 pm these #thunderbirds were walkin… https://t.co/G35v8PWWsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Depends what you want to get out of it.... @WomenInL10N @GALA_Global @brand2global @LocWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanaGautreau @DaniloMedina @rubenbichara @JoseRPeraltaF Simple https://t.co/ajSJHLXNTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people who don’t have kids talk so much about what to do with ur kids..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demoblogue2526 @JeffreyGuterman @realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner I wish I could put this pic. on a few billboards!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend told me I had to watch La La Land. He said it helped him understand our relationship better. 🤔 So, I guess… https://t.co/guULXnTzuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Yeah! (feat. Lil Jon &amp; Ludacris) by @Usher on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Yw20xuFvKa https://t.co/Crg6A0aME5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m totally having my child only watch Peppa Pig for their childhood because I would die for them to have a cute British accent]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the question is - will they? @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @GOP Singling out @MittRomney @marcorubio @BenSasse… https://t.co/TMkRVkheW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[3:13am eastern time and I’m rolling blunt number 3 😤😴  What are you doing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @maaggzzz, I hope you have the best day ever. Miss you and love you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJpshanley @russellcrowe I follow Mr. Shanley and was startled that you saw this before I did. Good words, good thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladytronics @krassenstein @questlove @jpmorgan Yes!! Call Congress!!! Write Congress! Ask them to release names of… https://t.co/VrfiqNl1Q3]]></document></documents></author>