<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[A fascist is somebody who identifies with one group — usually an aggrieved majority — in opposition to a smaller mi… https://t.co/u37y8DleuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least we can finally put the “maybe this team will sneak into the playoffs” talk to bed now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill Sympathy he gets because his brother died of Alcoholism respectively....but nowadays...he seems to b… https://t.co/7mGc8eP5AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations It is very hard for me to believe that somebody actually had sex with him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @realDonaldTrump You sir are a Nazi sympathizer @marklevinshow also you have Trump’s shit all over your nose 👃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And we are pleased to announce we hav another @realDonaldTrump as @POTUS nominee for public servic… https://t.co/QuWEAByZal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to throw it in neutral and slide back down a hill this morning on my way to #mnleg. Apologies to those who had… https://t.co/Pm61o2rU7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Bernardino County, business leaders highlight growth, while union raises concerns over job quality during State… https://t.co/PjhncXK5db]]></document><document><![CDATA[To eat or not to eat (@ Parish Public House - @parishpubhouse in Albany, NY) https://t.co/Il0XqDrhKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we have TWO winners this morning!  @ivankorshunov11 and @PandZander!!  Message me so I can get the stuff taken c… https://t.co/4vT3NQPPQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling someone ‘despicable’ is the new way being sympathetic.  Tell me again how these people are not mentally uns… https://t.co/pmWRDg9WsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION WACO GHOSTS! GDB @ MELODY RANCH WACO 2-28-19!! BE THERE! https://t.co/uFMbc5NUZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Peanut Butter Jelly Time: Strawberry-Rhubarb 2019 by @catawbabeer at @Catawbabeer_CLT — https://t.co/H3OSVi5tgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Young people have helped lead all our great movements. How inspiring to see it again in so many smart, fearless st… https://t.co/xbn67Zvd3m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Burris Found the highlight in slow motion. 😁 All jokes aside...that 1st step is lightning fast!!! #BoneZone https://t.co/4ZThVc87Kf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot stand that every elected politician is older than America itself]]></document><document><![CDATA[A long time supporter of my projects over the years, here is Matt’s e85 Z4M roadster. Sporting our GW V2 Taillight… https://t.co/vDmCPVxb3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[5480 Wilshire Blvd 5480 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/oNVpcDU24h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy after everything, all the moments, all the fun, good times and bad that I never meant anything. Was just being used. Hard to believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude exacerbates this buy turning into a stonemason in the final minute with those bricks he was throwing up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LakerShowBR @Lakers @KingJames @B_Ingram13 Harden deserved that, what a jackass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job today Dawgs! Nice work Anthony...proud of you son! @ Dean College https://t.co/ftZCEBulG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[FYI, I have heard that there is another round of testing for #Note9 #AndroidPie update for #TMobile customers. So i… https://t.co/PrPfxh02gQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGDing 445a-8a (@ YMCA of Greater Nashua, Nashua Branch - @nmymca in Nashua, NH) https://t.co/Rm18CllHYc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy how I rather be with some one and all their bullshit, then to start over,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rashford I have never been critical of you but stop pointing where you want it and start running towards where it’s rolling ffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiazCanelB #Cuba está cansada de palabras bonitas que si dijo #FidelCastro o cualquiera, acción y soluciones neces… https://t.co/lryyi9716t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_David_Edward I heard from her 40 minutes ago. She is well. Her boyfriend is with her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think America is finally ready to settle for Kattan!! #SettleForKattan]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little short snapping practice today. @youngballa2_ @camham_24 https://t.co/pMUBKwRM5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ochocinco I’ve been trying to get a fifa game with you for months now let’s get after it]]></document><document><![CDATA[A statement like this potentially does two things: a) it puts pressure on a weak mayor who desperately needs a tran… https://t.co/3Auk89dPSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wang_yuanfeng If Canadians consumed energy at the average world level, they wouldn’t survive the next winter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hamiltonian Bryce Kanbara co-curates ROM exhibit ‘Being Japanese Canadian’ https://t.co/x3xXgqT0NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nas1781 @BillSimmons You join a public debate when you only have TWO followers and I’M the idiot? https://t.co/HWDtxhbNcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Local by @bondbrosbeer at @glorydaysgrill — https://t.co/csVtfbVTKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 Judge Ellis is just too damn old to be a good judge.  He’s senile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mybrunchwith @SpintheVinyl I can give more names, but you will continue to either claim that they really aren’t le… https://t.co/YoRRfaeXyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maccracken @msaUMN @UMN_SBP @MinaJKian When are you stopping by the best @bigten school?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[CVS Health is hiring in #MtDora, FL! Click the link in our bio to apply: Pharmacy Technician #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItaliaSteve @60Minutes No, just Trump. He committed treason to get elected.  And he lost the popular vote and many… https://t.co/6DG4DocoMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moonwalkmcfly @Rschooley up to the Portland city limits, with a reprieve at Eugene.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElLordchiva Con este entrenador miedoso sin saber cómo responder cuando está abajo de 14 puntos va ser difícil pasar]]></document><document><![CDATA[EL SERÁ EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, CON LA AYUDA DEL TODOPODEROSO, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New Y… https://t.co/eT43EkovPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bitch you look like the newest member on this new mortal combat that’s about to come out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just two days after nearly getting no-hit, the #OleMiss bats got hot early tonight. Here's what happened in the… https://t.co/GyqXxoWNoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder The real threat to America and the whole wide world is sitting in the white House right now and we need to… https://t.co/O9GOf9vBvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[dont lose any sleep tonight ...im sure everything will be alright .... https://t.co/iZxKnse5Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Petal Prophecy by @burlingtonbeer @ The Deep End — https://t.co/t0CSEDnWO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Clamperl #Huntail #Gorebyss #ClamperlDay #Shiny  #Hoenn #InstantaneadeGo #PokemonGo #PokemonGoMonterrey… https://t.co/3xjXBexX85]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tan solo necesitaba dormir una siesta para que se me quitara el mal humor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillRTeamXRP @RealJamesWoods Heathen Leftist Activist not a Vietnam War Combat Veteran and an attacker of Christia… https://t.co/3fWcBEMIL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sage #openmic #openmicla #openmiclosangeles #spectaclepic #marvista #losangeles #standup #standupcomedy #music… https://t.co/ehkQHl23B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saints Baseball loses 5-1 today at home vs Daytona. Couldn’t get anything going offensively. Anthony Arguelles with… https://t.co/MZDKAF0EAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't unsee this. At the goodomensprime area at @sxsw #sxsw #goodomens #queen @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/1OsUlricQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrunkBrianF I wonder if Joe Gibbs racing got him an M&amp;M sponsorship deal, seeing they are so close 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @DallasFuel on one hell@of a game. Loving this team more and more each game. Keep it up boys! #BurnBlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost shodesusandmero with get_repost ・・・ For the series premiere of #DESUSandMERO, it's only right our first gue… https://t.co/eazhCFptXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smc33018 A. More: several reforming women in Observant Clarissian orders pick up Clare up as a positive, strong mo… https://t.co/f363oBuqjV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billy_norris @GavinDeGraw @UniversalORL @Bob_Reynolds @PhilipDizack @realLouisCato @Dmaemone @ezybakes Wish I coul… https://t.co/Fs46rxOcxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hereandnowrobin Taxes done but we are hunkering down going through bins full of old papers of ours and my mom's. F… https://t.co/mglodMZ12s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonHaskell1 @bigdee109 @coreyelvis This is not an executive order. It’s a declaration of a national emergency… https://t.co/LvuWl1IYNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Winston Salem Foundation in Winston Salem, NC https://t.co/wSi2yzDZHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Brett Kavanaugh!! That’s how you handle a congressional hearing #CohenCongressionalTestimony #CohenTestimoney]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nationalnappingday Is there a contest? Charley Greenberg would like in! https://t.co/jJHfNm1cxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walker_Harris3 @QCHspencer @hornets Some maybe, but overall I don’t think any players really care about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see Derek Dietrich has become the sticking point for the Braves fan base now. Just like we all thought.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EHammer84 @SecretarySonny @realDonaldTrump @POTUS The truth will come out he better get his A hole gresed up won't be long]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should my abs start a religion? #nofilterneeded #geekabs #bluehairdontcare #howamisingle #fearthetrout… https://t.co/A5ZEYNHMIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryan__Roberts @DustinFox37 Mine was Chico. And I dont even know who or what Chico is. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when a girl gives me the most amazing sex I ever had and then goes ghost on my]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ActingSecDef is supposed to make a  decision on the ground-based interceptor 90 days after the Review. The Review… https://t.co/YefcqAiUVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HOOnPD81Ur Kyrie Irving in the post game interview last night reflecting on the the Celtics 33 point b… https://t.co/FVaMfzVmsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frame by frame drawings wit after effects😪 and people still pay in exposures. I’m good lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solange might save BHM for real I think it’s gonna drop tomorrow https://t.co/8FdTNV9o2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ahendyyy @CaitPaula176 No you son of a botch, it’s Rufus. Fracking Rufus 4 life]]></document><document><![CDATA[From ‘evil empire’ to model citizen? How @Microsoft’s good deeds work to its competitive advantage. https://t.co/4xAFttnufV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabriellaR613 @Jenn198523 Get your ass to the border lady, can't see what's going on from PA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After decades of feathers and zippers Tetsuya Nomura added a design motif to his repertoire: plaid. Kingdom Hearts… https://t.co/FDjXphYKZs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#warriors #BayArea #GoldenStateWarriors #spontanous https://t.co/jmFbJBFQW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MorningJoe &amp; #MorningMillie 🐾☀️📸 “Start Your Day w/ Pawsitivity” #Sunrise #Mindset #Friday https://t.co/7LuHpAc01L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIimateBarbie Sorry, to paraphrase the Onion, the last adult who knew what the fuck he was doing died.   We're on… https://t.co/vYlsJ674P1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many people are trying to use me now, it’s crazy.. I have to be careful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 9 year @Chilis Anniversary to @ColeRocheleau today! 🌶🎉🍻 #ChilisHarrisburg https://t.co/3afFZL40Tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Store Counter Sales" in #Kissimmee, FL. Go on informational interviews. The best… https://t.co/QhvTfNKruN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neurodidact @Kamil_FPN @layerfMRI Agree - it's made even more perplexing when you add in varying timescales. Perha… https://t.co/h8GCTw8WqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait till daddy shuts your gravy train down. See how you react. By the way I think you will look great in black and… https://t.co/I7B2IjWNwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GilbertFireDept quick aggressive attack of the fire in the garage successfully extinguished it before it was able… https://t.co/xCneDWEC2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtraMoenia @bravimabasta @MonicaCirinna Grazie per aver chiarito a che livello sono rimasti quelli che ancora cre… https://t.co/ErfASKapxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisPerez_07  with a Good work out at EFT group training with coach Byron Dawkins https://t.co/B6WbWqvpWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaV_Magenta @TMobile @WLNtmobile @shohrehdirect @alemedibar @kori_tmo @tmely1 @mstoria85 @carolinaperezzz This… https://t.co/sTZrn47x7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StannyPhantom Because I like seeing you every Friday https://t.co/bitDQsBkLn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DisabilityRights #chronicillness #RepresentationMatters by @benmattlin https://t.co/pyo8mqW47J]]></document><document><![CDATA[😃🙏 aaaaye! MY "Eligible Legend Vol1" by Adam Lue instrumental #mixtape just dropped and i need yall to let your fav… https://t.co/prruwRT8O1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmalCandanguera @NicolasMaduro ¿Tu hablas de humanidad? Que ridicula e ignorante eres en pensar que es humano quem… https://t.co/smQMET1C97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejadedvoice Could you send me more info about your Wellness Committee? What wellness events do you all develop?… https://t.co/8DPiwKzhUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrat Party leaders should be demanding that ICE Agents go after the wealthy corporations that hire and expl… https://t.co/Rd8gV2GPgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madalieninvader @EEFWW It is the men’s rights group asserting their victimhood. If there is a victim, it’s helpful… https://t.co/vWa2hAO378]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zypisfy @yourmumspants @ellen5e @dadbaddy @zapher134 @PolyRhuagh @1CubbieKat1 @NickSoutter @Cern_lXXl… https://t.co/w3r60d1ygg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Burris Poile has failed more often at building a roster than any GM I can think of. Imagine being a GM for… https://t.co/GcC0wyfOBh]]></document></documents></author>