<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Tu cometes mil errores y se te perdona, aaa pero yo la cago una vez y ya soy la peor del mundo. No mms]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did I not know Bette midler was going to be performing?! I’m so excited right now. #oscars #oscars2019 #marypoppinsreturns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hockeyfights Omg this is so fun. Those guys look like they had a fun time playing a game.  Because hockey is a game. Remember? For kids?]]></document><document><![CDATA[New post up on the blog! Motivational instagrammers I’ve been loving lately! Check out all these lovely ladies for… https://t.co/bCHRJk6Fu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rdebar42 @travelchannel @grantswilson @amybruni @AdamJBerry I am sorry. I hope you enjoy the episode after you get sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joyfulng @VeaMiAlma @prosemerel @komaritski @Polina_Gordeewa @vikasknirmal @QogBazar @n6260 @cc_chicco… https://t.co/deP3kZj5t2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did y’all used to beg your mom to let you push the cart at the store too or???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @EdKrassen @FoxNews @HomeToGo @BeachesResorts @SandalsResorts @Disney @LifeOnPurple @JennyCraig… https://t.co/mDF1I8uTk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg honey 😳😢 am so sorry that  you get spoken to like that, those ppl are stupid and ignorant losers, keep your hea… https://t.co/wUkrufpNrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a long time best friend, I’ll miss you the most ❤️ @FabianCoronado2 https://t.co/WFhqeP9qqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just imagine the glow when we look to the Heavenly Father to be treated right and loved 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooo 😬 if I pull this off, it’s a wrap. You literally can’t tell me nothing! 😂🍾🥳 #All2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je viens de voir le couple le plus chou sur mon snap😭😭🥰🥰🥰 L’amour est beau 🥰🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Money from Heaven? Went to my front door to look outside for a moment and there was a $20 bill lying there by the d… https://t.co/AC1Jfiodgs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I took my 14yo cousin to see #CaptainMarvel; for 2 hrs she got to see a strong woman in body armor fight th… https://t.co/FV40YhzHMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I end the workweek and head in to a work weekend, feeling especially grateful for being able to work surrounded… https://t.co/DpybidBRWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbirdcota @PantVick @TheView Her face when @sunny brought out the true context of the garbage quote. #FactsMatter]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPINIÓN “Esperando a Godot en Caracas” https://t.co/jdg3Wumevw por @camilocnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash Schiff is nothing more than a puppet of the progressive liberal agenda.  He wants to get rid of Trump… https://t.co/o63HEvkNvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Iran Launches Cruise Missile from Submarine https://t.co/4ekg6u2Bd2 via @BreitbartNews 🥺☄️😡🤬...🤨😎🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[REGISTRATION FOR SEASON 2 IS STILL OPEN MAKE SURE TO SECURE YOUR SPOT! https://t.co/FLv1JKjENO  https://t.co/iNz2LezrTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris. Are you campaigning on twitter with these one liners? Different subjects?  I REALLY like you, but ge… https://t.co/VhzEVcoYK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSteinEWSD @KimKelleh @EastWillistonSD @kemnitzer3 @WilletsRoadMS @EWSDTech Amazing! 👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some laughter. 15 Terrifying things Children said to Babysitters while their parents were out. https://t.co/EVYlkBJG4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s because he has no business in that position. He has no clue on HUD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA This is all payback for Whitewater and the Clinton impeachment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some lady cussed me out on my way to work for what is still an unclear reason. Happy Monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cparham65 @Bmw2163Heart Collin Kaepernick was almost white and he was ok to cause a big disloyal  action towards o… https://t.co/TqyJqOn7bl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilvaObame @FrankMartin_SC We love you, too, Chris!! Thank you for being a Gamecock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update the girls were trying to kill a bee but 1, I loves bees and 2, most importantly, they almost hit me in the p… https://t.co/AQvaDgvZvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#havanatwists #braids #twists #kinkytwists #lasvegasbraider #lasvegas #iTravel #BookMe @ Rhodes Ranch, Las Vegas https://t.co/7TW19LPkPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@napsandtraps @OhDionne Sometimes, us recruiters are negotiating internally to get candidates higher salaries bc it… https://t.co/kSr9uheIlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArapahoeSO Can you tell me what was going on about an hour ago at Eagle Crest high school? Lots of police officers and riot gear?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trent Brown and Trey Flowers leaving is a shame. Both were amazing the past few years. Good luck to them. Next men… https://t.co/zRSghQsY2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pushed my button for @ImDexterRoberts! #TheVoice https://t.co/tbB3YZvglx U R GOING FAR! ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhoebeRyan   You are my #WomanCrushWednesday because you inspire so many people everyday, including me to keep goi… https://t.co/NkrUi4HrYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mueller was Hillary’s “BAGMAN”! He took the Uranium to Russia! Remember?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cambra696 @nathan_20220202 @Blayofficial @Charence You CANNOT be an officer if you’re scared . That’s like being a… https://t.co/QrBR8jA8ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suidlanders They live like pigs anyway. Not all have inside toilets so they crap in the street. Let them be with their bacteria.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CouchmenDBC Thank god I’m officially a Couchmen because now I only have 2 of those things to worry about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LYSSSanup @Julia_Byerly @LanierLela I want graduation tickets LYSS!!! And I’m proud of you too!! Getting into ever… https://t.co/J29xzI68nA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career advice for @CalCPA_Students  who want to get into forensic accounting https://t.co/ptY3QMQTKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get so shy when my nurse assistant is a young hot guy. Like there goes our love story after you know what I’m here for 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was painting my toe nails and as soon as I got done Zeus came over and stepped directly on them. Not even sure why I try to be a female]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malioto91 @Kevin_B19 @scott_lewie @Ryan_Brueckner I believe this will happen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a great, no cost way to start seeds for spring planting! https://t.co/tOkzhXFzad]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the Daffodils in bloom, it feels like Spring https://t.co/23SHYoUTTk https://t.co/Qi5LxZr0lx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Seems like you cherry-pick the Bible and follow what you want to follow 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdaCapps I am not ugly!! So back the fuck up why you doing this haven’t you done enough already damn!! Grow up a l… https://t.co/6Rq70y1MeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogsCoffee Yes, yes you can come home with me. In fact, I insist. 😍😍💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might not look like much, but there’s a lot of brainstorming and conversation going on. Design groups have made… https://t.co/6t2G2EiMJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know there are prizes inside every OREO cookie? Check out The Stuf Inside for your chance to win at… https://t.co/3luCB4HKEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzrat2000 @NightlyPolitics What distracts me big time is his hyperness, his toe tipping dance while he talks and… https://t.co/r1MCV7Yqsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where the magic happens @TheFamilyBeer #FamilyBusinessBeerCo #atx #austin #texas #hillcountry #what_i_saw_in_austin… https://t.co/ZeesFzSGhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposed to cook dinner at 6 but I haven’t napped yet so looks like dinner will be at 9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Land of the free, this is Starla, the kitten released. https://t.co/EMBBpMoouO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in: Buddy owns the Thunder this season &amp; I’m here for it https://t.co/TQFEJUd6OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC He’s a male Hillary and that’s not progressive enough for the Bernie bros]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day #2  #iftp wrapping up for @KentState students with team meet-up and photo. Pitches tomorrow 🙌 @KentStateCAE… https://t.co/CgM5TZMN2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shouldn’t be allowed to watch Mean Girls with other people. The fact that I quote the entire movie like word vomi… https://t.co/nidHelNGC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizabethjdias Are the also banning fat people, and liars, and cheaters because...you know.. https://t.co/vArhNEPx2l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule Next he'll be adding, they're eating them like Gummy Bears. Don't they have music to play him off… https://t.co/yiMYyjBvLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: why is there step aron i bail in the corner? mom: it’s for my beach body                          oh okay 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meek got Robert Kraft out here WILDIN' w/ that damn chain yo! Soliciting heaux?!?! https://t.co/PL608dbQQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatuzaNery @igor_fgs @renataloprete @AndreiaSadi @juliaduailibi @MonicaWaldvogel @LeilaneNeubarth Natuza é um sopr… https://t.co/rYkYhhWpzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason4006 @kyle_mckinnon12 Yes!! Love me some Bob Ross!!! I still have to go shopping.... 🧦 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@editorialunilit                            #publicamosparacambiarvidas        .… https://t.co/ubtl8tEyq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is today one of days where I listen to said music that makes me cry? Probably]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riggght. They know those photos were screenshot by the their fellow students LOL. I feel as if the goal should be t… https://t.co/A42NXTSFXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[revive classic musicals like ‘she loves me’ that aren’t racist or misogynistic!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her: I need my 8 hrs and 10-12 on the weekends.  Me: I pretty much have terminal insomnia. Sooo... 😬 Her: ANA! Take… https://t.co/Nhzu2Kpimr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transposition at the Highpoint Opening Reception Friday, Feb 22, 6-9pm. - Contact John Lee Matney curator@lindamatn… https://t.co/cyEalN0gWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMike4761 DEPORT THEM ALL. THEY DONT WANT TO ASSIMILATE THEY WANT TO TAKE OVER!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see @KendallHuntHE  authors in the spotlight being recognized for the great work and passion that they have… https://t.co/rpKviaK4uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay mabe the abs aren’t quite there just yet but hey their a work in progress 🤣😂#workout #workoutmotivation… https://t.co/NMTZ7PNGzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sfarler16 I WAS TALKING ABOUT THESE THE OTHER DAY AND NOBODYKNEW WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My twenties summed up in a phrase: "...it seemed like a good idea at the time."]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daydreaming bout how I rock it 💭 @ Beverlywood, Los Angeles https://t.co/igeuabEcoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Real Life Fox And Hound Are A Living Disney Movie And They're Perfect! https://t.co/1NbGf6YmYG via @themindcircle]]></document><document><![CDATA[mom: let’s go grocery shopping! me: i don’t wanna wear makeup😂 mom: okay don’t, just get ready...so im some in 10mi… https://t.co/lO4K4IX7RK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk hownto play darts on iMessage like i can’t even get the hang of it LMAO at this point I’m just bullshitting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stronger Faster! 🙌🏻🎼🎹🎤💥This track sums up my current energy level. Two days with @NoDayJobs and the amazing catch_t… https://t.co/L6lnng47Ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMStedman @TerryHa32444924 @realDonaldTrump how involved are you with this Fool? Another Fixer?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddyhintz His 1st teacher has some health problems and is semi retiring. New teacher seems cool though]]></document><document><![CDATA[MALDITOS ANIMALES ESOS QUEMARON UNA DE LAS GANDOLAS QUE TRAÍA AYUDA HUMANITARIA SON UNOS SUCIOS VERGACION]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez lashes out after pics surface of hamburger dinner, slams ‘stalkerish’ restaurant photog: https://t.co/4TeFCQ15AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make that $$! ...Nike Unveils New Colin Kaepernick Icon Jersey https://t.co/Muw1G24Pad via @blavity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctitusbrown @thecarpentries @RLadiesGlobal Informal short format praxis]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍁 I’ve been doing a few sketches for some new pencil work projects. This is one of my favourite songs...it will alw… https://t.co/qbqlOyslYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is funny, however she is not funny and has a clear vision to force her agenda through "at all costs."  She is… https://t.co/GotCG04gku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dank2234 @Patrici15767099 Its hard to believe someone in Chicago had to pay to get beat up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing day at the Strong Museum of Play.  Princess Palooza theme weekend made it even more appealing! #play… https://t.co/hNlNxrBAhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[El régimen está desnudo , todo se ha consumado ante los ojos de la comunidad internacional. El régimen amenazó a un… https://t.co/eosooY0PJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding a bench in the gym from 5 to 7 is like trying to find a parking space at the mall during the holiday season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dammit_Ange I always figured they cut and pasted Sam's form and forgot to change the details.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, I was invited to a special dinner celebrating Black History Month and to my surprise, I received a Certi… https://t.co/vy22p9QQUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand why no one thinks I’m hot https://t.co/R173XXId7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, Mt.Horeb UMC Seniors Ministry for being such a sweet blessing to me and my 94-year-young friend Martha t… https://t.co/Kmgr7hjdT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick, someone say something funny🤣💕 @ Disney's Grand Floridian Resort &amp; Spa https://t.co/SPFo7PWWS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ma5rina @90Mnica @SeInterpone @A3AmarSiempre @PaulaUsero @Luziliya @PimPamlimpiando  sad and yet grateful for the… https://t.co/JS6idqTArd]]></document></documents></author>