<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Mark_Penn @mbarminski This doesn't make sense with respect to Rosenstein, who was put in an impossible position th… https://t.co/5owG48TdPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PatriotsUnite #PatriotsAwakened #WWG1WGA #GreatAwakening #MAGA #Q #QANON #WEARETHENEWS #FAKENationalEmergency… https://t.co/VeRrK37J6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girllllllllll !!! You don’t know what you do to me ! 😩🤤 https://t.co/wrQFE5jt6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cada artista que se presente en el Concierto organizado por el Regimen, para desviar la atención de la entrada de l… https://t.co/V00YMtLM3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Why isn’t this Son of a Bitch changed with a Federal hate criminal? Oh well, more double standards for the FBI!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriffTheImpaler @HowardSchultz As I’ve commented before, he is just trying to resurrect the Republican Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is @kendricklamar ‘s LUST. One of his most underrated songs, it’s one of the most important and underrated songs of the 2010’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkenney is this even an attempt to make a promise you have no intention of keeping?  gawd if albertans fall for th… https://t.co/uokWPeVdZ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Yellowstone Regional Airport - @flyyra in Cody, WY https://t.co/hzFCVobZZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It reminds me of Summer 07 when I use to have teenage Summer Parties at my parents house on the Deck. I remember th… https://t.co/o874j1GvYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[the one thing I’m still good at is waking up with the same headache I fell asleep with]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant wait to hear the coaches at the @MissouriMCA coaches clinic....some coaches feel they cannot learn from peers… https://t.co/0o0VO6xnax]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Absolutely Okay by @CigarCityBeer/@struise at @TheBeermongers — https://t.co/JzWmOEzWIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveH_WSRW @Reds Enjoy... we’re still in the middle of a frozen tundra. 🤬😅 https://t.co/Pvsq3oEw1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder how many douchey guys were at the bar last night trying to pick up with this line: “Hey there, just wanted t… https://t.co/QMYjEdSyL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanShilinsky @CoNeTPC Lets leave it at that...my point is he’s a bad manager and by him saying he hit a few bumps… https://t.co/LK1Z7TxdbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When given the chance 2dance, always dance....  It doesn't matter who's watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mary really served a whole disco-sampling, feel-good bop last summer and y’all paid it dust 🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/2wTHyMD6lO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonRedmanWW I have seen and heard you in action. When it comes to public speaking and motivating groups/individu… https://t.co/1JoyU17rap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Fat crook,corrupt,devious POTUS advisor Sean Hannity looks like getting fatter..!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anchorofgold The Vols make up the entire ethos of the city of Knoxville. It lives and breathes it. Nashville is no… https://t.co/keJs4mNzvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denver.  Brings back memories of time spent trying to get new DIA going. Love Denver.  No baked treats or other indulgences.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrenaFluffy @EmmaCaterineDSA Go kill yourself. I'll listen to my trans daughter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delegadas con el president de la unión de Charreria https://t.co/EKnYZmOELY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killorn on the second try gets it to bounce of Khudobin. It’s 5-0 Lightning. EVERYTHING IS GOING IN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my mother. A single mom. A pillar who demonstrated kindness and responsibility throughout my childhood. Her eff… https://t.co/m4gh7SvMot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without this song, Warren G and Nate Dogg would have never become Regulators #grateful 342/365 I keep forgetting -… https://t.co/b9msipgtTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinRoberts @HEELZiggler @WWENetwork @WWE @WWEUniverse Was there too, feel the same way]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mochamomma We had a place in STL called The Loading Zone that only in recent years changed its name to The Zone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next on @NBCPhiladelphia — we upload our consciousness into the virtual world, at least it felt that way. Check out… https://t.co/i21ZdH92Gu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjlovesamerica @eavesdropann I prefer he do both - take what they give him, then declare the emergency anyway and… https://t.co/Bgp5lSGnfE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inaugural Bi-weekly #Kanban Project Planning Night with my wife! Tonight's drink is the #NewAge #Tincho.  She's rea… https://t.co/692y9PG1D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARONFOX is it possible to put the completed lap time as they stand on the list on the left during qualifying?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them they have no idea if the government starts censoring people they will also be censored,it just baffles me at t… https://t.co/MaR2mjhS2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryannemarsh Will the justice department investigate for witness tampering?]]></document><document><![CDATA[People from your own city rather show love to anyone else but you! dude could be in bumfuck Mississippi not know wh… https://t.co/cnh3gVh2EX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@speechboy71 The facts that you likened it to Catholics being aligned to the Vatican (or Chinese to Communist China… https://t.co/82VLYdRgm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[First lady visits Microsoft to discuss online safety for kids https://t.co/JNTQfwB2Dv via @seattletimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like every valentine’s day all these couples that no one knew existed come out of the woodworks on Instagram to shock us all]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingS37660272 @J__Gross328 @NHLonNBCSports @ovi8 Mario and Bossy also have the two best shooting percentage of any… https://t.co/JFS4UyWg1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Aurora Health Center Six Points in West Allis, WI https://t.co/otn315rFxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneyGodley :Saša Papac is a Bosnian-Herzegovinian retired professional footballer"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to snicker it off. bathroom decor,  funny bathroom art, kids bathroom #mirth #tee-hee #grin #clever https://t.co/owBlcu5IVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sotiridi Worse than pretending you are a girl with a dick and big hairy balls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/JyUiLWhT7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Padres offered 10/310 as rumors said they did. This is a no brainer if this rumor is true right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only did @Empower_2019 have a weak understanding of SGA structure during the debate, they are seeming to have a… https://t.co/8x4C2Rq36w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yokinup Right, it sucks cause no one wants to do anything on a Monday night lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NashSevereWx @NWSNashville Is there a direct link to the full text of this discussion?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to eat at my favorite restaurant in  RVA w/ my family + got our favorite waitress to wait on us! 🤷🏽‍♂️ #winning… https://t.co/mvNKamuelX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganalewis I’m riding this wave too and I’m gonna absolutely own it https://t.co/eQ26EQT0IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[India pt. II hit different when you got a shordie for it to remind you of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Though the fig tree may not blossom, Nor fruit be on the vines; Though the labor of the olive …… https://t.co/8GJebheAMn]]></document><document><![CDATA['IS bride' Hoda Muthana won't be allowed to return to the US, officials say  https://t.co/iXCBzaBsqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @Queenhildaglam And he still goes to his safe place. https://t.co/hYR6til4EN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a dream @BrettFavre signed with the @aafcommanders.  Any validity to this? 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YNB @HeSnob26 @JanetJackson @TheRealDaytime @YouTube You’re so beautiful sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @dbongino I wear the BLOCK from this psycho as a badge of honor!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The darker tone of this building fascinates me.  #NYC #NewYorkCity #BryantPark #architecture https://t.co/4zBF8KACNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack @AmyAcatlover YOU ALSO MUST BE A LEGAL IN US TO VOTE  AND STOP ALL ABSENTE BALLOTS TOO MANY DOGS AND DEAD FOLKS VOTING]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 38 Absolute Best Yearbook Quotes From The Class Of 2014. OMG these were sooo funny... https://t.co/s10OomiEAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unexpectedly tied to the house on my prime day to petition for @JamieGauthier1, but making the best of it.… https://t.co/B1Ho1i8Uwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThePassage season finale is INTENSE!!! @ThePassageFOX https://t.co/YePoUlah9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still feel very strongly about this. I’ll vote for any 2020 candidate that runs on a platform of abolishing DST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TMobile is doing skydiving demos via wind tunnel to celebrate the launch of the Samsung Galaxy S10 at Herald Sq h… https://t.co/9Ix5p8H5yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐴 #7 SomeBadDude was just that for driver @MMillerDiver and trainer Linda Toscano winning the 8th @TheMeadowlands l… https://t.co/BbQINuvLUk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matmenpodcast Made me a little sad.  Dean was always my least favorite shield member but I never wanted him to leave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSWVolleyball Does that include no contact week in August or will there be activities the girls need to be around to participate in?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs Razo, thank you so much for you kindly words you made my day 😍🙏🏼and here it is you before and after transformat… https://t.co/rM5MrV4KpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready to wake up? #TheOA #netflixTheOA #Netflix  ‘The OA’ explores an alternative universe in Part II trail… https://t.co/Lfzc6TJ8fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyAshburnPFN @MattyInfante @WingfieldNFL Still need a second corner. I think with the Graham’s defense the dolp… https://t.co/oIv4kZZMAb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m super thankful for @AugustAlsina  this man has saved me from myself a few times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bonifala He finally found some confidence on the court last night lol...proving my prior analysis wrong...I love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hour long drive back to Santa Monica. Guess I’ll listen to the greatest album of all time. 🙌🏼 https://t.co/HxE0NhCxhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC In any case, Bubba the Love Sponge is more qualified to be president than Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women wit deep voices always wanna argue...  Listen Batman save that energy to save Gotham 🙄🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arturochanel_sb @lubasse06 @Onejeitermore @GabyMeza8 Esparcir ideas incorrectas e incoherentes tampoco... si te of… https://t.co/7u8ZXvl9NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, I don’t think Manny is throwing shade at the #Orioles fan base. Do I think it’s towards the front office? ABS… https://t.co/9fWSWIzSGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work is over, the fun begin... @shwen introducing the evening’s networking session w/ @TheSpazmaticsLA sponsored by… https://t.co/BjeuDHQx5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weak fem hoes say it’s toxic masculinity but real bitches know it’s just big DICK Energy @ Sweet Soul Bistro https://t.co/01V8BOfKCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JS_Football @DLFootball I can't imagine DLF without you. You're the heart of the team to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing my trap durags until my waves get back. Gotta get back on my grit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/iL7p38Y41d]]></document><document><![CDATA[and that trouble made some beautiful music that spoke to me on a level a lot of folks couldn’t get to. And that mad… https://t.co/KDPPjvKoAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husker_Nick we are losing ground.  There listening to our campaign initiatives]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree and we have some ground to make up as the trend line is not great. Will take new models and increased outreac… https://t.co/mdploHxTZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju @SunlenSerfaty @MarkMeadows - Videos don't lie MoFo.....you are hard core Racist just like every other Whit… https://t.co/SNn35wRiKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I havent went bowling in a long time  But my scores were better than i thought 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who let a turtle get elected into congress? Mitch McConnell is 100% a turtle. There’s a shell in that baggy suit]]></document><document><![CDATA[One by one, 72 Torah scrolls rescued from the #Shoah were carried in slow procession through Temple Emanu-El’s soci… https://t.co/LO0rQcYbdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!! GOAT!! @Bryanbrothers @Bryanbros Thanks for sharing @IrinaFalconi 💪🎾🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSThisMorning @danreed1000 Cbs favorite topic sex abuse Charlie rose Moonves They love this subject. Especially Dickerson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @marklevinshow “You can negotiate with a dictator without abasing yourself and the country.”… https://t.co/9hQqPZhp7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOW. ..big trike. . Stay Tanned My # https://t.co/VGtvMZBjnU #jlauswaysellsswfla #nevermind #C21sellingparadise… https://t.co/VGlK0jZ2B8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE_MandyRose Trick question, she looks good in every color https://t.co/9HqeOLScl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Pursuit  CODE 4.... The Drivers going to Jail... The Police are Safe and All Ok... No one got hurt... But the MOST… https://t.co/rvmvfiP0a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenHHERRERA1 @rebeccarauber @PressSec @trumps_feed @HomelandDems @DHSgov She’s not.  And walls don’t solve anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LDorms @JoshJenkins116 Honest question. How does the service differ from Sunday school? Should we also be doing family Sunday school?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Utans, take the survey on the SLC Inland Port. https://t.co/TXlM0OYC2S  #utah #envisionutah]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cynthia18716465 @Justin_Nowlin @KSTiLLS @Kaepernick7 Most of people that are against Kap aren’t racists, they just… https://t.co/UdX11cxadQ]]></document></documents></author>