<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@travis_statham @MamabearNo1 @KetoDocCLT @SBakerMD @KetoCarnivore Ok. I give up. What is T H I C C? #yes2meat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dylan:"voy a llegar a mi casa y llegaré a dormir"  Dylan a las 2 am https://t.co/gmp1TnZp0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ready for tonight? #SouthernNotState #jokerzent https://t.co/Dil1YmuVzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkStateAG President Ann Diener, Gold and Money Back. Trump is deposed and known stole 2016. Arrest individual… https://t.co/2GGjIsRjr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinoandvetos People are seeing the truth.  It's not Trump on these things . They are losing voters and that the on… https://t.co/H7zWxqg6nI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel RepubliCONS are lying just like #Trump. Roughly 8-10 times daily.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i might act super tough but it’s really not enough https://t.co/nV3a7BbCO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[have guests write funny sayings on diapers to give parents a laugh when sleep deprived. :)... https://t.co/COUNE8kYFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaigeChristieUK Because the drama community doesn't stand for foolish nonsense, including the patriarchy and homophobia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChattanoogaPD @hodakotb @craigmelvin @TODAYshow @CDAustinGarrett Atta boy Tator has gone National 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impinkestgirl @mason4922 @cvalentine65 @DocHollywoodM @keanothedog @Nunya_Bizznizz @BandieraNancy @EveScottGarner… https://t.co/dlYxR8KKxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS 628 days til voters can send you packing, you disgusting dung heap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I constantly try to learn and grow from corrections, not assume I'm right in what they are trying to correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to a young teacher talk about Twitter for a professional learning network makes me so HAPPY! Just as happ… https://t.co/8d2RQkJe5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[People quit being cheap asses! Pay service workers with tips and respect. They put up with Joe public people and so… https://t.co/KyFRPytxzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am forever grateful for being selected for the @CALSAfamilia Mentoring Program years ago. My brunch sessions with… https://t.co/HaIqzU2bU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_kevsl Me too 🤣 and she only 👌🏾 this big tryna put hands on a nigga with a military weapon about $2 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl sells hempworx on fb and says CBD oil works 10x better than Morphine... I give morphine on the daily and… https://t.co/LdPWUExt9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday momma! I hope you know how much we love and appreciate you! We might not always say it but without y… https://t.co/CAncVeQ7qf]]></document><document><![CDATA[O Canadian winter snow clean up at 3:30 A.M. right in front of my house. #noise #urban #toronto #snow #cleanup… https://t.co/btcZI98uf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only thing getting me through these next few weeks is knowing I’ll be cruising the Gulf of Mexico with my gal pals soon 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AafLegends So we going to try something new at all this year or are we good with what we've seen the last three we… https://t.co/yeO4ggQOxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clivelyone75 @DJKatie888 @ShannonJoyRadio @RushLimbaughEIB https://t.co/zCWzE81rnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to weather earlier this week the Golf Teams schedule has changed..Good Luck to all Varsity 1, Varsity 2, and JV… https://t.co/xOTjLrgG2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy Trump had better be careful because those cuts to benefits will surely effect his base in a negative… https://t.co/e99YRz2xCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annieamitchell @yackie_b Mine was worse! 😂 mine can’t even do an emoji https://t.co/wMfSPYp77C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: i randomly met my husband at a college house party fukin it up to my fav twerk song at the time 🤣🤦🏾‍♀️🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[No time like today to book your next cruise vacation. https://t.co/ZmEJ8LSYNl (@ Expedia CruiseShipCenters Waterdow… https://t.co/bBoHIlmORY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndiraDammu You talk about this A LOT. I love it. I think a lot about all the future leaders sitting in MNPS schoo… https://t.co/kzs2isb11Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby boy’s annoyed face after I had to unfortunately turn on the lights and get up from bed..🙁 lmao. https://t.co/FcM5sahTH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neta qué pedo o sea me fui a la playa y me hinché y llegue a chihuahua y mi estómago está plano 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minne-SNOW-ta. There's clarity after a storm. It is bright. It is stunning. If you can be silent to see. The smoke… https://t.co/VFZms8Tmh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvaShadowgirl18 To celebrate Brian's results from appt with Retina specialist this morning, we had tea and brownie… https://t.co/LkVnysJu0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[2-16-19 it was a very chilly but quiet evening at the lake tonight. https://t.co/T0LkRZTuxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had so much fun with my friends this past weekend. Like real carefree fun. We gotta do it again soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BURY A FRIEND BY @billieeilish IS A WHOLE BOP! THE BASS HITS AND IM OVER HERE LIKE :) :) :) https://t.co/SqZUfcNe8l]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, health care shouldn’t be just for people who can afford it. Blocking care at Planned Parenthood… https://t.co/2n3A3IXvcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 Not exactly a "cure", but certainly temporary comfort.😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arsenal @MesutOzil1088 😍😍😍🥰🥰🥰 watch The Wizard work his magic. #NorthLondonDerby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stewartbob193 @mainstreethare .One of my favorite places too. @VisitScotland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Wow. That isn't even a veiled threat. You DO realize you just broke the law, right?  Pr… https://t.co/ZO1BfGkH8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[our uber driver is going to Japan tomorrow and won’t shut up about it good lord]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 46 of 274!!! No more days off...taking it slow while the back heals. (@ Fitness:1440 San Antonio in San Antonio… https://t.co/p6mkaDhMdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 @leeleeb50 Mealy mutherfucker mobster malicious malodorous malignant]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You’ll be forcing them all to change course, and they don’t like it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP,Peter Tork from the Monkees! I grew up with that group he will be missed!!!! Still love there music]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i HaVeN’t TaLkEd tO yOu bEcAuSe i DiDn’T kNoW iF yOuR bOyFriEnD wOuLd GeT mAd”   FIRST OF ALL there’s 0 reason to… https://t.co/nBqHqpPQSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeCaigoDeRisa  tambn pongo pajaritos a volar, @fastlicht @RICH_MARGALEFF  @diegodeericemx  o con @marianaecheve]]></document><document><![CDATA[To learn more ways On how I can help you attain debt free financial freedom and peace of mind from debt collectors,… https://t.co/9m8Ny4PjFG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenperkins1015 @Smallpox70mtd Writer’s Market?  It’s going to get exciting waiting to hear from publishers etc. I… https://t.co/F1Ij6FB38t]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂 Like I dead ass be battling with my depression and my anger issues and mfs wanna keep trying me. 😩 This is why I don’t have a gun anymore.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeHaimowitz @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump What the HELL are you talking about? Name an immigrant who has been k… https://t.co/D17G7XCdtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time @halsey tweets something I start waiting for @kennnny_b to roast her online.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird Weaponized son-in-law...can you get more autocratic?  Trump has altered America so much in 2 yrs,… https://t.co/vtxGzcVi1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Focused again  #metime #weightlossjourney #fitnessmotivation #vitamins4kids #kickboxing @ ILoveKickboxing https://t.co/9VRB9KJgg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CARTERDANE Happy Valentine's Day, Carter! Love you 💜💜 https://t.co/yub6m9apuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes self care is just skipping the stories of people you know are on vacation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS Yes. She has a right to know.  Stop watching until the 3 are together as a family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery @gatewaypundit 🤣🤣🤣dems just do not quit. They are like the energizer bunny. More lies more bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enid ate turtles.  Lydia eatin worms.  Somebody give these young ladies a burger.  #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[my boyfriend got me the matching bee necklace and ring from james avery 🥺🥺🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Septembers_Song Seriously there once was a spider 🕷 in my mom’s bra &amp; it bit her]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when your getaway car...goes away...a  stumbling bumbling ATM heist... Final score: Money machine 1 Thieves 0 Watch News 4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGkee The suit.  The suit they claimed wastes worst thing a president had ever done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@orionnichole Tayshia is hella shady and hypocritical though... wait for the reveal of where she was 2 weeks before filming 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyjandrews @IAmJerdog And by rain season, you of course mean swirling vortex of death season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Experts recommend using evidence notebooks in the science classroom. Why? It's an opportunity for students to use t… https://t.co/V5mAjHrUP9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Lady*Like teammate's place is an Instagram trap, and it makes ladylikecomedyshow rehearsal that much more fun! 💖… https://t.co/tg5YknTSN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pink thank you an amazing show in Charlotte last night, you are a true performer.  I attended with my dad, in memo… https://t.co/uKrNYJv0VN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to score a job at ABRA? You're in luck. Click the link in our bio for the job description and information o… https://t.co/2r9FIic9tZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also he’s seriously threatening to send a priest to jail? I’m so confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just opened ❤️🐶🐶🐶🐶 The museum of the dog #newyorkcity #nyc #parkaveune #museum #art #dogs https://t.co/Y6UcyDaWqb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vine al mall sólo para hacerme las uñas, pero terminé aplicando las de “para esto me jodo trabajando mucho”  con es… https://t.co/OjBmd7XHUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Duuuuude you have tweeted literally 4x in the last hour . Get your ass to work !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night was fucking insane! @ArtistHBTL @Highbridgelabel https://t.co/pnqNRQD8tM]]></document><document><![CDATA['Arrogant Jew!' Fox News viewers launch assault on Chris Wallace for grilling Rush Limbaugh and Stephen Miller https://t.co/6uwuzmFpM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton If Manafort is an example of long prison sentence, the prisons would be overcrowded with both local and… https://t.co/Sh5JwWTszY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tkprice4 @jwbul287 @dawnrolltide @daniel_harvey94 @Tomhashem3 @bikecop24 @finebaum @slmandel He’s betting we’re all band wagoners]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joanna's Maternity Session // Lifestyle In Home Maternity Session // Chicagoland Maternity Photographer  https://t.co/XiYOTRpdTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__nicoke Girl my sis in law was like she’s grounded for a very long time so dont invite her anywhere. But yeah lik… https://t.co/Xy5IOb2gyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL Keep fighting and keep the faith. Florida and @RonDeSantisFL are with you! 🙏 #FixIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know about you guys but I’m ready for the weekend and I’m ready for a drink!  🍺 🍻 @ Timberdoodle Farm https://t.co/FHmRcYNt01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJohnKennedy @CNN @jaketapper When is your time up?  You are incompetent on all of your views. You need to be re… https://t.co/fEhYI5apCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally tried this Tex-Mex restaurant with my dad before we picked up the kids from school.  Shrimp and pork taco… https://t.co/GpmiNQK2dF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹 The biggest, most beautiful bouquet of Valentines Day roses from the love of my life ... and this vase....… https://t.co/lHClCeCaee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totalake @bbusa617 Yes, but keep dreaming! Nothing will happen to these lying democrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayzieTO @VanessaGillieo @victoriaarbiter Give the good boy some food! 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA['True Detective' creator kept the finale a secret from the cast https://t.co/pYbdtSzkrB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jujubeekennedy @katienolan @yehwho @BaileyKnecht @annamelissa @MelissaSulewski @TheKaylaKnapp @minakimes… https://t.co/lubMm3Hioy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancywyuen And a couple Spanish-language shows also on Netflix: Casa de las Flores and Casa de Papel. Both sooo good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @alexandani it probably is a good idea to double check #HarryPotter quotes before producing the bracelets.… https://t.co/4PT5ogYLRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[*applies yet for another summer internship instead of doing lab report due Monday morning* https://t.co/TaWxP8ZEnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder_fucker Wish you could forget everything as quickly as things ended. I know it hurts, but pleaseeeeee try to stay positive. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You knew me when I was what 21-22 bitch I’m finna be 27 that’s a 5-6 year gap gtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si en la peda no ponen canciones de Los canelos de Durango que ni se arrimen alv]]></document><document><![CDATA[given the state of my phone screen i will be accepting phone calls only fromnow on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiberalLogic123 In her defense she didn’t deny that he’s a liar and a fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! It's a great day to serve so let's get to it. https://t.co/bZprHVXe4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to hear @AOC speak at #SXSW2019 - what really resonated with me was how having a capitalist structure means you… https://t.co/HZYYXIFB8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonLybrand @FoxNews Different kinds of news organizations, you say?  The MSM is decidedly left. They’re the gateke… https://t.co/giFGAtq24p]]></document></documents></author>