<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[ME AND LISA (CASKEYS MANAGER) JUST TALKED SOME REAL BUISNESS!!! chedda_chixs and @Pistyle2013 and the  bomb squad g… https://t.co/4zeCMw2STl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfterHoursCBS @BNightengale @ALawRadio Sick money. All baseball fans are paying for these guys.  Padres wasted their money]]></document><document><![CDATA[So good! Let’s keep instigating something for the fall 2019 in NYC my friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniebender @NombreEsJustin @alegriselle @BobChoate54 @rrfosho72 @heyyrandi @LMac_1326 @iam_workman… https://t.co/ssjDIet862]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have enough #zelda hats. Not sure tho. @ Mesa, Arizona https://t.co/867XJzwQk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TradeTheSpread @WarrenBuffett @MikeBloomberg Nah. DTC is the business to be in. Can't imagine how challenging it m… https://t.co/4mg8BOZNve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m_sheldon That hamstring is all they need to hold him out 14 days or what's needed to get extra control]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hurricanenita Ask @CharlieBonnet3 and @traciiguns - they know I will. 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlckstephens What if I’m #RockiesTwitter member and my gf roots for the Rockies and has a Twitter but does not par… https://t.co/AxK3Sd0OWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the price of a cup of coffee a day you can change the life of a Klobuchar Staffer... please help #tcnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[••• You Are Invited To The Gracias Choir ::: EASTER CANTATA ::: ••••••••••••••••••••••••••••• Witness a musical ree… https://t.co/glrR4IbnHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao. The struggle. 😂  #thestruggle #nyc #nyny #sobx #kermit #broke #brokeaf #travel #toofunny @ New York, New York https://t.co/plC7WTdG2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @TrumpsareNazis @realDonaldTrump That's for dam sure. Trump is a domestic threat and a Russian bought puppet asset.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkrticX @Indians @Mike_Anthony13 @Cleveland_PL @thiswascle @EncyCle_ @vinceguerrieri @BDbaseball6 @stomattu… https://t.co/7ZKHE8j5eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilipObin @APCNigeria I think very poorly of Atiku. PDP is the party of corruption, the party of crooks and thiev… https://t.co/FCWYUbn1LP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanchait There is literally no one in the Dem party ‘defending anti-Semitism. Don’t be so lazy. Read Ilhan Om… https://t.co/cr06VphnxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Witness Uganda was amazing!! So proud of my bro @dexterdarden. If you’re in LA and haven’t seen it, you should! Cre… https://t.co/oCOL6sKX2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another reason to LOVE @Tesla! #HatersGonnaHate #Innovation #IWantATesla]]></document><document><![CDATA[The wife is trying to connect all Oklahoma coaches wives. If you coaches can get your wives to follow we would appr… https://t.co/MgwFqoeqtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to inform you and Lynette that Trenton is not in the middle of no mans land. It is 20 minutes from Willis… https://t.co/OQstFJkmNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off the birthday runcation with @phisigbabe. Will run for Mickey waffles!! @runDisney @WDWToday https://t.co/BIT7FwoOnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer+shave can’t go wrong just chilling in my @OneHourTees T-shirt @ Roosters of Shops at Shenandoah https://t.co/RYNxnOfL7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PittmanTim @RepAdamSchiff Well, I don't know about that. The dumbasses that voted for him would have done so regardless of the facts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3mmageddon @MediumYellow10 It’s heat shield....it’s actually used a lot in commercial theatre and dance....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity: Making Your Faith in God Stronger https://t.co/gogt6hEO7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister is a Nursing PhD, ER mostly, my ex girl a charge nurse, I was a Chef with Marriott, I know way too much about you guys,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random thought about delivery robots. What's stopping me from taking other peoples' packages from the robot?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerxxxsweet @gaygringo_ @graysonlangexxx @HunterSmithXXX We’ll just form a train, it’s chill 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Credit where credit is due. Excited about the new primary reforms put forward by @TomPerez and the @DNC. (Especiall… https://t.co/zoNETv10tL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wobbleland ‘19 🌀🤘🏼 so great seeing Art 💕 .... where’s Perry?🤓 https://t.co/PaPhu2EQhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DF_Taimou @uNKOE Closer is also a beast. But Unkoe is like a turret back there and is responsible for so much dama… https://t.co/0CezZ119uY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I love being sick the same weekend as the Kansas basketball game and not being able to go🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @HillaryClinton Both Hillary and Obama knew about the interference long before the election but did noth… https://t.co/mSA8DCuoEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with some fellow MBA Alumni friends, based in the Washington, DC region. @ The Board Room VA https://t.co/vLXs715tl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wana know why bruh killed his patnas.i wonder was they tripping or was he]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOICEOFCHID Is it just possible...I mean isn’t there the slightest chance that one could not line this movie and still be a decent person?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woodbrid5 The same here the waves are pushing ice over the break wall on Lk Michigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doggozone @SallyMayweather I didn't get the gist without your clarification on numbers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NLIHC found US workers need to earn $22.10 an hour to afford a "modest" two-bedroom rental. That's about three… https://t.co/heUhKkymu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And she defeated the best Republican politician the @GOP could put against her, so...]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOOKY LOOKY WEDNESDAY'S EXPERIMENT @ Wiz's Eatery https://t.co/NPUwnicHdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you @6abc have a tv crush on #LukePerry @karenrogers6abc @sarahbloomquist @CecilyTynan @monica_malpass… https://t.co/cAZ06WoDLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilKim Looking for Big Momma Thang clean version can’t find it anywhere 😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[5am welcome party pulling into work this am! #MarinersST https://t.co/exOA9MzprT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OrdwayBroadway 2019/2020 next up a new regional premier #OrdwayOriginal this Christmas... #EverAfter https://t.co/GfnxAVE0EV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife and I had plans to drive to Aspen for our 2 year anniversary today. Needless to say, we had to pivot our pl… https://t.co/2AAUFJ6cXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[J. Cole AMAZING Full Halftime Performance at 2019 NBA All-Star Game https://t.co/5ubxif1DJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrbVenus @lacomayoficial @juanoscar2020 @juanoscar2020 La bola está en su cancha. Recuerde q se debe a sus constit… https://t.co/Pn2pCz81Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Yes! The flood at the border has to be stopped! It’s a disgrace to the citizens of this nation!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Schumer, Joe Biden Break From Standards To Praise President Trump https://t.co/36HVCuLBVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImNotAHRHitter @StelliniTweets Man imma not trying to get off couch except to answer door]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was everything i could of asked for!!! 2 weeks of college left and got to watch some of my best friends bal… https://t.co/Bvs89Vlq8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know three foreign languages and speak all of them at the 3rd grade level. This year I plan to bring them all to… https://t.co/cF1QkCJ6Qu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ked_smith @thehumble_26 We ain’t get blown out in the natty tho 🤷🏿‍♂️🤷🏿‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you someone who spends all their time sending you memes when you’re not together 😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[even if Trump gets credit for it I agree. Still not enough for a Nobel though IMHO his other negatives disqualify h… https://t.co/RH62asgC69]]></document><document><![CDATA[My organization starts a new partnership today with Summit County Public Health. I’m actually looking forward to seeing how this goes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I understand that seeing your first-born child is probably the most amazing experience ever, but have you ever had cheese and crackers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #SouthWakeCounty on Lk Wheeler Rd near Ten Ten Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luck was on my side tonight! Time to get some sleep and get ready to go watch some good races tomorrow at @themint400]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonylinert You’ll make a great doctor.  They’re never on time either]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MacLeodLisa bully. lies. #ResignLisaMacCleod #AutismDoesntENDatFORD #asd #autism #asd #onpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LEAxxoo Good morning Lea and happy Tuesday from my alternative music station]]></document><document><![CDATA[Die großartige Foodblogger-Aktion „Die kulinarische Weltreise“ (von @volkermampft ) führt uns diesen Monat nach Kub… https://t.co/45LveY9OLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[wedding portrait  wedding invitations #comedy #lol #smile #clever https://t.co/edpHuDbBKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews “Kid... have you rehabilitated yourself?”                           Alice’s Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if the weather is getting to me or not with it being so cloudy constantly here in SC, but I have been… https://t.co/pRVmvCfJwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise Jesus for one of the, “BEST VALENTINES GIFT I EVER RECEIVED”! (Birthdays on February 14)   HAPPY BIRTHDAY, t… https://t.co/K8jahQyMBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section 7AAAA Final:  Minnesota 65 St. Franics 60  @MNAtSports  #mshsl  #MNScores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_McCray Idk what you’re saying in this at least the first half. But Em has an incredible and unique legacy… https://t.co/oyQ3jpD7UO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wise man once told me to be careful what you pray for... some of the truest words ever spoken! You have to be bui… https://t.co/LDe6a1cYbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys You should be PROUD to have made it Without COMPROMISING Yourself! CONGRATS Anne!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I preach only worrying about #Inter taking care of their own business on the pitch, but I’d be lying if I sa… https://t.co/HOf4zRJmi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an On the Lam  by @BicycleBrewery at @brewfestottawa — https://t.co/Q9np3rbm0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a big fan of cancel culture, but why haven’t we roasted Aidan Gillen aka Littlefinger aka Mayor Carcetti a HELL… https://t.co/aokAGcgKEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't know who I doge more people asking for blood or homeless people asking for change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But do you really go to UCLA if you don’t do hw after drinking and going out?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy @ahardtospell I always knew it as a “French exit”. Have I been prejudice against the wrong people this whole time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryne_o_mite @Cubs @ARizzo44 @WContreras40 @javy23baez @KrisBryant_23 @faridyu @albertalmora @ihapp_1 @CEdwardsSBS… https://t.co/WiD0PXyAnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggamejames36 Man I got someone that can design the Big Game 36 Collection.  Jits.  God's Plan.  MFTK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEI @sciencemagazine @NuScale_Power One more pie in the sky nuclear fiscal failure being served up by the NEI.  Co… https://t.co/IKGnOzV4a5]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEBAA Show 2018 Drone Video Footage https://t.co/3DCZ6OGXs7 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk You are acting like this fearless girl and I love it! https://t.co/KVx96HPrdZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachMattPugh Thanks Matt I really appreciate it. Looking forward to seeing all of your new stuff at Snow Valley this year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @gerardway #UmbrellaAcademy It’s Great https://t.co/00DdrTpCoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvanLSolomon How long will this lawyer to determine whether she can speak? Wait until it has maximum damage in Trudeau!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartyR_Jays @Wilnerness590 Really? I have lived and breathed this team since the strike shortened 1981 season! I a… https://t.co/Yp9HYFTUiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE_MandyRose would really love to bring you out to some comic cons this year!  If you are interested DM me. : )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garden_yogi @The_STJ_Way @KwallsDaDon How does not wanting your woman to dress extremely sexually enticing in publ… https://t.co/FRZOdaUwm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoppinmama5 @u2biker @mymynags @kvmidd85 @1776KAG @gator4kb18 @MeltingInMarana @PTSD_SURVIVOR @ErikTheLizard… https://t.co/ptRU1v2S7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DregOfHumanity @McDonalds @Miss_Red_Me @realDonaldTrump He will forever be seen as a psychotic old man in this photo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RearAdBsBlog @stoolpresidente @Barstool_Quotes @BarstoolRadio https://t.co/DhbSN09ZK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMcMorland Do you wanna do a pre interview on the Albeist conditions leading to your death that way I can have an obit ready to go]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a beautiful Sunday. Bring joy to all. You can't buy it. It comes from the heart!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UAL756 I like flying it better than the jet! (The QOL in the jet is better but the things you can do with the PC12… https://t.co/RFa90ZfcWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANNUITY AGENT SECRETS - LEARN WHAT THE PROS KNOW! NEW VIDEO ☑️🎥 https://t.co/rxPuSZWrsy #insuranceagents… https://t.co/X7yRmIIOx6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMarsRover @JoeCCunningham @PrinterAttic You have to save your perfect sequence somehow otherwise it will drive y… https://t.co/AFnGeQq7Sb]]></document><document><![CDATA[$spy $spx is like to think this small pullback off 2815 res is the start is something bigger but I think it’s just… https://t.co/8T1eqYwStR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I purchased a bed frame for my new room. I’ve been thinking about it all day. I am a grownup person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @v_tweezy the cut gotta ni€€a taking selfies 😭😭😭 @ Miami International Airport - MIA https://t.co/CrGllZ54Rk]]></document></documents></author>