<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Gabe Lander (@LanderLab) gave an incredible lecture on the capabilities of cryo-EM microscopy.🔬Seeing the machinery… https://t.co/lAAZi0QrA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @IngrahamAngle @SenFeinstein The democrat party used to care about Americans and the rule of law. N… https://t.co/mIevfgc6i3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlisonTPatton @jonfitztv @dietotaku @Preaus @RealSaavedra @AOC Bull shit. God is protecting a country that partake… https://t.co/87rxfKk9TR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a 2014 @tigers game against the @dodgers. Kinda wanted to hear @fake_DDickerson and @Fake_Jim_Price but Vin Scully would do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussellCJ36 I have a 3 hour class currently for twice a week. I feel that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBradCurrie A2. To support transparency via consistent communication via twitter/FB/posted newsletters etc.  Emb… https://t.co/VKEuGjrrOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s my girls!!!!! In Heaven There is no Beer!!!!! B1G TEN CHAMPIONS!!!!! #GoHawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayybugs_ None that are good. The ones I’m in make me want to kms with the fur mama idiots who shouldn’t own them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 Flexibilty. It’s having a plan but the willingness to go with the flow. If the flow is to discuss a topic more i… https://t.co/GZW1KgkiJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I am retweeting because this is a beautiful thing to see. I agree about spending tax dollars on technology lik… https://t.co/8Y2pEZ2RNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peeperpea29 @karenslinn43 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Iluvinspireu @MelindaYoe @ClockworkHamma @JackConnie @ann4252… https://t.co/Bqg6eTQJS5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only good thing about eating a little at a time is that there’s more for later!! 😌 (just mad as hell I’ve been… https://t.co/Ii7jQl2N8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause today, we r excited and proud to kick this day off by introducing some of the inspiring women that join us fo… https://t.co/RzrpJIGdyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer @AriFleischer wondering if you advise the same for every (and there are dozens) poorly-aged tweet from @realDonaldTrump?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My goodness Charlie, thank you. Your hard work does not go unnoticed and I am certain you have a bright future in t… https://t.co/h24mDAb07h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jewtastic @Socaltokc @BIniti8nCr8 I can see why that would be a shock.  I think a dozen store brand are about $2.50 or $3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Jim Jordan needs to handle his own issues. He should have been thrown out of Washington last year. https://t.co/HzceLvhxvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nj_sos You are not fighting for every student!  Instead you are demanding certain districts be funded at above 100… https://t.co/4eE3zZq0MQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are so dumb! The rich pay most of the taxes in this country! Stop your sick lies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to know why I still have classes tomorrow when everyone else has the day off??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day one: starting the Disney festivities off appropriately...mucky pretzels! @ Expedition Everest - Legend of the F… https://t.co/Gubo4GGTHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgm2 @ricrush1 @98WSIX My sinuses are so backed up that my teeth hurt!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I’ll give it to my future daughters Barbie doll 😂😂😂 wtf 500 for that small ass shit what the hell is gonna fit… https://t.co/Xk1uaI4Y3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Servos Desconhecidos (Portuguese Edition)  https://t.co/Mjl0tXGZuu via @amazon]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TrasnocheParanormal EN VIVO | BebanaRadio AIRE JUEVES 28/02/2019 https://t.co/dXb3jGp49N vía @YouTube #Bebanavintage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjsoms98 Your teeth are beautiful Tan let your smile shine bright for all to see :)                 From Hales and T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bagelicious (at @EinsteinBros Bagels in Flower Mound, TX) https://t.co/b6XhOgxg8S https://t.co/mEYkC0TYYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[To voltando pro Brasil, mas ainda tenho umas 200 fotos da viagem pra postar. E isso não é uma hipérbole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost.  I will NEVER NEVER EVER PAY YOU  $1.00 to read your fucking post!  I get a morning briefing from… https://t.co/E4VvU3NpUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rweiss1234 They are not aware how much they are making Cohen look credible.  They look like idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luv_A_LEXI Lol god forbids if they die today or tomorrow, he’ll be fucked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I want to WIN in 2020. I can, and will, support our nominee. I like Biden, as well as Harris, and oth… https://t.co/evgC4Vg3ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to the week! #flirtwithgreatness @ Montezuma High School https://t.co/pgNhh1Waxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris Thank you! Please explain WHY you voted no. Please explain to those who didn’t understand what thi… https://t.co/jN1G6vwwbw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a comment how I was going to send Lennon to Cathedral in Indy bc I like the thought of her going to an uppity… https://t.co/iUkfxGTrM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Put #JeffreyEpstein  and #AlexAcosta in the same prison cell a$ap, and pass stricter #GunControlNow law… https://t.co/wJ9O4Ux3it]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We should never have a profit motive to put people in prison.” - @James_Mackler at the #JFK Club, Chattanooga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery Send them all south and make them do their jobs at the border for a couple weeks. Bet they’ll change their mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #MardiGras outdoors at #mardigrasmadness . Great band playing OUR music, big dance floor, 2 bars, nice… https://t.co/RpLG2bEtKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rising_serpent @ConstituentOne I know! Why isn’t this being covered???????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_mbutler 1932 William Faulkner completes his novel "Light in August" #OTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take one leave two - love this in the school neighborhood - I always leave children’s books.   #littlefreelibrary… https://t.co/FduZZ0EXAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GovBillWeld is in New Hampshire signing the eggs 🥚 before Politics and Eggs this morning. https://t.co/EuAcTr1R42]]></document><document><![CDATA[“aver si ya encuentra novio amargada felicidades” - my aunt 🙃 lmao girlll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodFirstGina @Hulk4Trump @SealeyGerald @WinnDuncan @KeithAl76434895 @TroyShilling @usaf1999 @SeniorHandyman1… https://t.co/pZ1xmIWJF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more #LoveYourPetDay #fosterlove #fostering #CatMom #crazycatlady https://t.co/q2He01inMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamaraneo Chase you down the street and scare the crap out? I don’t know hon. I like to think they are just really… https://t.co/n5dGNmNM0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sccsd #SCCSDCTE #ProStart #CulinaryPathway #IowaDepartmentOfEducation #IowaACTE #SiouxCityCareerAcademy… https://t.co/feJy1eEGGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherMyCarl @oldiesjunkie @phillysal2k @geegeeking49 @Steven_Scibetta @realDonaldTrump Wow typical Trump supporter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouAreInAComa That doesn't mean you give up on Voltron. It's always going to be there for you. it's just if it mak… https://t.co/W6l51vDc9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[These February homework-doers are enjoying lunch in the classroom😋 #Lakeside1819 #CISDcoverstory https://t.co/V3eJhnJrMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the new song #ColdInLA @whydontwemusic @JonahMarais @corbynbesson @SeaveyDaniel @jackaverymusic… https://t.co/fXamTNQdC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Familia Hernández #texas #ilovethem @ El Paso, Texas https://t.co/fNfx7kTOh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FBF #OnThisDay #2015 #Future       We had a blast that night! 💃🏽 @ Xclusive Elite Entertainment Center https://t.co/j3IdonwbDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[still cannot believe I was ga for @5sos. See ya in October! I could honestly burst from excitement. https://t.co/YbH0WqfovI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When considering whether to address @Glassdoor comments from disgruntled former employees, consider that future emp… https://t.co/A1AEqpEFsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Wednesday. This morning inspiration for you and food for thought truly 🕉🐉 @ Lawnton, Pennsyl… https://t.co/cPmdfMctE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking through ur mans likes just to see him liking girlfriend relatable content 🥰 https://t.co/z6NAZ4cBAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the best, most responsible course of action would be for the Kardashians to just shave their heads, burn th… https://t.co/A1MaChkmzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[today someone told me I kind of looked like Mila Kunis and it’s the best compliment I have ever received..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should've called my uncle Bobby while I was here... He prolly touring somewhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shitty thing about having had been in love is that if a guy doesn’t make my heart drop/soul explode when I’m in his… https://t.co/EVV1mSheYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRBVGB @2013AngelM @HillaryClinton I was referring to the comment about abortion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emma you were literally asleep in my bed. Then I got in bed and you decided to go to the living room and cry. What'… https://t.co/bPE7bcTFsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️ this! A little #NBAAllStar history for my hometown! We got game in #CLT @SHAQ even said so! @NBAonTNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Here we are again. Another year gone by and once again black Twitter is the best thing about Twitter, if I'm b… https://t.co/Mk34BFJgE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve dated a couple trash ass niggas and they had money ! Money don’t make a nigga NOT TRASH ladies ! A bigger pict… https://t.co/rGABF7nzNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics @kyblueblood He just talks. He just throws out bullshit to see what sticks. As long as idiots chee… https://t.co/Hb3X7xhzNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Sarah Elizabeth  I was born in the same day as the first day  My age is a bit of a blessing I like to it… https://t.co/eKxmSYPgj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixed media....Chalk Couture Ink, in Couture Teal on a Tea towel and an iron on sample that came with my Cricut Eas… https://t.co/jDcH3b0hZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday funday with the family 🛥⚓🚤❤ @ Atlantic City Boat Show Convention https://t.co/2EUkJfTIKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously so blessed to be Pete’s girlfriend. Idk how I got so lucky. Thank you every girl in middle school who rejected him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@punker_irl after the new senate democratic legislation against preventing killing babies after birth...ummm...yes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[over is pretty harsh, don't you think? but we certainly have a lot of work to do... // With a New Influx of Wealt… https://t.co/xa5XLbRfB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peeka_Boo5 That’s cool not bashing Kobe at all but we not about to act like his crazy triple teamed shots and not… https://t.co/2gv2MDQfQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well , possibly another one to get smashed. How long do we give this @NotFearix before it’s broken 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brynnak0 It was I could take it on campus or I could do it online but it recorded me the whole time and you couldn… https://t.co/ydTKoZnMAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Inventory In get it before it's gone. @ Mount Holly, North Carolina https://t.co/Yx9InTAP7C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out #IntelSelectSolutions at #MWC19 driving new use cases in #intel #IAmIntel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m confused. I think Senator Feinstein was very respectfully telling them why she didn’t support the bill, giving… https://t.co/qRsZLrEpfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s VERY limited spots for women w/children and/or pregnant to attend supported treatment w/housing, drug court… https://t.co/zYW3gONKIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Twitter sass over the last couple days caused a few changes. 20 of you got very angry and unfollowed, but 49 new… https://t.co/wZBhXE9B4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yard work plus a run with @americanjetset makes a very excellent Sunday 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @MGoBlueSD @11rrios You don’t like Canada?  I love Canada.  The better half of my family lives there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The goal was 6 miles under 60 minutes ➡️ finished at 57:02 ! I have some work to do to prepare for 13.1 under 2 hou… https://t.co/HVAl8NUnLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I USED TO LIKE NAPOLITANO BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED PAST WHERE HE SHOWED HIS HAND AND I LOST ALL RESPECT !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to relive our Henry filled weekend after all this time 🖤  (Minus the driving all over the state, no sleep a… https://t.co/Dr7M2smaUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro you will be a gorgeous bride!!!  I wish you many years of happiness ahead!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @KatrinaPierson @CharlieDeMar Can hollyweirdos believe their eyes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Praise God Almighty, Thank you President Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 bihhh please be going be like nooooooo smiling and shit sit down for 5 seconds and back doing wtf he ain’t soup… https://t.co/TCL4Rzild2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOtransitLE Thanks for the response. Currently waiting on the 14:13, fingers crossed we get out of union station🤞🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day to be a falcon, another successful charity week! #thegrovesway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marabscott Yes it was. That thing snapped off,  whipped around, and knocked someone over.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PickleAndNancy Happy #JellyBellyFriday Nancy and Pickle have a lovely day love Debbie and RIP Cinnomon!!😸😸🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm no better Sis but imma get it together this year .... I'm too old to be this lame 🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@majorolimpio Triste ver uma coisa como essa. Quantos anos jogados fora quantos já perderam a oportunidade de mudar… https://t.co/t3wYj9CoJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I be wanting to go to events on campus but I always forget and go home right after class #TUSKEGEE_RYS19]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just decorated a mirror and who knows how many other things for my sister this past season now i feel like the next martha stewart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meredithakers I’ve played this game before, but it was called Fishbowl. So much fun! I’ve never used it with stude… https://t.co/fxhuh0P4tq]]></document></documents></author>