<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Thank you for taking these photos and making me feel like a goddess @_madddisonx https://t.co/sqQd21nnqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said I was wholeheartedly messy this morning but after much consideration and spaghetti bolognese and anxiety medication im gud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmraynor @gmraynor get this! @Ask_Spectrum had an outage in Raleigh from early second half thru end of game! Don’t… https://t.co/tzbJOvt0ON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending my lunch break with my favorite #firstgraders! I think next time I need to bring a #selfiestick so I can g… https://t.co/eZJInqp66e]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Long Weekend Getaways To Have A Romantic Trip https://t.co/95KCNaleD5   #travelinspiration #traveltribe #travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflecting back to last week when I was in #Belize, flying over the #BlueHole via @MayaIsland! https://t.co/yeW6i2boAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@furtogo @Mackwell33 @cspanwj @RepThompson The same arguments can be made... his dept to society is paid.  You define mentally ill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ditto! We Cdns have always been too complacent in the face of bad govts, and we’ve had lots. Great to see… https://t.co/MLZFxsfFvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_8257 @WYPDavidHarland @WYP_ChrisCahill Been nice if this Legend had gone out and said something ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get chubby in your relationship, it means you in love and comfortable. https://t.co/erUOGfFNNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankeyLowkey My mom did that once in the microwave and it started to catch on fire 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to Hope World! It can always  make me dance when I’m feeling down! ☀️☀️☀️☀️☀️💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaxtonParis Awwww!!! Is it allergies?? I haven’t watched #RHONY yet! Yeah, I know! I was shocked when it happened.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParisJackson: WADE had LIED.  SUE HIM CALMLY.  👽. https://t.co/N60fPJisR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Announcer for the #NBAAllStar game with the echos sounds like The Grinch in this scene..🗣 https://t.co/xSuKZbVDCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@selina3sticks I do, too (and I say this as someone who’s far more in the pragmatist camp on this topic— I want the… https://t.co/o7Jy0mtE5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lightning100 @MumfordAndSons @BrdgstoneArena @615jayson @theadamculver Jonestown Revival....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELLEmagazine @taylorswift13 @ninagarcia This young lady might be a few years younger than me but she’s light years… https://t.co/p1ReHbXxCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slpng_giants How in Gods name do you sleep at night @IngrahamAngle!!!! You’re spreading lies that will literally k… https://t.co/NqGJkeF9km]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been quite awhile since I took “family photo” selfies... and it shows. 😂  We’ve got the @Airstream_Inc in tow… https://t.co/979iuug2Qe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because i can’t decide...which Fyre Festival documentary did you think was better?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly believe that there is something for Every Body through my program. Take #2BMindset, which is a great first… https://t.co/rO6cbAirBi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haileyxshmailey Then honestly you bought a priceless pair of leggings for $40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsosheriff how can you enforce the 15 mph on college st at king. People speed thru all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miagetshome Titanic, Moulin Rouge!, Atonement, La La Land. All of them bring me pain. Happy Valentine’s Day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomwatson anger issues - which is why he seems to be yelling all the time - even when he's not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who's counting the farts. I know, that's what they want the illegal aliens for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My students need a voice.  Can you help give them one?  https://t.co/B5hhyE74YI  @wkamaubell. @TheSharkDaymond.… https://t.co/7EWD5PUWay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live look at what I wish will happen to Jim Jordan  #CohenTestimony https://t.co/bTz5KtMfai]]></document><document><![CDATA[Squirrel shenanigans with music lol. #worshipwithnature #sillysquirrel #squirrel #funny #lifeinthehollow… https://t.co/W8JBoqQX9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My niece gives me so much joy when I have her it’s crazy😩💞 I really love her like she’s mine!😍 https://t.co/C3UpdI0Jn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growing up, my mum made a special effort to make sure me and my siblings didn’t buy motorcycles. This is her turnin… https://t.co/Am2gcIY8fJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teen Titans fandom in 2013: RobStar is canon so you can only ship Robin and Starfire with each other and no one els… https://t.co/Qe4AEVCqc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Olympia Heights FL Wed Feb 27th AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of T-Storm Hi 81 TONIGHT Chance Of T-Storm Lo 69]]></document><document><![CDATA[A recent modeling experiment sculpting my take on Gamera. Combining polypaint and Procreate to polish up ZBrush mod… https://t.co/ktrmvuYOxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump Right!  The wall got him elected.  Need to remember that when Congressmen who do no… https://t.co/kWxb0fJdfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more way to showcase our students, their knowledge and creativity...wow!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArchKennedy @Jenn198523 I hope not. But look at the rest of her party that have been in office for 40 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you 🙏 lifepharm for the gift 🎁 of Refive producthollywoodusa Oscar Gifting Suite yesterday @WCHollywood . Loo… https://t.co/B8GSDXJ9pk]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter where I go my makeup bag always stays up front with me, it will never go in the back with the rest of my stuff 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[University of Mississippi students vote to remove Confederate statue https://t.co/RI65yRD1e6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iceberg21Slim5 Probably has no walls and couldn’t feel anything anyway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennieee___ Dude same I was like I’m taking it easy y I saw the message today. I’m like great 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikiFirmin @Treacle_Vizsla @AlmatheVizsla @VizslamentesUK @effes22 @RichPreston Going to be another of you Masterp… https://t.co/eMhUb6Nq0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist This link works, but know going in that this is satirical. Humor? Horrendous Humor, but...]]></document><document><![CDATA[2k for a verified IG blue check? Oh that’s big cap I ain’t going for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jp and I don’t know anything about nowaday music buuuut give us that aux and we’ll play some throooooow baaaaacks 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reviews about Nā Hale Studios: "5 stars - Beautiful place and very well decorated. Perfect to rent out for any occa… https://t.co/QEcc4Jax5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jrboyy_ Your mom is a women with a beautiful soul. Be nice to her!!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[and then shame everybody who eats not keto as if they're unhealthy.... do u know how many times my boss (who eats k… https://t.co/vTmgn4vufR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLViviers Omg that's way too cold! I won't complain about -20 anymore lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[When IKEA debuts in your city .... every teacher makes a mad dash to the store 🏃🏼‍♀️🏃🏼‍♀️ New flexible seating opti… https://t.co/S2hwxFBpan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love you @mmckinnon, but not sure I'm ever going to forgive you for putting Dubya back in office in 2004.  😳@SHO_TheCircus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laying in bed coughing so I decided to grab a cough drop. As I’m unwrapping it, it falls out of the wrapper and is… https://t.co/KKJeefTpEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to you, my sweet, sweet bff💛 i hope your day is better than the rest! cannot wait to be with you in… https://t.co/bUmOl5dBop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah PIZZA!!! 🍕🍕🍕 It’s been a very long time since I ate #pizza  because I can’t have anything #gluten  Luckily I f… https://t.co/ThM0IAw8Gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have a boyfriend &amp; you constantly tweet about your ex then you have some serious issues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@libsareondrugs @CillizzaCNN @DNC Then they are really, really on the wrong side of that issue, don't you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetroVidGaming @XposeTrophyHunt @Protect_Wldlife @rickygervais @PeterEgan6 I have never understood how a person ca… https://t.co/w9V3Opy4w9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t even know bae brought us Love Jams tickets 😩😩 now I have to get myself together 😣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh. And you were still charged the full amount for purchase. That’s cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vcs_Lonnie @blueegg3r @MikeMicallef1 @VirginiaFreema1 @ap2ep2 @melissa_marple Yes!!!! Even when you say nothing at… https://t.co/BETwEShjug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharon_schwan @BxglL @72cricket @CSonafelt @rosemoczulski1 @sannbs @RidenerTina @MrsSpuds @ACog1984 Ah, nope - I sure don’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@actuallymaxie I hate to tell you this...it NEVER changes... https://t.co/4M4dMVaik8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayathmadw Please, let us connect soon! #MMUN #TeachSDGs #1500delegates #stuvoice @MichalMlynar #globalgoals 🌍💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiallOfficial @latelateshow @juliamichaels @JKCorden @benwinston Are you feeling better 😷 Niall ☘️💚☘️💚 ☘️💚 ☘️💚 ☘️💚 ☘️💚 ☘️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaTalmadge Has nothing to do w it, of course. He’s nothing but the flip side of the coin of the ranting criminal… https://t.co/E4FI4hmsYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Single one of them Must Answer the Question "Why have you Betrayed your Country for a FRAUD FAILURE ILLIGITIM… https://t.co/RH5Bzii56N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikischmidt1 @MichaelAvenatti So professionals can be unprofessional?   What’s the point to your obvious statement?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LHBLovesEdu You are the best!!! Going to sprinkle some love to yours ♥️♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[no gym in two days makes me feel like a beluga whale but then I think I need to chill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolitiBunny Good businesses pay more than minimum to retain employees.   Minimum is a starting point.  Raises if you are good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why people lie about being younger than they really are. I might start lying up and telling people I’m 42. I look great for 42.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreadLightly_RE $2.50 @mujiusa holder for my reusable plastic utensils, Dec 28.  (Last consumable purchase was 10… https://t.co/Q7P3fIYkjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Squish Cat may also be from Connecticut. https://t.co/VSB4Zl42QC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to read this thread through to the David’s last tweet. Climate change is a very complex conversation… https://t.co/MQPPKuFBpY]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're snuggling with your 1 year old &amp; she leans over to kiss you. It's the sweetest!! #momlife #momof2 #toddler]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poetrybydead And love and energy back to your tender ♥️ heart. Thank you. I love you too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigijackson261 Im here for ya Prince Michael. A year ago today I only wanted to be sure your dreams came true. On… https://t.co/ujwcJ1UfsB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Older population. Bigger population. Fewer public healthcare jobs. It adds up. @fordnation and his pals stand to ma… https://t.co/7qcdhTIZ6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’ll all become vegetarians will travel on roll skates will dress with the wine leaves all for their love of pow… https://t.co/y65LZYKO9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn Congressional hearing today with Trump fixer, Michael Cohen. Telling the truth about dirty tricks being played by the President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was such a joy to pass out love gifts today to the residents. Thanks to all that donated.… https://t.co/t9CC96AmF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushLimbaughEIB @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @foxandfriends @FoxNews  @LouDobbs @IngrahamAngle @AnnCoulter19… https://t.co/l61MNO4U9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to see the beautiful garden our Yeager students will create!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always a good weekend when a hometown homie comes to visit @ Ritz Bar https://t.co/YZoFK19lil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CLMcNaughton I am truly so deeply sorry for your loss. She truly was a shining light which will now continue to sh… https://t.co/FrcgT4vszj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone try to describe to me what this pop culture thing is without me actually saying it so that I don’t have ads… https://t.co/T2O2oLoyck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Well they are not gay but they also arent stupid like you wish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @CNN I don't watch them. Occasionally I am disappointed with #MSNBC but I still watch it. I do not l… https://t.co/CCL2SUcgsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, well dunking on this book was fun and making me feel young but then it got racist, so 🗑.  What should I read instead?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prizzillla I have had cramps for a day and a half and I'm just willing my period to start now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their record on pollution lauds them as the 14th worst polluters in the world. Fined millions for numerous environm… https://t.co/Zxwy8iNvH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Top Of The Hill Daly City in Daly City, CA https://t.co/fU4OOyqBQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Windagayle @army_bc @nanafrey7 @brandiz2 @ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @barb71 @MTumarkin @TrishDukes1… https://t.co/4hWkVEpAZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#safarilive Hasta la vista Peeps! What a great safari we had! So nice to have Tayla back with us for awhile! She br… https://t.co/TuBXdRgU6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Articulate_indy @doozerblake marketing jargon used on ANYONE is reason enough for a Silkwood shower... https://t.co/Ui3u9RfcVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY DEMETRIUS I LOVE YOU ❤️ THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING YOUVE DONE FOR ME! @DemetriusHarmon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icemanbb They are 26x4.0, but not sure on the brand. Came with the bike when I bought them a year ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[H_0: "I tell it like it is" will be followed with a racist remark. H_a: "I tell it like it is" will be followed by… https://t.co/qf0KeExnN0]]></document></documents></author>