<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ajsutts @inthewry In the summer I bet that's a lot of fun!  We have a lot of golf courses in our town and most wil… https://t.co/jLrBh3sc6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bitch came in 2 hrs before I had to work... cuz she damn well know I'll be there and fucking call her out..  S… https://t.co/bWak3UeFWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sheltieman3 God created the universe with a word. He can save your son from this scourge. Believe in Him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t care about all the shade @pac12 gets, @UW_MBB will be a Problem in the tournament. @Coach_Hopkins preaches en… https://t.co/zU3PxgMUDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m like Bruce Banner in that scene at the end of Avengers where he tells Cap he’s always angry, except my secret is I like brussel sprouts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockoCalavasi @RealTimers @NoahCRothman he is a pompous pseudo-intellectual who just throws out word salad]]></document><document><![CDATA[run it back                                                       turbo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Innovation means saying no to 1,000 things.” -Steve Jobs #MichaelHyatt #FullFocusPlanner #Goals]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the same reasons PETA freaks rail against old ladies wearing furs and not bikers wearing leathers...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Score in @EHLpremier action: @LittleFlyersHky- 4 @RevsJrHockey- 1. Luke Headman leads the way with 2 goals. M… https://t.co/c90nXBt9PV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Want to be an #AllProDad? #1 be in relationship with Jesus  #2 Introduce your children to Him [ #Jesus ].” ~ Dabo… https://t.co/0zNA5CvGE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScienceNews Dinosaur fossil strata ends 2 million years before Chicxulub. Dinosaur rapid diversification ended at… https://t.co/zgff0KRP7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[My day started off really shitty, but I just found out that ‘A Goofy Movie’ is finally coming out on blu-ray, so it… https://t.co/fUkvMiZH8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raptors who is this on your bench? #microblading https://t.co/iCpjVkEhtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino We still have a debt problem.  Congress has been printing paper money to cover debts for too long.  It’s… https://t.co/y7dmpCOJ60]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bretbart needs to have a mission statement - they act like a democrat spreading garbage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_christinaaaxox @SanJoseSharks Wow I've never had that experience. Thats really crappy. People should leave that k… https://t.co/Ebw5NfWtsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And today... #pullups, #bruteforcesandbags  #wheredidthecarbsgo , subbing #speedrope for sprints, then more… https://t.co/gDaFZpkMQO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chiefs365Com I agree in a sense...he means so much to KC BUT age wise, Ford is the “future”]]></document><document><![CDATA[On International Womens Day, it's fitting to remember Rep. Jeanette Rankin, who was not only first, but willing to… https://t.co/T9f7WspXkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The United Methodist Church will have a big history-changing vote on the fate of its demonination this weekend over… https://t.co/erbOIIofKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[just witnessed someone order 6 waters at Harry’s....whata terrible person]]></document><document><![CDATA[This day has easily been the best day in #ClipperNation twitter history]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcude93 Thank you. The school that beat us in the finals is the school that Mt. Pleasant consolidated with. One of… https://t.co/u61AQKe9QS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SithLordAR Still as fresh to me as it was in late 80s https://t.co/VubepWcHxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mayor's Christmas Tree Lighting in Overland Park, Ks...hosted by KMBC TV9/ABC Bryan Busby...RBSR©2018 @ Downtown Ov… https://t.co/6Mhzsc20Ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Should we expect a different course from Trump?  He’s nominated a string of incompetent folks with cri… https://t.co/fsuV72csfW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paczki stop #2. #FatTuesday #PureMichigan #destinationannarbor (@ Zingerman's Bakehouse - @zingbakehouse in Ann Arb… https://t.co/Gvlc68czxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBFeldy I guess the U didn’t even push to sell these tickets and with the state tourney going on it’s a tough sell… https://t.co/kyYQ7GeTKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rt if you think my heart nips are cute 😇 #staykinky https://t.co/mcNMBolVII]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obligatory 1st #chairlift ride of the season This is our lucky 13th time! @bromleymountain #mysunmountain… https://t.co/40ijf7ucAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TheHumble_21 @haha_cd6  come to @packers we got #cookies ;-)#NFL #FreeAgency #Championships]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you could have any single Xbox or Nintendo exclusive game on PlayStation, what would it be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to swan dive into a blunt and a man in 24 hours https://t.co/sFuID81ET7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 Amazing officers, looking out for the folks in their jurisdiction. These guys are amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnMendes   “If you’re a bird, I’m a bird”  #HappyValentinesDay https://t.co/p7HUF0SzMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lakers in 33 under Jerry Buss:   1641 - 855 (.657 win %) 31 playoff appearances 10 Championships  The Lakers in… https://t.co/ZrOAkX1WZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Woodsy1069 @BoxRec I believe they are politically bios and unfair all away across the board. Favoritism towards fighters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ihateuJodiee Your birthday ain’t over yet lol keep celebrating. Someone gonna come thru 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leelee1873 I am so pissed off right now because of her being prone to losing stuff then remembering it to late. Ri… https://t.co/1HX2PA61DF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nealbeforeme62 This tweet has a lot of rewatchability. You can reuse this on all Syracuse games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isnardobravo @franklin_d_f_m9 seguro colocarán en el informe q no hay nada q reportar al estilo padrino López]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grandpabodie @AKinkhabwala Let's see where Ben takes this team now that his biggest albatross is gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidwebb917 @AJHerrmannYES Cant argue with the fact - but will add judge and Stanton have only had one year together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich I think it's very possible that Kamala Harris and Cory Booker are involved. Is it a coincidence that… https://t.co/830inAnZkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Pliny the Younger (2019) by Russian River Brewing Company at @libraryalehouse — https://t.co/eyfnGoLITY]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If our 1st Amendment means anything, it's that the government cannot retaliate against journalists based on the co… https://t.co/8o87LI1FHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nosey people have the nerve to get mad cuz you don’t tell them your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it up to the Upper Falls. The hike was well worth it.👍👍 📸❄🏔❤🇨🇦 💯 💯 All 🇨🇦Canadian🇨🇦 👍and comment. 💯 💯… https://t.co/7yseULE1L9]]></document><document><![CDATA[*screenshot* just in case 🙃.  If Louisville wins, do I get my ten minutes on the morning show?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little sisters did it! They are the 2019 @cifss Division 5 Water Polo Champions!! #morenosisters #champions @ Wi… https://t.co/hfer4kfWDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d also like to know the panelists’ thoughts about predictive analytics. Is this an important tool for student suc… https://t.co/fe752vICbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BozT ...and you can replace “Catholic” with “evangelical” or “Southern Baptist” and still be just as correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming round 1 of the 1k w/ @ColdHandz44 @LuckyDefuses @TacoSargent @ItsCField https://t.co/dYt5LWDIq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WGAL Good job dad! That boy needs to learn a lesson. Looks to me like there’s some bad parenting involved but he i… https://t.co/GdEpIm284f]]></document><document><![CDATA[A second tier gay actor LOOKING for his “15 minutes of fame”.....😡👎👊🖕😳😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[On today’s 11-mile run in awesome NYC, I had a feeling + concept that the simple difference between a goal and a dr… https://t.co/fXJMaG6Dmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impressive stoppage for Ramirez over De Gracia. King Kong Ortiz up next!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music from @ThomasRhett coming your way 3/2 as he performs on @nbcsnl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every part of Richmond in one picture 😤 issa #gang 💉💦 #tbt inthekitchwithmitch triple_a_alex_ eviloneproductions510… https://t.co/22bMCw8Qn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Judge Berman Jackson issue a gag order on 45? #RogerStone #RussianAsset]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hangout, but just really really early.. Who's going this year? @ Hangout Music Festival https://t.co/9B6Q8I9vRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the past 2 1/2 hours going through over 700 photos from my parents anniversary, and narrowed it down to half… https://t.co/2jwuNLR1Eb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great defense by Kyle Lewis to stop Monroe. He gets the rebound and will go to the line, 7.4 left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[0 He that loveth silver shall not be satisfied with silver; nor he that loveth abundance, with increase: this also… https://t.co/67FfJ3zrZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phillipfulmer is just a great man and just what UT needed. Keep up the great work!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @steph93065 @TheDemocrats What the he’ll is wrong with people. Why would you want to ever hurt your count… https://t.co/FzNHCeJARt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I don’t thinks so cupcake. You are not smart enough to be the Boss Of Yourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨- Subscribes Now to see full videos and new XXX pictures. 👿🔥💪🏽😘  My onlyfans : https://t.co/R5Dspe4dnh  My justfor… https://t.co/3J4ee1ndD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[CLASS 6A BOYS AREA PLAYOFF Tonight's winner gets the winner of El Paso Americas and Hurst Bell next week in the regional quarterfinals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJimORourke @GoreMountain Skiing is awesome and the weather is good. Couldn’t ask for more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT #happyvalentinesday #allhearts DM me when you're ready to get the quality work that you deserve 🤴🏿🤴🏿🤴🏿💈💈💈… https://t.co/KoyYYCRa3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natalia_nix u have a hot sexy sweet yummy pink pussy n hot sexy beautiful gorgeous ass with hot sexy boobs n nippl… https://t.co/9riVOLsJoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyRDaniels @xychelsea Who do you think are on grand juries?  People from Sweden?  Another planet?  They are citizens of the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iDoNotKnow88 Oh that’s a good idea I can add that. I was also going to offer a blindfolded run incentive but I thi… https://t.co/JFDy1Vf6xX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This coming from the Coward in Chief. The idea is not getting reimbursed it is about protecting th… https://t.co/V0c8kf3Jla]]></document><document><![CDATA[*18 years later*  child: mom I have no time to study  mom: um excuse me? don’t come at me with “no time to study” l… https://t.co/T1jQGFkZ7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can I barely sit still today? Because I fly to Missouri tomorrow for the 2019 Missouri Collegiate DECA State CD… https://t.co/6DiEkOVWtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Yep and imagine if Manafort was a POC , wonder how long that sentence would be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @woodywood1999 @MynameisMok @Beantowndougish @TaggartRehnn @FrankBenXXXOOO @KingPeachDP @JoeMomma833… https://t.co/F5vtUox7hM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danyaravid That’s when you go to “oyyyy no hablo english, sorry!” Little Spanglish to keep them guessing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShowmaxOnline you can't be serious!? This morning my inbox had an email that you'd no longer be available in my re… https://t.co/hk78MfWC9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midwest stop No. 2, in a city I’ve been to multiple times but have never really been able to see much of before tod… https://t.co/ymKhRieqh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the #cbj got their tax return and spent it like crazy #stlblues #NHLTradeDeadline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do que adianta a Juventus ter Cristiano Ronaldo se o juizão não marca uns 3 pênaltis?  É muito desperdício de talento.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Love #denton #wefollowback #denton #alltexasweb #followus #alltexasmedia @ All Texas Media https://t.co/gkuEr00YNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The band Bed Of Roses performs at Blackthorn 51. @ Blackthorn 51 https://t.co/cbzqM9YMKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath Feels like the threads of the tapestry of my past life are fraying and disintegrating. Very unsettlin… https://t.co/YqWBLellKQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[These R&amp;B artist are Cute today but I'm CRAVING the resurgence of some modern Hip Hop Soul. A new age Mary J!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even after the details of her business came out I still think she should be more embarrassed about being in this pi… https://t.co/9Ri8XXJJ3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee hey gary ¿Alguna tendencia fresca de uva en el negocio del vino? Chardonnay fella aquí]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now see what Bob Nutting spends his money on. https://t.co/3u2BEJYLLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abobrow Just reading that certain politicians created the atmosphere leading to the decision to leave. I think tax… https://t.co/SEjtYTcvpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyBrunoShow @Detrieman @BillNye @AOC @TonyBrunoShow  Who said anything about “hate?”  You started with negativity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tweet by HRC kept short somas not to interrupt her drinking. More likely dictated to an aide assigned to keep h… https://t.co/T0SpeUpJJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNCLE @memetwalker UNCLE @robertAbooey WHY YOU NOT TAKE MY CALLS AT YOU HOME ON SUNDAY I MAD AT YOU BUT I STILL LOV… https://t.co/TXtCpDnfVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kamenta Hahaha!! He's more trouble now that the hormones are raging! I cant stand that freakin Eugene!!! And now Rosita is knocked up too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsbeendead @Double0AG Nah Dennis has a raw one forsure but I just remember Aaron and those Oakland Soldiers lol… https://t.co/0Nkgez6RkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We loved working with our friend @therossking on his #oscars2019 Red Carpet tailoring #andrewbrookestailoring… https://t.co/PtShxTTo8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GTracySA Yeah looks like it’s a slideshow. Had to do some more digging to get to the bottom of it.]]></document></documents></author>