<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I don’t really care if anyone thinks I’m “weak” or a pushover. Doing things for others gives me personal fulfillmen… https://t.co/EGqfCbsbIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Now and then it’s good to pause in our pursuit of happiness and just be happy’ 🎀 #NewYork #DUMBO #Brooklyn @ DUMBO… https://t.co/xiM7vv1Yxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DEVELOPING: Five people shot to death, five more wounded in Cancún after gunmen burst into a bar in the Mexican re… https://t.co/XfrXy6ZZP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PRnDCSportFan No....Bryce has done more for me than any athlete ever. He will always be my favorite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWammock so deserves this. She is a great teacher to ALL students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stretching and shaping of our character and will can be uncomfortable.   The tension this shaping creates isn’t… https://t.co/MOngvmRs5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[it feels like -11 degrees outside according to the weather app and mfs still have the nerve to walk THIS SLOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supersuz14p @The_Salty_Mommy Believe me I don’t back down.  But the apologizing has become become ingrained in me… https://t.co/FWgZiZMbk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you wanna fix something you should be honest with me whatever I ask i need an answer to. Don’t push me away caus… https://t.co/6HH7oCeacV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @DsOchoa why is no one complaining about the brilliant defense team that got this deal for Epstein, led… https://t.co/PS0NB2ja9I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieSchultz Don’t worry.   @realDonaldTrump can help all those workers with the Trump Foundation.   Oh wait, that was bogus too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Pittsburgh government corruption has made us suicidal. Watch our true life story corru… https://t.co/pH4aQg9cCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Oxnard friends DO NOT respect me. @roliedc @tiffxxxo_ They stay flaking last minute, aren’t available or HELLA l… https://t.co/6HLSCZIe4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is all about the journey and enjoying the moments. Don’t get so caught up in the chase that you forget about t… https://t.co/x1xHhPZj8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @loveimawreck my sister was at the Pontiac, MI show last night with me and today she listened to every one of y… https://t.co/OYxs7q5No2]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me after breathing and being sure that the thing will go away after I take the breath, but it doesn’t” “oK WELL SHIT”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiroGomezL @lopezobrador_ Y DESDE CUANDO LOS ADULTOS NECESITAN QUE LOS DEFIENDAN?🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[now whole ass pineapples are gonna be just as expensive as pre cut pineapple. fuck y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siunds accurate. #WilliamGolding #momlife #truth. 🤷‍♀️ https://t.co/ZfOAZYof9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan I was pulling for you. Talking crazy about 44PBO is my line in the sand. You may want to chillax. Being high… https://t.co/nK2dSGQ6MX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my sweet card from monkey Jackson...XOXO #LOVE @ Lucas VIP Backyard Bar and Gril https://t.co/11bZFpAPBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vegastheo @AsmGarcia @cceanv @CCEANBPDP I’m torn on this. On one side, it is a disservice to students in our most… https://t.co/rrE1TGAdEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Warren is a known liar.  I won't listen to a word she said or says.  Why you do is beyond me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Hatred of Trump? What about your hatred of our democracy? @FaceTheNation]]></document><document><![CDATA[#exsandohs #elleking #ellekingcover #maxfieldparish #rocknrollgoddess #angelaleeburnett #angelalee #vocalist… https://t.co/helfvpxHzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some news, as they say: I’ve joined the University of Guelph’s News Service team, where we’re busy reporting on som… https://t.co/r7QvfRZQmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[bitch I went to culinary school plz tell me how food isn’t anything to make money off of lmfaooo EVERYONE EATS i’m… https://t.co/RmpH3zqyLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[*No sabes cuánto te quiero ver.* ¿Ah sí? *¿Me voy mañana, nos vemos esta noche?* Eh... Tons no me querías ver tanto… https://t.co/2Cz6FFamwv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMBitters That's awesome. As Ford is not only discontinuing my car but the entire model, it's going to be harder a… https://t.co/ufnBU3vNdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stars of Broaway belt their hearts out for @PFFORG. #BroadwayBeltsforPFF @JennyLaroche @ArianaDeBose @PattiMurin… https://t.co/a8ppBChUcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cut my hair. It’s short. I love it. I think this is part of self care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[HI TEAM!!!!   TODAY is the LAST DAY to donate to my fundraising campaign for Team for Kids! I'm only $335 away from… https://t.co/PfDnFX5zAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayiWena @schmangee HEY! and what's the matta w/that? seriously more than @indystar here. lotsa restos in which i never eat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[DALLAS COWBOYS BLING ICED OUT  NECKLACE PENDANT CZ STAINLESS DOG TAG https://t.co/rtD2sqQGAB #necklace #bling… https://t.co/ScA9bcULOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoisesMantra this is my mercury retrograde intention too! to only speak if it’s rooted in love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Loppyyy @REALGoingInRaw I think it would be contingent on what he’s offered. The selfish part of me want him to do both... heck EVERYTHING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t BELIEVE i’ve experienced a full day of snow in new york city??? i am living my dreams and best life all at once i’m gonna cry x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats #ReginaKing #Oscars #AcademyAwards #BestSupportingActress https://t.co/xDH1bmeceN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need so much stuff before we close on this house. We about to be sleeping on air mattresses if I can’t find the p… https://t.co/k46fszczK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a sec I thought this was my Jake and immediately started replying “...and you think mom will care...why?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[US says it will deliver aid blocked by Venezuela, setting up confrontation with Maduro regime  https://t.co/ro5oBPf86C]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got to be kidding! Take a history class from Hillsdale College and talk to our brave men and women that have fo… https://t.co/ruSog0whtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-finding myself {a process}~ #blythe #doll #toys #pettipants #bokeh #mint #girl #blythedoll #amberrenee @ Miseduc… https://t.co/JO9IvRjleo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljohns I wonder if Ryan kept his word, would the wall be completed by now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The girl I babysit just asked me how long my parents have been renting me for. Pretty sure the word she was looking… https://t.co/IQFm4JxgI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't like your girl being sexy on social media, don't get with a girl who is sexy on her social media. She… https://t.co/ZaV1pwz838]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshMooreXXX @DickstractedXXX Well, well, well...I go to @DickstractedXXX profile after retweeting Josh's post to… https://t.co/OBwsdmsE9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to act like you’re 5 and pretend to pick the rock’s nose. #hiking #getoutside https://t.co/sB4cu198Ag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnamacbabe @dutchingmarkets @markogorman06 @Boripa211 @ShoubikB @AshAsran @majer_brendan @JustSallx @asho_1973… https://t.co/yLpUmu2m2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t be happier that I get to say “I Love You” to my valentine, everyday 💋❤️🥰 #Married #Valentines… https://t.co/7wJNuXwwCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIY – Tennis Ball - Love this little guy #mirth #tee-hee #smile #jolly https://t.co/PbndLh6bBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G9AgUo2T9l   Well, here it is. The stupidest thing I 'heard' tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[tied to that it is still higher than Europe," Reinaud said.  Drugs account for only about 12 percent to 14 percent… https://t.co/KSeNhD88gU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCraig1959 Umm, in the words of Andre the Giant, I don’t think that tweet means what you think it means. She’s a hater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Hey look...Tomi Lauren's mouth is shaped just like Trump's....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to own 100% complete sets of all 3; took hours and hundreds of dollars and I had them all in order in a bind… https://t.co/i4UfNc5HWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[--. --- -.. / .. ... / -.. . .- -.. / .- -. -.. / .. / -.- .. .-.. .-.. . -.. / .... .. --]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it sick that I miss these priceless 1D silly moments no matter how painful they may seem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[due to personal reasons i will be spending the remainder of winter in a hot shower, goodbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zimmerman on FA:"Listen I'm not going to sit here and say its one sides fault, I think there's faults on both sides… https://t.co/1KSuQDghNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#babes . . . #catsofinstagram #catsoflosangeles #tabbiesofinstagram #tabbycatsofinstagram #losangeles… https://t.co/F4ejsiG1OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenehowell OMG!!! 😂😂😂😂 @thetiny_terror  our husband’s definitely should wear this for trial]]></document><document><![CDATA[okayyy buh am i the only who thinks its not shade towards Jordyn ? https://t.co/Z5uRIzqcv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare new music from da kid. Check that shit out 👇🏾🏎💨🔥😈  https://t.co/d6sodZXocK https://t.co/AQnLScW9Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worked last night on formatting images for a new set of cards - what do you think? This set of six or do I need to… https://t.co/EmJ9dtyUDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah pray for @11zelaznog_oteb tonight he is sleeping with his dogs outside 🤧🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalLoveYourPetDay this is my dog Ozzie! He’s the best dog ever and I think he’s the cutest! #mydogiscutest… https://t.co/RCTjbmPbYk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ILStatePolice I live in Woodstock Georgia! I probably can't pick up any donuts!😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid is as stupid does #forrestforrestgump #bubbagump #citywalkuniversal @ Bubba Gump Shrimp Co. https://t.co/kx3oAop4IS]]></document><document><![CDATA[. Proceso de Imaginación de Poder para #venezuela en espanol  . La imaginación tiene el poder, unida con la intenci… https://t.co/i9KpSQOBGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 11am a proposed @sdmts ballot measure would be paid for by half cent sales tax increase.  Full @CirculateSD repo… https://t.co/FaXzpMab8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House March 10,1-3 One of kind WILLINGBORO home. Added features unground pool, full size basketball court. @ W… https://t.co/RexB8JNyx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this week’s books! Stop by to pick up your tickets for the @Mana_Zine and get great deals if you come in… https://t.co/4PGyliv2PY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jordiew @soychicka @Alyssa_Milano While the law is being passed https://t.co/xA5bj4q8TI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading @jason's latest: "Why People Don’t Get Wealthy" https://t.co/Ln7IyOFBlu too busy have fun falling in Love ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot see spiritual things through secular eyes. - Rev. Dr. Harold R. Mayberry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Mellie looks so uninterested but I must say when she is not around him, she is a different person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobChristie11 Wow he cleared them out of the area! Yea, not to good of a idea to give a chimp a weapon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#The80sIn5Words Front 242: Headhunter (Official Video) https://t.co/hvIzISj232]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjulienauthor @the__himanish @jmsullivanbooks All of them. She owns a restaurant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜 Shirtless Saturday 💜⁣⁣⁣⁣⁣⁣⁣⁣⁣ ⁣⁣⁣ And the results are in....⁣ ⁣ 1/13/2019                1/28/19      2/27/19⁣ Wa… https://t.co/l7L2wILyy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASUSkip Would love to share some of our information with you, please reach out if you are able christine@hilinskishope.org]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is MOWO going to cancel tomorrow or am I going to get frostbite on my way to class?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fearlessmomma13 Love you!! Girl you inspire me and you ecouraged me so much when I became a mom at 20 yrs old. Tha… https://t.co/N9Q3TqCJwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy he leído y cocinado, leído y comido, leído y escuchado música, leído y leído más. Ahora trataré de dormir escuc… https://t.co/suXIC4R9zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing @ZacharyLevi in season 2 of @MaiselTV just made this a really great Monday! https://t.co/2CdDvY7UvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel You’ve been missed! Welcome back!!!!! Hope you enjoyed your much earning and deserved break 😍💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2Aaron @KPRC2 @SylvesterTurner @ArtAcevedo @KPRC2Mario @Esther188rod  AARON THAT IS JUST NOT RIGHT HE CAN NOT… https://t.co/3AKTl9zAdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite StoryCorps animations. Reminds me of Mrs. Meeks from Princeton, MO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely no Republicans should be voting for a measure to strike down Our President Trumps state of emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love getting demands for free ads thinly disguised as news pitches crafted in a way that demonstrates the person… https://t.co/ctBc17YIX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ar00ster @leon1961lee @thehill @IlhanMN Dude, America never stole or deleted anyone's culture hence there are dive… https://t.co/KNBIq8vY9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago police deny reports calling @JussieSmollett attack a 'hoax'  https://t.co/WDcrAW5tyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my math professor actually watches Yuri On Ice, I wont be able to go back to class. They all think I'm a hardass… https://t.co/xUWzm7KoF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy little #livingroom refresh. @ Arlington, Texas https://t.co/kgE61TMTG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone's having a bad day #tucson @ Tucson, Arizona https://t.co/VTcAUwUsvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d be cute too if I had a year round tan but unfortunate I’m an Irish fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBaines We appreciate you and can't wait to see! Gonna love you no doubt if these past two eps are anything to go by 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsWiricksClass @SalemSecond @SalemElementary THIS is what happens when curriculum experts collaborate to plan high… https://t.co/w9ktO6NL79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just writing names down who gon be next. Tired of mfs trynna play me 🤐 time running up]]></document></documents></author>