<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I need Mike Conley hyping up the crowd after the And-1 injected into my veins please 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh, I’m still in shock about Brody Stevens. I don’t think I saw any comic more than I saw him in my 20s when I liv… https://t.co/kZBMtlHEGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanillatary How are we supposed to accomplish the mission when all these ladies are taking time off for maternity… https://t.co/ObkHgGUIyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to say that there can’t be moments where the opinion is misinformed or misinterpreted by someone else, but the… https://t.co/Axw6kkhcA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonRamsay @breadstkitchen @heddonstkitchen So that is what diabetes in the physical form looks like]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chanute’s crowd showed up big time tonight! Proud of our community and appreciative of its support.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did Roland Emmerich intimidate everyone in this movie’s cast?! Why does everyone seem too scared to give a decent performance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McSassy57 @StephGrisham45 @KellyannePolls @ChrisCuomo Funny maybe you should check your hearing.  I watched interv… https://t.co/kSxSyV3Bnj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyCobb @BrianShortall @IthamarEnriquez @AndyCobb you’re still following me even after all the wrestling tweets?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slasher @joerogan @alexjonesshows (6% Comanche? his wild side?) on @joerogan talking reckless on Indigenous Peoples.  SMH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of my jackets go well with my button-up shirts and I've ended up freezing the last 2 weekends thinking i could… https://t.co/PSqvsAKYcV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in Hamilton, ON, Canada? https://t.co/13T524px42 #CommunityCare #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slicked9778 @TheBrandiRhodes Have u read the comments about sonny??? Horrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@worldsoccertalk What is that in real temperature? Asking for the rest of the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos @TigresOficial 🐯 #HoyGanamosTresPuntosMás https://t.co/WmnaSevgQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yaneekpage @JadenG_ChargeUp Just reading the story with a modicum of awareness would allow you to see that the headline is trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The emergency alert coming on during the Cohen testimony was strangely perfect timing. Thanks @CapRadioNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaLanier54 @liger57 @Debbie_Vesino @GatesRobin @RealJamesWoods @Dougs1978 @lloyd4man @Liberty_Belle04… https://t.co/USbQfWK8KQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Star ⭐️ Duncanville HS WR @OmgItsZeriah Put on a great 👍🏾 Showing @UAFootball Camp this weekend!!! He has been in… https://t.co/7of8DtoUzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnDoyle603 I want to know the same thing! They aren't even getting votes!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to check out the park. (@ Chair 3 - Tenderfoot in Vista, MT) https://t.co/7hPfmh45d7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took me forever to binge the last two seasons of The Vampire Diaries and HOLY TEARS..😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye West fucking around and playing Runaway on the MPC https://t.co/XvPTNgvn2s via @YouTube hardest shit I’ve ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @SouthsideSoda. Big things coming! #SanAntonio #SmallBusiness  #shoplocal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either that or on father's day @RubyRiottWWE wins mitb then wins the title]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKaurrrr lol I didn’t sleep. I’ve been googling. This was done in 2017 and no one has seen it till this week seemi… https://t.co/nPmSqnRYis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which essential oils help with the feeling of futility after almost a year of covering local governments and taxpayer defrauding schemes]]></document><document><![CDATA[#new #nj #nyc #park #dress #art #artshelp #photography #model #mua #work #life #yolo #travel #shoes #portfolio… https://t.co/TDqC2TM6Hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[NC Highway Patrol: Bus crash injures Student &amp; Bus driver. https://t.co/NO5NWB5PeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[*two seconds into Lyft* “So Mrs. Samantha what’s your MAJOR” Astor can you please — and I can’t stress this enough — shut the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got our ass beat tonight because we were overconfident. Confidence is great, but you better back it up with inte… https://t.co/riUCm5NpXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSCapitals @dmddusseau Great, but back to where we started at the beginning of the period...down by two goals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaron_watson @joshabbottband @stoneylarue @aaron_watson @joshabbottband and @stoneylarue Are you guys all ready fo… https://t.co/m0IxLTJHhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the homie @florenciagalvan for bringing the good vibes tonight 🙌🏼 much needed after midterms. Honorary… https://t.co/7MgHb0jo2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[After being hit on the head in the ninth inning Saturday, Nick Solak had jokes for us this morning.  He went throug… https://t.co/yk9lYEW6SJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErikOnSax @fakecarlsagan @ShySmurf There are a lot of dishonest people everywhere in politics. I don’t advocate fo… https://t.co/EuALUzBOiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digitaldraco We met because she went horseback riding with my mom. Many years later we tried friends with benefits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahSpain I'm not sure why you waste your time with these people. This is how they get attention. A picture has c… https://t.co/0fwZIsTore]]></document><document><![CDATA[@webtilton @HoustonDynamo Hahaha we will be twinning. They have namesets there, let me know if you’ll be around to… https://t.co/2T32gFb7GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeroll4life Two bad contracts. Did you show this friend your World Series commemorative ring?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very opportunistic of the #MeToo activists to highlight this now, and not when the “movement” was created. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 Rule in photography- Enjoy it. Don't do it because you need it for a class for school. Do fit because you LOVE I… https://t.co/ifZrHmjalq]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a cool, foggy morning here on Cumberland Island. Perfect time to get outside and watch nature do its thing! I… https://t.co/ndpxnibGCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚾️OHSAA BASEBALL UMPIRE CLASS February 26-March 20 Fee - $135 Age requirement is 14 years old and up. Contact Ron Goleman (419)-513-0439.]]></document><document><![CDATA[💯 percent agree - facilities based competition makes zero sense with modern networks - no one needs multiple fiber… https://t.co/oZhvU3EftI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam Conover probes deeper than a cordyceps in Mind Parasites Live. @ Park West https://t.co/HsuhxtCabS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShiriSpear can you please tell those driving a 4x4 doesn't mean they can drive faster than everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@busysowingseeds The linked-to story was published on Jan. 20, 2017, more than 2 years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you need a Realtor in Miami? Contact in my bio. . . 👉🏻@MauricioTorres1  👉🏻@MauricioTorres1  . . #Argentina… https://t.co/NZX1G1Sm4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel was an absolute blast... if your a Marvel movie fan make sure to stay for both post credit scenes. https://t.co/mW0q0Xmqtn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john_folder @AaronCuddeback Sounds like a plan! Good luck! https://t.co/uPCdZ0fbWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conflicted about Jonas brothers album.. yeah it’s amazing but these are the same dudes that used to get to me with… https://t.co/Hgskxhyia4]]></document><document><![CDATA[In just 4 hours I will be preaching the final dedication message of our 2019 @WOLSnowcamp. I’m going to ask the que… https://t.co/g5hbk9Pg9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tinderoni Tip: Get chocolate at Walgreens 2 for price of 1 today https://t.co/73vMQicPDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is dope. It'll be better if there was like....an Asian in this pic. Or another diff colored woman. But still d… https://t.co/tdLFReZdw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I lost the girl of my dreams and I realized it the moment it happened. I could have asked for a second chance. We p… https://t.co/w9HzfIhuth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saikatc Maybe, but remember, "Constitutional Conservatives" tell us that the 14th Amendment doesn't mean what it says!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goofy ass hoe , iono why you niggas think it’s cool to let bitches play with the ratchet ain’t no fuccin toy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Don_Vito_08 @gaye_gallops @realDonaldTrump Four anti American people that somehow got elected to Congress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennesseine @KAMALAMODE @BernieSanders I love Bernie and I would never say anything like that to someone who disag… https://t.co/TgFMYXGEKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is everyone always sleep at night lol. It’s barley 4 am twitter too dead, someone wake up I’m bored haha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @CoryFroomkin Cooper the Great dane watching you this morning #WakeMeUp https://t.co/SPYcLXf31S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveLittleBigM @eedoogie @JessicaOtten1 I invested a good amount tonight! Went 4/5 in pick 5...missed bomb in firs… https://t.co/ttrFmmGGVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys like Bregman are what we need in baseball. Be approachable. Small interactions make kids day. Hell, I talked t… https://t.co/ySjGBrQOAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonCheadle Hard to demand respect when your hat broadcasts that you're really stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot date? Really? By God, if she wants a REALLY hot date… . Anyway, Congress IS coming!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esmedrodriguez @elabuelitosv @ElPulgoso_Sv @Eternal_Y @Vulcano91658391 @whatthefuck_sv @ea_valladares… https://t.co/aslVqixYjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed. Sorry for #Gio that he couldn’t stay, but the can’t bend the rules at will.  Hopefully the league loosens t… https://t.co/NFXAvNxURc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dog47Sam @LisaMei62 On phones? Forever? That is the sentence.  About fake news. Its in ya schools, not on the news… https://t.co/txAccX4ax4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkdikes832 @BallGame723 @fibonacci1123 @_mrfo20 @Raphy_Taffy I need a freak on site , I GOT ICE ON ICE ON ICE ON I… https://t.co/sVQRh3YULD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew there was a new $6B market for efficient horizontal lighting. Smart niche.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say it ain’t snow! #weatheralert for Friday morning!  #snow chances have increased. The top-left image is the… https://t.co/d9XMwHaUMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoveIsActuallyA I kick right in the Ol Ball sack. 😳🤦🏽‍♂️😆😆 https://t.co/q7FC0UNBeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#coppermountain #skiing #guystrip @ Copper Mountain https://t.co/MK20QPgdTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I searched Serge Ibaka choke and it was nothing, but thirsty thots asking to be choked by Serge Ibaka. 💀 #NBATwitter⁠ ⁠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoyalToSpeakOut @3lls3s @theamericancrow @LesMaga @onuj_juno @AnnieOne61 @andranitesh1 they dont have the answer 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cohen convicted for saying efforts to build a Trump tower in Moscow ended in Jan. 2016, when in fa… https://t.co/gi3Iz5euVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peteholmes @JuddApatow I loved this show and identified with your portrayal of a man of faith navigating the world… https://t.co/D0FK9emRqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cupcake_meg I'm sorry. Idk if I can help, but message me if you feel you need to talk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to the painful realization of of why the @SouthwestAir 7:30 flights outta BNA are so cheap! @KZKX969 https://t.co/7nacAiMAtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand The wall is for the people. Democrats are only concerned with selfish ambition and care nothing for… https://t.co/xk9RR0Aqga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctorwes @LeahHoustonMD Someone has to do it? How would the public know who is qualified to place a stent in thei… https://t.co/kDVbwfdk53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @Advil @jbillinson How have I lived this long not knowing what a bath sheet is? Mind blown. I will be… https://t.co/scaEm5wplP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UrinatingTree ... One down, one to go. Machado to San Diego, Harper (probably, maybe) to Philly. Think there's goi… https://t.co/w5um3KFn8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[And just like that, Sheldon has sworn in its first female officer.  Reserve officer Krista Bousema is 23 and a 2014… https://t.co/N7ClcGTPKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markrlambie #MachineLearning like other forms of #AI are tools that can be used to accomplish certain tasks. If yo… https://t.co/9cGDCiTd64]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIFT OFF!!!!!  Oh my Lord 😭😭😭  That choir did Beyonce justice. Take me to church! Please!!! Watch The Throne is an… https://t.co/IJpNf7K1NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianmctaggart @kidkeuchy is a class act. Love that he is out with these guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday morning with Frank #sinatraatthesands @ Spring, Texas https://t.co/Eg15uT2qeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to introduce you to Chino. Exciting things are happening...stay tuned...  #newmusic #newproject… https://t.co/NwrRxEuA8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas stay away from them crazy bitches, theirs something wrong with them 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 7:00 AM CST, 2 N Dodge City [Ford Co, KS] COCORAHS reports SNOW of 4.70 INCH https://t.co/pPq2chyiUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We used to do this shit during class, put our books facing up so we wouldn’t get caught. Had the homie next to me w… https://t.co/q2yRXP5xBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yummy. Nice hop juiciness - Drinking an 3500 by @TheVeilBrewing @ Cloverton Brewery Company  — https://t.co/qNBDpSFt96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XenosPetros He ran them too hard early in the season, I said it several times. They look a little goosed atm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnrobertsFox @DNC @FoxNews So basically there will be zero viewers of these debates?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this what what America wanted when they voted for Trump particularly white seniors and those in the working-clas… https://t.co/aqqx0DY5Nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkDorr @Oldguard12 Is this a pic from that one that went flying down the highway?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Maintain the Momentum of a Positive Life Change | Oprah's Life Yo... https://t.co/tLJVmjScSX via @YouTube… https://t.co/36ZRTeMxjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pa #pennsylvania #igersoftheday #iger #igers #igeroftheday #picoftheday #photooftheday #pictureoftheday… https://t.co/O1yFYiFHq7]]></document></documents></author>