<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@markohalloran Was going to send you a video of friends and myself dancing under a tree like stray wasps to I’m Com… https://t.co/KRtjgxkZ1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DOJ and virtually every government institution is ignoring the domestic terrorist #ChristopherHasson. Why? https://t.co/1Z3U9N3ZTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only seen the younger lady smile once and that’s cause my son was being a clown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how the dr at school thought I was a freshman☺️☺️lol im outta here in a few months dr 🏃‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[We forget too quickly that plagues wiped out land, crops and killed many people. The @GlobalLocust initiative track… https://t.co/KXXdaIptJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asmodaeus666 @tatclouthier ¿De dónde sacarán tanto dinero para premiar a los ninis con programas especiales?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yaaaaaaaaaas!!!!!! I literally just stood up and cheered SOOOOOO fucking loud for Olivia Coleman. She deserved this… https://t.co/WzlvtnybdE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to read a compelling book by a woman that makes you think what the world COULD be like, try The Power b… https://t.co/sZEVXBhNqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bit of comedy for you. #humor #snicker #smirk #jolly https://t.co/UdYtA14i1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misterwashburn @irvspanish @OnEducationPod @Gameboydrew @korytellers @mr_isaacs I’ll save seats at the keynote...o… https://t.co/qDGNkHuNDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Manhattan Beach, California https://t.co/q0kerNaC0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is really exciting. What do you think this means for Canadian content production? #CRI820]]></document><document><![CDATA[🍩 shots this A.M!! 🤩  • Controls hunger • Feel Fuller longer • Shrinks fat cells • Lose inches** (in as little as 7… https://t.co/Iqu8YUxoMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[You, Schumer, have been peddling that hog wash for years. The super wealthy oligarchs that keep you in office are a… https://t.co/7AsFDIQNza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best advice I’ve received in school thus far: Do not tell people you believe in climate change. Tell people you kno… https://t.co/dzPjpTriUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Mile High Spirits Distillery and Tasting Bar https://t.co/UHrCWBArZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight hundreds of women at our church will worship God with their whole hearts, draw near one another through pra… https://t.co/1KEvkk6J0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedavidcook Got a new song for you. Love it    … Sucker Punch by Sigrid https://t.co/ZogF5olwN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[fuck bc pills .. I’m bout to live off faith cause them mfs got me bipolar 😭 .. I’m ready to go back to the shots hell im mad 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatyMoeller @IdahoStatesman Now he needs to be behind bars!!!!!! ( Should have been before)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Piano lesson (@ UT Butler School of Music in Austin, TX) https://t.co/2KSxVmgWFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeinzKetchup_US I've never thought of or heard of mixing mayo with mustard ewww]]></document><document><![CDATA[DHS Nielsen: ‘Open Borders Have Failed the American People’ https://t.co/VT4v4y5vbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Smile #BossUp #HandleIt #GodsPlan #ThursdayThoughts #ThursdayMotivation https://t.co/Mmn489ACPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseyBurris @sightabby I literally took a screenshot of this like 20 minutes ago with the intention of sending i… https://t.co/Zaz5uf6tKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary @JenniferLWelch @JenniferLayneBr @drdanadwells https://t.co/HSxMorkaLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have fun in prison R. Kelly. Karma has itS way of coming. Not only did a documentary come out exploiting his whole… https://t.co/iEbf67pWH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Building automaticity in Multiplication can be fun! Thanks @gregtangmath #iginspires @ColleenEngle https://t.co/VgHsewiq73]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using a $5 point and shoot film camera and throwing on a #35mm hashtag to make yourself seem artsy and cool isn’t a personality trait]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart breaks a little whenever I see Nick and remember I can’t marry him anymore🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein The thing is: the policy priorities you attribute here to the "far left" are really those of any of u… https://t.co/f3ORwrFYv6]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES! Dopest album thus far saintrecords #solange #whenigethome @ Logan Square, Chicago https://t.co/8raBNh3BKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening 2 @MickeyGuyton on @pandoramusic better than you left me (live)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to present at @inVIVO_Planet conference in the same session as @DrDavidKatz, @jc_moubarac, and others.… https://t.co/PfrUhWrti4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo wtf. How can you remove a channel from existence because @DisneyChannel you have failed miserably.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allontheline @tasolomon6  @CherylHaase @warriorwoman64 @DorothyWilkerson @Deb4CongressNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need someone to come fix my heat 🤣 I was messing and unscrewed the wires now my heat won’t come back on]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your team puts passion into action...😍 #poweringpotential #curriculum #edleadership #ikigai https://t.co/Jn4ikQ11K2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekapman @ESPN1000 Not defending the sox but I'm sure the Cubs side of town is loving the distraction from its ra… https://t.co/0JGWjyuDtN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retired nurse here -warning watch for blood clots- the more active you were -then not being able to be active the m… https://t.co/haRVUSBhwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWhitehouse @eilperin @EPA Swampy Administration. No depths are too low.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why in God’s name is the PRESS paying so much attention to AOC ,,she hasn’t passed One Bill !!all her ideas are rid… https://t.co/rMW7qtc374]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leveling up my #ootd #outfitsoftracydizon at @lroynew ’s @lroynew Exhibit Opening at the https://t.co/DDX55x58MV we… https://t.co/SCjh924sws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Positive_Who All of the "Winter" ep of Circular Time by @Paul_Cornell is just haunting: what's going though Five's… https://t.co/Q7yHGDqrcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@globalnews @NANComms Just hope he resigns. I don’t want to hear his sorry not sorry 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Formosa leave me alone and stop using this crusty ass pic of me I quit like a year ago https://t.co/Yu4MiRmsnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NadineAstrakhan i guess “exciting at work” means “ur gonna mess up and get yelled at 😜” https://t.co/t69xEYrmWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alec's strained voice when he said "i didn't know this was supposed to be a competition" and magnus rolling into fr… https://t.co/4aro1prCUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Manoli_Canoli Oh my god i thought it was pumpkin pie. It’s time y’all!! See you next life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did @realDonaldTrump have someone pay Ms. Daniels a little cash to be quiet? Who really knows. Did @HillaryClinton… https://t.co/0tx48Ht3Hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThankYou to all who care enough about #humanity , about #freedom , about #Venezuela #FueraMaduro #EnoughIsEnough… https://t.co/68eobmWaR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to wish my dear friend Deana Hart a Happy Birthday!!Have a good Day!🎈🎁🎂 #yourgettingold!! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I charge $50. And look how big my following is....@rachelz971 @tonycolombo971]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was just something he thought would cause trouble for Trump supporters.  https://t.co/deMTZ03SLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year I got flowers from two people on valentines 😩🤣 y este ano las cosas se ven difíciles]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE CONCIERGE MODEL  Proactive wellness and personalized care is the priority within the Concierge Model of healthc… https://t.co/LAJfcWWI2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roberts19681 If he was smart he would be in Vegas working as an Elvis impersonator, what better cover up than that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[something about ur s/o dedicating a song to u&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koolkat6193 @OIQFC @DrBrianMay @BoRhapMovie @QueenWillRock Ok, now I don’t feel so bad only seeing it 12 times in… https://t.co/Rb3y8UyJjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialDOGNews @Derm_girl98 Yayyyyy #DogWGNA #DogsMostWanted #Welcomebackguys we are all so excited...God Bless y… https://t.co/Q1YwoJJoZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glock 43X Giveaway! Enter to Win a NEW Glock 43X (PX435SL201) from https://t.co/SYgd9dWsOB! https://t.co/GyHKibN9w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a baby is born alive, doesn't he/she have AUTOMATIC entitlement as a human being to life saving measures?  If a … https://t.co/wk0TcihfIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Powerful Warning - Lest We Forget The Message by David Wilkerson https://t.co/FycreA74Pl via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Arkansas lost its largest commercial bee operation because of dicamba use.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy tickets from the theatre kids for Dessert and Drama!¡!¡ t h i s  f r i d a y 🧁🎭🍪🎶 @ Vestavia Hills High School https://t.co/BFiylm52zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year, different times, different teams, same place, mostly the same people! 😉  OKLAHOMA STATE HIGH SCHOOL BAS… https://t.co/iV93R8iBsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BYOS ...bring your own stuff too  Hey Blooming Soul ...  #visionboard with me this weekend... let's #manifest our… https://t.co/7ZoNNU8WcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TC_in_TDot @anxiousmhe @NorbertElekes For sure. Inclusion is important for so many reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i went sledding. i went off a big jump. i don’t really know why i did it but my neighbor dared me so like i had to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenStabenow @SenGaryPeters We have 12 years to stop climate change and solutions are ready to go. Will you suppor… https://t.co/Fnr1y6Rj31]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be creating a few twitter polls for some of mine and @Teaching4Him16’s students to collect data for their pe… https://t.co/d33MiAuK2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Stop bandwagoning you dumbass. You did the same with those Covington Catholic kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing from @MayorOfLA about importance of gender equity on #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/V1hxbyEzgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free play Wednesday. All games = $0. Do attend. @ Lorraine https://t.co/cWFXW2SZ7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crecer siempre duele... Ya está bueno el bracito pa'hacer tortillas de harina 😎👊🤣 en 7iete6eis Fitness https://t.co/0HIHuXNDyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrappnfan @welliver_titus @BoschAmazon @Connellybooks @FanFestNews Fantastic interview! So great he recognized yo… https://t.co/eaA32ZOqQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[just thought about how a few days ago I was spilling tea to @cassiemelendrez and her consistent issue with the pers… https://t.co/bnXSLjmGIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Law Code of Gortyn shows us that money was valued in society at this time. It is the largest preserved document… https://t.co/VKOytbAgVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olgaNYC1211 @stevendupler I actually know Lenny and for an attorney he’s a good guy. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Handsewn Custom Made/ Color #HairbyEdie @ Palmdale, California https://t.co/qOhgVWaalW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#zuccfanforlife @MadisonScrocca so sad about zucc leaving.  #alwaysaranger]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma be Special Guest for @jozalynsharp 's #FilthFactory This Saturday at @LAComedyClub inside @stratvegas. This Sh… https://t.co/6uIvgg1ICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true have you seen th RS I thought they would actually cover the newest music?? @JudicialWatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy three months cheeks! We are fashionably late yet again, Miss Emma Hilleary, with your monthly picture thanks… https://t.co/OUGSLDkM13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @AlanBakerPhoto who brings the camera skills &amp; creativity every week! You da 💣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bwilmes @bittman @ryanMarthur The top benefit of long and cold midwestern winters-getting to use the outdoors as a refrigerator/freezer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm 150:6 KJV Let every thing that hath breath praise the Lord . Praise ye the Lord . GOOD MORNING  #HALLELUJAH #HALLELUJAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just feeling feelings ALL over @them with this one: https://t.co/ibecTWeunv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeChaseNme Some expect u to pay all the bills while they just chill and watch Netflix all day 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willripleyCNN What are the odds Kim watched or was briefed on Cohen’s testimony &amp; tried to gain the upper hand with Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredTJoseph I’m sorry that happened to you.  You were the better person, but that kind of winning rings hollow aft… https://t.co/znj2roNbwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordynwoods is really a savage. She said fu*k Khloe, Kylie, and True. Smh🤦🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[because im like to suffer i read side effects for the medication i have to take and i came across this https://t.co/xL52XvqDn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really sad and scary :( When it’s cold out, stray cats will crawl up inside cars to stay warm. Please alway… https://t.co/nQgenOavzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today at the Mid-Atlantic Flute Convention: at 3pm Trilovati Flute Choir performs my comp "Chivy" and at 3:15 Beta… https://t.co/Q0sQAg0Ogk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think anyone writes his chats,he wings it,I thought Presidents had a fact research er and editor,because he… https://t.co/nnhTq1t6Iw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m tired of y’all saying “but u never hmu” yes I do bitch. even if I don’t communication is a two-way street. putt… https://t.co/icjuWraV66]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoongi!! 🎉🎊🎂 A live broadcast is now showing on V. https://t.co/J2UMTS9aeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicole_bertrand @DetroitLove88 @Steelerschic85 @ltinsley1209 @sassyteapot63 @sueseashell @DemTeaParty2020… https://t.co/q8o8x6TO8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@collision I don’t know about you, but I just trust graphs that look like 1980s-era graphs more.]]></document></documents></author>