<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Hey @greglovesmovies - is The Wandering Earth optimized for Dolby Atmos? Considering seeing it tonight at Marcus Point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rinconderufo Aun recuerdo sus sentidas palabras al descender Tigres Dios bendiga a todos los q hicieron Daño a Tig… https://t.co/oCG9pFV94s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmorton142 I built one. With autopilot and everything it’s still 50k lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Im proud of you Pleb. Making big moves. Anthony is proud of you ♡♡♡♡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lightning &amp; thunder with the 4 inches of snow here in Powell.... @joelrileywtvn  More snow falling... https://t.co/KawaZseoiz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celso_guarei @Newsweek Is there any belief that cannot be justified by faith?   "I have faith that Muhammed is the… https://t.co/wScT5s52u3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmiller16 @CBCHighSchool Awesome! We gotta do something about their sponsor tho. 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1Mubu just seen it lmao 😂 miss ya too fam!! We gotta link when you comeback I’A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chewcoffeedip @FarOutFoodz @Lizardkingfish @1MonsterMission @BHOAdventures @unhsmitty90 @AverageHunter… https://t.co/DcSuIBWcV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw @Cirque du Soleil “Crystal” (on ice) with my lovely wife yesterday! It was SPECTACULAR! https://t.co/jvGDzjxbfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I learned some new things from @amlehr yesterday: there is a cookbook of recipes that use semen as a main ingredien… https://t.co/dAUHHJA7C2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hatsfree @SenFeinstein I thought all babies were born alive? Or do you still carry them to term if they die in the womb?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shea_lsm @jay_ashree @IsfahanMerali If you want diversity of thought, experience and skill, you don't get it through elections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psalm 139:14   "I praise you, for I am fearfully and wonderfully made. Wonderful are your works; my soul knows it very well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reaching people is not just getting them to church. It is spending time with them.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌎​​📍​#BangRevoltuionWorldTour checking in from Columbus, OH at the #ASF2019‼️ We have already "taken over" and if y… https://t.co/04GFm8CeMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatholicSat @ccpecknold ...and we should not simply forget now that it is over. Many questions remain. Powerful pr… https://t.co/rWyJNV6XTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome party when you arrive in Miami to visit your son on his boat. @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/N5V28jFy3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Great. You get the girl and I get the coroner.”  If there were ever a case of foreshadowing in a film ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was never handed anything. When you see me grind it's for me not someone else's pockets #teamjoker @ Lewisville, Te… https://t.co/vXEcLk7R9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiaraReneee @mynamejunebug Catch yo ass in the back shoot up your fe-fe dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The GOP members refer to CIRCUS....They are right but its the POTUS THAT IS THE CIRCUS ! @CNN @MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest "Naval History" came today, and I can already tell this is going to be a great issue...… https://t.co/yaMtzSCAGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work at @Salesforce, named one of the #WorldsMostEthicalCompanies by @Ethisphere. https://t.co/1X4qHnrr4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched John Delaney for 5 minutes and already can’t stand how many times he says, “right”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptKarnstein @zoidberg95 @Barry_Cinematic @HolmesBooth @tangoineden @mjpcuervo @ernie_fink I'm tearing up just thinking about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemoseAries @HumanistReport @SenFeinstein Uh huh.  https://t.co/WFhmVrS59p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Exacto17 @Samy12111975 @nayibbukele Dalton perteneció a la guerra Fría a lo q uds ya cerraron el 3 de Febrero vean… https://t.co/vsgnZHGVyD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came to this bar. I guess some dudes are performing. GAYEST SHIT EVER Lmaoo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Al_Hine When I wasn't driving - or trying to focus on navigating around Phoenix!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flako023sb @DonTical_Futbol @thestraygoat If it was in el Jalisco all hell would’ve broke loose by now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeMc945 My prediction, they will use the strongest possible terms to McCabe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PakistanArmyZindabad remember that if these 2 countries go at it, both with nuclear weapons, it’s hasta la vista b… https://t.co/pWlQxe7q7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @KamalaHarris And all those attempts by congress to pass it congress was controlled by Democrats so look… https://t.co/zBBMkjPHxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching episode 533 of One Piece. #onepiecesailson https://t.co/QzYaOCthrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update! I’m now doing digital outreach for team @ewarren in Nevada! Let’s win this! #dreambigfighthard #winwithwarren #presist]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to support @keishawill_ for her big night on thelaunchctv  . Live music ... Jack Daniel’s ... fingers cros… https://t.co/ZZKD6ivkrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg! Braun, just  caught that staples  chair like it was nothing!,.... tell me @WWE why is he Jobbing to a balding… https://t.co/Ww4OotQIkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachAdamGaylor 12,13, 22, 23...brings back some good memories, eh @coach_mattox  and @coachharrah ? #pact #1RtNasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Clyde_Chambliss for your leadership and doing your part to make sure our great state will continue to pr… https://t.co/hX4e5htG7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see a lot of this in political campaigns. Digital-first world moves quickly and in-house can often be faster, c… https://t.co/gWbGPsslAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@salmon71 @Escobedolara @Cicmty @retioMTY @_taxista_regio_ En ambos sentidos camarada https://t.co/eJVm8OX3uw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I unplug my phone and plug in my iPad when I mean to put my headphones on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally feel like it’s time to go back to dancing and in the studio like I use to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what the over/under is on Chris Wallace joining the new Jonah Goldberg NeverTrump network?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wlcprez Thank you President Johnson. Trying to spread as much positivity and joy as I can ♿️🍞 God is great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanBenefield @phillydotcom @jbaernews Corrupt unions, corrupt Dems, what else is new?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HockeyBtch2 Like chocolate and water, but throw in some cheese, it's on https://t.co/y9I82tuxiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cecilcounty #drinklocal #MDcraftbeer - Drinking an Elk River ESB by Mahogany Ridge Brewery @ Elk River Brewing Com… https://t.co/uG0dRcu5dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBoyVol Should've stopped by ole Crossville since you were in the area]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jalalapeno "I'm telling you, those Vikings should've kept Keenum instead, he's a better qb than Cousins....." Not… https://t.co/J7lpBH4k5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greeters by most accounts have been the light's that light up an otherwise bad or just eh day so @Walmart needs to… https://t.co/fH2nrX61YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDCCD @sdut @LorenaAD80 @SDMesaPrez @Baxamusa @GaryWarthUT What CA Bill is about including funds for housing for C… https://t.co/IRNNf4G8MV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KorovaMilkBar #AClockworkOrange #ClockworkOrange #NYFW #NewYorkFashionWeek #Fashion  #FashionWeek #NewYorkCity… https://t.co/7Sy3axQSur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really fun day serving the Charlotte crowd all the amazing @slingshotcoffee things at pourcoffeefest !  Thanks agai… https://t.co/qe8zZLMT5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for the Texas Top Guns being in @WestwoodISD today!! Great group of men that portray the history of Tex… https://t.co/iPqdhK20wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[71 degrees here compared to 6 degrees back in Milwaukee... Houston we do not have a problem!]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/LmAQlC0Ait]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my septum pierced and I'm waiting to pick up the nephew's at school. @ Checotah Intermediate https://t.co/vEI9z9npJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Robert25843149 @jayfonsecapr Te tengo noticias todos son lo mismo. Por que la corrupción solo se cambia la camisa cada 4 años]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need people like Dillon so you can point your fucking fingers and say thass the bad guy !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only a few free packages left!! The first 10 people to pre-order a watch from my website get a FREE care package fr… https://t.co/tEsswI9ci5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We will NEVER be a SOCIALIST COUNTRY! We were born FREE and WE will die FREE! Make your move Democrats!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an American Beauty by @dogfishbeer at @walters303 — https://t.co/Dg8GH8J1G7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldnt finish it. Its VERY dramatic. But this is like Power for Old People lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Presidents’ Day homie🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾💯💯💯✌️✌️✌️👍🏾👍🏾👍🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾🦀🦀🦀 @ The Obama White House https://t.co/z8pkTu26sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosGalvez21 @CarlosVictorM (1)Q opinan d este escenario?BSC-FEF procesan lo necesario n el caso Perez.Lo envían… https://t.co/04jIy0oKQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My uber driver lowered the window when I got in I just know I’m booming 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the way, step inside... #badlobby #scarylobby #thedoormanwillhandyouyourcoat #interiors… https://t.co/ZZnwJqD3wC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/FJu1FILYyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Q_fortheWIN @ROOFHOU @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Trump has committed so many crimes. Stiffing small contractors has go… https://t.co/Fz2WUcJwh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 draft for #NYR 2 first rounders, 3 second rounders (with potential to move higher). This is respecting the pro… https://t.co/uuGsosuwIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmokeyStafford @bdlefan @CBSThisMorning @60Minutes @ScottPelley Bots just wanna have fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unreal. Around here you could get a house, a second home, and an office for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnArtist99 Do me the honor of attending a Cubs game sometime this season with me, @MarjMellow, @DrakeIkeman, and… https://t.co/O0gm14s7ax]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump fake book.  real testimony.  Easy to read.  like this.  fake president.  real crimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing glasses will help me reach my life goal of eliminating all eye contact forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from the Tacoma Dome! @KamiakinBraves girls in action taking on Snohomish in the 3A tourney quarterfin… https://t.co/UREHVqQPUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day.......from everyone except us teachers who have to deal with Valentines parties, and candy, an… https://t.co/hmAAXnjNaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruCelt @GKeile @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump I think she meant ‘Lyin’ Omar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chugging almond milk from the carton doesn’t feel nearly as thirst quenching or rebellious as drinking real milk from the jug]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricGuillot14 As long as you got your asbestos drawers you gonna make it baby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSCAR_IM @KarlaRiveraMX Si le dan botas, flores y demás creo que se puede, sea o no sea real AMLO muestra su indiferencia ante el caso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the ADI for using our Kentucky content! Covering the Cats from one part of the state to the other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago 8.2018 - 1  Very happy to say that I finished editing my birthday trip to Chicago last summer. An overnight… https://t.co/NSFIiSdDnr]]></document><document><![CDATA[So fuckin true, he explains this so well. Hate when couples say they have to meet each other’s needs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As winter comes in like a lion in March oh, I dream of it going away like a lamb.. a little Summer wind! https://t.co/5lqCY5uKFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta be a different type of hater if you don’t like post Malone js]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure @veelarco of NEA the only Latina senior financial advisor at any of the 73 biggest venture capital firm… https://t.co/oY0KIOH01m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #WakeCounty on I-40 EB at Hwy 1 - Exit 293 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday  Back in 2008 @markmartin got his 48th and Jr Motorsports their 1st win in the @NASCAR_Xfinity Ser… https://t.co/NlaZ8Xdp1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @AOC @ewarren @CoryBooker you can give free shit to everyone in America https://t.co/IJCHf2zhWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @realDonaldTrump Not a coup. The 25th Amendment. Trump is a dangerous man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPLennon Well, first off the piece doesn’t mention Keuchel at all I’d love to see him asked why Paxton was enough… https://t.co/om4Zwu4y5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[6am getting cancelled tomorrow has to be the turning point in this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the Raiders’ seventh game to their 16th game Carr had 12 touchdowns, no interceptions and a 101.4 passer ratin… https://t.co/CzZgedKNj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @CodesTrump @Jeanleonetti1 @CommonCause @joncoopertweets @wikileaks @Snowden @RIPsethRich @FBI @DNC… https://t.co/mGXWGycTek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsErikMertens @BenMcEnderfer Haha Erik. 99 days until we get to see hotdogs all summer at the field]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Went to Vietnam, and Michael Cohen Made It Hell https://t.co/tmbS3b97yW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSB_BUNZZ we gon have to agree to disagree then buddy https://t.co/102Gis1MKj]]></document></documents></author>