<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My 5-year-old nephew Edward created a new superhero for me. Behold Tigerman! https://t.co/3G64uAWsc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Raleigh company says it got something it didn't expect when it bought a foreclosed property from BofA - a disgrun… https://t.co/pqomxw5OrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing other women settle for less than they deserve is heartbreaking 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be the first to see the custom reveal! On Instagram: ikb20_customs Shhhhhh 👣👣 🔥🔥 #goHeels https://t.co/OYvIfIdOZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOberg @NormanBuffong No living being belongs in a #factoryfarm. Go vegetarian if your can't afford animals rai… https://t.co/bGjMVCuYUW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday 😊😊😊 I am celebrating me today!! @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/r1hxUClyla]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jay76wd2 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Malanias just money whipped, with her looks she had better stay where s… https://t.co/sMasZ4OTzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drunk me thinking: hey what’s @m_garcia8 doing!!!  Him: likes tweet  Me : omg this mother fucking mine reader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating change. Showing up. Being present. #socialjustice #untiltheycomedown… https://t.co/ur98EF5ubj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Week I Was Laying In the Room Knocked, Sis Came In &amp; Said U Sleep With The Light On 🤣🤣..I Was Deady No Capp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He already won when you gave him wanted he wanted most : legitimacy. This isn’t a joke or reality… https://t.co/1dZRImkaFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m damn near 50k tweets   signing off  I also have had my twitter since I first became a jb stan so like almost 10… https://t.co/GFv7u10zFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream that over $1000 was deposited in my bank account. I woke up and it wasn’t a dream💜💜💜💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've watched Carl and his forecasts since I was 7-years-old. And I am now 34 and still watched😊 What a phenomenal c… https://t.co/qG5yHxZvfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the real tho, what a great start to #InternationalWomensDay !! WOMEN EMPOWERING WOMEN!!!!! #CapitanaMarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the work of art @ricekrispies a 7th grader made in FCS today 😳 I told him I had to tweet it out- it was a… https://t.co/Un4G816zDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[as soon as i get a quality cast iron skillet &amp; new knives it’s OVER for you other instagram chefs👩🏼‍🍳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wait_What_How Maps is wrong. I clocked it at nine tenths of a mile. 🤬 https://t.co/yL8DutPleC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guest speaker at my Leadership training sounded just like @jennyslate, took a while to stop picture a mature Mona Lisa Saperstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a woman sucks while trying to lose weight. My god damn period is craving a KitKat. That bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarpeoDesiree @Glenda68336051 @feebs1907 Well, SOMEBODY can't read a calendar!! Eh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibrake4ants @carolecadwalla bahahhahh Mercer.. this is the easy part.. let me find some tidbits.. we don't need no… https://t.co/RHctaAXTRg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool old gas station in Disney Hollywood Studios !! 💜✨ . . . .  #aerosmithrollercoaster #aerosmith #disneystudios… https://t.co/sgTTbz5hF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t gone to a class the last two times, turns out I have an exam today. This is the life]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my beautiful girls @payton__marie34 @reagan_cariato and Brooklyn...Happy Valentine's Day. I ❤you 3 more than you… https://t.co/vI2I1bW7jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wheninrome #exceptitscanada #lordstanley #hockeyhalloffametoronto #lifeofsales @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/3TWB8ydpLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually updated my Web site today. Nine months later and I'm finally crawling out of the baby hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes to this!! the same goes for voice teachers: cross pollination, not gurus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KThompsonTV Chileeee 😂 she came up to me and had her own call letters for her news station at home. I just couldn’t resist 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBowman88 @WilliamByron @nationwide88 @TeamHendrick @AxaltaRacing @TeamChevy 😃😃😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[SABADOS DE RUMBA EN NUESTRA SEGUNDA CASA MI ROMANCE LUCHO BARRIOS  CON LA MORENA K CANTA Y ENCANTA ALLA NOS VEMOSSS… https://t.co/nX28fR02nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkylarJameson1 @VitalVegas It's because their muscles are relaxed, they don't tense up as they're falling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last episode of @NBCThisisUs was really good but who’s shocked??? Not me https://t.co/Z3DXuLrxFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissaisloved It’s going to be ok look at my most recent tweet it helps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryBonoUSA He was a wonderful man and the people in Rockwall, Texas will truly miss him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trinitygossett Trinity have you heard anything about a family https://t.co/ITMdD7wfVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe in yourself!  #justdoit #focus #neverstoplearning #yougotthis #believe  #knowyourworth #leadershiptraining… https://t.co/kOkrqmOOoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life turns your dreams to dust, go vacuum! #NeverGiveUp #Resilience #Grit #Determination #persistence #Bounce… https://t.co/YNrxIHqUwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcoley1 @BonnieLatino @profstan72 Good man‼️ We usually stay at a Hilton Garden Inn if possible. I haven’t been di… https://t.co/qaHyPT8bsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister sent me the singing acapella dudes for Valentine’s day and they came BANGING at my door at 6:50 IN THE MORNING]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #moon is too bright to get an accurate photo with my phone. If you haven’t peeked at the #supermoon yet do your… https://t.co/eYudCwSJkN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m walking 🚶‍♀️ in my WHY this Monday morning...I’m waking in my PURPOSE! Thank you for the reminder… https://t.co/2N0y9MHL85]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iLLeStEyECoN Sometimes you just gotta be straight up and honest! Lmfao...  Aye, RT that shit dawg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet Brent Becker-the designer of the new @VictoriaISD band uniforms for @EastTitanBand and @BandofWest THANKS SO M… https://t.co/JnZKeYMQRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are they really gonna claim golfers influenced this iconic fake-hair hat? https://t.co/Vj46BGu6Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I fucking love my "boy" Haircut bitch. :) I don't give a fuck if YOU don't like it. You're not the one who pa… https://t.co/WnRNRzMkec]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it crazy to drive all the way to north Carolina by myself just to watch @MartyScurll at the end of April? 🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another Reality #ReleaseTheVisas #saveh2b #@realDonaldTrump @SecNielsen @SecretaryAcosta]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Murda On My Mind”still my shit tho. Even if it is true. I know I know but that song too dope 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eparton3 @SavannahGuthrie @klgandhoda @JennaBushHager @hodakotb Your loss!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never knew u can actually have breakfast at Tiffany’s omg I’m screaming]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is talking about wine tonite. I’m gonna be a savage and drink beer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athletics It was great to see you in Phoenix.  #LookingGood⚾️💚💛 @ Sloan Park https://t.co/wlFnt0DtRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up to 40% Off Hair Services at KyleiShea Styles https://t.co/YbVmf3TwgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan At least McCabe would have taken action to prevent students from sexual assault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnaLaCroix6 @Mistybucketlist @_____dclynch_ We have this big bright thing that is in the sky not sure what it is… https://t.co/xrfU6MtbAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I look forward to staying engaged and active in our neighborhood, as I have always been. 5/5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackCDLee @AydeleB @DanaElizabeth69 @4everleather1 @MasterDuke1 @Dreadpirate42 @Charbrevolution @Sheeple101… https://t.co/GcowSQGzYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you mean yourself the most hostile and corrupt president. You are the worst President and that will be your… https://t.co/rfU97fNQbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKGlobalInc @boltsfan850 @OutofConTxts @Greg_Tish @TastyPastryFL @wakullawriter @Jmacfsu24 @cbi777 @TLHBeerSociety… https://t.co/wbYTDUhQFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campfirewood is using music choices as a weapon against me. I’m in the car with no escape. #sendhelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burnbegin This is real. It is sexual violence and stalking. Perpatrators like this continue to escalate until a tr… https://t.co/5oYdtxowyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@profwernimont Thanks @profwernimont! And here’s a deeper dive: https://t.co/gyOuGJgOMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got caught up on sleep and am feeling great! Ready to take on my day! Time to get work done! https://t.co/YDkLx5X7QR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Texas vanity license plate I spotted in Dallas tonight was pretty cute. Siesta time anyone? 😉 https://t.co/pqwiEKkCMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot explain to y’all how much I DO NOT fuck with my father, why is he still even bothering me 💯🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome aboard Silver Castaway Club Members! 2020 Summer bookings are now open and ready for you to set sail! 🚢♥️🇬🇷… https://t.co/higI3r4v1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know shawtys was freezing this weekend at papas &amp; beer it’s cold out here 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it’s back to working 7 days a week again. With no day off until March 23. 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[woke up in my hotel room to people next door probably having the best sex of their lives 🙇🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone in @CAIS_Schools a chance to be bored during their breaks from school this March. Being Bored Can… https://t.co/6eRIABZm1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danny_buder @MrTommyCampbell @realDonaldTrump Asking for Trump’s returns doesn’t mean we don’t want to see all pol… https://t.co/URX0LaS9WN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reposting thatgirldolce: - via crowdfire  💖💖💖B.I.G. facts. Thatgirldolce inspired to inspire! 💪🏽💥#dreambigger… https://t.co/OR3v4gzW4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Infantry0300 @GOP #FeelTheBern2020 #FakeTrumpEmergency #FakePresident.  #TraitorInChief #RussianAssetTrump… https://t.co/Pa2wUk6wDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President declaring a national emergency over this wall does not pass the smell test. I mean, does this “emerge… https://t.co/yXa4XSnJE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[people who thought Kevin Jonas was the hottest jonas brother like 50 year old men now]]></document><document><![CDATA[133. Если вы задумывались о переезде в нашу благодатную северную страну, вот страница колледжа, ознакомьтесь: https://t.co/5V0kXDHCXw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cover ups different colors and designs One Size #coverup #beachwear #summer #shoppingnow #shoppingwow #musthave @ P… https://t.co/htyouXbCN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why in the world did Prince agree to an interview with you? Bet his subpoena (and indictment🤞🏽) will wipe that smir… https://t.co/xJHlnHXH1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyevansjr I just got your book Unexpected Places. Thank you Thank you Thank you, last paragraph of 15 spoke t… https://t.co/dnfm7pi8dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's time to act now... You have the opportunity now , It's a ribbon in the sky]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't be fooled by the clouds! We've got a beautiful breeze this morning and some sun starting to poke through! https://t.co/aJVd6n0TJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[He made me feel like I was 16 again.  I actually finally felt something..  Now I'm hella numb again. *sigh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[In an Uber omw to my internship.. Driver: This is just a name right? Me: I’m sorry what? Driver: “Family Matters” *… https://t.co/X6SZ9CWaD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[New MAC RECORD 100 free for Maddie at Texas A&amp;M this morning. 50.98.   @mhstigerswim @MHSAmbush @MTigersuntamed… https://t.co/6Gwpyanuof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a drink &amp; eating at our favorite and only good pizza place in Florida, Little Italy’s ⁦@featherman_bill⁩ https://t.co/Q1IUt4ytLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking off your liquid lip at the end of the day is about as a good taking off your bra]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ability to adapt to change is what guarantees survival. #futureofwork #talent #resilience @ New York, New York https://t.co/DlclYK4RyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNightlyNews The sad part is when two guns or any involved the fact was ot was in the vehicle in a drive thru it… https://t.co/eOy7wJpl6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took Twitter’s advice and applied for something I was extremely under qualified for and I got accepted!! 😅🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY, EVERYONE! I hope you have a great day! 👄👄👄👄 ❤❤❤❤  #ValentinesDay #valentine]]></document><document><![CDATA[What day is it? Daytona 500 day... I'd say its beautiful weather for @GanassiChip win😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the shit that be pissing me off 😡🤬😡🤬😡🤬😡🤬😡🤬 https://t.co/Wn7iClBMRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurelSchuett @SamHeughan @Sheugs @barbaramills1 @sarahjaswim @pjl24 @thesmilingcook @annap905 @GHJNancy… https://t.co/Y1Xx9v2B9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[.....................................  Y’all WILDIN!!!!¡¡!  Chill! Plz!   This just some lipgloss ma’am https://t.co/9S3cBCtrka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancySimonds1 @LiseNilsson2 @GinaPustorino @BerrysBeefsteak @JAMMFWarriors @Outlander_STARZ @36yuz @Tina_Bradley27… https://t.co/g8ZNuWiWFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me what you do if you got everything you ever wanted, but went ignorant and built your own casket? tell me wha… https://t.co/AAKSkueJYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aecastillo120 Lol it’s like you’ve never seen the movie. https://t.co/Z8owCUKkwg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are in a relationship DO NOT stop doing the little that you did in the beginning .. THE LITTLE THINGS MATTER THE MOST ☝🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sassy cut for a sassy girl. #rosalie 😎 @ Cookie Cutters Haircuts for Kids - Beach Blvd, Jacksonville, FL https://t.co/g9bDJuyPGA]]></document></documents></author>