<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Well, @gretchenwhitmer, you wanted pothole stories...I was almost late to testify in the House Approps Subcommittee… https://t.co/gKmgvbXtSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I expect Wahlberg in a Butler Jersey  In between home games,  Butler got on the phone with Mark Wahlberg to talk sp… https://t.co/biAE6lZHl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just backed Campaign for President on @Kickstarter https://t.co/MABcGu8AND]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s not forget it didn’t start with @KimKardashian it goes further back the mama had 3 of her boo thangs all in t… https://t.co/F7OlRKehFY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @SeaWorld if u just make a affordable way to see and watch whales in their NATURAL habitat, y’all would make ban… https://t.co/giwTyf1WoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did laundry and got a haircut at the same damn time. What a time to be alive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We would not have investigations of a corrupt president and his criminal family.  Oh darn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KingRuben23 He averaged 27 and the lakers were a playoff team that was the year he tore his Achilles against Golde… https://t.co/t5JbraFnE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @mstudio1970 Practicing his lines-memorizing what he should say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our community needs to have @breakfastclubam interview with @MichaelEDyson on loop for about a month and just soak… https://t.co/EX58jcSDQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREE STUFF!!!! The @RahlReviews team is giving away a free copy of the Legion of Dawn Edition of Anthem! See the pi… https://t.co/Jlqre8sfiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess I’ve got another to add to the list of life ruiners. Okie dokie then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[there’s two kinds of high maintenance.... one is cute and one is not. i’m both!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, loosing our four legged friends is hard, but when you know you gave them a happy loving home it makes it's… https://t.co/7zbdKBBwXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @DWStweets when are you going to issue a statement on @IlhanMN anti Semitic statements?  #FL23 #flapol #Sayfie #Jexit #DrainTheSwamp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t wanna party on weekend, I don’t want to drink👎🏽 Let’s go to the zoo instead, let’s go to museums / art exhibits 😍🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my favorite girl. #jordanyear @ Tin Roof Louisville St.Matthews https://t.co/p03P2yTlnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sam_vinograd @AshaRangappa_ @Liz_Cheney @CoryBooker How’s daddy Cheney’s heart health?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Aren't Millennials Having More Children? Are They Selfish? https://t.co/cRFXHd2yLJ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greta Van Fleet es una bandaza si duda! Que buena de representar el rock en el futuro. Gracias @JWrightp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ultramannnn @Banesco @PDVSA Si lo era, porque esta maniobra depende de la cooperación, o complicidad, del la parte… https://t.co/uxF9St1df0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyNBC12 @SarahBloomNBC12 @AndrewNBC12 @CandiceNBC12 @NBC12 Thanks Good Thursday morning https://t.co/yLWznwbkWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[King Karl  https://t.co/WqDxpvOarw @ Fashion Week https://t.co/Bol68cZhoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lweagle19 @grandslamcurl Well written Lisa you have made a big impact in curling along with your teammates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill History will write this traitor’s legacy. He sold his soul, his party and the people to Trump!!! Sleep well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's necessary that your get the losers out of your life, if you want to live your dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @drambuie, please reduce the diameter of the neck of your bottles so that I can use a speed-pour. 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenMForman @AZGOP Since we are all just guessing today...someone who wont care what you are writing about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a great trainer that will get you in shape plus also hold you accountable? Duane stevenson is that trai… https://t.co/VoiVeiX9sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @PressSec @WhiteHouseCEA I love how you scaled your graph to over dramatize a 2.5% deviation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "RLT Retail Sales Associate - FT" at NRG, then look for people you migh… https://t.co/tsAOvEuXIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejandraguayoa Preciosa  , listo para verte como cada tarde besos 😍😘😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKevDeYoung Yes, we must start with what God has specifically commanded His followers to do. And there's plenty to keep us busy there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fa7mi77 Choosing a dialyzer: What clinicians need to know ca. 2018 #Nephpearls #DialysisDirector  👉🏼… https://t.co/ookxjFHvLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I remember nothing from all my years of math class. Awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightfulWrestle Agreed. I don't know if they mean it to, but it feels like Vince is being sidelined racist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't usually post food pictures but this crawfish was pretty damn tasty! @ The Brass Tap - Mid Main https://t.co/RH0P46Vi0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @LynnPlan1777 Or you might get Smack, You don't better recognize]]></document><document><![CDATA[@consbyname @Himel55 @DeficitOwls @NcojoD @StephanieKelton An easy way to show this is by consolidating the balance… https://t.co/mpooJiqMZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I love him - But Tre has to be way more of a scoring option .. has to be able to finish his shots in close. L… https://t.co/YrJeVqXXyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFienPrint What are the odds you kept up with The Passage after those first couple episodes? Because I got news… https://t.co/NPhE5yHxyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Game day in the Bluegrass, hoping the Cats can put that Saturday disaster behind them and take care of business aga… https://t.co/WNrEupuIwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inzhuvatkina Ну так это дело не простое, чтобы этим потом можно было заниматься профессионально, нужно много учить… https://t.co/22cUTz3X8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDTrey5 guess Russ can thrive without just you I see. PG getting buckets in OKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eCareDiaryJohn @powellnyt I covered his '83 comeback for the Columbia Daily Spectator.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLPSTA @AOC When the hole that one has dug for one's self gets too deep it may just be the time to stop digging .]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this Precise moment is when identity myself as a Ledgend. #ruizing https://t.co/dbfuIGH3by]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russell Westbrook AKA Mini Mike Tyson @NBAonTNT @Reflog_18 @WindhorstESPN @notthefakeSVP @StanfordSteve82]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Carolina is ranked number 5 in baseball AND basketball. Not too bad. Can’t think of another school with two o… https://t.co/mYSaUta6lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninaland @JohnOhOfSydney You're right. Just like any other human being, consent is Paramount!]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you stay awake this late? Aren’t you guys tired? @ Vanity Fair Oscar Party https://t.co/BUIM4lGZ3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentines Day. Glad to see so many happy couples.  As for me I’m...  #ValentinesDay   https://t.co/iI8WbYW5C3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #fasci is a bundle of caning rods carried by a regional authority signalling he has support of local authorities… https://t.co/Y3YybfFxFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't tweet about it,  go in front of Congress &amp; set them straight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthEndRick You think Price doesnt have a publicist? He is in the public eye. Pk goes about it differently. Doesn… https://t.co/U2iOJ8mzdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ All you rave haters,  all I gotta say is PLUR &amp; SUCK MY DICK. This is freakin awesome ⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion : New York  Not being born with plugs : Not having a drivers license]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedroheizer @hopesolo They picked names of who influenced them individually]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Android phone has a screening option that I just started using and I strongly recommend  So many disconnect part… https://t.co/1VoJvqKfNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[And why is he not locked up? @realDonaldTrump #QAnon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump2020 #SilentService]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenesisMako @jpmir @TwitterSeguro @twittersecurity Pudes poner tu denuncia en Twitter, y aun asi te seguire llamando huachicole@.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley is so much better with Van Bree on the floor instead of Bar, it’s not even funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngleRick Yeah and Gruden and Mack cleared the air. I really truly don’t think Gruden wanted to move Mack.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwvcd Going to the whiteboard is an exciting moment in a meeting and never having to fumble around for a good mark… https://t.co/xccdAK0EIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/FgOlcB1iBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get the party started!   @LochRavenAcad knows and shows how to honor and celebrate BHM.  @lemoisdesnoirs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SexWithEmily Emily I've been listening to your show for a little over a month you are an unbelievable woman hell I… https://t.co/rSHOg4xlkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Star_Gem Kushner is a thin well dressed Mafia thug. He spends all his time trying to get richer by any means… https://t.co/RhEqgUSaxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycondocon Reminds one of the scene between Burt and Mr. Kidd in Pinter's The Room where meaningless answers form the dialogue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTak @riesejr @totalgolfmove @EaldormanZ @QuarryGolfSA Having dad witness makes it even more special.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ModelMajorityP @PatriciaMazzei @FrancesRobles @nkulish Honestly I hope the reporters who last week’s NYT piece com… https://t.co/8VZgN5Mfpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld Ask Dana to ask Carrie how much drugs did he let the Iranians bring into our country just to get the I… https://t.co/XoKu7FAVSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL @DLoesch I don’t understand why they would do that  ? Is there anything you could forward? Would love to read more]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bucks have biggest lead of night at 127-115 over #Timberwolves on nifty contested layup by Mirotic. Under 5 minutes left in regulation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danny_Funaro @danpfeiffer @PeteButtigieg If anything, I think he and Beto on the same stage helps them both. The m… https://t.co/eYcg3eLtbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottyFlew Great return for a rental. Sucks to lose another top player, but not sure how fans can begrudge this ha… https://t.co/OpJw9vdgp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandongroeny Yep. Gotta give him credit. Don’t know if I could stand the pressure if it were me. Thank Hod we hav… https://t.co/HtBBCq8NLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 thank you for not making the same mistake @KingJames made...welcome to philly, Bryce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instagram is a photo and video-sharing social networking service owned by Facebook, Inc. Bigdoggpinc is an Eyeball… https://t.co/3pR1VwbcMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacAintWack @RealmutoMVP2019 @LONGER_DRIVE @pivettahype Cuz does have some good hair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to be ready for 2020 elections, because I’m sure the Dems are already planning how to steal them. We can no… https://t.co/LDj8oCgquq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biden slams Trump's treatment of European allies as speculation mounts of possible 2020 run  https://t.co/nx17x2qe1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BroErn18 @Tyler_Polumbus How often? The Broncos and Patriots can prove 6 round picks and UCFA’s aren’t nothing either]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beth Phoenix gets jumped by Nia Jax and Tamina after they failed to dethrone the Boss and Hug Connection as Women's… https://t.co/h6W6YKkl6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I look at it, I like it even more 🔋 #Passion @ Hall of Heroes Iron Gym https://t.co/4QzCgkjVY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. This is exactly why refs need to be required to have a post game press conference in all sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BESTAquariumServiceNYCdotCOM #ReefAquarium  #NYC #SaltWaterAquarium  #WheelersGoby #AmblyeleotrisWheeleri… https://t.co/KRTvf6s9l9]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO ESPEREMOS LA MUERTE PARA HACER ELOGIOS HAGAMOSLO EN VIDA Y QUE SEA  DE CORAZÓN.!!!!   “”SE FUE UNOS DE LOS MÁS C… https://t.co/3ULpE3SagO]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Full video on my Instagram TV link* #jmpresses from the bench master #JMBlakley where you can find his video on Yo… https://t.co/4tpOCVs3mA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now want to see @LionelRichie wear a shirt with @katyperry’s face on it! 😂👏🏽 #AmericanIdol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Time In A Bottle by Jim Croce https://t.co/BiH6KNZy8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met a guy last night can play the fork out of a guitar  I still don't know for sure if I really heard him but I know I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baayoun has been noticeably wild today for Long Beach. Another one gets past the catcher as Maldonado has himself a lead-off walk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im so over Bernies old ass, but yall seem to luv him for some reason 🤷🏾‍♂️ https://t.co/gPF2Dyfr9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live your lives, but make every day count. Go on a hike. Go to the beach at 6:00 am. Talk to the person you think i… https://t.co/Y7pAInzGaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The spiritual bracelet and a truthful necklace combo.☮️ @ Valencia, Santa Clarita, California https://t.co/NQucM3z7Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have another All American... Congrats @berneyboy9 1 thing left to do.... climb that podium. #MepoWrestling #GUwrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/92qDM8wrwo   So. Cal. OG Crew! One 💚! ☮️☯️👹 https://t.co/5vIXspFKxY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ New Smyrna Beach, Florida https://t.co/ZRwUZOjEFd]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT A TIME TO BE ALIVE  🙌🏾 themadisonscottsdale 🚴🏾‍♂️ • • p.s. I had em rollllllllinnngggggg @ The Madison Scottsd… https://t.co/9TFkWfTKJf]]></document></documents></author>