<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DonMartinCTV @IvisonJ JWR could be our first Aboriginal PM after Justin steps down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bitchbi45 He is something else. Just for criticizing his alcohol choice. Hopefully your night gets better young lady.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was excited for a moment until I saw that Brian Herbert and Kevin J. Anderson are involved. Haven't they already… https://t.co/cgVjhopFbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alshipley Also fuck Chris Pratt. I thought he was the new Jim Carrey, he lost weight and became the new John Wayne]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking the Ice and propelling society, This year marks 171 years of women’s evolution.  The Brothers of Beta Upsi… https://t.co/gLyJbBeP6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been watching YouTube videos for like two weeks now I don’t really know what to do anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luna was on the move yesterday. She is camping out with David and his pack. Luna will be at Hollywood Feed today fr… https://t.co/UdZ80dpLUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matt_papa @gettymusic Had a great time at the conference and can't wait for the album.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ Rep Adam Schiff is like the R Kelly of the lawmakers. He breaks the law, lies through his teeth, but i… https://t.co/XLzZDALIch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealjmump @EricSal_7 Hate to say it but that 40% FT percentage counteracts a lot of the good LB does on Defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've said from the beginning with all these freshman in this game Cam Reddish will end up being the better pro out… https://t.co/UmYlZ51dsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaKareninaXX @eilperin @arianaeunjung @EmilyWax Does he have any proof that he is the "father". You would think… https://t.co/8FewBlHyOF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skinnyseanny @KevlarNguyen Microsoft surface pro, best computer I’ve owned, can be used as a tablet too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlschwartz @doritmi To push for vaccine injections on the premises of bias science, is criminal. I am willing… https://t.co/oYd3P0VGfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bj__smoove The money won’t come in he go blow his knee, Duke will just scout his replacement. I just think he has… https://t.co/8oLKNnyI33]]></document><document><![CDATA[some lady didn’t want to go through the “radiation thing” at the airport and they thought that was suspicious and t… https://t.co/dZrM9cO8zX]]></document><document><![CDATA[... Oh, how I would like to see all of you.   Our ship is so much more comfortable than the old North Carolina but… https://t.co/gaGkDWlNR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMapleRick Well, this is all if you actually believe his horseshit doctor. Literally the only doctor he would le… https://t.co/NWluIFTpDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) I love that my grandpa had a sweet ride in the 1930’s.  What a baller.  2) Domesticating a deer was easier witho… https://t.co/kiqqvQyqcC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Commitment I respect @stevenhelmick for going all out for #Education #ElevateAndEducate]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think about recording my therapy sessions, it's basically my biography week by week. AKA, guess what happened this week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. coast guard lieutenant accused of plotting a terror attack? absolutely sickening. how disgraceful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😳 Bruh I'm not going to rank it but tonight's Next Podcast was up there EASY. Thx guys. @XBot448 @DeanKnoxx @Kmega4… https://t.co/3st4yORboh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué chinga es andar escurriendo gripe y tose y tose.   Una caguama ayudará??]]></document><document><![CDATA[God can't love you more than he does now, no matter how much you change your life. God can't love you less than he… https://t.co/XICyL4MDce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@House_Feminist I'm not going to punctuate with a 🙂 because it's not sad. It's an expression of admiration for you… https://t.co/VUwCdwG4au]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: @GovWhitmer is following @MEDC protocol and not revealing a state tax incentive package for @FiatChrysler_NA… https://t.co/c8e7T6ATty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaTsevdos @DLasAmericas No es así, María. Lo de .@realDonaldTrump era guerra psicológica, que a veces funciona.… https://t.co/6qhSGf2eYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conidave @consmover @goodexists Day 1 grade 8 PAGE1 any school USA: I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable t… https://t.co/og6PZYogJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk Subverting the Constitution and Congressional powers to usurp funds from actual emergencies to fund a fake… https://t.co/8jEC7BpFuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dude @Fyrelith hit me with some new emotes and sub badges!!!! Can't wait to show them off! They are FIREEEEEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alchemist @DJ_Muggs @EtoMusicROC Communion time, Bretheren!! https://t.co/iMYYL9p1ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephlamport Joe, because I have a lot of respect for your opinion, your kind words are especially gratifying. I… https://t.co/kKGuwEt7WP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent, and so true.  A Buffoon that could not fathom how do do anything because he was a Harvard Graduate of a… https://t.co/q5y1S813jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bloggerboxing3 loving the progress keep it up 👏🏻 https://t.co/pbdSkdd17t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimIrsay , I'd love to see @ABethea41 back in speed blue this year. We miss you 41, come back for one last ride in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fanatics I’ve spent lots of money with you and this week you didn’t make it right. 5 days isn’t 2 days. Call me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein No one is responsible for this except the person who pulled the trigger so get over yourself and sit… https://t.co/m2M3G1UwPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj need pragmatic cadidate, not an aspirational one... likely a real authentic, authority figure... governor,… https://t.co/KI0sy2HyeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNSitRoom @CNN Just drop him off on the Gaza Strip, go back 24 hrs later and pick up what’s left of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGeringer Hope Les is a fan of TTB. 😂Guess we should let him off of this. (If he's a fan, add him back.) Yeah, I… https://t.co/YmZJULCqXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DriannaBavis We were just meeting to talk about how awesome you were so....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiorgioAustin @abbycelso @spenshabaker @BrittonBuchanan @itsjackiefoster @ChristianaD @MDjock SUCH a great time! [… https://t.co/GEdWqrsqHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the first day it can happen. Will the #Eagles use franchise tag on Nick Foles? Cost, risks, trade market a… https://t.co/uMQcp59Sgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/X3zrb49xSx  "The PBOC gambled on RMB. They lost." https://t.co/Cy8NvnKZd1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kermitthephag dad release him oh release him dad release him go around]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been feeling a quiet rage today. This song has been perfectly fitting my mood and has been my companion. I'm clearl… https://t.co/gilNd6fIsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often get people who come to me and ask me to help them find a job, or meet a. mentor, or give them push to get t… https://t.co/dAhRcZtfGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@effortfuleduktr The teacher is passive to the point of being unnecessary. The center example starts with the S hav… https://t.co/0NmAGhnhoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so grateful to work with physical education and health teachers who help us become better sports and better pe… https://t.co/JGfx2B5t2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lima Senior wins district championship.  My story in The Lima News: https://t.co/9BqhJCFOh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todavía faltan 2 horas y media para que empiece el partido estas horas previas parece que tuvieran más de 60 minuto… https://t.co/OlD5Ylk4vn]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Not productive anymore’: GOP strategist on partisan divide https://t.co/jYdxF3LZ69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BNDCIf6was9 @LifeThrewLemons @someboysmother @dishs_up @natsmama75 @SnarkyMommy78 @snarkymomtobe @h0tmessmama… https://t.co/PMLgMnm849]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexico , Trump Promised, was supposed to pay for a Wall on the South Western border. Now we pay Mexico, I suppose ,… https://t.co/OSW1VgsuMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JorgeEn84312036 @RandyAlonsoFalc @realDonaldTrump Me duele a mi nada de eso me duele a ti es al que le debe doler… https://t.co/q8qWQvh9fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday to the fucking legend uncle Joey! Aka  @madflavor https://t.co/U8cM8R5rBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Ur stupid to think us Liberals are stupid https://t.co/iX8XBOFoXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been thru it all as a life long @Bucks fan..have to say I feel pretty blessed to be witnessing this years squad #FearTheDeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNC’s new indoor practice facility, massive with a bunch of neat touches. https://t.co/sxULCZBmuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ekspiers @geteero Yeah it lies a lot. Especially the multiple times a day that resets itself and your WiFi in gone… https://t.co/HkPDHxQb1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[CPAC chants LOCK HER UP This week fatNIXON'S RNC/ Campaign Manager will be sentenced Already 5 others PLEADED GUILT… https://t.co/otf402YKax]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time for everything. Really enjoyed visiting the George W. Bush Presidential Center. It’s like stepping into… https://t.co/dMjlhZd9tM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donut87_ ciggy butt brain  just kidding if tea actually works for you DO IT DRIVE HOME]]></document><document><![CDATA[#flashbackfriday to 1991 when I saw four Fernando Valenzuela’s pitch. #mlb #fbf #angels #dodgers #photo #pitchers… https://t.co/F1QpIsKlau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emmav6522 this is a great start for Washington Capitals going on a 7 game winning streak as they lead 1st in the M… https://t.co/FVVPXFvbSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invitaciones ✔️   😱😱😱  75 de 100 alv 😎✌️ @ Culiacán, Sinaloa https://t.co/aOSN5fE0ze]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS You are a chicken shit bitch who ran from the war! You draft dodging coward!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never really understood Tommy Trixie and Tooties love triangle relationship until now #AlwaysWantedFairies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adorablebeautie @NGupta001 Do you like my Dick https://t.co/DBrNLcvMj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctopher73 @docholliday747 @matthew_arend @DrJerLowe @RyanBJackson1 @PrincipalSJV @Asael_Ruvalcaba @fit_leaders Agr… https://t.co/feK1snZ5Vs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all should feel that way. Always look to get better from previous season. ☺]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattspete @c40cities @ChicagosMayor @CloverMoore @MayorOfLA Say hello to Paris for me Matt!  @COP21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino @AOC @GOP ... in several ways. 1-Electorial college, 2- Your number of reps in House of Representa… https://t.co/1hVnCOVwE5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s get this! @AdamSKutner #AdamKutnerPowerPlay! #goknightsgo #vegasborn]]></document><document><![CDATA[After prodding from Geels, Eggers said he sees value in franchise agreement, noted if the city ever wanted to bury… https://t.co/gfoINNh8Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias Papá Dios. 🙏 Es bueno poder abrir los ojos, y ver a tus seres queridos a lado tuyo un día más. 🙏 Hay gente… https://t.co/rJOFwYG1MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Anothermiracle, #INTERNATIONALWOMENSDAY Let's face it; WOMEN RUN THIS @#$% @ 174th Street https://t.co/db57Elca4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IannottiRalph @KDKA HEY Mayor Peduto how is your "common sense" laws going to stop this?  Here is the real problem… https://t.co/m0M7VKy2O0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewSiciliano Never batted .400 Never had a 150 RBI season  Never hit 50 HRs Yup. Dude is trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF luxury tax on tampons? What ass-wipe politicians made this happen? We need to repeal this monumental crap. Luxu… https://t.co/eH1O7xmMD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelNStephens I’m not sure how but I came across you YouTube channel.... SO DOPE! As someone who grew up in chur… https://t.co/7gbFmPDvD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Espngreeny Thinking your going to be embarrassed by this tweet. Very little talent in the league]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetalentscout Baloney. Most of the laws banning felons from voting were put in place during Jim Crow, aimed speci… https://t.co/2u1vLKMiwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinRashell @BeckyKillinit Everything starts with the first step or the first word and after to first sentence it… https://t.co/heuEFSWITI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Speed_Peete @AndrewM57534615 @realDonaldTrump Captain Obvious here: AOC made me realize that Trump can'trelease hi… https://t.co/iHI0kDv0ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeVeonBell I really don’t care as long as you get out of Pittsburgh! Hopefully AB will be right behind you! Maybe… https://t.co/rcLSJNg7CY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horseshoe Bend. It's become a very touristy destination. It's a very beautiful landscape. They even have campsites… https://t.co/xe3xb5X1pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ripples in the sand during low tide along Locust Beach on Saturday March 2, 2019, in Bellingham, Wash. (©… https://t.co/RMPDHHaVR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LizMacD22 I know it's pretty early, but party dog simply could not wait, and said it's never too early for a birth… https://t.co/6ZfOCjblyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deporteologo @hugosanchez_9 SIEMPRE HAY TRAIDORES A MÉXICO Y A LOS MEXICANOS RRTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hotfussxhearts It seems like something an alien would come up with to try to enslave humanity. “Lets take the two… https://t.co/mXvj4r6Qzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garciabanchs @jguaido El sacrificio por el país es necesario para que aprendamos que hay que luchar por la liberta… https://t.co/rbXzwHcVF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story behind this Hotel is Walt Disney back in the day had all the munchkins from the Wizard of Oz stay here du… https://t.co/A9L0yaIT3z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottpannier @CarmichaelDave At least the Kings are trending in the right direction.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goal: Henrik Rybinski answers Seattle's fifth goal with one of his own to push the T-Birds further in front. 6-2 Seattle (3rd)]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SenWarren calls for break-up of mega tech inc Amazon "The railroads were the place you had to be, if you were in… https://t.co/iW4b9TJon8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had an old lady ask me if today was a half day for the school since I was out. Ma’am I’m 23 I have no idea h… https://t.co/j0Lfty7hnk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch This As Real Evidence Mounts That FBI Leadership Involved In Traitorous Coup  ! https://t.co/eiDGau4dZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is that Juice cat that talks the loudest? 😭 https://t.co/9lbE3frdyi]]></document></documents></author>