<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CrushingOnSaban I’m sure I’ll have another one when I get home — this day has worn me out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue my dissertation deadline is making me go boo hoo #ScienceValentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamfoundation Maduro  decide to be a tyrant,  keeping the country looking for food, and he can be in power, he and… https://t.co/cRtnvF7z26]]></document><document><![CDATA[I definitely got on my lil brother ass for this. I bet you he’s in dual credit now, BUT.... yall wasn’t passing the… https://t.co/US79PAPYf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actual snow. Well who would have thought that it would now in NYC in February? @dapper_matt932 Are you cold yet? https://t.co/WGoqS4Wufo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does my manager have to give me chocolate every shift in order for me to function]]></document><document><![CDATA[appreciate your loved ones yoo.. cause fuck. we never know how much time we got left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pleasure visiting the @OttawaBylaw headquarters, meeting the wonderful staff and touring the facilities. Appreciati… https://t.co/Q7vbY2Icx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[4. Disseminate recovery information -- certify recovery congregations. You dont have the opportunity to wait 24 hou… https://t.co/AY1M9NnK3r]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a white male argues that women who live in the US can’t celebrate #InternationalWomansDay because it isn’t Nat… https://t.co/shbah8AghO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan schwarma and fries with the little one 🐥🦄🌱 https://t.co/itIH5tbOJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[UN #CABALLERO Un caballero es aquel hombre que trata a la mujer con todo respeto, consideración, atención, amabilid… https://t.co/1Qky9d9GQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GrahamLedger Gimme a fuckin break. You flip flop faster than a pair of sandals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls sign, takes 20 seconds.  Tell your reps in congress and senator to cosponsor #hr961 #yes2safe… https://t.co/VkBzrxByyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lookie what @Leon_Helmink got me for the flight to the Netherlands tomorrow!!! ❤️😍🚀🇳🇱 https://t.co/ffutnWz3PJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I woke up feeling well rested, it’s sunny, I don’t have any work/meetings today... why does this feel like I… https://t.co/0mxFm2piQv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I am a vein of gold, littered with diamonds, indestructible, resilient, full of creative possibilities, Art a… https://t.co/kq6B7RtvxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriffinConnolly @shaunking I love what Ocasio-Cortez did in the Cohen hearing. Setting the foundation for getting… https://t.co/IOtMlbG07q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi @gracesynweaver see you in a couple of hours. Also if you catch me asleep at SX today just leave me alone and le… https://t.co/81qIuL8qw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6 #legsformiles with cyogalife Goddess @ In Balance Yoga https://t.co/JUGikIH1aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scribblymoth It was one of @tbvike 's xmas gifts to me. I prob won't get to it for awhile, but I leave it by my be… https://t.co/uVxaFdAe9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[A student in my class shared her favorite movie during our circle time.... she said Dr. Pimple Popper  Me: “thank y… https://t.co/N8SSagLrpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION No morning services in St Louis due to inclement weather forecast!!! Please share! We are planning to hav… https://t.co/x546bmijS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paying off a porn star with whom one had an affair isn’t exactly traditional family values, @SenatorRounds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tweetmommybop I was out on the road about 10 minutes before my neighbor was able to read ," fucking asshole," roll… https://t.co/Af3AT8H4sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so ready to be a boyfriend bruh...trips like this should’ve been done with someone that’s my forever right now...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel the Love! Join us at Four Dragons Institute to experience the power of Taichi for Health.   Every Tuesday from… https://t.co/4F7UA4qA8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapsindepthcbs If jumping up and down saying yes, yes, yes then I’m excited 😆 I]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Sundays are a big deal at GMCCOGIC. Women wear white. Pastoral staff wear their collars and black suits. They… https://t.co/F9treWzOXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going from sun burn weather to frost bite weather is borderline depressing... South Padre Island, you were too good… https://t.co/gYmpKGDThd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Giancarlo Stanton signed his 13 year contract at age 25, Harper at 26. Pretty similar !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is our deaf dog, Daphne's 7th birthday and #LoveYourPetDay  She had decided to relax today. https://t.co/m2uUqfcjLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[mjkenobi #myfaveperson #favorite #layinglow #cuddling @ Delray Beach, Florida https://t.co/GPZPSydwrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoredBookworm Ahhh I forgot about Envy haha..he’s playing so well too !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way the #NWHL handled all the travel issues with such transparency means I’m even more excited to get the merch… https://t.co/WngEoFLlog]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Orange Theory Fitness in West Hartford, CT https://t.co/Aq2xfPA2u5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DianaPalacios48 @DREMEmath Thanks for sharing @DianaPalacios48. I feel the same way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell. It KeKe.Palmer that way just like that make it plain my girl! I love it... Keep.encouraging sweetie in Jesus… https://t.co/n7Mp0J43e4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nathaly_banda Yo solo quiero seguir cagandola después de comer, que se me salga toda la basura 😬🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@science_of_art @harvartmuseums I missed this announcement! Congrats!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Polar vortex sounds way cooler than having six inches of snow and less than two miles visibility.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only regret in life is not seeing you at the Hollywood Bowl when I had a chance. 😙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning☺Blessings👆Come browse my 💄eStore *https://t.co/s88lSmxaKS @ Blackshear, Georgia https://t.co/SWMppDVeG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastManStanding Painting? Just a guess since I see a paint can.  Can't wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was quite the day on Twitter for anyone who likes the Romance genre. #CopyPasteCris]]></document><document><![CDATA[Race gear ready 🏃🏻‍♀️ nvmarathon #halfmarathon #napa @ Napa, California https://t.co/LEmAjkkVOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[instead of putting Disney down let’s celebrate spiderverse AND Bao’s well deserved win. thank u, next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to say Fawk Off you greedy sons of bitches to @Ticketmaster and @StubHub ! Literally ever concert, scal… https://t.co/uJilyjTKFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobplain @RIDeptEd @egreenwichnews @kmkwagner be allowed. If a parent has to drive their kid to practice or games… https://t.co/hUrSiBktak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found a #cat filter on #Snapchat and HAD to do #CATS #the #MUSICAL 🐈 #sing #music #classic #andrewlloydwebber #lol… https://t.co/AxthvS1VTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonjaJorsen Yes - and hi. The numbers game is such rubbish and makes virtually no impact on growing readership.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news: Lanes along I285 just reopened after food truck fire. I'll have the details, plus hear from the truck dr… https://t.co/hTgzZCcgqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than 100 years ago we were self reliant. We owned land. We hunted, fished and grew food. Then the government p… https://t.co/761ywISp1i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Popular opinion that needs to be reiterated: game of thrones is the best TV show. Period]]></document><document><![CDATA[One month till the @SBY_Marathon! I always seem to wear my shoes out right before a marathon and then I’m afraid to… https://t.co/RGgWJYC57M]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day I’ll do a Yura cosplay and y’all can’t stop me https://t.co/lKphniCTDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2- My favorite math and reading tool is @Seesaw. In math, Ss can share strategies and show mastery. In reading, Ss… https://t.co/Cr5XvtLKfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[que procede cuando las dos personas que más quiero cada día me decepcionan más?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StacyLGage @Fetusberry Well I'll count verbal chastising as being attacked. Being kicked out is more like being fi… https://t.co/dSVwe9piCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laffinglibrary @gtmarrone @kandrarene @vhellamns @Montgomery_es @WoodstoneLib @chforeman71 @RachelPeterman3… https://t.co/t1PvKIigQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update I found my AirPods, proof: God won’t give you more than you can’t handle but a bitch is close ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off we go! Debbie and I are taking 25 @foxschool undergrads to Spain for a week for a @FoxGlobal_  immersion....wis… https://t.co/mKfIXB7RBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremiahTaylorr Live for @kourtneykardash’s balanced and grounded energy. #Namasté #Kourt 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkySportsWWE @WWEUK My son #LeonMayne is who I’d take but he’s refusing to be on Twitter, lol!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Omar told it like she sees it...Just like The President Of The United States does...What's Republicans Problem?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akakatie1 @Mindlessrobot37 @KathyRaven85 @gypsiny @MagdaleneMoon @megawacht @LaurieMit @Mannabouttown… https://t.co/KaVYhR5Su3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday at Rexall i bought 100 sanitary pads &amp; qualified for a seniors' discount #Menopause]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gleisi Cala boca vagaba! Luladrão é bandido tanto qto vc! Vai morrer na cadeia aquele rato nojento e tu logo ira a… https://t.co/S2LBPyAiWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump @FBI No, that would be you and your scumbag son. Have they come to arrest idiot boy, ye… https://t.co/wvloJGLz97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je pense que ma story Instagram qui a reçu le plus de commentaires à vie est celle qui compare les abricots séchés… https://t.co/fNr42ACnLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phillies We got our 17 game package!!! Ready for more great times at @Citizenbankpark #RingTheBell https://t.co/LcFLg3YTWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyPantss1014 @VivienneCafe I am so sorry to hear this. Sometimes it takes a few times before they can get the d… https://t.co/zHqugnY0MC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feels so good to be back at vals_burgers 🍔 I pretty much grew up at this place and love going back whenever I visit… https://t.co/ApauM4mDlk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland the judge overseeing Stone’s criminal case asked lawyers for the longtime adviser to President Donald… https://t.co/my2cLdg8Wf]]></document><document><![CDATA[A 7am cycling class on a Saturday morning seemed like a really good idea yesterday. Now, not so much...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robicellis @kimseverson I know I can’t retire. 25 years in the industry, last 10 in food styling/media-12-14 hours… https://t.co/VCxrPw56W6]]></document><document><![CDATA[my moms birthday is on monday and obviously i won’t be there with her ...i’m so sad ughhh 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janashortal tears, you are an incredible woman! Your story is so moving. It just makes me love you more! (If that’s possible)]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh also if anyone has a reason why I should get the gold instead of the silver battery, speak now or let me keep the extra $20]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is PHENOMENAL! @TaylorNyree I bow down to you! So excited to share this in class today paired with California… https://t.co/FlDwl1D2Oa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been crushing on @durb1220 since this song came out 😂😂😂  and I still get swerved 🙄🙃😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you at #MSTA19 ? Join @wewright1234 and I at 8am in the Ford Ballroom to learn how to use phenomena to drive st… https://t.co/ut8LvhzQmy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Trump is trying to protect American ppl. What are you doing to protect Americans?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aIyssastephanie Yeah I got out of school early because I COULDNT AFFORD TO NOT WORK ANYMORE??? girlfriend seriousl… https://t.co/33UQZpsY0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj Since when has FOX held a democratic primary debate?  CSPAN should know this answer.  Please tell your aud… https://t.co/IcKLb9zOEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In movies the hot guy always falls for the “loser” girl but let me tell you what, I’m a loser in real life and do y… https://t.co/rOJpe2Xqxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everyone here is doveprincess66 Valentines Nails and I hope u like them. Leave a like, comment and share. So… https://t.co/J9gibWwYt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[R.Kelly made 150 million over the course of his career....homie said he only got 350,000 in his bank account...jeez. https://t.co/mrGsakmjeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao my bf showed up to my job w my little sisters randomly and I just love the relationship they have. like I don’t even need to be w them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jude 1:24-25 KJV Now unto him that is able to keep you from falling, and to present you faultless before the presen… https://t.co/VZTxJMkn6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a fun weekend (funny face) #Chihuahua #dog #cute #funny #dogofinstagram #petsofinstagram #chichidoll #socute… https://t.co/cMqDdNRX3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the past 6.5 months I’ve been able to stay at home with my kids without any interruption. We bonded and we cudd… https://t.co/DDDr9N84uo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Steplightly#heartshapedtire#concrete#love#he’soutthere##smile#staypositive#believe#signs#faith#Brooklynphoto#Brook… https://t.co/u7oJvIOeOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone give me vegetarian/vegan recipes or accounts because i’ll be home for a week and i’m gonna cook all day every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled for the opportunity to be a part of the @openmiddle social media team! Thank you @robertkaplinsky &amp; @Math_m_Addicts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump_Videos @antjonesmusica1 @ChatByCC @fishme30 @realDonaldTrump So someone named @ProTrump responds with an asi… https://t.co/hnBOvwx2Wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar @keithellison Open border are dangerous.  Even in Northern MN my friend had been threaten to have his… https://t.co/NMvIAqYZbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff out of every place in the body, the guy chose the chest.... Wow. But, it’s sad the guy died. RIP and prayers to his family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father and daughter fighting zombies together on a Friday night....PRICELESS! 💕 @ iT'Z Family https://t.co/Os2ohuA23R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willharding @kalinwood @derrrick Was it this guy?  https://t.co/zY65JhAOZs or]]></document></documents></author>