<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Me and my baby on a Saturday night ❤️❤️ #nomakeuplook #belichicktheschnauzer #mydogiscutest #mylife❤️ @ Livermore,… https://t.co/k8fOZ57vkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good job Tampa , lose one our best players to keep a sorry underwhelming/ unproven offensive linemen . Great job...@Buccaneers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be contacting the California board of education my tax payer money will not go toward institutionalized raci… https://t.co/0YLiZM6Srk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okWessler5 @Aug1405 @Sekusa1 @gdzyi @texasrecks @jmbenson1491 @AnnThacker2 @MABob1 @BrAiNfReEzE69 @LadyNY4Ever… https://t.co/ae2hKnqi2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judge Ellis represents " blind justice." Calling manafort " blameless" and a good friend amd person? True, by worki… https://t.co/EOnHzV4ldb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Antonio_CotaR @GobiernoMX Toño ya tiene sus extremidades 😢 para mí eso cuenta bastante 😢😢🤷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReaganBattalion @chuckwoolery @BernieSanders Reason enough for this old sod not to be considered a candidate for p… https://t.co/YQQ6NEPUe2]]></document><document><![CDATA[This moo year is mooving fast #comedy @ San Francisco Bay Area https://t.co/sjLotsfxaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little pup just ran up the stairs cause she wanted to cuddle. She’s now laying next to me snoring]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last year on this day, I was working as an interpreter for a medical brigade in the mountains of Nicaragua. Today,… https://t.co/A61XhdnF7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Non, l'allocation d'Adulte Handicapé ne doit pas être incluse dans le Revenu Universel d'Activité en préparation pa… https://t.co/KT91oDfmAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Terrific Day! @willylevy29 @WLWCalifornia @WLW_Florida @WLW_Slovakia @wlwrepdom @WLWPuertoRico @WLWCHILE… https://t.co/PqPNEFnRhj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Are you really that stupid? Jussie lied.  With all of your experience with liars, I would have thou… https://t.co/7GDt43R3SV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The mysterious, ephemeral  beauty of deep love-snuggle in and soak up this song with you loved one 💕 https://t.co/hF7Y2OHh3i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really miss mariah so fucking much like I don't think anyone understands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannaHD8571 @kellyberger72 @coito0528 @THDSooki @Ian8571 @Linda_Mia Awesome job @rhondajaramil10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Unarithewolf @foxonskis He’s a cutie. As a publisher of erotic stories, I support nude eBook reading. 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Klydevil You know what... points have been made. This song embodies taste! https://t.co/tdm4GoqeAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LingZhiTweet @mmpadellan The only legitimate places in my community to go for a massage by a professionally licens… https://t.co/PbTQKe1QUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phliKtid ❤️.  Sounds like there could be a country song there somewhere🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[About yesterday evening at @teasestudio ... such a short trip in Denver , really frustrating. Everyone was so cool… https://t.co/GspDnS4JGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump You rig the system against “We the People”. You commit treason by doing so.  Is thi… https://t.co/JsM2Ah0cHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t get this at all.  I have no doubt my @colts will be outbid here, but I’d sure love them to make a run at hi… https://t.co/E7vzLMmhPk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CFPromoter #Update #FicInProgress Chapter 40 of Stay in Touch is posted https://t.co/LQ1JKxpdil New help The image… https://t.co/f8PtcUYUFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelmaBlair You are strong. Your are inspiring. You are loved. You are beautiful. Thank you. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #Charlotte, NC? https://t.co/07lDial4hW #GeneralScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnniebbaker If pain doesn't subside, take another pill after two hours and pray for the strength to suffer throu… https://t.co/4nHCJDC9Hh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And perhaps stop #wrongfulconviction ?  Or at least help?  #XONR8 #innocence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot cherry blossom and another card for my collection.  Still, $3 for a 16 oz is reasonable imo (at @DAVIDsTEA in S… https://t.co/G8brZTM4nf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took a break from studying for @UofOklahomaLaw @OU_OGEL final exams to take my 3rd degree blackbelt test… https://t.co/UA39K9FEN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Things Your Ice Hockey Jersey Collection Must be! https://t.co/AeoonI9Y51 #CustomSublimatedJerseys… https://t.co/QmhoFpoPjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aboutlastnight #mamalulu happy to have her cousin visiting from Mexico and sister ❤️ #italianfood @ Fabiolus Cucina https://t.co/6hN1wgEAcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[yet this maroon wants libel laws relaxed?? he is NOT the smartest person in ANY room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the best surprise! My dad stopped by the office to give me a birthday hug ❤️ I don’t get to see him much anymore..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraceCMAChurch  thank you for the chocolates @CCCOmaha #greatcommission https://t.co/iXDcHBEDuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Uber driver just made us buckle the middle seat seatbelt...with no one in it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelenWalters ⬆️  Agreed, @HelenWalters — it was a fresh perspective and the very essence of, “ideas worth spreading.”  #TEDWomen @TEDTalks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff locked up California style.. just wasn’t unable to since I was sick for the past several days..… https://t.co/YijAUbRVFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolarBearSarah I like it when I have the oven cranked to 450, then drizzle olive oil and kosher salt, cook it for 10 minutes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch today! Thank you DC! 😚🖐❤🍔🍟🍎🍷🍹 #goodfriends  #unionsquare #NYCeats @ Barn Joo https://t.co/kBM7bEOmyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you get anything at thewineryrestaurant #LaJolla make it the Pork Belly Lollipops #HeavenOnAStick… https://t.co/J9UdxQwnEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bring them up on charges of treason @realDonaldTrump you have the power. Use it, please.#CCOT… https://t.co/wp6cbQreOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pure Soft Maslin Digital Printed Gown  Gown Color:- Peach Puff Weight:- 700 Grams Each Gowns Bust Size:- L(40), XL… https://t.co/qg82OSy5xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithboykin He won’t run again u heard him say he had two heart attacks yesterday he should be charged criminally]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhh yeaaa baby let me tell you allll the ways you are wrong https://t.co/1NeCIlGWfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green lake animal shelter please Jackie would  like his  dogs  he didn't do anything  wrong https://t.co/qOBk2sRugi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandpa is so mad and LEGIT just told me he is now a Clipper fan 😅😱  YALL, it’s this serious ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[The process of buying a home is SOOO complex and expensive, just make sure you find yourself a fantastic realtor 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Pix3M_ @ThePsyren @HalfTangible Honestly I like characters who I can connect with and understand. One of my earli… https://t.co/q1O86yly21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cohen_HR_Law @Bharper3407 @cbs3 @KimberlyDavisTV @Phillies Sweetest thing ever!]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏 I took today to run one of the fastest 10Ks I ever have, I had a damn good dinner, now I'm enjoying chocolate, wi… https://t.co/M26zkqJBZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems I saw that earlier today from the one and only Jamie Ramm.......😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to join me for dinner? @ Skinny Body Care Direct Mississippi International https://t.co/LFgMVKwOWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hear that #Serial theme my hair stands on end #thecaseagainstadnansyed]]></document><document><![CDATA[A whole lane of cars in bike lanes and blocking crosswalks in east Somerville this morning (and every morning).… https://t.co/VOnxdN9f3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Logan_N4 was right.   @phillipcude sat on the fence with this one.  When I seen you all for "college week" after b… https://t.co/2xTAR0yHSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewYorkStateAG @2021_free DO IT! New York has joined others and we will get him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️  #disturbed #3daysgrace #msg #evolution #tour #nyc @ Madison Square Garden https://t.co/NlctAfpn1L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeromiahValeska @ChainsMack @hellermyers @OddNMacabre @BlankPetra @Horror_Disciple @JMikeMorbid @MsChaunceyKR… https://t.co/Ct2sDFJ8f6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cjrab629 Fox News indoctrinated her. Once they leave the nest they are on their on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KistenNoel @StressFreeKids @JLEllisStory @gloriajkenyon @ClubMulberry @realmomshealth @leadegriffin @HebertEmelia… https://t.co/OdYs7hAS7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parks and Rec @TriviaMafia at @UtepilsBrewing was a super success! Chloe and I had a blast, seeing your Costumes, r… https://t.co/byrwm9QVV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you couldn’t make it out today, but would like to help support Loudoun Commission of Women and Girls, you can us… https://t.co/2Sh8LZhBJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please note that, once again, it is the victim conditioned to “fix” her behavior to ward off an abuser. This is rap… https://t.co/rUnPyUpynA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bethtcoast @Badeye69 I pray that God will forgive them and have mercy upon their soul.For we all must appear befor… https://t.co/xsR3upZE6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prettymskiller @bunchamoney77 Lol I had the convo with Bae about gifts for vday and all that was on his list plus… https://t.co/sTDOfJZNfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[my ass was 13 years old listening to dirty mind by 3oh3 like I was a raging sex addict .... MAAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night so far with my eldest! Can’t wait 4 @jvn !! @ The Food Market https://t.co/vIB79UbHUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeplorableChoir How horrible yet it doesnt surprise me!  The left are in fact anti Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone who has stopped by the Alert Today Florida booth! You did awesome in our #TrikeRaces and prou… https://t.co/LKYucxdlPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Verte crecer y que ahora me acompañes es un ORGULLO!!!  linaluaces Que emoción compartir esta noche con mi hija… https://t.co/iO2c839wnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously—has no one made the Jonah ⏰ smashing #DaylightSavingTime gif? Cuz there’s no “s,” people!… https://t.co/herOOJxzS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AirbnbHelp Done! The customer service team has already informed me that I have no recourse as I’ve missed the 24 h… https://t.co/yW2HNLRWVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickCannon badasperine.STAY SINGLE IT'S EASY AN LOVE ON UR BABY'S💜DONNA AKA GIGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj With it so easy to steal peoples Identity's...Why would you want to have a credit card? You have been trai… https://t.co/MqLOUkvi8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 Yes, I think it is.  He stood many insults without losing his cool.  I cannot say that about the Repugnants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marsha_sherouse The trouble is that I am of the same faith, and don’t understand the bigoted., conservative view h… https://t.co/v0QEHLlvG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you soberly sleep in a full face of makeup every night. You are Satan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Men are always blaming women about their actions. I’m Sorry you think I’m “provoking you.” you react because YOU wa… https://t.co/LkNCeCbsAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bullshit. You were so busy kissing ass in N Korea you didn’t care who you disrespected. You lying sack of shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think anyone invited your liberal self on this train.  #Blocked https://t.co/d1MRHWqHq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[At a closed-door meeting last week, Putin was asked about attacks on the handling of the case and the damage it mig… https://t.co/Ll0R0Y1Oeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realfauxdenim (Actually my favorite was when I tried to tell him he should stop storing his photos on the memory c… https://t.co/QjkOaTP5tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psilovejannet She would’ve heard the dial tone and I would’ve threw that 📱 in his face then go Angela Bassett on h… https://t.co/ARFLEeT9b6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at that smile! Yoda is a happy boy today!❤🤠  #lilyandyodasfunnyfarm #pairadiceranchtexas #minidonkeylily… https://t.co/N2RWIJkwQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump She is trying to rebuild her career.  Don't fall for it.  She is the same hate monger that she was during the shut down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all ever do things drunk that you won’t do sober lmao like shave your legs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won a pink soccer ball bean bag chair at Junior League bingo and a mother bought it off me for $10 and tonight, w… https://t.co/UVuN2Tu9bH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look 👀 down in my lap this is what I see 🥰 Elaine #CatLove #OldKitty #CuteKitty @ Springfield, Massachusetts https://t.co/jBuQaY1frW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: I really did flush this ring down the toilet.  It is floating with the rest if the sewage now . @tictoc https://t.co/j39r1IK7Iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[to the detained investor.   The U.S. Embassy said in a statement that it has asked multiple times to visit Calvey i… https://t.co/SQcH7Q23u9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This beautiful ensemble got 1st division!! They sounded fantastic! Congratulations JCA Band!! #1stdivision#jcaband… https://t.co/IEzXupfIBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have become part of the con that @realDonaldTrump is perpetuating on this country and they know the truth abou… https://t.co/Zkg1ANDnpJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite quote by Alan Turing. “Sometimes it is the people that no one imagines anything of who do the things that no one can imagine.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Who writes this shit for you, Gym, and how much did they get for their soul?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many, many thanks to our Commander-in-Chief, Chef Adam. He doesn’t get older, he only gets better. @3sheetsbar @ Th… https://t.co/qMrzRP4oRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mbkforum1 ‘ Equality v Equity: What’s the Difference’panel discussion and it’s ONLY an hour! So much to be said by… https://t.co/nxtAfqwi0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in Orlando ARE SO NICE. This Midwesterner feels right at home, but warmer. 😊☀️ I’ve never been to a conferen… https://t.co/ViZNDIOyKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So wonderful to see the Unity in #GanandaProud Thx for sharing @JackiMader @WeAreGananda]]></document><document><![CDATA[No filters view from my deck @ New York Medical College https://t.co/zv6qvOfzse]]></document></documents></author>