<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Fleet kicker Donny Hageman hits a 43 yard FG.  Ryan Moeller’s INT set that up.  At halftime: Legends 9 Fleet 6 #AAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot take- I think that Give Up by The Postal Service might be the best album ever made]]></document><document><![CDATA[Islamic scholar invokes Qur’an to justify killing Jews: “Kill the polytheists wherever you may find them” https://t.co/8HGKmQdGnW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xL3THAL_ATOMICx a full ride to go here. What's your point? Am I afforded a certain amount of privilege because of… https://t.co/VaDRks7AJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyEsqueda @calvinstowell It’s good till it’s not. I feel like it was very of it’s time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDanaRipley I once got a phone call asking to sponsor a family reunion 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonybova @ngschuNLU @BigRandyNLU Will that vest help me go low, Neil? 🔥 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the guy that yelled I wasn’t ugly today after Janessa yelled it @ me from across campus]]></document><document><![CDATA[squash6iixboss x @iamthekartel ⁣ CAN’T BE THE SAME ⁣ AVAILABLE ON ALL DIGITAL RETAILERS WORLDWIDE⁣ ⁣… https://t.co/fkhG0nGhqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk would be nice if AP1 cars could get a sentry mode lite. Just having that blinking red eye on the screen m… https://t.co/Mn4DlBno0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well if Cargill says they are full, this is what it looks like early in the morning. https://t.co/kZDdKaccoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Fellow Patriots and Happy Saturday to you All  GOD BLESS AMERICA BLESS OUR MILITARY BLESS OUR LAW ENFO… https://t.co/VfgwWJoL1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came too far and overcame a lot to be in the position I’m in now but some days I still wanna risk it all and start all over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 It would be an outrageous twist of Fate if it’s actually true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rabiasquared Tammy Lynn is a bot. 1.9k tweets in the month she’s been active. I’m not buying the legitimacy of that account.]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s anime just built so differently. The aesthetic, story telling and characters were so much deeper than today’s.… https://t.co/L00vgmtfFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends .           IT'S VILLAGE IDIOTS DAY ! https://t.co/FezEogiAg8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diamond campaign ! Location : White Sands New Mexico @ White Sands, New Mexico https://t.co/sACPwHPJBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueensLiberals @sh_nirmit We always love it when Nirmit comes to #YorkSimcoe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carmen50 That thing was four hours long? I had to turn it off after the Australian kids story. Well. He was still… https://t.co/zAJKx9V5X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COLLARxELBOW I am having a really hard time with a return/exchange order with numerous emails sent to you for reso… https://t.co/IU6KsahPWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samtheaustinP1 @ClintChasteen @Frank_is_Fun @drhockeyncoffee @gr8tvaluebiggie @JasonDFW @BrandonC1323 That breaks my heart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UTTuck24 @SLAMonline Oh it's Embiid all the way. I just had that pic saved and I love it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samaadkins @ATUBrokeThings2 @StephKB Maybe he's prepping for a visit to Little Rock]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to Cherry Hill East for Camden vs. Haddonfield in SJ Group 2 final @PurpleNGold_AD @YouGotTheHigh @HMHSBoysBKB @HMHSathletics]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Vols were still a little sluggish/sloppy but have a lead on the road, buckle up the 2nd half is gonna be 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artcrooks @NikkiSixx @MotleyCrue M.C. anagram: Outcry Mele  *mele (plural mele or meles). A chant in Polynesia, es… https://t.co/XyE6LULsUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t the NHL too violent for you? People hitting each other, beating people up! Can’t do that in public or you go… https://t.co/b45FwsNBh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Because you're an embarrassment, not to mention a childish idiot...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This black guys you guys balls cut off and hung yes is on his neck Hollywood stars you all suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greetings! And just a few final Scenes from an Outstanding Work Week!😎💯💪🏻💥 https://t.co/HtedgrXU78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinMassare A friend of mine told me about a family friend who spent $100k on one and a fateful meeting with a mo… https://t.co/wPSz8MLX9f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Julia_DWeaver Nope. I might have to go back later and make sure it wasn’t a glitch, but I went in through team up… https://t.co/bPqy8OsU36]]></document><document><![CDATA[A @NYSDOTAlbany plow driver on his route saves a family from a burning house in #Waterford, Chief says. Saratoga Co… https://t.co/wzCzXEc70L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DOBrienATL On point here. When asked this question I always answered Bull Durham. I disappoint myself that I forgo… https://t.co/oH9DnhnGC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is really impressive. @chrislyncarr is making a huge impact as a freshman]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Roses are red, Tillage is fine, If you want to build soil health,  No-Till is divine!”  #AgronomyValentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Geldon is Elizabeth Warren’s secret weapon https://t.co/JTQmNvIijW via @BostonGlobe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to my car and plugged in my phone and it turned on to 50%.... I...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarielosUca A ti,mis pensamientos cada día son más fuertes ,tanto que esta noche estarás entre mis brazos,sentirás… https://t.co/qsLZozildn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theryeedee can we get a Eddie Edwards and bye you have wonderful creations!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucid1 @reelmello @Zigmanfreud @RepAdamSchiff @TheJusticeDept Patience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz Behind the curve on Netflix. Be ready to laugh your ass off. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog What should a single mom with a minimum wage job do when she gives birth and has no other family ? D… https://t.co/sZNYX6T5mZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rick_barris @b_therightclub @cameronpercy1 Big difference between just off the green and 100 yards away. Players a… https://t.co/ep4zomhnx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard at the coffee shop: "I'm sorry he's not feeling well, but, hello. Who goes to Arby's for fish?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just something a little different   #gay #hashtaggingforattention https://t.co/R4eDp7nGez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Due to potholes, the left lane of Ward Parkway is the black diamond slope of Kansas City driving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of these guys! #theEASTway prevailed once again! #eastsidehoops 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Youth group and adults Burning Palm branches for Ash Wednesday  @anglicandioTO @VTS_Seminary https://t.co/SVC4byG4Or]]></document><document><![CDATA[At #amitahealthresurrection surgical waiting room. It would be nice if they had a some information for local restau… https://t.co/MZHcBwFi77]]></document><document><![CDATA[The future possibilities of solar are simply amazing!!  Time to Solarize the Nation ☀️☀️!! https://t.co/erTZ13JUGt  https://t.co/aqulQEeuwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods And why shouldn’t they be all over Smollett and this story? If you had any journalistic integrity,… https://t.co/YZiQXPBvTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonRothstein @SetonHallFan Didn't realize Villanova was still on the bubble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roarbutt @shhmeo @Rossmac212 IT IS a flippin piece of watermelon that morphs into a shoe! I thought it was a piece… https://t.co/O1ZsOnQgIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettCyrgalis @nypostsports He is a piece of shit liar. He should admit it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love my local peaks in winter, which is the best place and time to be runnin’! @ South Boulder Peak https://t.co/zmh35rcTED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump What silly nonsense our @realDonaldTrump retweets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissMiaKang Definitely looking like curry so far and this dude still had probably 10+ more years that he could be in the league]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Red Racer IPA (India Pale Ale) by @redracerbrew at @crafttoronto — https://t.co/bi73CCA9jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rupertmurdoch the ghost of Emmy Future shows a memoriam with no Rupert. Want to be first ever booed? Known forever… https://t.co/VtWoN12eXh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamcarljones Hearing Gary Anthony Williams with @cthagod reminded me how much we need The Boondocks back on the ai… https://t.co/m6fSFivN1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a beautiful Thursday it’s TC softball vs. Berkeley Prep. After 2 TC trails 1-0 https://t.co/fpJ0hV67y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boy with the dagger!!!!! I see you!! Congrats boys way to get it done. Proud alum!!!!! 😈✊🏽 @HartleyBBall @mdrayer1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pabst_Beer_8 @BuckCityBreaks I got my notification on for your live feed]]></document><document><![CDATA[the president could possibly be guilty of up to $400 million in tax fraud from his businesses.... write a story on… https://t.co/SMU3qiPA83]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cifers decks Viana with a big right ... Cifers not going to the ground though to follow up and finish  #UFC235]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ray_g10 Your a Hater ass vato ayy give micro AI some credit foo! The number says it all! #moneyfromdeep lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RazorbackBSB My view this morning from the RV park across the street from Baum stadium!  WPS! Stands are empty rig… https://t.co/ewjDXob3pa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFCBarstool @KaitMarieox when she arrives at a party https://t.co/IkCpnuZDdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMCContent Oooh... well, you just helped my diet. (I’m trying to run races this year.) Thanks for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferja2009 @TITORODRIGUEZZ @dcabellor Esa mierda no sirve ni para limpiarse el culo, un consejo vayan recogiendo antes que sea tarde]]></document><document><![CDATA[28° seemed like perfect weather for Chief to decide to wash trucks and clean floors. Im sure we will all have pneum… https://t.co/IBGa1KRmUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You go girls. Forbes: Oprah, Kylie Jenner And The Other Richest Self-Made Women In the World. https://t.co/Xrv5DJ5qXO  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my Service Dog Bricks watching Police Dog Yeager on #LivePD https://t.co/ol3NX83EuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This was one of the most disgraceful moments for the United States in modern history. Believing Ki… https://t.co/CAbdNkbXfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWrongQuest Nope I’ll be making a fool of you and your logical inconsistencies lack of evidence and religious in… https://t.co/sPVqZBLZqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/5/2019 - 05:17 Temp: 23.9F   Hum:  64% Wind: 2.0 mph Baro: 30.435in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, longsuffering, gentleness, goodness, faith,  Meekness, temperance:… https://t.co/Zj4DrFjLzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[tonight I walked into a bar and ate so much pizza side that did not belong to me :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could be tired all day but once your head hits your pillow it goes away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion Williamson || Mini Documentary https://t.co/zkSfuC7AUh via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKyTyShow @WillOspreay From what I’ve seen on the petitions and such Marvel/Disney can pull them as properties e… https://t.co/QUEiRXAMvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #healthIT community, Interested in being awarded $1M?!   “LEAP” into action and apply today!  #FHIR @HL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[. Once more, bringing you some more creativity and passion! With the talented @jennaainah . . FULL VIDEO COMING SOO… https://t.co/NUdotbeJ3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[All liquor shops closed, I’ll have to hope my bodega still has that 14% alcohol beer ... or 4-loko ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have learned to accept in school that I am wrong sometimes.  To get past that is a big part of university.  You c… https://t.co/yiIPkdwDxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV This overpaid odious ghoul is one of the worst human beings on the planet. He will be remembered for turning… https://t.co/vtUmP01oRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This also means that I’m at Westwood ~6 hours before puck drop, so if any of my Northwest Toronto people need to be… https://t.co/lSKf6ZokW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metalinjection even machine head's best was meh. i'd kinda hoped robb would give up after half his band left. sigh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People learn a language more successfully when they use the language as a means of understanding content, rather th… https://t.co/0v8qSeqryw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smartfinproject @fleetscience @shaperstudios Lol that old dude on the bike coming up to the group presentation on… https://t.co/Vr4qLi97pT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_livin @BrianKempGA @FrommJake If that were possible, he’d just ask her to paint a world without crazy ass leftists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck Negron.  Original Voice of Three Dog Night.  #chucknegron #threedognight #vintagemusicimages… https://t.co/Yx0gM7HRwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[bruhh lent is literally the worst my mom be taking that shit way too serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s de-gamify #CyberCrime. Calling #fraudsters and #cyberterrorists “#hackers” — instead of #invaders, #thieves,… https://t.co/PP75HLOPBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddisonGreenWX @FitzyWeatherTV @WeatherGeoff Space X Launch https://t.co/4l95woSvY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well the rain is gone but the cold is sticking around for the next couple of days. Don’t put away those winter clot… https://t.co/8LoWwY93PK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for the 30days challenge? March 1 for more information call 212-964-4414 https://t.co/KcwOE2OKU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Studies Show that Vaccinated Individuals Spread Disease - https://t.co/bQmEI8h9Y4]]></document></documents></author>