<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@hlovesglitter What?! That’s bizarre! Is it always like that? Temporary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[After weeks of selecting our favorite pieces, are springtime shopping guide is FINALLY ready! Now you can shop dire… https://t.co/YBzhcIkPw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday my sweet ZoZo!!! We love you to the moon and back! @_zoelane_ https://t.co/ihjyubPfkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marian40by @frognrollFF I’m so jealous! I don’t know when, or if, the will be here this year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hole has been barricaded, but every morning around 6am Lincoln tries to break through and spends 15 minutes scr… https://t.co/bjFsss6UjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning! @ChuckDeBroder @KyleHansonKVIA @NWSElPaso @IrisLopezKVIA @NicholeEGomez @StormHour https://t.co/OU7i1nFyvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The value is in the courage to act on impulse” -@stevenfurtick @ElevationChurch #MaybeGod #5050Faith #PowerfulSundays]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I go to strip club I better see em doing gymnastics on the poles TAKE MY MONEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Samantha! I hope you have a fabulous birthday because you deserve it! 🎂🎉 #birthdaygirl👑 https://t.co/nk1yHSg9X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sostraveluk @RoarLoudTravel @CharlesMcCool @RickGriffin @VISITFLORIDA @TouringTastebud @jay_eatz @RealSaltLife… https://t.co/7KWibXDcB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pops97705862 @artificialcaged @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump I take offense to anyone... regardless of political a… https://t.co/Mh7QfrjSi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Is Us @sterlingkb1 @lakers game. Thank you for being so gracious to take a picture with me!! ❤️ @ Staples Cent… https://t.co/ih6vi4xxh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richismo77 @marcushjohnson They are successful in spite of all the obstacles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be merciful, O Lord, for we have sinned. #AshWednesday #Lent https://t.co/AKGLy3bBOV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@can_star10 @goes5hole @NHLNetwork @88PKane @Rupper17 Btw I watch 75+ games a year and attend 5+ every year you obn… https://t.co/GrRuwUPkzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC 💕You. You have more intelligence than all of the Congress rolled into one!   YOU GO GAL!! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET IT SOLD!!! Chrissy Goheen REALTOR® RE/MAX Best Choice 573.518.4178-573.431.2210 https://t.co/EfmXqdhj00… https://t.co/oCr7voMo0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 more months until @festivaltortuga in Fort Lauderdale!!! Counting down the days to get away from the upstate Ny weather ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss Every single video, and photo, with ignorant statements by Trumpers reveal that they’re all extremely a… https://t.co/RMwTAAQ880]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homeowners are MORE cost burdened in #Edmonds than re tees are.  Our housing stock needs to change significantly!… https://t.co/NrIzGWsVNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @TedCruz has an idea on how to fund President @realDonaldTrump's proposed border wall... Make El Chapo pay… https://t.co/VAQ73FR02Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hard work of the End Stigma End HIV Alliance #SATX recognized by the @CDC_HIVAIDS at #CROI2019 - it is an honor… https://t.co/AJZXffQ95b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Keep McCabe’s  name out of your filthy mouth. You stood by as boys were sexually assaulted. Mcabe has s… https://t.co/KGecGAzBSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Imamofpeace @Jenn198523 @IlhanMN @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/NuAuGc72ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Survivor starts in a week and I’ve never been more excited for a season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenDavisHS @BDUtv_News @WaynePrep @SandersSELF JUNIORS, Class of 2️⃣0️⃣2️⃣0️⃣, it’s time to set your post secondar… https://t.co/qgnvCV55JX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also do not read his posts. He a toxic neckbeard and I do not wish that on anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe I’m crazy, but this mess makes me so happy! I have so many wonderful papers (and vintage maps!) to choose fro… https://t.co/vTUT6Jan6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ameritrust_Resi If this is your parent company, your company is in big trouble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You might fool the trumpsters that voted for you actually voted for you which was not very many bu… https://t.co/JzgxEBu23t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 4 of the @YouVersion Plan How To Make The Right Decision Every Time. Check it out here:… https://t.co/bEfIn38TUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 out of my 15 patients today are all under 2 months old and I feel like shitttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianklaas @realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner PS:  On behalf of and at the direction of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my top doesn’t call me “little bitch” but by my real name. You serious serious https://t.co/IaVpCGrvkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlaRa85304250 @ScullyMulderFG You are right about that, and we use real wine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shoutout to @MollyJongFast on @UpPastryPlate @davidgura  Woot Woot 🎉🎊]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is absurd. Funny Confession Ecard: I don't judge people based on race, creed, color or g… https://t.co/2ljVL5C8F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I call this girl power ladies and gentlemen. 😌 #JonasBrothers  #Sucker @daniellejonas @SophieT @priyankachopra https://t.co/5GLp5o6yBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly having a dude good friend is awesome. Like there’s no attraction whatsoever but there’s hella fun involved. #TryIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz Flowered material (sheets especially but also clothing).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzieCitizen1 @IngrahamAngle @JussieSmollett That interview is so ridiculous!!! Are we sure he’s an actor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChapquiddickMov actor. Jason Clarke captures Ted Kennedy in his darkest hour very well]]></document><document><![CDATA[and this is why lee jongsuk’s characters always make me grow so attach to them 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[And, build positive relationships with your SME’s! They’ll make time for you when needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the absolute SECONDDDDD I can adequately give it all the things it needs to live a natural life I want a leopard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neil, can you stop screaming your hatred for this president for one moment and maybe send some healing love toward… https://t.co/PBSBjydV0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best half term ever - I’ve had so much fun exploring another city and ticking off another state, and can’t wait to… https://t.co/JI5b5amEm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I’ll sleep in my car ... I need a fan, darkness, and no tv... feeling annoyed and exhausted]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from beautiful @slcairport with @SouthwestAir 🏔 ❄️ ✈️ ☕️ #SaltLakeCity #views #travel https://t.co/hKEk5tdgE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun show @PMJofficial 🎶 Great music 🎶 @ConstantineM was amazing ‼️#DreamOn 🔥 #PMJTour]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patricia_ann4 Hi Patty! Sunny and 37 degrees at the moment. Just back from P. O. and grocery store. Roads are tota… https://t.co/aUEZALxa1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Ha ha...why would Republicans suggest that? What benefit is there in this for them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que dia mas bueno el que acabo de pasar!  ☺️☺️  adoro tanto los happy endings!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to go follow my sis @arieldreamxxx she’s brand new in the industry😈👅 show her some love 🤪 https://t.co/e3dlqYw98w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 These candidates are merely poll holders and money raisers for when loser hillary clinton sticks her… https://t.co/h82MJBWLUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve imagined welcoming a baby into this crazy group of girls for years..... through the lowest lows to the highest… https://t.co/oc03zYh1hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting your eyebrows done really makes you feel like a whole new person 🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craneandcanopy blocked me. I’ve still had no response to the polite emails about their shockingly poor quality pro… https://t.co/eqV2FyoVP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90paula @Williamdmac90 @politico ....IT HAS TO END !!  OTHERWISE UNDER THE DIRECTION OF..PUTIN.. TRUMP WILL LEAVE… https://t.co/S4ggYKHNmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we lost another poor soul to a MLM. Im using this expression from now on if I see friends, family, etc. get s… https://t.co/cLWtV1UdRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelleBelle0524 @kygov @MattBevin @KYDOCJT @JasonRileyWDRB @WDRBNews No true oversight!  Fraudulent billing, falsi… https://t.co/YQvJbnDyyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A guy just sent me a photo of his doggo and it is now confirmed that this is a sure fire way to get me to respond]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we presented to @Region4FCPS schools about our school plan! It felt great to share about all of the hard work… https://t.co/SjgpCZmBqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 Run Homerun for my second bomb of the season!   #HomeRunMindset.  @BRrebellion @Chas_Pippitt @CoachPatrick_… https://t.co/ueG7Otj1RW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support this important legislation! #troa will increase #accesstocare #oacaction]]></document><document><![CDATA[TSA agents are easily the nastiest, most miserable human beings in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So important to be spending the day at Queen’s Park sharing the value of tourism and the visitor economy with membe… https://t.co/ajbKuetIDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastique! Félicitation! I have a new seat mate  in the House!   Congratulations @RachelBendayan  and team! https://t.co/imqmRwazXF]]></document><document><![CDATA[From @CCriadoPerez - “Invisible Women: Data Bias in a World Designed for Men”, https://t.co/RRh4qE8rLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️☕️☕️☕️ (@ Home Kitchen in Los Angeles, CA) https://t.co/MDwRospJsi https://t.co/4etCerkamy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silly_emily3 @illinois68 Poor kid!! You can make little ones and stick em in your pockets too. Lovely rice socks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[quem é vc na briga Theo Becker e Jonathan Haagensen? eu sou o GH que ele toma e nao faz efeito]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lev_Llylgamyn Wow, he looks great and the visuals were amazing. Thanks for sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only people tweeting “Valentine’s Day is so overrated!!!!!!!” are the ones that don’t have valentines 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinaj_13 @BandB_CBS I no right dollar bill he is more better with Steffy they have some the best chemistry together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DateDateline @realitvpod @momsandmurder @peoplearewild That’s what I say, at least in my head, every time I see Fy… https://t.co/HtLG2ElSsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m feeling really alone right now because I’m pregnant and exhausted and I have little to no help because Blake is… https://t.co/uW8KvQFrOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man swept away in floodwaters while trying to save 3 children https://t.co/JguJvVEZWo.. .. 😳... omg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scgovernorpress Billy loved Saluda County and S.C.  He landed with his men on D-Day and influenced lives throughout his 103 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien We are way past asking ‘why’ now aren’t we? It’s a complete farce of epic proportions. DT is gaslighting the entire world]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning #sk8fam y’all git ya Roll, bounce, rock, skate with the National Drill Competition Champions Of Muhammad Mo… https://t.co/yuyyWclVmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind Gee, you don’t think this could be a trump attempt to discredit WaPo, do you? That would be like attac… https://t.co/CVrmUy1HYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#oscars remind me what a time it is to be alive. There are so many amazing people on this earth who have turly mast… https://t.co/iryxmQ0XoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyHumpDay featured #rumpshaker is its_e_double_r  lol @ Gym Food Fitness https://t.co/EJlZIe2sMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You already had the Senate and you lost the House.  You are an idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a frankly dangerous amount of Samoas in my apartment right now. Thanks @psuway]]></document><document><![CDATA[The extreme jet lag today is going to make this Monday particularly enjoyable https://t.co/cuAUOjtLdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you think? Buy your it works products now. https://t.co/3ZKOHe3GH7  https://t.co/xhq3JRXaiI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here it is. Please let @ReginaKing take this award. SHE IS A QUEEN!   #oscars https://t.co/9d5VvQxn0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yearofthehandstand is going well @ Dynamic Fitness HPK https://t.co/di3LOk1PqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[YEAH!!!! Do I see a V.P. PREZ situation here??? Either/OR? I would L💗Ve to see Candace run for President someday😘🇺🇸… https://t.co/rHm33sxDvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It just hit me that I'm going to move one day and I'm not going to be able to take little Simba with me 🥺💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxannecooke @brielarson I just avoid reviews because most of them spoil everything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristeguiOnline @lopezobrador_ Anreriormente no decias eso, rápido culpabas al gobierno, es mucha “coincidencia” q… https://t.co/xUZocxdx9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚪️⚪️⚪️🔵 | 4Q | 4:37  UTA 74 TROY 58  Final media timeout of the afternoon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews Who are they polling exactly? Bots? 46% of the country can't be that stupid, can they?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I have the biggest crush on this guy at the bar but like I have no game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moseskinnah Same for Mexicans. My mom always packs my road trip snacks in one of those bags when I visit. Def not worth that much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC is younger than me but she’s everything I want to be when I grow up. She’s fierce and strong and she’s the adv… https://t.co/SUeSObPspa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man, who fell into Portland Harbor during Tuesday night’s storm, is recovering.  @WGME   https://t.co/K8ZRPZYVvH]]></document></documents></author>