<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel, with dinner in the VIP Lobby Lounge.. (@ ShowPlace ICON Theatre for Captain Marvel in Mountain View… https://t.co/LAzCSMxzTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rose  #discus #tropicalfish #rose #fish #aquarium #fishtank #pet #animals #animalkingdom #beauty #animalphotography… https://t.co/agZgKc2uAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My only two food related opinions: tres leche is garbage and tortas are basically scrap sandwiches]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrancisMastroMJ @ndress666 @HelixStudios @tylerxxxsweet @CalebGrayXXX @SebastianFoxxx @MaxCarterXXX @AlexRomanDGA… https://t.co/5ZYsc8qu59]]></document><document><![CDATA[FROM THE PITS OF HELL CAME A WHITE HAIRED DEVIL THAT REFLECTED THE LIGHT OF HELL GLOWING RED . HIS EYES WERE AS BLA… https://t.co/qTmv5XbBtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body is draped with diamonds, fuck your award, I don't even want to win it -@gucci1017]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cosmicserenade @Lustqueen_ Hey awesome! thanks Jen.   I'll shoot you a DM when I'm finished working.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tickets: Forte Music in Tiffin 419-447-0274, MC/VISA (.60 cents fee, per ticket) or Send a check made out to: FRIEN… https://t.co/VhgebBd38T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CEdwardsSBS Would you be interested in being a special guest on the #BehindTheMic Radio Show? #CheapSeats… https://t.co/83wKLsgHbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJ_Pittinger Tricky waters for sure. George R. R. Martin’s writing style is akin to reading a historical text at t… https://t.co/7XyFuLWhiK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nos vemos pronto thedannyfit ✌️✌️✌️ #daniela #mensaje #nike #smile #followers #tdn #ponte #futbolero #mexicana #23… https://t.co/p7uD4RJQxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gusto_dicaprio You know i had to switch it up. I used to have like 7 pairs of black jeans only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_shills @Siggmak Lost a grandfather-like figure of mine to pancreatic cancer myself. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @RRRRMMMMM14 Also murder on 5th Avenue if I recall correctly that's what Trump said but what the h… https://t.co/S8RnfRaixR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "System Administrator" at Kelly Services, then look for people you migh… https://t.co/h1FHA5IeJX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRoche3MR @MLS_Buzz @mmmmarvin It screams 1995 and isn’t even a crest. Not good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I do not get the whole Marvel comic book to movie thing. It will as easy to not see this movie as it was the others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2020 CCBL will no doubt be a blow out event!! Congratulations, Jim and Jill 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spintronicsHGW Nice, it's Nature's version of Quantum Gap High Fidelity 😉🐝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rusty_hodge You fixed it! Fondle your baseball cards? That is perhaps the most kinky euphemism I have ever read Ru… https://t.co/mqnpqVmGnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeCarpentier @thekatiekline @mnwild It’s time for an entire overhaul Joe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpsinicki Joe you don’t even know what a bot is!! Is that your response when you got nothing. Thought so]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbpost what a awful headline about @K_m_Mitchell . If you actually did your job and followed golf you know that he… https://t.co/oZkTEmMtZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @Selmergrl 3/ Bernie has never joined or worked for the party. He caucuses with Democrats in the S… https://t.co/bJLIeM6Msk]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/dtJV4jHkOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kinda like having eight picks. It would have to be extremely modest, to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pvziii @rachelrae56 BRUHHHHH YOURE KIDDING, I straight up asked you that in class]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 22nd to the King of Lawrence. Sorry for hustling you at darts on your special day @ La Fonda De Los Lobos https://t.co/NvmyTjmLtg]]></document><document><![CDATA[True statement but we still don’t kiss and tell frfr and how much did you give her directly or indirectly @souljaboy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITCInsight @MJWms Love the great work you’ve done &amp; the way God has blessed!! Love you friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great car show in the books, always a good time out here. 😀 #makeawish #makeawishfoundation @ Amarillo Civi… https://t.co/EOEAmTYSId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristinBoymom @JCreasy2222 History class 😂...AOC said herself, she's more concerned about being "morally correct"… https://t.co/ih5lB5ENu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥@2chainz 👍🏻➡️#MommaIHitALick ⬅️ Feat. @kendricklamar 👌🏻(#OfficialAudio) https://t.co/3YqNaR7JJe via @YouTube @Pharrell 🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@draininbuckets @LaurenUnderwood Where ya goin old buddy? Cmon you were having fun? Da fuq?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepCommandr But not me yet 😝. One day it will happen.   Kidding I am probably somebody that not even a bother lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregatronn6 Pretty sure this tweet will get you identified as a candidate to work in the white house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. 3 good thing glad I’m not going to work tomorrow. - Drinking a Two Hearted Ale by @BellsBrewery @ Newport News… https://t.co/GHcL2KMPG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My algorithm is becoming more self aware every day https://t.co/9H36gVP2Aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hcantrell10 @Bookem006 If he wasn't an athlete though he would have to pay 40k. So technically he does get that]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing more disappointing than this year's batch of Oscar-nominated feature documentaries is the shorts categories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnLayden Who are you, Metallica?  But yeah it’s a good pick. Worth a GDC excursion? Debatable! Hard when it’s so close to Nojo. :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clintworthing I have been writing for professional publications for 50 years — starting when I was in high school… https://t.co/tZvSRtq2PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hardball @MalcolmNance The rest of the republicans are breaking their oath to uphold the constitution. No surprise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonygoldmark @starfall42 This, Smugglers Run is a motion simulator same as Star Tours just interactive. Even then… https://t.co/VuLUnynF7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss you everyday Lisa I think of you all the time.. Find me somehow be in my life Lisa you're so special to me I… https://t.co/dHMBdzSl58]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only 3 men who could have survived this attack is @SenFrankNiceley who once choked a large animal on the campai… https://t.co/NwTjDNcTn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all single!!!! We all don’t give a fuck bout anyone’s “happiness “ I’m gonna get drunk &amp; pray I get to class on time]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go on a cruise this summer with a fine ass brother to blow my back out from time to time as the boat rocks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evetavarez Went through that with my whole class my last semester in college. That mf got fired when we spilled th… https://t.co/hYspmLf0zy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minuteman223 This weather was looking forward to testing the waters !  CRAPPIES, buddies already been out at warm… https://t.co/eT4FtcuEuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet Early start to the anti Bruins rhetoric! Will be a great 6 game series! @JMillsCPGA @perrytaylor96pt… https://t.co/AOf7HmpBdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLHSStudentSec  Most of y’all could use a grammar lesson since y’all wanna talk about spelling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My haters are gna LOVE my next move 😋  ... and yes, I AM being a smart ass  Press release coming soon 🤗 #winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last remaining brain cell as I click on ANOTHER #Kardashian link:  🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/vWGDIZ5q3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader YOU ARE THE ANTI SEMITIC PERSON.  LOOK WHAT YOU SAID IN THE PAST. SHAME ON YOU. ITS TIME FOR YOU TO STEP DOWN.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need to take a vote to succeed from the union the 8 states that want to try the President! Civil war is at hand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAKANDA FOREVERRRRRR! LOL they doing the thing y'all. #edmabrey #mylifeisahashtag #spokenwordpoetry #poet… https://t.co/vAiczpDO4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Fuentes Estúpida no, ni creas que te voy a andar cambiando pañales cuando estemos ancianas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Todoist.  Love the blue. But what happened to using the q key to bring up the task box?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know Stacey personally but she is an intelligent and witty follow for baseball fans. Please consider a dona… https://t.co/chF7FSIvah]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Are #MilHockey! #NSBFanPic @ UW-Milwaukee Panther Arena https://t.co/53KXRVgdTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmyeatwordz My client is innocent of all charges. Her dedication to time efficiency is being mischaracterized  a… https://t.co/efj2p5PxJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertxgonzalez @WSJ Grace Marie Turner hit the nail on the head with op ed on @AOC. Now we all need to stop givin… https://t.co/SpguurOVy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes The rational-thinking people left in this country simply cannot allow this to happen. Trump is grossly… https://t.co/wISQ3n9Jck]]></document><document><![CDATA[As our final day in the @KCRW basement studios approaches, let’s share my closing few hours 12-3p before we make th… https://t.co/enBvF3wW4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @PatreonSupport account is listed under @DavePalet name so we have to rely on him to fix everything!! 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[See your waste water at work:   (See comments for link to multi-million projects planned at Hutchinson facility)  https://t.co/2RovODpky3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Art Felrath Hines (1913–1993) was a visual artist and modern art conservator. #BlackHistoryMonth https://t.co/ajLH3Wtsz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Nick Loomis on an outstanding ACC Swimming and Diving Championships. @wwbrown19 @BrentWoronoff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllanNairn14 Allan is in total panic over this dictator Maduro falling from Power. Allan knows if Maduro falls thi… https://t.co/Wgq09qH8C5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coached at St John in 1994/95 ..great championship with Boniface in 1995]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWPNation It's #RicFlair 70TH BDAY CELEBRATION, RIGHT? USA NTWK, THEY'VE BEEN ADVERTISING IT ALL WEEK, ALONG W/… https://t.co/lbE007dlpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you seen this movie? (Don't tell the RadTrads). This is back when badly behaved priests were guilty of mob tie… https://t.co/l3siqn6scd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our second annual @njgop Statewide Leadership Summit is right around the corner #LeadRight-  https://t.co/VQzOrYV9nY via @Shareaholic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can never use the kitchen in my apt because my roommates like to make huge ass messes and never clean it up]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new @HilaryDuff music is giving me lifeeee 🔥🔥🔥🔥. We neeed another album Hilary!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandiceAiston I'm not into breakfast either....I'm a Sunday brunch type of gal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsmith31170 @acfehrenbacher Watched game on nfhs, definitely in control all game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VitalVegas Can’t wait to see what they put in there.  Because literally anything will be better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgshepherdvan Its insane. I never like seeing dead animals but that is.. crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@23_Andy_C Ha. I never thought I would be tweeting about a TV show at 8 am on a Saturday morning. Is this what soap opera fandom is like? Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[You my girl, you my shorty. If I call on you, know you fallin through shortly 🤞🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarijuanaPolicy So the oil companies have paid the the government billions of dollars to suspend making electric c… https://t.co/QFN5vSUicZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st apres ski. With the local.... Beer..! @ Stratton Mountain Ski Resort https://t.co/CdIPR4k2lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoWhatWhyCast not everything has to be a game! some things can just be enjoyed for what they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMGItsBirdman @AFCMaKir @dc_mma @cainmma Only fight DC has to make is against Jones. He already ducked Stipe once… https://t.co/W3LyenD6Gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[AC/DC-Highway to Hell Jimi Hendrix-Electric Ladyland Albert King-Born Under a Bad Sign Miles Davis-Kind of Blue Met… https://t.co/156JJSAkKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait!! I’ll be watching this launch for sure. If they are successful they will be the first ever private co… https://t.co/oEDOgXutBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcoren @AndrewScheer How about 4. Scheer is a power hungry unscrupulous hypocritical rat.🐀 #Scheer #CPC #StandWithTrudeau #LPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunnysideLaw But it’s a smart husband who has a nice glass of wine waiting to say Thank You! https://t.co/AeB8UO0Pke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to thank @CoachKoehring for this Junior Day visit coming up in March! https://t.co/sOlosDPZS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger also announced that the Genesis Open will become an invitational staring next year with a smaller field (120)… https://t.co/PYbttRjiWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreekFire23 Thanks 👍 Should check out that channel's content. Great stuff. Been following for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanuckHil @erniehardeman By changing the financing process to farmers.... do tell. 🤦]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zion-less Duke loses again...this time  to Virginia Tech. Will they blame Nike?]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “NYPD commander being investigated for allegedly telling officers to shoot 50 Cent 'on sight'”  https://t.co/XwR921Y3fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta be high to deal with the MTA in the morning.. the delays, packed trains, and that damn 4 train]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdice03 @LibertyIsALady No surprise here, he's a silver spooner, greedy narcissistic liar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@groktrev @markd428 @ConnorMcGinty @TheScamp1 @a_g_b1993 @MattOswaltVA “In a bizarre twist to the Jussie Smollett a… https://t.co/f4WtJsk20z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snikdaelocin @BarkFu Doesn’t look too appealing, but damn it’s delicious.]]></document></documents></author>