<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@pwilliamsNHL 10549 in SD and a surprising 8415 in SJ brings the fri/sat total to 172,136 for 25 games season avg i… https://t.co/YIAtIf9KLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseBagshawe @DefendAssange @wikileaks @metpoliceuk @GCHQ Why do they say "Free Assanage." When Julian Assange i… https://t.co/BciPmVUMDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you call this a “fopoon” you can go ahead and check into the nearest insane asylum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter: Matthews is struggling...maybe change his linemates?  Babcock:]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man y’all dudes need to treat your girl better. I’m tired of getting “wyd” text every other weekend y’all break up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooohhhh😲!!  S W E E T  U N I’S  G I R L S‼️  GO CARDS! L1C4  Born ‘n Bred 502 👱🏼‍♂️👦🏼👦🏼👩🏻🏀❤️ 👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Progression: Takes Patience &amp; Dedication-Work Hard... Stay Focused.  #holnessperformance   . . . #swiftseason… https://t.co/m3RjIbgxg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dhobeika @TheStarters 😂. Love that dude. I may send him a valentine. Hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally joined the rest of the digital music making world and got a sh!!!!t-ton of plug-ins #DX7 ftw  #DIYMusic… https://t.co/MnBkPnURRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Edmonton.  Lost in the shootout and still have to pay a 5% value-added tax.  #Preds 3 #Oilers 2  Updated recor… https://t.co/p9RTG3sGuH]]></document><document><![CDATA[El &amp; Yo • Ella &amp; El • Ella &amp; Yo • Nosotros!! ❤️👪 #losamo #lovemyfamily #havingfun @ South Pointe Park https://t.co/ZRf1jc3vej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dicen que hay más de 70 muertos por falla eléctrica en Venezuela pero eso si la "Diplomacia" Latinoamericana está intacta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘You changed my life,’ is a proclamation you hear a lot if you hang around Marie Kondo. The Japanese author’s KonMa… https://t.co/zBWyBNwWPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[mi vida es un momento pero compermiso k vine a triunfar @ East Compton, California https://t.co/xUXFNB4QZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Performing exorcisms at 36,000 feet 🛫👼👹 Doing Gods Work 🙏 #Banexorcist #FatherBananas #bananasvseveryone @american… https://t.co/6DNczT3gdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrat to 2020 Dee Buffington from Gainesville High School have been chosen to play in the 8th annual Academy Spor… https://t.co/mJfob3HmFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[No requirement that members of our well regulated militia have to be intelligent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving the @riotgames @espn Doubleheader on March 16 at @sxsw @SXSWGaming: “Building Successful Partnerships in… https://t.co/p0ErubUVUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @GavinNewsom Tommy, but 10 people were killed a few weeks ago. 5 in Florida and 5 in Louisiana, both ki… https://t.co/KMMHCVly0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the @SeattleTbirds 21st anniversary of the Hockey Challenge benefiting the Ronald McDonald House, provi… https://t.co/HPLNC1oiYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeUehlein One Bit everyone knows the rules! @barstooltweetss @stoolpresidente]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarcoStyleNL Yes, do it!  Your video on the damage output / mitigation calcs is one of the most helpful videos I'v… https://t.co/fDdNNOnbU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Paisley and Wife Kimberly Open Free Nashville Grocery Store to Serve Those in Need https://t.co/k0F4xYDcVP via @epochtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our faces when we get new followers 😃 Go Follow @breakouthecrazy 🙌🏽 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/1DyathCowV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EliseBlackwell Time Out has a pretty spectacular list. I’d definitely concur on Fat Matt’s Rib Shack, Krog Street… https://t.co/Eqt10vHid0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before there was Gronk there was Jeremy Shockey. Loved watching that dude destroy ppl growing up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dan_b_80 Should have beat the little thugs ass. That kids is already pure trouble]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet dreams everyone and just sleeping on that other passion. #Me 👉🏽😂✌🏽🐦 @Sixp8ck -📷📹 #CurrentRelationshipStatus… https://t.co/EjAHnPV8AW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @McGillGail @realDonaldTrump A little electric in the fence may help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darsal @pkoonce I mean, the phrase "drive it like a rental" exists for a reason!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sanchez clearly doesn’t have the pace he did a couple seasons ago. Would have gotten on the end of that at Arsenal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I personally do not believe that anyone who works for the VA should get upset if a Veteran calls them a wordy derd… https://t.co/nPLaKXHaPh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This political junkie has given up on even trying to catch any zzzzz’s tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrismcquarrie “Fathom.” In my early-onset adolescence, Raquel Welch was classic enough.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__tashina @kmichelle my favorite songs from her anybody wanna buy a heart album r: maybe I should call, love em all hard to do god I get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[My lessons from 2018 (sharing them ridiculously late).  I highly recommend a pinned note like this at your desk. https://t.co/fZKS4UEYhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow Of course she felt so violated it took her 2 1/2 years to tell us]]></document><document><![CDATA[This isn't nearly as discouraging as  a woman who has a great contribution to make, but remains silent  because of… https://t.co/5LEMEmrwPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potbelly @nancysworld_007 @jimmyjohns Too bad the owner is probably out hunting illegal close-to-extinct big game on another continent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No hotels out in the Everglades of South Florida so we are going old school with sleeping cots in the Southeastern… https://t.co/pwS9MRWMSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[AMG die-cast 1/32 scale at ozgadgetshop.com@#amg #amggt #amggang at https://t.co/fVmCY27woS @ Cold Springs, Nevada https://t.co/KTtSytjfIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigTopGville Sweet &amp; Savory Royal Manor Cider and Burger Covered w/ Beer Cheese, it was soooooo good...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm super glad @netflix is giving US access to Aussie TV shows.. cause I'll say it, they're heckin great! 12/10… https://t.co/W2Rge9JIDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Legere I suspect Beto, Kamala, Biden will be the main candidates if they all run..but there could always be a surprise or two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolan_sanch @victoracxsta Hey bro super nice this picture pic my friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkngoldjosh They weren’t trying to get into the Utah st locker room why are people saying that]]></document><document><![CDATA[specifically:  You can get 50% OFF ANYTHING YOU WANT FROM OUR SHELVES UNTIL 10PM TONIGHT! https://t.co/8irGvpjTIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/Dbz6zg0IJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#graphicstation #uidesign Some CSS tweaking before final launch. @ https://t.co/hbPHiRPhcE https://t.co/CV4XmdToeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching some @cospaces_edu learning with @AMSStallions leading the way! @MCSDFlorida #MCSDisTHEPlace2B https://t.co/sCwcC76REt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope @MichaelCohen212 testimony today exposures all your crooked dealings and things you’ve done… https://t.co/Top9FKcpAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and carbelan Enjoying the Farm Life with Amber our Noble Stead #Horse #Farm #Breed #Amber #Mare #Horses… https://t.co/DmdDtZLXC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyMurray I guess you feel better about killing babies than saving babies. You and your kind are sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine I’m not sure why everyone is acting so shocked. You are exactly what Tucker and his radio pals called… https://t.co/cfGZCVbpgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Per multiple sources I just read, the Phillies owner and Bryce Harper are together in Las Vegas. But even when the… https://t.co/nsKZnhFalW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FTDP @DJNurotic @FredAndAngi @fredonair @RufioRadio #Mood https://t.co/73mMBWDIfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chance the Rapper’s verse on ultralight beam was the best verse of 2016, no doubt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Demons (beat produced by Jurrivh) by A-ron | A Ron | Free Listening on SoundCloud https://t.co/uf8m55FTf3 @ Muzic E… https://t.co/0VMjfrLsWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally had time to watch the @NatGeoChannel 6-part series on the beginnings of the internet, Valley of the Boom. E… https://t.co/VbUtV9AE8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Underscores the importance for all pediatric providers to screen for second hand #smoking exposure.   We must have… https://t.co/aCcLz5Wf4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DRockWar I'm just wondering how it happened. Nor exactly running on the same circles. But thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Do We Spring Forward? Daylight Saving Time Is All About Money https://t.co/6ZWazLvayk https://t.co/iq1BoMf6NU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALSO YOU SHOULD HAVE TO SEE EVERY MOVIE NOMINATED LIKE IM NOT EVEN VOTING AND I SPENT MONTHS FOLLOWING TRENDS AND S… https://t.co/3ORqnxxzkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews 5) But sure, Ellen should apologize. Why not?  Maybe it will mean something to you and you will forgive… https://t.co/yh8rCmCxkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper They just make me happy every time I listen and have since 1997. https://t.co/zgvMovMro0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebossyauzzie I bet Q is the sex trafficker lady. She had incredible access. https://t.co/QEi1M9EJXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WyattWheeler_NL 😢 Good for @MSUBearsHoops but our son’s alma mater is Kickapoo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @GTAdams2 You can borrow my purge bucket. I won't need it until July 4th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching US TV in the background while working away..... Seems I have a ton of undiagnosed medical conditions that… https://t.co/lfzegResLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabanoeg @chuskio Que sigan votando @PSOE y después se vayan a las calles a protestar a ver si así los alimentan... https://t.co/pWawPhGmm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[POTUS can be impeached for actions that are *not* crimes in the judicial sense.  The definition of *high crimes* is… https://t.co/iDDleGrsRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wow. I also wish the future was now... Label something and sell it, that's marketing. Label someth… https://t.co/ZLkB6q2pwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[All these #antivax moms need to fuck off and let there kids not have mid life crisis‘ at the age of nine.@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total stupidity from you. Calling an accomplished individual a "Token" is cowardly and ignorant. What you call "bra… https://t.co/dg8fFR0tTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemphisSpence @BillBender92 @DukeMBB There is no evidence that continuing to compete for Duke carries a greater ri… https://t.co/nnjSsoJ4cR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexajanine123 That’s love right there, I remember my little rave family in 2009-11 we would pool money and do tha… https://t.co/0VJNzL3ukR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamseanspencer @KXnOFanatics @Hassel_Chris I’ll take that as you won’t answer my question. If you seem so intent o… https://t.co/7kM1nEwNYa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthem is a Loot Shooter in which no matter what loot you have, you shoot the same. Fantastic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@binge_mode Like yeah, but I had no idea “His Dark Materials” was coming. I was seriously considering dropping HBO after GOT, but not now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regina makes the rules 👚🛍 #onwednesdayswewearpink @ Charleston, South Carolina https://t.co/NXHqtikPgL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from #devsummit Day 2  #devdude #devdiva #geogeek https://t.co/MkhNdrpRXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halftime (Boys) Leesville Road 37 Millbrook 29 Summary: Strategies simplified LR: Get the ball to Carter Whitt  M:… https://t.co/QLeAE1radO]]></document><document><![CDATA[EMERGENCY MISSING CHILD ALERT: The DeKalb County Sheriff's Office is looking for 11-year-old Amberly Lee Barnett. T… https://t.co/bMqaCJ1k9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayserCathie @JRubinBlogger In citizenship only... that is, if she didn't defraud the INS by marrying her brother to gain citizenship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MeOnAJourney I can't believe this woman has the power to persuade NYC to reject Amazon. Wasn't Cuo… https://t.co/n6YjBGddJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I personally don’t feel like the position of stars determine personality traits or relationship compatibility]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very good thread. Opponents of #BetterTogetherSTL are inordinately concerned with “process.” It’s an easy way to op… https://t.co/8yFwE05lP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillisKing I don’t know why I ever try drinking my coffee when Cosby is on. I almost always lose it laughing so hard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grabbed a quick bite before they closed...shout-out to @thepizzacupcake #food #brooklyn #nyc @ Smorgasburg https://t.co/omowuhnL3Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @FuFubar1 @DLoesch this is why we need you. Keep doing what you do. I wish I could do more to reduce the s… https://t.co/M74nnFFlyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re-Tweet and I’ll send you the uncensored. Make sure you follow me so I can DM you. 😈 https://t.co/c6gmrR76a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[First shows of 2019!! Tickets on sale now!!  https://t.co/FR8G4gAceD  @GarciasAtTheCap @claycenter @MercuryLoungeNY… https://t.co/mOtv6lXO33]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, it has come to my attention that national treasure @Steve_Dangle lowkey snapped last night and I honestly hate… https://t.co/7mOwfJnOuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao whenever I see Trump doing basic presidential things like boarding Air Force One sometimes I just fucking lose… https://t.co/flyq1OBjbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave Is she saying there are no self made MAGA women (who we highly respect)?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to serve as marshall for the first-ever “March of the Dogs” parade kicking off 14th annual Not Your Typical… https://t.co/UAOtw5RbmD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mycjkhalaf @DOTConsultants @KirstenPowers No, no it doesn’t. It shows a strong young man who knows that he is winn… https://t.co/cV4q4OIkNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemeFakeNews @S7G_USA @xcor057 @DonaldJTrumpJr @MBNI_ You are rude and disrespectful and your orange leader has gi… https://t.co/g7KwntXwSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever your hero starts laughing, that means you do too! @allisonemiller @JamesRoday @heydjnash @tbhattacharya… https://t.co/XpHTtaMJUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen i‘m 71 tomorrow and recently married to a Colombiana 30 Augusto 2018 in Bogotá. i’m having fun teasi… https://t.co/tbtx9UMJ4W]]></document></documents></author>