<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to see avi in her valentines outfit... I luuuuv having a babyguurll💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I have to share this Saturday of last week I stepped outside to check on my boys cuz they was playing outside I… https://t.co/3vkV0478Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls enjoy this lil recap of @_alyssadelgado bachelorette partay 🤪💃🏽🍹🍾🍺 https://t.co/KelhEofT7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want every girl to know that her voice can change the world. #InternationalWomansDay #EmpowerWomen https://t.co/tc1girsXxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“'Cause I been feeling sentimental for days gone by All the summers singing, drinking, laughin Wasting our time” https://t.co/uYiHGI6bDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knott_michele @MacKidsSL @MrsWall_Lorr4 @gothteacher @Kpteach5 @jasontes5th @JenJReader @MrsWake3rdGrade… https://t.co/dOExUztqHc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3_putt I know! I'm only 24.. Sucks!!! I did a lot of Dance and Gymnastics in my life from when I was 6 - 20/21 and a terrible car accident.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_kmilllli I definitely need to look into that my whole right side of my face is swollen 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to spend the evening with the good people of @SOTENI for their Celebration of Hope! https://t.co/K9ve1NOAo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhweingarten @DonaldJTrumpJr NY IS WHER U AND UR CRIMINAL FAMILY IS GOING TO PRISON FOR LIFE JR!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had the worst Chipotle experience of my life.  There were actually chunks of ice in the guacamole they put on… https://t.co/2DP0nWCdPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite Captain 🥰😁#Team Nathan #Team Fillion#ONFD https://t.co/IvRQ1Oa6nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realeddiemac Frienemies since day 1 #FiestaCantina #aaryan_zein WATCH: https://t.co/wD2TeR41bZ https://t.co/zAqYhkgAQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @ChandlerUnified Hartford ES. @ThinkingMaps is witness to this learning in action and facilitate… https://t.co/f0DRCEffa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning my friends across the pond 🌸 @Omadre @OccidoLumen666 @gordon_hughes2 @belladonna_ag Jenny had a wonder… https://t.co/mhklNHkwar]]></document><document><![CDATA[march 2: @torikelly at house of blues in anaheim https://t.co/NZTNADEwcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: A las mujeres guapas le ponen el cuerno, imagínate a nosotros que nos espera. Me: de quien hablas?  Mom: de esa kardashian.  Me: 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #shrovetuesday 💜 imjussayin 💜 🤣 #keepcount  . . . . . ...#fattuesday #donuts #countingcalories… https://t.co/PPQfS0pUvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DothTheDoth bro what @itsrllyinaluv why are we portrayed as such cold heartless monsters?  😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you finna take hours to respond to a text message don’t even text me back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Research shows the more someone receives or witnesses kindness, the more they will be kind and happy themselves‼️ b… https://t.co/tMQlDbowZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG IM GOING TO SPACE if you drop futurmastic tomorrow!! @Dombresky ❤️🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MachiBousouk @MLS Bon choix surtout Bob Bradley le considère son « Messi »]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg... i got chills.... this is sad that it comes to this... heartbreaking]]></document><document><![CDATA[We went to the gym and I did an arm workout, now I can’t straighten my left arm without a ton of pain. Andy thinks… https://t.co/XBwkxTLxLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel manafort has given Trump the wayvin The ballot box we’re doomed. Till we find out how]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas I love ❤️ this picture and can’t wait for the the single and album then comes the tour our fav par… https://t.co/cEf59lV8RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[after what we can imagine is a lovely meal, mariah/ billy finds herself in manager's apartment and it is sic af. sh… https://t.co/4kT3wgOpP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wish i had the words to describe how much i love this show https://t.co/WdK9hIrNZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Landscape #LandscapePhotography #MoodyTones #Canon #Nature #NaturePhotography #MoodyNatureLandscapes… https://t.co/t2SaQ6LCDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fresh new cut for @rebeccapilozo ! We added so much shape to her long locks! Long hair needs shape to keep it flowi… https://t.co/F0bl81l4wK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulGusGurry I’ll never tire of hearing that... although the first few times it felt more special, now... not so much 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis   Honesty! https://t.co/oGjwc4SpT2. Do you recall what America is? Are you an American]]></document><document><![CDATA[Posture Day 21: Side Bridging.  I love this one as it works the lats, shoulders, obliques and even inner thighs if… https://t.co/JdtMdal10i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit, paid off our entire wedding debt free. Let’s just not look at our bank account for awhile 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juliecwhan @AmericanIndian8 Also, NO ONE said people shouldn't be vaccinated against preventable disease. What the… https://t.co/ZsGbZAYWvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got out of work two hours later than planned, get my teeth brushed, in my comfy clothes, lay my head down, and...… https://t.co/ZMYCdLQ6Ey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Cant wait for them to invoke the 25th and remove you from power.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it all week without getting sick. Now it’s Friday and I’m pretty sure I’m getting this flu thing. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanrominee @noaaraiza I see quotation marks but I don’t know what you’re referring to.. was I that drunk]]></document><document><![CDATA[said i’d make your life a living hell .... but hell was boring, so imma have to try a little harder than Lucifer]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cheeseburger #pitbullsofinstagram #myrescuedog #love @ Hernando, Mississippi https://t.co/kPmrQ5Fe9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDORIANGRAE I mean that was the language behind black panther, wonder woman, and Get Out and they all made a ton of money]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delivered some valentines today to some very special friends! 💕 #happyvalentinesday #iloveyoubearymuch… https://t.co/BLsivtz3q1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barr's summery of Mueller report. "It's purely coincidence that everyone having anything to do with Trump is a crim… https://t.co/SGXLRXy2eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the #NFLScoutingCombine the rest of day. Talk to you tomorrow. #NFLDraft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parscale #FakeNews is just fake news. I just don’t believe any news reported anymore. Sad... but true. 🤷🏻‍♀️🤨🤨🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you guys think of my new hair?😱 I haven't had it this short ever but I'm feeling it 💁‍♀️ thanks for all the… https://t.co/1s19gP0HML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is @travisxthompson always spilling honey mustard all over himself? 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going to start using instagram more often 😂 i’m late af to the boomerang app bc i could not accept that phhhoto was gone ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_cingraham Did you not learn your lesson from the crickets????!!!?!?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at San Antonio Regional Hospital in Upland, CA https://t.co/3d9JGfZi0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump’s Nomination for the #NobelPeacePrize Was Apparently Forged. Twice. @nytimes https://t.co/Mq7PQ51P4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[talking to my primo makes me feel so much better! he makes me realize so much and tries to make a better me by tell… https://t.co/zVGxULjk98]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good to hear you have moved off of reparations being “impossible” to administer.  There must be continued discussio… https://t.co/Y4vU3ST4Mt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Losing a newspaper is like losing the heartbeat of a town  https://t.co/uibxcet2B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s your longest social media streak? Right now I have 467 days with @timehop https://t.co/hN1bsaIgiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here lately every time I work I get superrrrr annoyed!! It’s constantly busy as heckkkk. No matter what shift I wor… https://t.co/7MQNIXLIHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I received an email sent at 1:45 pm today asking if I was available for a phone interview at 1:30 pm today... https://t.co/qHNIAcXSi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elidahotpink @lauren_navaira No no more for me lol I might as well just buy them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said I wasn’t going to Vancouver, but then there was a $3 northbound bolt bus.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiologistDan Listen now. @BiologistDan I will gladly pay a bounty for each trophy hunters head. .....Ahhh if only it were legal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacconeMaryann @kengordon @amysweezey @kylegravlin @Fox35Amy @Fox35Brooks @Fox35Bob @KristinGiannas @KellyRippin… https://t.co/xLXZTKms2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me more uncomfortable than when parents call their daughters “sis”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5D7wPoPUhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carolyn42052 @westaustralian Aren’t they? Real cuddlers. Such a happy little guy. We have a miniature Schnauzer al… https://t.co/h6tzuEy0Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Is trying to destroy your Country legal?  Why no charges?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not about the goal or the dream you have... it’s about who you become on your way to that goal ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commentary on CNN today... “Bernie can’t win without some @HillaryClinton voters backing him.”  Karma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicksonright Of course they are freaking out.  One or more of them will accuse @POTUS of believing he’s the autho… https://t.co/B0IzkKKRqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute 🚀 🎫, YES please! #hornetsvsrockets #runasonne @ Houston Toyota Center https://t.co/09pl49x3se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Counterpart_STZ @STARZ I am not an idiot but I do not understand what is going on and I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new hobby is going to the makeup Reddit’s and going to the constructive criticism posts and flexing on all the o… https://t.co/HTuVinI1KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog was being extra dog and I yelled “Stop acting like an animal! You’re better than this!” out of frustration 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Oh my God, the bend and snap! Works every time.” #legallyblonde https://t.co/Pi1avoyX2S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is in the air But so is influenza Always wash your hands https://t.co/bFfln88lx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfGodAndMan hey! Start following me so you could have 666 followers!! I think @s8n would want it https://t.co/W8SZbQmimd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made some AMAZIngggggg pasta n also had some sexy self care time where I danced and got nakeyyyy. I have been reborn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdClowes @joshtpm you will want to see this I cannot be the only one to point you to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsayarnold Really pushing the boundaries I might have to put your Moana dance break in since it was such a hit… https://t.co/jzcYPdHLq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@undisputed @AB84 @ShannonSharpe That’s why Brady has SIX rings!! SIX!!it’s sick but look at his attitude!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabeIkard to read or to listen- now that is the question. https://t.co/zO0NjXJgGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bungarsargon @netanyahu @ZOA_National I had a chance to hear Kehane before he died. He was deranged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This brings me so much joy. #eltonjohn #valentinesday #kcmo #rawr https://t.co/2hhmCCpvM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *checks on people 5 mins into their meal making sure everything is good*  People at the end of their meal: you… https://t.co/0U5nDhxyR5]]></document><document><![CDATA[not a grandparent but I remember when @ginitareturns came home for thanksgiving and I went to go see her and the fi… https://t.co/YETmsmWezN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it Sunday yet? I want to eat like garbage and enjoy a burger from Sockeye again. Also I liked their new hazy IPA… https://t.co/c2fNbTkzqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[animal pictures with captions | funny-animal-pictures-with-captions-010-005.jpg #mirth #laugh #smile #farcical https://t.co/a4b2PEbqLc]]></document><document><![CDATA[looking for fun/trade ill send previews kik 20skylive https://t.co/J3MdSFYfQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepTedDeutch Calling out the actions of a group lobbying for Israel IS. NOT. ANTI.SEMITIC. AND. SAYS. NOTHING. ABO… https://t.co/EVjEsMftak]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG I just caught my husband in bed with another woman🤣🤣🤣 and honestly it's the cutest thing ever 🐶 @ Montpelier, V… https://t.co/RMSj5TDz4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no business buying 2 Deer Valley wine glasses.. but they look me cute 😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Menudo weather this weekend.....  #curadecruda #hangoversoup #menudo #tripegoodness #almostout @ José https://t.co/MT2NkpaEJ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Mer’s Bday!! (@ StreetCar520 in Colorado Springs, CO) https://t.co/N84QmmoY5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinNunes That wins dumbest tweet ever. Do you really write your own tweets?  If so, stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Giuliani Drinking Before Insane TV Appearances https://t.co/ZyWdUaOUHD via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my 'just lost my fave bluetooth headphones, but also just saw Captain Marvel and am kinda optimistic about… https://t.co/3hxGxYB24x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump I love u baby ur my wife in my head. Please lick and suck on me and fuck me baby. Im bisexual and i want u to be my first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Fool's Gold by @aaroncarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/jzjHMKtgn0 https://t.co/ssZqbYj77F]]></document><document><![CDATA[So from the look of it the new tour choreography will involve flipping water bottles and getting them to land on wa… https://t.co/HivNv3k6as]]></document></documents></author>