<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Heres another shot of todays unexpected Sunset! It was awesome!!  📸 @canonusaimaging 📸 @tamronusa 18-270mm ..… https://t.co/Y6Ojq4rfUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkiraNaToriyama @Bruce_Cares She’s begging for y’all to stop trying to put her in clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are SUFFERING in the Midwest!  And you post this nonsense?  Where is the compassion?  #Iamjealous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people never go crazy!  What truly amazing lives they lead .. 😂😂🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us on a magical mystery tour of the Capitol- the newest episode of @AlbanyArchives is here!!… https://t.co/7VGSIXMDK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great showing! Ladies had an incredible season! Big congrats from Wayne!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you delete a snap and you check thirty minutes later and it didn’t delete 😂😭😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the OG says let's take a pic we oblige 😂. Love the fact that I get a chance to represent Coach Rich's coaching… https://t.co/AzHkzwFBf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Onion I Have One More Question For You With 17 Laps To Go. And Thank You For Letting Me Ask You Some Great St… https://t.co/n1aPYdvsB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[instead of a mood ring i can just look at what spotify playlist i’m listening to and i’ll know how i’m feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh-oh, there goes the neighborhood (j/k hopefully not) https://t.co/PZ8xbFH8wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @NatlGovsAssoc @POTUS @WhiteHouse Best First Lady in the past 10 years]]></document><document><![CDATA[She needs better people advising her. The appearance of “positioning” herself for 2024 while the rest of the GOP is… https://t.co/TLEyyWlhaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbusAFL @MikeAFalvo @AC_AFL About to go Live from the @ColumbusAFL press conference....]]></document><document><![CDATA[📷: Week 4 Story Telling: Warmth // Tell a story that makes us feel warm inside. . . . . . Besides making all the si… https://t.co/f2r0B4nYP2]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of mass the choir was singing some song called “Somebody is Knocking At My Door” - did we not already es… https://t.co/qXs5uPCgCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨🚨🚨 It’s a Sports Saturday reunion on @espn975 today (no one tell @SBNationMatt or @RoboHarrisJr).… https://t.co/XWdBhYQ9re]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mornin’Verse! Today’s Agenda: A day to relax after the intensity of the last few days getting ready for our… https://t.co/DNK17wxHsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerailwaygkp @RailMinIndia @PiyushGoyalOffc @gmner_gkp https://t.co/Vw0UJAGKbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Giants2019 @CapNegative Oh yes. We are going to take that message literally. If they mess up this draft, let's exe… https://t.co/lJgLVjuI8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Household net worth falls by largest amount since the Great Recession, new Fed data shows https://t.co/w2STGLGl6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[We (the US) owe Shinzo Abe a lot. Hope when this is over we can re-focus on our Allies in East Asia..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 They are underrated. Democrats like to fall in love not fall in line]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Lineup #craftbeer #beer #ipa #dipa #beer #draftbeer #growlerfill #beerlover #newenglandipa #hazyipa  #stout… https://t.co/zBgNARYTqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Paisley - Today https://t.co/KWTS5Anvf2 via @YouTube  past memories help get us through the day . Tragedies ar… https://t.co/wqgBU26HyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Styles is 14 yrs old and has no problem with speed. 8 iron average is 193 yards. This is special! @… https://t.co/pVh2sSWrn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like shit omg my immune system is crashing the older I get I’m telling ya https://t.co/OC626F0NH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaggy901516 @kendrick_67 @MarkZuckerman I clearly remember Mikey Mo getting a standing ovation when he came back… https://t.co/fnTOKGOH8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holocausto, versión tropical de matanza!! #Venezuela  #VENEZUELABLACKOUT #10Mar  #SinLuz  #SinAgua  #SinGas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ktumulty @matthewjdowd He’s looking for retribution but he keeps giving them ammunition.@realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@souljaboy I keep reading it hoping it'll finally make sense. I just can't make it. If someone did hate you it's no… https://t.co/ctxfDekNzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @TomSteyer So what? The Koch brothers put worthless assholes like you in office every other year. I gue… https://t.co/TBSc8BMKSr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of your opinion on gun control, the merits of the Bipartisan Background Checks Act, or the likelihood of… https://t.co/clGSf5isrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnIsner Sacó 92% de primero saques eso significa 45 de 48 es algo increíble]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Miami-Dade versus Miami-Dade in a fight over MDX tolls and transit dollars. https://t.co/GI4JHgJDNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a fact.  Al Qauda is an invention of the U.S. Government to justify a war.  What do you think? https://t.co/dKhXZSoT5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up from a nap, and I was confused by this to the point I thought I had awaken in another reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danbazile @JesseMacTV I know this guy. Class act. What incredible kindness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s all the snow? I waited an extra 4-5 minutes at least so I could have milk and toast for my cereal this morn… https://t.co/0h9XAQ9rGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on a chapter on data visualization with a few colleagues.   Should we include an example of a pie chart?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Glorious by @LordHoboBrewing at @shakespearessrq — https://t.co/IhEUmbpnKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump and yet the gov is wasting more money in a childish lawsuit instead of housing his homeless feeding his hungry!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @betseyross All of these statements from you, @seanhannity and others always disappoint. Big fan of you b… https://t.co/eCWlazFOHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early miles are the best miles.  #5at5 #hesback #notforling #wakethesun #nuunlife #nuunambassador #fridayfunday @ U… https://t.co/nx9JvVufso]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 26th Birthday to our amazing son @John_Michael_D!  We are so proud and thankful for the Godly man you have be… https://t.co/sKCunJVzG1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aetaylor55 @TurntableKittah HA! Well, just give it time.  Based on the story, it won’t be long until  it is considered “well written”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[in honor of @TheCW announcement today that @CW_Arrow will end with its #Season8 some #Arrow inspired art from the s… https://t.co/PLkvcmkITt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in 1967, Kurt Cobain was born. Do you kids have any idea what it was like before Nirvana? We had to fucking l… https://t.co/UOAu2tvU8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tblgucks it’s all setting up for a classic bolts mid week disappointment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geeanem @MikePoynton @SafetyGirl100 @BrendaFlournoy1 @kfoxhouse @Jr7Jimi @kleigh062 @BeacheyGirl @79uptowngirl… https://t.co/bERo5sXXWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwdeleo @KDPomp The Phils would be happy to pay him https://t.co/9bEwCV0Rxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[We back...the Delaware legislature returns to session today. Should be a busy week, with bills on abortion, the age… https://t.co/CUmOeh90iu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized that kids today can say “you took an L” and that would have the same bullying value as “your a loser” 😵😵😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fooch1993 Love it! Maybe a US Kids tour event is in the cards for a rehab assignment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonderful 😱 I Love It 😘 make me Happy 😁😀 Good Luck to yo Beautiful 😍 I Love you Taylor Swift 💋💜 you song,s turn me… https://t.co/zXCqhVjChF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“do you ever look at a boy and shudder because you can tell he’s republican”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newest instrument, a Chinese zither harp called a guzheng! #music https://t.co/CA7MfUFvjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rules are all there! Don’t fly at night without light, don’t let the flag touch the ground, Don’t dry hump it,… https://t.co/N53CeZCHCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodStryker @KAG4All Democrats are so anti American . They are an absolute disgrace to this Country !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMitchHowe @charibayanker @cboehm @PaulTenorio Might be, might not be, but I wouldn’t say he’s totally a reserve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More views (@ Gas Works Park - @seattleparks in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/4G6NU1Xe09]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Mitch would bring a real border security bill to the Senate Floor and take a vote on it instead of wasting t… https://t.co/m8cvRvoIOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G17eDlFVhD and water is wet, sad we have to keep having this discussion @globalgamejam @IGDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You saw the red rocks ; the snow top peaks of the white mountains. That could be you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be safe this morning if you’re in Ohio🙏🏾.. The roads are terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nixon_Now I have a time teller watch that needs repair but there’s no date code on back. Any other way to find this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenKessler Perhaps he did that because he has seen what happen to your Aces a few tweets ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing more politically engaging than favoring a “course correction.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reyacost La descripción gráfica de que como la gente por dinero puede traicionar a su propio amigo, después que lo… https://t.co/rTMVUUhkbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering what your gym is worth? The top 5 reasons to obtain a business valuation are: 1. Planning for sale 2. Obt… https://t.co/YwOGC1K0AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephan67212617 Depends on the year, but those two definitely vie for the top spot yearly. They are equally import… https://t.co/OfsQ1QR9A4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn what’s the wall joint?? I’m just making a list of all things I’m gonna have my future girl pick up don’t mind… https://t.co/0B6mYeCkQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrienneLaw So why are you watching it? Much like the NFL, people who echoed the thought of “oscars so white” just… https://t.co/Iv6BFb7Jy8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is poised to announce his future climate change strategy on the #4thOfJuly to push back against @aoc and her… https://t.co/hwxY81EpYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took @ClintBowyer +1000 today simply cause when I met him last week he looked at me and said. “So you love this redneck shit or what”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lina Lamont, Singin’ in the Rain: Well of course we fuckin talk, don’t everybody?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my man. Our 14th #valentinesday together and I still feel like I won the #dating #lottery. He’s one of the n… https://t.co/cfL38NUoHk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired of seeing dirty white forces, dirty old skool vans and dirty chucks😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where was @mariacmarino today on @SNYtv with @Jonas_SNY? @DailyNewsLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[. "DO NOT GO GENTLE INTO THAT GOOD NIGHT. RAGE, RAGE AGAINST THE DYING OF THE LIGHT." . . . . @ Downtown LA https://t.co/eHsmTTNpMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #CowboysNation! God is truly Great my friends!!! My Wife, Daughter, Mother in-law and a cousin was on… https://t.co/CbovnCbq4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertWhitekett @seanhannity With @Gop budget to cut #Medicare 2pay 4the taxcuts from the #GOPTAXSCA that didn't r… https://t.co/vakeiOWoc0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 4 of the @YouVersion plan 'Uncaged'. Check it out here: https://t.co/twoSqmnm9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VickyDavilaH Claro , no quiere que se sepa@la verdad , tremenda rata ese Uribe 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elegi el lugar que quieras y vamos juntos... ❤🌎 Feliz dia!! #ValentinesDay2019 #Love en Key West, Florida https://t.co/5OVnIbhFms]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Spaghetti &amp; Meatballs for today’s recipe and video!   https://t.co/VBn6KsnGRL https://t.co/jyg87Td6xh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keanukargar That’s what I was just thinking. 9-7 is the bare minimum to make the playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite things about going to college in a small town is walking into a diner for breakfast, hearing one… https://t.co/Gjuxvx5qvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t got no sympathy for anyone that leaves me lonely. Don’t hmu later on 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deonjoelpolo If you notice it as you’re talking, drop her. That will be the tip of the ice berg you’re seeing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has it hit any of you guys yet that the biggest superstar in baseball just picked to spend his career with us, and… https://t.co/RjCWe3py3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[support #scifimusic #percussion #compser #filmmusic #steventeaster #JAZZ #filmindustry #hollywood #limo #travel… https://t.co/p0FyZicV3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember them settling on a virgin planet, and sailing the fleet into the sun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Indiana / Ohio State Line in Richmond, IN https://t.co/XNYbqhDd5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper My buddy and I were just talking about that, looks like she is doing house shows. Maybe they know the… https://t.co/KxS1k6G5cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Turgeon is a garbage coach. I don’t care how many times I tweet this. Terps weren’t even competitive today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Every player plays every position in training...I’ve had to play centre back to help me learn the game” - Ryan Fra… https://t.co/Y52uexGs9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s much easier to take the system apart than put one that works together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDePriest @WKUFootball @Coach_Helton @CoachZLankford @WKUVinceLewis @TBrownWKU @CoachGrantWKU @WKURecruiting… https://t.co/96hMyBRwgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[First step well taken. Destination is Abuja. Aniocha Oshimili people have spoken with their fingers. Congratulation… https://t.co/Q9Gqd59tdG]]></document></documents></author>