<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[To feed the 324.7 mil people in the US while also planting enough biomass to really make a difference we could easi… https://t.co/ouUawAKi8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicky Jam en Reading, PA!!!! 14 de Abril!!! Boletos AHORA a la venta en https://t.co/gK882ccohb #allentownpa… https://t.co/4XOQl0TsiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@approxqueenjane @reynoldsgareth @thedollop @Kilgallonspub I’ll always love him and hate him for this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🥶❄️ The tallest #snowman in my city on top of @riovegas @voodoonightclub! 🥶❄️💙 #snow #lasvegas #vegas #vegassign… https://t.co/mxxugVhemK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soaking in the knowledge... #weareCBA #ProgramStrong https://t.co/V7SCq5WUHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StandUpWithPete South Bend is a violent city, populated almost exclusively by fighting Irishmen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story of the first fallen @HallCountySO Deputy was almost forgotten.  Now his memorial is on the @ODMP and his… https://t.co/7gMTYX50EP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Yankees manager Aaron Boone addresses the team’s depth and additions as the club heads into spring training. #mlb… https://t.co/K2kZ0mr80y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was curious to why @wonderparkmovie was rated PG. Crazy to think this movie about a theme park would contain “Some… https://t.co/7bQ3U6Ptr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleResists @SeeLaH @TalbertSwan People need to recognize that what's inside (mind morals soul heart) counts E… https://t.co/1jvjWW6O6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Chicago police believe Jussie Smollett PAID two Nigerian brothers to ATTACK him on the street and say… https://t.co/Uw2or0c1TC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save this in case anyone invites you to anything https://t.co/Oartqqbkn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper is asleep right now and i am sending him dreams of winning a WS as a Dodger 4 times in a row.  He will… https://t.co/EWRCywI7WQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS @AP @BBCWorld @Reuters  Trump  intentionally mock CHINA… https://t.co/YvK7JyNKol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nateoloca Pues te contestó  puro chavo ,  Yo amis 48 años  tardó unos 40 min.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nitzbluv How many “Lakers winning 50 games/going to conf finals” tweets you have bookmarked? Over 100 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other than @SamoaJoe there's not many people on this planet who are better on the mic than @BeckyLynchWWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who should never use God the way we use Siri, only talk to him when we need an answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to start doing gameplay videos and such again.  I wanna do challenge runs and basically show case hig… https://t.co/kDn0fNYHrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HV3_Golf How about a shout out for the newly crowned 2019 Miss ECU?? @itssstiffanyyy and keep an eye out for her y… https://t.co/HiDr0iMHF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to a new server: don’t go behind the bar unless you’re a bar tender   New server: Why?  ... honestly didn’t thin… https://t.co/Ih6koCyzGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't want you to miss this ⬇️⬇️. Call the main office at (765) 642-0206 ex. 21or stop into the main office toda… https://t.co/og29wwxTDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hey, just cause it's frosting, you're against having one? To be perfectly honest, I just finished m… https://t.co/dWa2CNeMQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Davis: light rain, 54°F 62% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1017mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the great chat @TheBradCurrie @ScottRRocco  and @wkrakower @EvolvingEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dodgerfanalways Not true. Baseball Players are taxed at the rate of the State where the game is played. So all hom… https://t.co/53IEsej9xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Humanstein @ItsJaimeHere Disney probably missed the window to re-release Song of the South. Now, between woke twit… https://t.co/9l9cvM6zC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to my guy and the new residency at @Operaatlanta every Saturday night. #TBT On Super Bowl Sunday we welcom… https://t.co/NcI3aIsmwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great things never came from comfort zones... #4amer #MyZone3 #S4E #LetsGo 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 @ Anytime Fitness Harvey https://t.co/Smsm3D3Ddb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Grandson, for a powerful message, kick ass music, and making me sweat like a weight cut practice #bloodwater… https://t.co/dKul9V1siL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk who Jordyn is but she sounds like a hoe and Tristan sucks at basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LV2SUP Well he was prepared to argue his loss in 2016 and then to his amazement, he won.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had to be shown how to eat ice cream properly and im going to test that out tonight kk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phase I test coming in a few weeks, I better get to studying! This would be an opportunity of a lifetime if I get this job! 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @ddale8 Matt you do realize when you fail to acknowledge any “alternative fact” spoken by the president t… https://t.co/8Ia1Pa3ac5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stay hustling for cash bro. The grind don’t stop. Blessed to have multiple talents. 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniefdowns My dad is an Aussie so I lived there until I was 7 (moved to US in 95). I remember watching him in the… https://t.co/MTrXujlNih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bangin 💥 out of leboomin this weekend for #wynwoodartwalk! 🎨 Dropping my new record ‘Love, Are You Ready?’ Feat.… https://t.co/KhAbbtyQCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne And on the other side, those goofballs are saying the opposite]]></document><document><![CDATA[How To Write An Essay (eh, I'll let the grammar mistakes slide) #hilarity #giggle #smirk #absurd https://t.co/XufYcB2wC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgrlzcom @lithium66 @kittysilk7 @jockosrocket @Vdsxx1 @ironPenus_JPN @Here_Diversity @theweirdguy007 @Tgirlfan69… https://t.co/QP88w6t3Ws]]></document><document><![CDATA[After careful deliberations between me and myself, I have decided to officially announce my retirement from academia]]></document><document><![CDATA[That old starlite Club an Bar down there in spavnawe okla they torn that Club an Bar Building down that old starlit… https://t.co/NDDSqzurws]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted I’m go be late when I walked out the house and saw 3 inches of snow on my car]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! Hakima Abbas just lifted up the concept of #buenVivir being advanced by women in Central and South America her… https://t.co/8VNFJqBtCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyjettt likes Drew Carey more than Bob Barker @Kelly_v_22 @whatalittleB22 @Popo303 @615HereICome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the challenge from @jwhitsitt to post an album cover a day for ten days that would make up the soundt… https://t.co/nQscCYyAN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andrew’s Spider-Man was willing to leave New York to be with Gwen. And he even stalked her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRuffalo @wesley_jordan Amen to that! I did as well and the lessons I learned were invaluable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RKELLY scheduled to appear in the same bond court today where #JussieSmollett just stood before a judge. https://t.co/dPzSM5CTLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlziplocked “Have you ever considered that maybe it wasn’t your fault? That the situation was just genuinely ter… https://t.co/lwBhYzhlPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @AOC @IlhanMN Hell no.  I'm an American. And hell to the no.  All governments can be corrupt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“But I can’t find my other glove.” It’s going to be another one of those mornings. @NicoleMaddenWX on when temps ge… https://t.co/bOw1WQlAg7]]></document><document><![CDATA[steptah me. #bisandtris #muscily #musclegeek #pecsandthecity #healthandfitness #fitness #healthylifestyle #wellness… https://t.co/Rb3JiBx9xC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @OliviaAustinxxx @OhMelissaMoore @xoxoashleyadams @MissJessaRhodes @thejessicadrake @char_stokely… https://t.co/2JAKLPS2hE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next wednesday... luxlafayette #HooksAndBars 2 slots remain. @ Baton Rouge, Louisiana https://t.co/eTzbpNeYm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Nixon… Really… I’m not a crook…  Trump… no, no, no… I know… I know you’re not a crook… I’m not a cro… https://t.co/fqFaUHnvFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck Jussie, Yes, I hope justice does prevail &amp; you get locked up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PardesSeleh @gatewaypundit you better find out if that's true fist ? U.S. politicians  axaggrates and lie all the… https://t.co/Pcb9QkhQLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe it or not, it is snowing in the so-called “Valley of The Sun.”  Overpasses are slushy are sidewalks are sli… https://t.co/qSC10KnmFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Henny_Hardaway @_Heavyy Yeah, I could see that happening, but even he’s a risk for how injured he gets, but teams… https://t.co/CuLTSFP0IV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Martin75548654 @KruppBeyerStein @CS00249734 @QueensDramaQ @HowardSchultz @representus Paid bot. Fuck off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought they were a fake thing the Internet made up, but no. They are real. And this is the face I made wh… https://t.co/xJvicZvpMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The voices who were saying #Insulin4All was "just shouting" are oddly quiet today 🤔😆 #T1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Kelly! It’s been a blast watching Ryan Bruggeman and SMSU over the past couple of years!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenyonCollegeVB Seal the perimeter because some bad winds could swoop into the Pirates Cove, at least some night a… https://t.co/qacYxxCq3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[8 minutes into 2nd half. No FGs for @UGABasketball. Down 38-16 to @MizzouHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gumiho_arts @MikomiHokina Very cute photo, Gumiho and Mikomi. I am looking forward to check out this duo set.]]></document><document><![CDATA[日本內政部拍5G通訊世界的生活，向日本人民宣導科技對日後生活的改變 https://t.co/BqQVKkhUZY  後面虛擬樂團的場景，1994年大都會的群英會在美國迪斯奈樂園的明日世界就看過類似這樣的虛擬場景，原來預測真的會實現呢~]]></document><document><![CDATA[A $35,000 check is not reimbursement for $130,000. If it came in increments, then where's the other checks?]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/u7SwKbNJW1 Did you know that you, yes you, can purchase my comics? All three of them in fact! (And man… https://t.co/PG5Oj2ZYij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hayden_heinze @sarahannebellCO @meganroselv @biancalutzz It's a fucking swaztica, are you dumb or just ignorant? "… https://t.co/bLBcWoiYCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[When will the snow begin? What about school closings?! #berkscounty @BerksWA #readingpa https://t.co/0fxO2ZkCbL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Combustion Brewery &amp; Taproom - @combustionbt in Pickerington, OH https://t.co/5403PLjrO7 https://t.co/K23kWpBDdx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bexofeasttex @ShaneRothrock @youjoshinme13 And where did u get the name sparky from . Its actually ironic because… https://t.co/eXcBJiu0Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace @Morning_Joe @mikebarnicle @JoeNBC @morningmika Yes but yours will beat even that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um I guess you can say this was the best choice I’ve made in my entire life... very well worth it lmaooo thank you… https://t.co/IUy6J4YYPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pistolgarrett Uhhh, yes it does. If he doesn't live up to the hype you aren't selling tickets. Saying his play doesn't matter is stupid.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#loveofGod, “Dear brothers and sisters, when troubles of any kind come your way, consider it an opportunity for gre… https://t.co/JF4yFXSszU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like these ppl. Cc: @RyanRosenblatt @blazindw https://t.co/dX4llhp5GD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#blackpanther #wakandaforever #marvelmonday @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/lWByZfGRwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yousef_Jabri @FilthyMcN @smiththeman @AdamZagoria I couldn’t care less about football. More power to you there. As… https://t.co/dsO4Azz95q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luv you, thank you for sharing. I’m a white make and was sexually abused in the 70s and 80s, tough call.:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Raisin De Roof by @nodabrewing @ NoDa Brewing Company North End — https://t.co/2IJbXUNoAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mianaught @JesseFrisinger @Tpeck2 @ReutersZengerle Everybody I know believes that God has ordained our leaders.  C… https://t.co/1ohJ7ehz9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike1332Mike @arrgster @FritoDink @JohnDennisWEEI @AOC https://t.co/0hngXFnW4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loooord she @jadapsmith speaks the truth!!! #Love #RedTableTalk #FactsOnFacts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find that reason, to get up every morning with a smile on your face. It will change how you see the world, and appr… https://t.co/dq7movmTBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Devil never shows you the consequences of sin. - SermonQuotes - https://t.co/CxemRNUwd5 via @sermonquotes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tucker_2024 @JacobJMP2 @Grunt0325 @4paulsilva @ButchOred @Stephen57036680 @EricJoh37288055 @AnomicAge… https://t.co/ri06t5x7jB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psst, #DaylightSavingTime starts on this Sunday, March 10th. Just a friendly little reminder. I don’t want you to b… https://t.co/jtW35oTMJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best contract in history!... Bobby Bonilla, hold my bat and glove! 🤣🤣🤣 #Harper #Bonilla https://t.co/05CK8QElHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cviterigualinga @RonnyAleaga @BancadaRC_ @TeVasMoreno @EcuadorRC Moreno no sólo huele a corrupción, sino q también… https://t.co/mPp9I68GdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtsw Live footage of Jonathan chait’s response https://t.co/1gcOrhoctO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoWade615 This is true ...lemme know when you see Us so I can laugh at you being scared]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foreign Minister of Brazil near border with Venezuela, at refugee center with Vzlan children. Brazil welcomes the d… https://t.co/bfDoSh6O3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEarnhardt1 @Xtreme_Concepts @iK9_Global @JoeGibbsRacing @NASCARONFOX @ToyotaRacing @NASCAR @NASCAR_Xfinity Go Get… https://t.co/ZeUof5m8i1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Citra Sour Soft Serve by @gunhillbrewery at @waterville — https://t.co/lFkt7oQC8S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THESagerbomb Now now, Kacy 😏.  Let him gloat for NOW...😉  Laugh now (Pats), cry later (Celts are probably done in… https://t.co/Gufl8Dp4wp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 That’s why they want it down, it’s affecting their new voting base]]></document></documents></author>