<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Running near on empty Wish somebody would’ve told me That id end up so caught up in need of your demons]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentsDay pulling #doubleduty started off 5a with #news /#entertainment for @wcbsfm then crossed the hall to… https://t.co/Vlr7d5PYvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[ѕσмєтιмєѕ ρι¢тυяєѕ αяє α ѕσиg уσυ ¢αи'т gєт συт σf уσυя нєα∂ PC: caitlin timmons https://t.co/Fiif8YNx6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[It should be illegal for us to hangout, because together we are TROUBLE 🤦🏼‍♀️ Shopping and dinner with Grants Momma… https://t.co/WiOSDGZJ9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wmcbethh Our weather report said we r going to get between 2”-10”. That’s a big range]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindy hop lessons! (@ Salsa Con Todo in Seattle, WA) https://t.co/OxMl2NGFm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is great news Only thing better would be to somehow make restitution for the Opioid deaths  https://t.co/C99ZJPoGXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Linda, are doing the work of isis and should be removed from the USA pronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyDSampJR Oh right. So is he overrated still? Or no? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday ❤🙌🇨🇦🙋‍♀️❤ @ Belleville, Ontario https://t.co/Np0aYNTNkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bat_biomes @lexibrownbats @KellySpeer @NYCuratrix since I avoided looking at her picks I had an idea... What if we… https://t.co/DgaG79ED9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volverá una sonrisa por cada vez que te lastimaron. Porque  tus ojos ya lloraron. Porque tus sueños ya hablaron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@releby6 Yeah but if you applied for the license you supposed to be treated like you already have it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DomoWilson1 Hey beautiful please look at my Instagram dm I am praying to God that you can just see what this youn… https://t.co/uf16gpK1B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing Rafael a Happy Birthday from the 1249 MET team.@Dkauffmann1281 @MsCarly_HD @goose_35]]></document><document><![CDATA[And to my dear elli, vharnang thunder, ang cute mo, nabuhay ka naman to talk about me. Hi pans! Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Ventura county Star!. This it's how most mornings my Newspaper it's delivered!!. Hopefully you can fix this.🙋⭐t… https://t.co/9hH4GG438C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you San Francisco. Going to miss waking up to this each day. #shiplove @ San Francisco, California https://t.co/nsCPEj2GMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh some hilarity. OMG I totally saw this taped to a light post downtown a few month agao and... #hilarity #giggle… https://t.co/aRqZmBbw0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t used my Chi straightener in a fat minute &amp; now it’s no where to be found 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinaiBrain @SloanFoundation @rajankdr @IcahnMountSinai @GradSchoolSinai Congrats! Well done and well deserved! So proud of you guys.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'M HECKIN LOSING MY MARBLES AT HUA CHENG PUSHING HIS VEGGIES AROUND HIS PLATE INTO A SMILEY FACE... THE HECKING DE… https://t.co/eHeo4ADZ6q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@astrologeranne1 thank you for following me! I am a believer, will definitely check it out, thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It must be something big!I cannot believe Lindsey has turned against his Country the way he has!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUSPress God bless you &amp; Thank you for building our Wall, Mr.President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh heck, look at that mischevious grin. Link is UP. TO. NO. GOOD. https://t.co/ymZUkei11h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best start to our honeymoon @VillaBlancaBH! Thank you, @LisaVanderpump 🍾 https://t.co/iOjsValFk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard #MAGA #Trump2020 #BuildTheWall #AmericaFirst #FreeEnterprise #Capitalism https://t.co/ZmyO8mAvVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look. I want to make my own money, I appreciate being slightly cut off. It’s a lot of tough love/hate —-]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring our creativity in Makerspace club! @DRDteach1 @AAD_Inc @PrincipalDarby @dnwillia2 @CubsChris79… https://t.co/Rud2ebGzA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌲⛺his book is wild and definitely not for the squeamish. Out in May from @coachhousebooks. https://t.co/9MACqcNyvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coles lease isn’t up until august but guess who is already shopping for a whole new bedroom set for us 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ND4LIFE1128 @realDonaldTrump What is it with you Repugs &amp; your obsession with HRC??😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MazurikL @magastorybook @POTUS @AngeleStar11 @ROCKONOHIO @1RealLori @whatznextfolks @pinkk9lover @RealSugarLily… https://t.co/U1jJHfZPzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1sgtmajor @BCMsolt @electricbluel @mystormee @TwistedOne96 @Liberaladam2 @Sissy_USMC @SassyT_Joy @Cowgirls4Trump… https://t.co/fpRjEENfAe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aardwolf2000 @jacobgrubbs19 @JacobAWohl Lol sorry to burst your mindless indoctrinated brains but this story has b… https://t.co/gJEzQCQhz9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re so welcome- it’s a great tune! I thank YOU! Love the “Bonafide” CD ♥️♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMFifthCircuit @CamryOfJustice This was my first concern. Will the @camryofjustice be traded in for a… https://t.co/C4F2ZQcFLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bust down thotiana is stuck in my head now cause of Tony’s stories. 🤦🏽‍♀️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im convinced my mom cooks when she’s PISSED everything she cooks is always spicy af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to hear from the West Chester Symphony today at the Arts Sampler @MidPointe in West Chester. #WestChesterOH… https://t.co/SxBSAtZPmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Counting money and sorting tickets!  We’re up to $1020 for GiGis Playhouse!  One more day KN families!!… https://t.co/zcbS2YfIfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh and I decided last minute to see a movie. We hit up Wendy’s first and packed my purse with chicken nuggets. He… https://t.co/iIqRmAzUZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Serena Starks and Jack Horton. OCADA Athletes of Character and Honor! @EdisonChargers… https://t.co/L9KhNHZe9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a midday work shower to get the punk hair and eyes look going. #Goodtimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chester66666666 @bdp3464 @KD8410 @MrGilyard @MSNBC @ZachStafford Do you not have GOOGLE?]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting accident led firefighters in New Hampshire to discover a car buried in a snowbank....  @WGME   https://t.co/HBH8Ul3YCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ex boyfriend told me if I found a new boyfriend he would punch my teeth out 🤣🤣🤣 (he was joking of course.. kinda)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terror and pit and snare await you, you people of Moab," declares the LORD. https://t.co/LqgMa6YorL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obama surprises press secretary https://t.co/7MQSN8FIGB via @YouTube after this final real press day in the White H… https://t.co/tG5GZTPceV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKrackman AND CORRECTION ON GALE SAYERS,GALE SALLERS WHO WAS AN A NEW YORK STREET BALLER!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods So, Venezuela should put Venezuela first? But Bernie hates it when we say America should put America first.....🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The highlight of my Vegas trip was finally getting to see Celine Dion! She’s just as amazing as I thought she’d be!… https://t.co/WxQ9Ti9Pna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Women’s Day! So many amazing women in my life I can’t possibly include all of them. Love… https://t.co/c4ZQ9Co6mT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @arkellsmusic any chance you're playing 'Don't Be a Stranger' tomorrow night? I'm originally from the 'shwa but… https://t.co/PLIRLLmVGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fawfulfan @WritesTruths after today’s one cutting abortion advice to poor women paving the way for more babies born into poverty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 1-44 Presidents’ Day. #PresidentsDay #NotMyPresident #NotMyNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back where the adventures really began - day2 in #toronto getting shipwrecked on #torontoisland. They say 7 years o… https://t.co/UQhXL6Iu89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siento que deberían aprovechar que Paul McCartney sigue vivo para que ayude a hacer una película sobre los Beatles… https://t.co/1yrmszFB2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu preciso trocar a música do meu despertador que pela atual já criei ranço]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRATV @CamEdwards I am a veteran, I am 52 years old. I grew up in the South, shooting from early childhood. I cann… https://t.co/NzaI1Z2kWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s national drink wine day!!!!! Red or white? @quadywinery Electra Moscato Red is my favorite by far.… https://t.co/qI13EEovmQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews “I think I will do the same” @realDonaldTrump  you should note that the DNC decided not t… https://t.co/z5IK9dYsae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting my embroidery on!! Making this for my mom ❤! #embroidery #crossstitch #butterflies #moms @ Pelham, Alabama https://t.co/52JxpZhb9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[I normally arrange my schedule so that I only have to work 6-10 am Friday. Since I was offered up to 6 hours of ove… https://t.co/CjLFSMaZtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingNLive I am looking for confirmation on this. I I find that it is true, perhaps she is trying to see if the… https://t.co/R7CjbpOJDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absorb + breathe the essence from the 3 slides. Inspirations + Clear Insights to power the inner navigator to SOURC… https://t.co/nRyxZJOxpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is a team that feeds off the energy and starts hard at home. We can’t ease into this game. We have to be read… https://t.co/wFXkn7bgQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess is obviously some type of terrier, maybe yorkie because of his ears. Toy poodle cause of his size and his… https://t.co/rO92fMNVs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbuJafar51 @reesetheone1 @melsonite Yes, remember what happened to Cat Stevens when he changed his name and appearance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OysterBayPatch @JosephSaladino9  Long Island doesn’t want Seaquest here!! Enough animal abuse already! This should… https://t.co/UGigNMkDi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@satefan I don’t what I miss more: the battery indicators or the “breathing” light]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/yRx6hBysFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR @EllenPage Sometimes people make mistakes. Ms Page should learn from hers &amp; apologize with grace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkDice @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Fox isn't news, it's an entertainment network.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ebuyhouseinc @nelasue17 100% right. As a realtor, I would love to see bad agents held to the Code. Unfortunately,… https://t.co/oLCBj3yAK7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup Bill said he doesn’t have Twitter, poor guy doesn’t know how much he’ll be roasted😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen &amp; hallelujah! Dogs are the best! God, please if they could live longer? Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen sister! You are a target of the trolls because they are TERRIFIED of truth tellers. Keep the faith @AOC!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@life_of_jennie @CaliKate28 Happpppppyyyyy BIRTHDAY Katie! We love you! Hope you have a great day! See you soon 😘 https://t.co/yg4dDHlEcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @RoaringRiotZ of @roaringriot for getting his raffle tickets today... Do YOU have yours yet?:… https://t.co/xe5LKhXVnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mraspinall @aweninspiration @tracyscottkelly @SJSaragusa @DrMaxineWalters @fablefy @melanie_korach Be careful… https://t.co/U5tf0dybaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW: Pres. #Trump meets with N. Korea's Kim Jong Un in #Vietnam https://t.co/06RsKJigO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@franknobenjamin You right but don’t say it like that say jigging or mo head ... the other way sounds weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chubbychicken @michaelcoren But even law is subject to interpretation. Spirit of the law or letter of the law?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer It is a desired scenario  Too bad. Trump supporters are not vicious or criminal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trade Chief Dumbs Down Contract Term After Donald Trump Doesn't Get It https://t.co/cFSXMEUGJr via @YahooNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roads2 @Iluvinspireu @ClockworkHamma @AnwarManwar004 @MelindaYoe @Jimmysimmonds1 @Peeperpea29 @SherryBretz05… https://t.co/QV0kp9lz9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBLievers @ammawhiney @LaurentianU @LaurentianMine That’s awesome! Congrats @LaurentianMine Team 👏#MineRescue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyeSportsRadio I’ve been to Allen Fieldhouse in Lawrence. Several times. Bud Walton is WAY better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have such a problem with their language, accent, or incorrect grammar then go somewhere else or do your nails at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackDaniels_US Not to mention the JD story in getting suffrage The Jack Daniel's Suite in Tenn. The Anti lobbyists… https://t.co/X1bON9O1FO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you take all the people on the commuter rail, put them in cars, how does traffic look?  Uh huh. The infrastructu… https://t.co/mLI3q1wd94]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shorty patiently waiting to see the vet #furmommalife @ Northpointe Veterinary Hospital https://t.co/GAYyCpnRJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that groundhog said spring was coming early? I’m ready to not see snow any day now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chaney was what?   Two years @amycharvey #NeverForget https://t.co/ybG2UAeTmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love that the Jonas Brothers have always just been these dorky boys and they still are and I HAVE A LOT OF F… https://t.co/MURjZMx5hH]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO here for this!!!! Keep the music coming @jonasbrothers https://t.co/KNOdZ40za8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My therapist asked me if the cultural differences in my relationship cause problems... I truly never thought about it]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Kim put that video of her singing that song that was the final straw 😭]]></document></documents></author>