<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Alan Lyszczarczyk completes a birthday hat trick with an overtime winner!  Assists to Adam Varga and Cole Schwindt… https://t.co/Nxk6FgMtPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stefsaysgovols Why were you paying? I never let the woman pay. Guess i am just to okd fashioned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are a few of my #thriftscores these are all up for sale except the #footjoy that sold immediately it was reall… https://t.co/Uqq9om2CZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Biscuits To A Bear by @levelbeer/@LaurelwoodBeer at @levelbeer — https://t.co/Ysw6HPT1T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @Sylviawimberly1 @realDonaldTrump It's like he's someone's poodle instead leader of the free world.… https://t.co/ABQz5CMxxj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when milanandrea turned 16?! Well guess what, it’s been two years and today she’s 18. Happy Birthday Milan… https://t.co/oIPfDRqX8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching the 2019 @SEC Women's Basketball Tournament: (8) @LadyVol_Hoops vs (9) @LSUwbkb recorded from the… https://t.co/AgaJTeNho4]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t think twice about putting that hat on but when they get there ass whooped they wonder why after.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNaug10 @db3imaging @LiveDirtUpdates @Koltengouse @knoxvilleraces @WorldofOutlaws @braddoty18 @WilliamsGrove… https://t.co/Seegh3crkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopTradersLive My pleasure Niels, it’s wonderful content (SIS &amp; TTU) and worth sharing. Not to mention… https://t.co/Ut8ptkhsS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will recline my seat back the allowable 2.5 inches on any flight I damn well please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes #Hearties #WCTH #HeavenWouldBeSeasonSeven @hallmarkchannel @SCHeartHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaunabrail Whoa. The book’s lack of varied expert perspectives is deeply problematic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[-Lost my phone charger on Monday  -Ordered a new one on Amazon and got it yesterday  -Lost the new one today :,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just don’t know point in firing him with a little over 20 games left to try and go on some crazy run to get the 8 s… https://t.co/WaJ2rNnMMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BburgHSBruins @blacksburgxctf big congrats to Ellie St. Martin your 4A State Runner-Up in the Girls High Jump #JumpHigh #Bruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSerrano @_BrittJo Oatmeal raisin never gets any love and it makes me sad. The truth is that all other cookies crumble in comparison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My real job and volunteer advocacy collide. "New and Contemporary" dining at #mariadbopenworks @RailPassengers… https://t.co/OeHn8I4qAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTSNOWman1 @EdValleeWx Just saw Bernie’s periscope, only has us for 1-3” by Monday morning, with that storm. Said… https://t.co/ZogKdkzCpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonjour mesdemoiselles je suis tout au sujet de camouflage d’hiver… donnez-moi votre dentelle embrasser mes larmes… https://t.co/5fJwRMXd7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Orlando and want to run with a group? Wanna meet new friends, runners, smelly strangers? This is just a few of t… https://t.co/330tURACRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Craig_Odinson @hitman604 @Aug1405 I’ve smoked a lot in my 56 years on this beautiful planet. @KamalaHarris is just… https://t.co/7BYSzFebvw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading out to North Jersey to support  @JNFUSA #JNFuture North/Central Jersey chapter for "JNFuture Presents: Quee… https://t.co/H8NgF3t05y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#kodakcarousel #slidetray #kodak #slide #slideshow  Unfortunately there weren’t any slides. @ Winter Park, Florida https://t.co/Zqi8FVVGX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice Mario wins the Jeopardy Champion, Ice Mario grand total is $20,390,000. https://t.co/1gt2mTmiqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FastCompany Hi, Abercrombie and Fitch has Made in USA. #AbercrombieandFitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbarmyman2 @dmcallister26 It's not just players that need supporting. This protest was in response to an attack… https://t.co/pKzRfroS17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdmontonJack The Oilers have 2 fourth lines. Not a lot of teams have that luxury]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m watching Legend with Tom Cruise (don’t judge) ad he’s running around in gold chain mail that looks like a beade… https://t.co/FHnxTeCHsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rex_rexchapman I’m pretty sure that’s Grayson Allen — former Duke player — practicing his famous flop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maeve_elder Thank u ! Im thankful for all of my liberal supporters. Very nice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elingeniero2000 @rgilzuarth Leyes a modo? Como se llama el cambio de ley en el FCE para que Taibo sea director? O… https://t.co/Xy6jXpuG2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh well.... I think Will Smith is so good he can pull off any roll.... #WillSmith]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tusitalatale I would say the Civil War was a highpoint because it ended slavery.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Herd Dat! Another recording in the books! Episode 53 and 30 extra Tall Talk minutes will be out tomorrow! Have a gr… https://t.co/mzi0wb8EZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_REX1991 @BaylorMBB @ViewFromHill That snow is no joke. Be safe. Thanks for making the trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@DTHballet at 50: “It's an incredible responsibility as Black classical artists to forge a new identity for this c… https://t.co/LpZymi4UVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barmore27 @KAG4All It wouldn’t have been if he was reading from a Muslim Book.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to get #preciousmetals all most at #nocost to you. Information can be seen here https://t.co/EPPeWLh9xF  Thank… https://t.co/AX1gIEeDSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#truth #discernment #word #student #studentoftheword #study #openarms #youmatterhere #lincoln #lincolnil… https://t.co/zKfpukOubT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano Guess it will be declared a mistrial now and he will walk free with all of his assets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madisyn_5 😂😂 that’s great. i can’t believe how it’s literally everywhere 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatsham87 @halcyon008 @Bryan_Gelfand @steveflarmature @969thegame I have argued that we need to make it affordabl… https://t.co/J8eaCPjdcn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joel7Richardson @oscoopie @DrMichaelLBrown @realRickWiles Ashkenazi jews control international banking including t… https://t.co/u8fbM5GwVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE you missed out again on inducting a legend into the HOF. Why wait till after they die to give them the honor.… https://t.co/Ca8Muc7S85]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bout to call whoever I need to call to fix all these damn potholes dawg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity This is very sad, maybe we should investigate them. They didn’t become millionaires on there Congress salaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@butterfliesblue Lol I’m not offended, only curious. Just looks like some naked black people to me 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dddeniser Live footage of me on that dumb bitch juice https://t.co/hpHinHkpnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByTimReynolds I thought it was funny. Not disrespectful to the press and he made the statements work with the ques… https://t.co/PvEOPynb9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheThirstyWench YOU'VE BEEN DATING ROBIN, I DIDN'T WANNA ASSUME ANYTHING]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with you Hayes. Like someone said earlier, folks see Montour and Fowler skate and tend to overrate them as… https://t.co/fbdEvYTzdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[But patricia steere is a lizard person. Reptilian media elite sent to brain wash us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World Wide Web — not the internet — turns 30 years old https://t.co/jhLx1hkSuj via @voxdotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctornk In which the internet dictates the exact number of lolis to be posted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell I’m sick of hearing about mueller, can’t the Democrats just face the truth.    LET IT GO!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew it was you, Fredo Bob. #floridagodfather https://t.co/RSpWBpsMiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaranjaKeita @kzshabazz @carrielogo @Blacks4Peace @IMIXWHATILIKE @ajamubaraka @TrueGame17 @citeblackwomen… https://t.co/V9575rnVsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltUS_ARC @DieterFrikadell @EdDarrell @JamesRider3 @puremoneylife @rln_nelson @wlbeeton @BubbasRanch… https://t.co/B9v17T65Co]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday breakfast and coffee run! @ McDonald's https://t.co/wGaNruKCNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston, MA: the answer folk's is blowing in the wind. "The answer, my friend, IS BLOWING IN THE WIND. Bob Dylan sin… https://t.co/ZQH8gg6wRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djbeema I have friends who did, I just had a visceral dislike from the moment I saw him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portland continues to put numbers in attack. Not all out, certainly, but more than 3 attacking players, leaving the… https://t.co/ZLi08cYK9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[TIL @TuckerCarlson was a guest on Bubba the Love Sponge Show w/ @TheBubbaArmy for years, most recently last Novembe… https://t.co/kC4qy25gHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had In-N-Out burger last month and it was trash. So I would assume whataburger is better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for Malik Jackson returning to the #Broncos.  Big D-lineman is signing a three-year deal with the #Eagles. #NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Regrann from https://t.co/ucEBmj9TEp  -  Beautiful Greece🇬🇷 , beautiful Crete❣Check out author's marvelous gallery… https://t.co/CtjnWN0BMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Betcha they try to leave you at the Flying J while you are hovering over the can...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOCpress Alexandra, if the FEC prosecutes you, its because you are entitled and broke the law! #stupiddeep… https://t.co/XSicKXCAKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aj_Stertz @CLJohnson58 @juliojones_11 When Hopkins has a developed QB throwing to him, it’s all over. Julio’s has… https://t.co/sH1GaWBqBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't blame them crab legs bomb af that's what I be getting I'd fight for the last crab leg.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jovempan se recusa a escrever a verdade! #mentira #indenizacao #indenizar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lost Nation Sports Park WEST - @lnsportspark in Lorain, OH https://t.co/1NSXB3d7TZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonmenon @SLNTPLNT @SilentGarrett @AlexreneC @mitchastark wtf why is gary wearing shoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pakistan Navy thwarts attempt by Indian submarine to enter Pakistani waters  https://t.co/ybl6Te76oF]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Sonics still existed I doubt Durant would've ever left the franchise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachRudi44 From the beginning of the game they were acting like it was a mouse playing an elephant. TVCS and Lega… https://t.co/FMdw1OjfNr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl That is an ugly visual. You dead.  Holding a dildo. Someone trying to take it from you.   Happy Fat Tuesday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceyBVoice @Username1716 @Rakpenguin63 @ellewoodsgolfs @TheRickyDavila No worries 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaltyandLit @justbolts @njmcal @BrownMonike @KamalaHarris Well if they are Christian lgbt people why should they b… https://t.co/58sEk2BnhH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sjurcak @JimLaPorta Direct oversight is not required 24-7, but a full understanding of the Marines under your char… https://t.co/sxUnTx9QB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @pewdrdad At what point will #Democrats raise their voices in condemnation against vile haters in their… https://t.co/ILOYqGjN4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahNewmanWAND @chaddare @DHSVikings118 @wandtvnews Was his house in Moline as a Maroon or East Moline as a Panthe… https://t.co/6Z1sdsIwol]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those eager to use #bitcoins to pay for #coffee, @Starbucks (which accepts twice as many forms of payment as yo… https://t.co/bMWiOD5LIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I guess that’s the nail in the coffin. My 2nd shipment from @SunBasketMeals hasn’t arrived within the deliver… https://t.co/UWNuZAuVkt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eddielack you can’t have rationale discussions with irrational people...since December Canes attendance is up with… https://t.co/iEcnDEsogM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Weddle a cheap upgrade at safety @nickeatman for the @dallascowboys?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michveezy Pretty much, sometimes I forget I'm not the only one living in this hellscape of ignorance 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the time you might not see what God isbtrying to tell you, but if you continue down that path I promise that God… https://t.co/bb5swCyzUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t even check to see if I made it home safely but you wanna fuck. NEXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benni1028 @yesnicksearcy @maria_russo @peterbakernyt Of course Fox is wrong and everyone else is right. It’s in yo… https://t.co/hOi2xSdHFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan. Ryan. Ryan. Of course she’ll be punished or maybe her hack boyfriend will be fed to the lions.  On the other… https://t.co/c8tLKO6rkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so sorry but I can’t do techno, edm, trance, dubstep...etc... not my scene. I feel like punching someone with a… https://t.co/sS3dXInrHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 year challenge with @TomReller! 2014 in London versus 2019 at @NFAISForum in Virginia. #Elsebier still going stro… https://t.co/EpBD7gpXAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nemak USA/CAN Headquarters - @nemakofficial in Southfield, MI https://t.co/59WjYlBix3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, you should love those around you.  Maybe, love that new car, or relationship, BUT your heart should be s… https://t.co/YLgsDEXyOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me go ahead and purge the list. Especially the ppl who are dead weight!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People love introducing you as “uncle” when it’s close to they kids birthday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rollicking_R8R Outside of Bell there’s no offensive FA that get me excited. I feel like Ingram could be a solid da… https://t.co/MMM8XxDl7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanluiscano aquí me tienes desde las 3:00 am contigo no me quedo dormido tienes unos puntazos buenísimos.  Te lle… https://t.co/7JtElmkixH]]></document></documents></author>