<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@jguaido Estos esbirros asesinos quieren violencia y sangre. Tienen armas y respaldo del régimen.  Pacíficamente no… https://t.co/CwCxTQ02a3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yours0000truly Oh no no no, just doing a different type of flow than usual. Apparently its called Buti yoga]]></document><document><![CDATA[She claims to know @leonardmaltin and his wife and daughter. But , does not tag any of them in her tweet to let the… https://t.co/qh21KYBVrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse ...and yet, no mention of Russia and it's attack our election, the very heart of our democracy. Hmmm....wonder why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerardoSarcasmo @EvaMariaSeFue_ Mmmmm ok . Nunca he visto una cédula de Bogotá por 80]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaysHummingbird @smilon713 Jared made money off of treasonous activity. I am shocked, shocked I tell you, shocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goood Saturday 🥰 #TampaOutcall available 24/7🌇🌃 #TampaIncall only at certain times🤷🏻‍♀️ I travel all over Florida🤗… https://t.co/pYmji3VC7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaysbookman I certainly remember. @sendavidperdue is an embarrassment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As with others that unselfishly give of their talents-u have no idea how much the support means to these officers,… https://t.co/pleYIZbhTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Puedes celar y prohibirle mil cosas a tu pareja, pero si quiere serte infiel, va a terminar siéndolo. Así como tamb… https://t.co/qS4awIQscH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday, that’s the first that happened my Orchid is is blooming, usually I just kill plants😔 I guess just… https://t.co/ILtwv3LmSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pepesgrandma @RealTrumpLady Ms Bug Eyes how do you figure that Republicans won't have to deal with the climate cha… https://t.co/pPzMFVCOyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited this Thursday, hosting free Do-it-herself. Learn to build a Pipe Coat Hanger at the Do-It-Herself workshop… https://t.co/kl7SmYhweO]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤓 it with @mattdanielwx at the Barons Weather Conference!  @WBRCweather https://t.co/rx1domsDpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[At noon, I’m taking the #PolarPlunge at the Ramsey Lake Boat Launch with community leaders like @TheNewHot935’s… https://t.co/hVfKO9Rf78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For the record, we liked you better when you were in Vietnam. Go back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hwinkler4real It seems that the hearts of the children who fought desegregation never opened up towards their fell… https://t.co/bB3qtqNQxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Makedni @misssjdoe @ak_square9 @KSpartiatis @M0N1KA_ @MacoStyle007 @bryant_luca @peacock1956 @dieselino07… https://t.co/BR1BGLrUmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#playing #piano #happy #kids #musica @ Coconut Creek, Florida https://t.co/wbkSwIdf79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smasood42 other sources are saying it’s apparently “unlikely” so you may be ok 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TLangley99 🤣🤣🤣Because there is #NoWayThrough if there's a #Wall, right @realDonaldTrump? That there #Tunnel was a… https://t.co/eiA4BwXjCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourMorning @weathernetwork Moonset to the west, sunrise to the east. -28 C #muskratlake #cobden #whitewater… https://t.co/wsFNbeFYrk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarisaLancione Salt Pepper. Now if you go with ground add to taste because it's gonna get spicy. 2-3 tbsp (or more… https://t.co/WYKMKbu6Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[being out here is the most positive thing that's happened in a while https://t.co/9cLrNFVZI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think a good deal of them should  be named after “Trump”, “NRA” and many of our southern politicians, (especially… https://t.co/SEX2SaMH7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsMollyRachael Critical lol! Trump not being elected in 2020! Cra cra @MsMollyRachael .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer vi la revisión de mi primer libro! “Emigrar y Emprender” Lo que una mujer debe saber antes de intentarlo.  Pro… https://t.co/3UM1y5QiDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan was so emotional, so angry. Poor thing, maybe he should use a softer, more likeable tone and smile more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this will make you snicker. For the mother who loves puns. https://t.co/ASMfb6DB4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[All eyes are on Washington, D.C. today where @realDonaldTrump’s former lawyer Michael Cohen (@MichaelCohen212) is a… https://t.co/WwOhzH0CIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[United States Department of Agriculture (USDA): USDA- update your definition of livestock-!!!!! - Sign the Petition… https://t.co/zG8GHAcuDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter Would you ever consider getting your pet high?🤔🤔😂😂 Just a question I’m throwing out there...personally… https://t.co/XzTtCANWki]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS! SO WONDERFUL TO SEE YOUR BUSINESS GROW. #dreamscometrue  Reposted from vinestmarket  -  E V E R Y… https://t.co/dM8P6UOoTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say it... If you have to apologize multiple times back to back in a relationship and claim that it will n… https://t.co/CFvxw20Dgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDiesel @BornReady2Pod @ScotPollard31 @leafsquad22 Wait - this has been a mystery for months...share!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfessorCrunk Saw this! ❤️ Will be sharing with DC1 chapter of @GOGbookclub this weekend at our meeting discussing #EloquentRage]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Highland and butterfield rd in Lombard, IL https://t.co/1Gk2AxGCc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamsClub I have an offer for 45.00 membership and get 45.00 in approved items. What are the items?? Can you point… https://t.co/Bl02FjJPx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannon_caitlyn Kevin was always my favorite. 😂 My sister was struggling between Nick and Joe with our friends and… https://t.co/1HNdo6ZgpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 61 of Kate's shoes and socks. Today doubling up with the hubby for double the Vans. #shoes #shoesaddict https://t.co/gSRsOmsEYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EpiSconroy It was super fun!! The kids there were generally a little older than my daughter (who is turning 7 in 2… https://t.co/5i6k4BBPoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TechySewell Between the weather and my exhaustion I feel like I could be getting sick! And I think it’s just tired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: Social activism doesn’t excuse you from doing shitty things in other aspects of your life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[EN PRIMEUR 🏡🏠  2 CAC / BRDM  1 SDB / BATH  1 GARAGE  $389,000.00 MLS 27750348 . 📲 514.898.4372 📧 jtaganyi@londonogr… https://t.co/cRikQL7TMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Groomer today just outside the second story window at Auburn Ski Club.  Awesomeness!  Here's to a nice long sea… https://t.co/6CQJXgQi6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmPharmD @laxswamy @RachelBPharmD PRN kitkat Q15mins for hanger and rage 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it to round two of the all author cover contest, need more votes to continue on though https://t.co/YzkbIMkGFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazzJennings__ Try not to let haters, like his mom get to you. Some people are just ignorant and some just extremist. good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's no better time to prioritize your over-all wellness but now. So happy that the @montagebh spa is everything… https://t.co/IwTiJDj71A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day at an Arizona dog park 😂🤣 #coyote #somuchfun #Arizona https://t.co/aQGZbWCFkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turned out to be Sarah Enloe instead who shared thoughts about Shakespeare as a place to consider politics in Pragu… https://t.co/I0dXkvfM8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerriLutaaya They are doing amazing work! A Scarborough original!!! 🙌🏿🙌🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiemartens1 I WAS GOING TO TEXT YOU  I realized how rude it was for me to ask Twitter before my personal nutritionist I'm sorry dr. Katie]]></document><document><![CDATA[There Is a Better Way to Teach Students with Learning Disabilities https://t.co/eWUv8ebBvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RalphGMWorks Poor idiot! Has no idea what’s going on. He should go and see by himself what’s going on. Idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurvivorManSeth I just paid $35 to do it online! I’ll cheat and do this crap myself😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaughtSpy @baseballcrank As long as the electoral college decides who wins, third-party candidates can only be spo… https://t.co/Hf8yBl34bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nocontextpawnee “I love your hair” “Thank you it’s genetic and unattainable”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to The Way It Was by @backstreetboys on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/4Dch5RNnWi https://t.co/q1ttFMih69]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care how bitchy it looks to check your receipt and watch when they ringing up yo shit... at least I’m not g… https://t.co/Zwcq1zxLTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michelle Neeley completed the Ascension Seton Austin Marathon! Time 05:54:13 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/LVN0ZIhEUh #RunAustin]]></document><document><![CDATA[📚 Если много о чём-то спрашивают, это знак, что пора написать об этом статью в блог 😃📝  Собрала наконец-то в пост о… https://t.co/mK0FXJHjyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelianblack Where the hell did #Fabio get $200K? Dude's done absolute shit for years. 🤨🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariannMeedWard Holt Dr. is also bad. The drivers come down too fast making it dangerous as well as bad ploughing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiyyahlong I’m just the type of bitch to pronounce it nuh-tro(ctogon)-sha cause it’s really not some “omg wtf” kin… https://t.co/5gSNHSjTLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you NHTI future Nurses for a fun &amp; meaningful day!! @NHTI @coreenggs #softskills #comunication… https://t.co/Df68mSGTOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wayne State president asks for investigation as board battle heats up https://t.co/MtQ07aPj3b via @crainsdetroit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker You're a disgrace to the profession of law, having no idea the concept of truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, not ashamed to speak his mind. Too often this is how we are viewed by Young Politicians and the Medical Commun… https://t.co/ZgPWG68bOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why no one should rely on a rodent to predict the weather. 😬❄️ https://t.co/GMIw6aphXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxMcReynolds @emLEbaldwin I don’t eat fish I eat avocado rolls, and yes I work at men’s club?? Ok hahahhah]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd @OfficeSigns workout is in the books!!! Thanks to @SandieFromOSC for leading us in a fun Zumba class!! https://t.co/x4OLQbERp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this kinda ignorant to post cuz flint still ain’t got clean water 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdonisPaulAP @AttackBunny1970 @SuitYourselfToo @FantomaSpirit @RealMissSteam @ProSouth_ @TheCognificent1… https://t.co/0eRmbaq1tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I recently attended an NBA heritage night and I thought it was going to be just like this...I should’ve known it wo… https://t.co/mF2XhwAHWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I turn my brightness down all the way but it’s still way too bright ... https://t.co/U3JL0Nx7Yb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder to purchase your Madison Academic yearbook. This will be the last week to purchase. Deadline for… https://t.co/EFFkaQ5wIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @FoxNews How is this so since Muellers report has not been released? But you know this how there is no collision?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatTimpf Most everyone in the Congress voted to secure the border at one time now that we have a man in office tha… https://t.co/tYJto9BGtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking, the hard way. Thanks @lisazari1 for the pic from shakennotstirrednyc @ The Cutting Room https://t.co/8qko0Mia65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo idk why guys on social media get butt hurt over truck make &amp; models 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet he still uses the animal pictures on a school bus to recognize which bus to get on. #Stablegenius]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need this bed. You gotta make a sacrifice before entering 😂😤♥️ https://t.co/VKUSIjNaNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day two of #PalmValleyPBL Instructional Coaching. I know there’s great that bye in store! #pblworks @PVSFirebirds  @PBLWorks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraKeathley: Child I feel you are kinda a train wreck today.  Child: I kinda have a lot to deal with right now.… https://t.co/Z2xk5VEfOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLTWorg @Inc @ruby_rios_ Can’t wait to listen to this one! TY @PLTWorg for this awesome podcast series]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is the last organic lab before spring break and I have said: “I volunteer as tribute” “Just like Harry Potter” a… https://t.co/n1z1osp721]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSantang5 @ginatognoni She has to know she’ll lose Nick. And Sharon should have known Rey’s slime. Love Brittany taking him on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: I just spoke with students and parents at Terre Haute South Vigo High School. One student tells me he waite… https://t.co/8DaZq8AHi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talkalot_sir @StefanMolyneux The number of slaves bought, sold, traded ect at this very moment are in the 10s of m… https://t.co/iB475QsAit]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Venezuela, massive blackout continues as Maduro blames U.S. for outages https://t.co/SvZ3sWt4w3]]></document><document><![CDATA[it rlly bugs me when people say "men / white ppl aint sh*t" and literally no one cares or will just agree. last tim… https://t.co/ZpKDla5vqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially #5 since chances are you probably don’t know the details of the situation 😳 be careful what you say!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have to wait a half hour for my sister to get off work so i can go home someone talk to me(:]]></document><document><![CDATA[How am I supposed to get out of bed when bryce has wrapped me up in his arms and the kittens are purring and cuddli… https://t.co/jBFMmO9zQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHY ARE YOU HOES SO WORRIED ABOUT OUR LIFES?????? DONT YOU HAVE YOUR OWN LIFE MF?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just feel like fighting someone today. It’s really not my day today and it’s only 1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're at Lake Murray Presbyterian Church today for some Carolina BubbleBall! lakemurraypresbyyouth @ Lake Murray Pr… https://t.co/WaLFEoQWeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Temple Honors the Egyptian Queen Who Ruled as King https://t.co/31yMtfO2gq via @NatGeoTravel]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll admit, Antonio Brown is one of the weirder examples of the “Madden Curse” being real... definitely didn’t see this coming.]]></document></documents></author>