<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TheTalkCBS Not necessarily it could be based on physical ailments doesn’t have to be anything else wrong in the relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the... LL Cool J dropped an album titled “Authentic” and I knew nothing about it. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEED IT. AS YOU KNOW TO STORE ABOUT 6 MILLION DOLLARS I WILL NEED THOSE BANKS. THEIR SERVICE AND PROBLEM SALVING ST… https://t.co/2BQPy26nQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 170 Trace Michelson finished 1-2 as well. He did a great job for us this season. Wrestling varsity at 182 pounds… https://t.co/7acO8BcuRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when my girl had went through my phone and presented me with all evidence]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrettHakey @MileyCylas I’ve asked 5 uvm employees what the president even does and none have been able to answer me yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebuckeyegamer @kjrevia Diana got a bath yesterday. She was up to about 6 lbs when wet.  The limp is normal for h… https://t.co/qkcim8nOnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hartaj24 Lol come the fuck on. Trump has a history of homophobia and doing things to hurt the gay and trans commun… https://t.co/SSaHRUNcqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet @nowthisnews All this is technically true.  Doesn’t change the fact that this proves that Tucker is a… https://t.co/43z4mOa0St]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need the ALC filled every morning. STAAR test is right around the corner. Tell a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bigtanktv Hayden Rubin C/OG 2 Star Center (RICS) #74 @hdrubin35  6’5” 295lb Riverwood ICS GPA 4.0 SAT 1350 https://t.co/cv9Ayh6pHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BishopBronner @BishopBronner this remind me of a poem that was in the movie Coach Carter, always love using it whe… https://t.co/PbRhouVRT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no one that hates Ohio State sports more than @jason_hostetter not even a Michigan fan lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, happy hump day! The storm is moving on... but only after leaving a bit of a mess. Today the thaw begi… https://t.co/Y1Zj3HXFJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum @IlhanMN Free Speech pal - unless you think others need some "special type" of permission to speak… https://t.co/ZpJBxsFMb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stallionlive @tmrwstulips Damn, I really need to update my phone in order to make this funny.  fuck... https://t.co/PP746w7wJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine As opposed to Slick Willie the Serial Rapist, Ted Kennedy the lady killer, Jack Kennedy who made T… https://t.co/pmZullWNyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess it's my day to RT every book I haven't read. Damn there are a lot of them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Finally? Finally? These perverts have known about this for over 50 years. They only acknowledge it now… https://t.co/K1iKgcBWgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekBlasberg THIS NOTE IS LegA-L tender WWW A-LL debts public And privAte  F O R.    Atlanta, Georgia WWW. Flower… https://t.co/hcNLiZatnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goto_blue @JackDeeth @original_FoBoT @SwiftOnSecurity Underrated tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@batterbarrera @NFL My bad it was Trent Brown. He’s been the only signing thus far. Show start]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi in Texas signing Patron Saint of Shade poster. Love it! #Democrats2020 https://t.co/yHpF0BtTAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st time taking class at @OTFBrandon @orangetheory Definitely going to come back here! Amazing studio! And of cours… https://t.co/jUBVNMIxdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indian person I know: “I want a fuckin’ waaaar. These fuckers won’t listeeeen.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet another athletes life ruined  and nobody seems to care. It only matters when the athlete is in the wrong appare… https://t.co/T4Kyzedoyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nhjordan1 @lyle_jarvis chance you’re in luck and it falls below the 52-week low of $60 into your price range, i’d keep a close eye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto fue el 3 de julio del año pasado. Fin de una era del Real Madrid! Fuera Cristiano y Zidane era de suponerse qu… https://t.co/b8kQYPUqsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jill4olemiss @ShannonDingle @whiskytngofxtrt @mythicalmarsey Baptized into church at first Methodist, Albertville, Alabama at 11 years old]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks the beginning of what will become one of the most difficult years of school and my life. May we be chal… https://t.co/zOjvdABJGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What: Tickets bro! Why: To see my band Okami come play along with Whitechapel, Dying Fetus, Spite, and more Where:… https://t.co/SahH9TibRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nepats263 @MarkDanielsPJ @PatsFanPJ I’d let hogan walk, loved his contributions with the team on our run to SB 51… https://t.co/CqnLGFc1ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jarmannoo she’s one of the worst people i’ve ever met. she’s disingenuous, uninformed, and to top it all off she h… https://t.co/a2Nu08OR9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[And my week gets better as Microsoft’s latest patch hosed my computer. Yay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anamariecox It was just meh but Exley acting like a goofball in the snow helped]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as Jesus condemns as hypocrites those who make an ostentatious display of praying, one can say the same thing… https://t.co/lMaUX3ai50]]></document><document><![CDATA[WADE, PAULITTE charged with FAILURE MAINTAIN FINANCIAL RESPONSIBILITY in #HOUSTON - https://t.co/HJ6qfPvUHn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@westdrea @Alexzandria_1 @YallAintShitTho You tryna say I ain’t good enough? 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so refreshing to speak about literature with folks. Makes my day, everyday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarkNt3 @marcorubio @RedCross 1) the same election that Guaido won the National Assembly, Maduro won the Presidenc… https://t.co/A7DCESN6D9]]></document><document><![CDATA[upon being in new york for 2 days i have realized that if i were to live here i’d be fat, broke but highly caffeinated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to Go!    Dustin Johnson, Bubba Watson and the rest of the morning players are about to Tee-off this afternoo… https://t.co/jYQgDbWPsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Witten is back the move was to help them not draft a TE !! He is helping Garett !! All I know  is on defense… https://t.co/K2VIhqyD4O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so excited to join my friends @MarandaTV and @MichaelMcLeieer at the Baby and Family Expo in @DowntownKzoo.  We… https://t.co/5FYLp2MhFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just bought the Daenerys covered Entertainment Weekly magazine. It’s gonna be nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new @POWERGolfSF gear is starting to arrive... https://t.co/pKebDkqiJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTyson  hey champ! Come to Birmingham, Al. To promote        IRON ENERGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theyearofelan It’s fun that’s all and maybe some of us secretly want to be British - I prefer @montypython for exa… https://t.co/0M5PyRFim2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TGIFRISKY ... Rob Keith, “in-session”, recording new 2DC+1 show airing Tuesday, March 5th, ya heard👂🏽  exclusively… https://t.co/YyzsZdOKNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ubercapper It’s a big picture decision. There would be too many reasons to list, but a vet scratch takes it out of… https://t.co/DFXKuxDB3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dozens more animals rescued from ranch in Skiatook after horse saved from frozen pond https://t.co/uRDrUVWZop via @tulsaworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every good thing must come to an end, thank you Clarkston Wrestling for these past 4 years! #4thinthestate @ Ford F… https://t.co/aioBekWtQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SB15 is so messy we have no idea how many other local protections could be affected. And honestly, can we trust TX… https://t.co/kgI9u9BHGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only Momo Challenge I care about is how many Tibetan dumplings I can eat https://t.co/lRRgeTXkyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladygaga  I just watched"A star is born"!! It was such a great movie and it really high home with the ending!! I h… https://t.co/hqnz7uw0Fk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! Really I had no clue, thanks for everyone who make this site fun!… https://t.co/imVFEdF9a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast One of the reasons I haven’t watched CNN in quite a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Sudan Collins old hometown of caribou Maine in class B high school basketball state champ tournament today… https://t.co/MOTLnfjPQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMcCook44 I agree 100%, loved watching him on Beverly Hills 90210 and many other shows and films.  Also loved w… https://t.co/6gHKtUi0cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Ole Gunnar Solskjaer for making me love soccer again❤️⚽️ @ManUtd #GGMU 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[“loving is easy, you had me fucked up...it’s easy when everything’s perfect; please don’t change a single little th… https://t.co/SVG0h1NAR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kalzingis @JoshGoldenTheS What u know about the willie 😂😂😂 Gun Ru kids!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a αβ Project: Mandarina Haze by @GlenwoodBrewPub at @glenwoodbrewpub — https://t.co/u9L8ufq4pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SylviaFOX32 Good morning, Sylvia! I hope you have yourself a nice day at work, and a blessed day! Thanks for always being awesome!👍😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTENTION #UNC #TarHeelNation Limited edition vintage logo #Tarheel tees... get yours now. #GoHeels #beatdook… https://t.co/OJJLKyflGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday March 1 - The 5-Minute Fix:     Pelosi to Dems: 'We are either a team or we’re not'    Via @washingtonpost… https://t.co/7zEwJWdn86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevLaurieinLex @KaraNSlade I do, however, still have and use the bookmark that the Middler class made for our Seni… https://t.co/jDLMfXkAIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meisterbuerger And almost no saw it live. That's something I still can't believe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you hear that @Suns . It’s pull the trigger lmao.  @brawadis #gettinghypedfornothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[All Set #Sound #Backline #LuisVargas #jimmysound @ Whiskey North https://t.co/FHSLYmVSbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh the enemy works so hard for no gain! After an amazing, Spirit filled day for the Women’s Conference at Fayette F… https://t.co/Q5yL9PrkKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@H2Omaker71 @JamieOber8590 He may only bat around .250 but in that tiny ass stadium he is gonna hit 50 HRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m thrilled that we’ve recruited David Abel as our new Managing Director for English Theatre. Equally thrilled tha… https://t.co/8KXSqrKySE]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@fred_guttenberg  Here is the link as well from @hometownhockey_  &amp; @Sportsnet Twitter pages… https://t.co/rC1ybT8YwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/bNu6ymsWhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackets shutting the door here lately. That combined with Bobrovsky makes for an uphill climb. #Blackhawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickLuvBamaFB @ABC4Devon @suraechinn @abc4utah Oh yeah! #NationalPoundCakeDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA  You two weeks late! Oye Viejo! @oldmanebro   You ever about this Andrew guy before? https://t.co/Rc9DsYpjkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@azul_vieja Se gastó mucho, pero se gastó bien? La ofensiva desde el torneo anterior no producía. Hay varias caderi… https://t.co/itwn10sv04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec How long  were they watching this place just waiting for the right fish to come along? Right being th… https://t.co/ZCF2gJfvTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This autumn I am thinking about going back to West Virginia again.  One of my favorite places to camp is up in Cana… https://t.co/2BskugAlcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 Now I would remind you, brothers, of the gospel I preached to you, which you received, in which you stand, 2 and… https://t.co/oiXD7iwFWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[This character annoyed me a bit but i got over it https://t.co/s87tXR6sPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is exactly why kids want snow days 😂. Good work getting them outta the house and playing! #FamilyMan]]></document><document><![CDATA[#stardust #rrbridge #overpass #newtopographics #photography #photograph #artphotography #fineartphotography… https://t.co/JmfNNivgNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's pick for US Ambassador to the UN withdraws nomination  https://t.co/SOr69aiMCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vwinstonv Para cuando controlan tu estupidez? Me parece que esta desbordada por un ataque cybernetico!!! Maldita e… https://t.co/R78WLKBTD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree @VanessaVanjie for the wining!!! @RuPaulsDragRace @RuPaul #DragRace]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the most attractive bi Asian on tinder and yet no one seems to swipe right. 💔👁👄👁💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood: (goodnight, I’ll see y’all tomorrow 10 AM sharp) https://t.co/TSkuWYEnl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a No Rules Vietnamese Porter (2018) by @Perrinbrewing @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/QxviaPZJN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final panel of the day at #MurderOnTheMenu-- more great writing inspiration from @tonyakappes11 @AngieGallion… https://t.co/tPbeRjj14i]]></document><document><![CDATA[#food brings everyone #together. #Happy 281 Day with #TeamCVS in #Rockland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenKissel @marcusparks The Godfather is aware of his shout out on the latest episode of LPOTL. https://t.co/kKIsMZBSby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexisKatie3 @dilruba_lees @DLees28 @CynthiaMark14 @VictoriaD6363 @Nata27Best @cheryllyndunn @TBGTNT May Almighty… https://t.co/SHwMfeOhZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surfermom77 This man is wright on there is good &amp; bad in ever race &amp; walk of life world wide]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn’t talk myself from attending the @IHSAA1 4A State Championship game.  👍🏽@lnwildcats #Bang! https://t.co/ZkTk8qmCnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Xavier fan at the bar:  “I’ll give what they did to 5/3rd a B-...” https://t.co/E6Uh8Iz1Tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu tienes 20 años metiéndonos la Supremacia de los Castros que bolas tienes tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertdunlap947 @Ed08792346 no worry, the dems will increase taxes for the evil rich people pay their "fair" share… https://t.co/jvyKzRA0kv]]></document></documents></author>