<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Debating whether I should turn my off later so I don't drunk text or tweet lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a toss up it needed the avocado 🥑  #eatlocal #lunch #weightlossjourney @ Dish Society https://t.co/39GQ6rPC3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the Biermann family more every episode of Dont be Tardy 😂 @Kimzolciak]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mirandalambert just got married and I’m drunk and emotional and about to cry 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shappy Totally true at the time, but if you look at the amazing work (numbers just released) being driven by… https://t.co/64RfTqMuSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @jonasbrothers  are trending and I don’t know how to deal with it. I’m so happy I could cry 😭 @joejonas @nickjonas @kevinjonas 😊❤️🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel hella bad for kylie.. like she deadass just lost her best friend. no matter how a friendship ends.. good or… https://t.co/FzbCsDMSRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dre_IAM Thank you! This morning, as I was reflecting, I’m amazed at the strength and power that I’ve gained!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeagleShiloh Beagles can squeeze into tight spots like a mouse. My boy could squeeze under a deck we had because w… https://t.co/aACu5JjIRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to love going into work at PBT, now I dread it..   And it’s gonna be my main job this summer.. something has… https://t.co/lnhcPcAZdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, of course.  No one stops to think; people just take sides without thinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Potosi English Brown Ale by @PotosiBrewingCo at @potosibrewingco — https://t.co/hei41L72En]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAZavaleta Eres de los pocos que sabe y hace periodismo, admiro y respeto tu trabajo. De pendejo no tienes nada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello people of earth. I’ve got something to say about this. https://t.co/JCJMrJQDd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddie_Runs @GarminFitness I can see it online just not on my phone for some reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY PARENTS GOT ME TICKETS TO @PreacherLawson FOR MY 21st BIRTHDAY I AM GONNA CRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to my masseuse Emily at The Grandover Hotel... best Massage ever🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[This all-star team @Jeopardy competition is unbelievably geeky! And, of course, I’m loving it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mick12346 @LeonardRoxon @TomTSEC @AGodlessWoman @BillTufts @FPVaughanIII @Keeks220305 @SpencerFernando @99freemind… https://t.co/PRnzm2dCeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marvil296 @DerekPa56710094 @CarlosD27801704 @pratoshnivedita @DansoyGomez @TheMerryCrystal @jill_magnussen… https://t.co/LxsoH8y9rR]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn't take much these days! I own a box of sharpies, if anyone needs one. For security purposes, that is, of c… https://t.co/6cOZIoPkC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone please teach the high school kids that being rude/annoying to your server as a joke is not actually funny. at. all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Since we're doing whataboutism today, whatabout your many false racists tweets, comments, policies, etc.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunrise this morning in Oneida! Happy Valentine’s Day! 😍💜❤️💕 @WBIRWeather @wbir https://t.co/F1dDiJOfPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet How is this violence continuing? These people are sick, twisted killers!   This has got to stop!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peek posted!! 🤩🤤 Check out my new pinned tweet 💋 https://t.co/Id9I6RTkbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys we are live a https://t.co/g3jb8dteLH live now on #twitch please join and mess with my cast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClementeCH En pocas palabras, lo importante aquí es nomás su dicho (de AMLO) Que estupidéz]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is amazing how stupid some people can be. #funniness #giggle #grin #cute https://t.co/2istak9OVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since @yashar has everyone talking about towels, I have to put out there that the real way to up your towel game is… https://t.co/V2z8DGzt2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you have a 5th or 6th grader who would like to play futsal at Shortridge High under direction of the high school… https://t.co/wXlDcjlwbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We celebrate all the amazing women across the globe on this special day! Happy International Women’s day!… https://t.co/j9Hvsi9rLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVERY SINGLE TIME ‼️‼️‼️‼️  #strongintelligentwomen #wednesday @ Financial District, Manhattan https://t.co/nYWf1mxvwc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annamccachren @Editer I like the way yinz think! Yeah, “take advantage of” and “apply” are promising options—thanks for that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghoragh Tal cual !!! Así me sentía !!! Como #LaPanteraRosa que la seguía la nube .🤣🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/UsHUTYRFqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ruger1976 “Breeding Soundness Exam” so we are seeing how his swimmers are swimmin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debber66 I don't think any on the Left of life is "Dump" They have an agenda that doesn't give a crap about Americ… https://t.co/Fk0SxO5Wgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where are the media? They are exactly where they want to be, instigators of violence against Trump supporters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world and happy Sunday.  We have heavy fog and light rain in Houston.  Perfect day to relax and enjoy… https://t.co/rwTeIb8oyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KEBrightbill From ages 3-8, I wasn’t allowed to go anywhere that involved service workers because they would say “… https://t.co/Qu8vO8NL82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump I TRUST OUR PRESIDENT PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP !!!!!! #MAGA #TRUMP2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[For all you Valentines Day peeps who don't have any idea what to give as a gift. ( 😂) https://t.co/aDapmNs9YZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[While showing off @FBISDSTEM projects at @FSMSFalcons Multicultural night (nerd culture rocks!) this young man watc… https://t.co/kOzTHwC07p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexbozikovic @aarts_michelle @myonlinelifenow @tdsb @TCDSB @JohnLorinc @tvo @HousingNowTO @OptionsforHomes… https://t.co/80TrgbDgpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the great opportunity to Keynote this event last year w @techmaverick... I’m SO STOKED to be going back to… https://t.co/MymWchuR4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little Monday inspiration from my own Harlem dining room. I absolutely hate for things to look like they are a pe… https://t.co/PNzhLpx2p4]]></document><document><![CDATA[With family!! But you don't know about that!! #rockypointemexico2019 #springbreak https://t.co/huRwIrGv3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson People claim voters without ID say it costs too much money, for instance, w no birth certificate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeekMill i tweeted you nearly everyyyyday when you was locked up. Was I the only one ? #askmeek]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am really so in love with my body and my boyfriend really made me love my body and see that I am a beautiful ass bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2 I tend to be an early adopter and instead of getting frustrated I try to find ways to incorporate new tools into… https://t.co/bzIgIBfxO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the flu. Jenni Lynn has pre-teen attitude issues. Joseph has endless energy. Joshua has a hockey tournament… https://t.co/7WiNRoFpRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepPressley They can’t even decide what to wear and you want them to vote???🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NumbersUSA What part of this NUMBER is to difficult for you to understand?  How about you host a job fair. https://t.co/by8iX4PJdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s okay, I didn’t want to celebrate president’s day anyway 👀 thx @VanderbiltU 😤👌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw @chrislhayes Bibi's close ties to this administration, is bringing down Israel's  image to the world a… https://t.co/DcmbVnGHot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1776BetsyRoss @DLoesch @valwayne Pretty sure it's over a year old. It was, I believe, follow by Sessions refusal t… https://t.co/jPZrzAFyb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJSchauer American should give EVERYONE riding on their 737 MAX 8s free drinks. 🍺☠️🥂💀🍷☠️🍹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unafraid unaware can't you see I am dying ? Wanna feel what is real anything is worth me trying..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss the way you’d wear your high socks and shorts on our Netflix nights make pizza rolls and have a few drinks.… https://t.co/PgNFGuFiha]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Everybody failed these black young girls”. Yup. That’s it right there. #rkellyinterview]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyNews I can’t believe big Pharma, they have a drug that could possibly save a child and they want the highest do… https://t.co/zU4ZLn54zl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jwheels74 @SFGiants Makes you wonder what goes on behind close doors.... Nope. Actually, it doesn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFTER THE POLLS CLOSE: Watch the election night results with us this Tuesday at Chief O’Neills 3471 N Elston Ave.… https://t.co/hS7v0EpDtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nsuttonteaches @WilsonCreekES Look at that engagement!!! Literacy at its best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else remembers 4 years ago when #Glee gave us the Brittana wedding. Wow, their minds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lozzaajl @ferozCarbon @CarlosBolsonaro Este gado não pensante tem o governo que merece, não é? Autêntico representante!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Day 3 of the 7 day book challenge goes to @JennyDaltonHill Post covers of 7 books You love:no explanations, no r… https://t.co/NImygrMuhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[La próxima semana esto se va poner más bueno con la llegada de Adrián bebé 😍 a Vega y Asociados 🙊😂🙈  #PorAmarSinLey2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanLerner is Tucker Carlson the type of person to jump off a bridge because someone else did?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsayballant @EconomicClub Hey @linsdsayballant this not about #Chase brand. Reco listening to interview/experie… https://t.co/o8k8fW8MZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know there was a Abe You can purchase at: Wm Morford Antiques, For about $350 or be a good negotiator!  Not… https://t.co/dqpTR5qakY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryan_leblanc not personally at an event like that but it seems the stanchions were also in place for the PC caucu… https://t.co/l5RFG5CZrR]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS. @ReginaKing @OscardelaRenta #Oscars #bestdressed https://t.co/bSx4YG1ZSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can thank our mama anne_pilla for raising us 2 hellions! 😂😘💞 . Wouldn’t have it any other way, strong, loud, yet… https://t.co/sayszqy3dO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am currently holding hands with the most beautiful girl in all of Atlanta. #Luna https://t.co/xohqNYPPPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly if one of my coworkers asked me if this was okay I’d send them home early]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting up is the hardest, but I feel so damn great after the workout 🏋️‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AUSTIN_LAINE @miglittt So what’s up with them gun laws don’t see any protection there]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EndGunViolence Maryland @MomsDemand members are n Annapolis to fight the gun lobby’s dangerous agenda for our stat… https://t.co/jNo5mBjUpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DSESArt You are an incredible person &amp; your kiddos are lucky to have you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher You always have owned where you are, even if you may not have known why. "Politics" isn't something separate… https://t.co/qHEhl4AIrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t be concerned with their scouting report; you’re not playing the same game as them. @ Springfield, Missouri https://t.co/NWAuMAecBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are real emergencys,California mud slides have brought National Guard in to help stranded residents the fires… https://t.co/zgwMHL7v6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending the day at the SheBelieves Summit, hosted by U.S. Soccer. Speakers include USWNT coach Jill Ellis, USWNT d… https://t.co/WGf4r6fCrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stumbelina Thanks for the tips!!! I think I’m pretty bad about the arms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elliott_REChamp Your so welcome! Love working with you and your clients! #CustomerSuccess… https://t.co/q5pjZScBfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is horrible. Tragic. My prayers and thoughts go out to all of the victims and their loved ones. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a new #home in #PortAngeles or #Sequim? Have a #home to #Sell? Give us a call at #TeamMcAleer… https://t.co/gH9ex66CRe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I just got in the most pointless argument with rave girls I’m embarrassed sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was one of the selfies that started my still growing collection!  TBT to exactly 3 years ago today!… https://t.co/w5a2zekDqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deedavis98 @kimm_winn @KleinForest She is so sweet, smart, kind and generous.  Congrats to Kim! 💚💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often wish I were not as neurotic as I am. It would make relationships, and life in general, so much easier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erogers Count me in! #Preservation #WalktheWalk  #PolisCulturalPlanning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Keith that sounds great. .have a wonderful tour. .😊 ❤ love you too Mia!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid capture by @ScottOConnellTG on Worcester bussing https://t.co/hwWpDgHRMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the @UMHB family!   My team is looking for a Director, Instructional Design to join our dynamic group!… https://t.co/CDk1zLTvmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gin Blossoms at House of Blues! Got to see the band members earlier in the day without even realizing it. Small wor… https://t.co/KZQpLZwO67]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honest question, what should I do about an extended family member posting something super anti-vax on social media?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JEarnhardt1 @iK9_Global @KyleBusch @ToyotaRacing @JoeGibbsRacing @NASCAR_Xfinity @ISMRaceway That is totally awesome]]></document></documents></author>