<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why these females be leaving you on read when you start being nice like fuck https://t.co/ycF1V11bCr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be there to stan the greatest pro wrestling champion Arizona has ever had to offer, @devinsparks. Get your tic… https://t.co/N2K1jUXLhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrGeorgeWallace @AOC Love all of the angry scared white men in your mentions now, George!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta be up in 4hrs for work. But @KayzoMusic was worth it !  Don’t miss his unleashed shows !!🔥🤯🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul__G__ @sawdustcitybeer @NickelBrookBeer That was one beautiful Belgian]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sigtruth @RheannonFae @Awhatdafudge @AOC Norway is a socialist country. Just saying!]]></document><document><![CDATA[T-Mobile: 5G won’t be more expensive than current 4G plans https://t.co/9SR5p7Kek5 #5G #smartphones #strategy @ Was… https://t.co/42eVr9ulh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ufc @Johnnywalkermma @Johnnywalkermma vs @JonnyBones would be a really exciting fight. Jon better pull a Mayweathe… https://t.co/AN7UzEfoEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McCreadyForNC @senatemajldr Mitch McConnell is running for reelection and is saying what he thinks his base wants… https://t.co/6ZbYuK4xCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same lies, the left puts out accusations that the conservatives are attacking yet provide no evidence of the attack… https://t.co/I4rgTADY8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UsMovie isn’t even out yet and I had a nightmare. Looking forward to not sleeping for 3 days.  #WatchYourself]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Hidden Falls Adventure Park (Official) https://t.co/lqHonloAYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarmsBrian @nascarman_rr I went to every Atlanta race from 1987 to 1990. It only held 70k in the stands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night’s @nbcsnl and @mikasounds ‘Lollipop’ skit was the unexpected mashup I never knew I needed ... and it was… https://t.co/BlI0EOA4ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the middle aged woman next to me tries to have a conversation for  my entire 5 AM flight https://t.co/boGYHWPwwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Following the #Sunset  #Miamisunset 🌅 in #Miami  .. ✌️&amp;💛 From: @andydejesus305  #miamirealestate Broker… https://t.co/FxiPP5s139]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @ABC Another ego trip to show his dictator power. It will be interesting to see how far this goes &amp; challenged!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coinbase customers are saying  "The future will be centralized" "Sell ETH, Buy XRP!" "Lottery tickets are a scam, b… https://t.co/5xSGkrGCVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[She’s seen a million faces and she’s rocked ‘me all. @ Hanks Saloon https://t.co/GDMdtJqzLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMLG you cannot violate our rights to bear arms. I grew up in lea county and now live in Texas and will never live back in nm. #Support2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I know several Michael Traceys IRL. I used to work with a couple of them, delivering pizza, as a cashie… https://t.co/Y3YffkKp0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cthagod for those of you that think you are owed something or you are the ones that went through struggle before a… https://t.co/a9wJx5kksw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I encourage all persons that are the subject of a criminal investigation to hire a criminal attorney. It’s common s… https://t.co/kHmsAZY0jd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrBremner_ORTHO Ditto. My body is slowly quitting on me. Do I get a 4th floor Olin discount on knee replacements?]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Adlam   Taprooting for Leaders #businessdevelopment #education #ACN  https://t.co/1mZumLshQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thin bodied, slight cocoa richness, subtle sweetness, dry and earthen dry leafy hop back. - Drinking a Mönchshof Sc… https://t.co/9iFsJw67Ek]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that so many people are saying this is fire is why so many trash rappers get put on nowadays.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Happy19111 @kip_djesus @369Majic @JohnnyNowhere @martydemic @Ceeb16779906 @MCJK33s @UsernameDawn3 @1BoomerWilliams… https://t.co/v7Ocd3ueP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[From me, the conversation would have been “good riddance.”  Oh, and that would still be my stance today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chico State rugby scores a try on the last play of the game to defeat previously undefeated Fresno State 26 25. Chi… https://t.co/f2KGXWGJxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YalitzaAparicio Felicidades yalitza!! Me hubiera gustado verte a ti y a todo el elenco tambien en el escenario recibiendo el Oscar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFXXIV Or it’s going places but appears to be stopped at the moment... #perspective]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ground / #beginning ?  . . . . . . . . . . . #Art #FineArt #Skull #work #loveTheProcess #painter #nyc #ny… https://t.co/2tpeDSgUxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[jessculbertson88 surprised me with @hotboxcookies today! #mywiferocks @ Columbia, Missouri https://t.co/aflmS63vw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamCirc Ya, other stuff goin on in March and April that I’m not involved in lol. May was the earliest time slot I could get. I tried 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly I have zero confidence that we can close this out. Hope I'm wrong!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews @NBCNewsMACH Does this mean a i don’t need to mow the lawn this week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Dear Congressperson, please learn to read, and ask someone on your… https://t.co/nf29Otxpqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristinaKilday @migrantsaid She and her son look fine to me, your exaggarating to make them look like there full… https://t.co/eJkhDzQmb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[also I was talking to somebody and I think I just for various health reasons keep the Mormon dietary code? Which is kinda funny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trailandultra A2: I have the @thenorthfaceECS coming up in DC in April. I don’t feel ready yet, but, I know I’ll g… https://t.co/32YvUjoMWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a dumpster enclosure down the street he's welcome to sleep behind. Always some bubble-wrap in the bins he c… https://t.co/EW998rEZAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOTE: SOURCES INDICATE THAT A LINE OF TETHERED CHILDREN WERE MENACING AN OLD-TIMER NEAR THE BUS STOP. TELL YOUR NEIGHBORS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump The checks were to a woman who was extorting him before the election about an accused… https://t.co/LCRHNPwaAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CloudNaii The only one tryna make sure we get it is an Asian American who is running for president right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easy_baba @Gorpo1973 @cardoso_deli @DeSouzaBraga1 @AnaRoch3353426 @lemos_dr @ElaineG16 @Valqurias4… https://t.co/V52MiJsxi6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeje66 @ToddBrommelkamp That’s pretty much what I thought. But it’s too bad, because I know a lot of people down h… https://t.co/iP57TDPObN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Riot Juice by @HiddenSpringAle @ Hidden Springs Ale Works — https://t.co/A4OXymHHPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life is just not going how I want it I look up bible versus to just help me a little https://t.co/O4PVFR7xCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lovely MC's, radio_sara and @brentporche!  @itsdorothysucka #mmrrocks @ Theatre of the Living Arts https://t.co/FHwOQidLz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@micheilemmett I still remember all the drama of him getting drafted my Quebec.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feed your appetite to stand out with our custom jewelry. #custom #goldgrillz #losangeles #ruby #fangs @ Los Angeles… https://t.co/rmNspPDtiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few spaces have opened on our #sleepingateverestbasecamptrek in 2019. Get in touch for further info. Info@iantaylortrekking.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Strandjunker Roger stone should be locked up nobody else that has threatened a Judge would not be locked up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keselowski @AustinCindric @PaigeKeselowski @amsupdates Good luck tomorrow Brad hope both of you feel better! So pr… https://t.co/hihu3badwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDiGrazio Please tell me Homer is making these decisions..we can't have hired 2 incompetent coaches in a row… https://t.co/vqEgDhqVmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Toyi @Margaritarosadf Ya está bueno con ese tema!! Si no va a opinar del tema !! Tampoco ofenda no sea hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. The day I met @nerdfighterliv  2. The day I got to drive a Ferrari F40 3. The 21 times on Splash Mountain and me… https://t.co/cfnZQCIoNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love Joshua Tree National Park, then you should thank Minerva Hamilton Hoyt. https://t.co/AtqWgrR7st]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so bad at Apex and that makes winning so much more exciting #CARRIED #SCRUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeighYoungArt Actually, grammatically, I think that should read “not as far as a potential season 2 and I are conc… https://t.co/lt99pNJL7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: Is the success sustainable? what worked well with little effort and how do we improve it? Providing the next st… https://t.co/VeHMjKCJf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit @mikekakuk, @brooklynkelli, Bauer, Echo and @GoldenRescue #volunteers today from 11am - 1pm at the @petvalu… https://t.co/rkezETxWyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hbowman1H @LynnBever @Rubiconski @MsLynneMiller @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/gQbrWtDLD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump says he's 'surprised' about charges brought against Patriots owner Kraft https://t.co/NrL1BYRkxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samacmcbride +1. The current misuse of the word “humbled” is a national emergency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Reference: Alice. Zelda and the Library are tracking her and she’s reportedly given up magic and is working at… https://t.co/MmoxtdEr33]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our producer and mom-to-be Heather! We all got together this weekend to celebrate her and her gr… https://t.co/8QEHplma2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smarmcharm O h my god what    I hope that the "blow up" thing was in bad context, and not relating to her being Mu… https://t.co/k6xsmzNkod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xwordmark @Bloggasaurus Which programs would you like to eliminate? https://t.co/1IevYzPXGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeyadventures NYC has some good places as well in NJ. The only thing of NYC is getting past the noise lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sendnetwork @sendvegas @sendcleveland @senddenver @sendpuertorico @sendphoenix Pastors of the SBC, join me in plan… https://t.co/FJRipU42Ay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime I wrap Zion up with his blanket I always call him an empanada 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SexySunday @kristenadkins @ErinAndrews @KendraAndrews1 @alliequigley @Kristina_Pink @De11eDonne @breannastewart… https://t.co/tqAfHJ1g4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are an accountant and a woman seeking a relationship dm me nobody ever taught me taxes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Libs ruin every thing they touch.  It feeds their hate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always enjoy doing Run The Line in Texarkana. Texas and Arkansas. https://t.co/tzCeIVjFx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @Luckylaurie2 This one is unfit also. https://t.co/MViXqjmXay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrapped another episode of lastmanstandingfox (where I assist the warmup comic) and went out to celebrate with the… https://t.co/vkxMu4rPuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheWalkingDead When your mom says, “clean the dishes before she gets home” and seeing not one dish cleaned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmorrison99 I play each course differently. Some dont require driver every hole!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big effort from CONCRETE ROSE coming back in the Florida Oaks. Amazing job from the entire Rusty Arnold barn and gr… https://t.co/n5rjpjud74]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when go out to eat and there’s bread and butter there https://t.co/Fh2ASwMVTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Snow ⛄️ day  Yoga 🧘🏾‍♂️ &amp; pancake 🥞  #yoga @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/QhtOmiW3yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@koolwhp Thank you. And no more novels with the word wife in the title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKThomp this line is the best line I’ve read in a long time: “It is the belief—the faith, even—that work is not li… https://t.co/BZck3YcV27]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, #MEP Engineers! Need a quick #DOAS unit selection? You can get a selection on eCAPS anywhere you can access th… https://t.co/Hww4gUvP4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fascists: “JEWS WILL NOT REPLACE US!”  Trump: “Good people on both sides.”  It’s like Steve King and Jim Jordan don… https://t.co/pzO9JXp9By]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunes y desde las 8am ya traigo el perreo a todo lo que da. Será algún tipo de señal?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NorthernVaWx @capitalweather It’s closed next 2 weeks due to rain and possible winds over 5 mph !]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK: Timeout Lyon. Hampton with a steal and a bucket. Colonels up 18-14.   1:53, 2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s crazy how i relationship can damage you. 2 years later and i still don’t feel the same. i don’t trust people.… https://t.co/zikf37lnWT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an observation, I have never even heard the name of seven of them.  Might be a good thing as Dems need to turn… https://t.co/0530ojdqRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Libro 📚: Una Vida Sin Obstáculos  Autor: Erick Torres Disponible ya 😊😃💯👍🏻🇺🇸🇵🇷🇩🇴🇨🇴🇲🇽… https://t.co/85Vl0XPnyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenMintonWSB. Happy FRI-YAY KM... WOW.  the clock is ticking . gonna miss you on our TV..😢 but. You know THAT.😘.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblondeMD @nataliemwall You might want to show the U the latest data from the American College of Surgeons and t… https://t.co/55MFd1WqTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pit BBQ... A must when in Dallas. @ Hard Eight BBQ- Coppell https://t.co/os5Cdi83K5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my fellow kangaroo @Jcovey84 for being part of our #fm9worldtour247! @killoughfmhs and @KruegerFM9 sti… https://t.co/HYPiMV4XpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom That $3.5B wasn't allocated to you by the American taxpayers to do whatever you want with it. Californ… https://t.co/Pc3Nv1pcZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbegor @janieo @philosophrob @RepBarbaraLee Probably not in the kind we citizens of this sham-voting country expec… https://t.co/aCvpMLi27h]]></document></documents></author>