<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dc_mma you can fight @francis_ngannou now. He is very slow fighter!!! just imagine how many times you can eye poke him in 30 seconds 🤣😃🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morrigoon @RepCummings He's way too smart to run for that sucker bet of a job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little kid across the street just yelled “fuck you bitch” and then ran off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎥 frames from the last @MizzouHoops home game of the season https://t.co/Sg90JkytPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@surliestgirl I keep going to start listening to it but I have been stopping myself bc I'm so busy right now and wa… https://t.co/dojrAf3qyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally! that spot you were thinking of has found its match OR we will help you create one for it! This Macassar Eb… https://t.co/b1tQBOG17a]]></document><document><![CDATA[WaPo rushes to Democrats' defense, lest anyone characterize the party's pro-abortion radicalism as, well, radical… https://t.co/hcU3fN26H5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoniogm The right is doing what they’ve always says they’d do. The left doesn’t know what it’d do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Bruins team has an eerily similar vibe to the 2011 team 😋😏 let’s go get that 🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a person ur attracted to just talk to u abt sex but dont have sex w you they a fucking cop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Believe &amp; act on it 🙏🏽 It’s already yours if you work for it 💯 https://t.co/5RpKSuDUpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seancollierpgh @HitchDied This is the most appropriate way to help me understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneAppel so appreciate your messages at the Lincoln Leadership Conference. Been at my new church for 6 months and… https://t.co/NLPgc7dpxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Raiders acquire Antonio Brown from Steelers: A person with direct knowledge of the situation tells… https://t.co/41LSGKAMMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists Sadly I just don’t understand how they got sucked into this. Just tools. And they don’t see it. @DiamondandSilk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does AB still count against the Steelers cap since he got a reworked deal @AllbrightNFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 I never thought I wanted a new governor more. Please @RockyForKy win this thing for Eastern Kentucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OOTPPerfectTeam 😭 just pulled 70 packs and didn't get 1 diamond/perfect I might cry @sporer lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 6:  I have accepted a challenge from @bbfalcons post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews - jus… https://t.co/C4yoSq6Nq3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Badababa @danceiskeyyaho1 @beinlibertarian @AOC OK one last one because I want you to know the point I was driving… https://t.co/7XI6VeDrtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe there should be a Constitutional Amendment supporting naps. Or Nat’l Emergency. Thanks Yeshua 😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[am i the first person to ever wear a @kaskade beanie for their drivers license picture??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movement in the learning space is a great way to keep kids engaged. However, procedures and clear directions are important. #dcschat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bungie https://t.co/h0jhFviMdG  I think the community would like to see way more of this]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know there must have been a long conversation about wether or not Queen Latifah was going to introduce “The Fav… https://t.co/ly74ehnYrq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're really providing quite a few options: https://t.co/aSb1Aa95pD https://t.co/pS2OtrjPu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southwakecoach Yeah see I was thinking you were talking about cars for a sec.... does Mozilla still do Firefox ? I… https://t.co/pO4TUv6uhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokey_77 @EditinKing @SantanaTeddy You’re from fuckin Australia, and I been to Gold Coast during my time in the n… https://t.co/8iKytfOTJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  To prove to all those doubting nimrods that the #BorderWall IS being built, let's install live ca… https://t.co/eg9bxS6sCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Chicago police spokesman: 'Empire' actor Jussie Smollett turns self in on accusation of making false police report.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SensFan550 @Jouer5 @BadAtHockeyMeIs @travisyost Sorry, I was thinking of Canadian wingers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/7EM8uGRFpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lebeaucarnews He literally said with some luck they would be profitable. What is this revisionist history?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlowin And then *what* do I find on eBay the *next* day? And your brazen attempt to get above list price for it, g… https://t.co/48Xrim4iM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#السيسي للمصريين: «والله لأقف أنا وأنتم قدام ربنا وهحاسبكم زي ما بتحاسبوني»  رسمي هالبني ادم متخلف عقلي]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_NotArlene @AntBenavides_33 Sounds pretty good👍 https://t.co/lb6EhiLTja]]></document><document><![CDATA[A4 Anything from @AVID4College. All things AVID; all the time! #TOSAChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[#McDonalds has gotten so fancy they’ve stole the joy of going to #McDonalds...   Sometimes better simply isn’t bett… https://t.co/e0cMGGLGfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, #Isles fans, maybe you should throw all that hatred toward Bailey now.  LOL!  #owngoal #ourdivision @Capitals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarthBarclay @UConnFootball @RandyEdsall @CoachCEdsall @RA_Downes Good Luck at Buffalo today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Keith_Langlois Another win the Pistons were supposed to win,a ugly win but a win is a win...of course of course]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Valentine makeup choices for the evening and weekend. Do what your heart♥️ desires Hair styledbyraquel Makeup… https://t.co/iUXxHtrHCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could be the best lookin slice of pizza out of the entire box and there will still be someone who doesnt fuck w… https://t.co/RNt78zkY1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol who cares about the Hurricanes celebrating after games. Bet the Thrashers wished they’d done it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends An Ohio GM plant is letting 1,700 workers go. It’s not as good of a time for them .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__MrHussain__ @brookeewinkler It’s from “pop crave” if you didn’t want pop news follow fox or cnn not a pop culture twitter page.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShalyssaMin7 @T_STREETZ69 ... I would say that’s me but we all know that I’m just going with the cheapest vodka th… https://t.co/zluT4bC6RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you guys do this to yourself? Nothing good comes from these tweets....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasViper1965 @ProWrestlingMag Uh because of a guest host we got the first Hispanic Divas Champion]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Beast with a little BP. Three out of the yard at Twin Creek. https://t.co/AfWhN6wA32]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bus was scheduled to leave at 8:33. It left at 8:30. Why have schedules if metro doesn’t follow them? Route 65.… https://t.co/H3vXxXLCwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espngolic I am not sure why #steelers stand by their Qb when you look at Big Ben  issues he has been suspended and… https://t.co/sqbL3BkaGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pst. @josuesmedia is the real deal and this is dope. Great videographer, better person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hero&gt; This man built a #StarWars vehicle in his front yard https://t.co/1XU3oQLSLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickrznk Ignore the picture I did not mean to put that in there MY BAD 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBA @TheCoreyBrewer @SacramentoKings Happy birthday from Arizona. #SacramentoProud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker @TuckerCarlson @seanhannity @FoxNews https://t.co/h5Fm7c0E4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JDYB #TLUHOOPS I'm so proud of these guys all 15 of them. They play not with each other, but for each other! Truly… https://t.co/5uLtQPCtOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[En parte me pone feliz de que @Miguel_layun la este rompiendo aunque no sea en el más grande]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So let's just get this straight, you're going to go meet with China, get taken advantage of as alw… https://t.co/1Mm2HkOOwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ComingSoon #MelroseAve #LosAngeles #Sacrament #Spiritual #Social #SeekingLife @ Melrose Avenue https://t.co/EoQ5thQR4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @305FoLife @lesleyabravanel @realDonaldTrump Whenever a Democrat whines... https://t.co/lCv1KxN6WE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DementedMinx @PhoenixTruths @SeanTibbetts87 Very true never go to Mexico and order them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way behind 11 laps to go @daytona500 . I’m going with my guy @KyleBusch . Hamlin “Veteran” even odds . And the new… https://t.co/Fm8BRI2ZQi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crap !! Dire que mon plus vieux s'en voulait d'avoir raté un filet désert en fin de partie cette après-midi !! Je v… https://t.co/s6OeBSDVoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoryLegion_GC @McIlroyRory @PReedGolf @marcleish Really glad you made the decision to play more on the PGA Tour. I’m watching a lot more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_honan I went to college with a very religious guy who earnestly insisted the actual name for a foam beer sle… https://t.co/Ql9iADS2eB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know where the bodies are buried.  For future note: bury your own bodies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does completing the qualifying process mean you get to redeem democracy vouchers? If so, how does a candidate complete it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beardown215 @Pony_Keg_Tom @kirkster7762 @Ebron85 @Lions https://t.co/lsO4DVhJNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spitzy71 @CraigSJ Acquitted in the court of law does not mean MJ was innocent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing one of my all-time favorite songwriters in a small room, crowd of probably 75 people, 5 minutes from my hous… https://t.co/RqMiKty8J2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys hoops Region 4-7A semifinal. Surprising 1st quarter as ice cold shooting Doral trails Belen 11-1.@J_McPherson1126]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so I’m pretty sure DePaul is finish last in the conference again. I could see Providence winning their last few to pass them up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump It’s a real problem! Trump needs to resign now, so that America can begin the healing process!]]></document><document><![CDATA[No One Is Taking Your Hamburgers. But Would It Even Be a Good Idea? https://t.co/OGM9c9EcWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#queenextravaganza #queen #bohemianrhapsody #whiskyagogo #losangeles @ Whisky A Go-Go https://t.co/0wgoQN50kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really trying to figure out who uses #AppleMusic because I’m getting nothing from them #NewArtist #NewMusicAlert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachdeesmith Love this . Building the foundation for future success!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Telf Excuse me? My allergies are horrendous, I’d appreciate you not making light of my medical conditions. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Boy when the post arrest memos and transcripts are released I suspect that most of Kushner's and MB… https://t.co/sNmrYAkMYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know ur having a shit day when you go to the batting cages to blow off some steam in between classes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyInCBus @jake_burns18 Melis has taken it really hard which has made it tough but she’s the reason he’s lived as l… https://t.co/7jERlKiThm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaharahShae You're amazing, Saharah! That was great! Happy Valentine's day! 💝💝💝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TripleH @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE I have to say that was awesome! When I saw Sasha Banks come up on the screen… https://t.co/cuujLtBWWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonyuandesign @round Meant to say shouldn’t but typing that was is a challenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer @CPC_HQ They won't have a world that is inhabitable #Climatechaos #Climatechangeisreal #formygrandchildren]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StusWood @TamposiNFL @AroundTheNFL @DanHanzus @MarcSesslerNFL @greggrosenthal “Turned down coaching the Bengals” — excellent work here. 😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Travlr_Boris @hochybrig @MySwitzerland_e Guuuets Morgä zäma ond hebs es rüüdig guets Mittwuch HumpDay stressfreien… https://t.co/86LAlJGjHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivingRangerKey I’m going to see it cus it’s part of the MCU and looks good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_salmonsjames_ We owe him a 17 million roster bonus by March 21 so unless we wanna pay him 17 million for no reaso… https://t.co/f1fSRiLFtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chaz_Carlos I actually quote tweeted someone blaming Kevin Hart’s comedy for the attack then said it was a “disgus… https://t.co/4dYrOPyxwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gillis9Rose @thecjpearson I hope people wake up and see what they are doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarryIsFunny yeah, I get sugared (similar to waxing) all down there and around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[POY- Rui Hachimura DPOY- Brandon Clarke NCOY- Brandon Clarke COY- Mark Few  1st Team All WCC Brandon Clarke Rui Hac… https://t.co/tFNXny0Brh]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's actually an active motivation hashtag for every day of the week. That's a sad commentary on the state of ou… https://t.co/sfpHByX3ce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawkworld_ Can we cross brand with some Silverhawks sometime. Xoxo #80sKid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron really got an Afro on top of his bald spot . It’s for him to let it go and come home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Titus goes to the bathroom around 4:30 am pretty much every day, and me half asleep I usually let him stay outside… https://t.co/UOg2aHwC5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxhoma23 Max. Huge complainer here. Tell me who to complain to and I’ll do it.]]></document></documents></author>