<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Day 2 - #7daybookchallenge - #bilingual I challenge @MrsHernandez25 https://t.co/T5SYTDqdNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge my sword to the realm! I just entered for a chance to attend the official #GameofThrones S8 premiere. How… https://t.co/RtIsK0reHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[pls... i’m so tired.. pls stop Winter storm expected to blanket parts of northeastern US in snow ❄️  https://t.co/y9sVbw9Uv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angela_schroden Hello dear friend! I was working at a school today, a place we both know; 😉 and I happen to meet a… https://t.co/OgMUw7abeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be weary of those wanting to grasp leadership. They are a bramble tree and will speak false promises... #youbetterwatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new Aston Martin Vantage has a beautiful rear end. 🤤  #astonmartin #supercar #sportscar https://t.co/67aJt6a6Il]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DracTweets @Abigail_Larson Got to love a well read man with fangs. (Great job, Abigail!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherylunderwood I watch the show everyday and I have know idea what this person is talking about. @sherylunderwood… https://t.co/3by8byST1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColoJen THIS! 🙌  I am so happy that this happened for you. Toxicity is so heavy on your shoulders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vpaolah Dude!!!! Dani was craving that yesterday 😂 we have birrote from Mexico 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀👀👀 Julius Randle living up to that first round pick status tonight cooking vs the Thunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet my Date for this weekend and Copernic Space, Lady Rocket Foundation And California Space Center have its momen… https://t.co/3dY4LXXWov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaSuePark @camphalfblood @kwamealexander @getnicced @AlanGratz @halseanderson @jewell_p_rhodes @JasonReynolds83… https://t.co/uHCeQIBgT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntheRhodes @NatashaBertrand They certainly hope it will. I hope the US Marshalls come and heave him into a convieniently close jail cell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk: Springfield Missouri has a very pleasant airport. I only flew to/from it once but the people were helpfu… https://t.co/S7K7t7SH4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jukehorse50 That is exactly what he is going to do.  And he'll do it with the backing of the RNC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look at The Cher Show (now on Broadway and rightfully designed by Bob Mackie) through numbers: • The show incorpo… https://t.co/qZ9eCS5R1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no feeling quite like going to commons after successfully completing an 8am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just don’t travel to Tahoe, or through the mountains. I’ve never seen CHP close the highways this many times in a s… https://t.co/yk28BopiYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eraaayne girl same 😂 me you alex and colin can have dates for the new game of thrones, with drinks... on your new couch 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southyarradan @marcorubio Russia and China are doing what? While helping the régimen starve it’s people to death.… https://t.co/x3ovdNm0Mg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megpillow @JellyfishReview @ChristopherJ_8D Happy day to you! https://t.co/sx3CUwa5AD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryder is hiring in #VeroBeach, FL! Click the link in our bio to apply: Customer Logistics Supervisor - 2nd shift #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cuteylogey Lol my dad let's me obsess over Logan when my 2nd personality comes out (bipolar disorder)and I'm down… https://t.co/cIKrusx1B8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peppa: papa cerdito súper salto de charco de lodo https://t.co/fQEgbIGimX via @YouTube us hahahahahjjiiiiioojsbxbbxnxxjxjjxidbxjxjx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeccaJLower @HonkyTonkJew If true, there’s no way Her Majesty allows this. None whatsoever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[um,, are there really people saying TXT is “saving” the industry when they haven’t even DEBUTED YET? even if they d… https://t.co/nN6L1KDy1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why everyone is so upset about Malia doing what every college kid does. The only difference is she’s sipping on… https://t.co/1mWBRuIUdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#datenight Date night even though there is a snow storm. @ Edina, Minnesota https://t.co/HgblK3S48e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agearan @PhilipRucker @John_Hudson @DavidNakamura He can see N Korea from ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnjaliHemphill @fox5dc It was so delightful to hear this young man talk. Very Impressed with his speaking skills]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning @TexQuestk12 in Denton today with @decaturisdlib @Mercer_Moments @TammyMcGar @DainyaPark @GeorgettaSlimp #TexQuest]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WendyOrent Wendy,  How does the CDC define an epidemic? Because Autism prevalence does qualify as an epidemic per… https://t.co/UKIWLdyTNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We weren't on the brink of war/ N Korea in 2016 Ben Rhodes, Mr. Obama’s deputy national security a… https://t.co/ghXO4fQzXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@jarrad_tweets and his love for The Wizard of Oz and how to apply its plot to your career as a #photojournalist on… https://t.co/7TDuE0rQEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls drive safe everyone. There are other people on the road trying to go about their days too, so please drive safely!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoboHoward @realDonaldTrump @JaySekulow @kimguilfoyle @GovMikeHuckabee @SebGorka @PAMsLOvE @marjonnat I agree 💯%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsLadyM_ Right?! Like girls have tried to follow him home before and I think that’s the creepiest shit ever. Are guys into that???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish my roomie @allisonkilkenny the happiest of birthdays and send her jewels, mixed securities, luxuries or cash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! Slow down or stop if you can for all Wildlife and our domestic buds!!❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#literacy &amp; #hiphop March 16th! It’s a family, community affair! fillmore_heritage_center Hope to see you… https://t.co/JIuu0i0ZWt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski You are missing an incredible series. (Books are better, if that matters)   I got nothin on the rest. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganOnAir @GamecockMBB Awesome to have you on the call! Show us some love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheColonelJim Makes me glad I've got a lot of crap to do today. It'll keep away from the stupidity 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s sad? I moved away, to grow and better myself. But I can count w/ my 2 hands the amount of times I’v… https://t.co/XxpUoYv5ef]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, so you’re telling me you guys never knew what he was singing about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#iceicebaby 🥶 @ Lake Michigan, Chicago Lakefront https://t.co/FXQDGyPF8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like @johnmcguire56 isn’t so interested in representing the people of #HD56...he’s looking to climb that ladd… https://t.co/kdPxKaRARo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m most interested in seeing how #5G will bring operational efficiencies &amp; safety improvements to #Industry #industrial40 #MWC19 @intel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my last work shift covered, knowing I already bought the tickets. 😅 Now officially able to go to LA to see @JZACMusic 🤭🥂 Cheers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HbesRrosales Great Season and Amazing work ethic these Kiddos showed!! Hard work paid off and they capped their se… https://t.co/pdlCeYFK7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NY1 @courtneycgross @LynnePatton U guys say ur for woman until she’s a republican or someone working 4 Trump. It’s… https://t.co/8tao9PPXOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherylArellano6 @PATLIEPATROL014 @patrickquiroz_ @itsmeangelieofc @PatLie_Trends @PJstersOFC Time will come di ba… https://t.co/EtOh9nNxRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yayyy I'm all set!!! Now all I need to do is drive to Nashville! @Avi_Kaplan @TheBasementNash https://t.co/xBykjKIG0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZwartblesIE Are all 3 all black? Love these videos. Puts a smile on my face every time]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my dear tweeples.  Thank you for following me and showing me such respect as a Gold Star ⭐️ wife. I try not to m… https://t.co/uOqTL57Yxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LRPow79 He shouldn't be thinking, first of all. He sucks at it. He tends to let mother do his thinking for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had enough money to just move every time the shower drain needs cleaning out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you get my pistol bro? "Yo pistol! This mines" "...but that's Rebecca..."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump Don’t advise him that! It’s a first step! No one has an appetite for a shutdown!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @RyanAFournier That’s complete bullshit! Trump voters didn’t want Hillary as their President! That’s… https://t.co/Q9cJojX8qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao @ all the people who preach about loyalty and they’re the shadiest ones of them all😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delivering a truckload of love to your timeline.   Happy Valentines Day! @ South Carolina https://t.co/szI5kbO0Gg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s funny is; I’m actually average height, shoe size &amp; ring size ... lol Average ... #BasicB* 😂😘♥️😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally had one of my tweets blow up, and it was on my ‘fake’ acc so no one will ever know😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if there’s no sex or abuse, slumber parties between a grown adult and children are not innocent and in no way… https://t.co/NYIKeYkwcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever been that kind of sleepy where you just want to lay in bed..but not sleepy enough to be able to keep… https://t.co/DSeNkiOq5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctordickerson @robbiclairesord @MomsDemand @JoMoBlogger Yes MO @MomsDemand! 👏🏾👏🏻👏🏿👏🏽👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sure raising a human baby is hard, but have you ever had to raise a kitten?]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGHurcomb UMKC Photography 1 Lighting and Still life Lab 3/4/19 #umkcart @ UMKC Department of Art and Art History https://t.co/SSyyjISMzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm old enough to remember how conservatives thought it ludicrous for AOC to even bring this up like it was just la… https://t.co/9giGVouylj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beeknightly Agreed, watched the first Bundy tape and was like eh... @UmbrellaAcad tho!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[En vista de que no vinieron los que nos iban a ayudar...  pues a marcar el campo sola! 😶 https://t.co/3Jqq5XuTnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you aren’t hyping other women up, I don’t want to be your friend. just sayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m going to east bay to see my kiddos on friday and i’m SCREAMING i’m so excited]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Umbrella Academy did NOT make me want a rooted blonde dye job any less.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddiecorman @ABravePlay You just better be nice to @maddiecorman — even inside your own head. 🧡#dontmakemecomedownthereyounglady]]></document><document><![CDATA[Modeling kindness and respect is so important! This we can do because #KidsDeserveIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[“They were just diagnosed with the flu/strep” y’all dont even know how often I hear this. please do not come into m… https://t.co/DtDOUgnIY0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Offset on the Ebro show makes me understand and empathize with him more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m still dead that I really punched Kendall in the face last night then bawled my eyes out cause I felt so bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaimeTheFave I dont like to eat my crust last. Does that make me a total dork?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamamerrickan Will you eventually add a size chart to the website ? I haven’t bought anything yet, but was about t… https://t.co/V0LcvpT4H3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know what I hate... when people leave and they don’t say goodbye... sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the one year anniversary of the tragic and senseless deaths of 17 human beings. At 2:21pm please take a mo… https://t.co/GeiQhblpKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm here in NYC because I'm getting trained by Workplace Mental Health Institute.  We had a great group today. Whil… https://t.co/MeLC0NUqv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollanMcCoy Yes. My entire caseload will be completed in 3 days. Not my decision. 🙃 #prayforme]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU 100 Women of Lake Highlands for giving more than $30,000 to Skyview Elementary! #risdconnects… https://t.co/yBFR97Ivnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you in my sketchnoting session in  State Ballroom F at 10-11:30 today? #ncties19 https://t.co/tpMWsx5YPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved this ice skating show at Busch Gardens, Turn it up! #turnitup #iceskating #buschgardens #tampa #florida… https://t.co/HcYaeB2aQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I lost all of my follows. I know others have had the same experience. Does anyone know why that happens?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what #corruption looks like. Comply or be ejected. How long will the PC MPPs continue to back this bullying… https://t.co/BygGVeijoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreshStartAz music 🎶 Download available on all platforms 🙌🏼 This song is 🔥#sendtherain https://t.co/CoKevWuxQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tale of the salad and the fork. First question out of the gate by @karaswisher for @amyklobuchar. #SXSW… https://t.co/xooCs5SLfT]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey guess what month it is....BASKETBALL MONTH. ITS FREAKING MARCH🏀❤️🗓 #MarchMadness19 don’t be offended if I don’t… https://t.co/wuhOz4hhOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emma Goldman should have said, "If I can't dance (sing, and laugh, hug, and act normal), I don't want to be part of your revolution."]]></document><document><![CDATA[It makes me mad that I can’t read the screens at work, but my glasses are just so uncomfortable I will never get used to them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLAOmar @WFLA @WFLAJulie Wow your job sucks... #not #takemetothebeach]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEMattForman @RepMarkMeadows Stop your fucking whinning about Garland. after yesterday when ALL DEMOCRATS voted a… https://t.co/LG61IFFH03]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleWaughTV asks if Robert Kraft has to appear in court or if he can send his attorney instead. Authorities sa… https://t.co/qMf3kDFcHO]]></document></documents></author>