<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@mstamp36 It makes me feel 😒 but also fired up to learn as much as I can about how these processes work, and what t… https://t.co/FJXnscxnyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel @GOPLeader @RepAdamSchiff Enough of hiding the truth from us!!! The American people have had enough of… https://t.co/a2lxn7Bcq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reid isn't dying he's in remission and he was single handedly responsible for f**king up Nevada for years to come..… https://t.co/wPXaF8Qjgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tajjackson3 Truth is by nature self-evident. As soon as you remove the cobwebs of ignorance that surround it, it s… https://t.co/qp40L7JDkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @RedRoseOf_Texas @KingofRagnarok @ThorxOdinson @LokixOdinson @SuitAndScarf @Skyeisthelmt @SKrompas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stinaserene I have the Hulu/Spotify duo for students, and it’s only $5😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend is halfway through Game of Thrones and she just texted me and I quote "Hoe season runs as long as winter… https://t.co/LxofNzHjbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALomaxNet @EricFielding @UKEQ_Bulletin @seismo_steve Too many reporters without and grab and go bags.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To think this little cut bled like a son of a bitch. Still trying to figure out what I sliced my foot open on but..… https://t.co/fFwDtN0HAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#livebythegoldenrule #goals #ambition #selfrespect #family @ St. Clair Shores, Michigan https://t.co/Ljw0s6ckpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else feel like they’re on first-name basis with Rachel @maddow’s analysts?   Yay ... it’s Chuck! Oh good ..… https://t.co/bsuE66oTtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We all know there was never no involvement with Russia !! These Democrats don't know what to do to… https://t.co/ywxwaXenzH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pokemongo friends!  My 2nd ever shiny legendary! https://t.co/lwXpXNqPUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wanna go back to traditional college but then I think ab all them essays and assignments and test and... nvm I’m good !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember to give straight trucks, semis, and other commercial vehicles a lot of space today! I drove a 25’ Ford for… https://t.co/0ohReDouoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So got my mare tubed with dmso to help with her EPM and they never told me how bad it would make her stink😷 can lit… https://t.co/OJ4kbjTjVd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraysonDolan i know u do it’s hard gray, but you’ll find a way to turn those emotions into something amazing i love u💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr You are sworn to uphold the #Constitution. TSupporting @POTUS in declaring a national emergency where… https://t.co/nJllPfiTQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lonniebnelson @RichlandTwo Thank you so much!!!! I love showing how our bees can shine!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course the weekend I’m flying out of town Taylor MIGHT be dropping new music 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️ guess I’m recording some… https://t.co/upxrBGbGl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBasherMWO @nbc25fox66 @mikewoolfolk @AhmadBajjeyWx Thank you, Jason!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to competing today! A lot of players have an opportunity to step up into bigger roles today. Excite… https://t.co/pwgEAfHRn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Nothing more threatening than a citizen of color cleaning up his neighborhood! I dont think I can slee… https://t.co/NbGHQus2Ot]]></document><document><![CDATA[The answer is always yes if you don’t believe me look at my header. GOT IS THE WAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerweber piece of shit getting another sentence next week. maybe that will make up for this ridiculousness a little bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are going to be anything, just be real. This fake, superficial, trying to be someone else, social media prom… https://t.co/KWf0Adw4RY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanTGrimes Now you just need color coordination! Looks great! https://t.co/Gddxf70J5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5 #legsformiles with cyogalife Ardha Chandrachapasana @ In Balance Yoga https://t.co/HShBLZWLCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left insanity marches on!  They are the Democrats! They are the Party of demons!   https://t.co/DMyOGViJPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBarnaby3636 as a diehard #preds fan I got what I wanted #Simmonds  and fiala gone.  it’s a great day]]></document><document><![CDATA[This generation both appalls and inspires me me everyday.   Today, they appalled me when a 14-year-old felt it was… https://t.co/gvdT7uMjpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be grounds for divorce for me if I were married to either one of them. Just saying. I'm petty and jealou… https://t.co/LgvMnA2ozn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That backdrop can mean one thing I’m at Chapel and about to throw down Let’s do this djroland001… https://t.co/acyaTBHXaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a sick parent is one of the most stressful things anyone can go through]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello everyone it’s been 2 years since the Hawaiian luau lake house incident I hope everyone is doing okay]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NASWNYC Thanks for recognizing @NMICnyc ‘s own Sarah Crawford-Banda #elevatesocialwork #socialworkinthecity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricDBarrera I didn’t eat one until I was 25. My mom’s attitude was like “Fuck you for asking.” Always had a chees… https://t.co/8ZCDuvhtsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikaelahelane I’ve watched this at least 10 times. Hilarious and brilliant! Her recent BAFTA won speech also wonde… https://t.co/PpIhNG5fuY]]></document><document><![CDATA[OK Google play the Grammy award winning album Golden Hour https://t.co/9kWSklHwqE]]></document><document><![CDATA[this ain’t even cute...she ain’t have to touch the second guy and her moves ain’t even all that for her to be takin… https://t.co/hjgLzJphha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elon Musk and The Rock are a Photoshop battle away from being twins  https://t.co/sbCqfi7kWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanioBar El contraste entre pueblo y FANB, es el gran detalle escondido de este video. Queda para la historia este #4M.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day I played Tituba In The Crucible, I knew I was meant to be a witch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCuratrix Well, that's not quite what I would have meant.  But clearly I need to rephrase it, because too many pe… https://t.co/4VjfwJvBzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike What’s up with only making a mens version of these sweet @SFGiants kicks? You do know that women are baseball… https://t.co/L0Xu01E8w8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why is no one in the media talking about what’s going on in Haiti?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are excited to welcome Reeney (Interim Preschool Director), and Lisa (Interim Assistant Preschool Director), to… https://t.co/LxNlIO1c0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@latimes Make these students work after school and with the money earned send them on a trip to visit Auschwitz ins… https://t.co/imzz1VYpGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weeks burger: a very messy but yummy turkey burger from All About Burger! #burger #burgers #turkeyburger… https://t.co/hN7fi1wJyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching #FreeSolo on @NatGeo , I feel somewhat inadequate that my whole body shakes like a leaf when I use m… https://t.co/co3dnHHTUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBC Bias GAVE us Trudeau ... and now a majority of CDN MSM are manipulating THIS Election too ... that should make… https://t.co/qGEuClrac5]]></document><document><![CDATA[We really had Alvin Kamarra in the building tonight and y’all wasn’t hype to see him y’all ain’t real fans 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want a tin type portrait done sooo badly. it’s not a want it’s a need]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALL IMA SAY IS.  It’s not official official until it’s Facebook official 🗣😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Your words could be used to describe exactly another country and it’s leader. Change “Maduro” to “trump… https://t.co/RLWuyMfbwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xaviersherrera Lol no where big just a local trip. I save my big trips for the summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlatEarthers can you explain where seasons come from because I am very confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dedecrim Hard for me to say. I claim a bar as my own, but I’ve been going there round about 1800 days in a row. Barring vacations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She has some bomb ass recipes, but no one that anal is pleasant to deal with]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏔 “...Dejen que los niños vengan a mí, y no se lo impidan, porque el reino de los cielos es de quienes son como ell… https://t.co/sgsdAcDM06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got to the line, "It’s not like all of a sudden the floodgates opened and we sent every Joey Bagadonuts from S… https://t.co/8ScztTmMIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always love being home❤️ @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/0jg8ndBm7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saandcl Michelle Wolfe - definition Disgusting Hag, knock that baby right out of there mentality, good luck findin… https://t.co/1phD7fBu5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSpadea @MattRooneyNJ I should give a shit about this since U "claim" 2B pro life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NewJobsForCharacters Aladdin's Carpet Cleaning Services (watch out, they tend to fly away) https://t.co/v3k0Qbu39w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just started to last expense report I will ever do in finance. Whoa. #FreelanceLife #ArtistOnTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Amen!  People (if they can even be called that) are warped!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off our @SalesforceOrg Power of Us Live! event. A full day of the Salesforce love and inspiration ♥️ https://t.co/1UVqExM5JT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerzeygirl99 @nowthisnews @RepBarragan Did you know Alex has pancreatic cancer?😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grilled swordfish over goat cheese and herb polenta, roasted eggplant, squash, zucchini, grape tomatoes and baby mu… https://t.co/7yC2cyXQjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks @iamikandy for reminding me that sometimes the worst things in life that happen to us can help us turn into… https://t.co/21z1kotFL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My weekend #mood is f*ck off I'm reading....what better way to celebrate it by finishing off NO EXIT. So far this t… https://t.co/K3PQ22xdVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona Snowbowl is busy today! Last live was blotchy so I hope this one is better.  https://t.co/7FEJ9n7KO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I un-blocked all the blocked numbers in my phone. y’all can’t hurt me. whatever you have to say is a reflection of… https://t.co/8AlJiu0nm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to shower because I have a work meeting at 6 but I don’t wanna fucking be an adult rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@46_still I know! Then the tears hoping it will get everyone on her side. She said she learned her lesson, but the… https://t.co/woy31QIslg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellejorden And letting Jamie go!!! Like did you honestly think that was going to work out...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enter to Win a Custom Nissan Rogue in Your Team Colors https://t.co/NexYnByIXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CVS pharmacy - @cvs_extra in Hartville, OH https://t.co/fEP2ZDvS5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Minds brighter than yours have ruled on this.  Quit using it to try to recruit or agitate using th… https://t.co/MexO6pJRMq]]></document><document><![CDATA['Explaining Psychic Question'  The question HOW LONG WILL WE BE TOGETHER? - According to Einstein, Time is relative… https://t.co/pFHTxwwfsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of hanging out with this lovely lady sherrylkingweatherssellsre  this morning! Miami Gardens is do… https://t.co/Edfegq4B04]]></document><document><![CDATA[While you all are watching Captain Marvel this weekend, I’m playing Captain Disinfectant at home 😂… https://t.co/tfec8C5XWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucasJiro Honestly 10/10 day otherwise. Even these guys were funny enough that I could laugh it off. Mic got fixed now 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is barking in her sleep and I really hope she’s not having a nightmare cause I’m gonna cry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a lil GEM my friend Mike Teló recomended me... This place guys has FENOMENAL Vegan food..you won't even notice… https://t.co/R6ZzNhBKP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So love seeing how amazing talent moves on to what’s next. Cheering for @nytlizrobbins #careerreinvention #bydn… https://t.co/2ZeA4QNLSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great food and company at the Fish House! We even had a visit from a beautiful pelican https://t.co/Bl1vOn5RSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueEyeTheSpy Why are thousands of illegals getting in this country at the border. They’re being bussed into San Diego and Phoenix!!! 😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! 🙏🏻 This is great. @BookRiot @BWRBooks 📚 #mash4077th #4077thmash #alanalda #lorettaswit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m facetiming my girl and watching Harry Styles videos and she said “I wish you would look at me like that” HDGDUSJSBSJ TEA😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[barnett newman, onement, 1948, moma, nyc 🇺🇸 #barnettnewman #onement #zip #moma #eua em MoMA The Museum of Modern Art https://t.co/3qxxn5iRO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess the yoga is not working. Are the classes Court ordered for anger management??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to take on the city of dreams! Hello NYC✨✨🏙 https://t.co/wf8w4jFkId]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maria_risener @DrPhil I have two children with autism  and an ex husband who took off- u have no idea that these m… https://t.co/UeOBuGrRIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[pitbulls are banned from apartment complexes because they can be potentially dangerous, and yet...men are still all… https://t.co/p8PH1KylqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m serious, I cannot stop crying. I’m not even sad my eyes are just so watery and keep dropping them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goes to work: Writes all day.  Gets home: Writes all evening.  Four ... more ... pages.   *Dies*  #MidtermWeek… https://t.co/ZPle2UuO7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK Me too. Not that I have been on twitter long or have tweeted much - but a lot of people start "followin… https://t.co/001Zy5vvfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cmblom2420 @RepMarkMeadows This time he brought documents to back the truth. Trump also threatened his father in l… https://t.co/7jOZIgTUjb]]></document></documents></author>