<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Love me some @drinkatfranklin and all the @UnionHG restaurants. #Foodiechats Best spots in @ChooseChicago for sure.… https://t.co/vkeLj7hESn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadapsmith I think it would be cool for your Mom to sit down at the @RedTableTalk with @TameraMowryTwo to get a fe… https://t.co/50NM4TkbvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This kid runs his house. Teach our kids respect. Kids will do this but won’t make eye contact, say thank you to som… https://t.co/XlTJLV2a7Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnsBible Looks like @realDonaldTrump work on Tariffs is helping.  Trump Org really benefiting from this bigly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisaponyexpress @GarDolphin733 @galvan_naomi @JasonCowboysMan @Tinanicole96 @GailYou72514463 @NancyFrazer1… https://t.co/NLJfxY8Rbi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the educated tweets!! 🙏🏾🙏🏾🙏🏾 I have passed this to my followers also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like a real college student for the very first time as I’m currently wearing sweatpants to class #NoSweat #GenBioHurts #Ouch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@concrackhouse @4YrsToday Everything you said is BULLSHIT. Same script. Shove it where the sun don't shine...in RUSSIA!! GET OUT BOT!! NOW!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“God I really like that Tom Brady fellow he’s the best” or “chicken parm is gross”. Either or and you know to call… https://t.co/SuOTWd0VQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[MORE DUCK AND RUN combined with STICK YOUR HEAD IN THE SAND Foreign Policy...SAD....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mj_lee And there’s almost three feet of snow on the ground here AND WE HAVEN’T HAD A SNOW DAY HERE IN 40 YEARS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best. App. EVER! Free to play, easy to learn. Over $225k in prizes. Think you can beat me? Download Vestly now. https://t.co/5XSdhvP9Sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prattprattpratt When Conen was asking you what exercises you did everyday, you sputtered and lost your cool. You k… https://t.co/8ny25eWHNE]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a long day to end the short month, I want to thank all my friends and family who showed support and reposted… https://t.co/GOaJJSX6Cb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reck1568 @PowerGPUcom Oh. I buy power. Yeah they fucking BLOW. ! I bought from them years ago. Had a temp module i… https://t.co/tDif1QdnBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you think about the lack of recourses in the West Charlotte Community, Id give a band to anyone that could nam… https://t.co/s2f72Zd2vL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“for though i fall i will rise again though i sit in the darkness The Lord will be my light” micah 7:8    💡 for any… https://t.co/c6eAkefYtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon_Pardy I feel like @partypoker and @ThirstLounge tats have been paid for and are waiting for you to ink up. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAO https://t.co/mP5NOkjSU5 explains how to solve world hunger without huge investments. Allowing people to take c… https://t.co/63kLSJiTev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our hearts and prayers go out to you. I can’t imagine your sorrow. Do not stop fighting Andrew. You have more suppo… https://t.co/Yq2qJ73IsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoFilter 🌴🔥 HAPPY #FRIDAY! All I could say was, “Oh my GOD” when I looked up and saw this view!  _________________… https://t.co/Q6GkrvimSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real societal change happens in and through Christians who are being transformed as they pray, then demonstrate a c… https://t.co/xmHv18BQPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarriottBonvoy my first hotel stay as a #Bonvoy Memeber! @LeMeridien here in Houston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it on something that outlasts it. William James]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump you need to be locked up for lying to use American people  .u only won because of Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[The time is nigh...@GSAthletics_MBB can clinch a title at home for the first time since ‘92.   #SouthernNotState 5… https://t.co/MahAxVhhu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian Conrad 6’2, 275 Lbs 3.8 GPA All CIF All Moore League- Senior looking for a college. @apufootball… https://t.co/jVEtUjaT99]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a lot of fun at McDermott staff Birthday parties! @ church of Christ on McDermott Road https://t.co/wPlKCvKoF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr Chris Wallace.... Steven Miller got his ass handed to him by me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975TheFanatic @975Mornings You can’t block John Heyman if he already block you https://t.co/cPYV7IMgkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[No point in spending much time replying to this line of low class, obviously liberal crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m addicted to peer pressure! I love falling victim to it. https://t.co/xPZq6wUA17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current mood: nineinchnails at @kingsbklyn last October. As always one hell of a show. Though this clip is of a son… https://t.co/tKdD75Rz55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rottenapple4480 @EricIslander If your getting a proven young talent like matter for 7 years it’s worth it. Look at… https://t.co/OPLUGUn1r8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rihanna when she sees a Lebron and Beyonce joke https://t.co/N2jwXKISYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsSoCaLSAVAGE think he got a gf irl and quit twitter but I have no clue. There’s so many people from my old twitte… https://t.co/PRYF5gaJZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richiesuavee @DeuceThomas How does two of the rockets best players foul out? How does that even happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeterGartman @DavidBCollum Ok, so are we talking about in addition to property taxes? That’s not unexpected, but D… https://t.co/D85UmgCz2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys, Luigi here! . . This coming up week I will be turning 15 weeks old! To celebrate I would really like to f… https://t.co/WxCGzhJcia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Citrus Berliner Weisse by Untitled Art at @flyingsaucerral — https://t.co/nlDJrbDOi1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flockofdimes @thepinhook @teentheband it was such a fun, wholesome, and heartwarming set, jenn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing you a lovey day.  #papimilo @makeupbymilo  #sunrise  #florida  #🌞 @ Sunrise, Florida https://t.co/0oAip449i7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaldRoberts It’s a beauty, filled with amazing stories and strategies to help #teachers, #runners, and everyone el… https://t.co/vzPQmcVJiN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @michaeljknowles Or the $64,000,000,000 that Obama gave to Iran]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Classmates Reunions to meet back up...Detroit Pershing High Love https://t.co/8DU3zf6mbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qué hago comiendo pop tarta de desayuno? Tráiganme un pan con torreja pls]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Study the Constitution. Let it be preached from the pulpit, proclaimed in legislatures, and enforced in courts of… https://t.co/FlXN5gTald]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BLOODY VALENTINES DAY!   Because if it’s true love, it’s a punch in the face...  #cupidthedestroyer #cupid… https://t.co/kAnjViKbBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP @realDonaldTrump dressed for Vietnam cocktail party with Kim Fong Goo 🤔 https://t.co/iGblf2kJnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of questions heading into tonight's Academy Awards ceremony. I asked https://t.co/sUYcCuXtDp assistant editor… https://t.co/ZpIz0Gnwpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chozen Martial Arts Academy can help you focus on your dreams. Go to https://t.co/vIiiplEMq1 @ Chozen Martial Arts… https://t.co/9ZF9yQAZLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haquesman @_haallee Says the fool that thinks slapboxing is a personality trait 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperDaveJoker @GaileHolly @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @POTUS @USATODAY No, they just punched him in the face. Actual violence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DetroitParaDPX @amybruni @AdamJBerry @PaperRouteProd making is beautifully creepy🎥🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[As Brexit approaches, Greek Ministry provides guidance for UK Citizens in Greece https://t.co/9EX9UHBcOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or some combination of kids and $ amount. There is no sure thing at this point, but its a good shot. As good of sho… https://t.co/rI5m8V0n7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RGreggKeller We must be doing something right if they are all against it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m going to send out some legit bullying facts every hour. Feel free to share. Fact #1 - Cyberbullying is ge… https://t.co/9J6tV7aKvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbeersFIGHTS You’ve been on fire with ur picks man 🔥🔥 good luck here 👊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nascar_opinion Let’s have a Bristol double header day with two 150 lap races   One of their races should be ridicu… https://t.co/TM6l7ZV6An]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tantas anécdotas y tantas aventuras juntos ¡Gracias por todo amigos! Que se repita pronto... en Mexicali, Baja Cali… https://t.co/Hzl1stuLkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellmoreJFK will observe a moment of silence to honor the 17 lives lost during the Marjory Stoneman Douglas High S… https://t.co/6X4FlwqEqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar @realDonaldTrump @amyklobuchar you would be a great president I think you'd do excellent job, I hope… https://t.co/PNoQ7nf09P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j66anderson @LVMotorSpeedway @Lucas_Oil @JohnBommarito @BommaritoAuto @ImpactbyMCS Solid showing last night my dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachel2manypaws Do you have bluebirds? Everybody’s got bluebirds now when did that happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc if Michael Jackson raped the shut out them white boys they foul asL for tryna say some when folks dead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDNpoll_watcher But if I did that, how else will people have someone to sanctimoniously tweet at in order to get their Internet Points?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollinCapone The answer to where he was for the Hall trade is in the article.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman Yes, I am a Democratic Jew as well.  I believe there: is no such thing as too much equality.  I wa… https://t.co/0l8C3W6Svz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadank1 @brianstelter @ReliableSources Did you notice my location? Quincy ma.  Only City of Presidents in AMERICA.… https://t.co/tANMmDBjXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is downright shameful😮What in the world😡😡😡 I pray that all of this isn’t true. To go so far as causing yoursel… https://t.co/2U0UnMQWvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindofSnaps The eyebrows take away from the fivehead and wrinkles 🙄🤦🏻‍♂️ https://t.co/VdnMHNDaO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii If the fascist wall actually gets built, we’ll run and win on #TearDownThisWall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Christina63034 @yogagenie This is one of the reasons why I am not involved with the Catholic Church.  After being… https://t.co/po1voTXp9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaturallyTyraG Falsely call the police on me or something.   But I would refuse to acknowledge ones presence after that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavWill13 The only team I thought he would excel for was the Phillies.  He will most likely kill it in that park.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisawesome63 @BennyBallin2010 Guzman is definitely not #1, most experienced tho..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armandodkos Naw it is who he is, he believes that if WWC makes more money they stop being racist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre game sledding! Ready for @RamblersMBB #OnwardLU #GoRamblers https://t.co/GoRpAnE9HZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone tells you, you can't", their showing you their limits not yours." -Unknown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve watched #SerialMom like 5 times this week. https://t.co/fMQyKH3k6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not checking work email after 5 pm and on weekends ... it greatly reduced stress]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerMosleyTMO Going 45 in a 30 screw a ticket... cuz I ain’t had that T Mo in a minute in a minute. I’m on the wa… https://t.co/SIAPfQXIN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great week my friends! Don’t forget to #StepOverTheEdge. https://t.co/GLb26cYCK8 @Lolz1975Tilly @Julz_Crown… https://t.co/ouBbMJmq7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[ROMA DE CUARÓN GANÓ EL OSCAR MENOS UN LUGAR EN LAS PANTALLAS DE CINÉPOLIS  Oiga usted que poca madre del dueño del… https://t.co/SKjfrWzm78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SneakyJoeWGR Correction, 3 more ints, JA with a better YPA and this those tds number is which is close, is one less season than tyree]]></document><document><![CDATA[View tonight. Hopefully viewing this a lot. #FlaPanthers https://t.co/N4kyzwlXqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do pedophiles make such good music? #LeavingNeverland #SurvivingRKelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magastorybook I didn’t think it was possible for any human being to stoop as low as you did this week - but, hey,… https://t.co/kvO60C8VoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *opens Google, types “gay shakespe”—* The internet: https://t.co/xof22s1mqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B70737 Yes : i Know that !! I'm living in a Dream World make it plan and Simple and Nobody get Hurt !! That will b… https://t.co/NJ634wwa5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadians - we drink whiskey to keep us warm, then we put ice in it to make it cool... then we put some sugar in it… https://t.co/GcjfNOQbBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big thank you to everyone in Toledo who voted for us! So honored to receive this amazing award! remax @tcpaper… https://t.co/h5Zg2SNHUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyndalKnight @_youhadonejob1 @courtneey_clark @chaseo_lane @KaileyFrancetic https://t.co/TzNT1rQwhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AaronHGriffing @NickSlyBirdGuy You'll hear about the "Magic Hedge" the moment you step off the plane! The lake sho… https://t.co/I33riyflYu]]></document><document><![CDATA[meu maior problema hoje com o canal é que eu não tenho tempo pra editar, mas quando aparece aquele diazinho livre e… https://t.co/8pRUMvOlHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ion GAF how 💯 you is in my face if yeen loyal behind my back  then fuck u 💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seated for LITTLE MONSTERS, Lupita Nyong’o vs zombies! #sxsw https://t.co/2twVJTLf0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbotnyse @johnkrausphotos @SpaceX Not quite. But in the upper atmosphere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherryT33116069 @ThisIsKris10 @MickeyKnox_xxx LoL 😂 I bet she had a hard time explaining that situation 🤣😂🤣😂]]></document></documents></author>