<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@sweetriknlady @DJZJCZ @jennifersterri1 @lcotton92264 @tracybarnes2604 @Pennyyo79 @sharon_kk @IrisD236 @MelloSutts… https://t.co/qfwTnQzvSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaroncarter Gonna stay up for this❤️❤️ just havs to be tired as fuck at work tomorrow but it will be worth it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Best President ever and they are so envious and jealous of this good man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kind of my new favorite swimsuit here. Thanks @target! 🐆🐆🐆🎯 #bodypositive #cheetah @ Midnight Pass Beach https://t.co/NujR0NVza4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fusion Lift! A little multitasking! #wedoitdifferently #welift #dailyfitpost #fitchick #fitness #fitnessdaily… https://t.co/jtnhhNlIV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @LindseyGrahamSC @margbrennan The barrier (wall) which is not needed takes $ from important services… https://t.co/QmTKrYwU89]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2. I accepted a challenge from @MrGullion and @CGeorge_AP to post the cover of 7 books I love; no explanation o… https://t.co/1dNN3mjVwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing my shitty whore makeup for you baby ✨💕  Mine by @slayyyter https://t.co/6uU0XDar60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TriSARAtopp I’ve been going for 9 hours with a 10 min break. Not good. Crazy effin day 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder..well I guess I'll get back to my date with Management, Reproduction, Food Bac and Bug... #funniness… https://t.co/ju5WkhVEJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @jdawsey1 Please tell me how is your wife or anybody else advising him!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Am_I_Write @HollowayLit #AskHollowayIntern Thanks for doing this, Samantha! My question is about the so-called slu… https://t.co/MNL9FlMBuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chadwick_Moore @SprockDaddy Ok now we are officially in the twilight zone - Rahm Emmanuel is complaining about Omar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Br0wn_ you’re making me think long john silvers is just a money laundering scheme 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kina_purrs I can’t with you 😂😂😂 coming soon in June I’ll let up  know ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard you got some new homies, got some new hobbies, even a new hoe too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bee_baileys @ParamedicNat1 and I will be sharing the stage here, reading something we wrote together for the… https://t.co/OOfWNneXfG]]></document><document><![CDATA[im only awake rn bc i wanna listen to the new jonas brothers song in about 6 minutes thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throwback to September 2016.  I have not been able to do this pose since then.  I now realize that my approach was… https://t.co/JLetnMu0ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[really not fucking with Blari &amp; Bels rn.. cause they doing what I should be doing 🙄😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 6th birthday to my puppy!!! Love you gizmo! You have changed my world! We also make sure not to feed him afte… https://t.co/p9xKdw1msf]]></document><document><![CDATA[These numbers are really really important. I see the US Methodists becoming their own church.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PWCSNews @SuperPWCS Steve, u cancel school tm I’ll give u $100 Monopoly money AND I’ll give u New York Avenue.  🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Via FB): 6. Ashton Anchors (Star Ocean 2). I love my weird shy anxious whirling vortex of death, and his character… https://t.co/WNzmVjF1Rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery @BreitbartNews But in order for us to get it he should have said he was against it till got to senate!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aisag2003 @Winston_ES @EISDofSA @DrH_OnTheEdge @EisdPtacouncil @EISDFE @winston_pta @csanchez8254 @Rebecca__Rivas… https://t.co/ue3ErrrLBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @JasonHughes_12  on your win!!!! https://t.co/OyFap9wZuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah baby! Years of isolated, solitude, and insomnia have paid off. Level 1000! https://t.co/IsWPoXa8Wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Kansas City had good Clubs. When I look at my friends in Cali and Texas clubs me lit no matter what day of t… https://t.co/qjOnmXLpkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[UCLA launches the country’s first intensive affordable housing development course https://t.co/5E2DpfaTIy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CjChatham @bryonthor @Oh_tooly3 There’s a vast difference in the coverage the NBA and the WNBA get though. Which c… https://t.co/NeBvjJIDih]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true!!! YOU make a difference doing what you do best!! https://t.co/7Zcs5XWd1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think i want kids until the 1 time of the month i have to go to Walmart and I see toddlers having tantrums every 3 aisles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Оппозиционер Мария Баронова перешла на работу в RT: https://t.co/IABRMndogO via @ru_rbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Harass, Harass, Harass, Harass, Harass, Harass,   I’m Just making small-scale attacks on the enemy… https://t.co/k2mMSZDYS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Edwards @JeffreyGoldberg @TaylorLorenz Well @threadreaderapp simplifies it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[«Your power against me is useless! I am a FORCE OF NATURE unto myself!» 😠 . . . #AFOL #smallafol #lego #legobatman… https://t.co/26iu4xa2An]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Michael Tomasky, for the autographed book! #ifwecankeepit (@ Dick O'Dow's Irish Pub in Birmingham, MI)… https://t.co/1MMeJVjCy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotwomennn @CheriJacobus @TheCapitalTruth @Jeannie1Genie @Perpetual_Now @elva_morris I doubt she would go out in… https://t.co/4uSJIOdT0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t work baby girl your time is coming. 🙏🏾 keep ya head up n keep working]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport - @atlairport in Atlanta, GA https://t.co/nJ4O2Br4wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldSoulMama Mama... you need a new soul.. this is inexcusable and detrimental to women’s rights to their own bodies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talieb3 @JacygalResists @7brdgesroad @lovemyjessica22 @MsEmmaPeele @CharismaMolotov @ElleWibble @Momof2in1year… https://t.co/03nZrdTrkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY SUNNY 🌞 WEDNESDAY, TWITTER FRIENDS! The crocus bulbs Hubby @rawlins_steve planted in a pot indoors are starti… https://t.co/SLCboJN41k]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had a bad breakup in the 6 grade and never recovered and consider that’s the hardest relationship ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jkempcpa I very much doubt it will be Sanders. Don't have a strong feeling as to who the Dem nominee will be, but… https://t.co/2nTG3s6MMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @SilverTConsltg   to post the covers of 7 books that I enjoy; no explanation, no reviews and no… https://t.co/AZJyvB1rLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1075daverocks  While we know @JessieDavid99 won’t be giving up🍺, swearing et all for lent. #morningbuzz   I am mor… https://t.co/w9qHjam7fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[El trabajo por cuenta propia es excelente porque puedes ser tu propio jefe, pero definitivamente puede ser complica… https://t.co/YNl9nKpheF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies, has anyone ever told you to be “careful”? This really resonated with me tonight when my husband (for the re… https://t.co/VDhAmTiJR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at dt girly arms. What a wimpy pos next to a true American hero. It sickens me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a couple of first timers here at #ICE19! Welcome @MichelleAnklam &amp; @ChargersLibrary to the fun!… https://t.co/RsEUrM2tdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL They should look out for the students and best financial plan to do the best within their budget,… https://t.co/2xRPRdeWEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what finally uploaded?! Enjoy MINIMAL MAKEUP MONDAY ON A TUESDAY lol love you butterflies. Now I'm going to g… https://t.co/kbtJxu8MDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjillian You are doing so freaking awesome so far! Keep it up girl! #kickcancersass]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogerJ_Cole @MissBeehive @dovey_karen @leslie_wilkes @CrowleyOnAir @RealDMitchell @DepechistWorld @yvonnemilnedelw… https://t.co/rDj75hFOrh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mediaite Well, we now know who is one of the stupidest people in South Dakota. @SenatorRounds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family time at the ol wfuclubtennis tonight! #exerciseandfamilytime #cherisheverymoment @ Wake Forest Tennis Complex https://t.co/Ar9xEk9FPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooper’s Hawk in the rain 🧡 “God gives every bird his worm but He does not throw it into the nest” - P.D. James… https://t.co/qOeXBgaxGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Opening Day to this baseball loving boy!! 🐯🐯His first high school game is today!!  Go Tigers!! #todayistheday… https://t.co/HWlEIMrCbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[this girl just saw me walking outside my building and still held the elevator for me https://t.co/1qQwgnGXkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My ingrate son didn't like the light up sneakers I got him so I took em back and got me a new tote instead. Why doe… https://t.co/b9DYkN1VPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eres la persona mas hermosa sin importar lo que otras personas digan de ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachbarnhart @KevinFady Or people are powerless to stop and powerful approve.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expectation vs Reality   #kaybye #makeup #jeffreestarcosmetics #maccosmetics  #sugarpillcosmetics #katvondbeauty… https://t.co/dEFS0nMTtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[These companies willingly sponsor a show with a host who thinks raping child brides is less bad than a stranger mol… https://t.co/vP83hr8ehG]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's hoping the toaster oven and the dishwasher can peacefully coexist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weirdest phone call to a parent: “Can you please come pick up your kids because the smell of skunk overwhelming our… https://t.co/Xj6CHKBQY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I wish I could just dye my hair pink and tat myself out but 🤷🏽‍♀️  c’est la vie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will work for Instagram pic. 📸  #whatimwearing ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ Outfit details (more deets at link in bio!):  Jacket:… https://t.co/dBK89qHPjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sexy Disney Princes: Eric #humor #snicker #grin #humorous https://t.co/kykRop6QWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramiroczar Hell yeaa! We need that maruchan with that limon and maybe some tapatio if possible? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandiKHOU It's a toss up between Thomas Jefferson &amp; Abraham Lincoln. How about you? #iamup]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my perfect world Bradley Cooper proposes to Lady Gaga after performing at the #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No problem.Makes perfect https://t.co/E60y5io4w2 a few$M,take a little pressure off Un and prepare… https://t.co/DVSoRDD41D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Bandit1980 @DCComics @Marvel @kinky_horror @LolaMurder @tmudder4 @ohamymarie @Embalmist @AgeofSmut… https://t.co/K5a6UG4bXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[The show was mediocre but the afterparty was delicious https://t.co/gibSZWM0nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whistleblowers sounded alarms about plan backed by Trump advisers to transfer sensitive nuclear technology to Saudi… https://t.co/5heXwF1XC8]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING EVERYBODY. IT IS MARCH... WHICH MEANS @Brewers BASEBALL IS BACK THIS. MONTH. THIS MONTH. 💙💛 #ThisIsMyCrew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a really great day!  🔆💛 #Saturdayfunday #Legoland #weekendvibes #goldmembers #brosforlife #boysboysboys… https://t.co/XtV143kxmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[had to play sweet home alabama and all summer long to make sure that we were, in fact, in alabama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @Lawrence @LynPaolo I'm thinking, with a very high dose of an antipsychotic medication?]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀 forward to this dance every year!  @evasheroes brings such joy to so many in our community! Brad plays while form… https://t.co/jNL8wUtRru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SupportMW There’s some good pics of @MauraWest!! Just stunning!! 🥰💞😘 https://t.co/YHSpC6CVkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me #WIN a $75 Amazon Gift Card! Easy entry! Enter @CloudMom's #giveaway here: https://t.co/FUPKjqAVUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PISDEdtech Kristi Fortenberry 2nd grade @Spradley_El Dorry I’m late to the party... Open House. 🤗 #Prosper4ward https://t.co/KTDx8Fpae6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kalúke... and the laser.🐾💕🐾 #kalúke #biggestkitty #affectionate #bigboy #11andahalfmonthsold #felinepersuasion… https://t.co/oTgMoyCizo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why Mrs. Grimm is awesome! Kids. Come. First. https://t.co/eEWFTzz8YU #ProudToBeAWildkat]]></document><document><![CDATA[After seeing this done last year with leaders @MMSMesquite1 I'm excited to read #TheArtofCoaching with… https://t.co/qWeKPRxmtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsVee_ It is strange. But like much of everything else, I’m thinking that it’s by design.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends and family — help me fundraise for rare cancer research at @Sloan_Kettering. Every donation to my… https://t.co/o0XREvnubO]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL. That is not what Alan said. Think for yourself, snowflake. And learn to read.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for @tanamongeau to win the #ShortyAwards. That is all. https://t.co/lPwTSOaPXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Elon, that profile pic looks like fade to #Mars the red planet?? Don't panic ! You have millions of peopl… https://t.co/1C5wC2nFeh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeallMs What a great point! AND this year I take about ten minutes each day to spend some time reading professiona… https://t.co/AC9auRmlWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟💥🌟 PSK FLASH SALE 🌟💥🌟  The original Premium Starter Kit with Desert Mist Diffuser is now 10% off starting now unti… https://t.co/DlLICIIxVi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picking up trash in his own yard while black. Since when is that a crime?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does the Jonas brothers new song sound like they never stopped making songs for the past 4 years, I love it 😭😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[as much as i love BP...this is way too much to be charging for a GENERAL ADMISSION TICKET ! it’s literally just a G… https://t.co/pS5xRNif8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[In mundane news, I have introduced my @ElyriaRose to the old Chris Carter show, Millennium. Like many, she agrees t… https://t.co/gG6MzioTbR]]></document></documents></author>