<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Named after female revolutionaries ... Two hour wait ... Have to try this place... #Denver #Colorado… https://t.co/4SfKuC0LC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Barbara Jordan of our generation, google it all u newbies https://t.co/zhbrhUMY81]]></document><document><![CDATA[More well-paying #Ohio jobs gone under @MikeDeWine and @realDonaldTrump.   But I’m sure a Dollar Store will open so… https://t.co/RUPkKigRjW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up feeling blessed to be alive.👊 . Wake up with an urgency.💥 . Wake up knowing that you are the only one that… https://t.co/cmlc3IzlQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yet they were doing all they could to get Machado...plus who in the hell would Harper be blocking? Robert? Eloy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say hello to my little friend... #onset #filmlife #actorslife #waitingtoshoot #snowman @ Catskill, New York https://t.co/gydv6jWEB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the time of year @StateFarm reminds me to evaluate my life insurance policy. And I’m reminded that when I die… https://t.co/yJEBsGBnJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished day 18 of the @YouVersion plan 'It Starts With Me'. Check it out here: https://t.co/2q3jLNbgih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rosenstein to Leave Justice Department Next Friday, Sources Say https://t.co/U6qsUN3YIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ederson won’t get enough credit for this pass. And people would still rather have Alison than Ederson. Laughable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we're slamming from a bourbon flask before @Metallica -- obviously adults here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently treason, which was once punished by death, now only deserves a slap on the wrist. Judge Ellis has given… https://t.co/on5MyxVpWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Here_4_It Oh okay I was using Google for the Pharmacies Benevides which is one of the largest and best stocked pha… https://t.co/ZUkpO0ijnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cooking calms me!!! #iluhtocook #menthatcook #husbandmaterial #him #melanin #thehen #saintlouis #smile #locs… https://t.co/FvvPONsidL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbadger26 @MarcusReports @SNAFU_Sara Assault weapon is whatever Congress declares it is,  or a president decides i… https://t.co/OYQIPN5A6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the game Highlights from our game vs Tennessee Wesleyan https://t.co/Z2LPMBZ5Ip  Huge S/O to… https://t.co/amQZlmdjyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re excited to be in #NYC today with @rarediseasesint to talk the future of international #rarediseases advocacy!… https://t.co/jV0IWnUJUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coworker just sent around the email announcing teams for trivia night with a picture of Alex Trebek. He had no idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ishabazz Amazing what you can do when you’re not meeting with lobbyists all day and working on reelection instead of policy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP_Politics @AP Wasn't it called the California Bulls**t Train? California gets back less than $1 for each $1 sent… https://t.co/4S6Yl8oD65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xzamilloh @Trishmcb71Trish @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump The game’s about to start, I wish you both well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine Good.  Go right to the source and sue the Continent of Africa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[light rain -&gt; clear sky temperature down 35°F -&gt; 32°F humidity up 77% -&gt; 85% wind 6mph -&gt; 8mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poco Anything With Your Name On It Should Be Filed Under Jokes For The Democrats. !!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good set of twins?   #hugginshonda #hondacivictyper #hondaculture @ Huggins Honda https://t.co/2ITmhpM8jJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattzap Make no mistake you continue to peddle this garbage.  McCabe is going to prison and someone should break your...]]></document><document><![CDATA[What law school allow tgis guy to teach there, also so i can make sure i never gire a lawyer from that school. If y… https://t.co/IOC5GgT95W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP you guys are a sell out this bill is garbage I hope a good independent runs your party is going down you all l… https://t.co/0NkqpBS3TJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t count all,the times I have been in the cashier line at Walmart and the persons in front of me with expensiv… https://t.co/hEnoon5mgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N3GatorFan True. Wife (5' 2") does fine reaching things most of the time, but seeing over people can be a problem.… https://t.co/KDSFO7R6i8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and Shine! off we go to Minneapolis for the Thunder game tonight, reports from the court at 5,6 and 10.  #News9Thunder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the greatest storyteller of all time @madflavor https://t.co/4gsZ5mRM6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sak pasé? Wah yah seh? Runnin up, all this cake Bag it up, den come right away  https://t.co/nTGatuXjcG https://t.co/j47DqX5tKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld  👏👏👏 Well Done Greg ! Getting in Juan’s grill after years of him insulting and Jesse and threatening t… https://t.co/CDscHvdRCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you just listened to the reporters following the @indians you would think their odds are.much worse....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap. That shot to win the #TacoBellSkills at the #NBAAllStar by @jaytatum0 was amazing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say life is a roller coaster they are dead wrong. They have the ups and downs right but you know what y… https://t.co/fwhmT9Ihg5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I'm so proud of how @UNCGpepband @uncg_danceteam and @UNCGcheer did tonight. There were so many more Wofford… https://t.co/rFuM5z8jlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bhofheimer_espn Thanks for all your help, Bill! Excited for the future]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still really need to get to a game in Vegas. Tickets though....them shits expensive af]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is our grand pup Dexter. He doesn't like the other dogs on TV. https://t.co/j2YTZUa9q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_pence @realDonaldTrump @MattBevin Only in America.... https://t.co/BnCZyfldby]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeanie just needs to show a video of the last 18 yrs of the Knicks Front Office in order to scare everyone straight… https://t.co/K5SfDIXqrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlooritHammer Looks promising here seems like management is getting things together]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demthagod He usually doesn’t smell, but the past two nights he’s been so ripe. Ew.   And I’m still waiting for my text response... 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SilliestShane @grandma_satan A moment of silence for the dearly departed, please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonEvansLee1 @chrishemsworth @MensHealthMag @Hearst Thank you. Congratulations to you, as well, sir! https://t.co/sflRCJnnDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LanceMcAlister @Break_Man @barleycornsky Had smu +4 ...it was super bowl for SMU and they played above their heads… https://t.co/aLPlTr1oOK]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna know why the twist to open caps on Wallflowers are opposite of literally any other twist to open cap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kj_brent @EddiePaskal @travis_braz It’s not only real, it was my Christmas card back in the day 😂 Shouts out the M… https://t.co/TbS34nQn6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvilERUReady Oh man I love that album.  But Boss Audz keeps it on her room.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatAtDisney If the disability boarding wasn’t there then Space Mountain would constantly be broken down. https://t.co/RiTqDCS8jJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasie @ScottWalker @MittRomney @LindseyGrahamSC Or Dukakis on the tank. Woops. https://t.co/jVNe2qU7pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoffeeIsLife06 Always. I would hope most kids wouldn’t fall for it, but I’m afraid a lot would]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirensaysnope The fact you went 10 hours without needing to go to the restroom, hence the realization, is amazing unto itself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@G2themez @Seiderman That's amazing, if only they were playing better to make this cheekiness more fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas @RyanHockeyGuy @JesseGranger_ Nate’s offensive involvement/engagement has increased considerably with… https://t.co/etaoYnz6ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jteater12 @ashleybell22 congrats to both of you.  especially Josh for being able to convince Ashley to marry him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBilas @DevonairJackson @texas_sportsman @Aaron_Torres This is so terrible lol. The athletes are students. Free… https://t.co/CkjbLatriG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Sanders is a typical lying scumbag Democrat politician. Never practices what he preaches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr You never know who may be around to lend a 'hand' to good  old Lord Farquaad and his band of fake r… https://t.co/SGQC4uwUlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigvecc @KOAAGrant I’m not sure I’ve ever received a more appropriate compliment. At least I think it’s a compliment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bendiciones muy buenos días bueno a empezar el día con toda la buena actitud contamos con un poquito de nieve]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Elate coming to town for the #AzeriStakes @OaklawnRacing that makes me a very happy horse racing fan. Yes shes my… https://t.co/yBsNDLh14Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more he defends his position the deeper his hole gets dug  The longer he allows himself to stay in the ditch it… https://t.co/kjJ4Wox6zz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clippers' Williams becomes NBA bench points leader in win  https://t.co/A9Bm9IiQLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcusleshock You have that and we have Spinner Sharks ! https://t.co/DLs6h5SFrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you guys know that the giraffe has vocal chords but due to its incredibly long thick neck they can’t produce su… https://t.co/pHL0XIwCzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeevedFerret I will remind ya now, with the time difference I have no idea when things close or when it's the last… https://t.co/0HocPk4B5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorSalgado21 @MichaelFox400 @rvillz_65 This man was pretty flames tooo https://t.co/BNzAJBZh5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlonchoo1610 @juliomario55555 @oscarca93800318 @argiro1961 @IvanCepedaCast @AlvaroUribeVel @JuanManSantos… https://t.co/xkaZSIghWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few pics from the last few days. Great to have the family out in #grandjunction with me! @ Colorado https://t.co/KgyLEjM6wh]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's a silent guardian, a watchful protector. A dark knight https://t.co/eIfCvZb3JE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whaaaaaaat kids actually have a snow day tomorrow?! Damn lucky kids lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Tennessee baseball team is all over a solid North Florida team 10-2 right now.,]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lance Stewart - Marry had a little d*ck ! https://t.co/34E4wqOIl9 via @YouTube This video would make a great meme someday for young adults!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyItsGregA @MattRandazzo Great, Nolan will graduate and THEN you get a Portillos. Not cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sumnerd @alisontroup Well, This was just a joke that took off :-). Can’t wait to read link!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for all of the loving people in my life. What a blessing!  Thanks for having breakfast with me, @jjtejkl .… https://t.co/24ZLWXTqaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kowenmoffor Like I just said. The man deserves complete disgust and people want to divert and justify. Why?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @SchneiderCNN @TheLeadCNN This lady just lied her backside off!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeylawrence @DavidFaustino Can’t wait to see. I was there in the crowd watching.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheaSerrano In my neck of the woods in Jalisco Mexico we would just call this Carne con Chile]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bugslife #BLESSED @ Westlake Village, California https://t.co/NyURJhHNCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillianDain @WWEUsos They really need to be in conversation for best tag team champs all time]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not the start JU was looking for, just 1/7 from the field to start while Liberty is 4/5. Highlights from there plus… https://t.co/5rAbAgW23e]]></document><document><![CDATA[La pobresa de una nación se combate con trabajo y no con pensiones ni canastas básicas, lo que AMLO esta haciendo e… https://t.co/LgklY7PSV9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Garagehammer @maximum_pants @Pjschard @SexyDragonMagic @FenskeNick @Rhellion Yeah, I have my own army book, but tr… https://t.co/jxzldFIxq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disneyland 2019 #StarWars #Disneyland #Disney @ Disneyland https://t.co/kheKX3V1Q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpearlman @gehrig38 He used to come to a grocery store I worked at in high school.  Large portion of customers… https://t.co/jpjG30fOH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home Norcal playoff game tomorrow (Tuesday 2/26/19) against Sequoia at 7 PM.  Let’s go Pack!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Israeli PM calls French cemetery vandals 'wild anti-Semites' (AP)// 'wild'? .. nor sure if 'wild' is watt idea… https://t.co/krfnNefR8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJHughes45 I hope if you wrote an autobiography that “You Up?” is the title]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coyote fur is in big demand thanks to popular parkas https://t.co/mRPO6C4y1m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dónde encuentro a  alguien que jale conmigo a todos los estrenos chingones en el cine??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting close to first pitch! Join us for @libertybaseball vs Delaware on the radio at 93.3 FM Lynchburg or online… https://t.co/Y5eridbDDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer “Some other reason” are called “crimes” or sometimes “felonies.” That’s why most cri… https://t.co/XRfpMvUptH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliblackdragon @B_WILL_B We will talk about this Marli!! Sorry I didn’t call you the other night, you know how tim… https://t.co/6Dgf13fGWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need new glasses😭 I’ve had the same ones since my senior year of high school 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be waiting for the police at my house to help me scrape the ice off the sidewalk their plows put on there! I’v… https://t.co/kYdus9qixk]]></document></documents></author>