<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MarkNel1026 @VRanschau @Field_Farms Mostly it’s been driven by them wanting tongue and hearts and products that US… https://t.co/5iktYWtosf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithbrainz @kimrhodes4real @realGpad We could just meet them at the finish with our DD cups.  Sounds like my kind of party]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mountain Lakes Resort in Lytle Creek, CA https://t.co/EF4r8zfYUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofpuppo @Saberdani I can get old pics. I still have the name on there too? Don’t really go on, too dead 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBROINTHEAM @oldmanebro @LAURASTYLEZ @Rosenbergradio @ShaniKulture @DJKASTONE @DJJUANYTO good mornaaan Fam!! Did y… https://t.co/B1XRZ3h3DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday #workflow always repping @whitesox #southsidehitmen https://t.co/3Palwv5ICb]]></document><document><![CDATA[This poll proves that all the people claiming that everyone on the left wants the Democratic Party to become the pa… https://t.co/FgifPPzSaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AssnDeptsFamMed has been active this year collaborating with many other orgs/projects for example CAFM, CERA, CFAS… https://t.co/dfCMvzQTGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be dramatic or anything but I lost the charger to my vibrator in the process of moving...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDailyWire Yeah working three positions4 extra credit 2pay for untrained but not being trained themselves2more… https://t.co/FhWjVPNvVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[a whole year since shit went downhill, &amp; now i will only get stronger from it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC... I will ask again...are you sure you went to college??? You are the creepy one seriously.. listen to your "O… https://t.co/KUE8dcSOmw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Signup to be the first to hear about Beto's 2020 decision: https://t.co/rX8bgu46Ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else sleep with a #pitbullpup on their head⁉️ #thisisnew #BeauBentley #sundaysnuggles🐾🐶 #furmamalife @ Fayet… https://t.co/P5uhj6kCKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kennassty True, but that wasn’t really the same because i didn’t get that drunk and neither did you 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FardigJudith @nprpolitics @realDonaldTrump Only ones who screwed DACA with the Democrats the president laid out of… https://t.co/TDZtiz7sXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be in #Hartford, #CT this upcoming weekend!  3/1-3/3.  Prebooking is available now, email me! Kimberlyrenee@pr… https://t.co/O4287wejwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MutantMaRc Ya gotta start somewhere If that's your dream then you gotta reach for the stars and dve in You have a… https://t.co/re3jJZbc5J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because weekends are for coffee and this North Park San Diego stop was one of my favourites ☕️ communalcoffee @ Nor… https://t.co/St0muYHpbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaMei62 CEMETERY is the concrete company who used blood in their concrete to make it breathable and stronger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna call out @ChrisEvans for helping out #blackqueen @ReginaKing when she won her Oscar. Made sure she didn't h… https://t.co/1TVX8TOaYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckECheeses worst customer service at your store on Midway. Understaffed, machines out of tickets, waiting, wait… https://t.co/LJ501LekyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@animallovr2 @PetraMcCarron2 I dont think Jussie told the embarrassing truth about his relationship with the Nigerian lover🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MedTricorder I think you may have been more aware if you were a racist or heard about Selma,or blacks not allowed… https://t.co/iuBgH7nj4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to all the dancers today. Who will be crowned Miss Broadway 🎭 Mr. Broadway 🎭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning hoes, make it a great day! @ Greenway - Upper Kirby, Houston https://t.co/fEmtiDbMm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby Nope, because I’ve seen many Presidents, and you are no President Mr. Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fell asleep, wake up and think “it must be around 4 am”.   It was only 12:11.   😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGarrisonSuper introduced EVERY NKY Superintendent - emphasizing they are UNITED together in opposition of HB 205… https://t.co/LXhtY7FKg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I figured today I must have gotten a bit boring. I enjoyed shopping at Sam’s today like I was on a vacation. So muc… https://t.co/UNGo6C6tMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[boston REALLY is a title town, huh? #newmacchampions #makinghistory #golions @ Bobbi Brown &amp; Steven Plofker Gym https://t.co/pt6E8O006v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to get back on a regulated sleeping schedule, so I won’t be sleeping tonight. Catch me looking like a zombie tomorrow 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kevin_Jacobsen Confession. I saw this in the theatres when it first came out. I was 14.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Tamar!!!!! BB 1st. Black Winner! #cbbus2 #BBCeleb 🍺🍷🍾 https://t.co/27MpMWmIBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s True Love #LoveOnTheMenu @hallmarkchannel https://t.co/TVi0RF0EFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please meet these lovely Swifties @taylornation13 @taylorswift13  @olds0ulswiftie_ @OldManSwiftie @dreamer_lorde… https://t.co/4dJI06Qns5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tonight for our #CobbInTechChat to chat about #studentengagement #CelebrateMonday https://t.co/c3pkb0Todr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy’s Little Side Kick. #trays10 @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/AQ6EECBSQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adorkableash_22 OH MY GOSH 😭😭😭💕 I cant believe she is turning FOUR! But I absolutely love that!!! ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelleWright1 I can download the abc live app and all of the episode are there to watch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flowerpot197 @34FryingpanA22 @TOMRJZSR @CarlBotha2 @GracieLovesUSA @t2gunner @Liberalknoitall @J_Allen_CA… https://t.co/2ebLmpim2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disgraceful how the ppl of Syria have to face foreign threats trying to steal their resources! US or Israel have no… https://t.co/YA56zTIbHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spidadmitchell I played basketball with my 7 year old for 30 seconds and was in search for an oxygen machine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impeccable curbside appeal is only the beginning to all the luxury and style you will find inside this Fort Lee hom… https://t.co/lKxnwqcphi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogersParkMan 🤣 If they bought your broken blender line, they didn't understand what they were ordering, and, perh… https://t.co/CgDUj3bVVL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking from a dream where I am telling someone in the dream about  my dream. #smh #crazysubconscious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mahopac and Ossining 2 hr delay❤️ #thanksforkeepingussafe @MahopacSchools @OssiningSchools https://t.co/4bUkaEBuwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like the type of state bird will remain a mystery....  @WGME   https://t.co/SsiZo79LVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words to live by: “anything is possible, everything is not” Never lose your optimism, but ground yourself in pragmatism #agencylife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Helen Mirren, Do you see Julia Roberts’s dress? Because THAT’S pink, hunny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solidarity with Oakland Teachers!  Invest in teachers, invest in students, invest in education, invest in our futur… https://t.co/JeooV0BqhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday, we interviewed Joe Coen of the Diocese of Brooklyn. Wait for it to drop at the end of April. (We’re a bi… https://t.co/bnn9eogizy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Do I not see #KylieJenner  in this video? Jordan looks like the girl kissing him. The girl next to him with he… https://t.co/LHHQkBX8ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu e a minha amiga não saíamos juntas a muito tempo, dai a gente resolveu sair hoje, e então eu me lembrei porque n… https://t.co/8o2vJo7LnA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus said to him in reply, "Blessed are you, Simon son of Jonah. For flesh and blood has not revealed this to you,… https://t.co/XXZjIUkMV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you aren’t PRESENTING the hell out of your gorgeous lady when she wins at bingo then baby WHAT IS YOU DOIN ?! .… https://t.co/9Q3CL6UcVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moisesgarcia97 @iwanvargas Lo de la forma ya se ha dicho anteriormente de muchas maneras. Para mi los dos Solari e… https://t.co/zVCaLFduxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom always used to say “this world is going to hell in a handbag!”   And that’s what always pops in my head when I read the news now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillieNelson Was at the concert in El Paso tonight and you are amazing!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFlipster @DavidWohl @AnnCoulter NOBODY! She’s an angry disrespectful hateful woman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t move 500 miles to work with 2 year old Thoroughbreds in training but life had other plans and it’s about gro… https://t.co/EnYIDEeCOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mood simply because I'm in control of it! #Enjoy your #day! Have an #AMAZING #life!  Great memories and amazing en… https://t.co/sB4I9wVJsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wbz your EAS test sounded like a drunk old man, as if it were running at 1/2 speed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamingSquid They do look alike. He’s very talkative. His meow is so tiny and cute. He’s a sweet boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’re dating, your family liking me is the most important thing to me tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought you were my the one for me that’s why I gave you everything 🎶🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at CVS pharmacy - @cvs_extra in Hampton, NH https://t.co/QaNUL0J76L]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA: it IS possible to be a feminist and still call other women out on their shit. If I see girls using the same ab… https://t.co/OjgwQHimaU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously another reason to watch this show @CobraKaiSeries #cobrakaiinschools]]></document><document><![CDATA[OUR LONG JOURNEY HAS BEEN REWARDED.  I met Percy during my first year of book blogging, so reading about her daught… https://t.co/Hp2eKQJK7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrickesque @BernieSanders @SenSanders  does that mean you'll take advice from Trump https://t.co/jcTtnFwTca]]></document><document><![CDATA[True peace comes only 'when the flesh is ruled by the judgment of the mind, and the mind is directed by the will of… https://t.co/xw0tr8ATBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far I have an “A” in my class and that’s been going well , except Sunday I was sooo exhausted but I got both of my assignments out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @NRA And rescind its tax exempt status like yesterday!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EsoxPhallus @misty4630 @CelticTiger357 @Renevelation @Franklin_Graham I’m only telling you what I believe is true… https://t.co/gi9pCE0JH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dunks and a strategically placed basketball.  My sweet Trey is growing up so fast ❤️. Miss you my Sesame.… https://t.co/ILkWOxKJDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. It’s stuff like this that you miss going to such a small school. I’m just... wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cfrank149 @hiyellowgoddess @MMoorw Do you have any suggestions on who? I @ a whole bunch of celebrities but again, that’s not enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gone fishing.... 😍🦈🏒🥅 #ohcaptainmycaptain #toews #sjsharks #gohawks @ SAP Center https://t.co/aESkHCZ7a8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jxviisxxvii I sold my switch and got a ps4 just so I could play this game LMAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @SethAbramson @ClassicCherub You really think or are you just messing with me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations ladies on an amazing season. Best of luck to our seniors, you will all be missed!😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryScott_Jr @DonaldJTrumpJr @trumps_feed Wrong actually Donald Trump was rewarded with the Ellis Isle Award righ… https://t.co/qYziRHVdUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[[ASMR] I recorded our cat purring and this shit is low key soothing as fuck. @aforsakensin https://t.co/s1yv6N1Bst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghelt @realDonaldTrump He could. Likely will Trump cares. OVomit did nothing. Made terrible deals with or enemies… https://t.co/6TItnjfXgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCalMusicGal I have always thought his live shows were off the chart fantastic. Underrated is right, I've often g… https://t.co/Z5gXafSEIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricRDeschamps Happy Valentines Day to You♥️       Have a Wonderful Day 🤗 https://t.co/SolgykBLB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accepted the challenge from @WRCrowley111 to  post covers of 7 books I Love: no explanations, no review, just cov… https://t.co/ndFbV1Ocjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone is outside clapping really loud. I think. Or its wood smacking against something. Not sure I wanna know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rainy gray day in Chicago calls for indoor activities. I spent my morning volunteering with One Million Degrees a… https://t.co/IqFhbjh369]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current feels on the new @Pokemon game release news https://t.co/Wt4z80ICzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cabbage is Everywhere due to St Pats.. so.. make Soup! #soupisgoodfood #cabbage #kale #carrots #ginger #garlic… https://t.co/eR55UXce8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewamiller @DelWilber Maybe so but us at the grassroots level. We understood this was to promote trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lucky fan meets Sam at the @KonaBrewingCo party  yesterday in Hawaii! TYFS on IG #sis_brasil  @SamHeughan https://t.co/rP0EnvXYAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the countries subdued to communism have been lied about it and taking under a “change for the better” experimen… https://t.co/6i5CEjhdSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m the birthday unicorn 🦄 #happeebirthdae @ The California Clipper https://t.co/jyCXQfEv9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Efecto AMLO en el mundo, ¿Una teoría posible? https://t.co/qKG3NJLolH via @YouTubem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day at the doors!  Super grateful to all of the volunteers who have been coming out!  #knockknock #cpc @ St.… https://t.co/BJfGlPaZW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ulta Beauty is in an incredible season of growth and we’re looking to add a new Hair Stylist to our team. Click for… https://t.co/ZbbM2byQ8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this some symbolism with Johnny tied up with the Cobra. Hopefully season 2 he can get some of the control ba… https://t.co/TC3RTqQrJ5]]></document></documents></author>