<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@whiskey_dreams_ It wasn't too bad. Stop by anytime. Especially on Sunday for.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarsour and the insidious cancer she represents must be marginalized. There's is an active well funded effort afoot… https://t.co/7XQ35AvXhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarcasm? I buy it. There had been assertive new regulations in the past few years, but, we are in danger zone on th… https://t.co/EzvJTWRcYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I appreciated the brooms. That was pretty good. But cutting down the nets at an opposing team’s gym? That’s some se… https://t.co/TofwyMOoxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Although she will likely never approve of any other woman in his life)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interviewed here, along with @alexgwhiting, @BarbMcQuade and others:  Trump faces a legal reckoning – but are his w… https://t.co/bXtMJWGbVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foursquare has been around 10 years.... #Wow (@ Things Fall Apart in Milwaukee, WI) https://t.co/ChCHfZ307S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brimetimenole @NW_Horadam @mwgarbett @cqholt @conorsen No one wants to spend evenings sitting in a church basement… https://t.co/Fy5cns3rSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsJeffTiedrich Although, "Cheeto Fopdoodle" has a more resonant sound.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An interesting account of Irish participation in the pilgrimage to Santiago de Compostela going back to medieval ti… https://t.co/wW5IdT5XyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigB_EOD Here's the latest revised data: https://t.co/eJPd0AuM2c (and here's someone's take on contextualizing it… https://t.co/kvtCWJiOn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriotsQueen87 Watch lacrosse both men and women. Some of the best college teams in the world are in New England.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My house is being totally demolished on the inside, water damage and asbestos. I'm exhausted and this crap is just… https://t.co/e5MoUz88r2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Liar.Of course it was your juvenile, bullying, threatening intent. You are a a disgrace to your position.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartASJax @Sports4Jax @wjxt4 @LocalTVSPXPrbs @MarcelASJax Big Facts!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn. Their potstickers were fire and they provided me the chance to have my first St Paul sandwich. Here's hoping… https://t.co/QmVaGLT872]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti You’re a delusional asshole who still believes in stupidity!!!  No normal person who supports… https://t.co/ewzL6ufAY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[انا الوحيد الي اذا شفت شي حلو فالانستقرام ومافي احد اشاركه المقطع ارسله لنفسي؟]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RitaGamer @PlayApex Rita is the guy in that pic from a video game? I have a cousin that makes visual art (,guns, s… https://t.co/VuDlgGQ69e]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Testing begins at Santa Anita, site of 21 horse fatalities since late December: It was shortly aft… https://t.co/RcmZhq0EzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning my a.m. crew and #HappyHumpDay everyone. ☕️☕️ @sdeebocane  @KPRC2Britta  @KPRC2Amy  @KPRC2Haley  @kprc2owen… https://t.co/tJlmO5VDhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kind of think @Tesla should’ve straight up started the first $1B Kickstarter to isolate their future risk project… https://t.co/Y5e9D5Bl7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LetsGoPens A rebound from last night is much needed. Find a way boys! #BeatBruins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1SonuvaGunn @PhilosophyTiger @BS__Detector @IntelegentF @CriticalCripple @puertoricofilmC @doctorofinfo @UKchimp… https://t.co/zjKRwybYXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevebloom55 @IdiotTracker @Revkin @mzjacobson @arevkin @sunrisemvmt Building without understanding seismic issues… https://t.co/WL3F3jcAdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thomas1774Paine @RealJamesWoods Hey we’re all right here having a POW WOW with the rest of Wackos 🦹‍♀️🤡😂😂😂👍👍👍😎🇺🇸🇺🇸… https://t.co/I4Zi3Cj16Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then there's me: I don't need to go to the doctor, Motrin will fix it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayB7897 like a kid dying to use a new toy. i blame u for pulling out your snow blower for a forecast of 3-6"]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I did on my lunch break today. I visited long-term care facilities with my mom for my dad. Life has de… https://t.co/9Z72wsnQYq]]></document><document><![CDATA[For over a decade,  I missed many birthday parties.  I missed many after-party’s. I missed many trips to Vegas.   E… https://t.co/6YHZzlQPJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stealth40k I’m fine with what they showed. And Battle Royale Tetris...interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daguilarcanabal I was aware of that. You are mistaken. Harpers crossing and berkeley are both built with public funds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alluraknightaz @PhoenixxVIP So glad you got the support you need. Be prepared to need continued support s things p… https://t.co/rvveOYCVxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[but Netenyahu doesn't want peace because it would be the end of his power. Don't be fooled by Netenyahu, he's just… https://t.co/YWUrvkPr9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lessleybitch You act like this on Twitter but in person it be like😂: https://t.co/ex7j7NAUOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarinelliSauce https://t.co/wJ4SnbqEW0 https://t.co/BbNlk4IO0F  @petershankman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1hannahlloyd Society does .it’s all a competition of who’s better . If you don’t figure out what you want to do Ri… https://t.co/Yj4KGHYJqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cedarflats @wolv54b1 @AngryScotBrew @almostablaze @RJellyman @CasaskullMark @beeryeti @TammyJaben @ManvsAle… https://t.co/gqutiYjLtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actually Donnie you can take it out of the excess taxes we pay, remember we’re a net contributor a… https://t.co/5c0VnLMKaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinNewburn Here’s an action figure set for you. https://t.co/oz2PsZmnVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miiimiiii1 @Carl_HarrisonUk @CWar12 @Maria_Hinojosa @AlOtroLado_Org @wef 46.6 million in US not born here. Not a b… https://t.co/UD86fbSG2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Persona 4 Mario Kart 8 Deluxe  Xenoblade Chronicles 2 Tetris Final Fantasy Tactics]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marshmont_63 University of Colorado = CU University of Kansas = KU University of Oklahoma = OU]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're just wayside extra's----- trying to be brilliant but they don't know who they are so they don't know what t… https://t.co/mn8s5yM1WB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I sell my stock in Nike for messing up the #AdaptBB launch this morning? 👟 It seems like no one on Twitter w… https://t.co/tXztqzODhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I can’t believe how much love we have received thank you to everyone for all the messages and nice things that… https://t.co/dPlrWyhkSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLReese @SaraCivian It will never happen would need to have the Sabers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pad 39A Swing Arm, now and then — an amazing modernization from the Apollo and Shuttle days.  "We want the things i… https://t.co/FnVlF4ozEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaxToOnething @MapMyRun I was ocean kayaking. Think it was pretty close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow Had to put my best friend down in January. I still cry from time to time. Take solace in knowing you're doi… https://t.co/UYJI0Npz5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comrade_JP_ @Neolibshilling @ShawnDCstudent @tommyxtopher https://t.co/PQh8fZlA3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsStephPerera One of our favorite relatively new spots is @maestososd. Had a great meal there last night and thei… https://t.co/qO1jvGOfv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[They turned out pretty darn cute if I do say so myself https://t.co/fy9kRhPbMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee, will you be on my @Thaducation podcast please? https://t.co/gQM0VnMYwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully autonomous vehicles will take at least another five years to perfect, with the cost and complexity of rolling… https://t.co/DpzDgQj8Fp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maisyeyc Tomatoes are much more versatile, cucumbers are just crunchy and gross]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oops! Stole Mimi’s mug on live tv. 🤦🏼‍♂️ @ King Broadcasting Co https://t.co/cASJmP5zk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FloppyPlants No this was actually all my fault. I misread something an caused a panic in my group. I have taken 10… https://t.co/ZFFrtECNIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bachman &amp; Turner - Takin' Care Of Business (Live At The Roseland Ballroo... https://t.co/NcirRDWQt8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is her plan for China and India do we go to war because they don't want to participate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at that full, bright moon tonight! #fullmoon #moon #kitsap https://t.co/FYs8RXXsrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fucking stop! Stop thinking your profession is the center of the universe. If it wasn’t for the scorn engineers hea… https://t.co/9ATQOW7XDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mseverson10 You guys have below 500 teams making the playoffs. Its a joke. There’s like 6 good teams and the rest of the league is trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I didn’t get the memo because everyone’s either pissed off or sad tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @realDonaldTrump is not being investigated he needs to be. He is a threat to national security.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny thing about the Texas legislature, they’re only just now considering passing a bill that would recognize Sele… https://t.co/oP9xTmliVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just did a 10 second quarter mile in CSR2. https://t.co/B0a9lUqNCv https://t.co/kBRF0jYEjI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylamb8 Those types of replies shows u don’t understand.  If you don’t see emotional highs and lows, ebbs and flow… https://t.co/Amclf2gBiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[“What A Man Wants” is actually pretty funny and a good watch. @TherealTaraji was excellent as always. Go see it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🛎️🛎️🛎️Dinger Time Again!!!🛎️🛎️🛎️ @CofCBaseball RF Cross Holfert @crossholfert crushes one to center to extend the C… https://t.co/OaQQi8byA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The more I think about it, I feel like the reason the infinity gauntlet looked busted up after the snap in infinity… https://t.co/SQtMhDrzCV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsByJamaras @edson_e14 He in his right grade bro I already checked after they played Lamelo 😂 he actually pret… https://t.co/pNF6s2A5r6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Grind when they sleep” - Shop: thenosleepcloset @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/bWObB1RfKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% agree with this...little scared of the potential locker room issue, but if that's under control, all upside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiTownSports The Democratic machine is well oiled. I don't want to hear a dem say "term limits are elections"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I’ll believe it when I see it until then I don’t believe it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ed_perezP @CescWolff10 @pochodiaz @LORENT_SALEH @MariaFdaCabal @PoliciaColombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy we have people like @AOC in Congress. Holy crap. Can we clone her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just started Dating Around on Netflix.   Is this really how straight people are on dates?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swalwell is the living embodiment of a politician is the most neutral way possible. Like, if you had never met a po… https://t.co/uv06NE86Bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine having over $300 million and choosing to live in Pennsylvania for 13 years instead of California 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe they meant to put “District” in front of Manager...JK! @cleve_travis Awesome March so far Team Meridian!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know whatever happened to the interesting wall sculpture that used to be here at the base of the Pru? 🤔 It d… https://t.co/SaA1un0bEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard yall got the #GoodGood stuff up/out there‼️ any space druqs❓ @ The Space https://t.co/byHH3GGd9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bruch #mimosa #Fresh it's #SundayFunday stop by the restaurant $1 mimosas while supplies last 11 a.m. to 3 p.m. to… https://t.co/q6yQFwTt06]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great match until the end...... @wwe writers fucked it up and the crowd is dead. Good job.....and you had the crowd… https://t.co/FA1m4adyWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notevenvegan yessir! i guess this second grader passed all of the multiplication facts up to the number 12 and my… https://t.co/sHbnt5yaJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods CV Driver - Glad to see Tiger beginning to flare his feet at address! @ Palm Desert, California https://t.co/nApcBYPJSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[New mood: stop apologizing for things that are not your fault and were never your fault. Stop apologizing for your… https://t.co/2ZpIdRuqcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@logan_schoepf @wiatraksamuel @DylanZelon @PIHLhockey Wasn’t there BUT  Very good teams should be afforded the chan… https://t.co/yS3YN6oTWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@digiwonk I feel seen (or not seen by my phone while waiting for bus in neg windchill)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ttowns11 😅😅 I just saw everyone else quote tweeting it with past jobs. Missed the “reply with the number” part. https://t.co/2g62gp9aRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ducks two-seed in NCAA's latest seeding projection https://t.co/tcsu6hHURE via @247sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It is unconstitutional and should not be permitted.  Get a judge to issue an injunction to stop th… https://t.co/3sRPgXoA78]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UpSideDownWELLSFARGO #Rise #Love #MACS0647JD #Pure #Bliss “I stumble into town just like a sacred cow Visions of”… https://t.co/pZTV8yQUJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[MAINE MENU: FRI  twinbill at DNF (3 pm), SAT hoops vs TAMU at Humphrey Col. (1 pm), SUN spring forward w/series fin… https://t.co/CFRC27kRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoMatterWhereIAmITurnTheclubOut #shreveport #Louisiana https://t.co/Hm6M0DZghv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a must watch for those wanting to know the truth about socialism!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RussBeenToolin @madameatloaf @srecupero @downwithBKing Or Dylan McKay?..he was theee toughest bad boy https://t.co/8ZD09paZqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Ayuntamiento de Culiacán https://t.co/QrZHhomu79]]></document></documents></author>