<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Snapped a few cool pics on our approach into NY yesterday. Waking up to a sunny day here in NYC and so happy to be… https://t.co/6l4a6aHdWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[◽️The @theflowerfields March 1 - May 12 in beautiful Carlsbad, CA. Follow us on Twitter for more lifestyle events… https://t.co/uDGhiJemms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateComf5 I went to bed early, it was nice but I'm still tired. LOL. Hang in there, hope your day goes by fast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crei que tenias un poquito mas de luz larga, disculpame, pero no son los amanuenses y programas radiales en  #Cuba… https://t.co/YeL2OqtySS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norvina1 Well hopefully you won’t forget my face 🤗 first one is using Riviera! https://t.co/oSbWbatck0]]></document><document><![CDATA[there are people out there who don’t like bobs burgers...those are the people i wish to not associate with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr @SprockDaddy Nancy does not have control of the house. She thinks she does but Linda walked right i… https://t.co/fydXjuBCuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christian got me a lil cow for Valentine’s Day instead of a teddy bear 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we were passed by a cop , the 2 paramedics arriving on scene and a fire truck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can my bitch ass stop drinking a bottle of wine every time I have a bad day]]></document><document><![CDATA[This random ass frat boy whipped up to me in one of those lyft scooter things and started singing to me y’all I’m really hollering]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww...tb to Big Ben showing his kids some ❤️ before the game! 😳 Such a poor leader/Dad 🤣🖤💛 #Steelers #BigBen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissYamiMami @EugeneTattedUp They got it on their big ass video cameras still. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[i woke up at 6am on a sunday to see 3 first half subs #munliv https://t.co/GJx7ArH8z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silentstoner_ Niggas don’t careeeee .. if it was they dusty ass homeboy they would help tho smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s in the box 📦 #LaVidaDeMia_ #MiasMaking @ Cambrian, San Jose https://t.co/kdS7DgrZoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxycharm are the delayed boxes going to have the face palette issue? Please reply,I'm a loyal customer and was most excited for that item]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m about to get my wisdom teeth out. 🥵sorry in advance if i do some stupid shit lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song is in my head at least once a day. It's the most upbeat form of hell. I don't even think I'm upset about… https://t.co/mTRCneC4o3]]></document><document><![CDATA[marzy just got on houseparty crying under a table in starbucks ... my god]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your campaign lied and cheated to get you elected. I’ll have a Happy President’s Day when we don’t have a fake President.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@miss_pryor What a powerful experience for all students to have—getting to experience a story through the perspecti… https://t.co/n4TeLCe4GG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are so awful and so ridiculous, Mr. Bone Spurs.  How dare you speak badly about Blumenthal whe… https://t.co/zkd49T0CzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Candelaria y cumple del papi!! #famparty #loveit❤️ #familia #enjoy #liveandenjoy😍 en Ciudad Juárez https://t.co/Vm1Jsj107p]]></document><document><![CDATA[love seeing these kinds of messages from my dad 💛 https://t.co/HiohSvT7TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGLearns Definitely not new. I like to extrapolate that article to anything new... Change is hard. We grieve, accept, and move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eedoogie Well thank you! ☺️ The last couple days I’ve been tagged in a tweet and asked about 2 others that I could… https://t.co/Ztg9zLEErt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening follows happening,  illusion after illusion. A new door. Into the halo. Into the sun. Death’s pale blue b… https://t.co/VGhtmUTn7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s all fun and games until your photo with 2/3 of @DREAMERSjoinus looks like it was taken with a toaster. thanks… https://t.co/4W8NfpvcX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to be speaking with the amazing @DrJRMarcelin ! This conference was amazing to attend last year and can’… https://t.co/LVCXPJ2KWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecularOutpost @SunnySh21535716 @MaddowBlog @maddow Please present current news and facts. The air quality is bein… https://t.co/bIqCoU4NiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazandAJ @991PLRFM What a weather difference in 24 hrs. Too bad it was t yesterday’s weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welwyn #welwynpreserve #funwithjen #glencove #hempsteadharbor @ Welwyn Preserve County Park https://t.co/ZBPVnNiYWc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone please tell me what a fancy #hotpocket is?? I am intrigued! https://t.co/MyhFFm0Zof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping Canada's can take a minute tomorrow and welcome the heart of our country to Ottawa tomorrow  https://t.co/IAsRZltboF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead Tonight's episode was awesome! What an absolutely epic rescue by Daryl!! 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @girlscouts got your hoomans @TheGroveLA #girlscoutcookies #dogspotting #hoomans #grovela https://t.co/4DNUlBwyNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWarren End Citizens United. Take the means of corruption out of our elections and our govt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to laugh. “Shanks. You’re susch a good friend.” | 11 Dogs Who Learned The Hard Way Not To... https://t.co/J96gfjr5AX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate a lemme show my whole ass in the pic but my caption say “ just took my grandmother to the doctors”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Fictional Journey by @Hitchhikerbrew @ Hitchhiker Brew Plant — https://t.co/OXNW7dx3QN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terryatthebeach @Time4U2Know Yes!  Remember your 2 Presidential Alert Tests bf end of 2018???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianDietzen @NCIS_CBS @SeanHMurray @CBSTweet @CBSTVStudios @WValderrama @margoharshman @CBS Once Upon a Tim!!!  W… https://t.co/g6Alt2mVJE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así está la autopista Francisco Fajardo a esta hora frente a la Carlota  https://t.co/ZUSy5onEB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[New @GQMagazine  Lucas Hedges in the new Vuitton shot by Ryan McGinley and story from the cool brain of Alice Grego… https://t.co/ELZI7gI0b3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows we don’t need tapes of Trump’s racism?!!!! We see it EVERY DAY on national television and on Twitter. Also, stop yelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Why would it be a emergency to Democrats? To Democrats non Americans here illegally are an "opportuni… https://t.co/3El8TBqpra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UserAM169 @AnnaVarela2 @TwitterMoments Ok sweetie.  You are part of the problem.  I’m sure you voted for Jill Stein instead of Hillary. 🙄🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christielester Starting in April I actually earn more vacation days (been at my job 5 years) so I'll be able to sa… https://t.co/ITK1MUBlUr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristyRecruit Is there only one wave of offers today for WDW or another one this week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww babies!  I’m going out for a walk, maybe I’ll see them and bring them home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rpondiscio @karinchenoweth @nypmetro In my neck of the woods, parents just called a sick out over student behavior… https://t.co/4M7aKX9oQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[but u can’t wear hats inside school anyways so stfu and stop bitching that no one would let you wear your shitty hat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn was already living in calabasas  with her mother . y’all actin like she was broke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewisjmiles WE SHOOT OURSELVES IN THE HEAD DAILY! And THEN ACT CONFUSED 🤬🤬🤬 #FALLBACK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending as much sunshine and birthday wishes I can to our Cali native 💙 Happy birthday to the one and only Rossi 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even know how to do my makeup but I want it I want it I want it 😍 it’s so pretty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical Friday night hanging out at the Canadian Embassy for a film screening. 😀🇨🇦 #canadianembassydc… https://t.co/MOBATAi09U]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are able, engage in physical activity.   You can eat anything you want.  The 🔑 is calorie intake.  Your calo… https://t.co/T63vlxiALB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I knew #AlienMask was @latoyajackson!!!!!  The badge was a dead give away!!!!  You rock!!! #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[((SPECIAL EDITION)) All About Kenneth!📺 @ Hertford, North Carolina https://t.co/U0tchgraZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi No one checked Trumps background. What about his kids. Why should they hold such high clearances. I know they are not cheap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even federal prisoners have to draw the line somewhere. Roger will be fine. Judge Berman will probably sentence him… https://t.co/EwU42YG1cK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaNoonUK @Stemettes @AdamHertz @VanityProjects @jesslynnrose @jesswade @annmarie @GirlsWhoCode Ooh you’re good :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is what 40 years of  “Good Lovin’” can do to a man ❤️ Happy Valentines Day @twk8008 😘 #40YearChallenge 😳… https://t.co/KNHeO17kYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gus_FTW You look handsome just as you are. No need to lose weight. Beg for treats! 🐕❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mirrperez I literally just moved out!! That drive is not fun! But Long Beach isn’t even all that closer! I would stay looking in LA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachTimDuffie check out @DevynButler7 from Allen! Would be a good addition to OKSTATE defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanBeans This is how I feel about catching up with This Is Us. I’ll wait until I want to cry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HAPPYFRIDAY EVERYONE!!! It's gonna be a Great day here on location! My no meat Lenten Friday #rigside… https://t.co/cMNgw46NvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanisilver @Refinery29 @Refinery29UK Love your article on singles! I think you might appreciate the new section f… https://t.co/at3JzkphMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skipr619 That right there is the real life giving nectar. Now if you must insist on bean water flavor, I'll make you a White Russian. 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a fabulous performance of #BrickellAve! So proud of my students who had the lead roles, were narrators, and st… https://t.co/jppbGRtzdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many of us want the “End Result” However, getting to the destination without learning from your journey will cause… https://t.co/pvJ0DC9hiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twin Day!!! @AMSphysed @PTOAMS @avenelmiddle @mrhugey_AMS @MrsChandler_AMS https://t.co/G9NwAy1p1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[this less-than-profound thought brought to you by a long day had by yours truly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all about accountability but i will not explain myself to anyone who is not paying my bills or tucking me in at… https://t.co/tcahEXRe65]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @ocjag for the #robbiewilliamsconcert it was magic✨#lasvegas @ Wynn Encore https://t.co/mcCIlTF0uD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunshinelokii i’m trying to understand how you’re so pretty i- https://t.co/EMTGfvaxTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the most hardworking professional Make Up FX Artist paticurriemua . During 2 days of filming… https://t.co/AOMuQD7rdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrdachshund86 when i met Sec. Castro and told him i was from AR he told me that he loves reading Dale Bumpers speeches 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Everyone...Please join me in sending prayers and condolences out to the family and friends of DJ Luv 1… https://t.co/7H2uovxJwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau Come on Canada...North America is counting on you for this kind of leadership!  I know you are going… https://t.co/AzCXSKPkVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdLawCenter @FairFundingAC @ChristopherBFay @FBPSsup @GovMurphy @NJSenatePres @vingopal @SpeakerCoughlin @NJLD11… https://t.co/wTpgkOD8OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penis is free and abundant. They need a new game plan. This might work. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, it’s sad to see kids more humble and sincere than your own elected politicians]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished watching the Jonas Brothers carpool karaoke .... man the nostalgia hit 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Guava Pastelitos by @Coppertail @ Keg &amp; Cow — https://t.co/sslryrO7IY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Music__Mentor They are completely different songs. One is a love song, the other a hard rock staples. I listen to… https://t.co/B4GODKlPe8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danwootton Glad Madonna has gotten over her snit about Born This Way being too similar to Express Yourself. It was unbecoming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great reception to integrating Sex and gender into #BrainBuilders #brainstory #sgba #cewh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueWaveBob @krassenstein @HeyokaMuse And if you kept saying there was a crisis for 2 years and nothing came of it… https://t.co/fFDRjgamMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCNews “Giving 'back to the sisterhood:' Women-lead team designs new @YWCA_Hamilton” highlights the power of… https://t.co/znNwis0U2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter how many times we go to @LEGOLAND_CA I will never be a #MasterBuilder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's talk... #RemoteViewing @iHopFederalWay #psychicmedium https://t.co/s4XdLEoCr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2021_free @Arriadna I agree with you Donald! It’s a horrifying disgrace to our country. That you are being investi… https://t.co/c40e8yd2BD]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @ritaangeltaylor and her partnership with @CARE and joelgoldma1999 Giving back, changing lives, making… https://t.co/MRWrbcpEhn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clint_Stutts @DrOakley1689 And upon further reflection, said comment was basically just gossip; I was talking abt… https://t.co/RgKccXKdSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Family Justice Center of Ventura County opened our doors today. Honored to represent VOICES in partnership with… https://t.co/zEilPC68EB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itssAutumn On the highest of keys... I will cry if I see him peform there goes my life live]]></document></documents></author>