<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[We need to talk about our generations addiction to eating out. I cut back dramatically the end of last year and I’m… https://t.co/w1Cr9ovvL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrGBeth @jasonsdozier @oh_HOLMES @Freeyourmindkid @tonetalks @BreakingBrown @jack “Yeah it was Haitian slaves who… https://t.co/gb2j2hFhkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boy did I steer those nice people @trumbulllibrary wrong when I suggested how they might fill out their ballots for special prizes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAIN VELASQUEZ IS BACK! Can’t wait for tonight’s fight! Excited! @cainmma 🇲🇽 #UFCPhoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathantripp @carlosgil83 I’m with Jonathan on this. Definitely would do you a solid in terms of content, but can… https://t.co/twF36STd4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre  https://t.co/CsUz7R4DGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump "But  you say, 'Wait wait wait,' isn't he a huge business success? Doesn't he know… https://t.co/STQnQuiot1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnapClickKat Wish i was closer i would give you the real thing and trust me i’m built like a bear, so i give the good ones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdcam01 @JacketJoeyT These are real people that haven’t died yet, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keillan21899 he’s an alumni from Whittier working at the Capital, i think he should be slapping mine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are they still blaming you? @marcorubio Are you secretly driving around blowing up transformers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowbnkr @callerdotcom It would seem like the money from new cattle coming in would go to pay off older debts.   Th… https://t.co/n2iKx5DSHr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tips being given to CPD in the Jussie Smollett case are just rumors that folks believe...  ...like those HIV ru… https://t.co/MYBm4d4Is9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/jUmU8Onmn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GadSaad His parents don’t need to look back, they are living with the embarrassment right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz I paid the money to the lawyer I waited the time For all the approvals Did everything right  we left the U… https://t.co/GrTqXWYpEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. LOOK at these. They’re so good. And frankly, that price is damn near criminally low.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So For the First Time, I am actually comfortable with my Bowling Arsenal going into Leagues and Tournaments, so hug… https://t.co/CnmSt2AiTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody: girl: MY PUSSY SOUND LIKE MAC AND CHEESE!!! https://t.co/SYLcjdv91x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhyteJaki @Jimrod @CharMcew @SocialistVoice @terrychristian Why does government only give us shit shows?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1beardedgolfer Him and Boo Weekley.. Jeff Foxworthy made a career talkin about guys like them....yeeeha!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling a little scruffy today #lazysaturday @ Herriman, Utah https://t.co/FqnM2lyOnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even on a snow day the twins still putting in the work with @coachgodwin #progress #workuntil #ballislife🏀… https://t.co/45LUzOvPL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first time  experience with Plato's Closet ! https://t.co/Ismuu1qZ1Q via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_McGurk @BernieUpstateNY @SpeakerPelosi I really like how she invited all of those kids to join her Grand Chil… https://t.co/5Q32IVv7ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirstenGFH Welcome to Bernie Sanders’ Minnesota! https://t.co/5Y9UuJqgYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enriquecamou Bueno, lo que tú quieres es que el buen Jorge se arruine... tú no sabes de bromas Henry, my friend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive, why is it no one has mentioned the Picaninny on top of the cabinet at Elizabeth Warren's house during the big beer summit???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@apunkybrewster It appeals to a whole different group.  A LOT of people pop into C stores on the way home from work… https://t.co/uPwteRMieH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great show ! Can’t wait to watch them again in April ! @TheRedPears https://t.co/qvwoPpCXdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in bed with my dogs and honestly, this is why I want to stay single because this kind do love is always]]></document><document><![CDATA[When life throws you a curve ball, you have three choices.. Step in and take a “hit by pitch”, take the strike, or… https://t.co/oscmtvWu1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Help Me Find It by @swprophets, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/xKzV4jN5Jn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dill_NoPickle @Ravens I agree man. I mean sometimes loyalty means nothing I guess. I mean regardless if he was rot… https://t.co/lri19W4Hko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fishwilsoncc @ShimonPro He was leasing it, and I think he can’t afford the rent now. Thoughts &amp; prayers. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NintendoAmerica #thankyoureggie you were alway a great dude to talk to! https://t.co/xhCbhPUkad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OGTedBerg any chance you're heading down to spring training next week?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Short term goals by the end of April: #1: Get my walk around weight 147-150 (@154 right now) #2: Get my Blue Be… https://t.co/quIjAMLY6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TownofKingsbury Well Ft Edward has had a history of taxing local big business while duplicating the costs of opera… https://t.co/GDOJ9GkOAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MasteryChat A3: My dream is we move to a personalized learning that evolves around students balancing various proj… https://t.co/8Vs3T9gxWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah I put this on Instagram already and no I don’t live there anymore, but found the dome lights from my old house… https://t.co/5a4n52Fktd]]></document><document><![CDATA[New bookshelf got all my cool weeby nerdy shit on it and I'm in all sorts of love with it 😍😍😍 https://t.co/raKfNqX9YV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC Why don't you concentrate on Americans &amp; their democracy? Stay out of Foreign Politics. You are not good at it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public Service Announcement: I have landed in Daytona. For the next 4 days, you may see a crazy number of #NASCAR… https://t.co/9ACe0WxXuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strattacaster @kevinkelly Well, now I REALLY want to know what it is...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkibling I thiiiiiink this was a “social experiment” by two comedians...  ... to see if anyone would say something… https://t.co/vh7f4XRmSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sydny_boyd @griswoldkmtv Yea except I don't want her yelling GLORIA at me at 5-in-the-morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bernie is nuts- same insane hand gestures, same insane ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sevenxenemies @broadNabroad Ngannou didn’t?  https://t.co/mA3CXfbrgH  Because it seems like he did  https://t.co/nRAdex3SwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity popping up at the #TrumpKimSummit was like SNL cast members lobbing the host questions during the monologue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a feat you see accomplished very often. Proud of the way Lindsey competed this weekend, but more proud of the w… https://t.co/7LDbTsxP3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sixers game about to start. Hey @TheBSLine what is their record again on March 6?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyDeCello1 @theroyreport @mrjackson_65 @JaimeBoswell2 @Tabchoops @TheHoopCentral @THSCAcoaches @AustinTGCA Go… https://t.co/cnoThL648V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wdunlap @realDonaldTrump Yel your right we could have use that money for some good used buildings the wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's all the goals from @lansingignite's 7-0 win against @DU_MSOC today.  #LIFC | #LANvDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several more #Venezuelan military defect by crashing through fence in cucuta at Colombian border! #VenezuelaLibre]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrhurriicane Yeah. Hopefully Madden 20 will be better with this. Love your Cards series]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait i’m done those aren’t comparable family matters didn’t have a real main character]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsmeDazx I feel your pain. It is akin to working on a multi-day print and having it fail 3/4 through. I guess not… https://t.co/BLEy4PCBXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yandreaya I almost forgot to say thankyou for adding me as a friend on Overwatch my mistress, I love you, glad you… https://t.co/o9frV8zjIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[And also leftists: Let's shut down Foxy Lady in Rhode Island for misdemeanor. And put infanticide and pedovores in… https://t.co/Ks98bPiA5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Reasons To Buy The Galaxy S10 Over The iPhone XS via @forbes https://t.co/yxaHVvdURo #iPhoneXS #GalaxyS10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fullofgems @Darkskintigga Why would we ever want to be emasculated ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Not Robot – #WhatAggravatesMe https://t.co/cFqGIFnpza via @www.twitter.com/jknight841]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robdaemon No two men are good enough to get a chainsaw on a long pole. Just stick with their poles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New on the Blog: Fire At Dusk https://t.co/01JHETC9nG https://t.co/RAGOoTqnJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing some @DraftKings for today’s race. #NASCARRacingExp300 #NASCAR 🏁🏆💵 https://t.co/c7TmTiPYyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kica333 Having a Diet Coke or lite beer with it cancels out all the bad stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s all auto tune!!! 😑 Like wtf!  Dude just proved he has an amazing voice to millions of people...then drops… https://t.co/bUMNjwW2a1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbindyjilly @MarkBuran2 Isn't that the truth. This Winter has been ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want a better idea of your future climate? Try this map https://t.co/FUiDqWvklJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our undefeated streak in San Diego is still alive! Good win boys!⚓️ #AllHandsOnDeck]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Tigers!  Shout out to the State of Maryland with 5 teams in the top 20.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brady_kness I see your squat videos. No way this could be about you! haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans know what they’re doing. Had Mark Harris not gotten caught, who’s to say that John Harris would ever ha… https://t.co/IEZkQpiD8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been nominated by @MrsDeweyGHS to post covers of 7 books I love! No explanations or reviews, just covers.  Eve… https://t.co/jMkOU7P9bP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does shea look like he is going fall every time he runs or is it just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedWingGrips @BlueSea1964 @RashidaTlaib The destruction of democracy is the agenda of The Justice Democrats. Alexa… https://t.co/GtA7q6FtLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s really gonna be crazy when Bron gets the lakers to the playoffs and wins a series lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[#panda🐼 repose on the couch #dainty #daddieslittlegirl #partipoodle @ Chandler Cottage https://t.co/3yyaIu6S7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accepting any of these as gifts for the baby. Where are his uncles?! Lol @LenMaddJr @JaiBass0916]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is not something ready-made. It comes from our own actions.  Dalai Lama]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicochetWaters We need another “Operation Urgent Fury” in #Venezuela to finish the @NicolasMaduro Dictatorship   T… https://t.co/ey0KzKzUBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TurboTax  #TaxHero  #Sweepstakes I had confusion about my deductibles and Turbo Tax sorted me right out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanBegley @TimBontemps Shouldn’t he be getting fined by the NBA for opening talking about the teams he wants to pl… https://t.co/b7jDGknakI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Blythedale Children's Hospital https://t.co/ujdlqzNZiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nala and Coco seem to be doing OK! Nala actually seems happy to have someone to play with! @toledohumane… https://t.co/8Z68WmhmJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to buy this card. #mirth #chuckle #smirk #merry https://t.co/tQKPZNkYab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMaryHicks @ggreenwald @davidmirandario an awesome #Brazil #labor #strike history lesson on your anniversary, gentlemen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathySm33865925 @charliekirk11 @realDonaldTrump @TPUSA The liberal media sucks and is full of lies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peoplefor @RepCummings @MichaelCohen212 @vanitaguptaCR @cmclymer @Public_Citizen @CAPAction @AFJustice @NAACP_LDF… https://t.co/KXNl8t9nk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get yo do did by my boy Frank at Wild Boar Barbershop in the Heights! Tell him Johnny Boy sent ya! 😉 #barber… https://t.co/48dtrWRgHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Initiative 976 would cut transportation funding across. It will cause huge cuts to road maintenance, buses and trai… https://t.co/lHonJ23kFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does D.K. Metcalf’s slow agility times limit his horizontal breaks?   Notice the 3rd step with his outside foot: •… https://t.co/LyA7HI7ULI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you need something from @express, shop at the @southdalecenter location!! The employees are #FABULOUS every sing… https://t.co/lBPazsu5A6]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRUMP’S TAX RETURNS!!! Wow!!! #pelosi #OcasioCortez #whacko #maddow #martiallaw #prosecutedemocrats #rt https://t.co/2Xe2owWTc5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffCoxSports Good hockey show asthma weekend in Detroit at the Little Caesars arena! @PghPensElite , Little Caesa… https://t.co/sTThcf8Fz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excuse @bmsellers91 and I as we disappear for a few days...off to hogwarts we go! #lego #harrypotter #hogwarts… https://t.co/ApREL6eR3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsianOptionGirl @CEtoruom @realDonaldTrump Read deeper my child, let there be light doesn’t refer to sunlight. You… https://t.co/5TYkR8p2Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall don’t hate country music you just don’t know anything about it.  Same as any other genre you “hate”]]></document></documents></author>