<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Master &amp; Commander is a great example of what the studio system is capable of production.   Fine film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashmettCarcamo Don’t worry that day will happen you’re ep will be a classic and jay z and kanya will be beating down your door for a verse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBeastYT If you do it I will make 10 accounts and sub to pewdiepie on all 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are through three quarters with @athleticshpcsd leading Saugerties 44-35.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday Funday! I'm back at Bailey's in Townsend, MA from  4:30-7:30pm! Awesome food and awesome people! Come… https://t.co/JpEPCwxRRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch “The Rock‘n‘ Roll Era! AC/DC Thunderstruck . Belly Dance Diana Bastet Show” on #Vimeo https://t.co/fZs4Zj3ofb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickiknowsnada @PaulyFred These people have caused a great deal of anxiety and depression in the world, literally.… https://t.co/2mmiOxAc1X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Reading Cohen's opening statement to Congress should be an excruciating moment for anyone still su… https://t.co/QRW4MSck0A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVietor08 @RepClayHiggins I hope he gets the deposit back for that rental]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SturgisSports @MUSTANGSRME2 @thiespiegel @Gmwtiger2_Greg @AOC It is really sad that at 50 years of age you cannot… https://t.co/3trVZHkk15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker, Tucker, Tucker, you are just as bad as that foul mouth Bill O’Reilly – so how many women have you fucked ov… https://t.co/GnqhjSrwpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrangerPanthers Thank you!!! Can't wait for the season! Big things ahead for us this year! 💯🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emojis mean so much more coming from your mom cuz you know she spent TIME looking for the exact one she wanted]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish the US had headlines like this.  Instead, we only talk about increasing car sales.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary could have done it in 10 hours (giving speeches for Goldman Sachs).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellanRios @sonic_cosplayer @sonictoyhunter @teeturtlenews That’s awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting on him to read my message and fucking answer me. I’m ready to start a war tho. Or it could be nice haha. We… https://t.co/quoyEUw5SX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a few more days until #TOS2   Register Now Free @ https://t.co/Y0LV9vi8ve   #QBs #RBs #WRs #TEs #OL #DL #LBs… https://t.co/NHZBzLo7RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is Canada moving closer to Pakistan - a theocratic state with a failing economy that exports terrorism?  Why mo… https://t.co/i2Gm8EJSJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is about time. I bet most players are excited about this. But, I’m sure you will hear from critics who won’t agr… https://t.co/0OPciTqmxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[...Return to me with all your heart,...  #sanduskyia #,mississippiriver @ Sandusky, Iowa https://t.co/hpSGVoISiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crash shuts down S. Ocean Drive (A1A) in both directions near Jensen Beach in St Lucie County.#BreakingLocalNews… https://t.co/aUprEspCxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hockey_Robinson That’s a cruel question I don’t want to even think about answering lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialKolaO @atiku The Devil showed Jesus earthly riches to distract Him from saving Mankind. No amount of evil… https://t.co/5JU1LJJdJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyMercerUK You may need to change your leader if you want compassion]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need an artist that’s good at trippy art im tryna buy a big ass canvas painting 🖼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HGrayston @RealKiefer There are people who think he does and he said he was done playing jack Bauer had no interes… https://t.co/Ovj3epsPBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calvinlocal10, #Haiti is a Country #Nation that will never get better. Who ever runs its Government? Will be full… https://t.co/jRXpWhWH6R]]></document><document><![CDATA[For William Sweet,clearly the favorite has to be current Philadelphia Eagles starting offensive lineman Halapouliva… https://t.co/pFANVx8R3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast with my lil’ dude. @ Kelly Raes Country Cafe https://t.co/mm5OttobCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4fishgreenberg Tahoe was like that when we were there. Probably worse now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not fault AOC for her thoughts, but to air them as a Representative of our government, now that is a totally d… https://t.co/UVseJxKqgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinyLou_13 I want Fearless’, and Enchanted’s, and YAIL’s, and CIWYW’s  my dream album is a combo of THOSE masterpieces so my heart bursts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeLangeLV I’m not sure. I can see that, but I can see the argument it was tough to hold Merrill out. He’s produc… https://t.co/GhM2xWudOi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommybeth77 @becky_jed @senatemajldr Sure whatever promotes your agenda right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuck_Shick_Esq Enjoy the trip.  San Francisco is a neat city.  Great sights and excellent food opportunities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom No Joe they don’t see the need but why aren’t YOU criticizing the president for being a racist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregkeown23 @Colinporter03 Not only did he look into the eyes...he gave them Buckets too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition to get @alyankovic to play the 2020 @SuperBowl halftime show who is with me? https://t.co/J4tIeuwu90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @JaneyrJanet Bigot @marklevinshow doesn’t call @Jim_Jordan a bigot for his $ take on steyer. Amazing… https://t.co/zMITz1SLzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you finally meet that someone who tries their hardest to be with you regardless of how difficult you are, stay with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Staring at you @JoshGottheimer! You have strong opinions about tropes last week. What happened?]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the performance of Lamar Jackson, I’m really not surprised Baltimore will be trading Joe Flacco to Denver. #Ravens #Broncos]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most Genuine Rapper in the game dropped another banger🔥🌹 I was stoked I gotta meet him when he was on The Love… https://t.co/JT6joQ3mCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 at #IBS2019! Stop by Marvin Windows and Doors in booth C3819! https://t.co/muHUYgQhut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgurley Decent pile of BS going here.  Trump, for example, has proposed immigration reform more liberal than Luis… https://t.co/s5vd8fEIac]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how much time goes by you're always going to be very special to me Lisa I'm always going to want… https://t.co/wVDLTEJL6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Picture Perfect Lead Generation at SXSW 2019. Visit https://t.co/1SFzJGeLb9 for more information.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badhopper @RahrBrewing @birrobeerlovers @TheStraightHops @mtravis63 @JHMSparky @brewerytravels @BJJoyce81… https://t.co/kxGNxlEAAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jberkley17 @WayButler @lbarronlopez @TomSteyer @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows According to the Treasury, the “narrowe… https://t.co/nN1SVZPhSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhwfung At which point you should seriously consider wtf you’re doing in the city, if that’s your quality of life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shoutout to @strykerthecat for the #love @ Lafayette, Louisiana https://t.co/iKqQf4ArnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredthealien316 @ImSteveMigs @321battle @TonyBaroni13 @JoeyRyanOnline I agree based on what I've seen on Twitch, b… https://t.co/0Mmz53qt6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AccionNacional @lopezobrador_ @jorgeramoshdz Todavía que por su p$#&amp; culpa se ponen regegos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic Wow. He’s even dumber than he looks and acts and is. @donaldtrumpjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀🏆 Congratulations to @KnightsSM Girls Basketball... The 2019 @CIFSDS Division I Runner-Up. Tremendous season!… https://t.co/wppeaOu8Ww]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t want to be out there now. Hopefully by mid afternoon it will be safe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Distinct_Words @Luke4Tech @Deadspin They are always messing with men’s mancaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmaAmaLeeLee “I’m really sorry, but the grammar in this comment is awful. I mean, how are we supposed to really ab… https://t.co/aCs3ipX6E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cliffkirby @Orwell1971 @jguaido @capriles Y que carajo has hecho tu? Para criticarlo hace falta haber hecho algo por la patria .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life movea pretty fast.. #newadventures #refocusyourheart @ Oviedo, Florida https://t.co/GSSiAZh0Zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your a semi driver, uh yaah, your a piece of shit.  Signed,  Every other driver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, @moo! I don’t do biz cards often but when I do...MOO!! @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/FhoImnCToJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one would remember the Good Samaritan if he had only had good intentions.  My wife is always reminding me we are… https://t.co/5Gdozf4Uxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulhwpark Dang, I didn’t know you were on a first name basis with Sixpence None the Richer- I don’t know them so… https://t.co/DXhSUGgCCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rosecoloredbae @aaronmayto Yo this shit came up randomly on Spotify yesterday shit goes hard, sounds like a young jcole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You struggling in your online sales?😰 Discover Few Steps Of Marketing To 10X Your Income🚀 Our Step By Step Formula(… https://t.co/NBfwovBHTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iEricKohn I like Houston’s unis. They’ve endured so many disasters that it’s nice to see them get a winner. I’d st… https://t.co/9KRHoyy6LJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/vAjj8aFNsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg that “period” shit gon be the death of me.. it’s making my nerves bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrick_Coffin @Catholic_Radio Someone needs to see how much money he has in his overseas accounts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enfriadas en hielo como en el “otso” tiendasoxxo @corona #winter @ Chester County, Pennsylvania https://t.co/CiOLVooq0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does Brad Stevens keep taking Semi Ojeleye out of the game? Let him finish the game!  #Celtics #NBA #Sacramento]]></document><document><![CDATA[In celebration of #InternationalWomensDay, follow some great thinkers like @samelilydia1, @kariweston, @fastcrayon,… https://t.co/5chEnPHffh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terence wuz robbed! @T_Blanchard #oscars2019 #SpikeLee #bestoriginalscore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Denver let’s play! #Weekend (@ Denver International Airport - @denairport in Denver, CO) https://t.co/9eAJFiy2N8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRogue10 @4_andersons @calebando @chickstoops @MortgageHound @louisbennettscj Love you fuckers... #CantWait]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god the Pittsburgh media is feuding now too. This is insane. #WeNeedHelp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paminthelab @kristinabonitz the article I mentioned https://t.co/ZEuqnONG9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nealbrennan’s 3 Mics is brilliant. My dreams took my favorite line too far tho. I was a thousand months pregnant w… https://t.co/3b0SonP2AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VRBEagles @dr_loyalions @DrMLKJrAcademy @SContrerasAP @SorianoJer @AUSDHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics of course Trump wants that it's not like he's trying to hide anything from the American people with his dealings with Russia]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude whips his uncirmcusised wee-wee out, MID-AISLE, and starts urinating in this small ass bottle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final Knoxville beats Illini West 42-24 to advance on to play West Hancock tomorrow night. #wcisports]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m excited to getting around to watching it eventually since it’s happening in the middle of the night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chiharu - Sushi &amp; Noodle in Brookline, MA https://t.co/vNxviPkePE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@revistaetcetera @isisguevara @Irma_Sandoval @lopezobrador_ ¿Y es Secretaria de la Función Pública? ¿Y el Estado de Derecho?]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC says she has college degree. Apparently she learned nothing. The climate has been changing on this rock since i… https://t.co/NJpZmZXKTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole_Cliffe They paid my $355 Costco grocery run when my credit card didn't go through.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDre1909 @DrunkBrianF No the truck and xfinity series are developmental series aka minor league! You listen to t… https://t.co/wOrxjEaz5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felicidades a @alfonsocuaron y todo tu equipo de trabajo ,por los 3 #oscars que se llevaron esta noche. 🥳👏🏼/ Congra… https://t.co/dfyoR4nO5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Inversions.. Thanks to the @POTUS tax plan there have been More .. and there are more planned for this year..… https://t.co/IxZZJexOx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, my Skype interview went well! I’ve been invited out to do a teaching demo and have face-to-face interviews at… https://t.co/KUGdcjF1c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t get how people can call radio stations talking shit about Ben Simmons after seeing stuff like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWaxman @Patta47cake @JuddLegum That’s all they want the freedom to be.  It’s the party of aholes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hybrid1979 @r0xie_f0x @SwettmanF @BertJ4411 @Diaper777 @aleeyun_nvaazun @all_eyezonmi @Lo_Gannicus… https://t.co/qWOEvUeljo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC I DONT MIND CARYING MY OWN CROSS JUST DID NOT LIKE HAVING STONES THROWN AT ME FOR IT ,, SO ILL STAND WITH SA… https://t.co/5MFuZAkZWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juancsalazarm @poetayfilosofo @bautea @jguaido @MariaCorinaYA @HenriFalconLara Hizo un buen gobierno en Lara, esti… https://t.co/YNWKaZfgmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@broncoguy781 What I sent is an actual link to the site. It is pretty easy. You can create an account too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What would you do if a girl like you rings the doorbell and I answered the door fully nude?]]></document></documents></author>