<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@rehughesjr @KevinBurns1969 @MotherJones Thank for we're not a Democracy! We are a Republic!! https://t.co/CyXk8BTFTb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janiehaddad @ryanjreilly Liar Pants-Liar is my favorite English neighborhood.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Despite traverse through the Tetons Mnts, in and our of service, I still managed to snag R-Type DX. This ma… https://t.co/TeeIawqeNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ashton5SOS thank you for everything you have done over the past few years. love and appreciate you more than you know sunshine 💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamMGrant That’s the number one question my UVA grad is getting on job interviews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cancer is horrible. That’s something we can all agree on. Keep fighting  Alex Trebek. You’ve been apart of our fami… https://t.co/mxw6eRdegw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need to buy this book again. Since she don’t want to give me my book back]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DitchMitch ..I will give to any @TheDemocrats running against him. It’s about time someone in Kentucky told them t… https://t.co/16X6uTibqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing I was planning on not going to class today because my teacher just canceled it. 🤷🏿‍♀️ Life works out sometimes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cToddGilbert Have you see what your constituent @gail_vasta wrote?  Just wanted to make sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuekerk @theparamuseum @Weird_Dana Shoot I missed it! I was thinking it was tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to see @JMCOfficial ! @ The Official City Limits Saloon Raleigh https://t.co/Hmeo2a6wzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jryerson1 @RosieBarton Pathetic, not historical, not cutting edge, just boring.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Regal Cinemas Cypress Creek Station 16 - @regalmovies for Captain Marvel in Fort Lauderdale, FL w/… https://t.co/7clXJyskcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJS71 @angelbabesgrany @JeremyHubbard @RockyMountViews @KDVR https://t.co/bNjzmJFf6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come and join the party tomorrow night from 6:30-8...full meal ready in under 30 minutes (including brownies)😋😋 ➡️… https://t.co/okHX1l1H8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently, a fake PAC is soaking up Trump donations https://t.co/I5516sGWqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTM_TitanAP @heatherwarrell @CTMontessori1 Seems like you are changing like a caterpillar going through the metamo… https://t.co/IAlbSRNn1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding FR clothing for a short women is nonexistent..they just don’t don’t carry them anywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Probably longer than out takes you assholes to blame Democrats for all your bad behavior]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IllectricRiver @SevenLionsMusic @Deorro @Gramatik @gjonesbass @RiotTenMusic @bleepbloopbass @LUCALUSH @manilakilla… https://t.co/ESmbaO9Q27]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @caseydband &amp; @ReadSouthall did a concert together, that’d be great. 🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is only one thing in the world worse than being talked about, and that is not being talked about.” ― Oscar W… https://t.co/a0uXwjVuMn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreasavage @stevezissis @truTV Two more episodes is not enough! More!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This nigga didn’t have milk to put in his eggs so put wine in it and ate that shit too. I’m DEAD😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[yo my daughters step mom saved me at the bar when a creepy dude wouldn’t leave me. she a real one for that 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why but I just realized I’m probably gonna end up like one of those poor white girls that get shamed on nationa… https://t.co/ft9aaPBv4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[After watching the dirty behavior of Ohio State fans behind the Iowa bench I think @DrakeKulick’s body bags 💼 comme… https://t.co/IUzcA5DKI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, I waited to wish @whistleandthumb a happy birthday because I was hoping to include a Spurs victory. Instead l… https://t.co/n8cz1fdkyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time with the gang @ the @fijdog concert. ❤️ https://t.co/PEw9lsznF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk When will the nightmare stop please people how many people must die how many]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three #murderinos having a time.   #ssdgm #staysexydontgetmurdered @ Sony Centre for the Performing Arts https://t.co/Um8dwsozNH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypriley Prepping for tomorrow's snow storm   Bottoms up, buddy   Bottoms up https://t.co/zYQL5v9teb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@O_Rant20 you are starting to sound like @pwilson_4. https://t.co/ZC4gT0fUiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guys wanted my  autograph, oh yes I did give him that. What the hell I'm a celebrity in my heart. @ Lindenwood… https://t.co/Br6ioegFSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ravey_baby I clicked till I got to the beginning and  😭💀💀💀 he really thinks he’s that one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Socialism is Evil and The Devil is hard at work!! Look out because God is Watching and when he’s Fed up t… https://t.co/4e9hluGxpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good grilled cheese sandwiches. I'm surprised that more people do not know about that block.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Shout it to the crowd in the back cause I don't think they heard you. Never do that. https://t.co/8xONVJ0v10]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that Izzy is "scared" of rats 🤣🤣🤣🤣 @EmeraudeToubia @arosende #SaveShadowhunters #ShadowhuntersLegacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was driving with my bestfriend and she started to sing and she got all the notes in the song perfectly. when i te… https://t.co/YtXyygir8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prairrie @qanon76 @realDonaldTrump Snd that’s why you fall for the pile of hogwash. Multiple sources and then you… https://t.co/OZJPSBHLHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Gracie!!! #bday #photography @ Salisbury University https://t.co/SS9H0HbUS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khanhakim_k @LudMarx1 @AintitMarvelous @PatGrant7777 @Jonatha97947998 @LionAndy2 @fufucat2 @saladesvertes… https://t.co/obxoN0ZrnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmjlyons @corinne_locher @ksplanet @fascismfighting @ColleenKenney11 @KLinduff @PatriciaMillin @Mindpollution3… https://t.co/ZGMg4bWa9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Une superbe simulation montrant la formation d’une amas de galaxies 🌌 #GalaxyCluster #Espace #apod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarreraGeorje @bitsofbri I feel like if this were true, she would know &amp; just ask her. lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArronJamesMusic I don't have the VHS, but I have he limited DVD release and the blu ray with the slipcover that… https://t.co/6zbkCH52nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched a video of a couple who said they wanna have a kid only because they got four nieces. Bro what]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weather forecast is predicting rain for next weekend.  Whoever is doing the rain dance in LA.. PLEASE STOP!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Students and Families: STOP URI FROM HOSTING A GARDEN BROS. CIRCUS - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/pqG12Xx7i2 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisstoMrstoMS @MustStopMS @SelmaBlair I don’t think I’ve ever heard “tight skinny jeans” as a symptom causer befor… https://t.co/XEiNzTtePJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Pitbull puppy Nylah is like the sweetest puppy ever and it scares me sometimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffrey_vallis @chrisgloverCBC @CBCToronto I agree disgusting. Why didn't anyone help him out? Sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[so Im finally watching abducted in plain sight ...... I’m sick to my stomach 🤢🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Done 🎼 seeing @slipknot August 16 @ruoffmusicenter Noblesville INDIANA! omg I’m so excited  #Knotfest AND just as… https://t.co/DeqJEmYZip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@faactnews Some great new resources to share!  @KristinKSmall @amweiss426]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you sadıkberki @sadkberki  for liking our show! Happy Valentine's Day! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[I played with an iPad Pro retouching some photos and video (what I am looking to do with my next tablet) and that t… https://t.co/a21nbxoMab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam Don’t sign the bill! Shameful that republicans are wanting this to pass!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TCCW85 Yes.  I really don't think I could have a good time with her because she's just so extra  And all over the place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StripeysRiposte @ColoradoMGTOW @manlogic2 They live on Reddit groups complaining about mean women hurting their feelz.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 So are you saying women just vote for the candidate they find sexy? Way to be a male chauvinist pig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMickyDolenz1 happy birthday ! You still rock !! https://t.co/slArGmqOhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of y’all haven’t ever had to push your car, jump in it and pop the clutch, and it shows!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet Where is Paul Ryan. Mine Flynn, and the Keebler elf Sessions ?  Is there a place where they are banished… https://t.co/b30x601475]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not into lesser of two evils logic but there are better politicians to direct « cancelled because they’re not p… https://t.co/8BBfssy3Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite pass time is getting drunk alone and trying to learn all the choreography in @Kehlani music videos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsStaceyCarney @Carla_Pereira2 @PeelSchools @JosephVetro Aww thx @MsStaceyCarney So @Carla_Pereira2 is a dear frie… https://t.co/MCoEitvmVh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My diet was so poor today. I’m still eating Doritos even tho I have to be up in 4 hours for work (;]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day! This year we took time to acknowledge the amazing support system we have around us… https://t.co/IGotk0E2CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[there hasn’t been a time we’ve been in the car together and he’s not holding my hand @KainKain612  💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VolTwitter Listening to Only Prettier by @mirandalambert on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/ls2kN0pJSH https://t.co/GYsv2AFBnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Math fun times! @LPitrucha @OutleyE @AliefISD @AliefMathK6 #aliefmission #aliefproud https://t.co/DeNx9gbZp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimOBrien If we look in her closet I BET there’s a coat made from Dalmatian skins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Domestic terrorist Christopher Hasson had a hit list which included leadership and members of @DemSocialists among… https://t.co/1IeB9kgd76]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com Humans started out as 2 in garden of Eden in middle of Africa, so they better have dark skin or the SUN would BURN them UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go! You can do it boy, go ahead; you just need the rhythm 💃🏻🕺 “ No pares sigue sigue “ 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loading........ @iampettigatez  . . . . . . . .  #pettigatez #shopping #retail #cheap #stlouis #stl #314 #clothes… https://t.co/dg6yOVJUI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAY TUNED ❗️❗️❗️❗️👀NEW DROP.....  @tapedelayfilms @queenpheena @jackknightthelegend   . . . . .… https://t.co/yi0MaftjX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I need a sedative to come down from this heart attack I had from driving on the icy roads. 🆘  #howmanydaysuntilspring]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1. Having goals in learning for Ss to set and achieve.  Allowing Ss voice, choice, and leading in discussions to h… https://t.co/1Jbe6ksWM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NxxbmoXLhK 1:32 we can try to I have lots of work for 3 years and it's not going fast]]></document><document><![CDATA[P A N I C !  A T  T H E  D I S C O We’re OG fans! So excited @ Oracle Arena https://t.co/cADiWlieyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh what a night!! Congrats meredithrdulany telfairball2019 @ Savannah, Georgia https://t.co/61ywjkqbyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relationships of all kinds can be difficult and complex. @ Lady B Collective https://t.co/834R7exhyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CAAWS @Kikoola96 @Jmizz20 @CurlingCanada @OntarioIsSoccer @ASandmeyer Great panel discussion! Thanks for organizing today’s event.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shawn’s mom made dinner and I felt obligated to eat it but I ate three pizza rolls and now I’m full 🤷🏼‍♀️ wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clreimer @danibizz Yup, snot bubbling bullies. I feel terrible for their victims but in both instances of their wa… https://t.co/KiUBppeAy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moxienh @johnteti Shouldn’t have to be. But when I search my your name the only person that comes up has one book… https://t.co/tbkBdT6XAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fancy! I’m more than twice her age and don’t buy wine that’s more than $15 a bottle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the boss says you can dress casual for work ❄☃️ @Hinchtown @SPMIndyCar @IndyCar #INDYCAR #5ToTheFront #snowday https://t.co/fEIoNWSXHh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I discovered my Patronus is an Eagle Owl on J.K. Rowling’s @pottermore. Find yours: https://t.co/cOjLuRQkEe #ExpectoPatronum]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love how my mom stops recording when she hugs me BUT ISNT TANA SO CUTE IM GOING TO CRY &lt;33 @tanamongeau https://t.co/JpuhKAOO6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metallica Day That Never Comes has finally arrived! Please play Day and Fade To Black!!! 🤘 #MetInLouisville @robinevitts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevDead2 Additionally can we note that I looted him and didn’t even know I did that.... lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 person is dead and 4 injured after an apartment caught fire in North #Sacramento overnight. I talked with a man w… https://t.co/yx7ix91Jn1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ransomedpatriot @ResistanceGold1 @paulpuckett911 @WHurensohn @BarkinDavid @TrumpsAlways @debbz8 @dmon4ever… https://t.co/TVigdXBXsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏅The Kid Is A Superstar🏅I am extremely honored to receive this award. This award would not be possible without your… https://t.co/dbgfx3Chg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodness! The ppl in Alabama had only 20 minutes to find shelter before the tornado hit them]]></document></documents></author>