<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s going down now!  #redhornbrew #greenhousecraftfood @ Red Horn Coffee House and Brewing Co. https://t.co/kZen4aX7cy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BDKoz @HeidiL_RN Hey genius, we make the same calls as PD often arriving before them and with no protection.  Not… https://t.co/zJdxRmg5Pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vdl515 @momimbored @AndrewGillum @SenJoniErnst @ChuckGrassley That’s because he was the golden moon they still hav… https://t.co/Fnr4BwkgU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is surgery day for my brother for his herniated disk https://t.co/wmKxZctJWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasbtico @eljimi @LosWhitexicans ¡Ya me proyecté! En vez de estatuilla de Oscar se llamaría Los David por David Du… https://t.co/ERwEubVrbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @Oma8612 Nikki Haley was governor of South Carolina and Lindsey Graham has been senator for SC for a lo… https://t.co/5jwncwFcsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class B girls BB end of 1st: Waverly 10, Elkhorn 5. Hear it on @KFORRADIO 103.3FM/1240AM and https://t.co/Cpow8mKULA #thevikelife #nebpreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got 3rd tonight beating Prince, Light (2-1) Kinda jank we take those, then losing to GalenTheWise (3-0) fuk, then J… https://t.co/e4zvYraXO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The last time that Republicans won anything worth mentioning Dwight Eisenhower was President. They have certainly g… https://t.co/tY6MlROdt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gulyona @IslaDeViva Исходя из логической цепочки нашей дискуссии получается, что лежать на диванчике это твоё призвание ;))]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never heard of Mr Mikes Casual Steak House, but the commercial says they have the game Perfection at the table… https://t.co/81e1kckJuc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp The MSM, time after time, proves their inability to speak truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Calitaliano777 Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets start up sonething ups onething up ww caught up for real but still live 8d music is yhe shit let's roll start this]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're using the richest Black woman in the world to dilute @michaeljackson image to make you believe that's it's… https://t.co/cGBxb2V9bY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Fox News the propaganda arm of the Trump presidency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts Troops - Always love Samoa’s! girlscouts #girlscoutcookies #DaisyGrace #SupportSamoas @ Moment https://t.co/8TugPOQ0RP]]></document><document><![CDATA[UP IN THE MORNING WITH THE RISING SUN GONNA RUN ALL DAY TILL THE RUNNING IS DONE!  Got our bibs ready and counting… https://t.co/c1kFgtxHtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Episode 018: 12 Years a Slave to Climate Change is OUT NOW! @YesKWAYi and I discuss political pandering, the urgenc… https://t.co/p3PBImpgux]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Thank you. On behalf of Lot’s wife and countless thousands  of nameless women , thank you and Tabitha.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr Love is in the house. Spreading the love on this #valentinesday #wcvb https://t.co/vvFYCAht0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pete_satit @UtdArena @Stalker2k19 Agreed! As well as play on the right. I think another right sided player is need… https://t.co/CfMgVUikqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer camp sure has changed from when I was a kid! #CyberSecurity #RSAC #CSO #CISO https://t.co/qEislbjshl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simply, the complete malfeasance of Trump and Republicans as to EVERYTHING...  Makes the starting place as to which… https://t.co/ljoFqyOFPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[BB posted for @F3_WTF_Ruck, it was an honor to lead https://t.co/xMWzAfwtV1 https://t.co/LE9liprU8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FPOnTheDL Winds are picking up here.  Only going to get worse.  Stay safe Marie]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at L'Auberge Casino Resort in Lake Charles, LA https://t.co/w1vU67wRNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritePads If I plug in my VCR at exactly 12:00 will that work the same as setting the time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be sure to check out Beyond Mountains Coffee from @WoodwardAcademy’s own Sean and Katie Kilpatrick… https://t.co/KVTvdWAlat]]></document><document><![CDATA[At one time or another, every player knows what this feels like. From being done putting on those cleats in high sc… https://t.co/9xzsLuLvkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WentRogue As a kid, I watched him to mock him; but I secretly felt guilty about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pensé que los árbitros eran Aliancistas? Como fue que nos botaron a dos? No cantan la posición adelantada ni la man… https://t.co/UsPdLJ8H4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a nice surprise to return home and realize the time on my bedside alarm clock is once again correct. #springforward]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takes 20 years for you to build a reputation and only 5 minutes to ruin it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swankystill @_ValTown_ How tf all my tweets get deleted. Wtf system took it off? Wasnt i speaking truth or what?]]></document><document><![CDATA[juice wrld is easily my favorite artist as of rn. idc that y’all made some of his music mainstream i’m mostlt talki… https://t.co/5D7CQO1NaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foods to help improve happiness.  Serotonin is an important chemical and neurotransmitter in the human body. It is… https://t.co/zDnICNhAuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well he was only caught once stealing two sodas. But a person doesn’t suddenly wake up and become a crazed soda thi… https://t.co/zhqGP1KYib]]></document><document><![CDATA[The media gets Draft Day haircuts too. @NBA2KLeague 💇🏻‍♂️🏀🎮 https://t.co/MmD7OV44dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sonicsman @Supersonics1967 @sonicsarena Great win in first round series over 55 win GSW.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraceeEllisRoss @MsJillMJones @therealgolden47 @RealPersiaWhite Cousin Ronnie is holding up pretty good too babe!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: James Halligan Obituary - San Francisco, CA | San Francisco Chronicle - https://t.co/2Y1UKVB0ZD: J… https://t.co/kkKKZ5PqRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I showed a #Realtor pics taken with Ultra-Wide camera on @Samsung #GalaxyS10, she had to have one to prep new listi… https://t.co/E2Fv9CC49L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, I’m done with this winter business 🥶. Time to reflect back on some warmer times 🌞I could really use some L… https://t.co/agbUYM7p97]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he brings the experience and insights of having been an @EWEButility commissioner, so he can attest to how… https://t.co/ccGLB6Kpq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DodgersNation And this team again is passing up a golden opportunity to put this team over the top to win a World… https://t.co/YS313ZVUQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@icecube He damn near had a triple double his ass had 9 assist I was there I seen it!!! LoL it was a good day... #levels]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dunkindonuts I just waited 50 min for my food &amp; you were out of bacon. My heart is broken]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parejaycomplice te ves muy bella un saludo.seguro lo tendrás .ese trío.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carolinecroe @Ding_Gorgeous @MarenMorris @DaytonModderman Idk! I stole it from @marenslambert]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marissadraws Mine got me a publisher— yadda yadda yadda— mildly successful career in comics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRAISING ALMIGHTY GOD  @LionelRichie and #Commodores sang it beautifully, #JesusIsLove! This I know.  And the bea… https://t.co/6449qybFQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Union County Fairgrounds in La Grande, OR https://t.co/QDpjh41Qjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic disruption: A reminder, King Street, between Queen Street and James Street, in downtown @St_Catharines will… https://t.co/tjJbHnEyOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Troymush203 Nope. Kobe missed the playoffs year after when Shaq left him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to How Fly for the first time in years. Remember this, @BeauJamison?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else surprised that Jason Bateman isn't in a Marvel movie yet or is it just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicharrones for lunch at Casa Zacatecas in Riverside , and tacos! @ ZACATECAS CAFE https://t.co/p3fsLs7g8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CanesGiveBack We will be there from 5:30-7:30pm before the game to assist with collecting those unused medications!! 💊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@castillejos_m @Rayados Todavía no digiero lo que acaba de hacer Alonso, increíble nos mató, entregó el partido al… https://t.co/MCIvg1AQ6L]]></document><document><![CDATA[11. Interaction style—but Morton thought he’d be great.  And he was right.  So, over the years, I’d go see perform… https://t.co/7Qi0RFxsQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You and I have been chosen by God to LIVE and live a life that is full and abundant and each experience of our live… https://t.co/ftUtHqwIpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how @yuri0rellana and I can have a full conversation off of GIFs and Memes haha 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone have the exact date the world is ending in 13 years cause I wanna put it in my calendar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me on @kkojradio as @JCCBBasketball takes on TMB. Tip-off coming up at 7 https://t.co/xxMYNAFgrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listened to @gwtpod Episode 1 and was dying. Enjoyed that way too much for someone who knows absolutely nothin… https://t.co/ZJKhGBsLck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear friends:  I would like to dedicate this thread to exploring the artistic (e.g., digital/music/visual/written/p… https://t.co/0ZXgBurf8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gorskon @ABatemanHouse Progressives just didn't work for me, so I stick with my lined bifocals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido tiene un as bajo la manga y muchos no ven eso, el régimen lo sabe, entiendo la frustración y el desaliento… https://t.co/50ZN2wjbJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you just say we need Mitt Romney? LmAooo 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 omg you really are a comedian!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el 9, descubrí que @adrianm10 probó las mieles del club 22 jajaja https://t.co/P8bDnb51pV]]></document><document><![CDATA[So here we are. With deflated expectations, a plan to plan a meeting to plan a task force, and a handbook for the p… https://t.co/YesJ05qVrU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident in #SoutheastOfWendell on Lk Wendell Rd and Applewhite Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a huge fan of Trench, but this is the one track on that album that is done to perfection. Love it.  https://t.co/3MUWahr4gi via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JU2419922 Don't you live in Hamilton? I am in Milton - I need you to tell me how much snow fell in Hamilton. ;) I… https://t.co/sMmDTzZ0AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidgaliel @ddale8 Wow!  Someone running for Congress in Houston (I forgot her name) was posting examples of gerr… https://t.co/sGZSPymaPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of some shopping therapy... (@ Saks Fifth Avenue in Etobicoke West Mall, Ontario) https://t.co/0cTHAieiXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment when you drop 2k on a phone and won’t be able to put a case on it 😬 #GalaxyFold]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t even know this was a thing and when I heard about I just wanted to know the logic of whoever thought of th… https://t.co/V2242hCfif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all need to fix the officiating problem in the SEC.. #hotgarbage fucking awful!!! @SEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1 Ranked.                                     6x Conf CHAMPS.                       LAST UNDEFEATED team in NCAA D… https://t.co/6P7LSLsPO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always like what have I got to lose?  Enter for a chance to win a MacBook Air! 👀 https://t.co/6lWrhGfFjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Archie Miller was black he would have gotten fired at half time. IU STINKS hahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[They need a search function in iMessage like PDFs have so i can easily scroll back to previous convos by searching a word]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabiona9 lmao first of all fuck off i don’t even know u second that has literally nothing to do with what i said. no correlation. exit]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Academia adds 'hydration station' https://t.co/Qs4FMSqk9U via @chanhassenscoop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC30 How 'bout,since our prisons NEVER rehabilitate ANYONE, except those who just love freedom more than life its… https://t.co/YpsPXJ8HLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desde @Coparmex_ens  nos oponemos a que se viole la Constitución estatal en #BajaCalifornia para obtener beneficios… https://t.co/PpJQ01R8fi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @TaggartRehnn @Riopedre31 @chance4gardener @KingPeachDP @JoeMomma833 @Beantowndougish @lynn_maryellen… https://t.co/mLO2VzrjZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCI_Athletics No arguements here, it has been a treat to get to compete against both of them. There are other good… https://t.co/Ma2xLhxYRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJRHSimmons He just ran the 40. Usually, those come in the next few hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Residence in Atlantic Highlands progress photos #TMArchitects #cedarhomes #architecture @ Atlantic Highlands… https://t.co/kUt6NTYwee]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my day was pretty good! Wow! In person, Yosemite is amazing! https://t.co/HyAAEoSFbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because of the hopes, dreams and aspirations the dwell within me; I must continue to develop the tenacity, resilien… https://t.co/CMv9kEnFbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A non bet better sir orbital primary. No fun in sad moments i know shedded tears too weak no more dear love moments .part of now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CARandDRIVER @Porsche Lamborghini Porsche Bentley rolls Royce all got suvs now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a 2 hour flight but downloading 8 hours of podcasts is my aesthetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where do I get @SadieLundquist jerseys?!? She’s the coolest chic I know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m Rooney, I’m telling players that the radio shows are over. Done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharleyCasserly I have a lot of respect for you but your comments on Kyler Murray was down right disrespectful and… https://t.co/omRfLk6wYo]]></document></documents></author>