<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NurseCakeHelen @SabahatHizlan @morley_georgina @ClevelandClinic @cwru @NeuroethicsFord @boissyad @CleClinicNews… https://t.co/tWJhA7Ee7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteAbe It’s 63 in Orlando right now. People are getting out their winter jackets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daughter vs. Mother Vegan Smoothie Challenge on YouTube! Who does it better? Click on the link below to watch the f… https://t.co/78uHhNtbrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCREAMING HAPPY 20TH BDAY TO MY ROOMIE!! Thank you for being such a blessing in my life and pushing me in my faith.… https://t.co/oWN1rfTjAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBarri I believe that being a lying grifter will get you any position you want in this administration.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ramos4Texas thank you for today and I apologize that we were unable to stay for the resolution]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASUNMBB championship. @LipscombMBB vs. @LibertyMBB #beLieve Go Bisons! @LipscombBisons https://t.co/ikf6g6sNBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407  wanna pay off my student loans? Rumor has it you got a big check today! 😊 #onlyanhrfromphillyyoucanstaytilyoufindaplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unbreaking America: A NEW Short Film about Solving the Corruption Crisis https://t.co/TvajDxZ6hQ via @YouTube https://t.co/fZ81fo5lRL 👍🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[HTML coding with @codemoji123 #SDEisthePlacetobe #YearoftheDragon #STEMfriday https://t.co/q5cMrXNVK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did this six times to se what you were talking about...I’m so fascinated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who don’t know, I love listening to podcasts on my nightly run. Imagine my surprise when I hear @UTSWNews… https://t.co/DxHctTrMyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Says the guy who declared bankruptcy 5 times, drove every single business he started into the ground and is too stu… https://t.co/JyswXS9wDq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump For the rich. Your base is still reeling from no tax refunds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamelaalyynn oh yeah i’m not that dumb like some people that move out and can only afford a couple months of rent then have no money 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnthimself @nowthisnews @justicedems @sunrisemvmt @AOC Lots of unemployed folks,  but that's ok,  money will be gi… https://t.co/Gsxqhr6S42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMACKIETMO @TMobile @JonuelH @asandrea89 @avillarrealdeal @Lilly_NYC @JennieMontanye @tiffthetechie @TChainzDC… https://t.co/Bn03c1Jud3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@warmheatherette Omg this is so cool! And we have some itchy faces in the snow ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Achez22 @TheTrialsofMAP @Eagles @MalcolmJenkins @Ike58Reese @36westbrook Zack just sent me this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did yoga for the first time today and decided I’m going to start going every day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_kingda16 @patchfarmstead I am thinking more piglet than wild boar...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The President of the United States mocked Jeff Sessions' accent yesterday...Mr President, I am a proud Southerner.… https://t.co/DkdMuPtmDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaWBZ @PanMass Thank you, Lisa. After all the bills are deducted toward the end of the month, I'll see what's le… https://t.co/b5M5cUAYKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh heyyyy, it’s my jobs birthday tomorrow (Pisces stand up)🎉🎉 Come hang with me and enjoy a line-up of events that… https://t.co/E5QEDzu3HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico The journalists knew when they could be around to humiliate Stone so the world could see him do the perp… https://t.co/GmzZuNL4Zs]]></document><document><![CDATA[for the first time ever, there’s not a single toxic person in my life and i’m so HAPPY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binging with Babish: Spaghetti Tacos from iCarly https://t.co/RtSWMWGwj5 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlbertoRavell Por eso estamos como estamos porque no servimos como seres humanos jamás no unimos ni nos amparamos unos a otros]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ja0nuy おはこんばんちはです〜。池の氷も影の部分は溶ける気配がない寒さです。明るい時間が増えたのはホッとしますが...☺️今日も早足で駅に向かいます!本日もよろしくお願いします! https://t.co/FGYyJZTbB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[American Financial Network is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #Finance job openings, including "Bili… https://t.co/R9vAReATws]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been broke down by anyone before. Nobody has ever made me feel less of myself. Or made me feel like i wa… https://t.co/dDLUROTxTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom is finally off today I’ve been looking forward to this day all week]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teaching the future assures lives are not squandered, sacrificing for the development at whatever cost the gift “Of… https://t.co/qO2cOUZZy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturdays are for Beau and coffee 🐾 ☕️ @ Tavern 41 https://t.co/7GrbLMbGXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Desert View Middle School Parent Conference Night was a Success! We love welcoming our community into the building!… https://t.co/STB3CBOFKI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryceleonardo @Jasonk19941994 @27anny27 @revndm @tonyposnanski @alanilagan @TuckerCarlson @Progressive @CapitalOne… https://t.co/KRg7bqDmTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TDavenport_NFL Thanks for watching @TDavenport_NFL! I appreciate you retweeting my @nll segment!! 😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my niece after Mass on Ash Wednesday, St Mary’s Catholic Church https://t.co/mobowKYaLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few more from our snowy session.... #nwaseniorphotographer #seniorpictures #seniorportraits #wendydunnseniors… https://t.co/6ZN2Z2I3aj]]></document><document><![CDATA[The original word for mask is known as "larva" - in a thoroughly debunked society, there would be no social peace.… https://t.co/mLyLf4rd7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @Aug1405 That's horrible! Totally disgusting! It's even painful to watch. I hope that she was O.K. How this could happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge to post the covers of 7 books I love. Day 2 read everyone of these until the twins went t… https://t.co/CiRscwxhfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DocCrom I’m on my phone rn but it’s the NLE website, “online practice app” via their “Exams” drop down menu— the l… https://t.co/srdRWnaMch]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC This Sat America’s TS Adult PinUp Model Sat Feb23 ...This Fabulous Performer Isnot To Be Missed @ RBar 460 West… https://t.co/p8RsoSRIXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwwbigbaldhead I loved this episode so much! I believe it's my favourite.  I love researching family history and t… https://t.co/FJx25eIS57]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did RuPaul tell us not to fuck it up every week because she wanted to? Was that her long game?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: the big idea in CSforALL is the ALL. It’s the idea that every student should have access to a rigorous, joyful… https://t.co/D5oIvVR4Cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly. I actually laughed when I saw it like, well, if anyone has a legit reason...🤔👍🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Westchester county  New York She lied AND may have had an apartment there, but THAT was a ruse to prove residency.… https://t.co/G2ZANKjVaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever burped &amp; sneezed at the same time?? bc i really think death just flashed before my eyes lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlsreallyrule I just imagine his sycophants telling him what an all caps BRILLIANT idea it is! Living in an alte… https://t.co/kQA78CKceI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading means having a vision and sharing it with others. When a person get to inspire others, it is possible to sh… https://t.co/Bd8Snsz0BE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mf really rank on some random dude that probably eat hotdogs in his beans lol.. rice and mushrooms is amazing bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally every time jude law came on screen this is what I did in my head https://t.co/x298Eg5PfL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when WeWork banned meat for environmental reasons? 🧐 https://t.co/2wwOUq1Up8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the @Ren_MI_Links #ladieswholead event! Wonderful ladies celebrating each other for we've done and what's… https://t.co/Gxo6ltmhrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The internet has been my family for 10+ years and that is not healthy. I try so hard to stay close to them but it’s… https://t.co/fkZ2KxIPuo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking of this moment........thats history.......... https://t.co/JyDi9gl8Y6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good insights on the power-law debate from @pholme in @NatureComms. “Network Science is successful because it is ap… https://t.co/fbveFRNjLj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HudesMatthew I anchor weekend mornings. 5-7am Saturday and 6-9am Sunday. (I was off this past weekend). Then I rep… https://t.co/HBA9xBjOMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[end of an awesome run as lady Bears 🏀 fall to Avery Co 65-54; @ShaunaeLichelle w/20; finish season 18-7 GO 🐻… https://t.co/iXJcUDfWfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@budweiserusa Bought 2 cases of 25 oz cans the past 2 weeks and when drinking each beer the inside of the can smell… https://t.co/JWHCY53QFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really got into our books today! @AmericanReading @Scholastic @ScholasticTeach  @warrenstjohn #books #soccer… https://t.co/vaVgr2YkiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lashes by Anne #lashes #lashesextension #thousandoakshighschool #newberrycollege #highlights #westlakehighschool… https://t.co/mDmgvCQM6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defra: Not Born To Fight: - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/Ds9jQvaZNz via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new #Solange album is pretty fantabulous. That is all. #SaturdayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon Ducks acrobatics and tumbling bested Arizona Christian University 277.755-247.745 tonight, Feb. 23, 2019. //… https://t.co/dIu3pwUGlc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first time I saw a trauma bay was at @orlandohealth the morning of the Pulse tragedy. It was silent, mournful a… https://t.co/oIGQuJJXxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just spent the last 15 min singing Sucker by the #jonasbrothers to my dog. He gets it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshBreslowWKRN @WKRN @StewartCoEMA Most people would say it's worth 60k]]></document><document><![CDATA[An empty Amy’s Ice Cream container always makes me sad because it means I ate it all, but it’s so hard to come to A… https://t.co/DI57pwLt1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heyyy what d’ya THINK about this? Kicking things off at #Think2019 💥 Can’t wait to hear from Ginni! https://t.co/hehSVpILij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asmr53180713 .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different kin… https://t.co/pwKg1S6Wxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MzEiGhT8_2u @bjae__ Hahaha never been able to tell who was the bigger kid ❤️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danforthfrance https://t.co/xNLtKtRF5w Nurse at abortion clinic tells it like it is. They have been killing babies… https://t.co/lz8YzJs1Js]]></document><document><![CDATA[If cardi is in it best believe I’m listening to it #bardigang @iamcardib 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimPhamKREM We will miss you here in Chattanooga,  but follow your dreams! I have family in Spokane!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @mike_sell to post covers of 7 books that I ❤️.No explanations, no reviews. I’ll challenge some… https://t.co/ZEPi5zdI6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[For deest.aany 18th #clubbinwitdaAUNT @ Ricardo's  Night Club https://t.co/J0lxqUGhJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inclusionchick @CCSEMaryland Thanks for the shout out @inclusionchick. You are correct that it is through… https://t.co/1XE0wZ8CtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaNoireDe @ahn_dray_uh @DrewskieC did you want cpd to put out an unnecessary statement saying “the fbi will be the… https://t.co/j1lKaStH8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, I guess they give you the outfit for free. I couldn't find anywhere to buy it. It was already in my inventory.… https://t.co/7FvQMlDUld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ordered 200 business cards ... wondering where I’m gonna even find 200 people to give them to. https://t.co/gwFmVF30pB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessiStone @AndrewGilmanOK @Eddie_Rado @mattravis I can sleep anywhere.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That one kid in gym class who refused to admit he got hit in dodgeball https://t.co/lJKe3rZ7Ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Washington, DC, check out this job: https://t.co/ekFM4wDjoS #Accounting]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've come to the conclusion that it is impossible to sleep next to Austin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day from me and Peanut Charley Reese! #valentines https://t.co/zYGR7uAsKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a week @MadingES! We had so many awesome activities! It’s fun to learn @MadingES! Thanks to everyone for makin… https://t.co/o70CpoATVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pay too much to dorm at sfsu for the power to be going out at least once a week]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted my greatgrandma to see me at my graduation, other track meets, even down to my wedding day. My heart hurts SO BAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow ilysm 😭😭❤️ &amp; i know, it feels like my hard work is FINALLY being recognized and i’m so happy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beerappreciationsociety has the best board at #MSB. Thanks for this taste of home, stephenmandula. While this does… https://t.co/o6TM05Nwf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets Kevin McCarthy must’ve had an epiphany. During the campaign, McCarthy said  he believed Putin was… https://t.co/K5HJDIE8PQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why should this method of transmission be any different than others ... tax preparation feels like a chore with gru… https://t.co/3NF3ex2VLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[McFirst poisson frites minute maid + un deuxième sandwich mcfirst ommmggg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hilaryluros @Bornabrit1 @fenrir_71 Just how do you get money laundering from soliciting a prostitute?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TH55202331 I follow back !! VIP on #TeamMAGA #BackTheBlue #SaveTheBabies #KAG2020  #MAGAVET ✡️✝️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searched thru a ton of podcasts including the top rated ones on iTunes ...   Not one ☝🏼 could keep my attention for… https://t.co/ZDKVeUZWVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne @AidenWolfe I think it is more about her being a Democratic Muslim woman than it is about anything… https://t.co/MPWkq9CFhQ]]></document></documents></author>