<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is a very specific problem but it’s cold in LA and I only have flannels and no sweatshirts and I feel underprepared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I watched @TheHateUGive and @greenbookmovie back to back and LET ME TELL YALL, I am so tired from crying an… https://t.co/ppOBdkHrZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My butt hurts from all the walking I did in LA can’t wait to get back to NYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmalikauthor @erbearmoynihan You need cards that self destruct.  Because hilarious.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What makes. You think the changing world is all bad and we can control who  and what Happens to it more rain desert… https://t.co/Oc8PDmWttx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awonderland because of the angle we were at your visual has no nose https://t.co/rR7ELLcs2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheodoreArt Ya great comparison we are literally living in 1930s germany]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlars7 @studiowalters @MsJBoyko There was a lot of joy in the hallway today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo como estupida queriendo ir a Alburquerque pensando que encontraré  el East High School  ahi y realmente me entero que esta en Denver 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA['Lego Batman 2: DC Super Heroes' Teases Characters 'Arkham City' Style - ComicsAlliance | Comic book... #humor… https://t.co/8hfCQ08Rl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being smart sucks sometimes. Like why can’t I just think about sex and scamming? Lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Constitutional Republic stands, Bernie Sanders, America's true real winner by vote would not have weakened Amer… https://t.co/vrru1eQOQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Nicole Gilmore!!! Heather Lindsay ,1,111.  Good girl!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure is!  Should have checked traffic before leaving the house... inching past the Barbur exit #pdxtraffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XanBeans Then he tried to tell me when he thought I was from because he’d travelled all over Africa. https://t.co/3tcBzNUFHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HOLLYJBIRD @sarahlbrumley @craftyforhome @30days30ways @sagebrushfarmNV @suziday123 @confessions_cup @GiGiBclub… https://t.co/iSU5lB7S5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weight loss tip: get sick af Literally lost 5 lbs in the last 72 hours and it’s still dropping 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottcowley I grew up in Texas.  If we didn’t smell like brisket, we smelled like queso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cramoukji Ha. Pretty much. Just for hundreds of other people's love. Hopefully it brought some joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“...For example, you can compliment a co-worker on his or her appearance and still offend that person. Intention ma… https://t.co/4rssPDRc7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjameskennedy awww, thanks for the pic! I know you all get it alllll the time, so I hope it’s still fun for you… https://t.co/HyshuUf7z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite if you’ve ever been late to something because the drive thru line at Pals was so long it blocked the inter… https://t.co/JZ3zoLMiZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some touristy things from Portland so far! 😜📚😋🍩🌤 https://t.co/bEPlDtoKyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful afternoon of creating self portraits!🖍🖌✏️#missnancy #makingmemories https://t.co/m7ewbwGdYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the new day comes new strength and new thoughts @ West Ellenton, Palmetto, Florida https://t.co/CCgl3ALscu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and I haven’t talked for a whole day I think she forgot about me 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarcasmStardust I’m working on that. A) I need to, and B) my sister’s getting married in October, and I’m maid of… https://t.co/d3uyr2Nvwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEdwardsBball Nah mark..no excuse for a mans shoe exploding lol..if these were adidas or any other shoe we would have destroyed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only took 3 hours this time... 🙄#lashqueenbeauty #nylashqueen #hairdone #beautyinsideandout #naturalrouge… https://t.co/brdhKX5bTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[i cant believe i’m really in nyc right now and seeing 5 broadway shows over the next week 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[swipe to the end for a surprise ;) @ Millennium Park https://t.co/qKK3N3tSfu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @jetrotter They just can’t admit when they are wrong. The Dems have character flaws!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have either a wicked bad cold or a sinus infection idek and I just got back from a st paddys day bday and its 1:3… https://t.co/zzilGNdhcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just watched the entire first season of stranger things and I’m still trying to figure out what the hype is about]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 days straight of snow ❄️ #winterwonderland #threefeetdeep #notinfloridaanymore⛄❄⛄❄ #dreamboat https://t.co/3o9roGerxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to expose GOP for the cover up and plot they concocted to retain power. Hillary was right about the vast ri… https://t.co/IjkkJEYe8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[been thinking of what Luke's family and what you all are feeling.  My mother died at three o'clock in the morning o… https://t.co/JZsEYMJhtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive been w/o my best friend for a couple of months now, and I couldn’t be more grateful because even if we are 8,00… https://t.co/n961EGYq3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my parents watching @Jejvinson’s audition https://t.co/JVUWk0e6dM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so tired. I hate that I can't sleep at night cus mfckas want me up during the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been so into grotto getting my house together I need to take time to get my hair an nails and feet done]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day #coding and learning all about #robots and writing code to move the robots!! In addition to coding, there… https://t.co/L5Kk24Mc3e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrChrisWJackson Yes but an increase in rigor should not equal an increase in grade level beyond the grade level test.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadusasAffair @SmartAssCanBe LMAOOO that was a rough patch in my life y’all 😭😭😭😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an IPA by @DrinkCaribru @ DRT Route 305 Bus — https://t.co/1kyh1wIvQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our little Sammy has jaundice in his ears, eyes and gums. He has some swelling in his abdomen w/major vertigo and h… https://t.co/BwKbpOb6NH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lapittenger "A low humming of mediocrity runs through me" is imagery of a level not often practiced by the mediocr… https://t.co/mU6Cac7VXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy March!  Only 3 more weeks until spring break - you can do it! https://t.co/hQepB3sxHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerinacoma The church is one thing, faith is another I believe. I just.wish you Peace and Grace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s so beautiful... when the love of my life says “your family is my family” this is in reference to my… https://t.co/EPThLD73nO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody attend The Miracle Center Church.  Sun, Mon, Wed. Please let me know. @ The Miracle Center Church https://t.co/nx664tL1Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow... really was married to a rich dude for too long... I thought my laptop was for word docs, emails, &amp; shopping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After we planted our sunflower 🌻 seeds, we watered them for the first time! 💦#smithfamilykindergarten  @ME_Mustangs… https://t.co/YjNN5ZkFss]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanIdol @LukeBryanOnline @katyperry @LionelRichie Luke is just a awesome human!]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pXy6AM7jQG / Louis Thériault - Cut Ties With ITR Animal Torture! https://t.co/A2pwt2N320 via @CdnChange]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waited 9 months for nothing, but hurt and broken promises. story of my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just came back home from my acting classes and found this at my step door 🚪 💐😍❤️ No doubt a real #gentleman knows h… https://t.co/MzpPpkDPdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akann90 I need you to bring it back. #atlutd #UniteAndConquer https://t.co/vZRc7KEzLJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#imisshim #ilovehim #jason #jdickey #jasonboy #jasondickey #speakupandreachout #stopsuicide #withyouwentsomuchofme… https://t.co/7kRdULQ3c9]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the most dedicated #Preds fans, making it to almost every home game. How amazing are these two?! 🏒 https://t.co/WcKEy49EdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The judge said he'll think more about whether the plaintiff's counsel is allowed to mention @IARCWHO's conclusion r… https://t.co/l0iden05ZC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It be seeming like mfs be itching to have a problem with you as if you ain’t already got enough mf problems to deal… https://t.co/OhHwpaURGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't think of a better way to end the night. #roomservice #stlouis @ St. Louis, MO https://t.co/NnlupR5dyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone come love me and hold me please bc I can’t deal with this fucking feeling]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 month and 18 days until i get to see this queen live.   The anticipation is KILLING ME.… https://t.co/gZVt5VzLtU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bee-Gladys Knight #BeeMask      Alien-Latoya Jackson #alienmask Lion-Rumer Willis? #LionMask     Rabbit-Joey Fatone… https://t.co/a2fnO4bS9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[desperately trying to find a makeup youtuber with normal people skin so i can find out if the foundation REALLY works]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 @GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS This is from July but lists the various gov investigations. Top… https://t.co/jgohAVMyAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lost 6 pounds just this weekend and if that doesn't show I'm stressed Idk what does]]></document><document><![CDATA[pics of best friend things | Every Tall Girl Needs A Short Best Friend - Totally... #laughter #tee-hee #grin #comic https://t.co/sTqukYQyEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bigwin#beatualr #astatemb #pinknight #breastcancerawareness #breastcancermonth thank you steamrollerblues for the… https://t.co/8djbmuyOXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A family that prays together stays together #jesusfamily #whatyoudoforchristwilllast#asformeandmyhousewewillserveth… https://t.co/4mmPibaf6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@small_titters @ABC @LinseyDavis @GMA I hate to be the one to tell you this but yes you can my husband's from Scotl… https://t.co/5moDbS7eTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes indeed. Especially the nice sweet ones from important people in your life ✨ oooo chileeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovefool by the cardigans is probably my favorite song to have stuck in my head]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I miss this? Was out getting coffee and just got in now!  #rethink_learning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paint me in poetry Drown me thoughts  For I am like the patterns I don’t always make sense But I love in sequence -… https://t.co/D03saBRjED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible. The fact it was one of his first reports there, too! Ugh. I love this story. Congrats, Bob!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seeing the harents tonight. #FleetwoodMac #Atlanta https://t.co/fPkcLim2EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @RedMtnAVA @hedgeswine @fabienlaine @outwinesblog @GailBenzler @jimofayr @john_mobbs @cuvee_corner… https://t.co/EsrBjcmbG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad we didn’t get to see Mike play before he had surgery on his arm this season but as you can tell Landon was so e… https://t.co/0xkFYmFRWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump I've come to the conclusion that a lot of us white people are stupid!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the pleasure of starting the day at The Christ Hospital Annual 1st Year Anniversary Breakfast!  This is alway… https://t.co/mEvsuAW376]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VectorSigma4 @AndrewSolender @farbeyondblue4 “They eat kids” 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/gEJESWeYSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is crucial, and we must raise awareness about the importance of telling our school’s story. #LeadLAP… https://t.co/X810UAhBOa]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Girls of the Wild” by Nikita Gill • #InternationalWomansDay #StayWild https://t.co/1ZXT4UMXeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What has changed since the #MeToo movement? “Everything and nothing.” -@susanthesquark #SXSW2019 https://t.co/07jlUpbfqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Microblading is  a semipermanent technique for enhancing the appearance of the eyebrows, in which pigment is scratc… https://t.co/lFXHwZ6XQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why you think you can come in here with all your premeditated anger about a pipe YOU BROKE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winesalongirl @MalcolmNance @jenesq2 @Impeacherator @SpeakerPelosi Exactly! And prosecutors will admit that they w… https://t.co/juc2hvyRAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTweetOfGod Hasn't helped... ash burned it self out... or message not understood...take your pick 🤓😎😃😇🤣laughing]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you are what you say you are, a superstar, then have no fear, the cameras here]]></document><document><![CDATA[mirth right? Cyanid and happiness comic #comedy #snicker #grin #clever https://t.co/vnbma9ldjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CS_Cooop Sure but plenty of young boys who end up playing in the NBA/NFL/MLB come from poorer backgrounds and stil… https://t.co/77QxQTmTV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[😢💕 I really want my daughter to be able to experience this with my husband.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadAtAnyLevel @BristolGirl125 @MaryNChaney @bshrivastav @jensmcfarland I’d be happy to help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnNeilKeeble1 @SAFEatx @BankofAmerica @NikkiGrahamATX @KVUE Thank you for sharing this message!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuándo toman malas decisiones y no saben que a quien más le afecta es a la familia...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajoneswilkins It’s a big deal! And, I know they’ve been asked to take it down weeks ago...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happy #internationalwomensday   There is so much to say about being empowered and free as a woman. My prayer to ev… https://t.co/kADBVGNm0W]]></document></documents></author>