<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Especially if they beat #Tennessee in the #SEC championship. Now if they go 3-0 vs the #Vols definitely a 1 seed. .… https://t.co/9TCfBsu1At]]></document><document><![CDATA[After the new #SNL I love rolling in to #VintageSNL on the NBCW channel from Seatlle. https://t.co/pkabGnJBcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Platanoooo Power🤣🤣🇩🇴🇩🇴🇩🇴🇩🇴 #dominicanindependenceday @ New York, New York https://t.co/HhWcOvzQf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just started thinking about what if there was a huge earthquake right now, and thought about how scary it would b… https://t.co/09CeNmnT5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeLeftSucks @dvibrationz @PolAnimalAus @NikolovScience @reneread @dunvirkin @M_Sighil @KCTaz @3GHtweets… https://t.co/VCt5xDcTzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The grand jury report on this went directly to the House Judiciary Committee considering impeachment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dell XPS 13 Review: This Time It&amp;#39;s Practically Perfect https://t.co/T7p7hu7BxU via @gizmodo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I think I'm going to let @WynonnaEarp fans name my little travel buddy, I'll take 4 names then but it to a vote… https://t.co/qoNfMSjbcx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna cry when I meet @RealMelina at @Wrestlecon this year because she is my inspiration &amp; she inspires me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be nice if you had an intelligent thought. There's no reason to assume you ever will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to see my name trending but with the context that it goes it with...not so much. #FreeTristanThompson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Ground hog day for you! Are you going to tweet this again next Tuesday too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Americans’ net worth is pitiful. Increase diversity. BCG | Want to generate inventive new ideas that can win… https://t.co/VVWI0QDyqR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanmdunn Only exceptions in the inner deaneries are St Rita’s and St Mary’s. The newer parishes to the extreme… https://t.co/AgMHwePtdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods They come after mine they better arrive in Ambulances. Cause that's what they will need when they s… https://t.co/GUfoOUfVGm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before: Duplicated logic, state, effects in each reusable input. After, just one line to call a custom useValidatio… https://t.co/hMECX4eQuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers for the bereaving today!! Steve Hinkle we Honor you!! #BackTheBlue]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @CorinneOly @Whitney_Dillon3 @jill_cheerleade @cheyennepaige_3 @bbykayk @__laracampbell 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDLHughley You could tell Kraft is getting old. Told his limo driver to leave the car running while he went inside for a second.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@defjam @Royceda59 @Logic301 @Eminem @TeamVisionary I love how em rocks the @PRhyme_Official hoodies since day 1. P… https://t.co/zhH1Fh4yk4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drjosflynn @hswapnil Yes, this is a dilemma.  Allow patients to choose an inferior treatment regimen or work hard… https://t.co/IfmqSRXTHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson I thought you damn asses we’re counting on Mueller bull squeeze ? Pick a lane dip shit .]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sea Captain  Portrait of Sigurður Jónsson @auroraarktika  #Hasselblad X1D https://t.co/P8LOoXVWyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of thsinwill matter in 50,000 years. We will pass, ironically part of the same story and timeline, yet far awa… https://t.co/8OWO5t5xF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreeRalo BREAKING: The Feds Offer Ralo A Plea Deal After Almost a Year Behind Bars!! https://t.co/FbftskRoeZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUAIDO en las Mercedes le habla al pueblo venezolano desde la Plaza Sadel llena hasta los teque teques. Es valiente… https://t.co/h17Y81kM44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDaIey #InvasionofPrivacy #KingofRnB 👀🌠💰💵🎼🎺🎻🎸🎹🥁🐐📽️🕶️💪🌎✂️✔️💯‼️  https://t.co/L6NMPExHxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToTalIy_ Looks like they did the stabbing for once https://t.co/4Er2sC7hAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chance4gardener No it’s Spreading like a disease here https://t.co/c0dwYMk4F1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well just got done streaming for the night, off to bed than off home tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 We do live in a world where everyone is taught to be a victim!  #KAG2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Motown #Mondays #DianaRossandTheSupremes #Trinitarian https://t.co/BC1LizKAyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to a new study the financial responsibilities of having children can reduce a persons happiness. But it a… https://t.co/fywf7eAXcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expanding on a thought... I'm increasingly unconvinced that "fans" really improve any experience. Sports, movies, m… https://t.co/Mwc3SEbA3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[“For I could wish that myself were accursed from Christ for my brethren, my kinsmen according to the flesh:” Romans 9:3 KJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodolfoLanderos @SirJohnLaguna Pero esas copas no le van a ayudar a pasar esta fase]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpuopolo @realDonaldTrump Only to cuss him out and levy a barrage of insults on him]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥#spikelee #oscars #tinker #iwouldalmostpayanythingforthese @ Rhodes Ranch, Las Vegas https://t.co/6bDWqw3tLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_p What's better then waiting on the crew demo then by watching Galacticraft!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With another road closure on Thomas street, nearby business owners and managers say they're worried about losing cu… https://t.co/SIOLxBjbQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Poppe Awesome our boys will only be a couple weeks age difference.  Wrastling buddies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Seahawks If you trade for Antonio Brown, would the headline the next morning read "A.B. to Sea"?  Just wondering.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisastark351 @flyn4fun2 Harris is still young. I like Biden against The fat orange man he won’t take his shit! And… https://t.co/Kq7YcISOUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday https://t.co/YJepM5V5Fi! sepiaprasada @ The Edmon https://t.co/fMn5qyh8Pt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 Right around his overall approval ratings.  Imagine that.  Who saw that coming?]]></document><document><![CDATA[DaBaby Today (Remix) ft. LIL BABY [Official Audio] https://t.co/59X6FGfXmT via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KochLiz His status is climbing. Took on espn and the nfl and is in the pace with dale at #DAYTON500 barstool is on… https://t.co/Kzqbo9M9GX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 Better watch next she will want deceased people that voted for Dems to still count]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sandraccalvarez creo q se debe apoyar el talento de Venezuela y respetar a cada diseñador, asi como se respeta y s… https://t.co/Z6n8SFR7ub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiquidPoach @KingArtGames @IBMDeutschland @lab1886 @IBMSecurity @MitsubishiElect @SwissCognitive @swiss_un @UNOOSA… https://t.co/BINXANHjAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that I really would appreciate it if everyone would like not tell me anything about my ex like I… https://t.co/s9MzhunWW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren She would be better off spending her money on state/local candidates.  You know, since education is a loca… https://t.co/wLpHI9Au59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeBatardShow I’m sorry but Allyson’s basketball song could be the greatest thing ever for AM radio 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doesn’t expecting the unexpected make the unexpected expected😉😊 #old #extra #photography #background #spec @ No One… https://t.co/SsjTDWGbjb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CryptoJChains @bitninjasupply @WomanBlockchain @mrjberlin @lisamightydavis @ZogLord @Radioactive3D @CryptoEuclid… https://t.co/pE3WQNUIbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlenderSherbet @AnnCoulter Reminds me, oddly, of Indiana Jones bringing a gun to a machete fight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Believe by 1 fell into the house on Super Bowl day Kiln 4 https://t.co/9MkYg57ic5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drewryancarter Don’t forget to mention the extension we gave Daniels 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado exempts cryptocurrencies from securities. https://t.co/sNLVeK3FIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Koutchboom @TheChewDefense @BLCAgnew @ChloeGMoretz @gretafilm @1sttimewatchers @SixxDemonBag @SamShotFirst… https://t.co/x2cJNavJN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveSteffenhage @NBCNews Are you indicating he would “prostitute” himself for political gain?]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to mention the thousands of obstructed view seats behind the goals. sounds familiar. https://t.co/Ej1uDSpdHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people you make in college are not friends. They are family.    If you don't agree, you attended the wrong college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panchitoaleman Un amigo tuyo, exvicepresidente, hace pocas semanas me comentaba al respecto:”todo lo q es regulado, termina destruyéndose”]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Reagan administration’s policies in Central America are an excellent illustration of the “good ideas do not nee… https://t.co/igpr7rMWLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 4:57 and the Chic-Fil-A line at the Airport is already 20 deep. Peak Atlanta. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance Isn’t it funny that just last yea—I mean yesterday, republicans on the House Judiciary Committee coul… https://t.co/NdDvkuHQ4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmonst5 well done this weekend Christian!! Super proud of you here in Morgantown!! Best of luck at Nationals!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s specials- Roasted pulled pork, egg up, salsa, avocado mash over grits  Roasted poblanos peppers, tomato, ch… https://t.co/CvX4qj3dz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pa #pennsylvania #igersoftheday #iger #igers #igeroftheday #picoftheday #photooftheday #pictureoftheday… https://t.co/hnHAa44ZXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Red Bull Vending Machine - Stockton Plaza in Hamilton, NJ https://t.co/Y3UyQ9Ml9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#architecturalmarvels #worldtradecentermemorial #oculusquest #manhattan #newyork @ The Oculus at the World Trade Ce… https://t.co/PnomVLK7VY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adefran46 @coachlewis1987 @bpalm5 Thanks for all your support this year! We will be back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Belgian White by @BlueMoonBrewCo at @courtyardhotels — https://t.co/SLpC6ZPnIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool. Last year we tried to buy books with deep cultural relevance. Unfortunately we only had enough 💰 to buy about… https://t.co/KaqvWwlNVZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan You know you would come off a lot better if you stood up for America]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamLatina I WANT TO FUCK YOUR PUSSY IN THE USA 🇺🇸! https://t.co/W6zn5MS0Uz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lucy Juicy by @SolaceBrewing @ The Eleanor — https://t.co/OFNMlbpYSD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to stand with Ryerson staff &amp; students today for an announcement made by Ministers @Bill_Morneau and… https://t.co/RUlzXUfj4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cro Crop and Roy Nelson are having a "you can't knock me out" contest. #Bellator216]]></document><document><![CDATA[#craftbeer #beer #ipa #dipa #beer #draftbeer #growlerfill #beerlover #newenglandipa #hazyipa  #stout #porter #hefe… https://t.co/jnE7GqQW5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Michael Cohen’s Explosive Prepared Testimony: I Lied Because Trump ‘Wanted Me To Lie’ 👋 👋 🍊 @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diplomtc_Immnty @educatorsresist @patsajak I don’t think you know what those words actually mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One 💙! ! Impeach Trump &amp; prosecute, now! 😎😄✌️👁️💚💣💥! https://t.co/i8r1Yp1O1Q https://t.co/NPEHzW4Zma]]></document><document><![CDATA[don't rely on yourself https://t.co/lTeVHmeGJD #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/cCE7ul7z8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wakin up in the mornin gotta thank God. I don’t know but today seems a little odd... https://t.co/xZ62NaIvHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Currently...  Pat Connaughton +15 Khris Middleton -11  this is petty and irrational but I’m tweeting it anyway, Go Irish, Go Bucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibbsMshairgrl @LaurenDuski @Spotify Lauren is kinda a really big deal huh Shannon 👍❤️❤️❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foodandwine This product should not contain the words meat or beef anywhere on its packaging or in its promotion, including yours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Coatesville, Pennsylvania https://t.co/qAdQgNlMgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Beverly...in a nutshell.  Entertaining per usual. https://t.co/M9KJGyaVxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monopithecus Jajajaja con sus chistes de tíos que se casaron siendo primos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spoke my mind, and now I realize to make every second count. I just wish I could’ve told myself that before I made… https://t.co/ZiNKqHAQXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The most dangerous part of youth football is the ball and the field.”  Packed house for @CoachTomlin here at Natio… https://t.co/ZyNpNTUaa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished! #joker   #MaJiKartwork #Batman #dccomics #themanwholaughs #drips #watercolor #evil @ Majik's Maddhouse https://t.co/yqxICeJmkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imtheMDP @SethDavisHoops Dude. You are literally taught the exact opposite. From like 1st grade Rec ball onward...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDrPhilShow Her children need to stop condemning Sonya for the past if they want a relationship with her:  "Ther… https://t.co/Nkrrjab1vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Updating @USFVinikMBA Class of ‘19 job placement - with 8 weeks left in the semester 9/24 have accepted full time e… https://t.co/HOET0nhwOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Earthquakes and 💩 Going on rn In Cali and ain’t nobody said nothin !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol @panosofgreece doesn’t fuck around.   “We aren’t firing May? Cool, bring me somebody else. I’m firing somebody today dammit”]]></document></documents></author>