<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JasonCmplxFtrs Sorry, no. We do have a tremendous amount of related material available online via YouTube,… https://t.co/cLj0fMIjS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cleared all notifications from #iPhone, feels so good! #FridayFeeling https://t.co/LPrS6H7hK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going into week 2 of the #NationalEmergency. We're at the border, and I think we're gonna need bigger sticks.… https://t.co/Z71qLcppFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tú crees que alguien se muera de la generación? -Ericka preguntándome a las 8:00 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1st line of this I *swore* was leading into a pitch about the perfect wine...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FibroSloth OMG it can be debilitating.  I feel ya and hang in there.  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffMuteRKelly @rkelly @CNN @MuteRKellyDet @MuteRKellyTampa @MuteRKellySTL @MuteRKellyChi @JimDeRogatis @MeTooMVMT @TIMESUPNOW Disgusting]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random thoughts at 4:00 am and on serious pain meds   1 I should probably not be on Twitter   2: there’s are really… https://t.co/jwqOBEXQxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebeccaNichole @jessica_smarr @Greeninthemiddl @JTReese89 @thesnarkygent @ToriGlass Should’ve told 13 year old gir… https://t.co/AQqiWrK15x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whose arrows are sharp, and all their bows bent, their horses' hoofs shall be counted like flint, and their wheels… https://t.co/qI4t1O75PR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potus is turning his back on American workers. SUPPORTS IMPORTING MILLIONS FOREIGN  workers. Same old CON game, sa… https://t.co/XKkaIhnePI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelcantu it’s okay sweetie you’re doing the best you can we completely understand we all get like that it’s per… https://t.co/kLB6go381C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Board member Bubba McCall - “We can talk about this and talk about this but the mold is not going away.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all really think flirting with boys who have girlfriends is a personality trait huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_IMXpensive lol I know it can’t be and if he fall asleep in bed with me and I don’t feel him I instantly wake up l… https://t.co/QRhcUz4N63]]></document><document><![CDATA[@molratty @Patriot_Musket I think it was the lighting. She looked fine on red carpet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes Lord. Holy Spirit thank You for Your comfort and leading control. Praise Jesus 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trudging through the whole 7.5 hrs of the Michael Cohen hearing and I am astounded about how downplayed all the highlights were]]></document><document><![CDATA[H.342 would guarantee a public defender for anyone accused of a crime in #VT (currently only available for “serious… https://t.co/ug1PHBZNqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArdoOmer My body is terrible and periods are the devil, and I dont even have them as badly as other people do! 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TathamSmith @jbwhite777 @Jay_Rombach @DeathByLipstik @debratankersle1 @gloriajkenyon @gerrinnesmac @geeanem… https://t.co/zRT3nKJJeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another awesome basketball clinic at WHS! Thanks to Coach Wilder and the B-Ball Hawks! Hawks Helping Hawks!@Waltham… https://t.co/pris6U8NQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCharlieRicker @G_Ray34 @DragonMom98 @jimmyreu81 @SabresFunStats @lno09281978 @DownGoesCrown @csm3d @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/j4IVOcskSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never in my life did I think I'd be excited to go home. But 10 days can't go fast enough. I need dogs and the mountians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pubschoolops Nat’l Board Members dedicate their time to so many worthy causes. @cicistheories has been a blessing… https://t.co/fv3sb6t08w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Rep Nadler chairman of the House Judiciary Committee said the panel will be issuing document reque… https://t.co/tOCWEJAmyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felicialovejoy9 Yes! All the best and then some 😊 https://t.co/0oSdi35vwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horrorgal8 @Lbarron30 @pedroasantiago2 @Gretch314 @nyyroro @StanleyLabady shush yo’ mouth girl, you are gorgeous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen Dude, do you feel better yet &amp; what did you eat when you resurfaced?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Technology is best when it brings people together.” Matt Mullenweg . And that it did tonight  @kctechcouncil “no c… https://t.co/DR098fUCT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me Widows with your twists and turns and the rest of  it. I love you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody was shooting outside the movie theater on 87th in the Chatham area late last night😩 wow !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s that girl?  #gypsy @ Philadelphia, Pennsylvania https://t.co/zMeWlCVfWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrisbinMatthew @jemelehill Poof... here’s some sugar. https://t.co/T7SqbL5GgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Record label pimp game 101. 10 year #michaeljacksondeath anniversary. Make something go viral. A documentary. Divid… https://t.co/YGqZgak2cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing a @needtobreathe shirt to a @mumfordandsons show? Yes, because it’s wishful thinking that they’ll work toge… https://t.co/OESZrU6vuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st grade families enjoying the beautiful El Paso sunshine on #WellnessWednesday 💙🐍🧡 #TeamSISD #ShookTranscends… https://t.co/wsI1tIbeCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiring managers should ask applicants what their Hogwarts house is because 1) it helps determine personality fit fo… https://t.co/jEHhqkZyW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best thing I’ve ever said to someone was when they wanted to throw hands and I told them I would pay for their gas to watch them try.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you @DonaldJTrumpJr #loserson and to all standing behind you and clapping #shameonYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t really care for this woman commentator at this gymnastics meet. She’s really negative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sploofeek Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading is way more fun with Finger Lights, especially for a reluctant reader! 📚🔦 #iteachspecialed #thisishowsman https://t.co/LQcds48XC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPhilGoff @dreamhampton @TheRock Set to record the entire docu-series. Congratulations to all involved for bringi… https://t.co/8YpMuowCJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ❤️ how this combo turned out! Color Street. Get you some. #highlandhoundstooth #riored #accentnail #colorstreet… https://t.co/UFru6saktB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even the subway is trying to make spring happen. @ The Oculus at the World Trade Center https://t.co/oc5H1wcWh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheri_lynn95252 @RoverDov123 @Bren_O1967 @DrJimmyStar @greg_dabbs @DavidDiehl20 @KFearri @petergraigs… https://t.co/vix6ewwpB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS AN INDIRECT TWEET TO MY DOG: BITCH WILL YOU COME CUDDLE ME??! LIKE THE FIRST NIGHT YOU SLEPT WITH THE OTHER… https://t.co/P1ajMF2BOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezdoriga Ya no cabe tanto “poder” en su poca inteligencia, y los “intelectuales” chairos que opinan de las pende.... de este drogadicto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassMiass In fact, for a time, a person could direct email him at the University he was at....]]></document><document><![CDATA[S/o to all the ladies who tell me how beautiful I am.... I love y’all 🥰😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jesus_Luvs_Us @roads2 @ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @AnwarManwar004 @MelindaYoe @Jimmysimmonds1 @Peeperpea29… https://t.co/EPFuywmr71]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do we need better mental healthcare in Indiana? Yes, of course; but this is not the route to take. There has to be… https://t.co/c3jTAS4Tfh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise &amp; Grind... ⚾️Happy HS Baseball Season⚾️ WEEK1: Tuesday, 2/26 🦅@ SouthFork 6:00 Friday, 3/1 🦅 vs Vero HOME 3:30 🦅⚾️🦅⚾️🦅⚾️🦅⚾️🦅⚾️🦅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueWalkPoconos RIP Sgt Hinkle you will never be forgotten @FloridaChiefs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird huh? Haha. Yung dating nagdedefend sayo sa nagsasabing pangit ka at bobo ka, yun na mismo yung naiinis sayo d… https://t.co/RpI5m9H3gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@business @realDonaldTrump You’ll NEVER understand a Woman’s reproductive struggles. @PPFA is so much more than jus… https://t.co/Z26MxUU57n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRIANMBENDIS @comiXology I’m interested to see where this goes but I’m a little nervous right now 😅. No spoilers b… https://t.co/tjJsGQXyRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few costumes from "Dumbo" at Sunday's press day. * * * * * #Dumbo #DumboMovie #costumes #TimBurton #PressDay… https://t.co/lfaMfyMF4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait i get to see @MarenMorris next monday &amp; it’s been a minute IM SO EXCITED   pls pls tell me you still play how it’s done???]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna go with my boyfriend and my little puppy 🥺 https://t.co/ERfkUh80Ii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby I said 5 years... He got 47 months. I knew he wouldn't get anywhere near what he should have gotten.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont call me 1-2 days after my birthday to tell me happy birthday if u was on social media the day of. Keep it! I dont want it, fuck u]]></document><document><![CDATA[only thing im excited about tonight is my friend getting sum dick, what has my life come to]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i’m sad i play a shot across the bow by mayday parade excessively loud and scream the lyrics and lemme tell yo… https://t.co/Rn3BcUwtLl]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s doing this thing called “Lent” in which you sacrifice pleasure for no good reason....so he’s stocking up on su… https://t.co/ikj1JuiM40]]></document><document><![CDATA[is isaiah rashad THAT good or is the production on The Suns Tirade THAT good?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @IvanDuque Glad to see someone step in and take on the presidential role in the absolute void of the current occupant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabriceMowbray Yikes! Strong words for APA. I’ve grown up using it. Love it unless the journal counts references in word count! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@St3v3Harv3ysBad @QuarkCyber @aidachavez @rtraister @sunrisemvmt Oh so they were trying to convince Feinstein to se… https://t.co/bCsUNTuPPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG the sounds of the night that go soundless to ya if asleep 💤, #insomnia definitely not silent, what the fudge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roxie32819 Yep, another reason why I’ll never visit New York! The Bad Guys are in Control! That includes DeBlasio, Cuomo, and the rest! 🤮🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday from #candctitle ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️ #valentinesday2019🌹♥️ #friendshipday @ C &amp; C TITLE AGENCY, INC. https://t.co/qln4rnZhmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am grateful for my health, both physical and mental. February is always a difficult month for my friends and fami… https://t.co/cdNhWt8czc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynda3035 @Tosca3333 @Marina935home @MissytheB @Axolotl_2019 @2kewlabs @sandyincanada @Lpowell588Lady @jypseywheel… https://t.co/oGprqKNvKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itssuzann @ibrake4ants @carolecadwalla It is scary..it is..it  just is so scary.. we have had a front row seat abo… https://t.co/aCeRnuQjlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve said it once. DONT FUCK WITH ME. SCREW ME OVER AND ILL DO YOU 10X WORSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooo we got our tax return today and this was his way of telling me 😂😂😂 https://t.co/YNK3oqKIWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lil_Shump Directly proportional to the amount &amp; quality of the 💩talk😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[mmmk so vans always land facing up &amp; pineapple is peelable ...  what’s next? is trump impeached]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making pour decisions 🍷 #winetasting #vino #stonetowerwinery #petitverdot  #virginiawineries @ Stone Tower Winery https://t.co/k5I3xNVbmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewCotz Saw you on @CP24 this am! Good advice to keep home and get a new renter! Nice to see you doing well. Kudos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want thiiiiiiis so much. My trail pack bounces way too much.  https://t.co/WlGUQ1JyhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Don @realDonaldTrump hurry home. You’re missing all the fun. #CohenCongressionalHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Respectfully Sir -didn't you take an oath to protect our country and constitution or are you now joining… https://t.co/lBC4FYaWfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In life, it’s not where you go, it’s who you travel with.” -Charles Schulz (Thank you for the best birthday advent… https://t.co/b0h2ATpuL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamfindingfaith I pray that you touch at least one soul today! God bless you and this occasion!  Let His will be done! I’m with in love!🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[7. Ensure your kids spend time with their disabled peers and disabled adults. Combine this with respite and camps.… https://t.co/j5b6Xa9v5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamecockWBB WE GOOD, PLAY OUR GAME! PRESSURE DEFENSE! WATCH THE SCREENS, BOXOUT,REBOUND! LETS GO GAMECOCKS!! #OWNIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Lorena Bobbie and hot damn. I get it tho girl... but you crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pendeja. Just because you’re a girl doesn’t mean you can do whatever the hell you want to a guy without consequence… https://t.co/JIlqBV4KFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeDunman @loreestark Like @MaryLouMarzian put in her amendment, they are the tax payer funding of the @ACLUofKY  #kyga19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasiebrickkkk girl i’m screaming it’s all i’ve been listening to lmfaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brett’s ex is literally so crazy SHE JUST WRECKED HER CAR ON PURPOSE SO HE’D STOP HELPING ME 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me on March 1st: “Don’t get too excited. Play it cool. It’s still #Winter in #Buffalo.” Also me on March 1st: https://t.co/P3kseiqtky]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Brooklyn Diner in New York, NY w/ @cdemers80 https://t.co/wOw3h1Ob6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love my business partners! #CollectiveTeam #SXSW @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/PwlWji0GNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all I thought it was safe to twerk on @ExtremeBeauty and she literally tried to get in my pants ..... IN THE CLUB... I’m scared.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sounds like you know you are in deep shit now.  GOOD.  You are a DISGRACE to the presidency and an… https://t.co/v2eostVRnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TIFF_NET @Criterion And against Paul Newman for Hud! Wow! Love Sidney Poitier!!!]]></document></documents></author>