<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Beautiful winter views today at the Covered Bridge.  . . #nature #naturephotography #landscapephotography… https://t.co/IPBVSz8T8p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaisaNauska Hey how are you?! I ran across yoir article https://t.co/4owCdcR60s It was very interesting. I wanted… https://t.co/UWpQazbW5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve got a lot of problems in my life, but at least I don’t have Verizon right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mannn let me be a lover boy in peace wth is wrong witchyall. Let me love a girl a million miles away since there ai… https://t.co/n6Q2l7A7Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gg_is_ambitious What’s Kamalas plan? Or Warrens? ... exactly https://t.co/Hszs4sFrHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Itll come brother. You’re extremely talented and have all the intangibles. Top #JUCO punter 4.5⭐️ AVAILABLE NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Park Lane Station (DART Rail) - @dartmedia in Dallas, TX https://t.co/uPfXNDLySJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and @Cuppatan made a matcha mille crepe cake hell yeah https://t.co/iughuwcciI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typically i dont believe in the death penalty, unless they have a history of ordering pizza with mushrooms and/or olives on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xMelCole @NICKIMINAJ i just got my passport let me know what’s guddddddd]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's definitely something going on today! #WeAreHilton #100BestCos https://t.co/YD0Irg57K8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeOgno @charliekirk11 Really?  How would you react with bold face lies being told about you? Dr. Ford essentially… https://t.co/af1kTNAHo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think people can’t walk down to the border and see with their own eyes that this is a bunch of horse shit? T… https://t.co/9tdIa31Qzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLFlames  Hey Flames, my wife and I are warming up NYC for you, ready to watch win 6 and 7 in a row!! https://t.co/YPuEhKCoGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight Live In Concert 8pm In Downtown Norfolk! https://t.co/VNFFATDkgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's your job as the coach to get your players up for teams with a losing record. If you lose then that loss is totally on you! Period.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You can't stop the future You can't rewind the past The only way to learn the secret ...is to press play.” #facts… https://t.co/73tXjv5iN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Malcnificent If I could I would blow a couple thousand in there easily in one trip.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briangv92 Que imbecil ... como a usted no lo violaron verdad? O a alguno de sus hijos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black people couldn't vote until 1964. Jim Crow laws were enforced until 1965. Racial inequality/police brutality a… https://t.co/iOJJYz0wAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/mAEVPKtPxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JushiPutin @AOC @RashidaTlaib The irony of deflection from Rashida the actual racist! The hypocrisy of liberals kn… https://t.co/VVIO00khSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Marketing is the generous act of helping others become who they seek to become. It involves creating honest storie… https://t.co/NkQ6eIe63t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraUnderwood You look amazing in the outfit s you https://t.co/fLOeRE1Wpf are very beautiful Sarah😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasTechMBB and @KStateMBB tied atop @Big12Conference. Both play tonight. If one wins and one loses, team that wi… https://t.co/1N9IJJBtRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahh Boston Your My Home! Can you name this neighborhood in Boston? #boston #newengland https://t.co/seJr70zkGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheComradeVideo @StazJohnson @amandadeibert @Jezebel Pair with Gucci bandolier pouches and DKNY spiky shoulder pad… https://t.co/R1uAMTDtLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pledge to remind the @NRA #NRAPoliticians everyday that they are putting $ over lives We shoulda stop it after Co… https://t.co/ajfKe69AiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aerial drone images of an Ocean  view condo in the Ocean Towers building across from Palisades Park in  Santa Monic… https://t.co/v8vPTxoQCZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @GTSFarmer @realDonaldTrump Although I am happy for you and George,  I am saddened that it could not… https://t.co/kupPJ60Dn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinLand18 @realDonaldTrump This doesn’t address anything medical and certainly doesn’t “destroy abortions” all… https://t.co/NohWOnO19k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katywinge Roses are red Violets are blue Nuggets are good Disagree &amp; I’ll fight you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very sad to hear that famous NASCAR painter, Sam Bass passed away this morning. I’ve personally been to his shop in… https://t.co/a9Qqbvzi95]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poem, “At Prospect Cottage,” dedicated to the late, great filmmaker and writer Derek Jarman, will appear in the… https://t.co/5TL7hqroO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/FNinBvt7e1]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF, Guys. It’s fricking Day Light Savings tomorrow. I’m going to lose an hour of sleep. FML.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Henry #Purcell - March / Music for the Funeral of #QueenMary (Funeral Sentences) Z. 860 https://t.co/yhyvRmaUX6 #RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crazy Quotes and Sayings | Daily selection of quotes. Smart, stupid, funny, love, friendship, etc ...... https://t.co/e0iliGw59L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RapSheet Fuck you Ian this is why everyone likes schefter better. Find a different job dipshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmilam94 I don’t think there are enough tow trucks in so cal to inforce this. Plus irvine would face a lot of law suits over this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4 I have accepted the challenge from @SCMPriest to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews-ju… https://t.co/f8kDSRqsUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstTake Nick was always the best choice as QB for the eagles. He proved his worth too bad the front office can't… https://t.co/xIHT7255Sq]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you define courage... ?  Many people think it is in the grand gestures and the major acts.  However, courage… https://t.co/14svSxZvEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xpaladoshiss @katalin_pota @scapelliti @jamezdhawaii @KermitHigby @GallivanScott @jackhammer3853 @adirado29… https://t.co/RGpukOrpbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The left is always saying Trump lies. They see lies differently than normal ppl. If TRUMP says ppl shd stand for th… https://t.co/407nw5d4Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attending #SXSW? Heard about #Montreal and its #AI ecosystem + curious to learn more? Come see us this pm, for Queb… https://t.co/W2QyjY0UO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was called “wifey” today, so I sent a pic of my ringless hand... this nigga had the nerve to cash app me money fo… https://t.co/V4FaPiBRpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[-First chase was early 90’s with my bike on Mt Sequoyah in Fayetteville, AR.  -First chase with tornado: 10-4-98 in… https://t.co/NmCyM1bYoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind He's encouraging the summary execution of drug dealers, justiceless rejection of asylum seekers, busti… https://t.co/0Gv62W8xFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats STILL Don't Get It: Neoliberalism Created Trump https://t.co/2wjsoQgHqa via @BernieSanders @justicedems… https://t.co/KaKf94ITNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ignoring that he’s been caught lying once already and is already going to jail. What reason would he have to lie no… https://t.co/umG6KtXmut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kmhairston @chvrlesjr I don’t see how that can be an accurate statement]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonederoJC @La_SER @MonederoJC Eres una basura humana, igual o peor que todos los que conforman la dictadura venezolana.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peaceloveguns @a_nice_frog Nothing feels as good as the things you build]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattyRenn Put a note on car “Nice parking job Asshat. Thank you for your service.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who was that French reporter at the #AlsMTL presser? .. whoever it was ..  @joeyalfieri https://t.co/6BF99uTFVU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sean_colgan_ @jake_menders You’ll be missing out on all my great #content just like Stroman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GZSports_ZM Think they'll get a comp pick when Bell signs elsewhere this year or will it be next year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DARIII__ “whew Chile that’s enough time for me to have lance the way ima want him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsYorgi @ReneeCarrollAZ @TwitterSupport @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @SenTedCruz @DevinNunes @DonaldJTrumpJr… https://t.co/oTmNNcVBZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's hoiit Auiehl fishy fishing pork rinds Puiehlf pork rinds uiehl dramas judo chop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OompaVB @DesignationSix @FoxNews @GothamSteel @McDonalds @Arbys @PetSmart @Chewy @facebook @UniversalPics @Disney… https://t.co/cmX56jkP9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just given a talk to @fastpr_book to these fine people https://t.co/Gq24dK8W8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rabidrabbit56 @woo_furs There is a Netflix documentary about that chicken and how there is no Chinese origin at all]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today would be a REALLY good day for Botterill to get Skinner’s signature on a contract extension.  #Sabres #Bills #INeedABeerAlready]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my tendy, I will NEVER LET ANYONE TOUCH YOU. 🔒⬇️ @dunnyhockey https://t.co/Dm1I5XihwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[if the Beto campaign jingle isn’t a rewritten version of Lido by Boz Scaggs he should just stay home]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sen. Zaun announces the committee will take up SF213 - guns in employer parking lots - tomorrow, not today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FabulousFeder @shudder Yay! So glad you liked it! Thanks for spreading the #VideoPalacePod love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Violet_Monroe damn... guess i'll just have to wait for Exxxotica FL &amp; NJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spain - @iBrentCharles w/ @swankydougemery (Piano), @Donthagreat (Drums), Senegal Apostolo (Bass)  22nd Annual Me… https://t.co/qN811CWHLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost As much as I dislike Bill di Blah Blah. No one knew in 1996 what a scumbag Kelly was. From a staunch conser… https://t.co/lUGg15Mf5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunningFoolMan When I talk to my players. I always talk about being thankful for the opportunity to play travel so… https://t.co/mBdtB2WVyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP See??!!! He didn't wash his hands. Pussy-grabbing or Putin's  Pecker...don't shake his hand!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOSHALLENLOVER @dave_mathews1 You sure he’s not just doing it because people have such an issue with his joking about it???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back n Biceps (@ Georgia Fitness Acworth in Acworth, GA) https://t.co/aNHbFTqzS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn @marcorubio // tired of @POTUS having to fight Republicans to provide security on Southern border for Americans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All y'all need to give this a listen! — ♫Ain't I'm a Dog by Ronnie Self, from #SoundHound https://t.co/fXzvBMLDv0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sprite @callmerashmi @ and me too can’t forget about og lama @ObiE_Iyoha  that would be dope to see #lemontree]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungStallion_ That’s crazy!! You have stuff uploaded and have gotten paid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when will this go on TV? Anytime soon? ⚡️ “16 states file lawsuit challenging Trump’s emergency declaration”  https://t.co/vyQZ2qt8Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissy_linfoot @tinymanatee @millibeeeee @spinsewz @jordandepauww 29???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy she is with him. I notice a badge on her chest, it’s a picture of a Korean man. I ask her about it and she te… https://t.co/X6E2MCCnY5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news for all conservatives who are being shut down by the liberals with violence for just speaking out Nichol… https://t.co/hH3mrn0J5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Grant Williams for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/Ap0utlH0UE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrump SAD THE PEOPLE BELIEVE DEMS THE HATE THE MSM HAVE TO BRAIN WASH PEOPLE ON WEAK PEOPLE  AND THE ONES WHO LIVE IN THE BASEMENT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fmlykath @DadoftheDecade @dmag1127 @Alyssa_Milano Kat, you're trippin on something. He wasn't supporting Trump fro… https://t.co/2v6JyjWwyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancybaym A senior colleague in a different department approached a colleague and myself in the student union on c… https://t.co/r3KHUDYsrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity He also lied to FBI and leaked ! When is he going to raided at 5am with swat teams and amphibious equi… https://t.co/lLLKmGGtrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @holochronicles It's  being reported all over social media that #StarWars  #EpisodeIX  teaser/trailer will  be… https://t.co/tFwffBWaIH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMSurDeFlorida @marcoasensio10 @AFCAjax @realmadrid Gol en la tierra donde nació su fallecida madre. Bravo Marco A… https://t.co/whOUWTFrWw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjeffreyross @RealGilbert Damn, that’s a couple of handsome fellas ..... ahahahahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nollie 180 Switch Crook to Regs!  @cheapthrills13 bringing that heat to the street!  #oSnapMedia #ThePhotoSniper… https://t.co/PAad5xfKaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCBirdBall Thanks BC for coming to JState and playing baseball against us. I hope y’all enjoyed your stay and expe… https://t.co/Hff70lPK0T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeredithBarack vs herself in #dreamselfboxingmatch🥊 #dingding🔔 #fight👊 #knockurselfout #youwin xoxo #wceveryyear💗 gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghstbabey I bet, but really loving the new handle. Are you gonna change your insta too?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Nice try.  Watch the entire last few minutes of the show.  @billmaher was actually talking about th… https://t.co/UmZpRya7ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Riverdale students - the theme for tonight's boys basketball tournament game needs changed please. The guys certain… https://t.co/V8Z8dABGhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgbgolf1 @realDonaldTrump Yeo Trump derangement syndrome is real and being used as a teaching aid for Psychology.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomO5Tiff @Shamusroan13 @SMaxwellStory @sweatsntopknots @DadFiction @gentlemanvet67 @MrsTyler78 @jdstalnaked… https://t.co/Aff7JdDLBy]]></document></documents></author>