<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HAStarsRead1 @shallweteach3 @KDGhoustonAP @MsRiveraEla @Menard_2016 @MargauxTeaches Tracy, what’s on that poster in the background???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish I would care as much as I used to but you took that away from me]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a generation rising who are more hungry for the things of God then the previous. They're going to offend ma… https://t.co/ron0cTRjuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Vikings Got Lucky and Hit Greenland During a Warm Spell: @atlasobscura https://t.co/YbMF7ET1FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will NEVER stress myself over a guy .. do right by me or forever mf wish you did, at the end of the day whose taking an L ... not me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, last night: Gawd I cannot wait to sleep in tomorrow morning.   My brain, 4am this morning: I wonder what the la… https://t.co/eM8jF84VpC]]></document><document><![CDATA[【買付4日目 ニューメキシコ州ギャラップ】 今日の天気は晴れ。 雪がかなり溶けて行動しやすくなりました！ 買い付けは順調すぎて怖いくらい。 https://t.co/FwUWIYweEH https://t.co/KsWeUeqrmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥Taca fogo, taca fogo. Fênix não morre, seu bobo..." (Thai Flow) ⚠️Saiu o videoclipe do ano, com as minas mais brab… https://t.co/i1MDv2x9VE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Of course you do, because you're a compromised twat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[😢This Spotify app update is gonna drive premium subscribers like me off the platform for real ...I’m very sad becau… https://t.co/tTNyGs6Yqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_anaacabrera19 @byanneyt1 @abigailaranda_ Oh no that’s not even foundation. That’s oil on her face 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es verdad que lo novios norteños te llevan tacos a la oficina a la hora que sea? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my first love 🤩 @justinbieber https://t.co/OGcv35uabQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GriffinOrch @GriffinMSGators Congratulations!  We love our Griffin Gator Orchestra @CorbellElem! 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick shout out to the girl in the bathroom that helped me while I threw up, you was on acid and still helped. You… https://t.co/cUMoZeqD2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[This eagle drama is too much for me to handle. Someone make a soap opera]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyyoshin @MichaelaOkla Crazy ex girlfriend it's an amazing show, first three seasons are on Netflix, go watch it now please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this #worldbookday I’m celebrating my NYT bestselling author and twin @TonyaHurley as she hands in her 10th book… https://t.co/K5P2A0QgtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wear your mega hats ,shirts ect. Then when hate shows itself let it, any assaulted, file law suits break them for good no need for abuse,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jiveDurkey I love that his personal time is leaking out.  Our paid employee is doing a terrible job and it's being… https://t.co/IaCBgUYnND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuapBoston1 @7Craighead NOT ME I AM A TRUE BOOM CONFETTI JOHNSON  FAN BABY]]></document><document><![CDATA[well they finally stopped selling mango Juul pods in the stores, so im gonna quit now. ive been wanting to quit for… https://t.co/YgQ7CchY5g]]></document><document><![CDATA[But then there’s the overlap, including people who are on both sides lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msjolene Amen. We doubled the time other pro leagues have survived. When do we pass “survive” and reach “thrive”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your girl calls you on her 10 minute break to tell you, “My panties are on inside out..” from the night before… https://t.co/nqnbEHJsdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan @AymanM @theintercept @IlhanMN U have it backward! Jews are the ones being gaslighted. Yes, I know GOP… https://t.co/60sNajqZd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never forget: this diagram in my International Relations textbook showing how the U.S. makes foreign policy https://t.co/iVIH28B6G1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stwissmann Also the spaying and killing a few days later is horrendous and elected officials have to stop this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making a birthday cake for my oldest! I think she'll be so excited! https://t.co/gLCiFhmc78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Becca’s has had really shitty day followed by an even worse night. Ready for tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi Thank you Nancy Pelosi for representing the USA and speaking for our country.  President Pelosi!  Un… https://t.co/5rCRU2M3qJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So you’re not idle!!! Jumping in shower!!! Work time!!! Have a beautiful day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all better stop posting videos of other people’s car and pretending that it’s yours, wyd if someone ask you to pull up ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a first time for everything - push up contest at lunch between your principal and an 8th grader. 😂They were… https://t.co/04d8SAcVBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[A classic story on stage this night at New Amsterdam Theatre. Wonderful! en Aladdin - The Musical https://t.co/GCI7Lnhgnn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thousands of teachers, students and supporters marched in Annapolis, MD to demand more funding for schools. https://t.co/px0mxaPBp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sor_Patrocinio @SuiteDelResort @javierurdiales 🙏🏼por todos ellos y por Fatima de 16 años embarazada y con 2 intent… https://t.co/YmCPCVIOnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AU4thGen @dalton_sullivan This is my first day off in 2 months. I am a tax preparer. I rarely have time to look at… https://t.co/UMBIiCfV0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Escape room meets scavenger hunt.  Here’s your chance to join a private hunt.  Contact me to register.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is Pompeo? Or Bolton? What is wrong with him!  He IS A DANGER TO OUR COUNTRY! Aren't people worried about the… https://t.co/mmrbAbXUJk]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; i’m going to break me a million hearts. I'm hell on heels, baby I'm comin' for you 🥃 https://t.co/HpznJIWntr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rfragan @ffoxxface @ProudResister @Alyssa_Milano @realDonaldTrump Oh, but I am going to define you. In writing and… https://t.co/jrLST7wE6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stopthistrain28 yeahhh, i also do have a soft spot for kinsler. friendly wager then? will they win over 85 games this season?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work screening. #captainmarvel #workperk @brielarson #internationalwomensday #girlpower @ Walt Disney Studios https://t.co/WjleBksn1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ruben and I move in together in a few short weeks and I can’t wait to start this new chapter in life with him. 😭💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenho uma notícia pra contar...  A primavera chegou 🌷Spring 🌹 Hoje começou o "Daylight Saving Time", horário de ver… https://t.co/XmGqwLq7U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overtime @mcclendon_jamel @LeVelleMoton @Complex I’m sorry my ovaries just blew up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this cover- can’t wat for the next book in this series- amazing books!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somethings cannot be discovered in a rush, give yourself permission to ruminate when needed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. 🙌🏼   Nobody who has achieved more than you will judge you. Nobody who has run a marathon will judge you for th… https://t.co/BVBZ6V8fY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt HE SO BIG😫😫😫😫😫💖💕💖💕💖💖💖💖💕 LOOK AT HIM BEING A GOOD BOY AND LISTENING TO DADDY💖💕✨ https://t.co/ypcJYp2hZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to the bus drivers who tell off the passengers that are too oblivious to move for the person with the stro… https://t.co/BTL8dnHhWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning!!! I’m filling in for @Fox5Kaitlyn this morning on @GoodDayAtlanta! She will be back tomorrow :) Join… https://t.co/8cXssaQFvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[we love furiously checking our emails to see if the fursuit maker we wanna commission has responed to our quite form]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes life gives you lemons so you drive 20 hrs to ride dirt bikes https://t.co/3wjrwhelB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XKatieLynn1230X Love when you post pics of the dogs.  Always a mood booster]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiecouric @AmericanCancer Something to look forward to on my birthday this year....🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that this feels like it was just yesterday...? #sophomore #jeannie #hamstercagephotobomb https://t.co/W0P27enPsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#restorationhardware #rooftop #girlsnight @ RH Rooftop Restaurant https://t.co/E2fg0JCTN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The rigged and corrupt President is the enemy of the people]]></document><document><![CDATA[dirty dishes, stretch marks and broken hearts make you HUMAN not a burden on humanity! 😱 Yes #Woman you are phenome… https://t.co/KOnzS1bdb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewzimmern Being a hotelier I come home from work in the early evening. on Saturdays.....What’s my guilty pleas… https://t.co/fa8gX1oFh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top Telehealth implementation development in USA call us at +18444455767 or visit our website:… https://t.co/dNXZ1abV0q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jason_w21 but when a girl says she doesn’t want you because you’re white... racist ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t have the heart to tell him it’s like he sense that he is gone it makes me sad every time I play this song]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONLY 3 SHARES:( CORNELIUS WILL DIE without shares/pledges and no rescue or a furever family will come for him! Plea… https://t.co/7da0IwXdiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sunshine and blue skies, tailor-made for a walk in the Arboretum. #crocuses #youmustbelieveinspring… https://t.co/fR5YgUsgfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited for you @Rodney_Wedig I knew you weren’t done yet!!! #foreveracoach]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest Rome, GA Education/Training job opportunity and click the link in our bio to apply: Substitute Teach… https://t.co/jg1vhYlNrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Utahn named Joe Dye spent a beautiful evening skating on Jordanelle Reservoir. @UtahStateParks #skating #sunset… https://t.co/zfCgVz5Ktq]]></document><document><![CDATA[my nails atm are very short/unpainted but that whole “way to her heart is boba, has a very very messy car, is broke… https://t.co/afjDFN8ztZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday Face ❤😍 #BirthdayGirl #PiscesGang #30Club 😘 https://t.co/AJJkGDBoTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NstyWmnWendy @Tam_Resist @mydoggyruss @CindisPLace @mom_ceo_dj @Vickivbreezy @Kewlbearhelloki @CIAnderson3… https://t.co/F5tpvV5NRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suns SIGN @kellyoubrejr THIS MAN NOW!!!! @ Talking Stick Resort Arena https://t.co/g99oGezVVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Hillary Clinton just get out of politics already? Like damn, no one likes you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We ready to go 😈 #hotones #firstwefeast #hotoneschallenge @Heatonist @firstwefeast @seanseaevans @MikeyMicMike… https://t.co/EylBlwtbBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McGeeSmith @CiscoCollab @aruna13 @_amychang Thank you for celebrating with us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never fails- if I go to the ER wearing pajamas and ready to be there, they turn me around quick. But this time I… https://t.co/n0SboFfCMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[texting a suicide hotline what’s everyone else doing with their Saturday night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeez. What does it take to fix InShape hot tub Monterey?  Salinas InShape hot tub dirty today. Swimming pool is ver… https://t.co/N8My0jSycg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiet. Beautiful. Musician. Talented. Greek. Humanitarian. Missed. George Michael. @georgemofficial #BMyValentine… https://t.co/s6KV17zJEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[7AM, only on #YourMorningAlbany: Shaker High School Student @maddyvandenburg talks to us ahead of her big… https://t.co/YRnEjKvSxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the Sea Wheeze Half Marathon single-entry lottery. This is my first time entering any race lottery, ever.… https://t.co/PL6seBPccb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oureric Eric Thomas, cafe vigilante of justice.  10/10 would watch this series]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half of my heart is in (Little) Havana, ooh-na-na 🇨🇺 #mendesmeanderings @ Little Havana https://t.co/RpOojoaL3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnimeLives @AOC WTF did you read max??? If you call her response "bitching" then I will assume you are a "pig."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry....but do we have the money for this....asking for a homeless friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Exactly.  Why should we pay for our education,  learn And master a skill, continue our education and w… https://t.co/YkrkY3KSVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So is there a particular birthday one celebrates that transitions men from progressive into #StephenHarperApologist… https://t.co/K6k4cZ2n2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @SassyCassyCat @BloomNight2 @sharon_cantley @deborah26449389… https://t.co/8xX4E6FQxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because @mariettacollege gave so much to me during my time there. The education, the activities, the memories and e… https://t.co/l9Z1yu9wZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life tip: any white dude who uses “fucker” in regular conversation is usually pretty cool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CD_hbic @Roman_Forbes @laurastar001 Live. Breath. Gas Yung on Social Media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2goalie02 I agree! Think about people who do this to their baby while pregnant!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar @RepAdamSchiff Why can't they indict him for lying to the public or false advertising or something.  Aren'… https://t.co/yhsqt3TDGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Solanges new album.  I am also deeper than the average bear and smarter too🤷🏾‍♀️🤷🏾‍♀️🤷🏾‍♀️🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Belle_Vivant @urbanx_f @KrochetxKorner @Just4TheCause @Awithonelison @MacUmbridge @bcbiochemist @mc40_e @iXeno… https://t.co/pWVRHaYa6a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio You are the biggest thief in NYS, besides Cuomo!  Take your slum apartments that haven't had heat mos… https://t.co/oDoWox0j7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[kinda sucks i’m doing an unpaid internship but also is kinda cool that I don’t have to commit too many hours compar… https://t.co/BP7ax1WotX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought that something that was very hard to obtain would be worth it, but it just fucked me up instead.]]></document></documents></author>