<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We all know one thing that is going to change in 2020. You will be gone]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opening Night Party for @AJewishJokePlay  Off Broadway @TheatreRowNYC  The Creators @marnifreedy @PhillieJJ and Dav… https://t.co/ehxzE3OBXt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked about @realDonaldTrump  she says “we’ve got to talk about our ideas.” She says talking about Trump is a “rabbit hole.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@typical_sdot @BrooklynBrigade NBA store custom shop. Unfortunately they don’t sell a D’Angelo shirt straight up. You have to customize it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of Pima's starters (all in double figures) now on the bench with 3 minutes left. Pima on its way again to the N… https://t.co/yzrKsc7PeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to apologize in advance to everyone at SLC airport. My @Delta flight is delayed and I will apparently have… https://t.co/oDd1RwJjHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humanitarian Award at @MaxwellFootball Club to Zach Ertz of Philadelphia @Eagles https://t.co/d1euGAkQ9M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenho @chokoleitWiTS Gosh! That cheers is not for Chokoleit. I deeply symphatize his passing. With his physic… https://t.co/ZX4RCZl7TB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So if you like fitness, eating healthy, going outside, relaxing indoors and watching movies, doesn’t care about dri… https://t.co/M76BmL3kcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAGreyhound @CocoaBeachFL I can’t wait to go back! I was there in early December. Still going through my camera ph… https://t.co/G7Caw9QXTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art inspired by #DitaVonTeese &amp; #SebastienTellier  #rendezvous https://t.co/qVmvkaHoEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[95% OF POLITICIANS ARE CROOKED LYING CHEATING LAWYERS NEVER TO BE TRUSTED. THATS A FACT. @POTUS IS NOT A LAWYER BES… https://t.co/D5ahqFG9gy]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Tj6VRCmtyV @G_Hannelius yeah i know u love me thats y im gonna fuck u one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swim night! .............................. #professionalsuccess #triathlon #running #fitness #swimbikerun #cycling… https://t.co/sePFMYCr30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heroichollywood I could only stomach Jessica Jones for a few minutes.🤷🏻‍♂️👎🏻🤢🤮 The Punisher was punishing.🥴👎🏻🤢🤮💸… https://t.co/UViFei1UGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please explain why Florida, Auburn and Oregon are top 10 material but Ohio state isn’t ? And let’s not forget about… https://t.co/e2aanxNqr3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcampbell001 @PAlterBoy1 @puntanenyahoo @DieterFrikadell @SteveSGoddard @StormSignalSA @jonsaxon67 @hjearl1… https://t.co/rhkGh1CALd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daddy loves when I have 2 or more nuts in me!!! What’s a quickie?!? 🙂🙃😋😏😏 now I can go to sleep #BENEDICTIONDICK https://t.co/vOEFnhNAEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonoastiazaran @lopezobrador_ I-M-P-R-E-S-I-O-N-A-N-T-E la diferencia entre el antes y el después... y ahí viene e… https://t.co/s3tRWqERD5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #gratitude #tentoesdown👣 @ Pear Orchard, Beaumont https://t.co/5GMEQKksnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's National chili day! Where can I get a good bowl of chili? https://t.co/b2Y2qWiWFB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You just gotta euthanize it, chain-of-custody tag it, and stick it in the freezer” is a phrase I just heard.  Turn… https://t.co/7gxyiMO9Yw]]></document><document><![CDATA[When did we start caring what cair thinks. They have ties to terrorist organizations. Why should they even be allow… https://t.co/A4ouss3DlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFowlerESPN @TheSteelCrew @AdamSchefter They had to get rid of this guy and in the end its theae guys that have to… https://t.co/aUfI9DXuAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The caravan is being still again. SEE youTube  @Texas !  @FoxNews Lorrado border crossing is now being breached.… https://t.co/IzxmHrSAq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had some great conversations today with my PAs and I’m just extremely grateful to have even crossed paths with th… https://t.co/e3WAjZcDCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @AnnCoulter Does this woman understand the meaning of the word,the reference? If you want a honest d… https://t.co/wgQQfC2AeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s official, St. Louis is being abducted by aliens. https://t.co/UZQjeLfmXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU. NEVER.. SERVED. A. SINGLE. DAY. YOURSELF...YOU DRAFT DODGING DOTARD!!!  #CadetBoneSpurs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LBisaillon @AnnCoulter No it's not the point. The point is hes not and you think he got treated unfairly, when in… https://t.co/HgqDbL7FRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSchettig @PlayoffDangelo @MrSuccsessful97 @The6th_Espada50 @MustBeTheMoney2 @RealSkipBayless Be more fun, please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Green by @TreeHouseBrewCo at @BottleRevApex — https://t.co/NVBVvVTuyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[good morning‼️☕️☕️☕️ it’s 76°F/24°C #TwoForTuesday! #ZakarTwins! #PublishedWithoutPermission… https://t.co/ezQNg1067I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GumbyJohnson @FieldYates They dropped TJ Jones if that's what you're thinking of]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen There are few things more amazing and memorable. Orgasms come and go. This shit sticks w ya in the feels. The right kinda way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too bad the Boys can’t stay off the Weed &amp; need to bring back a retread TE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It only makes sense for Miami to have another star named Dwayne, upon Wade's last season coming to an end. #HaskinstoMiami]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are being beckoned to produce the fruit of repentance in our lives. We are being led to consider the suffering o… https://t.co/HcmD88xepv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KWCHMMurray When my grandson slid off the road into the ditch due to black ice there was no body damage.  However… https://t.co/CVtWOwbhLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohhaidavis Whoa.   That’s like giving up booze for lent, and even that is only 40 days....  Can I finish what I am reading?]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's an urgent need for class diversity in the judiciary in addition to race and gender diversity. Getting all s… https://t.co/zE4tISuCit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Armand0Ramirez Your lying 🤥, we literally have had plans with the crew smh #cloutchaser]]></document><document><![CDATA[You see a shell, two chevrons and two x’s.   They see a sun rising between 2 mountain ranges, two boxes stacked on… https://t.co/xCxQQpVlJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelle_furlow @dworakt Thanks Michelle! It’s all in God’s timing. I’m extremely grateful for the agencies and tr… https://t.co/FaHz79PSmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All guns on the ground in #Blackout should be empty. Its BS when you drop next to someone and they pick up a gun an… https://t.co/DYi0wZk8QY]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fun few weeks of events are coming up, kicking it off tonight with our 2nd Annual Ping Pong Tournament + tap take… https://t.co/39zdUuFPez]]></document><document><![CDATA[My DMs are ONLY for BUSINESS! So stop asking me how to get in Porn thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep waking up at 3 am super hungry. I'm craving grilled cheese and quesadillas 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunnflores I haven’t watched S2 but it wouldn’t hurt to try? I’m loving S3. Can’t wait for Sunday night’s finale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pppapin Yeah it's been especially high-impact here. I suppose what stands out with this particular case is the glo… https://t.co/oGDvvPYD88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NealRoss @BostonIrish2018 @bartola721 @SarahHuckabee @SteveGuest Robert Francis did not have 10k.  Trump probably… https://t.co/bVJQ8vsc9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livefromhereapm @LordHuron @amandapalmer @MichiganRadio @DetOperaHouse I will admit to not have listened to the sh… https://t.co/HfOB1SDm7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised given the ads I’ve gotten from him in the past few weeks.   He should be running for Senate. Ugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 Samuel 18: Saul gets weirder and droos on the evil side. David gets a friend in Jonathan and a wife in Michal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the Marie Kondo-ing going on, is it a good time to go thrift shopping, you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethaninreallife @Zazz13 @dukefan9207 Sources close to him say he bikes 25 miles every morning before breakfast and… https://t.co/dcRYrxoJMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekChadMelnyk @MikePasq @KOB76 @Tiddy2Bang2 @t_gale21 @CamStrong53 @Buster_ESPN I’m saying people from those par… https://t.co/EbuqE9Ps59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_UnaSonrisa_17 Muchas gracias e igualmente deseo que lo sea para ti ,!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah - you should know something about lying, Pinocchio. You’re never going to get to be a real boy...  #PresidentPinocchio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chipper311 @311 @pnut @NickHexum I may have read the same article but was hoping to get confirmation in hopes the… https://t.co/1xK7v6hh76]]></document><document><![CDATA[He HAS had sex with more women, or moved on them like a bitch, than most Presidents—you must admit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. That's really good. - Drinking a Beer Geek Breakfast by @MikkellerBeer/@MikkellerBeer @ Jinya Ramen Bar  — https://t.co/mVyNarZKkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then what's the point in having a police department?! Some of these judges needs to go! Take away lifetime appointments.......NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[day 1 after having my nose cauterized: every time i sneeze, i fear for my life....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poquito de la session de hoy... @ Goleta, California https://t.co/bTBVDV5tmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyJongFast Get out quick, before you’re mistaken for the other inmates and committed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC The media and the Democrats need to stop blaming trump for all the violence they’re the ones causing it !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESbeINSPORTS viendo Madrid vs Girona desde Richmond VA @JoseHDonGoL @Jaimefmacias saludos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who can play #LadyMacbeth and WWE wrestler Paige (that would be British wunderkind #FlorencePugh) deserves e… https://t.co/l14xwtJQ8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idgaf. Luke Walton is laker family and if they fire his ass I’m done hahaha. Lebron ruins franchises after he leave… https://t.co/yFYALgP6xA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffgreer_ @re_anderson21 Oddly, the 30 minutes right before that were some of the best all season against the best team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old friend: *updates me on life events*  Me: “man, that’s exciting! I’m happy for you!”  OF: “when you visiting me?… https://t.co/xFwvhuzAtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROBERTO97393371 La mitad de la Argentina,tomatelas forro,por que no me buscas a mi inutil, nada me gustaria mas qu… https://t.co/2Xtta5tST7]]></document><document><![CDATA[New video Drug Lord available now!!! Make sure to like, subscribe and comment on the Snake Lucci Official Channel!!… https://t.co/VET02SdzHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Fra_ Interesting how you disregarded KC, Phil &amp; Den also signing free agents today......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cavillasgia @villasgia @Fer66deAlizze @Eltox1 @Samuelon110 @_on_toy_ @prosperous05 @elsay80 @skrdrod… https://t.co/jonxyHG17J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olddragonlady40 Normal? What’s normal? Do YOU determine what’s normal? God I hope not! We’ll be stuck in the 1930’… https://t.co/Mp0R65AZ3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow was so deep on Tamarack today that at one point while #skiing on low angle, dowhill terrain I just came to a s… https://t.co/POMkGuairE]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are about 10 examples of this same shit tonight alone. He does this all the time. Always has.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stressed and anxious doesn’t begin to describe how I’ve felt the last few weeks, but I’m so thankful (and honestly… https://t.co/oEGxt2kCPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:23.9°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano "Shut up Melissa Alano"...is not indicative of the majority of law abiding gun owners attitude. So p… https://t.co/q088WcfwX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBCBoysBBall Congratulations on the Excellent ‘Sailor’ representation on the All Conference Teams!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cant believe i lived in Atlanta all that time and never went to Mary Macs until last night, finn im goin back today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Project_Malmo thanks so much for creating this. I wanted it 5 years ago, was too complicated, now I am in a place… https://t.co/bECm9Xg9fQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The face he makes when the fellas invite him to sit with them for a quarter. Judah feels like a big kid 😊.… https://t.co/PSMvGJqCxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aravosis @MalcolmNance is this the same @Jim_Jordan who thinks it's cool to protect pedophiles??? yep, it sure is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the evening with my amazing wife enjoying the spectacular LP. @ House of Blues Boston https://t.co/1rjZz9C8K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Introductions underway for Campolindo and Serra! Tip-off just a few moments away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@epicciuto If you see James Buchanan trending, THAT’S when you get nervous!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all cannot tell me aliens aren’t real.. all those galaxies and earth has the only life?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Commandtechno @28delayslater @DMC_Ryan @BenSullins @answerswithjoe Basically haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse How do you explain the first 235 years that the US existed without one?   I'll wait for your answer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MutCallahan Not really, would rather hear rerun's of ESPN overnight radio or something. we can't stand out and his fake stick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaBoyChavy You would’ve won if you took a play out of my book #360Splits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO Women wearing white pants and pink hats are taking over the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the 5A @KSHSAA state tournament, the @BSHSWrestling1 have five wrestlers in the medal round. Cassius Vanderpool,… https://t.co/58yPTUcW4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HighSchoolMeVsAdultMe  HS: I want to move to FL &amp; go waterskiing  Adult: I’m finally moving to FL to go waterskiing]]></document><document><![CDATA[VANTAGE CAREER CENTER Open House and Taste of Vantage Monday, February 25th 5:00 – 7:30 p.m. Tickets to try tasty f… https://t.co/Rg8KiUW9OV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Dickson is shopping at the Hancock HEB like he's not the Punter for the Seattle Seahawks lol I love it]]></document></documents></author>