<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I used to buy copies of @TheUGseries and create customized @TouringPlans for my theoretical @WDWToday vacation, des… https://t.co/bCXffEwC9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching fist fights on YouTube in the morning really gets the blood pumping in the morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ganulvian @jhory1914 @JosephNSanberg @Marc_Perrone He just owns the workers labor product, which is often the same as owning the workers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prageru Valenzuela is a case lesson in what can go wrong when an aurhoritarion like @realDonaldTrump tries to take… https://t.co/0WrxsfLe6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KySportsRadio the only reason why I know the presidents and what they were kind of known for is because of the Animaniacs song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@A_suhailaa @MaliyaFransi This was in my memories from one year ago today 😭😭😭😭😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/LY9HJG8DuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewBrandt You really think it’s that high? Some lawyers are smiling if so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only one hour does not sound very pleasant. It's been years since my health issues cost me sleep, so I can't compla… https://t.co/WW9lgOciih]]></document><document><![CDATA[I thought they were a scandal free administration. Isn't that what the lefties say.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do think, is this ironic? @OneMinuteBriefs @dalger2001 @TheDrumAwards @TheDrum #TheDrumAwards Full brief:… https://t.co/y0lWMnm0pS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night with Stacy and @DierksBentley. Great concert! https://t.co/JpBlELuEd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball Panther baseball scrimmages at Meade Co on Tuesday. Good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming up this Fri. night Feb. 22nd at the Colony Woodstock NY, I am performing a solo acoustic concert drawing on… https://t.co/mhHCrYJpvX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddieeee42 @JonHeyman It’s honestly getting really annoying that these players aren’t signed yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BareZachow1 @JoshGolberg  who's bringing home the gold balls this year in the @wiaawistate ? Need to fill out my bracket]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kvng_wvy Great player, leader, friend, teammate. I know he will do great things at the next level. Can’t wait to watch you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acreditar q a troca do presidente seria suficiente para mudar o rumo da nau brasileira, após 15 anos do partido gra… https://t.co/y8EiOs99gf]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 4:24 AM CST, Salina [Saline Co, KS] BROADCAST MEDIA reports SNOW of 4.00 INCH. MEASURED AT KSAL. https://t.co/nuKtPknVch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Dumber than a super tanker full of rocks we love it out here, if she is the face of the Democratic… https://t.co/0YgsUSxNj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wednesday March 6 - Grabien News:    AOC: ‘Green New Deal’ Needs Higher Taxes on Rich to Fund Communities of Color;… https://t.co/lSArza0gg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopp @TFTC21 @nic__carter @MartyBent @twobitidiot Definitely curious what 0x54/h thinks about the threat model and… https://t.co/FhG84h7E2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried putting in contacts before work and I poked my eye and now I’m going to walk into work looking like I have pi… https://t.co/wWLNnoLjMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former Net Kenny Anderson In Hospital After Suffering Stroke https://t.co/Jmx7SeuotO via @WFAN660]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a partial cut of the video of the suicide bomber who killed 40 Indian police in a Kashmir  bombing.  Why do… https://t.co/3HBR4Qye9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[But @ATLHawks got blown out in the Luka trade, huh? Stop saying that, people. It’s a lazy take. @929TheGame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand nice vote caring for families. Kill babies atcany stage. What a candidate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frogsgirl2016 @realDonaldTrump Best President Ever https://t.co/uBta2gAEzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wouterhoetink TRUMP to FLAG Trust respect und mein. pinto  what's Flag. Response...  Freedom to Learn About God? A… https://t.co/hla42IcmRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t blame Robb, Frey invoked guest rights. Guest Rights is as sacred as any law or tradition gets in Westeros. It… https://t.co/jnn1snauEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissHesslein @FRSNewJersey @Jeremy_P_Reich @MoralesMTPS @evanabramson . If only NJ were as future ready as it was… https://t.co/Em4R55XhlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilCattermull @LarryLarmeu @digitalcloudgal @CTOAdvisor @Vecchi_Paolo @BillMew @tcrawford @waynesadin @mccrory… https://t.co/zCTUnL5zeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump YOU ARE A CONMAN LIED TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ANOUT EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ADH6626 @NBCSNationals Stephen looking good!  Please let him stay healthy all year Baseball Gods! #Nats]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFF_RyanB @amazehayes_ @FFzinger @pahowdy @DFF_Koala @Moo12152 There is an instruction video for writing a scrape… https://t.co/Zoy0xZug6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reviewjournal Come on! This is just getting a little too overboard!! Geesh!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[90 Day Challenge: Day 3 (@ Disney's Guest Services Call Center in Orlando, FL) https://t.co/w0NW4Yr0f0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump So lets be clear...since when do liberal critics tell the truth? They dont. Trump is win… https://t.co/BA7asF3MfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never understood the idea of finding yourself. I had too many goals and ambitions to just go wander somewhere. I gu… https://t.co/ZIWCV48g7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPosnanski @tommytomlinson Came very close to including this on my list. Best book ever about being a fan. (I’ve s… https://t.co/ybtZF9GgCJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howard on the right.  Bernie on the left.  Both out to weaken the Democratic Party.  Don’t be fooled again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 SELLING PRINTS 🚨  . I have started selling prints of my favorite photos. I will only sell 10 of every photo. Ever… https://t.co/dumxNEDVPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could Rick tank without it being obvious..seriously..looks like it's obvious in Mavs last two blowout losses..j… https://t.co/rLx0DyhAVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@panekbill @ElleRguez He's a pain in my ars, tryin to keep up with!!🤣🤣🐾🐾👭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikefromWCH He said the Phillies are a weak organization set up for failure. Klentak can't develop a system, he's… https://t.co/ypYHbhpcKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read the first word and knew something wild was gonna come afterwards]]></document><document><![CDATA[My professor gave us all the questions on the exam for our study guide 😭😭 bless her heart https://t.co/fDX0hvNxc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from @robynkonichiwa crowd giving some love with Dancing On My Own https://t.co/lgRqxvI3SF]]></document><document><![CDATA[No offense, but the King of Country is NOT this guy! Roy Acuff, George Jones, and @GeorgeStrait all have worn the c… https://t.co/YYNDs6fN16]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tacitassassin13 I've been asked about ashlon dulin's film.  Any chance you have a good link to any of it? Cheers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously glad everyone is ok...BUT are we really gonna act like IT didn’t straight kick Beverly on the shot to ini… https://t.co/N1pZg60nKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mail Day from @dmntakeover!  Now I need the rest of the Sandlot cards!! https://t.co/0qgs6lRPuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndroidDev I find Android is the best buy far to any other, how do you get the full use out of it ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the Campbell 3 that gave Oldham County a 16-point lead at halftime. https://t.co/f64nCAylKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[AP FACT CHECK: Trump says no more planes or cows under Dems  https://t.co/pZyLvDqOCt via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toodo_Belen Si hablas con algunas personas y ves que cambiaron en forma cíclica 4 fotos durante el día, claro que te das cuenta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I enjoy my day off. A little dusting in Maineville OH. @Local12 @WCPO @NWSILN https://t.co/isIegLnXlf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe has been blessed with a wonderful family, and many wonderful things. But she’s definitely had a rough time wi… https://t.co/46Ob93nexL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Location scouting for an upcoming shoot with xoexxapoian and doris.sangeorzan and I managed to capture this image.… https://t.co/NJjwyzd1G6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwiftHitter @karmanah_fx @offandpacing_ry @atTheTrack7 I mean she has a tvg account and might bet $2 WPS on someth… https://t.co/zXvuRGza7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Felix's Restaurant &amp; Oyster Bar in New Orleans, LA https://t.co/k81Ayrd2KK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy how some people go straight to the smoke pin after lunch rather than going to heat up their food. Nicoti… https://t.co/AUIJGoqIDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniel_rockholt @PaulReindlSD @BenAndWoods Nah. You can’t erase that stink.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I though this was a giant bass in the crystal clear water #upper_niagara #walleye https://t.co/y12akY5bhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepDennisBonnen Teaching is a profession. A one-time $5000 across the board raise won’t solve the underlying prob… https://t.co/V4VyGogRYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you drop off donations at your local thrift store only to find someone recently donated a bunch of vintage… https://t.co/r0BVYGFuyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Being a custom to failure, you should not be to to upset losing another attemp at dismantling our 2nd… https://t.co/7hBgQ5mScT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aileen_montana @brittanaaay3334 @UTSA such good times! Y’all took over though!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dexwesley The federal government's job is to defend the United States and its borders. This is very clearly a local and state issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howwwwwww did she think this would make it better and not infinitely worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CallMeSYD @501PayB I love how y’all sitting here planning this man career 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[That extra 5 pounds was heavy but still got a squat clean PR of #225 😅 @ CrossFit Attila https://t.co/bC0QtWbjiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happyvalentinesday❤️, y’all. #thursdaymotivation #houston #texas @ NRG Park https://t.co/DtxcZF9WGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Theist313 @ZeekBPrint @michiganinsider That was definitely a sequence where they beat themselves. No question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC THERE IS SAFETY IN NUMBERS ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO THE QUALITY OF HEALTH CARE ,BECAUSE RIGHT NOW MEDICAR… https://t.co/zWxK85LYSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby @DonaldJTrumpJr Juan Williams? Have you went mad? Seriously! WTF are doing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OLawDogg @RyanAFournier you kidding?  what he and others did is treason. the punishment needs to fit the crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin said I look like Canelo.... Canelo wish he looked like your boy..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things are empty and quiet now @NHSRattlers Ira Floyd Field but it won’t be tonight. The state ranked @NavSoftball… https://t.co/C7bfPmCoLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[While Great Debaters,  who are also scholars, continue their excellence in competition, our scholar-athletes are sm… https://t.co/mhIR937DbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bridges_brent  Good video, I am offering free fly fishing lessons when it gets a little warmer. I went this week but didn’t catch anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNNFL just get @PatMcAfeeShow  #ForTheBrand and Monday’s are saved all fall long. Monday night football deserves… https://t.co/BJt7Id9iNP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmomahony keep active.. your passing trough this life to eternity. ❤️⛪️🇻🇦😇🙏🍷🍷🍷⌛️🕯️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeStoughton35 Thanks Mike! Really appreciate that. Got back to my roots with the radio call, and enjoyed it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasMaduro Se te acabó el tiempo papito.“El CAGAO socialismo del siglo XXl” DESTRUYÓ a Venezuela.¿Que carajo qu… https://t.co/nPLVTjBgZO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Announcements! Announcements! Annnoooowwwncments! You guys have been amazing followers tossing SO much love and swe… https://t.co/eKle0EE1Jp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank u guys for such an awesome show gabnomods it will always bring back the my wedding day and our trip to guam w… https://t.co/LiczI109uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is a slow moving security line to get into Council chambers, which is unusual. https://t.co/HF2Q6l2j99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas That’s what I interpreted that as - thanks for confirming felt that way to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely wonderful. Thank you for sharing this. God Bless this young man and his family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There have been 17 fouls called in 6:41 seconds of the third quarter. 54-45. Momentum is definitely on Trojans’ sid… https://t.co/K34r0O3vN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ah yes, the yearly flu/flu like symptoms has finally arrived. Nice of you to show up, dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPostOpinion: Dems’ 2020 race is starting to look like a chutzpah contest: https://t.co/CBiVeJ0OBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Declas2019 @realhublife @realDonaldTrump @RealSaavedra https://t.co/K8Rf94OE2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfannc5 @archer1111 @oreomina1 @canbowhunter @snaggerr22 @F150SuperSnake @Bearman1130 @burnside4141 @mbabs21… https://t.co/DNvmJVoOXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready for our Winter Wellness Day on Wednesday March 6th! #Williamberczyps #Winterwellness #YRDSB #opheacanada https://t.co/X0Z3BuEXz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[#worrying is in my nature. 🤷🏾‍♂️ @ VA New Jersey Health Care System https://t.co/OjtSjGppJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Irvine showcases Ducks' new practice facility at the Orange County Great Park https://t.co/D4UKLWZTON]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shooters gon Shoot   https://t.co/S4grKOmhIg   @AutoRtz @Retweet_Lobby @RSG_Retweet @ZooRetweets @TwitchGain… https://t.co/vmvpm29UuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomascol 2/2 who did not believe the truth, but took pleasure in wickedness. II  Thessalonians 2:10-12  Yes, belie… https://t.co/dXKrjHKorl]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are an embarrassment. Watch Pence get the silent treatment in Munich. It’s embarrassing #MarALadass]]></document></documents></author>