<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@805foodie Aw. Sending love. At least your food looks like it’s smiling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine giving your all to an organization that can’t figure out its arena situation, can’t fill a building, and ca… https://t.co/l3LYHmQXNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I officially have my first items posted on TPT for sale! #teacherspayteachers #wolhoyswonders]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get too excited until you hear what he has to say and how he reacts to Pres Trump - the DNC is a crumbling pa… https://t.co/wUSsRXb03E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bringbackfear @replicantpinky @12nighthorror @BetterBrainsB @NYounker @crashpalace @JustEm_78 @Dismay00… https://t.co/uNPb5Gi47Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever spend 20 hours on a 🔥 project, go to sleep &amp; then wake up like wtf is this shit ¿?¿?¿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoDavidson7 @AnnCoulter Oh quit beating around the bush Bo, tell us what you really think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uuDCK8AnuH I support my sisters @TrinityTheTuck and @monetxchange ! Courageous 👏👏👏👏👏👏👏👑👑👑👑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics I listen to what Joe Biden says. I think Pence is a patsy,  and a crackpot ..From where I stand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DigitalLearnin5 @HESSPLASH @Ms5thGradeLlama @HESlovingood Yes, there was a conversation about weather to measure t… https://t.co/0VmFd7wndl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear #Tahoe, why do you always deprive me of snow on my trips and rub it in my doing it all a week before or a week… https://t.co/NSUplbnkx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourgirlDomino I was about to say. I didn’t make that : hour drive alone for nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I ever on @Twitter? Because over on @instagram... https://t.co/AwIzQJ7Nxl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Helped me know I had to flip the tape for next shower. Anyways how fucking good a band was Alice in Chains? Very good that's how.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuanoBano @BlancaSprkls is def # 2 neck fur. I’m salmon head. Always leaving my leftovers behind 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@v_fibrillation @BrowofJustice @AllisonRBond I'm curious too. (About the poor historian)  Another one to add though: "Soft BP" 🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy weekend friends 👋🏻 Feeling the need for spring time like me!? 🌷Yesterday was in the high 70s here in DFW 🙌🏻 y… https://t.co/GhwevsBTBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[No. Just no.  I have a permit, and wasn’t sure 8 hours was enough training. #handgunpermit #carrypermit #Gunsense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday dinner for the Pisces gals. ❤️🖖 (@ Jones in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/H8cnAtqCun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimOriolesTV  Why did you start to break down at that point, Jim?! I was okay until I heard you and then I was rea… https://t.co/qTBrtP6kd4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking of ✨ #VitaminF ✨all @bthreebalm products are packed full of the essential fatty acids your skin craves. Re… https://t.co/YP8aw8gh9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAm_EbonyART Lmao that fool said you can’t double jeopardy me like that lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@psychdr100 I know we should be moving forward NOT backwards! Trump is a Nazi I hope he gets impeached! #ImpeachtheMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams @deplorableWAbre Juan, This is how is starts and is very dangerous irresponsible. They want to sil… https://t.co/NoQYEGfTqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me burst out laughing. He Looks So Proud Of His Collection  // funny pictures - funny photos - funny... https://t.co/vWAZ7dXxNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elDon_Yannick Who knows maybe slivers of your thoughts will wind up like poetry in fortune cookies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[not even being slightly dramatic, my life has dramatically improved living in a place with public transportation...… https://t.co/OQ94Dm44bU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul I thought you were an isolationist.  If so, a border wall would help!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a travel ban, her I have gotten no email this morning from my professor cancelling class....what's he gonna… https://t.co/HFBOUBf9A8]]></document><document><![CDATA[☮️💟🕉☯️ #RandomActsOfKindness #SmileAndBeKind #KindnessIsMyReligion @ Manteca, California https://t.co/6XxxkADdZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FindingAnswers @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse ....WHAT ABOUT 'THE YEMEN'S CHILDRENS ???  TRUMP'S 'FRIEND SAUDI KING IS 'STARV… https://t.co/7dW7dLhz4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joellesliefro @xScarletSiren Congrats, @joellesliefro! And, yes, you are good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept for 9 hrs!!! Wohoooo!!! Grabiha gyud kakapoy gahapon!😭😭😭 but work pa diay ron. Hahahuhu. Saturdy is my Friday😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayneMB68 @AbuseChat Unless someone is actually in it, they don’t get it. I too would have judged had I not lived… https://t.co/ZamoTmcV44]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Underneath It All by @nodoubt on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/CCPeydi7mN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have strong beliefs about both sides. It breaks my heart to see or hear Rebublicans say the Dems believe in the m… https://t.co/QyLJTbRDkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M73Mohammed @Nisrin42625243 Thank you. When I have said this; I'm trolled and called anti-Semitic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Draw me close to you!   No one else will do!!!!   Bring me back to YOU!    If u r reading this...let Him know... u… https://t.co/A5BpM2Rc4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌴 Florida #latergram | American Dreams 🇺🇸 My set of cool day in hot Miami: https://t.co/rNbQfsVds5 @ Florida's 22nd… https://t.co/LdaLyQSr1a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to Sow someone how much you care with some Loving Swineness and help piggies abandoned piggies! DONATE use Pay… https://t.co/4QYG3enwJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Grab #aerosols and carve out a #welcome sign on the building. 2. Run and do all of the things I want to do witho… https://t.co/RNq5HZaTDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jurbina @intercone Ni hay perdón. Por eso el infierno tiene que existir!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real saw a whole ass man prob in his 80s in a wheelchair with oxygen and everything at the club tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi everyone my Sunday gift to you is also my Sunday gift to me: discovery of @larryburb . You best believe I’m goin… https://t.co/GkLsEa8tzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Alexandria, VA? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Membership A… https://t.co/lFEylH3AML]]></document><document><![CDATA[A really cool and informative thread on Judaism/prayer. My fav bit:  “I don't think that I pray for a pony and God… https://t.co/Qaz6WnGJBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to quit leaving my book at work. I’m getting behind on my readings 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennettsben @Stop_Tweet_Spam @EaseYourMind77 @Niklas_Nubien @HillaryClinton https://t.co/9bHwkJTlmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmcobb @StLouisBlues Funny when we had the two let up goals back to back, I was like hmmmmm Is Allen playing??? Sure enough!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTNHoller @StormResist @ltgovmcnally @GlenCasada @stopbyrd I should hope so.  The victims of sexual assault need… https://t.co/nPuSgWoaLT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aiden's 3rd grade concert. He is so precious 🥰 @ Charles Nash Elementary https://t.co/wkvgY9JQMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG!  They were so excited about his all day long.  Their final combination shows how well thought the connections… https://t.co/Yfgt9z0pNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[A symbol of performance, courtesy of dodgeofficial.   #cias #cias2019 #thepassionwithinus #dodge #hellcat… https://t.co/T5oYv5Yz3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are always #signs around us telling us to #go #merge #reducespeed #stop, but we all need the reminder to… https://t.co/wc65LnKIDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu Ok. Seniors. Time to get to work to get these jerks out of office!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWilfonWSB @wsbtv Yes @Wsb Tv I just heard the breaking news from @'atlanta Journal Constitution. #AJC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And sure enough he woke up and came to sleep on the bed with me even though he NEVER wakes up at night]]></document><document><![CDATA[I relate to all these things, pls send a prayer bc I have a math and geography exam tomorrow :,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrippledChic Hi cutie pie!! You are awesome! Thanks for sharing! #DisabledPeopleAreHot #ChronicPain]]></document><document><![CDATA[selling this one too size 4 y’all just lmk what you are willing to pay for it’s Sherri hill 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guarinolm @lindatake @HoarseWisperer We'll have highs in the teens and lows in the single digits next week. That p… https://t.co/t3AxJxhk2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️#Stephanie’sbabyshower🤰🏻👑🎉🥳🎊🎁😍#waitingforbaby @ Li Greci's Staaten https://t.co/sQ8hlOehPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@being_ulti @hos_ultimate As someone else named Simon, how do you deal with being so much cooler than everyone else?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends @FoxNews Sunday morning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚺 I am very proud of this picture. I began my wedding day completely overwhelmed by love. The energy in this room f… https://t.co/KUpW8xm7I3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mackadelic_12 and I meet up for one drink ........................ end up going home at 330 #sundayfunday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone once accused me of only posting screenshots of perfect charts.  Perhaps there is a bit of truth to that, bu… https://t.co/RVogjrhKm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[💋 COVER REVEAL 💋   Kiss and Break Up by Ella Fields @_EllaFields is coming March 8th!  Release alert:… https://t.co/tNpSijYrOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son’s class did something similar to this! #IAmColinKaepernick #LetFreedomRing ✊🏽❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si fuera interesada y gold digger ya estuviera hasta casada que asquito]]></document><document><![CDATA[You shouldn’t be allowed to discuss the primaries unless you’ve actually read since high school or college.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiggroAmigo @leeleebb21 All of it!!   😂😂😂. I’ll grab the spoons and forks https://t.co/eTVzqBMmTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you have never worn jeans that were still wet from the dryer and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thefunrevucc @nowin2613 @Perednia My pastor used to be in Corpus! He said his church there was conservative, it wa… https://t.co/a5B7HyUOsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couples massage at driftdartmouth  now #margaritas  and dinner. Starting the weekend right. 💆🏼‍♀️💆🏼‍♂️🍸🍸 @ Not Your… https://t.co/mhAMjA8m9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominick_ra no reason really just on vacation, visiting my brother while he’s off season...]]></document><document><![CDATA[58 hours of work this week...  58 hours of work next week...  THEN FINALLY OUR VACATION IN THE BAHAMAS ☀️🏝🌊🚢👙🍹 https://t.co/7A1vaHAFSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[In one of those roll-your-windows-down-and-blast-country type of moods 👋🏼👋🏼🎤🎤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think that more #WomenInGovernment are needed to advance gender equality today. Do you agree? #SheBelongs… https://t.co/XBrpQyEyk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on letgo! https://t.co/eJYUnLQmfK - White and black camper shell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into Mark, Griffin, and Ben tonight. Loved hearing about their futures. It's been awhile since watching them pl… https://t.co/JSasQIeE7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[On this sunny #IWDay2019, @rhodanazanin1 and I are here to give you the gentle reminder that Notorious RBG closes o… https://t.co/b1S70IAzmB]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will work for me too right?  . . . . . . .  Spoiler Alert: It won’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a shit day and are still working 10 hours in and hear something like this...😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courttace @RickyPDillon i haven’t seen him since 2016 this isn’t fair we are manifesting today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously I lose several minutes to reminiscing every time someone mentions it  please, please stop talking about… https://t.co/uc5sYs7Sbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you realized you hit zero! #CHEERSPORT2019 #wylieelite https://t.co/pW79WKh29m]]></document><document><![CDATA[GUESS WHO IS HOME AND SPLOOTING ON OUR COUCH ONCE AGAIN!!! Thank you all for thinking about my little Ollie, he is… https://t.co/soaa87sbbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCAdrianH @CBCOttawa @KBQWrites our time is now! 😂 #mismatchedshoes #ithappenedtome https://t.co/dNnJmB7rV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I so cant wait to be on a plane come Wednesday! I need this short vacay real QUICK!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning ☀️  Shifting mindset  Re-focus Speaking positivity @ East Orange, New Jersey https://t.co/89KCb1E2tF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein Kept saying it last night. At least MC turned it around in the end. Michael Cohen you are doing the right thing]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Always the childbridesmaid never the child bride *Gulp Gulp*” 😂😂😂😂😂 #Bigmouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tired but inspired. Hanging with @txafterviolence folx is nice. You, too, can support this project that combines ar… https://t.co/6UXRX0I8CJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Besides the obvious ones that I already know of, who’s from the St. Louis area?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't usually go for the super hero/super natural type shows, but I just started #umbrellacademy and it is amazing! https://t.co/LJGwMGULYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone can get it done — Alex can! Sending all my good vibes to my favorite game show host 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitnoelleault We need a plague that takes all of these people off of the earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell asleep at 8:30 last night and honestly that’s the best sleep i’ve gotten all semester]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the immigration people we would like to provide you audio visual and written aid in order for you to properly u… https://t.co/A1rwvwwEsb]]></document></documents></author>