<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Sunday funday is here so let's visit the Honeydukes! 🍭🍦🍫🍥 Wish you all a beautiful day full of good vibes and smile… https://t.co/aao5h19ciU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Unfortunately we’ve gotten really good at building refugee camps,” says @CarylStern of @UNICEFUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mstracuzzi2 We are blessed with the best grandparents out there that’s for sure #grateful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday Court❤️ celebrate the hell out of today and have the greatest time girl!  @seargantgoober https://t.co/jrSYTh61hI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning #ChampionshipSunday @djworldjunior @djohnsonpga grounds crew hard at work tpcmyrtlebeach @ TPC Myrtle… https://t.co/pkQjFkIfPw]]></document><document><![CDATA[shit days like this result in netflix has asking me if I'm still watching a solid 8 times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland "Anytime I start doing any fairytale or folk narrative research, one of the first things I do is go to… https://t.co/LXdzMG2ONR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just really thankful now that things didn’t work out like I wanted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing some creative small group art today. We talked about what makes us, us. The pictures turned out beautifully.… https://t.co/UZM7HXhEXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stage is set for ⁦@evanasmith⁩ to do his thing. ⁦@TexasTribune⁩ #SXSW https://t.co/6jISwqr1NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if I just dont go to prom? I mean it's not like I have a date or anyone will ask me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being from Houston is a fucking curse when it comes to driving bc when you drive ANYWHERE else mf be driving slow a… https://t.co/CQCeCLRcPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@semajecollier That been done months ago for some! But ppl will find new reasons to hate ppl everyday! 😂 But the lo… https://t.co/0q7auM2Lpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[missed him in the lobby but caught him at the game... bag secured https://t.co/hSb8U843h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us for Karaoke ON ST PATRICK’S DAY Sunday March 17th at oceanviewbarandgrill 8pm-12am. I’m hosting with Daniel… https://t.co/6nxTZ5uIHP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Preach this. I’m 23 and still growing. If ya still got cones, ya ain’t done growing, sis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@summerxrose_ I cannot this is like smart but scary at the same time 😂 what if the end of the routine was *James Ch… https://t.co/W4AAL9NnZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to remember that God wants us to live one day at a time. We can’t worry about the future and ask “what if”.… https://t.co/mdjoFwUpNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[but I won’t cry for yesterday - there’s an ordinary world somehow I have to find 🎺]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EasyA is one of my favorite movies. And the scenes with Olive's parents make me laugh out loud every single time I watch it! 😂🅰️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started our morning with a close reading of a Shawn Mendes song! @ James Van Allen Elementary School https://t.co/dRAlR7K8o3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Power and control. There’s a cell at Gitmo waiting for him and his cronies. MAGA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working 2 jobs, building my dreams. Having a girlfriend... being an adult, being a daughter. Dammmmm I need a vacation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is my first year since my sophomore year of high school not doing anything for spring break. wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[While directly Myanmar and Saudi Arabia may have cold words, KSA has been on increasingly friendly terms with the C… https://t.co/3C6Xlq4u16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewieG24665333 Just an excuse to eat with my fingers. https://t.co/qC1S7X0q8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[our players differentiate from the others by being better! @CCAPEcon https://t.co/5ujASzTB2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tedakin @shudder @therealjoebob Sooooooooooooo many!!! And I want to do them all!!! 😋🤠📬👏👏👏 https://t.co/Q8dlmcBpsc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny jokes, Lmao quotes, jokes quotes, funny pictures, funniest thing ever, Omg hilarious  …For the... https://t.co/CFK2wPv4zY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I wanna know is, where is Jonathan in the AU?? College?? @LukeBaines @Kat_McNamara #ShadowhuntersRewatch #SaveShadowhunters]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was some kind of beautiful #doodlesofinstagram #snowday #mammothlakes @ Mammoth Lakes, California https://t.co/uRwefDTs5P]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl and I just rode Avatar. The first thing out of her mouth once the ride ended was, “I want to do it again!… https://t.co/qvtHO3QtpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meek on infanticide (one piece on Born Alive Act); media mobs on pro-life teens (one brief post on Covington HS) bu… https://t.co/kPB5gF08EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[RealTree Camouflage Baby Mei Tai, Baby Carrier Men, Baby Boy Carrier,Mei Tai Baby, Reversible Baby Carrier,Cotton... https://t.co/lVy0uelsbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi  #DoctorWho #TheUniverseLovesPeterCapaldi https://t.co/25uadbDwHq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you SO much to everyone for coming out last night for an unbelievable show @RockwoodNYC ...@leonbridges you w… https://t.co/c8lZMFHOiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs How pathetic of a human do you need to be to spread this BS? Attacking the men and women who ridk their l… https://t.co/xwxroX1z8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok #oscars, you can just replay Spike Lee all night and forget about the rest #weregood #addapostrophe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, this..... Our firewall is down. Literally. #ccdc #cybersecurity #cybersecuritycompetition #cybersecurityteam… https://t.co/6cAbmIroXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😳😱🤦‍♀️.  she’s just so incoherent, makes no sense and should be evaluated by a physician....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckSexton It's pathetic the @sunrisemvmt uses children this way.  First brainwashing the children, getting them e… https://t.co/E5lqduTOlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be on this stage in 10 mins. Feel free to join the conversation!!! #ETHDenver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pa. first lady visits Elmwood Academy for #SchoolBreakfastWeek  #NSBW19 via @cumberlink https://t.co/tsMlLSsxLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jlmitch_ Started this last week and I am so weak haha. Had one coke last week. We’re gonna shoot for none this week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye my people it’s our last few hours  let’s enjoy it🙌 #BlackHistoryMonth #whyourmonthshort]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ParlayShea187 I’m bored... soooooooo, break up with your bf plz. Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrOverstreet101 @ERobbPrincipal Some districts don’t allow less than a 50!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I have a breakdown scheduled next week... stay tuned” - @steffevette             Planned breakdowns &gt; spontaneous breakdowns]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t heard 11 minutes by YUNGBLUD feat. Halsey and Travis Barker you are missing out!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi es pareciera que es tan farsante como el fox.Otro gran logro de la cuarta transformación, una a una están cayen… https://t.co/mOgssjfMTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who comes to the gym to use their laptop while sitting on a bench when there is a computer room right through the door? #cmondude]]></document><document><![CDATA[tony hawk has a daughter &amp; I literally just found out today. I’ve been living under a fucking rock I guess wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to our cousin, Sean Salazar!!!! We are so proud of you! @TexT0var @PatrickTovar1 @tygatovar @mrstovar… https://t.co/TDIqSnfkEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exacto, ¡todo el mundo puede hacer y deshacer! porque cada quien es dueño de su vida y de sus actos, por ende ABSOL… https://t.co/0HUfkzvQRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dead serious I would pay good money for that service. Think about it, when you need concert tickets, Black Frid… https://t.co/IDBMBOqkzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to you on your 4th State Wrestling Title! It’s been a great pleasure watching you wrestle and announcing m… https://t.co/Hm1AZO4Nex]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bravo! Well said! This is a must hear/must RT video!  Republican Congressionals and Senators, please stop being suc… https://t.co/geahIZhWCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think we were meant to have a full week of school this semester...or even school on a Wednesday in general!! #SnowDay258744]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️♥️😩 whenever I look back and see shit like this my heart melts all over again]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4! I have accepted a challenge from @jedjohnston3  to post covers of seven books I love: no explanations, no re… https://t.co/DE3XUWFe05]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boolinheavy @jack_kananian @Browns @firstenergycorp The ravens went to the playoffs.   Rethink that for a minute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allantercalivre @superaguia2000 Psicopauta do Mourão: Super EGO extremamente desenvolvido.. 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[ALLY + JACKSON MAINE FOREVER (well not forrrrrrrrever....) cc: @TheElwins  🐕 🥩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaineFinFan So, he’s awful but worth a 3rd or 4th rounder? Makes sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Friday night at #nightingale__la No cover Open from 10:30PM #davidelaffe #Nightingale_LA  #andresrigal… https://t.co/8tGcyWDXPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This rando on snap has been thirsty for me for so long and he asked me for booty pics and I sent him a pic of my ex’s hairy ass booty lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BethBossy Absolutely agree!! Too many ppl rush to judgement before they hear everything....take things slow and un… https://t.co/6Z7tMCZ3Om]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lucky to live in the Smokies—there is always something fun to do! 🏔 🎿 ❄️ 🧣 😎 obergatlinburg… https://t.co/GAGm3IZJoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will readily admit that luck played a big role in my success. Luck opened the doors, and I figured out what to do… https://t.co/I0KZLk7Q8M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wingster26 Moi aussi sur la route ........ de New York ! Mais moins de traffic que toi !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course, people (regulars who come here often) gottta be dickheads and show up 10 minutes before I close to drop… https://t.co/k26WufnqwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristianoLegit Red lights are nice. Shit makes you feel like youre in a Zane novel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finish The Race : Scarlet Letters, Cords Of Redemption https://t.co/szlBqFgNq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super corny but:  https://t.co/fp1XJlPdVk https://t.co/xJeOsuWW2s https://t.co/Mc7ihdGhY1  Gaffer/AC/Dolly Grip/SFX… https://t.co/PqswmJJ31c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump who the hell is Tim Apple? Whats your name? Greatest memory of all time. Greatest delusion of all time. Donald Putin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynBlogger @Acosta It matters because we are paying this dipshit a salary that someone else would like to work for… https://t.co/i15ZNMdg1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible work!  Excited about our continued strong partnership with @codeorg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't want to work in a man's world, I want to work in a corporate world.  @llaltrello #BalanceForBetter… https://t.co/KvNdTi1eQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CANT BREATHEEEE “I jus didnt tell you the truth, but I wasn’t lyin” I cannot I cannooooott]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris Typical POS white privileged punk ass asshole...he’s already on the way of growing up like Kavanaugh and Trump...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gummalumm @AdriennePed @AHAWisconsin GO RED BABY https://t.co/GB4y2GnzgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamRubiDilaik @ColorsTV @RubiDilaik @VivianDsena01 #RubinaDilaik Outstanding perfect performance 🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🌟🌟🌟🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[I watched part of this and stopped when I realized that he was turning over all kinds of information that is SUPPOS… https://t.co/3fNhC5F8VU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I must admit, it felt odd making this change, since I’ve been #teamvalor since the beginning. ❤️ Nice to have the f… https://t.co/BSOVfG1vUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Moon....I tried to capture her beauty...but she is wild and untamed.  #supermoon  #morningmoon… https://t.co/2AoDGFoKP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday,my trainer had an attitude problem and I'm like, I'm no mind reader and I don't wanna be. If something is… https://t.co/hmg7SlgGYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithboykin If Nicolas deserves 250 million dollars for people dissing his MAGA-hatted smirk-what do the parents o… https://t.co/NdP8aSe35d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Otc I don’t care if I’m in a place to judge or not if your a mom and out every night I judge you but if I see you e… https://t.co/j5YfzGsMct]]></document><document><![CDATA[But like does anyone wanna get me these brushes because ya girls broke now 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic @HillaryClinton Bahahahahahahaha....TRUMP IS YOUR PRESIDENT!!! TRUMP IS HILLARYS PRESIDENT TOO!!!!  🤪🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_williams Dunno. We just had to walk down the platform past the characters. It was cool.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArendRox I fucking love this!! I always tell people how much I hate people cuz people suck! I keep my group small… https://t.co/ha1D56uK5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flawlessubeauty too good to be true 🥰🥰 Already purchased mine🙌🏻🙌🏻 #InternationalWomansDay https://t.co/zaMn2lpIOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many closures still coming in due to the treacherous road conditions. Download the @KCTV5 app to monitor them! https://t.co/33hUvTKLNK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm Android but I thought some of you like to know this. Google Keep on your Apple watch! #googleedu   https://t.co/0RWP3eGsby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTMinEngSR @jschrimsher2 @CollegeGameDay Jealous????  I think so.  Just keep having your NCAA championship game in… https://t.co/Z0iUfeYmhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because inside we’re all a little hopeless sometimes. @rickygervais just has the guts to bring it out of us all. Ca… https://t.co/Sp1MIxDdDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catchypseudonym @xobabyspicexo @Machinist_Paul @KamalaHarris I think I was pretty clear. It is both sad and funny… https://t.co/BofEt7fEA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[“There is no fear in love. But perfect love drives out fear, because fear has to do with punishment. The one who fe… https://t.co/IgpEA9JcDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[If any of my lady followers are a size 9 in jeans lmk I have about 20 pairs, 75% of them with the tags still on!]]></document></documents></author>