<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ABC Whenever this dude opens his mouth our credibility as a country takes another hit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capturing carbon: Can it save us? By ⁦@cenmag⁩ https://t.co/mChUa2jUmm #ClimateChange #NegativeEmissionTechnology #NETs #CarbonCapture]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lewism1986 @NYGiantsRush Do you really think a 22 year old Haskins can't move as well as a 38 year old Eli 😂 C'mon… https://t.co/PQEOsvXz8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TulsiGabbard We are supporting you and donating to your campaign. #Tulsi2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Break 2019 Dining Services Schedule Van Dyke Stinger’s Café Closes Thursday March 7th at 5:00pm Hometown Clo… https://t.co/IKEnwgGFVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Correct me if I am wrong; but, didn't Obama do something arguably similar  BTW I gave @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/pgh3f3Wf5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe ya box trash to them if it don’t get a reaction outta them🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[A photo from yesterday’s @teamforkids Saturday long run up the Hudson River bike path. Great day to be outside. 📷:… https://t.co/ONcL8aNCwo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the principle of the situation the cowboys suck but I support them through everything 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[No matter what we say, think or feel. No matter what laws we pass. The Word of God will not change or be compromise… https://t.co/pyOViJFtfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[EVEN BETTER THAN I WAS THE LAST TIME BABY! OOOH OOH OOH OOOH! I’M GOOD!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Magic20099 Pretty good Mike. Getting some adulting stuff done. How about yourself?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khellatw Think about all the times you was down n ppl counted you out. Then relax for a sec n take time to evaluat… https://t.co/vG6oykAtUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@insoucianse @FiveFeetApart You mean the book that was written after the movie?]]></document><document><![CDATA[watching gravity falls and fighting the urge to order a bumch of kinetic sand online]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookieSci @HehmanLab yup.  https://t.co/vtwqr0IlyM https://t.co/q27BpdcY5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re desperate for sunlight when you’re jealous of the weather in friggin’ Liverpool... #rainraingoaway https://t.co/LRJst3oG6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it over to PInnacle View MS today to visit with more of our 2019 LR Central Tiger Freshman!  Next up Is Mabelv… https://t.co/84wg6SAPWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFDukie @brianschatz I don't have a "basic science Ph.D.," I have 7 years where I researched alternative energy, f… https://t.co/2Ovrttq4oW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlternativePlacesToHaveSex Lots of room in a old Rambler https://t.co/ofkzM4xcOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both Kirito Euego and the scouts are planning their moves ahead. #AttackOnTitan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ianfroeb They're also bad at cutting through sheet metal. I tried it so you don't have to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to try a True Chef (https://t.co/0uqukUL3LZ) meal kit from @TopsMarkets. It was an exciting adventure, but… https://t.co/OZviEtKEFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JADCAL4Me In nine seasons, the only time I’ve seen trees knocked down is when the Saviors did it to block the road… https://t.co/W6tMLzjpwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I admit it..I’m an out and proud @cher fan!  #queerstakeovertwitter https://t.co/r6Fg9HqSxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@overstood I struggle with this too. I was _just_ looking at an npm package that hasn’t been updated in 2yrs, but i… https://t.co/tD2hFe5anj]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Friend” lmfaooo yeah okay it’s my fault she was staring at you all night, but ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta feeling this album gon have a lotta skips on it just like Quavo and Takeoff solo albums 😂 #Fatherof4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@975Mornings @MarcFarzetta Don’t blame Harper or Phillies.  Greedy agent mostly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBillCassidy The next time the water is swirling around our knees at least we will know that our elected officia… https://t.co/koNsdFSgdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monstershockey deliver the SHUT OUT , Deliver the Mullet Brothers Deliver @CleHostGroverMC in my book, that is a HAT TRICK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elnortelocal Pues muchos quisiéramos una concesión, no se van a salir, solo quieren hacer presión]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigchampions @billybaruiii @CaptOkland @pascalekarmona @realDonaldTrump @GavinNewsom @POTUS @DonaldJTrumpJr… https://t.co/zVB2Adv1AR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeithAtSu Considering how much a fan Bill is of Trump, I would be shocked if this happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[So very sad ......if true @JussieSmollett  has hurt so so many...hope he gets help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kait_lorraine Belted Kingfishers are always just BEKI.  Probably my favorite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shlyn_inman 😶yikes. You shouldn’t drive at night but if you do... https://t.co/lFgduuGrJW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDouglas21 @Caram3lDelight She’s already mine... she just don’t claim me on here. Everybody knows what’s up .]]></document><document><![CDATA[That ‘06 team was tough!!  Anthony Gurley &amp; Corey Lowe was a scary 1-2 punch.    Congrats @PaulConnolly43]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosen_Thorne Remember when she took a superkick from a dude wearing a shoe with thumbtacks glued on the bottom and… https://t.co/RypLxvwMYV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Fayetteville, North Carolina https://t.co/11CEclC1Xa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @BlueSt0rmRising @maydaymindy9 Gov Jay Inslee/Sen Amy Klobuchar #2020  #MightWork]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDennisDavis @arrgster @JohnDennisWEEI @DavidJonathanG3 @FritoDink @AOC @IlhanMN @lsarsour BTW, my "3rd rate" co… https://t.co/YRgKunJaIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianGrNotABot There’s no such charges for rape.  U should b ashamed of yourself throwing that word around for suc… https://t.co/06xDeUXflT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro imagine Antonio Brown to the Packers I’ll be sick to my stomach . Aaron Rodgers + Antonio Brown . They’ll have like 50 TDS lol 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlynamCSN  I really do not like how this team is playing. I do not like the coaching style  that Brown has. who co… https://t.co/SakKl4ybiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BossLife #joligarçon #cestpasmorocco #YoungEngineer @ Hilton Houston North https://t.co/iMWHCpgDyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarbradyMcCosky Fershweiler or however the fuck you spell it as interim head coach 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man is looking down today and hopefully going to see a better race today than yesterday. NASCAR you better get… https://t.co/mQ6mOmQYVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suck at texting, unless I really like u then my annoying self will double and triple text you lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wherezaldo @Schmittastic @garyvee Play is huge. And it’s where I get a lot of creativity from personally]]></document><document><![CDATA[@memneon @anitaleirfall @keithfrankish Ah intuition and knowing when and what to question and when and what not to… https://t.co/O9IsIWRqJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 I hope @mattgaetz ends up in the same prison with @MichaelCohen212.  Matt can be Cohen’… https://t.co/DsGm3oI5S0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked this morning on my show (check it out on itunes) if the #Preds were equipped for the playoffs... talent wis… https://t.co/k5exOfj5aM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about random shit in the shower and forgot if I even shampoo’d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sentantiq I think it’s “quae volumus, et credimus libenter et, quae sentimus ipsi, reliquos sentire speramus” “Wha… https://t.co/PMCuDnkFSN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii It could've been about any meeting. My hearing's pretty good, but, doubt I would've heard a whisper fr… https://t.co/8yPs2PYATT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clevergalCA @STEWest @RickPetree He may be mimicking his favorite personalities: dictators frequently use body doubles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just took a tour of the @Ableton offices in Pasadena. I love it. These are my prople. ❤️🙌😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ChrissyNae Drink some Herb 🌿 ☕️ tea, take a Laxative, good hot bath 🛀 and good rest will do the job.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very pleased to celebrate Chinese New Year at the Taiwan Merchants Association of Toronto gala along with many of m… https://t.co/dzBA3eu0J8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring value to your customer and you won’t feel like you’re “selling”.  It’s how I excelled in mortgages. I was sol… https://t.co/IHqCLshIZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science has a hard time combating what we're doing - yet all your "theories" completely ignore science and reason. #BehindTheCurve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wouldn’t want to play softball at Cocoa Beach on March 8th?  Good luck CCM softball!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@forcedexit Any literate person would see that the antecedent of ‘it’ is ‘treatment’!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@landaeta_javier @krampaw @orbnord @ninopagliccia @SenSanders @ConsuladoVenVan @Redconaicop @camilateleSUR Far from… https://t.co/jXobADHQen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some highlights from our 5th annual Basketball Without Borders Global Camp at @nbaallstar 🌎🏀🌍🏀🌏🏀 #bwbglobal… https://t.co/lQbo2VNJT1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The win in the house ?? You missed that little tidbit, Dumb Donnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gonna be me and  @KingRey_71 embarrassing our family and friends when we’re 60 lolol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwestr I stand corrected, I had no idea I could get a modem for my original computer but I guess I could. I'm only feeling kinda old now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I realize it's not just Melina it's @trishstratuscom and @AmyDumas and @JackieMooreTx and @Madusa_rocks and Bertha… https://t.co/BS66OJwRSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow @silviabril "Juego De Juegos" translates to; "Game Of Games" lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This exactly what I been wanting to tweet I just couldn’t put it into words]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam @dexybailman Nobody gives one fuck about what that racist pig thinks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s going to be hard to beat this starting line-up...The second generation of Incognito.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Surabees @DonaldJTrumpJr NOT. So biased and unfair. If it was not for corruption Dems could not survive!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if I am paying for my so called sins.  People know what I did and I have changed.  I wonder if this is why… https://t.co/ugaL14wXlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jairo_winck Se ele quisesse jogar seria um grande jogador. O problema é que quando ele foi para LA já era porque n… https://t.co/i4oVeIgXSJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting pumped for Senior Night! Thanks @ladyindiancoach @FearTheCavalier https://t.co/RWkx2CxWIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CleFoodAndBrews @willmyersjr Definitely. Highly recommend watching twitch and subscribing so you can get the file.… https://t.co/ppN6tlZXJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeSacksEsq @jadler1969 Relitigating this is too much fun for a Thursday night. Let’s save it for Saturday night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlziplocked That humans are nothing but propagation systems for genetic material.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Shake Chocolate Porter by @BoulderBeerCo at @denairport — https://t.co/JcqPPnjm6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao never gets old. Guarantee these two kids are best friends too. Buddy in the striped shirt already knew what st… https://t.co/tXiOBAJQpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RedforEd Leader in Marxist Magazine: Teachers Must Embrace Community Organizing https://t.co/f5ozWCH7ni]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/FE024ib6TA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurrayBarstool @Bucks Glad someone picked him up after Timberwolves let him go]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KassandraSeven @LindseyGrahamSC @seanhannity @FoxNews Tune out FOX prapaganda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayDoll1010xl This just in Ryan Smolka gets a long term deal before Bryce Harper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 of the challenge to post covers of 7 books I have in my queue: no explanations, no reviews, just a cover. I’l… https://t.co/w7qQ0Nr5Gn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelCutone I read this as “breaded curtain” and I’ve been daydreaming for 15 minutes now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was to try and do this I’ll be missing some fingers maybe a hand 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kingkeraun @KingJames @BET That’s what the brothers do ... cap is a sell out... for settling]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever wana see me angry just mention the Cardinals screwing Spielman out of a 3rd round comp pick (Bradford).… https://t.co/3MAZy7LaUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The calm before the storm.  #WarriorUnlimitedMA and floyds_shorei_ryu_karate representing Central Coast out here in… https://t.co/MrzYztp3Mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb. 26th 2019 Day 2981: 30 min LISS Cardio with Arm Work with My Brother and Mentor Sagi 👊🏼💚💪🏼 • • • • •… https://t.co/mRbU1IK39M]]></document><document><![CDATA[The entire Star Wars Galaxy cast just had a full blown debate about whether or not Gretchen’s hair from ‘Recess’ wa… https://t.co/LuC3O2SSkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 3: Midland Dow 33, @CALadyCavs 29. Molly Davis with all 10 of Dow's third-quarter points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet wait a fucking minute. who asked her and who is she to say shit anyway? fox fake news? oh hell no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make-A-Wish surprises 12-year-old cancer survivor with trip to Costa Rica in Jersey Mike's https://t.co/q4w8KzBHMz… https://t.co/lY0JTkKdVY]]></document></documents></author>