<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Aaron Feis Jaime Guttenberg  Martin Duque Chris Hixon Scott Beigel Alaina Petty Gina Montalto Alyssa Alhadeff Meado… https://t.co/xGfKk2O5Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[After today, I have so much respect for people that shoot weddings for a living. Stuff is not easy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thdmichaelbell @THDhulecki @THDJAKEM @LegalleyF @RonSerpaio @scottwhiteHD @michael_HDE @StaceyTank @THDRyanSilcott… https://t.co/CVsMK4sUMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️ “Venezuelan opposition leader calls for demonstrations before his return to country”  https://t.co/Vg9HsVDB5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@originalfrazzel Yes. Now I have an excuse to have some today 🙂Thank you for making me aware of this important research.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t let my sister in my room...but yeah I’d probably give her a kidney]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the brand new TNT amusement  episode  #1469 if you're not subscribed please like And subscribe https://t.co/fzf5Jy6jC2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those who spend their time looking for the faults in others, usually spend no time to correct their own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for the train to get going. Heading  north to Kent for work again. Just about to bite into my beef brisket… https://t.co/oTvWe16bQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sent an email to FD's Customer Support. Got the automatic response saying I'd hear back on the next business toda… https://t.co/gH5boKjoUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[WALKJ OFF! Kjerstad wins it for the Hogs with a single in the ninth, and Arkansas wraps up an opening weekend sweep… https://t.co/rEZ4EEICY1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Dear President Brainless, Say all you want about @RepAdamSchiff but we still like what he's going… https://t.co/ryd5wfA95O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aubreyhagle What have I said that is wrong? Science and statistics prove everything I've said]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSAdams @Encrypgen - the only marketplace for genetic data giving all of us control over our data and providing… https://t.co/cm7dsR8912]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz Yes, the emperor has no clothes. I speak Spanish and the dialogue was dull and unbelievable  cinema verite ? Cinema ennui]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last night before I go. Thanks Mike G. @3lau @dhorvippromoter @timenightcluboc #timenightclub #orangecounty… https://t.co/kaltQh8Jag]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juvabu1 @kharyp @dailykos Daily Kos is a pretty influential site for progressives. The founder, @markos is a pragm… https://t.co/X0chOy7vNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great day with Salado ISD @NASA_Johnson. Lucky to work with @NASAEPDC and @NASAedu https://t.co/iWLqEaUcEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I knew anything about sports, I’d make a sports reference here. But, Go Books! 📖 🏀 https://t.co/EFTfQTyMxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man Something ain’t right ice rain in San Diego and snow in Vegas ... somebody playing with nature🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@david_hanselman @ChrisMartzWX @clause61 @SteveSGoddard @MatthewHavicon @InTimeLiving @MLBinWA @realPitBullDog… https://t.co/7qCF24Y7yU]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1863 Lincoln gave the Emancipation Proclamation freeing all slave in the southern states. Did congress vote on t… https://t.co/CL6Ga6VL8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth @realDonaldTrump They passed a resolution condemning it.  Told him to resign. Can't force him thou… https://t.co/HxTiVgbrPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning beautiful people of #twitter #lafayette #louisianamodel #nudehousekeeper going on #cam soon see you th… https://t.co/FGkzHfnsWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a year or two of serving as the doll in this real-life dollhouse, the babies would go on to homes in adoptive… https://t.co/CAMMU7UhVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VometCometCapt Good. I was a freshman in 2010. I don’t even remember what made those yrs worse...I suspect fratlan… https://t.co/6KdiGDBu1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always look forward to the yearly snap from @Mr_JPibb driving in the mall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I see in print that someone is involved in a simulated game at spring training, I always picture a bunch o… https://t.co/C4rYG6VSLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmoneyResists @NYCRobyn @GOP I don’t find his parenting safe. I really think child protective services should step… https://t.co/bXRYpYBfuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misseagleLIIna He better Burn the Redskins twice. Year. IJS and now that Landon Collins is in Washington, I hope h… https://t.co/DfF408LyjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BOsPfzdSOJ #55 on the list Duane Glass. Holds lots of titles such as a state champion but my personal favorite is Grandpa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight @KingRicochet was great, but if u wanna look that great u need someone that makes you look awesome , we nee… https://t.co/qARSghQpD8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If she really did this she has no place in any kind of leadership, what she needs is help in being humble]]></document><document><![CDATA[@28delayslater Had to negotiate for my keys back. She borrowed the X on Monday and was lobbying to drive it again.… https://t.co/FQOPMoybQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rottenplanet Exactly. There’s been at least one or two released since that one, and I’m just...I’m not excited for… https://t.co/A9LTNiFleW]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case any of you were wondering.   PS. Still petty AF. ☺️ @ Bryarton Village, Raleigh, North Carolina https://t.co/xzzd1Ghf9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hella_Apocrypha Ahaha, wayyyy too good. I do not deserve to be in the presence of, nor even aware of the existence of, such grandeur.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bring on Atlas, the Buckets and the Sandbags #sanjose #letsgo thanks for helping to get me ready coachserj… https://t.co/GhrrXNRUAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another day working on my craft #FitLeaders. Today was 315x3. The focus is dialing in and the body is responding.… https://t.co/ulFJCszGJ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elsebas_2419 @GuerrerosDRCs @hierro_santiago @emirmontoya @VolveremosMashi @EcuadorSinParo @Loslengualarga… https://t.co/AyCh1kORs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@women_want_more @rawhidevelvet @keilahbeeherrin @TheBenRyan @JuliaBell00 @thewomenofcoun @criticallycu… https://t.co/I14P3TRLJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GIJay4400 @MargaritaLewis1 @NPR Lets remember US aid was denounces by the Red Cross as a political ploy today. If… https://t.co/ZJZc29aAU9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @MjrCitiesChiefs @MCSheriffs It’s just like anything you have good cops and you have… https://t.co/rlYiZ2xiMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jvplive @VestaDear @Ilhan @IlhanMN @JVPDCMetro @jvpliveNY @JVPPhilly @JVP_LA @ChicagoJVP @JVPSeattle https://t.co/JXGZuQ2cxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fredgatesdesign @NY1 East 90th between York and 1st. Closer to York, near the Avis Car Rental (the building they t… https://t.co/YfTfNYJIMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sports Media Guy: Player salaries and the Sport Ethic  https://t.co/4OOOlVPpm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StansburyShow listening to yesterdays podcast. Also love Christine McVie couldn’t agree with you more. #StansburyShow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBSkyen @RiotYuka That doesn't say he's her father though, just that he'd protect her like one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Boy I hate “insert stupid thing here” Me with a Girlfriend: Boy I love “said stupid thing”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon says farewell to SOS Dennis Richardson https://t.co/OZVPkzxtc3 via @Salem_Statesman]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhosterhoudt @TheOrangeCone For my dollar, I’d rather see 2 mains on a well prepped track than 5 on a used up track.]]></document><document><![CDATA[SeverL people yesterday told me that they are discussing this book with their student leaders.  They said “how to t… https://t.co/18UPXCBE03]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. When he says "and so many other clues," I was literally crying LOL. @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/Yoqzpetr6J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great event tonight in Shelbyville @ShelbyKyGOP Lincoln Dinner talking about the great accomplishments of the… https://t.co/c28brYLJ2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should get this “W” but Zion going down altered Duke’s game. Especially on the Defensive side and in the paint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing same but have not confirmed.  They are expecting a blizzard in these parts tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have to say it’s pretty cool to play with awesome musicians you went to school with! @utsamusic #mariachi… https://t.co/ZK0yTpXjs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Well, not really. She compared Trump’s border wall to the Berlin Wall. Trump’s wall has nothing to do… https://t.co/T5mSi59f5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some live on the inside, some die @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/HrWkl3MvRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sleepifoxxi @TaxBeast @vaelophis This is why I've joined the #Fandom to AVOID being like Katy who wants to see Non… https://t.co/iM8kvTszSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedZone921 I’ve come up with nothing online this AM since you mentioned the old gymnasium where Men’s basketball o… https://t.co/VSpfI9SGJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potter_kitty @MattWalshBlog Conservatives didn't picket Mr. Rogers' funeral. Westboro led by Fred Phelps did  Who… https://t.co/NoSllZOWq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wfaa I know it has been awhile, but while I was working in Big D 8 years ago, I really enjoyed your news-particula… https://t.co/RxYDM8bXWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Payton showed me this life sim game and here are some highlights https://t.co/JAYcT3Spcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah and a snowman. (Hannah is in the pink coat.) @ Pakrul Compound https://t.co/kZHXsPdkg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDovey @CoachBKU @JamesConner_ @Ogthetruth @coachTcsm @CoachMoseOUAZ @CoachGilford @CoachDovenberg… https://t.co/E7Wcar1947]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must impeach Trump. In turn removing these liars and traitors. Some in jail and some of them are going to jail. https://t.co/Ow90SJE32u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retioMTY Rápido!! pongan una gorda del lado izquierdo que de voltea esa madre!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just hit my 1000 in Apex Bois.   The bread is sweet. 🍞😩🤘🏻🔥 https://t.co/qsG8ANazYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also was so busy having fun this weekend didn’t get any of my codes 😂😂😂😂😂 oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[إِنْ هِوَيْتُونَـا هِويْناكُـم  وْبَنْتِصَبَّـرْ لَـيْ جِفَيْتـونـا   مَا عَرَفنا اْليـاسِ وِيّاكُـم  وِيـنْ بَتسيـ… https://t.co/7e21jvshBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madeleintlSUR El chavismo lleva 20 años saboteando el sistema eléctrico venezolano. Pregunte a cualquier ingeniero electricista venezolano.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to former @wwe Superstar @mrkenanderson #HappyBirthdayKenAnderson @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/4P6ziQ3PZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Xbox If I can re-experience the Left 4 Dead games, now that me and my friends are older, I think I would relive so… https://t.co/ZMpCkfvVKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phew not a good couple of shifts and a bad end to the 2nd for the #Preds]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just a reminder: we made up the concept of Hours.  And numbers.  And arbitrarily assigned any particular number to… https://t.co/wolfOyModT]]></document><document><![CDATA[And no one is happier than @Kurkjian_ESPN... free from the shackles of Clearwater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ryguy047 @Daily2deuce That's the point haha. They're just scrambling to find a way to get "people from Philly" mad… https://t.co/KYV9tgfyl8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LollyDaskal Isn’t this hard to internally manage, even though you know? Influences affect and can impact drive and… https://t.co/D1GnVjvTpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 things I know.  1) I have not seen A Star Is Born on its 4th remake and 2) Shallow really isnt a good song and co… https://t.co/5xo2qmmxbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithkg6 @Raynall21 @tongue_inteeth @BuffaloWins I listed them because many people have asked about that and respo… https://t.co/XU7rpIMKa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bucks are out LIVE on cam - https://t.co/kTL5C4Ylcr https://t.co/l4xHHm1XtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I, for one, am pretty terrified that the FBI could "autonomously" invoke the 25th Amendment, needing the agreement… https://t.co/en7z4hRMil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy Nothing is too low for the left !!!!  They are stooping to new levels !!!!  What a douche bag !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaw_parquet and get all of my genealogy courses done so that I can get a job without feeling like I’m overextending myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkKaboly People, like you, making comments like this, are starting to sound even more insane than AB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UpdateDuke @gobigorgohome71 Yeah they’re way behind schedule. Miami game is almost 24 hours away]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, but you know how delicious salty &amp; sweet things like salted carmel taste Sven? It’s just like that!… https://t.co/ogpfB1NvOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ San Diego Zoo Safari Park https://t.co/2NXBuj1hGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just landing at JFK....It's cold here   . @ John F. Kennedy International Airport https://t.co/OztyfvtYuI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s only Tuesday and I’m ready for the weekend! Need something fun to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet has been showing up on my TL every Sunday for the past eight years and it still rings true]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and the hometown hero ejaaz at snoopdogg Pre Grammy Party at the Snoop’s Compound.....Shoutout to… https://t.co/SGFnp3Qypt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickyDavila @marklindaisagi1 They were raised to read and eat the evidence]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo Charles B just said Jussie could have saved all that time and money. He should have called Liam Neeson. He would… https://t.co/XjWgvxS5qi]]></document><document><![CDATA[impulsively got my ear pierced last week and today I impulsively got a tattoo .... who am I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haktuar Yea bro shit is just twisted and fucked up, idek if it’s worth me going thru the trouble of getting a lawyer at this point]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Danielcoutz oh man. I can see what you mean with that one. with it being a men's retreat, since you know your audi… https://t.co/pz9ly3ztYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s time for the #WoffordTerriers to be in the Top 25!  With tonight’s blowout win over 22-5 UNCG, there is no dou… https://t.co/HCIcIpMGDM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKidIndigo I had to give you the bowling smoke bro. I couldn’t help it]]></document></documents></author>