<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Delicate #iHeartRadio #iHeartAwards #BestMusicVideo @taylorswift13 @iHeartRadio @taylornation13 i💛TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Natalies going to be 20 in August, Miles will be 16 in July....where the fuck did my babies go!!! Why do they grow… https://t.co/OvGnAOw0gV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek @uvinjo_us He's Absolutely right and as someone who was raised by my parents to have respect and self wor… https://t.co/6BiDdxwh8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the reasons I don’t want to have children is because of how terrible children are treated in the US.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder I will not support a candidate who maligns this country in front of the world.Stand up,wave the flag,b… https://t.co/6fb7wFKsEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Not aware of erosion of trust and should have been.’ - @JustinTrudeau #SNCLavelin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else have a chicken that bathes in or near their water bowl?! Baby Henna also refuses to dust bathe and… https://t.co/STpwpNTJId]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AmericanIdol y’all just may have saved a life with putting the suicide prevention number up after the final audition 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love online boutiques, don’t get me wrong but every time I find something I really like it’s sold out in my size.… https://t.co/yneE5wHxEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[But without strong community benefit agreements and the upward push on rents...those better services won’t be reali… https://t.co/gPFQUUX1tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women's to all beautiful ladies,  #womensday #womendance #ladystyling #empoweringwomen Today dont forget to c… https://t.co/qelwXSKPkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: The score and the music from #BlackPanther are not the same. There’s a soundtrack and a separate score. Y… https://t.co/LGk9f6zb4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[DRUG ADDICT AND A PEDOPHILE WHO LIKED TO DATE UNDER AGE GIRLS...BUT WHITE DIDN’T CARE ABOUT HIS CRIMINAL ACTIVITIES… https://t.co/Mvz3rFN5iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall ever just sit in the car after getting home and chilling before going inside]]></document><document><![CDATA[the first thing emily said to me when she saw me tonight was “oh my god i forgot how short you are” ugh 8 years of friendship going strong 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 He needs to be punished because he is very dangerous to set there and lie with a straight face no te… https://t.co/gnhcIj97Ur]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ser mamá es poder decir con orgullo "Ese fue un buen eructo"  y seguir con tu vida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StormyDaniels you are my hero and I’m so excited for you to develop your craft and see your stuff! I hope the gate… https://t.co/Jy8wyGCYjU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visualize the end goal minus the barriers, believe, and work like hell. Be the crazy one doing something bold (if t… https://t.co/k5L6huG4mh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people make fake accounts to lurk on someone. I will never understand that shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister I think we call that getting the evidence before we throw out accusations. We’re just getting our “d… https://t.co/1uFYaI3hEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stoked to say I was in the same building as shirtless @brendonurie 🥰🥰 @PanicAtTheDisco #prayforthewickedtour2019 https://t.co/tFVd7zfrT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlmeidaUlci @SenadorRogerio @jairbolsonaro Olha só quem está falando 😂😂😂 Só assim pra vc aparecer @SenadorRogerio… https://t.co/Gorwa7Hosj]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE HOUSE MIGHT HAVE PASSED IT BUT IT STILL HAS TO GO BEFORE SENATE !!!!!  LEARN ABOUT HOW OUR GOVERNMENT WORKS !!!… https://t.co/aiI8YZ3pUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hahaha_kitty I use it to send in my timesheets for work  since it makes it a pdf and I don’t have to send a bunch of pictures]]></document><document><![CDATA[In tears! Love, love, love Adam Lambert &amp; Queen opening. #Oscars #Queen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to create a space where voicing opinions, emotions and concerns without involving arguing. Shits hard especi… https://t.co/vHk5uAGnp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Lent! For those who are Catholic, have a happy 40 days. What are you giving up for Lent?  ✝️✝️✝️ https://t.co/kadjN4QEoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶whoever said money can’t buy your problems, must not have had enough money to solve em 🤑]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kev13F @EvaShadowgirl18 @Putneyman Canadian Geese who knows what they're thinking Kev!! BTW Only just now saw this… https://t.co/rdRey8oerR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CivicCommonsUS @knightfdn @cherrystpier I’d love to nominate Sarah! Let me know if there’s interest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johniadarola Omg John...not funny.   Not sure I like you any more after that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like that they give you good solar quotes with no risk. California Solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar… https://t.co/fnWY1pGPhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanIsntFine @DWImpalaOwner Ummmmm.....  full frontal???? I couldn't read it out of respect to Dean]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAPHNTR @NWSHanford It pains me to say that I didn’t have time :( but I’ll definitely make a trip for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[you should but laypeople will STILL find a way to try to tell you what the law is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKhakpour I feel so bad for you.  I to have had depression. The only thing that helped me was when they put me on… https://t.co/pndQEh7015]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again he sides with a murderer. Hard to believe an American President stands head and shoulders with a drspot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Whiny white privileged male just like @realDonaldTrump. Like father like son]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to read a chapter of this book,before I head back to the concourse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnimalRescue @shaunwalters041 1/3 of "humans" are actually not humans at all. They have no souls. Those are the… https://t.co/CbjRZRCW4e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdrjbray @PalmerReport @realDonaldTrump Trump got 3M less votes than the other candidate that's how many he got in election.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealEvilHRLady I don’t think they share it as much as this scientist would like.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportingKC @KansasRaceGirl @danielsalloi #FanAppreciationMatch #SKCvPHI @dega_boy_87 @Pixxydoodle @4judyblue… https://t.co/583HKB80Hl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still together with my man-go after all these years 💛🧡💛😁😍 . . . . . . . . . . #fruitmeal #monomeal #fruit… https://t.co/DRxd7uhnNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If listening to Hozier's music doesn't make you feel something deep in the pit of your soul like one of the old god… https://t.co/8UhoV5B6Sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cami_augie @michelleike “Who sings I will always love you... WRONG ITS DOLLY PARTON”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we know what Ruth Bader Ginsburg was doing @CNN https://t.co/7WKLmn6Ldw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indiegogo Hey, I'm supporting this fundraiser, please have a look - 'funds for my son to pay hospital bills' https://t.co/SdXVZBX1RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mood. . #Repost theanticrystal ・・・ Because everyone loves a #sunset and a #llama.  #breakingtheruleofthirds @ Mill… https://t.co/nIpYl4rKGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the the best amazing twin brothers I know @benjimadden and @JoelMadden 🎂🎈🎉🍾]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BLT (bacon, lobster, tomato) Benedict @BlueHeavenKW did not disappoint. Thanks for the recommendation… https://t.co/Mpo7LXtHvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeenMom A million times over YES! These two are amazing parents ! Cole is her dad! Paperwork doesn’t change that b… https://t.co/k20ST05Dnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[No explanation is needed! Ladies listen up! This is the future! #enoughsaid #herfuture @ Idaho State Capitol https://t.co/yQYVY6YwTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @SenateDems @HouseDemocrats  get ur shit together or we will be on the losing end of the 2020 elections!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is a little Beach Therapy for anyone needing a little Happiness! Looking to Live The… https://t.co/6CkSCximQV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we pass a bill excusing a parent for assaulting another person who kisses their child on the face/hands? Bc https://t.co/1pwxtsfUzi]]></document><document><![CDATA[anxiety is so real and so scary and i really need tips on how to lessen it or something bc i’m dealing with this ev… https://t.co/pVcEF3u1Qt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #chickenfrancese with #garliccauliflowerrice and #everythingbutthekitchensinksalad #TQOFE #blogger #writerslife… https://t.co/xTj1U7IsxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[was 62 on the beach today and people in florida were we wearing winter parkas, mittens, hats and scarfs.... UR KIDDING!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting in our Airbnb in Seattle reading a book next to Rico as he naps before our last night in Seattle. And i… https://t.co/FAwnm0igTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is the head of the campaign and therefore responsible for what subordinates have done( we ALL KNOW under his… https://t.co/7zHxioqcsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shakeyourbooty #partdeux with my #gg my #girlygirl iveronicamann 😘😘😘💃🏽💃🏽💃🏽 #rarh #goodtimes #torreypines… https://t.co/ubPXSYBpSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Detail from today’s painting 🍈🍈🍈 . . . . #painting #contemporaryart #oilpainting #melon #hangingmelon… https://t.co/e0nshaK8qA]]></document><document><![CDATA[MARCH 16: The Dollop Podcast comes to @CarolinaDurham: https://t.co/AnAZUHpnhx https://t.co/vOkjwk0RwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferSharpTN @beckyalbertalli @angiecthomas https://t.co/qdA3XpZUaV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shannonrwatts @MomsDemand Who’s gonna tell these assholes that’s not how anal beads work? #NHPolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man not having health insurance really hit my tax return HARD!!! I need some pepper to go with this salt.... thanks trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Impulse purchases I made this evening due to anger: String cheese Fruit cup (gotta stay healthy in times of crisis)… https://t.co/85OQ1VERxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[33/ Guess which state was the first to sign onto the Article V Convention of States project to amend the US Constit… https://t.co/O6CxhfbGCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today's Thought!!!! 💋👄  #everybodysfit #personaltrainer #fitnessmodel @ Every BODY's Fit https://t.co/MvLGBdyOr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it time to refresh your bedroom? We have so many. PS everything is up to 40% Off today in my S6 shop. Link in my… https://t.co/NgyVgugXFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture Day today!! The boys ran off before I could take their pictures.  My gorgeous daughter is getting too grown… https://t.co/tSeEGYv0pC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Only1SeanSmith @divarobbie I am so looking forward in seeing your friend @divarobbie ‘s show. I’ve been looking forward to it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLimbaugh 😂 Definitely find the humor. Much.  She is a riot, or as they say in the south, “she’s a hoot”.   Po… https://t.co/XPJcj7d1fx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherscope @dnewhauser @AOC Ugh! I'm Latina. My Dad always said if someone doesn't like you, it's their problem.… https://t.co/w7BE6SvPtR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HauntedMeg Imagine if it was like Fatal Attraction but with a mannequin! (You still get horrifying sex plus now wi… https://t.co/JMcAi1Nok0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kross700 @JLee418 @chevychevelle48 @laura24fan @ToddTPrice24 @DaleJr88FanNate @JudyJ31830202 @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/SNhWRsc2YQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder I have to agree. I'm not a fan of his kid, either. He's just a big, ugly, mean tantrum throwing toddler. He… https://t.co/546K1zDmnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just tried to order insomnia cookies but my dumbass put the wrong address so someone just got free cookies and no… https://t.co/SHIWAmhLco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoyceWhiteVance How much of that money do you think will be allocated back to Daddy for his Wall?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me chuckle. Pusheen the Cat (Pusheen)- #Pinterest #LasQueMeGusta. https://t.co/5AUjejER0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@runmeb I have a friend in the book business who got me a comp. copy!  Loved it! I love how real you are!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've told myself that one day I will whisk a completely smooth roux. Today was ~almost~ that day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Bleed It Dry by @alterbridge on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/8JEsU4fAjd https://t.co/0OQFqaTqjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok so like i might’ve stepped in too much horse poop while on the parade route, wore dance boots for 2 hrs and then… https://t.co/0hmKpeI8zI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Cantrell notes that this bill does not prohibit anyone from exploring or understanding their sexuality in ther… https://t.co/NRBdkHYmUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swanie04uk @RamseyPrincipal @JCPSKY Thanks for all you do and let’s celebrate the defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoundRePhx @KarenG_inAZ The Latin Rat Pack strikes again... ha, cha, cha! 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle just started the pot stirring!  Lisa is not even wanting to talk about it #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevKeithBritt @NKassheimer @PockeyTony @CigarCyborg @jkbloom1 @tommortl @FayeWood17 @PreacherKeith1 @euby04… https://t.co/jV1cvyHeVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snickles1977 Wait, he pulls you over because he can’t see it but I’ve seen ones that haven’t been registered (diff… https://t.co/1tpkdIeGlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5: I accepted the challenge from @KaylaFrazao to post the covers of 7 favorite books of mine, for 7 days. https://t.co/shyOqmnQ7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[The look my cat just gave me when I took a bottle cap out of her mouth..  But umm excuse me Salem where did you even get this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck off those that block me!  Your all about yourselves stuck up assholes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok after putting this NY video together I can honestly say it’s coming out really good!!!  just one more piece I ne… https://t.co/sgYZwKzAcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickhogan4real and I are real excited to try these spicy nuggs @BurgerKing don’t let us down https://t.co/DGHihQ7tE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimberlyCWood Very short fact sheet for him tonight.  And Zion is on the bench so what else can he talk about??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steve_runquist I didn't even know that flying pushups were a thing, impressive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bev0723 Gas terrifies me. Took years for me to embrace a gas cooktop (and a father in law who would light his ciga… https://t.co/h2qR0bFQXm]]></document></documents></author>