<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Omw to get an exclusive #DESUSandMERO MetroCard. Make sure to cop your own before they run out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get better everyday, week, month and crush the year! #orangetheoryfitness #strengthday @ Orangetheory Fitness Trian… https://t.co/L14nYVpDcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgleasonicps ok Danny, you can have Invert Zoo back. I can't keep up. I keep finding myself saying "for the purpos… https://t.co/ey3Lgpi4p2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LawMurrayTheNU @JonesOnTheNBA It's not just +/-. But your tweet was, and that's what I was responding to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #udel Newark campus and other UD locations in New Castle County (including the @UDLibrary) will open at 11am on… https://t.co/SwDYry1GaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani What a beautiful soul. I felt her encouragement. Lucky man @TWooodley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YairNetanyahu @ZviHauser איזה חמוד, הוא בטוח שליברמן וכחלון לא מתים להחליף ולהעיף את הביב שהם מזלזלים בו כל היום.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit them LSU boys need to be running Olympic Track! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸 @DevinWhite__40 @G_Will29 lighting that combine up. #GeauxTigers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra What is her IQ, lets have her Take a SAT ...test...she does not have enough attainable knowledge to d… https://t.co/9RIWOuk1ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RdubHall @jaredcwilson It was definitely A Band Called David for that tour. Not sure the personnel. Im sure you’re correct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Taylorville Tornadoes 2019 Baseball will host Morrisonville/ Raymond Lincolnwood tomorrow at 4pm. The field is… https://t.co/e9n0uG8IBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LowellMiller17 @Robertfritz33 @RapidRiverLures @thgrace78_grace Crazy Yooper!😜😂😂😂👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@escapedacult @thedailybeast That's the most ridiculous theory I have ever heard]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/fJZKCmRSMG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @realDonaldTrump Maybe you should take a look in a mirror. Trump is a great president.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @NavyFederal Credit Union in Webster, TX https://t.co/10nviPCD31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sd90_43mac @dane @yogurtboy @facebook @Google Most major sites are primarily v6. Those left on IP classic only wil… https://t.co/fZ6a2G98HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andy_Staples The @Whataburger honey butter chicken biscuit might beat them all fwiw...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LPetrelliTV @Budweiser You don't  realize how big they are until you're next to one]]></document><document><![CDATA[Borgman compares Starburst to Hadapt. Big difference is Starburst is open source. And guess what? They're profitabl… https://t.co/5AKdotVcFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tof71784 @NickSwardson I am going raspberries, strawberries and blackberries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChildersRadio Won't matter.  Fans don't flock to stadiums and TV sets to see a particular HS player.They tune in t… https://t.co/cYanATydxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJones_32 @kdkseven @BalailDr @AOC BOSTON u grad.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Grade8 page1 any… https://t.co/T8sdAdeUwN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FknSaid @CryptMidwest @OddNMacabre @KirkMcCall3 @Halloween_1014 @sootygrunter79 @XGlamourGhoul @Horror_Disciple… https://t.co/znATIllWAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frostgirl11 It looks like PARADISE! I'd do anything to go there to escape this CRAZY WORLD we live in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nuggets got crushed again by @warriors! Until they can defend,  their playoff run will be short. When @warriors ar… https://t.co/pXrohhUoPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tommy is now being “hounded” by the puppawrazzi! @PetsforPatriots @HumaneSociety @emaysway @whatwouldDOOdo @wwp… https://t.co/ZPBkYH4mHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5PCfxo6Dbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, I have realized that no matter what I do, my brother won’t get his head out of his ass long enough to… https://t.co/dDmWOfVJH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the Clinton’s and Democratic’s should pay for it not OUR TAX DOLLARS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarrettHaake Very cool  Even cooler that your dad was Jesuit-educated too #AMDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleycroftgolf best of luck at Wild Cat Invitation Arizona , swinging the club nicely englishman1958 @thepga… https://t.co/2sz6THubzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@favor8art They really need to and must step outside the "Laker family" when hiring for the FO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was delicious! Thank you Dr. Harvey! Look forward to another Great day in the Valley!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning brings a new trailer for Joanna Hogg’s Sundance Grand Jury Prize winner THE SOUVENIR. Just beautiful!… https://t.co/JOi2dH8V7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexgomez18 @NicolasMaduro te aseguro que el numero es mucho mayor, seguramente en el interior del país murieron m… https://t.co/FPCn013wyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann This is like the Russian bed pee incident. He’s a germaphobe who doesn’t drink - hello.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made it down to the Island. Mardi Gras Galveston starts tomorrow. Time to get crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makloubae But it is a capital offense in your religion #IslamIsTyranny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen This is so correctly and succinctly stated! 👏👏👏👏 #bravo #Thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend and I have both slipped and fallen on ice in my driveway today. I’m dying.   Those who slip and fall… https://t.co/hCydgmnVov]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dre__cole Oh you have no idea....get here NOW!! https://t.co/N2rC2PIK7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast Respectfully... @AOC is a socialist... just a hair above a commie.  @realDonaldTrump is a capitalist... in… https://t.co/HfD6THbMGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SherrodBrown @TrueFactsStated I agree people over 50 need insurance but drop the age to 62 first and see how that… https://t.co/DaObeHncX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like The Office episode where Kevin shortens his words to save time....]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tomato #spinach #tofu soup...and #integralblanco #bread   yep. the best thing about winter is #homemade #soup.… https://t.co/HgZ5n1UwMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @Skrippy33 for getting me back on the Magic the Gathering train. Not sure if I should be praising or c… https://t.co/7GCw8aS1mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanavannn @F_ckMyTweets She won, and then a producer offered her a solo deal and she dipped right out. I think the… https://t.co/SmzAYVY99n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrkLovely1 Sadly, that is true Lovely One. Good evening my friend! 👋🏾😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[No other culture in the 🌎 has transformed so drastically in such a short period of time. We ❤️ to reference Africa… https://t.co/iJly92z8jL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll be in the same dugout, @StanfordBSB for the game #2 [or dos in espanol]  BCC ESPN the Ocho +1 https://t.co/EDrOWtzGdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadDrahn44 Yes sir!! I’m definitely ready for warmer days!! Have a great day and week, Chad! ☕️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're boyfriends so jealous you can respond to a Twitter reply run before he kidnaps you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Soundole I had a good laugh with @slamb0b and @LauraIntravia reading this aloud over breakfast]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank u guys for all the love and support since the beginning @_UnderTheRadar_ 🙌🏽🤝 #2GBTG #JuiceCounty 🥤🍊]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week Trevor and Trenton Jenkins of Jinx Machine/thejenkinstwins and Tim and beksmallwood of @kevinandbek joine… https://t.co/lw7ahdnmx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meditation Words... Think About It 🤔🙏🏿🇮🇱🇺🇸🙏🏿 @ Florida's 14th Congressional District https://t.co/NHisqM5wtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Everyone west of Manhattan will think he's anything but a joke!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyCohen136 @FrankyG_ Bam, but it's only a matter of time before that changes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KQUEENSALLIANCE @regrann @1Rayvon lawg Mon. @emprezkilla mercy queens! respect https://t.co/4jQzESQqtS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud @soccermomTEX @Teri_A_Adams Anyone saying it should be now or taken off the table my statement applies… https://t.co/SpeDww5jYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Steve Scalise: Nancy Pelosi has to remove Rep. Ilhan Omar from the Foreign Affairs Committee… https://t.co/2Ok2cMo5Q7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you baby Jesus for offsides (when in our favor) https://t.co/h6rt7orrKo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PasqualeRotella on @InsomniacRadio is getting me hyped for @EDC_MEXICO   Can’t wait for @Excision this weekend 🦖 https://t.co/23DORvavgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful #ThingsWeShouldTalkAbout  Pregnancy Resource Centers and their compassionate contribution to those struggl… https://t.co/nGAvgQFoxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMcElwee Better yet, they should organize a fundraising dinner themselves, to raise money for Feinstein's next… https://t.co/Lovhk8wzUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgse @SXSWEDU @HarvardEdLD T   Va cygclc yateuypgdyptyrcy ygcg by f termr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my brilliant former graduate student Zach as he embarks on this crazy and wonderful adventure!… https://t.co/OE0OCPXoMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My response is how does he know that is best case? Best case would be if he played 30 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @politico Of course there is this information because the Trump administration has done nothing to… https://t.co/ixlJKFQ460]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCBrigade14 @now_bham @bhambackline So happy to see this. Something special is starting... https://t.co/JeEz8qNaZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta get out and vote,  even for the local elections. 🇺🇸 @ West Hollywood, California https://t.co/yz9qTIktqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckySmirks @RepAdamSchiff @amazon @JeffBezos Still laughing here, too. 😂 I love the Tweets that the President men… https://t.co/rmjfiIKxxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Gracias por ayudarme a llegar a los 25 seguidores! ¿Qué otras personas te parece que deberían seguirme? Se prendio… https://t.co/QHwGWAmWqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best high you can have is having somebody there you at the end of every day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@verygooster @BigBlueUnited It still doesn’t make sense. We both have no idea if any winning team wanted anything t… https://t.co/aXliqnv7D2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joerexrode @AdamSparks I’m with you on the other two... Live I felt had talent and a few food records and a vastly… https://t.co/i9tGNpsHVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#guggenheim #guggenheimmuseum is it a #carpark ? @ New York, New York https://t.co/itatz0NpIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, friends,  Which online photo archives/collections do you use to find publishable images? I'm looking… https://t.co/wAPQjNU2im]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: Fox News crew flees Palestinian grenades at violent Gaza riot: https://t.co/0khGhORI4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelMarie222 @KimKardashian They are calabassas roses and are actually 3 ft tall. Kenny G is in fact 7 ft tall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlose34 Este tipo de vídeo lo vamos a ver muy seguido. Primero unas lágrimas de cocodrilo y como siempre, “me ob… https://t.co/RbhQwZxgON]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Championship Bracket (G4) - @NTBasketBall def. @EBAThunder 70-54 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRogersHood 4. You don’t know me anywhere near calling me a false prophet (you misspelled it BTW LOL).   5. You… https://t.co/jaBHsK40iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[A thorny problem but a good read  @ColoradoSun especially for everyone who voted no on last year’s Amendment 73. We… https://t.co/5lhbMsYLge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlessandraAster @AOC He happened to be on the right side of history once.  That's a good way of putting it. As I s… https://t.co/dsMWSqeYly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KwameDwase Do you think LSU self imposes and puts a ban on this year? Whatever they win is going to be taken away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeardedNolesFan Yeah I gotta do something besides school or I’m gonna go crazy. I mean it’s already a lot to keep… https://t.co/IyFwCxoe7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get a start to a WWE Raw episode without the Authority starting off every time?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBZ08650647 @ShuttleCDRKelly I don’t live in AZ. Great state tho. Had a hero as a senator. A man who your dear lea… https://t.co/9qtYmVPtqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you don't realize what you're  headed for..Embrace your creative self..Make your own path through capitalis… https://t.co/CA1QqWE0dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all won’t be disappointed! SOMEONE TAKE HER!! She’s funny, has good energy, and good to talk to😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caro_milanesi @mikahsargent @caseyliss @joesteel @dansturm Vodka is diluted alcohol. That’s literally all it is. W… https://t.co/UibyFvFmM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just went LIVE before the @CPTwolves state title game, watch the starting lineup introductions courtside here: https://t.co/3NJmeBqWX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please Ivan Duque president of Colombia help the area of your country which is flooded!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still awake, was planning on going to sleep early, guess the plans felt through 🙄😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep. If the loser of this game wins its first ACCT game, they will be a rematch on Thursday for a spot in the semif… https://t.co/49RvvjPOGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCun11960413 @GregLasak @MinaMalikForDA @MelindaKatz @RoryLancman @JoseNievesForDA @CabanForQueens… https://t.co/YnJHY8IExr]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a damn lie. You just dont like the truth.   Facts are facts bro.   You view it as hate.   I see it as hones… https://t.co/cQIPDtApUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picked up a new Mala today. The beads are big and have flat spots on it so it rolls through my hand nicer. I really… https://t.co/JFrzkfcdid]]></document></documents></author>