<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Really confuses me how many people grown people show up to the DMV without either a passport, birth certificate anything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 31st to the baddest b*tch @rihanna #HappyBirthdayRihanna https://t.co/TwHmN3YpTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norilanewink @jordynwoods What’s the t? I wanna know why everyone is mad at her! LoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[!! !! !! MISSOURI SUPREME COURT: gay man can bring employment discrimination claim under state statute for sex-ster… https://t.co/0Wh2yl238Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YCPAlumni  It's not about how much money one has, or status in life or the accolades, certificates or physical pos… https://t.co/DsZmh93Ch7]]></document><document><![CDATA[INEC is being a joke at this point. Why are votes still manually collated!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaddCompani @TheOriginalNai sheesh no wonder why this drives many to drink to soothe theire frayed nerves]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Promote #SupportIndieFilm #horror #HorrorMovies #FilmInWa #actor #producer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning and happy Friday.   We are already in March... wow. Life is crazy. Stream will be on soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jo_el97 You don’t need a man girl. You got this for you. I believe in you. I love you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[В який переклад пірнути перше? З допомогою... Щиро дякую Андрусишинові за цю коротеньку збірку слів. #переклад… https://t.co/pZmlN3DUtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a phenomenal nap on my flight, I’m still half asleep! Thanks @SouthwestAir 😍🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealXPac Sad thing is they now will probably put that animal down because of her stupidity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its Kevin Hart's Laugh Out Loud All Star Comedy slam dunk. Live NBA ALL STAR WEEKEND #hornets #nba #nbaallstar2019… https://t.co/rkGSf44Q5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dihollywood @Babatikidido @bigkstone Orange marmalade is nasty. Don’t @ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just #representing house #slytherin for the #hogwarts #houseparty splashrno  Showing off my #wand skills and using… https://t.co/FodM6RR4S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislasoya you know that this is all your fault...🤷🏽‍♂️😂😂#JustSayin #Vegas #lasvegas #palms #party #concert #linq… https://t.co/AazSLAgj7a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandrooFC_ @Josearreola222 @_mlara13 Messi prob driving the car thou 🤷🏻‍♂️🐷]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhantomXterior @AOC If that were the story, then sure, I’d be crazy. But that’s not the story. NYC just lost millions in new tax revenue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkusWagner82 Thanks for sharing! I mostly bought my copy for the Star Fox collectibles but might consider invest… https://t.co/1PDQvwcpWi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philquinn1 Glad to call him my friend.  He’s a Richmond guy that’s not just looking to move on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frankgore @buffalobills @NFL Thanks for coming to buffalo it’s an honor to have you here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KDJmedia1 Championship games are always tough- Way to go Dobbs Ferry Eagles!!  50-45 in OT - last time DF won Sect… https://t.co/09gXF1zqwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@t35ch @joanil911 @Treyarch @CallofDuty Yea I had an SnD and control like that once. We still managed to win but it… https://t.co/WMxP6ujRyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[UAE Khalifa Housing Project has been completed and ready to deliver to those lost their homes during 2008 floods ca… https://t.co/5Fa6AVRtGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My main...The Ibanez Universe UV777 with custom mirror plating by J-craft custom Japan.  #ibanez #universe… https://t.co/3YMMfcRhDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viajaVolaris Gracias Volaris...Por esos viajes tan "cómodos", "seguros" y "puntuales". 😐 Sigan así 👏. Ojo… https://t.co/ZQDpB8x8v6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JanaVugteveen @homedepot2771 @donwehner2771 @BrandonReinoehl @ELoichinger @bobsaniga Sagan is a lot #RockStar #2771inspires]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m content. In a while I feel good about myself, my future, and the people I have around me. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJEck_TV @SHSBlazers Stupid  call  a momentary hang is a controlled way of not getting hurt coming down. Nothing flagrant about that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickJRishwain Both my grandmas died and took all their recipes with https://t.co/cEtftpusHY should be passed down to the next generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoihoisado It's amazing to me how commentary is consistently the worst part of the broadcast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_canubian Isn't that awful? That's why I'm glad he's getting so much bad press. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlgardnerirl Good one (no surprise that it placed me squarely in Dublin!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brookehazexoxo @5Kporn_com Check out @brookehazexoxo's newest scene!!! Please #BookBrooke!!! #BonerInspiring… https://t.co/eL4Hu0dl65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @KatrinaPierson That’s right defend it defend distract morons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamGreenway @swbts I'll be praying for you and your family as you (Lord willing) take up this mantle of leadershi… https://t.co/20tNMFL7Jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[SOME BACK AND TRICEPS... ADD SOME RUNNING AND CORE WORK AS WELL.  KEEP BUSTIN ASS, NO TURNING BACK NOW!!!!! 💯💯💯⚾️⚾️… https://t.co/28DPUHHxyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjaTheAuthor @KamalaHarris You have the option and freedom to leave ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d watch a Rose and Paige prequel show but I doubt many other people would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/Fg3ndkQuHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m sorry to say sorry but my only problem I have with you is that you think is real as a friend k… https://t.co/nUIqmCqvkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This reminds me of 2011 Barca final ..when we had no chance and couldn't even play the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[New documentary about a NYC street golfer nicknamed "Tiger Hood" is surprisingly beautiful https://t.co/l3prkiL4kL via @GolfDigest]]></document><document><![CDATA[G looking effortless! #golflessons golflessons #usgtf #swingcoach #coach #golftraining #athlete #practice #golfer… https://t.co/zOACj6vfyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photobombing by Celeste @ Hyde Park Roller Magic https://t.co/qzxK3NdRI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sadly,  if this happened in America, those guys would have been arrested.  Has everyone forgotten 9-11?  Nothing bu… https://t.co/kodoeFzr0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@knicksjets4life The only thing he knows about basketball is it's a round object that's orange.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gervisdmedina @ejrl Quien dijo que el Monstruo de Cucuta es cristiano? Todo comunista es discipulo del diablo, adv… https://t.co/hlTq5JJSpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[6340a Wilshire Blvd 6340a Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90048 https://t.co/AmfpU0tc7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something old, something new.  Buy in or get out of the boat.  #outdoorshasstarted #row #ropes #mobility #grind… https://t.co/u9pFirSIzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious #Kombucha #BDK #BDS @ Midhurst, near Barrie, ON https://t.co/k4pn8LWpWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GailSimone It's kind of hard when there are already legit Transformers called Erector and Drillnuts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The president’s budget clearly includes large cuts to spending on Medicare and social security, directly contradict… https://t.co/ToXR946aac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheComicHunter @joshmccormack @MattJ_O @DreaVilleneuve @JoelRRenner @ScottOntiveroz @brenhillspeaks @AlHopper_… https://t.co/n46WIDcF0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[WELL IT SEEMS WE ARE MAKING SOME GOOD LEGAL PRODUCTIVITY. ALONG WITH RELIGIOUS PRODUCTIVITY ALSO. FATHER LIKES THAT… https://t.co/9oygFnTezu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottHambrook @WriterLeader247 @NovaFootball @devine_sean @PennypackerRoss 💪🏽💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Cynical EdTwitter,  I am sorry I have lots of tech my kids use daily and I am also sorry I like to give Teache… https://t.co/GHr1w22ZPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@banshee72 Then deport his fence hopping butt. You don't do it right you don't have the right to be rewarded for doing it right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surreal, to be an “India Hand” on a day like today. Horrific attack against my adopted second home, yet largely unr… https://t.co/5sCi8VoBjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two words that automatically get me on board with whatever you talkin bout: SHAUN..WADE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Phonz @MelanieMuses @amymoussavi @zihla Such a good session so far. Thanks for investing the time in crafting it. #sxsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techie_teacher1 @ReadingCindy Awesome! We should all get from the same place and get a group discount!! 😂 #NearpodChat #NearpodTransform]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caseyo4 @JayPolger @ChrisBrown0914 @rogcast81 @tigers Having a few star players doesn’t guarantee a sell out every… https://t.co/SKkM8n0T5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool. Congrats @klinetothetop   Looking forward to seeing you kill it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some new items to my #collection #berniemadoff investment papers #biggest #ponzischeme in #history @ Las Vegas… https://t.co/xLCzeIRozk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkradieWKTY @robmiech @wkty @KeyStrokerGrant Yes, he misunderstood the directions to school. He was supposed to be… https://t.co/3qdb87Pbak]]></document><document><![CDATA[The beekeeper yet again! #COYS #TOTDOR Great movement, Sonny! https://t.co/Gr8ZtjBIAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baltimore Twitter: I am craving fried chicken for lunch and I work downtown near Mercy Hospital. What are my options?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharLovesYeshua @krassenstein You think I care what these conservative women think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or she’ll possibly get a guy from 915💆🏼‍♂️that’s how she rolls I heard🙅🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treyhayden6 @ChipotleTweets 10 mins later after I let the tin foil cool off I began to cut through the quesadilla which was really good btw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceWorlddd on my 21st and @BobSeger the same weekend 🤒 i’ll be on hurt mood the WHOLE week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthonyTrendl . #Yuge #CreativityNews #Einstein on #Creativity https://t.co/dCXkjLzLJG #CreativePeople #Einstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxnewsgal Good morning, Lisa! I hope you have yourself a nice day at work, and a blessed weekend! @foxnewsgal wil… https://t.co/dRhDKeL2of]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triple Swoosh ,  I’m a damn walking Nike Billboard today !  😂 #justdoit @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/EKph2Ud3Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garyvee great text yesterday. Thank you for the encouragement! Have a SMASHING Wednesday! @SmashCreate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sure can; beef up security at the border crossings with the money you are going to waste on the stupid useless wall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key 🔑 to a brighter, fresh, and fabulous complexion is here! 🙌🏼 ⁣  Our LumaMax Glycolic acid pads are physician… https://t.co/gIStWTuIfl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieMcCarty @imchriskelly @ComedyCentral Same. Mostly for @JimmyFowlie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ultra #8 of 50 done! Marin Ultra Challenge 50 Miler. My goal was about 12 hours. I finished in 10:37!! It was a gre… https://t.co/ff0Zt929Ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 years ago today (3.2.15) you crossed the rainbow 🌈 bridge Seven.  We miss you terribly.  We miss your bark, smile… https://t.co/4MUQalIKGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackFord @JussieSmollett He's only laying out his agenda he's NOT speaking the truth. This attack never happened.… https://t.co/T8yy621vzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaltyCorpse @justsomegirl81 I have Doogie Howser as my wingman, is that pizza crust?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3NerdsLoveMT I got it all done but it totally took way longer than it needed to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuiceWorlddd gonna be in Portland in April 👀👀👀👀 oooo idk might have to be at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nebia @philipwinter_ @cheddar Yay! #Spatime - will @philipwinter_ be discussing @Nebia from his at home #spa showe… https://t.co/Y1CwlVRMgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonIsbell Beautiful shot of Jerry, Chet, and Waylon. Wonder who took that one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of the month. Putting in a full 24 hours of work into the day. https://t.co/Bly3cM9QM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't have happened to a more deserving person. Just proves what the Nike ad was saying about Colin K.  "Believe… https://t.co/iXkiZvXUkd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPOTG Beans is supposed to be poppin up randomly like Jcole and frank ocean do. Spending that money on the calm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ECC leads 27-22 at half over Johnsonburg in Class A semi. Green and Breindel exchanging threes late in half. Fun to… https://t.co/c96BJiGAj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans pay the price for Trump's wall crusade @CNNPolitics https://t.co/hcqo4cdInL #Resistance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join💥The Grind💥@64spadespoker every night as we’re warming up for our New Homegame❕MTT’S ~ Dbl  up S~n~g’s running… https://t.co/RJsWYdcVRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFGiants don’t need Harper with that money they can lock in proven stars like David Wright, Joe Mauer, and any num… https://t.co/SmRInXbRxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SallyWalker is trending #1 on twitter! ☝👀👑 #IggyAzalea https://t.co/68NTNMhpOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlotteOC sianynuttall @SXSW 3/11/19 SXSW sisters..let the fun begin!! #charlotteoc #sxsw @ Empire Control Room… https://t.co/ScMbtSZhLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Note to play by play guy, both teams are the dawgs. Use State or Georgia as an identifier.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FatherGeorgeO’Brien #celebrated #40years of #service #professor #scholar #friend #godbless #catholic @ Good Shephe… https://t.co/GvHo30tKpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin' at the Swissôtel before the BCBS Five-Star awards ceremony. @swissotelchi @ Swissôtel Chicago https://t.co/B6SHJybFUl]]></document></documents></author>