<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Final: Grand Island defeats Lockport 45-33 to win the NFL title and complete an unbeaten season in league play. The… https://t.co/TibT1uC8bb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain or Shine.... it’s on @wavelosangeles.....9am &amp; 11am.... who are you bringing?   . . . . . . .  #Jesus… https://t.co/BI6H0pZZj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drivadeneiramd @me4_so @SWexner @juliomayol @NorthwellHealth Exactly - the expectations piece is so important. A f… https://t.co/Mvv33RR4pf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“She will remember the moments you made her feel loved more than the times you said, ‘I love you’.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did 6 years in prison and tbh, @rkelly already sounded like an inmate in his interview with @GayleKing on @CBSThisMorning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you EdWeek,Sean Cavanagh and SXSWedu. Here is the video of the interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve learned that if you’re consistent in what you do, you never have to explain yourself.#FreeTrenton @ Sunrise Lu… https://t.co/6FsHtQqGQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaeComm @TopFenceClimber Do smaller teams automatically have a home tie against larger teams in earlier rounds?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I heard,"Layla" , by Eric Clapton the first time, way back when, I'd change Layla to my last name, which almos… https://t.co/lKNmyjxvhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbillinson @Kris_Sacrebleu Typical trump loving moron with NO VOCABULARY !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuksa gloves vthe puck for a much needed faceoff for the Saints #mesports #VarsityMaine]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dsummergrad Am U getting bot likes from you? Can you read my Instagram, respond and retweet anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kinda like 2 guys fighting each other inside of a house that is burning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[نهايه رقمي الجامعي ٩١١ وكل ما اروح مكان ويسأني الموضف عن الرقم اتوتر، 🌚😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna sit back, play some KHUx (because it’s more relevant than ever), enjoy the fuck out of Fate/stay night [Heave… https://t.co/Gc9CxPOTKV]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Orlando: broken clouds, 80°F 44% humidity, wind 6mph, pressure 1020mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshFlagner @DCapriato You guys are tweeting about not getting enough sleep but people wanna call me old? Smh...]]></document><document><![CDATA[⬛️◼️CALIBR GRAND OPENING PARTY 🔳⬛️  Saturday,March 9th  Hosted by Androgyny  What's your CALIBR? Twink-Bear-Thot-To… https://t.co/Uztw8IjESi]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our country is doing very well.” -Trump, making a statement while declaring a national emergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calvin_knapp @plumbcrzy If he's the best. He will be the best wherever he goes. But if doesn't then y'all were wro… https://t.co/yYRJM8Mxrb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@babb97305 @MSNBC @Zaradia @MeetThePress Its a shame that people are so ignorant that they don't realize their righ… https://t.co/EyybiDBUQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bobby @fodadawear laying down mad knowledge about Mental Fitness. Great initiative and thoughts. Check them out for… https://t.co/tHT6td8AJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kngofstrngs @FreeFood4Humans @Zhombre @petersversion @HillaryClinton Conclusion: your argument is so full of contr… https://t.co/EoVMV6GY95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peacendeath Man, I was still a kid too so cleaning that shit up with my dad was pretty awkward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stanleylucas01 @LovinHaiti @reseaucitadelle @fpierre4 @MPpresident2015 @ONUFemmes @ONUFemmesHaiti @martinejmoise A… https://t.co/JpKL7NZ7Tk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Vote American Vote Democratic Voting or not voting has consequences for ordinary Americans Vote against ha… https://t.co/i1cxULmvPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richfromatl Jim from Tuscaloosa was the west Alabama state rodeo champ in 10th grade before an injury ended his ca… https://t.co/yW984pVhI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @theresa_may @atiku @USEmbassyAbuja @10DowningStreet @UN @UN_HRC @HRC @USArmy @BritishArmy… https://t.co/oDXd54su44]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBGxo_ @awkward_duck @IWriteAllDay_ Lies. We don’t listen to each other. We don’t listen to anyone, except our pre… https://t.co/JD3MXtNuiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CubanitoenCuba @ReutersLatam Hahahahahaahaha, desesperadito , maricon de cuneta !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Copeland - Lay Here (Official Music Video) - PREMIERE https://t.co/eRFenIhqI1 via @YouTube @copelandband love it. S… https://t.co/WCEJUkyFks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in Vancouver, WA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/25dxe6JmF0 #Education #Teaching]]></document><document><![CDATA[“My privacy has already been violated, yet I am still willing to testify publicly under oath. Tyson has made the sa… https://t.co/1Ti0eYVIIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is ignorant. “Afghan” was once used to represent an ethnic group, but due to ethnic migration it now represent… https://t.co/1hePy5jbt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssurovell @DRIVESMARTVA @DelegateCollins @JeffMBourne @SenMMason @vabike @BikeFairfax So I should call the governor's office then :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mantitwo @_samanthica Bueno una imagen vale mas que 1000 palabras y que 280 caracteres asi que manden fototetas pu… https://t.co/2Q0qvXJd5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you ask a #readybase developer for their update in morning standup @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/MNZhRYvn1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh can’t wait to see this stupid ass at the bar. “Hey Jim, heard you shot your balls off”. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's $100 in FREE Postmates delivery fee credit (good for 7 days). Sign up with my code keck4 or this link https://t.co/mxclBG6KKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camilo_009 @PutazoFaitelson @cervantesalba A ese nivel estamos, jajaja, como la ves!!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Let’s stop lying. Do the simple math. Refunds smaller. Tax bill smaller. I ask you again, stop lying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBoers @DaniCarlsonSays @news8brandon @jackdoles I mean heck yea.  I could stop feeding quarters into that machi… https://t.co/XU5IHxgmaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading Matters. Please donate to SMART.  #engagepdx @SEMpdx will match every $ donated https://t.co/vipHR7gWcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leikthf @RepAdamSchiff Wrong President. This is the good guy saving us from the bad guys. We needed the coup in 20… https://t.co/OeDQ27EVGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherishere @SenSanders @brenda_archer Maybe it’s different by state. I didn’t register to vote until a few year… https://t.co/zfJaGWsPjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lalaviealoha @juscallmekirsty @amyalkon Your recommendation is just good Common Sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @realDonaldTrump is a dictator 🙄 y’all playin. Guarantee the US gets them out. Bet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a good reason why educators weren’t ready and STILL not ready - Security is not mandatory, it’s optional an… https://t.co/87w93YXy5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susaneholliday @Alyssa_Milano I WILL TAKE YOUR CHILDREN NOW  SHITHOLE MAGARATS.   DONT MOVE. ENEMY TERRITORY I WIL… https://t.co/pc9MOysCHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Fabiilli @Meganlynn_25 @yaboypabIo @TripleD215 I’m well aware erie is ass. He for sure thinks you have peterman still]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d Agree. Also read/quote re dementia and/or regressing hippocampus. High correlation to behavior, and rec… https://t.co/Fx4rOUIRS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the BEAT GOES ON AND ON https://t.co/yYFIr63lcW https://t.co/IA3r3j9cbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously there’s no way this flies like this. It needs more wing and more tail, but u could make it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TokyoNegro @cyberstephanie Yes!! You missing out! I binged the first season in one seating that's how good it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEJeepMafia I really want to Jericho with a satin finish but I’m gonna use the trailer this summer to see how it works out]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 times in the United States in 2 weeks, and one passport officer to every 3 planes, takes 2/3 hours to get between… https://t.co/IqHdx2VMbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It'd be pretty cool if Greenway won the State championship. Beat the the #1 team in the State in back to back weeks… https://t.co/2gazRsEZQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 hours left and counting till @anthemgame goes away (temporary) - ahhh!  Got the first taste of a real #crappack f… https://t.co/1z4wwHLigD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pithy tangerine - Drinking a Jason Hates It! IPA by @AldusBrewing @ The Fig &amp; Barrel Pub  — https://t.co/zrTCVpuGom]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only scattered singles left for Saturday’s game against Iowa State. On paper it should be a packed house...we’ll se… https://t.co/fTlF0Kz7GP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mardi weekend got a bit Nesty🎭#nestnation #cubs #bars #life #friends @ Shag's Des Moines https://t.co/ovHLxSNlWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This manual typewriter is a bitch to lug to the coffee shop. #MillennialWaysToLeaveYourLover]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Man, I haven’t movie hopped in a theater in awhile. Thanks Cian]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peta If you want PETA to show some accountability give PETA the Rosanne and James Gunn treatment and pull your don… https://t.co/QVOR9pk4tz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindsaykruse @VotedForYouBut @realDonaldTrump Not for me there wasn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabbyBarrett_  new song “ I hope” came on the radio.  All I can say is WOW. My new favorite song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Section 7AA Swim &amp; Dive Champions!!!!! #RangerPride #RangerTerritory https://t.co/14zKpzeatY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vprofessa @nytimes I guess the ease at which someone will lie to you to get a vote is something you just don't care about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very cool to celebrate the 100th anniversary of @GrandCanyonNPS at the Senate today. We are truly blessed to have o… https://t.co/ubNMIoDpZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's humorous. Birthday card by Evite Postmark #laughter #lol #grin #jolly https://t.co/qTi9HewPRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cadbury Chocolate is better than Hershey’s. Don’t bother arguing with me, you’re wrong. 🍫 @CadburyWorld]]></document><document><![CDATA[How we’ve increased #energy in #California from cleaner, healthier sources!  #sb100 = 💯% #renewable  #cleanenergy… https://t.co/TLF0J5nHOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Hey dumbass the liberals are the ones faking gate crimes left n right. Your party is the party if hate. Look in the mirror]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_Lo828 @TrumpStudents @RyanAFournier You don’t look to the media but the vast majority do.Especially the young. T… https://t.co/I0hYNmKhsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Woman reported missing near Cahaba River on Sunday has been reunited with her family @JeffCoSheriff reports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angela Bassett looks incredible for being 60. Her docs legit should buy advertising on her dress.]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. GDP Grows Above-Forecast 2.6% as Business Spending Picks Up  https://t.co/ptGzYnNWM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after being asleep 99% of the past two days due to the flu https://t.co/zdSDGdi3aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only TWO more weeks until @Shaysaywhat and I are back in the Sunshine State 😎 https://t.co/45x8eRtTOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rescuingcujo @MarkDice @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews lol.  I'm not in any group except the volunteer group at the Chil… https://t.co/lnqfTNoJpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobHinx @Helenmarchant9 Breaking out the poetry eh?  Two can play at that game.   Roses are red  violets are blue… https://t.co/s5FZq3X510]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think people that believe in zodiac signs have a firm grip on reality.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday February 16 - CBS This Morning:   The Eye Opener:   All that mattered this week on "CBS This Morning"    V… https://t.co/NLjzklna4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡Your real estate dreams won’t come true unless you take the necessary steps. Reach out and we’ll tackle your goals… https://t.co/8unaFTMSoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accident reported in #WakeCounty on I-40 WB and The 40 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGGYAZALEA Me either let’s talk about the single and album ❤️😂 love you 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein @sarahkendzior What's more amazing is that in 2015 you could have asked the NYer and they could told… https://t.co/aHXNdfuatv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl He always believed what he wants. Truth and facts are not his strong points.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @mrjacobwilliams with get_repost ・・・ Thank you everyone who watched the new #wildnout battle on YouTube wit… https://t.co/gCtPoQQblw]]></document><document><![CDATA[TRAINING : Commission’s Rules  https://t.co/JLOeveYMOg  #ham #hamr #amateurr #amateurradio]]></document><document><![CDATA[C-F’s Trey Follis brings his team within seven with a big 3-pointer. Athens still up 56-49 with 1:02 left in play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something the left will deny because it doesn't fit their 'destroy Trump at all costs' agenda.  And they can't help… https://t.co/N4UsxJhpS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with these two awesome human beings earlier today. https://t.co/2ILcvZwxgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have it a not-terribly-convinced 48-47, Page. @MMADecisions #Bellator216  But probably 30-27, Kongo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jortizfinance @theinstantwin @intersectality @AOC Can I use this for the wall when people from NY comment on it? Y… https://t.co/Y9KCxpag2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minorcynic Indeed, but you can’t cure secession with another election. Once she’s conned the electorate into it, t… https://t.co/mWKR8LX187]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ecnordstrom @R_Nordstrom A to-do list for your next visit to Charlotte (whenever that may be). https://t.co/AtijkwmRDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 2 - Morning Report:      Poster linking Ilhan Omar to 9/11 causes melee in West Virginia statehouse;… https://t.co/JUZJ5BRuWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@midwestright @ShawnG927 @Maggieb1B @SickOfTheSwamp @Beg1Girl @realCalebLawson @Patriot988 @RoseDC11 @Rbigzs… https://t.co/RZVANpEo2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsedwilliams @netflix @AJ_ThompsonJr Let's make this a tag #BringBackTheGetDown]]></document></documents></author>