<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can't believe the level of dishonesty and subversion in our White House. We can only pray for you 🙏. God bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DayDaDancer 😓 waayyyy too much! I just spent $100 today buying food to start back up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is wrong with our decision makers. This kind of thing is just CRAZY. #WeThePeople must stop this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcabellor Eres una lacra...narcotraficante que terminarás colgado por tu culpa..!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmandasFault Depends on where you live at. North pole??? Better have a cold drink. Egypt? Shits gonna be warm..]]></document><document><![CDATA[My challenge to my nursing students today is to start being the educator, the advocate and the voice for our mental… https://t.co/bpDJzzWqjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[LUNCH IS BETTER WITH FRIENDS. @napkinfriends, that is 😎😎  Pretty much everyday I get off the bus at Westlake Park f… https://t.co/aA9A3qXcrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have my own ambitious solution, expose climate hoax, have scientist admit the hoax via math and stats under penal… https://t.co/MYYFNXUuiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already I have had a conversation with a friend on GMT time. One positive aspect of all this technology is to make… https://t.co/Lgc8P8f3PP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mserinthompson The shows are going on!  Hopefully your venue’s line is indoors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stefano Gabbana should never be forgiven for his continued attrocious and blatantly racists behaviour.   Supporting… https://t.co/GoqPtrJKza]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of the @BlueJacketsNHL are playing well but Kukan is absolute trash. Don’t really understand how he keeps getting minutes  #CBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS Good Morning! The #American see your working really hard "Negotiating" #WallFunding and… https://t.co/R0cvfj9G7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Estate Market Update for #YorbaLinda #realestate #realtor #luxury #anotheronesold #interiordesign #property… https://t.co/wWSlKukw2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[High School Me: hope I die before I get OLD!     Me now: Hope I get old before I DIE! #HighSchoolMeVsAdultMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to see my congressman John Lewis on stage @Oscars2019Live_ 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Iris_Folding as #FineArt #Paper #Art "Panes" framed in wood and glass. https://t.co/eQY5Moj2xB https://t.co/F0PB8yQ2XC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@db19781942 @mlombardiNFL Difference is that earl was under contract. Bell was not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DumpTronaldReal @SenSchumer chucky try to do some real work instead of just bantering on TV. We are tired of your… https://t.co/y6EVkFf7Sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I vote for Rep. Cummings for something or what? No? Please? My goodness. This is astounding. #CohenHearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidAmerland Then for most, going to https://t.co/Azto1Phjop will be the entities for dummies tool =)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SunshineLK10 @SaveOur1st @KimberlyMrsRR1 @youlosenordys @TG2TruthSeeker @ImabitcSumtimes @BellaInxs2 @RL9631… https://t.co/hFhw30HGIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewzimmern I play in an old man cover band and I usually have gigs, but when I don't I rest and go to meetings.  Love you @andrewzimmern]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobGoldsmit19 and @MitchPotterf will wrestle for 3rd in the state tomorrow @OHSAASports @WNHS_Wrestling Very pro… https://t.co/yPlRNw5JwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful metaphor of a “small cemetary” carried in the heart of every #surgeon.   @LoggheMD @arghavan_salles… https://t.co/lDaIO4IcBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing in the theater it was the mall rats script made me cry. Oh and I cried before the movie even started… https://t.co/tDuQXRwJRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Various basements... #inthebasement #interiors #industrialinterior #monochrome #mydayjob #itsaliving… https://t.co/kBPeFc6Srr]]></document><document><![CDATA[big happy birthday to pjaimes, hope you have a great day love ya ❤️🎂 @Jaime_Garsteck https://t.co/o862W8MrI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[For Really Really Stupid People here are the Two White MAGA Hat wearing attackers Juicy fought off while eating a S… https://t.co/EfjjG2h7Vw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsNaomiiG That movie’s the reason I’ve only seen, like, two semi-recent Disney movies! Big Hero 6 and Frozen! Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffalobills please sign T- Trent Brown to anchor our left side and move Dawkins to RT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheliNBC6 @KristinNBC6 @RoxyNBC6 @AngieNBC6 @AdamBergNBC6 @nbc6 Goooood morning Sheli :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing says gansta like ridin’ in your daddy’s jacket lol!! @ Oak Park, Indiana https://t.co/Fkv83gRlJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump U mean u spent last 2 years lying to Americans and stealing]]></document><document><![CDATA[An accurate representation of all of the white people dancing at the Bruce Springsteen cover band concert I attende… https://t.co/rNeliQHZCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiw0711 @FutReading I gotta agree. It’s not hard to assemble a very good team. Guys with RTG teams stacked with SB… https://t.co/NSUAPHKNke]]></document><document><![CDATA[“To the weak became I as weak, that I might gain the weak: I am made all things to all men, that I might by all mea… https://t.co/CwwOP6TLGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Titans GM Jon Robinson on Kyler Murray’s size: When it comes to QB, you want a guy that can take the snap, make ev… https://t.co/mlMNNaCzLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fallonlv @LehighMBB @kleufroy3 @PDre34 @james_karnik Where was @cb_beballin]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a very productive Mid Winter Conference. Much was accomplished as we prepare for the National Convention. https://t.co/jjIgNIdEdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom woke up early ran out the house and said I’m going to get Selena cups 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danharrisndp @acoyne #cdnpoli What happened is obvious to any right minded individual with one iota of objectivity… https://t.co/kfpfWY7QKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jitimmons I’m thinking it’s roots are gone from the original separation https://t.co/2FTwDh9UH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradTonoff @LibertyMutual @JennaL15 @karenlilla @bobthomas @AndreiOprisan @LizSPollock Or let a pencil neck geek l… https://t.co/IsyBzOcyCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[HBCU’s are the real Wakanda! Tell Them We Are Rising: The Story of Historically Black Colleges and Un...… https://t.co/4ukHSJz2Tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I stop watching NBA basketball. These dude play like 3rd grader that can dunk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @Kokomothegreat not forgotten, #derfuhrer completely ignored his wife]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @UHouston Red Dinner organizers—enjoyed being at the reception last night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's sad how immature young people can be... disrespect others because you dont know who they are or their backgrou… https://t.co/1c5BUORY3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTraverse1 Mike, I spent some time listening to his in car radio.  He was really angry all day.  Early in the r… https://t.co/ZDI5kfkaLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took today off to recover from last night’s Oscar party. @UncoolJohn and I walked the Eastside Beltline, had lunch,… https://t.co/tL2qCenZ2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is sharing clips of this interview, but I highly recommend watching the whole thing. @mehdirhasan puts on… https://t.co/k0upOt3icH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalshFreedom And what evidence do you have that the people are more compassionate? What evidence do you have that… https://t.co/nQYtvIk1L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Austin, TX? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Power Performanc… https://t.co/FGzQ1vnPlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pete58bos @Annna987 @kylegriffin1 Son worked at deutsche bank, trumps bank to launder russian dollars! Follow the money!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a final:  @HoustonRockets 94, @dallasmavs 93. Luka had 19-15-9, Brunson 18-7-4, Maxi 10-11. Mavs are 27-39 on… https://t.co/XpaqQ9oU15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityOfAnkeny Thank you everyone for your hard work clearing the roads and sidewalks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DOSgaming top 10  Wolfenstein 3D Commander Keen 1 Shadow Knights Hovertank 3D Catacomb 3D Doom Ultimate Doom Doom… https://t.co/A2hCO9g2Wx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtheistEngineer Since firm follows function, such eternally superfluous attributes are an objective indicator of poor design.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wess413 @campbellitstrue @trudygonzales @eugenegu @realDonaldTrump You could choose what the law and the medical c… https://t.co/fZNYeFDGbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mondays👎🏼.. However Spurs get back on track Wednesday. Join us at @EndeavorBrewing for kick off at 3PM as the boys… https://t.co/1dIyNprQp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[64% of Americans believe the President committed crimes before becoming President. 46% believe he committed crimes… https://t.co/Q5m8d6AjYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Favorite President? Save the Date? Is this the kind of stuff you think is important in your job? Y… https://t.co/7jVk4LkDF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would have been more surprised to find out @JamesKennedyUK wasn’t on drugs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBaxterBean @jonallendc @samstein No way! Don't dignify Fox by appearing on any of their shows are being intervi… https://t.co/qBjJ3TEMML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @jrpsaki @CNN @PeteButtigieg Why can't you say nice things about a candidate? https://t.co/FaW4HRWfdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyFergusonXT Bruh fight McNuggets next fight win or lose you win. I think if you fight and lose to Connor it wou… https://t.co/6RneCoz99d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norinrad10 @Tennessean @TNedu @HaywoodSchools @JoinTQEE @tosstn1975 @TSBA_News @TSBA_OnTheHill @SCORE4Schools… https://t.co/OtwUxOq8oz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rage against the machines or Kizz your way through it https://t.co/OZNo9Sqg5l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordan_amano By design, the games are not long and the act of rerolling your game is a common occurrence even if a… https://t.co/jVlWca6TPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillEduTheater @Peter_Grinspoon I’m with you Bill. Sometimes it feels overwhelming. For the last year I’m focused… https://t.co/zmBG9QyWDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kensington Trails addition in #kyletx features homes starting in the 200's. https://t.co/0GGSHuKabI]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@StanginNbangin I see things differently  I go walking and take pics weird things https://t.co/KYG8DiWKqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzo and “cuz I love you” restored my faith in love 😍 https://t.co/WhsI5tZR3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the honor in meeting @bungarsargon from the Forward, she heard more about my political and personal journey and… https://t.co/748alN7W9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some MSM chattering class better get their little heads around the fact that “Empire” made Jussie Smollett ... not the other way around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exercise tip: If you put your alarm clock by the end of your bed and snooze your alarm 10 times a day for a week, that’s 70 sit ups, guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@georgiaoddie We can't agree on everything. I support what I said because of certain facts on the topic, and I resp… https://t.co/8oUrNO1uGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @POTUS and @SenateGOP for you amazing tax cuts!! Awesome work as you cut my tax return by over 75%!!!! Gu… https://t.co/B4TdKJZkWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gilgamesh30 Si, claro, en 3 años máximo estamos de nuevo a la cabeza, trabajando con dedicación y con apoyo internacional.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brasilmagic It is. Corporations and farmers have long received tax breaks and subsidies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg my left leg has gotten so skinny! only 2 more weeks! @ Old Louisville https://t.co/M5xUqg16Tx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LessGovMoreFun @POTUS How in the hell did they come up with a 1000 page bill in 2 weeks? Not a big fan of gov shut… https://t.co/fE6KGa1Jd9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJDionne They had to speak up, @EJDionne,  Trump pimped them out at last year's  SOTU, and totally betrayed them yesterday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @DonaldJTrumpJr @BretBaier Coming from a liar who denies knowing about but who seemed to  know about mo… https://t.co/wogbJPG4hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexsAdventurez Funny thing is, I would always use your face as reference hahah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both, delusions of grandeur along with indoctrination equals disaster. One thing about Bernie. He really does belie… https://t.co/2hXhXDHF7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iceland Grillz...  $6000-10k!  (Depending how icy you want it.  14-20 business days turnaround.) #GoSeeFRED 🥇  • FI… https://t.co/g9T8usKcDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous #sunset to end the day here in #clinton #nature #igers @ Clinton Town Beach https://t.co/fgcWYPmDTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post #meetandgreet with @olddominion for their debut appearance at @rodeohouston Thank you @curtisbraly for the… https://t.co/yfGvOhnK26]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaSAlford @JackPosobiec @theGrio Love how she changed her cadence at the end, when she must have realized how… https://t.co/8G4cgg6E37]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator Thom Tillis just made the list of RINO's that MUST go.If we don't get these people out we will eventually be at war with them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arturo_Bours; Nunca me pondría un camisa del @PANporSonora o del @PRISonoraMx; sin embargo Porto con orgullo la de… https://t.co/f5HsSUXnMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CynthiaNixon @JoeBiden @DrBiden Of all the attacks our community receives consta by true haters of us - Joe Biden… https://t.co/oo0ZpxFcWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hozier looks like the guy who brings a guitar to a party and tells you that he’s an artist that wants to show you a… https://t.co/tg8s4mAtZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinWashut @Sean_Callahan Still appreciative of what @CoachMiles has done here. https://t.co/rhZ36GQLJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIRST Time For Everything by BlairWilliams @manyvids https://t.co/ph7C14CuZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBeavas @The_Schone @KodiakJedi @ChaseRocket373 @KingVasquez @joeVevenflow @bwakenny @IsrarBasim @CFB_Brett… https://t.co/dIe8mMn59R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoverbird I'm trying to get AREPA approved, so in a way *my* dignity is on the line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 That lawyer nick has isn’t playing. I hope the entire MSM AND LEFTIST gets sued!! And icing on the c… https://t.co/3NF3sqXZTB]]></document></documents></author>