<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[From @BujuOfficial to @kendricklamar to @ChronixxMusic, @AgentSasco picks songs that represent Jamaica’s diversity… https://t.co/FKiV0u5Z16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@step4battle She was incredible! Even her post-mortem comments were insightful and spot on. Nora O'Donnell's faces… https://t.co/Vph9Zhha88]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are many foods that are high in protein and help build muscle.  Why do people keep suggesting we eat the gros… https://t.co/swkxR8eISY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Willjstrobe @tmack894 @thedailybeast I'm guessing Trump wrote this himself. It's a hot mess so full of typos and g… https://t.co/dJofx9MIz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicalGypsy15 yeah it was weird. It was a Bob Marley birthday event @ the trap I was sooo confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning world🌎❤️! @ Saint John Paul II Academy in Boca Raton, FL https://t.co/cWOPUVt88o]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard to let go of what you were just doing to move on to the next moment - a participant #intertwined2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill @Advil02 Why are you comparing wrong against wrong?  Whatever statement you are trying to make isn't effective.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #JonasBrothers are releasing a new song at midnight. Excuse my 14 year old self as she screams in a corner. https://t.co/lcYgWSH1QG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never talk about the #Kardashian’s but the Slut shaming of @jordynwoods from them, a story BTW that was publicly… https://t.co/GE8ZRlnh8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you have been brutally broken, but still have the courage to be gentle to others then you deserve a love deeper… https://t.co/WJ2oPcFR9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes! I like the idea of adding @CameronMaybin to our roster! Still has some speed and can play all three OF positio… https://t.co/khhilXzBL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsbtv coverage continues! Watch Camden Murphy on Saturday during Bulldogs Gameday at 10 am! https://t.co/oVOSa0Rzuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 28th Birthday Matt! 🎉🎉🎉 I’m so proud to be your mom. 😘 @ Minneapolis, Minnesota https://t.co/0BoafV0aEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyshaped There is. I’m shook. I have not been okay for the last 2 hours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lysswhit it's the toughest of the suite, for sure. I used to be pro with it too, but now I'm like...WHAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Times running out for the other 26 states to name their candidate. Seriously, this many is making party really weak.]]></document><document><![CDATA[can we stop pretending like the black parade was a better album than three cheers for sweet revenge? thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm trying not to abuse this gift.  A forum, of sorts. And I feel lucky that I  have met so many people who care, p… https://t.co/JdVeI0NbHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good times celebrating #oscars2019 with our favorites... @Angie_Edgar619 @cadillac #oscars2019 #party #awardseason… https://t.co/VQsokIW0hQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime i look at my scar i just feel like i failed him not being able to keep him in long enough to have a norma… https://t.co/aaULp95Q4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you call a boomerang that doesn’t come back? ... A Stick!   Bahaha why am I like this 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a bad take because if you’re anything less than elite, or getting scholarship, you’re going to have debt if… https://t.co/53ZdekkuFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Ballet!  . . #valentines #millerwestonadventures #latheatre #ahmansontheatre #matthewbourne #dancelife… https://t.co/RISbeW2YRu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicole20245261 @ThomasKlineMD you should tell your story exactly as it happens and how you have suffered because o… https://t.co/9oKNqxFcif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akcdoglovers  You must be so proud... Yet ANOTHER greeder in the news about ANIMAL CRUELTY!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marvelousmalone .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different… https://t.co/8hW6yODkgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tryna b a good bitch to niggas who not deserving is played out, some 2016 shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate when the fucking lyft drivers be asking me how to get somewhere. motherfucker you have a gps, use it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence At least you can read and spell! Most of the dumbasses are lucky if they can say the same! Like listening to you every night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Eltrain Every day and I try to make at least one other person smile too! #tryeveryday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ran three and a half miles (on purpose) and this is my “who AM I?!” face https://t.co/Yq4YBJ5TS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllister_Band just released an amazing new single called "Come Back Home"! Go stream it on Spotify to help them… https://t.co/SHcoSAgctn]]></document><document><![CDATA[In n out cashier : here’s ur cup sir ( to Izzy )   Me : ITS MAMM   WE ALL LOST IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg @JoyceWhiteVance This is horrendous !  We should take care of these needs right NOW !… https://t.co/nkZ5T1CgkH]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little guy seems to love basketball!! 🏀 #neilu #RedNation #LittleRocketsFan @ Houston Toyota Center https://t.co/ixu1Kq5XYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to our 2018 - 2019 Teacher of the Year, Mrs. E. Abrams! We are so proud of you for the true passion… https://t.co/kDKdQtf87e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @Bucketteamrisma 🏀! #Mustangs @EMPEHIAthletics #SupporttheCourt #Senior #GirlsHoopToo @fshoops32 @FSHOOPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really got “Studio” by Schoolboy Q in one of My “romantic” playlists...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping to hear @AlanChartock ask @NYGovCuomo on @WAMCNews roundtable about getting major #climatechange policy done… https://t.co/NqLaTqjoQ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who invented the heated blanket, but I just want to say thank you to that person #alwayscold]]></document><document><![CDATA[I changed my loyalty to @ultabeauty and someone used my phone number and stole all my points! Now I have to wait 48… https://t.co/D3o5xZWvLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The show @pen15show is everything I had forgotten to remember about my life. 🙌🏻🙌🏻🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djohnishi 大西さん皆様こんばんは！ 今日は久しぶりに #thenite  拝聴させていただいております。もうすぐ大西さん2枚目のアルバムリリースライブですね。おめでとうございます。楽しみです。アーティストビザ延長時期で… https://t.co/mHMGQze3IE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton @calpizzakitchen And now the mystery of where that spring came from...hmmmmm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my listing on 7638 CHADDS LANDING WAY #Manassas #VA  #realestate https://t.co/eLZwQTLiFO  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almostablaze @CasaskullMark @ml2370 @HomonLang @ccsunflwer @LinemansLadyLuv @scottydog57 @ethan1655 @panekbill… https://t.co/F0JJPgMqCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Comfey__ @SuMoh7 @KevinGrau10 @sunrisemvmt @OversightDems Throw Kemp from Georgia into the fixin’ bunch🤮🤮👿]]></document><document><![CDATA[In second row for launch party.   Shhh.  Don’t tell the people who pay big bucks for these seats our sky box is way… https://t.co/ZpcznKGoEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brigitte_ER @soledadobrien Brigette, Bernie supported a lot of newly elected candidates.. @AOC being one.. We need… https://t.co/uGqNjMiXq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the #FridayFortyNYC for @HPPlayNYC on @TodayTix! Get tickets for performances next week at $40 ($20 per Part) #CursedChildNYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all I thought I-75 was bad...Iowa roads make me feel Im on a damn horse galloping]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jack_mocherman This was one that freaked me out, but I remember liking it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift in 2006 post breakup: “When you think Tim McGraw, I hope you think my favorite song, the one we danced… https://t.co/CeON9aEqRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[That?s some hilarity right there. #funniness #lol #smile #playful https://t.co/u02JZYBWBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittanyFurlan  I LOVE SEEING YOU SO HAPPY‼️❤️ HAPPY LOOKS GREAT ON YOU 😘🤘🏽 https://t.co/bvBbrl8LLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnaaksSoupbone @TheStarters Aww, thank you so much! I'm just doing what I love! @Suns games are my happy place and… https://t.co/woG4ruMu9L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldTomTrump @Saveyourjokes @jsteele78 @Alyssa_Milano He was running bc he was terrified. It doesn’t matter if h… https://t.co/wQig0UCOeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Fred Rogers would be quite disenchanted with humanity right now. #SundayThoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[The couple that hates contractions together, stays together https://t.co/S5UJSXPOum]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard it was snowing in Vegas yesterday 😳. Work-day in Miami... Caporicci #chef #italian #apparel #miami #vegas… https://t.co/WIM4GwUtR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hal was an amazingly prolific drummer and also a generous person. He was so supportive of my son who is a better dr… https://t.co/cewlMQ8roU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Mary  I was born in the new year  My age is a lot better than my life  I like to think about you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momma’s grab those kids and squeeze them tight! #babysdontkeep #mommyandme @ Fort Worth, Texas https://t.co/pfWvuBwVsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got you running from my love and you’re not fast https://t.co/yG7r0WU15U]]></document><document><![CDATA[What day is it? What time is it? 💁🏻‍♀️ Between daylight saving and a time zone change I’m just confused 🙇🏻‍♀️😂 What… https://t.co/LrORUdJ3sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoCoGardeners Don’t forget about @BryantCTC plant sale! Regular hours: school days, 8-10am, and 12-2pm. SpringFest… https://t.co/GrFVp09XTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a fun weekend away at the doveinn in Golden, Colorado. It was soooo nice to get away and the place we stayed… https://t.co/log0NhbNmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My baby girl is #21 and I’m officially #50 - the perfect pair!  💕💕💕💕💕💕 @ Mandalay Bay Resort and Casino https://t.co/8N49beJIg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lisa Schade, Broker, CDPE, SFR LSchade@Renax.net 847-367-8686  Re/Max Suburban 1344 S. Milwaukee Ave Libertyville,… https://t.co/4Ai7yyWK2m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real Madrid fans brought up Ronaldo when they lost to Barca, guess what they bout to do in a bit? lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsseej23 I feel this. Hard. Why can’t we have nice things like cute camisoles? https://t.co/hcrskfkqCW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC They really don’t deny they don’t know what they are looking for. I think they should be put out of government. Than sued]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @PressSec You broke Trump's lie meter today Sarah. https://t.co/YtyBjYMIpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThriceSavage @OU14Pres If you are implying that people are only mad about what he is doing because he’s a white ma… https://t.co/HV4k9A0Bqf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@femalebreezyyyy people talking bout “a spring break I won’t forget”........ can’t relate lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC She wants to run for President.  Start a Socialist America.  Will Americans stay asleep?  Watch?  Kinda like c… https://t.co/FfrlIapxvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@63_cabaa @paoloigna1 @RulesBenitez @analons @mlkjhpoiuayoube @RosaTrunk @somnath456 @Edward733 @HeikkiOjala… https://t.co/OTZOokjx29]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frank's Red Hot grilled chicken  and steamed cauliflower 😍😍😍 @ Little Elm, Texas https://t.co/32ZVuCEgKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne must a forget about season 1 where @lisarinnaa thought her videos were nasty as, and when… https://t.co/uHvXAEVxd6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the last hour assigning photos to contacts in my phone. This. Is. Amazing. Feel free to submit options.  #DalesinHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not me and not the Democrats you must be referring to mr. Trump himself the criminal that traitor #ImpeachTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @ChgocadChic IS THERE ANYTHING A WHITE PRESON DOES EVER, EVEN BREATHING, THAT DOESN'T OFFEND SOME OTH… https://t.co/iPEska4XTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is yet lacking, dear one, is your willingness to move towards complete commitment and dedication to Me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yessifarts  makes me fucking SOFT!! i cried at the presentation and cute little note she wrote!! anyway, excuse me… https://t.co/A2W9hihGZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WBVikings @TarHeelFootball @BallCoach34 @GJrWorth @CharlesHyman10 @CoachP_eterson @superreub @rafeel_ampong… https://t.co/MLitmC6hXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKevinBrady Why try to pass such an unnecessary bill? Non-citizens already cannot vote. There is also almost no… https://t.co/Uhr2oAh5PE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got off the phone with my CEO and I'M ON MY WAY TO THE TOP and it's coming QUICK I can't discuss what/how… https://t.co/dcwxEqf3Ln]]></document><document><![CDATA[sameeeee , i used to literally never cry. but then again that’s cause of my dad. soo all that built up emotion floo… https://t.co/Ww2yl04Lvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexissylvester @Excision I LOVE U AND EXCISION my two fav things in one place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buster_ESPN Post mortem on Bryce Harper: do you think if the Phillies put an expiration date on their offer (as yo… https://t.co/s70WMLF1MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesgarrigan @dmschies @paddy_cm @ayuros @Desmos @nearpod https://t.co/maKJfTVbpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boxerbuddy4 @dodo @a_dogs_journey That's the best learning behavior you taught them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimCarrey I beg U, DO NOT trust gov w/your healthcare. Woman w/Wrkrs/Comp w/severed back waiting 2 years 4 bone fu… https://t.co/EuaCQD6GOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SubwayListens I’ll be on the hunt, thanks! Egg was my favorite sub choice!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Unhappy Holiday” is an official selection of the LA Under The Stars Film Festival, and screening tomorrow, Thursda… https://t.co/IfjGQPLA3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of the time I have to sleep with my hand creating a space between my head and my pillow because the sound of m… https://t.co/eFoe9WCbsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: store manager -State college, PA - https://t.co/r0Lc62QrNo #BusinessMgmt #StateCollege, PA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Vegan #toothpaste is the perfect vegan and fluoride-free option for the entire household. Try it now. You can shop… https://t.co/ytqDVb90Wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok now there are evacuation warnings. Stay safe Sonoma County. Not where I am so far.]]></document></documents></author>