<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I have to get something off my chest. About 8 months ago, a Tim Horton’s near Banff messed up my breakfast sandwich and I’m still pissed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 Heroic British Schoolboys to Be Honored for Saving Man Attempting to Commit Suicide https://t.co/sBuWNdb88b via @TheRoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't give a crap anymore. My heart is gone. @ Mesa Cafe &amp; Bar https://t.co/nwrGU7LT57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewvaga Reservation still requires park admission, which I have. My pass has no blackout dates.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msalsberg Try removing all reflective surfaces from your house. Works like a charm, trust me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @hello_ouchhh - 1 million people experiences their Poetic AI projection mapping experience in Paris https://t.co/Pjpx8uFq7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadingWPassion The WORLD Can make you HAPPY if your CONCIOUS of it and have a CONSCIENCE for it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only Democratic President I like is @BarackObama. I also support Trump too! @The_Trump_Train #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Millennium Biltmore Hotel Los Angeles - @millennium_usa in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/CfxnvoSzja]]></document><document><![CDATA[really cool @YouTube videos). Anyways at some point I'll have to do a triple parenthesis because I really think tha… https://t.co/W1akfLhsro]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do kids go to spring break in ft lauderdale when miami beach is 30 minutes south???]]></document><document><![CDATA[High school me after talk about how  ima be in them guts all night long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lreed314 @PARISDENNARD @BetsyDeVosED There isn't, profiting from the public school system. Nothing but Gangsters!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KierstRutterr @makeithaylll If it doesn’t have a little sugar in it it’s not right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hardest part of my childhood was finding out that @TrueKofi was not Jamaican]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the @BellaTwins returned I was happy. When they left I wasn’t happy. I almost quit watching @WWE. But I’m not a quitter. #NeverGiveUp.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Usos have regained the tag titles! #WWEChamber #WWE #WWEUniverse #ProWrestling #WWENetwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rath_resilience @pcrickard @CNMonline @RS21smarter @mfidel999 @cabq @CNMIngenuity @dot_of_scott @BlockFiestaABQ… https://t.co/sx7qWlW6Wn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackhutton @tonyschwartz Not to worry ..he will be deleted Before hisz term isz up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UMBC published this article about Wednesday’s Alex Hooper show in Fell’s Point!   https://t.co/vIU2m3Xvln]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyday is a blessing and I’m thankful for my life style a living finesser I make shit happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the heck? I’ve never even tweeted to Larson. 🤷‍♂️ https://t.co/MyMtk55cjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I experienced extreme emotions over an event that I had zero control over like I have never felt before. Ac… https://t.co/N4qMk1fRtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feb. 22nd 2019 Day 2977: 30 min LISS Cardio with Shoulder Work with My Brother and Mentor Sagi 👊🏼💚💪🏼 • • • • •… https://t.co/mJWDoLkmWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finding the “old” in Old Bisbee is easy! happy snowy memories #bisbee @ Bisbee, Arizona https://t.co/VaOn7dJYxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kaskade Redux at The Mirage goes on sale in 45 mins. BUY now don’t CRY later. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I would of had a nice whip and crib if I wasn’t “dating” a gold digger🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is it with all hover board falls. If you notice they never have helmets on. Safety first damnit]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of  work staying hydrated and minding my business. You should do the same.🕯 @ Beverly Grove, Los Angeles https://t.co/xiZXDDMscn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Angry white folks get salty at Phoenix Art Museum becoming more diverse, and actually more interesting.   Sorry nob… https://t.co/Kmu00D2rJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaYz7eD @ProDiuM Like I said, you don’t even know what you’re talking about lmao. I don’t read horoscopes fam]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: ‘They Created an Underground’: Inside the Chaotic Early Days of Trump’s Foreign Policy: Former top… https://t.co/c1LYr1WY0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[“TÓMAME UNA ASI COMO QUE NO VEO” 🤣 I was so 🔥LIT UP🔥 when this happened, there’s an actual clip on the conversation… https://t.co/Tn2elutrun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday from Baltimore!  Light snow overnight shouldn’t impact my final full day here! @ Parkville, Maryland https://t.co/eFNkIQRvS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tammydawn76 @ABC I’ve known addicts. They’re great at avoiding the truth. But yeah, the crisis comes, and they’ll… https://t.co/0Xifv1a3H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like the new destination for Dominican Republic’s gay people is Colombia 🇨🇴👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Il est la les types @Moscato_Show @VINCENT_MOSCATO @EwanjeEpee @IKF_officiel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poetry https://t.co/XMUtY0LNSD via @YouTube Poetry from more than me. https://t.co/87RxzUZXQP]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're working an overnight shift and start experimenting with filters.... @ Los Gatos, California https://t.co/yPu1B7zYdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenHowe THANK YOU!!! I have always wondered about that nonsensical idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @AnnCoulter Pulling a gun this time, next time shooting a gun...!!!  It’s coming, and it won’t be pretty..!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wally's brother Shunsuke is on WWE's Japanese announce team with Funaki.]]></document><document><![CDATA[01:10am since 5 p.m.this evening Big Shots there's three of them that came in from the airbase hospital they have d… https://t.co/pyKOZjICBv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A6: All means all. Students don’t come in with equal access or opportunities. Equity is how we raise everyone’s opp… https://t.co/UCu6Q1LBJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#365Until50 #Day184 #AustralianShepherd  As you can see, my plan to work on edits for my book tonight has been met… https://t.co/vmVO2C4dBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can all learn something about bouncing back and pushing forward from Breanna. https://t.co/SK1hYcykRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP The only difference between him and Trump is that Trump hasn’t been convicted—yet. You people have celebrated… https://t.co/sfpf4yEv7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five Portland bands wish was still playing: 1. Pleassure/Green Slime 2. Stag Bitten 3. Explode Into Colors 4. Greenladies 5. Preblon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaxxon8 @IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump @GOP Secondary cite (also by me), but here are some design challenges for… https://t.co/AWVBC1uTBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for @Reenie_Hutton #7bookschallenge. Sharing covers of #7booksIlove here’s mine: https://t.co/zxikPrPdbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorLorenz False. People in SF jaywalk but without purpose and fear of taxis like in NY. It’s a very lazy jaywal… https://t.co/ke50IgVRoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always talk this old man who’s a welder when I go out to smoke and I think i’d literally pay him to tell me stories all day lmfaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Meloni For @LindseyGrahamSC’s legacy’s sake, I hope whatever the blackmail is is good because it’ll certainl… https://t.co/gaxicsBGqC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se fijan del por que no me gusta usar el sarcasmo, lo considero un tipo de violencia disfrazada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MySixthSenseTellsMe to follow @MorrisAnimal. Also, if we get 10K followers by the end of the day (extending it one… https://t.co/Cv5fVuONWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamGriever Expectations were already fucked from Treyarch not being able to keep up with their own promises and pi… https://t.co/Az6HXCufDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews You'd have to be a prostitute with no self-respect. Wait.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devin Funchess just got 13 million on a 1 year deal.   He had 4 TDs last season and never had a 900 yard season.   Explain the logic here?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NMSAmen You can when they are younger (yes!) but an adult slipped in somehow. We luckily observed it so we can iso… https://t.co/fjU59BfONG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dog wants to sleep on the floor when i know damn well her mother spent way too much on this bed. @ Houston, Tex… https://t.co/BZa78xG12x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vortex_RL @UMichFootball @nflnetwork It could be about a Michigan waterboy and Buckeyes would show up. Also, Higdo… https://t.co/BXjMqrM4Sy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton @kelly_clarkson Do u know where boogie hill is ? Is it still there in ada]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of a coin flip, what if you did a cross bar challenge to determine who got ball first]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titodinzey @DonaldJTrumpJr He may be a bigger scumbag than his father.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesslbest That’s the point....nonverbal communication makes up a way larger % of actual communication than does verbal. Just healthy...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertpepinbob @Darknight1922 @mike2069 @RBoutinJDQ Oui effectivement...   Alors on le garde avec nous au #RSEQ1 ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist No because hes authentic.  Christ FDR couldn't even walk and he was elected 4 times he was so popular!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialChanceH @adamhxoxo I love you Chance! Hope you delivered my message to @allisonemiller and @greene_lizzy l… https://t.co/kSjIGY8jQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HighsocietyJ Read my Linked In posts, tweets and listen to the #GlobalLithiumPodcast &amp; you will know who I favor......]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that's a wrap for the 2019 CCAA Women's Volleyball Nationals. Not everyone was available for the pic after last… https://t.co/832FVKQkfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AustinC_199 I am not a Pacers fan so I don’t really care. I would appreciate it if you didn’t tag me in anymore po… https://t.co/tA2WV2rM50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bill_Maxwell_ @unclechud It’s a stupid system of Govt. we have, it’s a male dominated,antiquated system that needs to be overhauled.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@My_Power_Tie I’m crying. Best video I’ve seen. The  timing of narrative and clips is on point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And governments have practical experience with this during the down cycle when bid prices fall as private contracto… https://t.co/HsEUHV8YsH]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019, day 65  2+ new pages today, now 75 total on my second script of the year. I truly believe this could become a… https://t.co/168VbwkQ28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForthRightStrat @CPAC What? Reagan predicted a game show host would come along and spend 2 years attacking our lib… https://t.co/WSr2Hpp7sL]]></document><document><![CDATA[On to the next one... great team victory by the Lady Lions. #LUHSPride https://t.co/1Ido2KpCqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe According to my wife, it takes me closer to 7 seconds. I believe it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the ub game last night. Shout out to my employer for the sweet tickets https://t.co/rgySQDuDux]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you buy fake followers it fucks up your account   - 1. it makes it harder for your old followers to see your n… https://t.co/u8jfEhBt8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovWhitmer please rethink your .45 gallon of gas tax it’s not healthy for our economy. #taxestaxestaxes… https://t.co/h5gKgCXQBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagPieSC1972 @PamKeithFL Probably none after they took the baby home either. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MysteryCr8tve When I was a kid, his curation of short stories  just blew me away... even more so today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pero se burlaron de mi amigo @Andy_Rosales10 cuando dijo que Tigres le podía ganar al Real Madrid]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soimwatching Klaus and by association Robert are our newest gay icons. https://t.co/ogSvAVj25O]]></document><document><![CDATA[not gonna lie, bragging about being #201 in pretty much anything isn’t a great look]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valari4 @LbL_Hor @PaulaMons13 @Sui_Lovett @emma_bakos @bekojoanne @kizzy4464 @Iggy_proof @CPRluvsGaga @Gagamina… https://t.co/PtxTwO4nxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SifuMustache Interested to hear your thoughts after - maybe I’ll catch it on Netflix or Amazon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz “Don’t Let Republicans off the Hook” by William B. Turner https://t.co/FyTjbZ3jti]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you need to hole up in a trailer full of fairy lights to get right with yourself it is what it is but please kill that word with fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[Infórmese cuáles son sus opciones.  ☎️ 305-903-0728 Info:jromeroob@yahoo.com https://t.co/Anz0CkrcDj #realestate… https://t.co/noVBUsU6e1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just thinking about who has the most to gain from the persecution of an elected official who represents a predomina… https://t.co/DjyZmsuVaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my childhood crush and idol @Bajan_Canadian   i was such a huge fan of yours back when i was youn… https://t.co/8ZZoG90bsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TropicScar @BeatsByBeardly @ResurgenceATL @dvorlando @NYCFC @MLS @OrlandoCitySC @TerminusLegion https://t.co/5AaK9ss7SO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @Travis_Borne @mark_carnelley @MarthaPerezBook @AuthorEllie @CasamentoArrigo @TrishSuter @okangel27… https://t.co/YItn2vSG8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricWFMJ If it is an "average" ratio of 12:1, we would have only received 2.1 inches of snow. Now the question loo… https://t.co/RXZgvVWbgf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MAmovie I am sooo ready for #MAmovie. Thank you Mr. TATE for filming another MOVIE in my hometown “Natchez”]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes I really be on my bold shit and put my future self in situations that I would normally not get myself into😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Senator Ron Johnson from Wisconsin! 1 of the top 5 elected officials!!!! https://t.co/xPSKe6NIkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@results_cheer Yes @benlearsays !! Thank you for your amazing vision and sharing your talents with us. We love you!]]></document></documents></author>