<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[EXPOSED: Brian @krassenstein admits he is paid for his anti-Trump tweets. "...there are higher ups that are paying… https://t.co/WbtLcaIW7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I came for the Ariana Grande reference. Stayed for the genius that is @KrRutherford]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rocksound Um throwback to the Breakfast Monkey https://t.co/9fdpRZqqag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a lovely evening hanging and getting to know my Instagram and now real life friend wellness_made_simple  tonigh… https://t.co/sBkSutIIVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[El problema no es que no saben lo importante/necesario que es comunicarse, es que simplemente no le importas lo suf… https://t.co/L852tXYQhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of birthdays to my favorite wine drinking buddy, personal hype woman, and sweet friend! Forever grateful f… https://t.co/ixSgwFMNl0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Barry on HBO is an insanely underrated show. Bill Hader is unbelievable in it. There’s your weekend binge recommendation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnightMemer2 @mrcrom1 @Amazon_Queenn @Sanskretro Boring.  What do you think you’re accomplishing by repeatedly pos… https://t.co/WRcNewby1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great night! Dancing, singing, feeling the love and savouring the community ferl you always provide 💘 never… https://t.co/gXPv6QS944]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never listen to a ruling class in a supposedly fair and balanced government run by billionaires exclusively, when t… https://t.co/Cm9OT7xQ0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialSCUSD @sacbee_news Regardless that was not the topic of the Bee article. It’s misleading.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Tis not true Marco A healthy tree can produce a stunted plum The will be rotten before it emerges The t… https://t.co/60GASARYh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[After spending the entire weekend behind bars, R. Kelly is waking up  in jail, preparing to go before a judge this… https://t.co/uHZtmuqRWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking into boarding the dogs for vacation and it costs almost as much as the vacation. Why do I have dogs? 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Diana contemplating how she’s gonna get rid of Marlena???? #Days #Jarlena https://t.co/BNMBMGoaec]]></document><document><![CDATA[im so excited to see @MiniKiwiMan its been WAY TOO LONG (11 months) but STILL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I talked to these two Irish girls in the bathroom of this seedy ass Bronx bar for, I’m not even kidding, a total of… https://t.co/XiKP6bn6i4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @RyanAFournier @JussieSmollett @TheRevAl @ABC @RobinRoberts @GStephanopoulos @CNN @TMZ @POTUS… https://t.co/75ta9qVrB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amazing @squishable Art team created these new #toothfairy items just in time for @ToyFairNY. Stop by booth #10… https://t.co/6xEQTOKFVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying real hard to get on the avatar bandwagon. Trying to get myself hyped for Disney’s Animal Kingdom. Rememberin… https://t.co/V5ZjlgspOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many Disney crewnecks do I own? Soooo many 😂 keeping me nice &amp; warm in this cold weather today 😢 https://t.co/XPQzSlKnUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[never had a breadbowl but rly wanna try it @panerabread can u help a girl (who loves u) out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t Let your Pride get in the way from making certain Decisions because that shit will come back and Kick Your Ass.💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Booker2020 #Harris2020 Why would I eat a gross lentil burger when I can now eat a delicious Impossible burger?   #Bernie2020NoThankYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of the best lists I’ve ever read. #FreelanceLife  https://t.co/nwZEktuJSM]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 of my favorite hops. I love this brew! - Drinking a Stormrage by @calusabrewing @ Calusa Brewery  — https://t.co/gRRbN2bTxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchoBlue75 @KendallCoyne Well, you don't have the blonde hair streaming behind so you don't look as fas- naw, it was Kendall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaina @JAYVERSACE You gotta give her a chance. She’s thriving 👏🏽 https://t.co/TxDnPOGZFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dining al fresco because it’s a balmy 50 degrees. @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/ajYmspte5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Netflix Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  C… https://t.co/Vw8cO8oEXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Waves_of_Gray Oh wow. I’ve seen that movie more times than I can count.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dog reunited with family 101 days after California wildfire https://t.co/BwUX3yfexN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reachrecords #UnashamedForeverTour if anyone is selling one ticket to the Charlotte show I would be SO appreciative!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalepmills I notice your arm is totally on both of hers, just in case she, um, gets slap-happy! #nocheatingondazel!😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Masterdate level unlocked! #happyinternationalwomensday to me!!!  #captainmarvel #hollywood #arclight #mcu… https://t.co/N0J3ycxC2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryan_s_clark @SabresBuzz It should be doesn't matter exepct it is the  right COACH comes, no matter WHAT color he ism]]></document><document><![CDATA[An excellent read - Why Catholics should oppose HB205 (scholarship tax credits).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y si nos vamos a correr con todo y frío? 🤔 #Tijuana #sunday #jogging https://t.co/O53h2AV2pR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski An I think a whole lot of cases that are true should be prosecuted also but their not This shit is t… https://t.co/RDypSmu2hU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queen_biird The weather after people were complaining it was getting too warm so early in the year.. https://t.co/T9Falos66P]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a Saturday morning when I could be sleeping in,  I've already done my chores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity A little power corrupts.  To some people a little power corrupts absolutely!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I made my way to Oak Creek for Winterfest, a free community event that’ll be featured in an upcoming episode… https://t.co/MlcB5R9BLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also my sister @loriburnsbrooks working the production booth at the Pac-12 women's tournament.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so slow I’ve never been so bored out of my mine. What a waste of a coffee and an energy drink]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks like the roll they have restrooms in concert arenas, and in office buildings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett   We believed you!  We cried for you!  We sought justice for you!  And you lied to us.  How could y… https://t.co/H8fPyEETWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our guys are still at the port in Oakland and SF working 18-20 hours on the cars out there. Fat bag!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codyjohnson I’m loving the new album &amp; Doubt me now is my sons ⚾️ walkout.   💜⚾️💜#AxeEmJacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariselaSilort Jajajajaaja y si fíjate! Ya voy en el 18 de la temporada 3 😏😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trapolah @j_fried_pickles I know it has happened to me!!!! So uncomfortable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A child of #AntiVaxxer contracted #tetanus in Oregon, was hospitalized for nearly 60 days, and the parents now have… https://t.co/z43oSxCJ9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I wake up: I can’t wait to get back into bed! At work: Definitely going to nap when I get home.  After work… https://t.co/4gVjHiTeH9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DayOfEmpathy #Cut50 #alabama #March5th @cut_50 @splcenter  @EmpowermentAll1 @drkimberlyk @OffenderAlumni… https://t.co/GnBgb5qCRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Far out in horse country🐴 There’s an art installation from the movie Giant you have to see for yourself. It’s liter… https://t.co/r9TEWAe7a8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This song made me feel so loved and taken care of @BenSPLATT thank you for sharing your story so that I can grow st… https://t.co/WcGAXLKlHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the book of life comes to an end, allow your memories to resonate in the chapters of others.~HBG #life… https://t.co/8SF5cMglT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CeqCgekehx #weekendvibes #free #relax #enjoy #life #health #desirelovell]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s worse.. toilet paper ads on pandora or Adam and Eve ads in pandora? 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡MI VOZ SI IMPORTA! 💯 MY VOICE MATTERS! shouted, gritaron los estudiantes de @BSDWhittier @BSDWhitney @phcartaya… https://t.co/bykr6ZqwCg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not dissing those issues or the people who do those podcasts that I love. @gopTODD is really the only one who c… https://t.co/2WS8qiQ1mi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Salimapeacejoy @RedEyesPage @ananavarro @k18c79 @IlhanMN U didn’t get it, Salina. Jake was trying to show how so m… https://t.co/OG3cn3N323]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImDexterRoberts just watched you perform and OMG I am a fan!!! ❤️ from Texas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ecamner for a job well done today @RWUBaseball #4 #GoHawks ⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle and move on. #funniness #chuckle #grin #farcical https://t.co/qQFvhAARu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins @marcthiessen @hughhewitt @henryolsenEPPC @WilliamJBennett @VDHanson I’ll bet they’re really afraid of Jim Swift]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmtrakAlerts Thanks for the answer and I’m hoping it won’t be an issue for me,  but I’m trying to find out about t… https://t.co/5ojDwjFtkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ SIGN OTHE TIMES Blogtalk Radio https://t.co/svoIlOU4FE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson The HATER is finally CAUGHT with his despicable lies and behavior against innocent people, who beli… https://t.co/piLnAnSyUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FOXTV I’m submitting this as an audition tape for whatever your next live show will be]]></document><document><![CDATA[It must be the day, low patience. Right now there's someone here that I'd just like to smack. One of my girls is to… https://t.co/oWlCDWJxVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtractionEngr @CNN @nischelleturner @smerconish No but there is a definition to follow. Conservative is withholdi… https://t.co/Wl3tx6QJui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Politics aside, “Show me your budget, show me your values” is a very good line.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir I fly Alaska for the friendliness! #iFlyAlaska #AlaskaHappyHour]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great evening at Sneaker Soirée for Girls on the Run. I will be writing about this incredible organization. https://t.co/8ctRWxpjaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mimirocah1 @MichaelCohen212 In a choice between 2 proven liars, trump loses everytime. He's a pig. He has NOT ONE… https://t.co/kCplk0vXWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[They never can. I would think that just hearing and seeing what Ven curls is going through. People would shut him d… https://t.co/S2luH0Hr6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr From a party that has no clue what bathroim to use either..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s coming? Register to attend. All info is located on the flyer 😊 @ Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/kvfgxAAYIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My next #WWEChamber prediction (which will most likely be as wrong): @mikethemiz and @shanemcmahon are awesome and… https://t.co/nY8zaR1CJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up to his arms wrapped all around me 🥰🤤the BEST... but he moved bc I grabbed my phone 🙄🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GimmieDaFries Lmao idk then. Maybe looking up different brands of rice from other countries. America’s food has a… https://t.co/V1VbFb8179]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raggityanni4 @ControlBurn12 @AmrutaEswara @RepSwalwell https://t.co/ne4UyXNAcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea there was a local connection!  Loved her in #CrazyRichAsians]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being single used to mean that nobody wanted you. Now it means you're pretty sexy and you're taking your time decid… https://t.co/yfeFXKbgEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MONDAYSHOUTOUT to my followers that retweeted me multiple times this past week @midnight_bird76 @tdidraevolve… https://t.co/ZH2fHAGxgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@repmarkpocan... Rep. Omar sb censured for her antisemitic remarks and removed from the House Foreign Affairs Cmte.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Food Friday @OssiningSchools OHS room 126. Blueberry granola parfaits were on the menu 10 out of 10 loved them. Some had seconds😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieputh Omg YESS!!! I’m a laundry 🧺 fanatic! My OCD really kicks in...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bocomo200 @boonehistory @briannalennon @BooneElectric The Community Listening session planned for today in Ashland… https://t.co/y7XggXKQbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like #NFs have this cool sparkly quality to them. Like their dreaminess radiates from within. #ENFJ #INFJ #ENFP #INFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[U can listen to sad songs but ur not sad, u just want to think for a little]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire crews say when they arrived on scene, there was a person near the storage units on fire. They are speaking wit… https://t.co/ZP3JyOTO2Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some journalists can be... whiny about how they’re treated nowadays. I get we’re important to democracy etc etc but… https://t.co/RnPRIweBfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToughGuyMankas @vroberts9 @lynda3035 @Tonithecat32 @fluffybasil @SassyCassyCat @BloomNight2 @sharon_cantley… https://t.co/DoQ94m5J95]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalenaHonaker @JayInslee The Trump administration changed a bird-protection policy under the Migratory Bird Treaty… https://t.co/dxeCY0VRdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉🎉TWO lucky @TheNewClassy readers will win a family 4 pack of 🏀 @Globies 🏀 tickets! The prizes are one family 4 pac… https://t.co/UJpWea74yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was in snacks? Parents fearful to send kids back to school after eating tainted candy: https://t.co/BRUxTuszAc https://t.co/273Z6thcpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevBIOU13 I think the common denominator might be people with bad taste in girlfriends]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait until I'm not huge and pregnant and ag least a bit? Smaller looking so I have confidence to go hang out with people again.]]></document></documents></author>