<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I honestly don’t think it’s the fact that Khloe is just blaming Jordyn for it all... everyone KNOWS Tristan is a do… https://t.co/jVvz54nZPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[On average, brands that employ a strong omnichannel strategy retain 89% of their customers compared to 33% of those… https://t.co/Qof4mHXDQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cta278 He's also able to take part in who replaces him - he'll still be there just in the background.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeff_gluck Here's why I say yes, no one was able to get out and run away with the race. There was alot of passing… https://t.co/aikNq0WDel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como o espectro do comunismo está governando o nosso mundo – Sumário https://t.co/P7lXXo6pHz via @ntdtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Equinox 61st St for #CycleForSurvival @8am on a Sunday! #StruggleBus #WorthIt Love you dad! F*ck Cancer! https://t.co/bOtRug3ULj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd @ColinCowherd @JonGoulet @gregtoohey @JoyTaylorTalks @jasonrmcintyre https://t.co/gUFNzeIA4l]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@dananessel⁩ to Catholic Church “stop self-policing.” More ⁦@WOODTV⁩ https://t.co/QAQW7jZQ2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martyn_sharp @danreed1000 LaToya told the TRUTH about her pedophile brother Jacko! "My mother showed me checks for… https://t.co/nyCZjYfqWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[God sends grace to your place of suffering before you yourself arrive at your place of suffering. God’s Grace helps… https://t.co/NFIMaGLoT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colbydroscher Weirdness is a quality I appreciate, well, most the time at least.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you say “no” to training, you are saying “NO” to people. #bigpicture #investinpeople]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenpgiles @Ben_M_Berry @panohiohoperide Oh. Well that changes the equation...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aimes_sweethrt I like peanut butter and chocolate. I don't really care for Reeses]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hugo Carvajal, the former military-intelligence chief, pledges support for opposition leader Juan Guaidó and says h… https://t.co/biGiCDEcDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnieSchultz I'm so w/you and am no longer worried about FOX. It's the journalists at MSM that do not see this th… https://t.co/MpK9tdUaKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[My flow chart isn't complicated at all. #TheFutureIsVoting #RegisterToVote #HeadCountRetreat19 https://t.co/RRVLC1ZU7L]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO EL SOL SALDRÁ PARA TODOS, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/t53Th2SM37]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/l5TmfSfNas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate to blow your little theory, the the head of Uranium one had left the company 2 years before Hillary even took… https://t.co/b15CiTqUbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok Mr Kelly for a special Sat court so he out on bound . my guess he gets 5y prob .10 days public service]]></document><document><![CDATA[17:56 Temp. 50°F, Hum. 86%, Dewp. 44.8°F, Bar. 30.03 inHg, Rain Today 0 inch, Wind 197° 1.2 kn]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s no secret I’m not a Trump fan, but this is true. Some members of the media have such loathing for him that the… https://t.co/EX8lKGU3vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro How about I worked for what I have. You can to just work hard build a business that serves a need for t… https://t.co/PG901YunI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Racism is taught by the parents. No one comes out the womb feeling this way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just wanted you to know how that song touched a big hearted 7 yoa kid. Thanks for bringing us songs with heart and real emotions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ftv_MatutinoEx @estarc62 @Alonso_Cabral @adevaldes Que Mugrero al 🌶 #quemugrero https://t.co/aHjafI14I3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamison_farris @SkysBlue99 @fleccas @VANS_66 @PacSun It’s so funny when random dudes with like 100 followers threa… https://t.co/q2R7WIoi6n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carve your own path by being unapologetically, authentically and genuinely YOU!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump When you have to quote the joke of a human being Jesse waters the end is near smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[BAM!!   This weekend put this bad boy under contract!!  Super congrats   to our awesome clients so they can get the… https://t.co/Jhpdw2StuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone in Congress please do something about this @tedlieu @AOC @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASubsMuse @D87ip28cx Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nicoxw1 Who cares what she says,she has shown that she is unhinged already!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡🍾For Sale in #Margate‼️🔥 3 🛏, 2 🛁 home with custom made pool, travertine deck, upgraded kitchen with SS appliances… https://t.co/SlUJI4qqck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KikiSchirr I use ExpressVPN from China a lot. Works fine in US. Since it works 80% of time behind great firewall,… https://t.co/MRkTtpS5Jj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayo SHOUTOUT to @garyvee @NipseyHussle for inspiring my boy @DellyEveryday to DROP A SONG EVERYDAY OF THE YEAR ‼️‼️… https://t.co/XoWNqfnQKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC Mayor De Blasio's wife spent $900 million in taxpayer money—with no record of how it was used https://t.co/gU5eFkSiYL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @TheDemCoalition @TheFlaBar needs to investigate also whether Trump instructed Gatez to engage in felony witness tampering]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four straight Tyler Newkirk free throws increase Walsh's lead to 71-64. 30.5 seconds left.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@patsajak Brother, I hope your planning on hanging around another 50 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Drizzy6Woods @matchaboyguy Tbh at this point the only thing Im looking forward to is arsenal winning Europa ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[turn me up lil cuz! one step closer to getting that ring!!! @J_Guillory13]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody give me a cheat sheet for the most generic emo chords ever cause we're gettin real basic]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is from a series he did called coach B here are the links to 3 of the episodes:  https://t.co/pgUrc9dAj3… https://t.co/j96RcfZLgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cesar_0064 Is this your train layout and I hope to see you in may for the party holly is having for Jessica and Fr… https://t.co/s5AQcEZTZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listo para degustar un buen café @ Caribbean Isle Apartments https://t.co/Hzs5AhdoaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThBenkoe in der Firma läuft bei jedem Microsoft Windows, und das benutzt du jeden Tag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paying some respect to the man who helped me become a southern rocker in my early years - Ronnie Van Zant.… https://t.co/VUwteijHQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad really emailed me an article explaining why having more than 4 shoes is stupid lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[NDP’s Nathan Cullen won’t seek re-election this fall https://t.co/F4ec490LmD via @torontostar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir delayed flight from Columbus to DFW early on today due to mechanical problems. Boarded at 8:30pm took… https://t.co/QbHWWsc2Zo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mue_blew @chrxstianh__ @HicksFlair @Luxe_Leesh 😂😂😂who made this @__armanii___]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realjoewright @NyQuilDayQuil That’s interesting, but the article implies you the intense dreams later when the med… https://t.co/bjyDW8vMec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShotgunSpr @StanfordMBB @USC_Hoops @ThePeristyle @FightOn247 Thornton missed two free throws in last minute to clo… https://t.co/OPtgKCSlMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWEUniverse: RT @hulkinghitman87: @WWERomanReigns All I can say is CONGRATULATIONS BIG DOG! #WelcomeBackRoman… https://t.co/VqHaV4Br4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_becks22 @mfishbein44 They wile File a motion for a temporary injunction but since actually construction won’t ta… https://t.co/ULLsbgvwWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NevadaJack2 @RodStryker WE THE PEOPLE FIGHT YOU SOCIALIST FOOLS IF PRESIDENT TRUMP “ DOESN’T WIN “.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_SalmaFikry @munamohamed @HumayAG .@M_SalmaFikry this also inspired me to share these photos of mom making Gulukn… https://t.co/PXKvkERf3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter I wonder how many witnesses now think of going to TMZ before their local newspaper or TV station, let… https://t.co/QkGyTeiOoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@girlspIusboys @lexiybarra42 bouncer: *looks at me holding this* this expired 4 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt Really no one hated Fox News till Obama launch the campaign to demonize them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think anyone should give Harris a pass, but it’s frustrating that Biden and Sanders are graded on a curve https://t.co/nScsMRXPQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funtravelchat @travthroughlife @FunInFairfax @Adventuringgal @Nicolette_O @DanaHFreeman @markandkylee @karynlocke… https://t.co/Qj6qIgy4ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been saying all award season that #Roma is going to win #BestPicture. For the past few years, though, whatever… https://t.co/KfrrgGkNzq]]></document><document><![CDATA[For real estate professionals, tax time doesn't have to be a time to dread. Trust your tax reduction specialist to… https://t.co/P96XJc1E9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[These longer days put me in a good mood! More daylight means more time work on our fitness. @soulcycle check out al… https://t.co/HfBXnIaTQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Where is muller the military,congress,are they socialist too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lead_Austin #bestclassever2019 tackling our #Economy today! Was reminded today of why I am and still need to be a… https://t.co/m7iURvtM56]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oisparahkaa @skill_specs @ianspam I mean I've seen classic view, that shit looks like ancient view]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been concentrating on NFLX for months. Today, I bought FB. What a mistake. I lost 20%, not too much given thei… https://t.co/YLZswoHRJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lauzirika @BrianWCollins Curious if you thought to hypenate someone like Sondra Locke who also directed (and would… https://t.co/DJiH9XtteE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NERevs NEED to get better at creating offensive chances. Started the game well today but couldn’t string together… https://t.co/QCIAmYOVY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ani_23s Bruh this fat arrogant fuck has kids. Imagine them seeing this when they're teenagers. How can this dude g… https://t.co/xtjBjQbvJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent the past week trying to write a song entirely from AI / predictive type – lyrics, melodies, and chord progr… https://t.co/RG2kuAVtJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IcewaterOlson The hit rate for below average athletes at corner is ridiculously low, but evens out with the rest o… https://t.co/y3EMmEdkf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bravesoat @Alex_More_xxx @Alex_More_xxx is CERTAINLY one of my favorite cocksuckers]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a beautiful thing when a king articulate his thoughts in a concrete manner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starkshark7 This has to be clickbait I could argue those are some of most underrated QBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing NBA All Star Weekend. Some of the Best Dunks Ever! #allstarweekend2019 @ Spectrum Center https://t.co/hfgclqRjyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing anti-Semitic in what Omar said.  We should support nations because they support peace and democrac… https://t.co/V8lVpbrxBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SinBinVegas @mcfreelv ok. gotcha. 13 min on the PP why the hell not? nothing else was working. gimmicky? not in my… https://t.co/ifqLr80cMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted the challenge from @jennekrajecki to post covers of 7 books I LOVE! ❤️No explanations, no reviews. Ea… https://t.co/UdxX4zntBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[ManU vs Arsenal Cincinnati vs Houston FC Cincy at Atlanta.  What a Sunday.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 50Y FG in front of @Chris_Sailer felt really good. Had 55Y distance. Headed to @MUKnights today to sign my pap… https://t.co/noGw0276Ev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adjectives seem fairly innocent additions but look again. These small imported mechanisms are in charge of attachin… https://t.co/2iXNBikZxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ac13alex "If you wear a Boston Red Sox uniform, you have to know what Tony Conigliaro meant to the franchise." Jac… https://t.co/FwRwiiEzTH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smittygrrl What about descendants of those killed while fighting in the Civil War, WWI, and WWII?  What do they ge… https://t.co/xrCcBMY97c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain I know thousands of Dem women and not one believes in late-term abortion or infanticide. Are you drunk?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying all day not to say this but...  Break up with your boyfriend...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very happy birthday to the best colour commentator not working in the NHL ( and he’s better than most of those gu… https://t.co/hOTQIDnT14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickconfessore You guys need to get back to work. And candy corns rule.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers @AlanDersh What could have made him turn from respected legal scholar to just chasing fame and dollars? Is he a whore, or more?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#10thplanetnewport #10thplanetjiujitsu #newportoregon #training #exercise #fitness #motivation #lifestyle #jiujitsu… https://t.co/rkRg7aUoz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard this tonight but isn't it the truth!  Adulthood: Its like looking both ways before crossing the street and th… https://t.co/MRFesERkDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump Where are the arrests for these crimes ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has declared humanity blameless and without fault in the Christ. We have these many problems in the world becau… https://t.co/gXu8MosXKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are at a loss for how to make an artist with moderate success relevant again. #itsover "The spicy press releas… https://t.co/EuhwV67Te6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like say what you want to the company page ... leave marginal journos from underrepresented communities alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buffa82 just to prove I wasn't Monday Morning Quarterbacking with my Andrew Knizner take. Tweet from a year ago. 😂]]></document></documents></author>