<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at Newark Liberty International Airport in Newark, NJ https://t.co/esszzvqMR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BallGame723 @mkdikes832 @fibonacci1123 @_mrfo20 @Raphy_Taffy HAYWARD!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Rui Hachimura for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/UQVDN9pSUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My social media feed is locked in a dead heat about whether Karl Lagerfeld was a visionary or a fucking asshole.… https://t.co/OanbyLXXjJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itseffinjas My wife is from Mexico and we’ve gotten it from both sides. They don’t even seem to realize what jerks they are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been posting too much food lately...taste this instead.  . . . . #friday #friyay #deserved #nightout #drinks… https://t.co/T9g6wC9LDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @chefjoseandres Who are you, except an extended loser??]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you tell me to move on , I do it then you get mad ? https://t.co/pB3NBUjItG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THICCOL0 @NombreEsJustin @BRlFFGRAFF Im @flattered but that kind of seems like a big commitment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbySapphire @MoreThanAPilot @GoldenDicePod It’s a honor that the great @BobbySapphire would want my tokens.   Tr… https://t.co/AyZR02iY8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sex Education: Season 2 | Announcement [HD] | This show is so relatable and painful! https://t.co/7NOqrXPOK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire your inner lawyer and become your favorite preacher, reminding yourself often today of the gospel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiattenberg I love you too @jamiattenberg and you will crush the day into peppermint dust. 🍭🍭🍭🍭🍭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así los quiero ver en Portland. @kimjarevalo @CindyCorrales9 @ProudJimNi @iibarraaa @Angel_Enrique75 @Guantracha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3ManFront Pat Bradley is my new favorite person in the world. #IBOB @colecubelic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone find Susan Howe and show her my mysterious book about Salem, full of witch transcripts, missing its first 3… https://t.co/8yI68xdYHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @BetoORourke—-Do you believe in National Sovereignty and the right of countries to establish and control immigration?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's high time 🌿 spaceykacey #kaceymusgraves @ The Theatre at Ace Hotel DTLA https://t.co/fCbzILyWju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexboulerice @LP_LaPresse Je veux féliciter votre chef Jagmeet Singh pour sa victoire éclatante et sans équivoque… https://t.co/zMVP8HFNHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@firenicefly @MattHancock @DavidRamCFT @cftrust @IanAustinMP @lbeswickcft Yes, some have called me names then block… https://t.co/rct1FxMkM8]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING: 14 people have been killed in Alabama as tornadoes rip through the South. https://t.co/Sgv4IayKmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poppcorp Goood morning and happy Thursday! One more to go then its Friday buddy! Yaaay! ☀️👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoCalBears10 That’s me! Live in Southern California.I had been a Lakers fan since I was young. My family got me in… https://t.co/luQZ8AlLAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EckrothRodeo Unconstitutional (ticket cameras) you have the right to face your accusers.. and violations must be v… https://t.co/4lhAz3RbK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Ann that’s a sign you need a baby in your life. Not twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little show is underway! Minis! Auction! Friends! @scfd_co https://t.co/E6meBKwv3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just know what it feels like to want to die.   I know what it’s like to hide what you’re feeling because no one c… https://t.co/m78nj90Bzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night more than 650 seniors joined us for our 7 annual Senior Sweetheart Dance! The room was full of energy an… https://t.co/CaThdWIFyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We have to find someway to get rid of this illegal authoritarian abuser]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cash me on the morning news in Arizona😂  📸 @xohannah87 https://t.co/m0M1wL22F5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly considering writing my paper over stealing other peoples mans...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to sing shit constantly. I remember this kid a couple of grades above me gave me shit for humming Life Is A… https://t.co/qgwFnop4WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[En el norte seguros de las decisiones y rumbo del sector vivienda, sabemos que el carácter, solidez, juventud, capa… https://t.co/KXDiNYpaYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Y'all come to Texas. We did and we are living the freedom dream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great week of hiking and backpacking in the AZ desert. Hiked about 45 miles.  Thankful to God for the opportunity. https://t.co/ncLFjtqVpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntruj Can’t use the like button on this. I worry about this every time I chop veggies. Glad it’s still intact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @chortletown @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487… https://t.co/jCwjCt1ja7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muse was amazeballs tonight! Had an awesome time enjoying it with my bandmates from @diginfinityband https://t.co/zaY4KAQKw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I celebrate Mom • Sisters • Daughter #InternationalWomensDay https://t.co/9wRqZhYIij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this hole in one I got at the Winter Carnival!  Come out until 2 pm! https://t.co/OI4M9xsrpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[HALFTIME: Dolores 34, Ignacio 29. Tristen Swagerty is leading all scorers with 13 points, while Bryce Finn has nine… https://t.co/Ife8djEHEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkvball Yes it did. But again, Clyburn walked and went uncalled. That was the make up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Power is out from tornado warnings.. maybe I’ll have an excuse not to watch the Oscars. A dream, literally a dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #HalleSlayed on @TyltEnt—Halle Berry looked flawless at the #Oscars in 2002 https://t.co/iYxg1iDPNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most major California reservoirs are near or significantly above their historical averages as of midnight, 23-Feb-2… https://t.co/ExWCCtNtH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[HISTORIA!!! Soto la da en público, esto debe ir al archivo general de la República. 👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Kylie, get your sisters and go sit in the corner, Malika, go and find you a job, and Khloe, go and call your fat… https://t.co/3uA7KhVJQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz WOW! One party is concealing crimes and destroying democracy, and the other party is having a debate… https://t.co/W1OKset7IB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree Bryan! I had an amazing week and my conversation with Nikki was inspiring! #getscreened @LiveMooreCo… https://t.co/mSOwOdqzUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already excited for the match ups this summer! Can’t believe we’ve known these campers since they were in in elemen… https://t.co/YCpr9ffFWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rpaulsenphoto If Matty is healthy he’s playing. That’s easy.   Ladd probably shouldn’t be in the lineup. MDC or JH… https://t.co/0yvfmxPUBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump That paid family leave proposal is total bullshit.  It's not "Paid".… https://t.co/uVDnGFyrI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a way, it goes without saying: People *really* like finding new music. But an important nuance is: do they like… https://t.co/SkaQpfviUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeonteyP It's insane to me that he didnt see how counter productive this all is]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thread is a bit wordy/meandering, but its core point is excellent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster @cmclymer @AOC @Talkmaster you’re just another ignorant, rich, frightened, old white guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandakich @IUBloomington ...and certainly not for the better.  Sadly, IU has become (insert irrelevant basketball school here).  Pitiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems a little late to the party. He died 10 years ago right? So just now you wanna ban his music? Are you actually… https://t.co/4emdUd3oe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JZarif @tigerbeat This is the foreign minister of Iran.. and.. gotta say, he’s right. As Americans, we are humilia… https://t.co/mUjMJcE5A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the way from Arkansas to get BBQ!  Made more and still sold out early!  Record Friday!  Thank you!!!… https://t.co/P3KYLJ2yKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimBrownlee2 @pjfinigan @SIU_Baseball That was @Jhbrownlee every midweek game!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Met_CindyFitz  @ShiriSpear @NWSBoston  @WX1BOX @clamberton7 27° 3” snow Hopkinton #15-252]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great, it’s actually 12:58 AM, so I stayed up even later for this garbage 🗑 #BYUvsSANDIEGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y para terminar el día... LOS FALCONES también les desean un feliz dia de San Valentín! 😜🔥❤️ Quien ya quiere ver… https://t.co/tadqgvg1Lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiroHQ Would help if indicated who you were previously in this tweet... Had no idea why I was seeing this in my fe… https://t.co/UHzMJ9xoex]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American Indian people tried to have a simple way of life, hunting, fishing, and preserve the way of life. The… https://t.co/E5MenXIsoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the only way to fix my sleep schedule at this point is to just move across the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS how is it not a crime for #dems to waste the people’s time not getting ANYTHING done for th… https://t.co/CcVxP5snq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sir?  You trained me to be the meanest mfer on the planet.  I am.  But unless you make them give m… https://t.co/8zJ1BEhGdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richhomieerin Well if he was talking to you like that, then he deserved those angry replies. It definitely looks l… https://t.co/rTXhM9AWHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaz_chillinger @BontaHill @_YoMek its a regional rivalry... they aren’t even in the same league so you’re saying… https://t.co/IELXnfl2pz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve recently accepted a challenge from @edocarroll to post the cover of 7 professional books, no explanations or r… https://t.co/6tTq0L23Si]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to all the @NKYVC teams @UltraAnkle Bluegrass tourney in Louisville this weeeknd. Great job 16-1 Tsunami f… https://t.co/rbSj9NLPpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, he’s co-opting a July 4th tradition that I went to every year I lived in Washington DC?  Next he will announce… https://t.co/mRqj9AQwyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebCalloway Not yet. I shaved it all off and started using this oil and it’s been working big time tho. What do you use tho ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot how boring elkhart is when none of your friends live here anymore 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu Indeed. But, it doesn’t hurt to remind the public again and again. It’s what the Right does through their… https://t.co/9w3gLh7eBu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davemeltzerWON how likely is @WrestleMania to be held in Orlando in 2020?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harwoodhoya @bgpowelll Ready willing and able to sit at the table it’s not hard to figure out the @MPSSAA_Org simp… https://t.co/FGKop3BOGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The class pay gap: why it pays to be privileged – podcast by The Guardian's Audio Long Reads https://t.co/hveG00merH #nowplaying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC I’ve never seen “bed-shittingly” used in a sentence before, much less as a vague Oscar diss!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Oh but our American MSM will not mention this as it fails their narrative of hating Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an awesome job @joeybroadcaster is doing. Love listening to him and @Panger40 is the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finals have begun! If you wanna watch me MC a show choir competition, and watch some incredible choirs, now is the… https://t.co/9cUOccexdn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler bitch ass left 2 minutes after getting into the coop. BOI I TELL YA BOUT THESE NIGGAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 63 of the #365Project #StuartLittle   #MichaelJFox #JonathanLipnicki #HughLaurie #GeenaDavis #SteveZahn… https://t.co/nVd29IuHha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taygoldenstein @statesman @HoustonChron Congrats, Taylor! This is so awesome!! 👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the issue with fish, TMAO and heart disease? https://t.co/urRG2aJcpI @joerogan @CLEHeartLab @ClevelandClinic @questlab]]></document><document><![CDATA[When somebody shows you a couch online and the woodworker inside is like,”I got this” https://t.co/olnuRiKy4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brogdon has been really struggling in drives post breaks. Lot of misses on layups]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynnFYI @MatlockFletcher Or his phone, which a real victim would have used to call the cops IMMEDIATELY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@froquedm Eh, he follows me so he'll eventually read it. However, I had to express my words after reading so many a… https://t.co/7HrOKAjomR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoreyOMS Bro I can't even approach a female out in public 9x outta 10 cuz of that shit lol I gotta be off sum liqu… https://t.co/28lBTXWoY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best kids I’ve met, and without question the most over looked.  He will do amazing things in this life,… https://t.co/w7hP5VegCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecPompeo @HelpBobLevinson Thank you Mr. Pompeo from Wichita, Kansas 😇🇺🇸🙏🏾🇺🇸😇🤠 https://t.co/mixGYsprhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waresgsbcentral @ChrisMWilliams Amen. This team got some great road wins and beat KU @ home. And now twitter wants… https://t.co/rClG4xCwQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter #FakeNationalEmergency #TrumpBankFraud  #ImpeachTheMF https://t.co/FSat5RYk4E]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t think the president of the United States should be held accountable for his personal antics?! Hahahaha ok… https://t.co/4s4dD2s42Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[#breaking: In SECONDS on @komonews at 11: Shooting at BECU Credit Union in Everett at 11127 Evergreen Way. Watch… https://t.co/q1W8z1sb1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like #LinkedIn is just a bunch of employees posting articles explaining if their boss was more compassionate they would be happier.]]></document></documents></author>