<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Depressed is full blown time to eat an entire pizza along with a bottle of wine]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized how many times the government has seen and heard me takin a massive shit 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[r.i.p. Luke Perry. Still in shock knowing you left this earth way too early. #LukePerry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday Lunch Special  American Classic: Bacon Cheese Burger 🍔   Beef Patty with Melted Cheddar, Lettuce, Tomato, M… https://t.co/jafKY52GaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJTobin1 I share your outrage, but you have the authority to do what I cannot: take Bishop Paprocki’s lead an… https://t.co/ULgYUkPSih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at the host stand at work trying to vibe out to the country music in forced to listen to everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic alert: long term lane closures began today on I-440, plan accordingly this afternoon  https://t.co/cWywxxy7Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow Day Self Portrait #winter #selfie @ Port Washington, New York https://t.co/ZWHBP8jKai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DottieHardin @deedawgz13 @dj_mac_nificent @standbyme44 @HuppertzLaura @RosieRrbjj @stwissmann @Mac_Styli… https://t.co/uGIgxHMZgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizmccracken I always have to read it again right before it’s published.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please raise your hand, Twitterverse if you’re willing and able to see if #ChadAndKaren are still there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know that Mx is a non-binary written salutation (like Ms/Mr), but I don’t actually know a go-to answer to this on… https://t.co/punE6XPXKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmph.. well God moves in mysterious ways, if you thought a person was once for you and now you feel wrong.. that pe… https://t.co/LKXg24AdGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulonwilliams Even scarier- They Photoshopped Jesus following Trump. #Sacrilege https://t.co/Ixflxs4wMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maverikedu12 @pushboundEDU @1stEdResources @EduGladiators @ASCD @ASCDconf @AMLE @DrBobbyMoore @LaVonnaRoth… https://t.co/lJD3rSYyLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hailz12342 Incredibly sensual, full of promise for a burning love that will be fulfilled. At the same time, it was… https://t.co/Vycfl17Yp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew69927936 @thetoonager @_RebeccaParham Ain't no mountain high enough, ain't no valley low. If creators can m… https://t.co/9d45xMjcNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedWolfDreaming It is that look only a cat can give. Somebody probably would not share their cheese.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day, babe. I love you a lot!! 🥰 https://t.co/xiaMhEZ7RA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@44Jaworski @mommamia1217 @serenalburg I was politically active at 16 against the Vietnam war, fighting for civil r… https://t.co/oPJd4la1nd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kiddlebug_susan She belongs to my neighbour! She is so damn sweet!!!  Boop that nose! #PoppyTheBC https://t.co/vQie6yB6G5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheering because although some people may not like lady Gaga as women we must recognize each other’s achievements a… https://t.co/olzkEycoH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump @PressSec Please do not sign the bill, do a. Continuing resolution, until you read the… https://t.co/DoOvO8EeB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaellacer58 I know! Sad he died but the video made me laugh. Ooooops.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*men who wear scarves on the outside of their coat that serve absolutely no purpose* YOU’RE the next bachelor! #TheBachelor #scarves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harry, Ron, and Hermoine every year getting in deep shit:  https://t.co/MbyW7jMAmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing how people look at you so differently depending on what you wear and how you do your hair. We really do jud… https://t.co/nIiypmGNKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PStieple @QPprincipal @KathySteinhoff @arorvig @HickmanStuGov @HickmanLMC @KewpAthletics @kewpieguidance… https://t.co/o6fHGRAnct]]></document><document><![CDATA[(reading a script in front of an audience of millennials) yeah, its true, my girl boss is a BAMF!]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOCKAL BAR AND QUICK BITE — 3256 W. Lawrence Ave, Albany Park, Chicago! #wednesdaywisdom @chicagobars… https://t.co/TUkJZocQLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StopTheBleed is hands-on program showing how to stop uncontrolled bleeding until help arrives. Training has been h… https://t.co/8LoIkktJBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music for the weekend. 1. Claypool Lennon Delirium: South of Reality 2. Temples: Sun Structures 3. John Mayer’s sin… https://t.co/sOb9Waxytr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Songs that have been stuck in my head for weeks... yep, just this one. https://t.co/nkZYPUx7lL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HQ_IQ @B52Malmet They don't even understand the Amendments or the Constitution. These are college educated folks.… https://t.co/XUd1KXZSS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeted Trump: ‘“HIV Is Cured In 2nd Patient, Doctors Report.” @nytimes Such great news for so many. Tremendous pro… https://t.co/O1ctgC9eTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love kids so my @AtYourBeat fam will be holding an AYB TEENS OPEN DAY next week Sunday 3rd March 🙌🏼 On the day will… https://t.co/i0FYuMa1z8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The joys of working in healthcare? #twdiii @ Legacy Community Health - Fifth Ward https://t.co/Xk8ynIeE88]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi my name is cara and I’m hiding socially bc I feel like shit for not going to work yesterday :-(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is Emma really about to make me sympathize with a fucking puppy murderer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nathan King decided to get lunch at Steak 'n Shake with his two kids, but that lunch is now costing him $3,000 more… https://t.co/Wk8EVOZStT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best crew in the business! 😍 Sitting in the middle of a frozen #KeystoneLake &amp; starting a #snowballfight. 😂❄️🤣… https://t.co/yLSXsykeUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day Tea with Sandy D’Alemberte! Loved introducing my mentees to this legal giant! Thanks for spending t… https://t.co/IUGIGOF0BV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scout_Finch You expect us to choose from this list?! There seriously needs to be an "all of the above" option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So stop asking for advice or ranting online about “ #menaintshit ” when you’ve been warned multiple times but conti… https://t.co/28YYoliIrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#yes #itsfinallyhere #morc #getmeouttahere #miamibound @ Plymouth, Minnesota https://t.co/TzXxQddr0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amargadaxo LMAO NO he wasn’t a pro 😩😂 He just played well &amp; Man U was his fave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOfficerTatum Their fingers were up in the air waiting to see which way the wind was going to blow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least he went to an appropriate place? Not doing Epsteins crap. Sex is not bad, Prostitution is illegal but i do… https://t.co/tMYZsVbZjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see @robynkonichiwa at @TheAnthemDC in moments! #datenightsaturdaynight https://t.co/W4x7pX453D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RStarzAthletics @sc_ladyhoops @CyCreekGBB Oh great!!  Must have that taped good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying not to buy fast fashion but I need new freakin bras and I dont wanna spend $100 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mob Boss @POTUS should be PROSECUTED. It is almost too late! The country is being RAPED by the Criminal GOP!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@debratankersle1 @jflorez @confessions_cup @hmgivingsoul @JackConnie @Cbp8Cindy @suziday123 @linds4fins @ja2cook… https://t.co/0JQA5LRbc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evekendall76 @FactsFantasy #amandaknox How about the 2 cell phones that "Rudy" tossed so that Amanda could make su… https://t.co/SggImPAMuT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers I’d suggest you ask her to prepare something different–something your wife loved as a child that no… https://t.co/WgXCzY9KoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KuOfTheCentury @jesawyer Water-based lubes that don't mess up condoms are amazing by the way. There are so many lu… https://t.co/645fNauvAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul All that bad mouthing Trump.....who knew you had a plan....all of us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m usually reluctant to say things like this, but I was struck last night by the fact that Kody, Mitch and Tony ar… https://t.co/ymRC4S68yL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cbcfifth @stanlouttit This is the biggest, saddest, sickest stain on Canadian History....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSpuds @BxglL @sharon_schwan @sannbs @ChicagoPenguin2 @CSonafelt @RidenerTina @72cricket @ACog1984 For sure Stacey]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Stan the youngest self made billionaire . Go argue with me argue with your ashy aunties about it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could afford it I’d pay $550 for someone to take those out for me cuz damn 😭. They’re precise tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spacecoast_stve @SpaceX @SpaceXFleet @NASASpaceflight @ChrisG_NSF @johnkrausphotos @fodzilla1 @mhaskell24 I'll fin… https://t.co/lABqTOhk0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #MardiGras / #FatTuesday !! How are you celebrating!? 💜💛💚👑 #PKintheMorning @POWERATL https://t.co/VRFy092jRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillWineBanks @FrankFigliuzzi1 Great picture, love it when either or both are on MSNBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soyons plusieurs à soumettre les soins palliatifs comme sujet pour l’emission Tout le monde en parle. Vous direz à… https://t.co/5M33yH9fSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bio students analyze their proficiency on unit standards from the Unit 6 TEKS Check, make plans for showing mastery… https://t.co/kO8vZvNWr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djabatt @JohnFPfaff We definitely do. My mom just confirmed it. Abd a list of other things I won’t mention here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cureari I'm trying to figure out when I became so anxious.... probably in my early 20, but now in my 40, I'm anxious all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[But are you shocked, Cassie? You’re looking super defensive. Hopefully you didn’t want to be an actress after this. #fake #THEBACHELOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOD FOREVER BLESS THE MEMORY AND LEGACY OF THIS GREAT AMERICA HERO! 🙏♥️🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuePlanMty @CervezaTecate Miriam de los Santos López #QuePlanConTecate]]></document><document><![CDATA[holy shit, my pal @SharonCancio is ON HER SHIT !!!!!!!!! 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 yes sis !!!!!!!! 💕💕💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jilliemary @Tom__Coleman @jaimemiserachi @PattiBrookd @happy02013guy @DrJimmyStar @PatGrant7777 @kdshroff… https://t.co/POEDbvwdfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[6th place on the Leaderboard! We kicked butt in the Escape Room for @dividedheaven bday! And I was not on board for… https://t.co/sOkhDKFvKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are y’all listening to these days?  (psa, suggest weezer and you get blocked 😂)]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are a friend in or near Philly... I need help cleaning and organizing.  2 disabled, depressed people = 1 dir… https://t.co/Di6gWHFfhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobbieBarstool If it’s a show about nerd shit and I’m not on it I’m gonna be heated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Application for Graduation has been Approved”  BEST words ever! It’s finally happening. Ya girl will be graduating on May 10, 2019!!!👏🏼😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj The "What A Boutism" about saying something true about Israeli Money in American Politics, and what is sai… https://t.co/yqR7XQ6ubd]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg can’t believe Kylie Jenner was promoting @lauvsongs and @troyesivan on her story 😲 https://t.co/dg2tEqkTsJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been so long since i’ve had to go through this that I really forgot how painful &amp; destroying it was]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: *so close to falling asleep*  *my sister bursts into my room, turna on the lights, and opens my closet*   Her: do you have a shirt? 😐😶😐😶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Diary,  If yo chick come close to me, she aint going home when she post to be]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing keeping me going this week is knowing that @mulaney is hosting @nbcsnl to start off my Spring Break,… https://t.co/qkDAp45exU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending my last morning in Spartanburg listening to this LP from my buddy jimmyjacktoth that I picked up at… https://t.co/9t4XGYpn6V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelianblack Personally I think your sammich looks fucking awful,I am just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferJolly Darn was there last night for theatre but just reading this now. True confession. I read it as $10 w… https://t.co/U6OC0I0Z0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@russfischer Honestly I feel this. I remember going to Hollywood Video or Video Paradiso instead of Blockbuster bc… https://t.co/u0Hyba3iBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure who drew this but it's a definitive invasion of my privacy. @ Haus Wessel https://t.co/AkQ0DiC1jW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of warmer weather and enjoying the warmth in this hair! #btconeshot19_warmbalayage ⠀⠀ @ Black Hawk Hotel https://t.co/WajdNBckKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendssss. I’ve been watching it on and off from start to finish since I was probably 12 😂 (I agree with the offic… https://t.co/iVOLm4du3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KkRk59USYk  C’mon! Support our riders!!!! Team @GavinSolmonese @tedgavin @jvanetten @serratelli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tamriel1776 @LolliStark It’s too late. I guess I’ll have to it tomorrow afternoon. ☹️😕😐🙂😃😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LustNirvana Wishes I was the redheaded sister 💯 https://t.co/vEVbs6E8nz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🦊Foxxy and Greybear playing through the window on #Caturday:)🦊 https://t.co/EZLlRwKhSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a video with full content! We need to stop jumping to conclusions and propagating edited videos whose only… https://t.co/24OlzFpchF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump @TrumpDC Ready to go back!!!!! God bless America, God bless @realDonaldTrump @EricTrump and the whole Tr… https://t.co/t5cPrllwN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Withthewin2 @NothappyMatt @chaddwilkinson @martigriffith @USATODAY @soledadobrien Not true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JemarMxchael @WhoaDelco I just wanna let the world know that deserts get cold...]]></document></documents></author>