<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[$SPX hitting resistance for the third time and now the question is do we pullback to continue the bullish reverse H… https://t.co/FeOlwVoalG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we are shooting the Pretty Things Vaudeville cast at Boudoir Louisville studio! #boudoirlouisville… https://t.co/KtceF3EoA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SEAsheltie @SounderBruce @antonbaa @OysterGreg I spent the last YEAR hoping a truck wouldn’t miss the curve, becau… https://t.co/OcjBWk4VVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up at #UFC235 ...   No. 14 light heavyweight Misha Cirkunov (14-4) vs. No. 15 Johnny Walker (16-3) ... this should be fun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boys Volleyball Went 2-1. Finished 2nd in our pool. Play tomorrow at 10, 12 and 2. Then depending on finish in pool… https://t.co/20HKlCCRwW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HanoiSummit @HouseDemocrats denigrate the concerns of the #Korean People @DNC proves again why they are irresponsi… https://t.co/KtHaHpZAtl]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one on  right thinks MAGA hats are raciest its a great slogan by republicans who saw the nation in a global decl… https://t.co/xDJriDcWh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, can we talk about the fact that legally, in the state of South Carolina, me and @MachineGunBrtni are married...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha. #MiamiFl gets sacked by the @TheDemocrats @HouseDemocrats for #Milwaukee which proved to be the better City t… https://t.co/3reEyEnKyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJSxSTL There are so many excellent fights on this card! I’m really interested in seeing Askren as well. He just d… https://t.co/Tj0qMET4dt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MistressEeclips Hot sauce or chili pepper would do the trick. Make sure the skin is open just a bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jury is back in deliberations this morning. Could we have a verdict sometime soon? Check #thread @kfdmnews @fox4beaumont]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeWil32606343 @dave_sills There are always people who ignore warnings there is nothing we can do about that]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firefighter suicides reflect toll of longer fire seasons and increased stress https://t.co/cstoov7M19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrizzTurner @ira_jax @SouthernmostPen @BuffaloBill95 @GodspeedOnUTube @AB84 Good idea. It was funny while it laste… https://t.co/0XcKwd56Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Of course you do...Putin has told your Treasonous Traitorous ass what to do. You… https://t.co/YigzUcVfVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harlan Yes! They put an entire nation’s republic and democracy at stake. And for what? Childish partisan loser men… https://t.co/SeJWmpiJPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your love is so addictive, a public health advisory was just issued about it. #arlegvalentines]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bromancing in Austin at the @Twitter #TwitterHouse at #SXSW19 w @NathanJTweets and @KevinSaysThings https://t.co/QasXRv4d7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Results of @BMTCTN 1501 Patients with MN standard risk aGVHD who got upfront sirolimus had similar D28 CR to predni… https://t.co/LPRiC9Lo3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leelaaland @ChasingOz_ @NRA @DLoesch Does the mental ward know you are missing???]]></document><document><![CDATA[There aren’t very many free and open source products on the Apple App Store but every now and then you can see what… https://t.co/3W2BWPowAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish Nielsen would stop monitoring ratings for news networks and programs. There needs to be less clickbait, less… https://t.co/AnmoGTo2an]]></document><document><![CDATA[It reminds me of when liberals were yelling at George W. Bush for his college transcripts instead of the fact that… https://t.co/zKfQsDmsnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 44: Skills are currency! Acquire skills create currency. Be the mint. #dirtyhandscleanmoney #skills #currency… https://t.co/Tb9d0WmcOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandsmartin no from this brotha. too much baggage. he seems to be in for himself. hard pass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took me so long to come up with a witty caption that I couldn't BARE it any longer📸✌️🔥   ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ #model… https://t.co/NfUotrZNLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennantJeff 😂 I hate any inauthentic politician, regardless of party tbh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Z- what do you think of the mind scape? C- I have grown to hate it.  I don't find anything good about what I am goi… https://t.co/0oIqQBxzZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The source of happiness is within us. Troublemakers are often well educated. It isn't just education that we need;… https://t.co/oyKLRlie0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprise here. #fail Prime Minister Trudeau's rhetoric reveals deep misunderstanding of taxes… https://t.co/YmTWJk6liA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday to all the ladies. He He He #bikes #motorcycle #adventure #life #wifeymaterial #goals… https://t.co/6pPWKpOeSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This early afternoon ceremony was an emotional one, but so so beautiful. We had a perfect day here in Charlotte and… https://t.co/DpY4WRrFau]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyO1011 Lastly we didn’t outlaw gambling. We made dog racing illegal in Florida. You will still be able to bet… https://t.co/Q48AwSWLqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahPurdy Glad you spent that time with her. Enjoy those special moments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Myles, congrats to Eagle Nation, EARNED AND DESERVED Thank you for all of your dedication to your sport and continu… https://t.co/Vyl5gsPwyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was it just me or did @RondaRousey get like no reaction from the fans #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhScotty @MeghanMcCain I’m really not sure the connection is quite there between an article in The Federalist and… https://t.co/NI2BulqUEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 to 15yrs of renovation! Like, damn that’s a long ass time! 😜📸 #discoveraround #freedomthinkers #letsgosomewhere… https://t.co/Bl993RRO67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wisdominspirit @rosemcgowan Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box |… https://t.co/3fjzYfTnqD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump made the rich much richer. Over 80 % of his tax cut went to the really rich. That help me. But bad for the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lenten 2019 Fish Fry Fridays Schedule for one of my favorite KofC Councils: San Fernando Mission Council 3016 - Viv… https://t.co/svlrWVit1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final, @SkanHockey beats Webster Thomas 5-2, advance to face Queensbury tomorrow at noon in state Division II final]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ewing sarcoma cases are characterized by fusions in EWSR1. Which of the following is not a common EWSR1 fusion partner in Ewing sarcoma?]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in his new kit, I saw Keita play a match in which he didn’t look utterly and completely out of s… https://t.co/yHw3S5Xa5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man what a weekend. Huge shoutout to the volunteers, host homes, small group leaders, worship band, speaker, and th… https://t.co/gAQWGMZdNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johngutierrez1 Morning John  don’t know how you sleep after eating all that!👍☕️😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZNEWSNET She made the choice to leave UK for ISIS controlled area. The consequences of that decision are her’s alone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@originalspin @jesthevu The lead cast was pretty diverse which is why I'm not crying "whitewashing". Mainly just sa… https://t.co/oEhKliKeJy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what DAY it iz... #humpday Happy Wednesday #CourtneyAnn @TexasThighs plz go FS$P IG: @texasthighs https://t.co/nQGqBLeTvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuniculaTv @JohnDeere @FoxNews @TuckerCarlson He has no such remarks, but your remarks are subject to libel so there’s that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek Dick Cheney is in no position to criticize any other administration's foreign policy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THERE IS HOPE "".WE CAN OVERCOME ANY OBSTACLES IF WE PUT OUR MIND TO it and have FAITH as a MUSTARD SEED.GOD IS A… https://t.co/RSEhPY6Y16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyDore You think I’m saying that Vandy is our best wins or something? We have to play you. You’re little bro… https://t.co/BWUMhrOtgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Willow_sMimi @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer https://t.co/pcH9v4DSFC You are absolutely right. What can we do about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton MASSIVE.  INVESTIGATION on Trump 3/4/19: https://t.co/99zmDULje9]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, help me not only to know Your work but also help me to obey Your word. I desire to be close and clean before Y… https://t.co/Dgt9rTRc4W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Goss30Goss @LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Lol you still cling to the BS Russia story. You will be so let down when it shows nothing lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GandySteven @Jamiewho0924 @chelzyb20 @EFisher8445 @ballew_mark @Fuerstenberg15 @bsw224 @GitzMichael… https://t.co/bPy5NOYXrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing my friends thriving!   From opening photo studios, hair salons, bars and tattoo shops, getting signed… https://t.co/Uo9DvGBRJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeReevesCTV what this guys name? He’s on a weather promo you’re running right now. I don’t remember him https://t.co/VOR8uatLg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Washed_nignog @UNikk_Sounds @RelucOptimist @NWDuval904 @DevyDev_ All good Brody we ain’t going nowhere. You know were to go if you need us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rudeboyyiddo Well there’s none of that vile black pudding, so you win! 10/10]]></document><document><![CDATA[While watching old episodes of Kolchak: The Night Stalker I'm reminded of how garishly awesome the 70's were...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Damn Loatian Child Outta a SweatShop Ruined the Best Prospect in the History of History.  Yikes  Your Move #Nike]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to be that vicious poke from the kid in the first row a few games ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very weird #icey #snow #landscape @ College of Lake County https://t.co/MPKfJfLF2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Jambo House - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/N8SYsyr7Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love our sweet boy! #diginyall #puppylove #wholeheaplife #nola #boardercollie @ Broadmoor, New Orleans https://t.co/D0mUprDTNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeteBlackburn Bartolo lol Hate to see Mo in an Angel uni, great swing though]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week when i presented my session “Flowverload: The Worlds Greatest Intro to #MicrosoftFlow”   I asked every pe… https://t.co/2tmi6L3EaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STLDead @mamamoose05 @ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump What did Obama and his “cronies” do to keep trump from being inaugurated?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZBTurf411 Same thing in Florida. Very frustrating. They set up the interview to keep their unemployment going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty flippin awesome we are back in space 🚀👍😊 https://t.co/4LtNmoIM5r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baldjoe @sullivangolf @sb_straitvibin I’ll always be sure to let you know if Duke happens to lose as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a tween wearing headphones with the "Jesus fish" on it. I bet he only listens to Hillsong and other godly music. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if the Senate pulls some chicanery and revives it, the repeated failure of this bill at varying stages undercu… https://t.co/9jvTb43xLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoseCanseco 86 Donruss pic in a 86 topps border? Yep..I drew that Jose. Respond like a normal human. @NickKorora https://t.co/bDN4GKOgKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athomas_tr @Triseum @KamalaHarris @NPSAlumni @npsfoundation @techreview @HarrisCorp @ACT @USDOL @elearningnetwk… https://t.co/HCsr8wukyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 1039 NE 10th Pl #CapeCoral #FL  #realestate https://t.co/CVx4TDOZ2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrAlexisPereira Hadn’t thought about it like this, but now that I think about it? You’re right]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt I missed it. Must have been in the theatre next door at the multiplex seeing Muppet Treasure Island.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday ! Fast Talk, Big Teeth, Big Mouth, (nice Bod) 😀 She's got the boys of the #DumocraticParty behind that… https://t.co/vCIUWSC8Nt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffMarek @armdog @StuMunrue  just got done listening to @SNHockeyCentral at noon, a great show and great job by C… https://t.co/JfgCXLlz9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_brandon_howell @tulanerecruits @TUJewett @eddiesmith55 @DragonBaseball @FuturesBaseball @CarrollDragonFB… https://t.co/2B69gN7H26]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get a @Jeopardy question right that Ken Jennings got wrong https://t.co/lFLglsZLs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth 😎✌#Beware Of The #CompanyYouKeep, #Science Says You #Absorb Their #NegativeEnergy #staypositive… https://t.co/Pb0c4GliG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Candidate Trump promised not to cut your Medicare or Medicaid. President Trump just proposed over $1,00… https://t.co/2wwIy45vEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lnanderson Is Gary right? 4 more inches of snow for Maryville? https://t.co/G9zMkWzddw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing this rebel alliance flag at @wooberryyogurt #starwars #rebelalliance #rebel #worcester @ WooBerry Ice C… https://t.co/nziflNLABr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Stabler 8 PAX went on the Tour de String Bean this morning at #TheRush. But where was @robhallrealtor? https://t.co/NRHWjabBko]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta meet that female quota per year.. I think Molly Holly, Victoria, Sable, Francine or Gail Kim (who I’m sure wo… https://t.co/gqJqPeuiZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 @andersoncooper Said the propagandist that gets his talking points from the @DNC.  Let that sink in. #LiberalLogic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LatanneRene @paulsperry_ I was trying to be, so fair enough. Doeant mean im still not luaghung my ass off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[crazy how niggas out here paying for streams but trying to act like they are popping 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw a #SonomaCounty license plate cover. Guess this is meant to be. #TFCRelo]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why Prince William's children are properly in-line for the crown.]]></document><document><![CDATA[500 NAMES OR MORE!!! edwardjones #marketing #sales #usa @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/lzjmY22mte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jheimbrock @AMCTheatres Hmmm. The forgetting to turn on the projector makes me think 34th or Empire but the “amazi… https://t.co/Mod0gLNdXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saddleback College is part of the South Orange County Community College District @ Saddleback College https://t.co/4IbX5kUy1y]]></document></documents></author>