<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@80sThen80sNow @veggiegurl581 It’s an all American Classic to me.🇺🇸 https://t.co/3EJwVVg7IH]]></document><document><![CDATA[And a bar fight in the bathroom to cap the night off 🤣😂   YOU GO KAY BABY 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your tiny hands typing while you toilet twitter are going to be your undoing. Keep it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want all the girls my exes have also been fcking to know if u wanna be friends I’m right here]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even send Brett attractive pictures anymore. Just absolutely terrible ones with my double chin 😂🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so thankful for those that are able to be honest with me even when it’s hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of spending $15 on a movie ticket you can help and feed a child for a month (: https://t.co/Kz5kFXkED8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElectionBabe Sorry, I can't do that. When you see evidence of machines dropping Black votes out of Black precincts… https://t.co/G0BTMOtNbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That’s a dark day for Jews, don’t make it about Israel like @AOC and @IlhanMN who targeted, in her… https://t.co/D8Mqc3DY7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Panther Fans for making the West Gym Loud and Rowdy! Didn’t have a seat? Scoot in and make some friends b… https://t.co/ftocBymWZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjriedy @VertexPharma @US_FDA @CF_Foundation Thank you vertex.  This can’t come soon enough esp. when it comes to… https://t.co/6OeAkhW7bO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful no one was injured! Many lives could have been lost. This happened at 2:00am. Thank God for the timing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Too late.  Tried the walk back after #Helsinki, too.  Not buying it.  He has chosen to believe and… https://t.co/cTHZNBgfhN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we go back to the days when my main goal in life was wanting to be able to do a back-handspring?   https://t.co/itS9yF48au]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acting out the Legend of Popocatepetl and Iztaccihuatl. Totally accurate. @Apollo_JH #ApolloGearUp #RISDconnects https://t.co/FjddkcfxoU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magical moment from a magical house show hang with caitlincannonmusic @singsarasing @meganburtt 🌟 thanks zmc1965 fo… https://t.co/gz4Lt5wc3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camillelaguire @seananmcguire There are so many stories to be told about women who dressed as men in order to lear… https://t.co/EPPSrIBQuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Lindsey, take a couple of  history courses.    Columbus never set a foot on either America - north… https://t.co/Kci25yKVDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have absolutely no idea why, but I just signed up to run a 5k in March.  2019 got me doing some strange things, m… https://t.co/CTieoDPw2H]]></document><document><![CDATA[The sequin things @NickCannon keeps wearing on #themaskedsinger makes me want to call in and know my future. #hellomissCleo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 90 minutes of weightlessness and peace and science. #float #bouyant #peaceandquiet #thanksboyfriend… https://t.co/6sepFFROhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[the proudest of my day 1 best friends❤️💛 go ball up on saturday https://t.co/mRVzEBVutK]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I only go to nice steakhouses if someone else is paying, because I’m just as happy with Taco Bell” work convos have never been so relatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoneyGram So is $500 the max amount in Canada?  I’ve gone to every single post office in Toronto...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @LindseyGrahamSC this is exactly what you would expect your top law enforcement officials to do if they bel… https://t.co/aaMSDazgHW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patbagley not sure but that Vitiligo (pigment missing from patches of skin) on his face explains the makeup and hi… https://t.co/QbCJPuGAXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chauncey and Midnight have no #FridayMotivation ... they're both having a morning nap! #FridayMorning… https://t.co/YCc6f6YdcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra ment part 2 #REDMAREinLA_Day1 #RedVelvet_REDMARE https://t.co/bSiJK5pYXc]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what’s really going to save local journalism: belly bombers. #jacksonheights https://t.co/9kOrRrc7Ei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegsAquinde Korek hahaha. Tpos may pag filter pa hehe  #POPSSSSMusikero]]></document><document><![CDATA[With God all things are possible🙏. I believe sleeping with my Molly Furry #PWow is a temporary Comfort. ❤️☝️😇📝… https://t.co/UIUWktOhTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepRonKind How much has the Mueller probe cost investigating Russia when our real problems are China and Mexico?… https://t.co/hy9ua2wWFb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacklynnbj @KLinduff @ResistanceGold1 @ransomedpatriot @paulpuckett911 @WHurensohn @BarkinDavid @TrumpsAlways… https://t.co/Sj0WtmQ3YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can’t expect people to invest in your potential when you haven’t done the work to invest in yourself. Heal and grow ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason It is not free. Do you get ads? Do you pay for WiFi? Amazon knows you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[thx for taking on hersh with me @ Hershey, Pennsylvania https://t.co/FdkytLB8K0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @sdXpdx Okay Richard! But only if we rename Social Security and call it Capital Security💯🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgw968 @DonaldJTrumpJr @realDonaldTrump As Fredo would say, “I’m schmart!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Ex Vice President Joe Biden is a pedophile and a child pornographer.  the Obama Administration owes… https://t.co/g9GYXPnxPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS I retweeted ❤️❤️ #TMobileTuesdays #contest #win this would be so awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrumpOrBust2020 @HLAurora63 @SpeakerPelosi Time to  stop wearing high heals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Building strong relationships with students and having a positive attitude. Bringing these two strengths into t… https://t.co/UklLVIiEPM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @FLOTUS Please help the children that were taken from their parents at the border.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@browns_fan_77 @GregDecarlo @EVornheder @dana_zinz @DaveMusen Yep sorry 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 30th Birthday #WorldWideWeb! How has the internet improved your life? #IAmUp #WFAA https://t.co/9bSvdk5b1T]]></document><document><![CDATA[things didn’t go the way I wanted but in two weeks i’ll be ready for war. #nationalsbound https://t.co/ZP4X8z3X1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk much but don’t say u don’t like someone if u don’t really know them 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachelorABC The ABC lawyers are like... #TheBachelorFinale https://t.co/S5JtvOVdim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody @DerekGarretson That looks more like please daddy, please please please]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FakeTrumpEmergency #Resist #Resistance @realDonaldTrump #MuellerIsComingForYou #MuellerTime #RESIST]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took off my wig when I got back to the rental home and some dude asks me, “what happened to your hair?” It’s in m… https://t.co/xuF1nPT7o0]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will foreal offend you and say something mean and then laugh at you for being “sensitive” and not “understan… https://t.co/rV7KCev2DZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeSammi_ I just don't like her? I just don't know, its like shes too attached to Connor. I get weird vibes from Ava.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fourens_ yeah not having to take anti depressants every day anymore is “a problem”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whether you’ve got lazy or crazy days ahead, arm yourself in colors of embroidered classics #livingcoral… https://t.co/zO8mLw9xNt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hector_Tanajara Dude it’s good there have you been there? I used to go in high school they already know me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHicksGOP @realDonaldTrump So what will be done to stop this fucking desperate, psycho, animal??...  Who cost… https://t.co/MKWDJ8LCwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThisIsUs #CarlLumbly sooo different from #TheDitchDiggersDaughter tonight. But a father's love is a father's love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thor_benson @charliekirk11 @AOC thinks she's President. Recall her stating she would be signing the bills in Congr… https://t.co/pECHjkusjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Central Ohio lags country in providing free feminine products in schools https://t.co/0vpPpcT7Fg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I then greeted early voters in the 22nd Ward! #ChiMayor19 https://t.co/AuqFuYvwjt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth the travels! This happened! ❤️ @atmosphere @rhymesayers Eugene Oregon https://t.co/Glu4U6TyiO]]></document><document><![CDATA[More fun moments #aboutlastnight💋 ... @ Soho Beach House, Miami https://t.co/bHqFrOgqYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[BITCH YOU ARE A CHEATER YOU ARE TRASH. YOU CANT BE RETWEETING SHIT LIKE THAT. LMAOOOO  YALL AINT SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesC_MarksAPLan @GO_MarksAPLang You don't know what you got til it's gone. I'll be back tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmv312 Just always be honest with him. Don't mix soaps up with real life. A lot of the things that happen in soaps… https://t.co/eTiBsdaGpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok did they just say “unfounded “ so I found it and then. I couldn’t find it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heeyitsRinnn What a cojncidence were at the gym if ur at Nasty city Hooters lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP @poroshenko @ashrafghani @NATO @jensstoltenberg @POTUS What a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Yellaaaaaaa I just saw your Tweet, I send my condolences and pray Yeshua HaMashiach ,Jesus Christ will take you i… https://t.co/P4HV1WzmBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Sharenting’ ... please just stop, everything your kid does isn’t ‘amazing’ ... it’s just normal. https://t.co/37FRqH3toJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people tweet about tv shows that im not caught up on. No thx, i don’t wanna know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leemaxfield29 @stephenkelley85 @TedHiff @JasonSalhaney @mexusmx @AggieSalterITS @Skymazef3 @KristinGlaeske… https://t.co/zaRtysgrAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaggieJordanACN Hawaii Five-O, because Kono (Grace Park) and Chin (Daniel Dae Kim) left as a result of factors aff… https://t.co/oostNAu1W8]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body really outchea waking up at 6:20 on the dot every morning again 🤦🏽‍♀️ could’ve sworn we had an agreement ov… https://t.co/JGYVu6StpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pasoRN50 @brycetache Aww shucks. I'm just taking the opportunity to help refugees in need. I love that I can have… https://t.co/CR1bwgMHZG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa... number 3 in the US?! But... we’re all supposed to be ASLEEP!!! #TxTisHere @TXT_members https://t.co/jxo3e5HkxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amen!  Our @POTUS can’t be bought and he is a businessman that won’t let us pay $20.00 a bolt. May be an exaggerati… https://t.co/3SflVpZEeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Google to expand its #Charleston-area data center again 👍  https://t.co/kdOE0eTweG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still tired. Still a little sick. Definitely still a bit stressed. But I got to have dinner with one of my favorite… https://t.co/LG68oUBqrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Federer 🇨🇭 vs. Gojowczyk 🇩🇪 #HoppSchwiiz #PistolPeteInTheHouse #BNPPO19 🇨🇭🎾💪🏻🐐🌴😍 @BNPPARIBASOPEN @rogerfederer https://t.co/BQbTeMg1yD]]></document><document><![CDATA[4:30 this morning I had to wake up and clean diarrhea out of tanks kennel. I cleaned it and put a blanket in there… https://t.co/wI9nmwis6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[the Canadian equivalent to giving strippers singles is by giving them a cup of loonies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcramsbball @bsc_coach_p @VSUBasketball Wrong VSU but thank you we appreciate it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time we’ve been made fun of for our accents and it was from other Minnesotans 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey y’all! So, I’m actually scared to make this post but I’m #takingchances this year and following music a bit mor… https://t.co/GozpBoCQ5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find it odd that MSM ISNT reporting on NEW LIES  Cohen got caught telling Congress or the NEW CRIMES his 'lawyer' l… https://t.co/mMctFUHZZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to put my arms around you and hug you... like nothing else mattered in this world!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @soledadobrien Brian - love CNN but I find that sometimes your tweets come across as mean spirited an… https://t.co/Cn69vzGRGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorArmstrong Omg! How can anyone be so heartless and evil??? There are special places in hell for people who tr… https://t.co/tBlJr6IMT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This really how men be. “We can do things couples do but I don’t really wanna put a label on it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherManKG @WCBIWEATHER We will forget this chill starting tomorrow and Sat me thinks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to trying out all my new goodies from my @fabfitfun Spring 2019 Box 🥰😍💜#showmeyourmumu… https://t.co/AmXw4tCSBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that a severed head has consciousness for four seconds is literally the most scariest thing ever...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiebachMichael Thank you for your unwavering advocacy as always! #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very. But I’ve never known any republican politician to work hard unless they were denying people support, healthca… https://t.co/0ke5qS1iUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking to switch service providers and get some free savings perks? Message me for my Rewards referral code and we… https://t.co/mzbXDUqczB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog @valwayne One is black one is white Rosann is conservative Jesse is Democrat🤔😱🐍👹👹🐍🐍😇😇😍😍🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🙏🏻🙏🏻🙏🏻👍👍👍👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My crush on eric foreman is happening again so I’m gonna go watch that 70s show instead of ignoring it now. Thanks for reading xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johanna4892 @diana_x0 @FrankieB_knowin Jo jo are you busy ? Can I call you ?]]></document></documents></author>