<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AOC, I knew and dated my share of pretty girls. I married the prettiest girl. Some very pretty girls are friends o… https://t.co/owX0Lkl6dn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your honesty. I’m a proud conservative and you seem to be a good Democrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrillman_ I thought the Captain Marvel story was very middle of the road but Brie Larson was outstanding. Jude… https://t.co/zVrysDKJXW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StPaulResident Right? Love what they are doing... They were going nowhere with the old group]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 6, 2016... #flashbackwednesday #onthestreet #streetphotography #shadowplay #shadowsonthewall #monochrome… https://t.co/rHk6nhIoBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen those fashion runway shows... who would wear that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Dallas: mist, 38°F 86% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adnforRJMaine @magnolia_icph @Talpog @mainedcm @aldenrichards02 ALDUB together is happier.  #ALDUBxADNLoveLouder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoje venha celebrar a Santa Ceia conosco na @FOL_ATLANTA às 10am e 7pm. Vamos juntos celebrar ao Rei dos Reis e Sen… https://t.co/1kFyAlAAIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been right for a really long time. Been wronged for a really long time. Been wrong for a really long time. Get righ… https://t.co/ZNHz4UHAMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[how do y'all take those selfies that are in the sun without getting your phone's shadow in the way or hurting your eyes hmm science]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAnderson541 @DustinBenge It is, as is public confession, like an altar call response. Baptism is an obedience… https://t.co/M0uhXnYINC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today feels like a good day so let’s ride this manic wave straight to hell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dan Jenkins was, quite literally, a sports writing genius. Many have tried to emulate his style. Few have succeeded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wanna All Black Crib! ⚫️ Walls Black Decor Black Tub Black Pots Black Carpet Black Bitch BLAAACCKKKKK ☑️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcorbin63 Thanks a lot. Now I have to take a motion sickness pill 💊 to keep from getting sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lord knows the thoughts of man;he knows that they are futile.Psalm 94:11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the Cajun feast and subsequent leftover feast seen here @ryangehrke 🦐🦞🦀 📸: @aebymusic @ Beer &amp; Claw https://t.co/fsScESJS7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[#reviews #ketoweightloss #ketodiet #ketolife #ketogenicdiet #ketorecipes #keto #inspiredtobebetter #ketosis #diet… https://t.co/cSuW4tx3Bq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @DineshDSouza That is EXACTLY what the MSM does. Division Division Division. Fighting. Us against them. Controversy. Ratings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daenku32 @SenToddYoung Medicare/Social Security taxes = both massive over reach of the US constitution. EVERYONE b… https://t.co/kWHD1a9djX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregCampNC @GapObscene @M_Livius_Drusus @KipKipkruse880 @NRA The Military is bound by OATH to protect and defend t… https://t.co/aceHU1dqbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Tijuana! :) #Sunrise 06:13, noon 12:00, sunset 17:47 PST (UTC-8), March 3. Day length: 11h 34m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Russ took one philosophy class at his junior college and now he’s Socrates]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I made it out the house with no makeup today, which was not supposed to happen. I wanted to go LIVE but my ey… https://t.co/RURbWlgxSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC 25,000 jobs would have invested in a lot of human capital and generated a lot of wealth for your constituents… https://t.co/SZJCQuEASL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#enchiladas #phoenix #barbacoa #arizona #hatchchile #fiestatowns #mexicanfood #ole #flavoroflove @ Cocina Madrigal… https://t.co/eGZldIGuvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eoinmarron @HassanOE I think 90% of the time I read comics it’s as homework. And I love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sliding into the weekend like.... #MascotRace #PlayNAIA #HappyFriday  @Musketeerhockey @SiouxCityXs @KSUXTonyM https://t.co/WN89RVX9A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should congressional candidates have access to public financing on the campaign trail? @RepWexton #VA10 says Democr… https://t.co/RWrbxGbWSa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonnyHMH Bullets can not kill the boogeyman!! Silly book writer. https://t.co/BddY3ZwS1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's not really a joke. You literally are the worst market in the NHL...maybe tied with the Coyotes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoopvilleAdam Well let's be fair Adam. Creighton and a ranked SIU team played that day as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimBrando @JacquesDoucet @wildcatnews @WAFB Tim your a very smart man, you know what’s up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reunited with my Bluefire best friend&lt;3 G1 forever honeyy🍯💙 @BlueFireWild https://t.co/iYqSBt7R1f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bird’s awesome.  Take a break from the turkey in the WH.  Smile with this. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my last 5 bounces:  1. Family Of Geniuses track (my band) 2. fuzzy indie rock track (for @marmosetmusic) 3. wannabe… https://t.co/cfk41d2Tc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find that Hidden Valley Ranch dip commercial to be ummmm gross.  I don’t like ranch to begin with but I certainly… https://t.co/fWHS6sfpZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre❤️!! #medianaranja #valentines2019 @ Hyatt Regency Milwaukee https://t.co/Sq7KZtccxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbendery @NRA @FoxNews @SebGorka @FoxNewsSunday @rupertmurdoch @HARRISFAULKNER @AP @LouDobbs @seanhannity… https://t.co/l9FkBcrd2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[This vibe thing isn’t working alone.. Takes two to make the dream work..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PimpMasterYoda1 @JustinWhang I just started playing RDR2 and the first word that comes to mind is "tedious".]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the Evangelism of the next generation will be hospitality. - @jayrpathak   #ArtOfNeighboring… https://t.co/OUykLuAjvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vizekonig @JC00011 @michellemalkin How did the economy triple under obama ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobParkerFS1 @FredNBCLA 600 wings? Isn't that your normal daily amount of wings? Everyone knows Rob loves to eat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickTyler55 @B_Eddy10 @MarkJAralious @SmithLonnie22 @GarvisScott https://t.co/FkwX2LeIL5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyMayhew9 I’m extremely optimistic that there will be more than 82 games for this team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CupersLee I still don’t understand why a team that’s in the middle of a rebuild is in a hurry to sell off a 27 yea… https://t.co/Q6EPFBiV5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you so much to everyone who grabbed prints from me at captainscomicexpo !!!  I had a great weekend and I was… https://t.co/X73sbW1DUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kira742 @COSChallenge @ConejoOpenSpace Amazing — both your pics and your ability to run that far in that terrain. 🏃‍♀️🏃‍♀️🏃‍♀️🏃‍♀️🏃‍♀️🏃‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheers 🍻 from San Bernardino to Camden from my big bro @CalvinJcmd Happy Birthday to me 🎂🎁🎉🎊🎈 @ San Bernardino, Cal… https://t.co/p7bT9xsXIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgihurd @AShchennikova @sunii567 @Luisablanco20_ Say EVERYONE'S favorite gal. (#goMorgigo)🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neghassi @geraldwbrown @grayfox1980 @RachelRumbelow @RealSaavedra @AOC It often gets lost in text something you ma… https://t.co/a0F2iHzFwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome seeing my dear friend @briansolis new book on display at the Austin airport. #SXSW https://t.co/BPQBOdiLKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Request nap. (@ John F. Kennedy International Airport - @jfkairport in Queens, NY) https://t.co/Obw73dmvmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I desperately need two Scuttleboss’s on Gigantic Spiders. Any chance anyone has one or two they’d sell me? Id great… https://t.co/pPQpU0LVal]]></document><document><![CDATA[The HONEST LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES WITH INTEGRITY ALL KNOW this is a criminal enterprise and except for about 20 c… https://t.co/wwQevInH3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @NUTrackandField on winning the Big Ten men’s indoor team championship. #Huskers https://t.co/6EFjqZENLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It was Delany’s pursuit of Nebraska in 2010...” I hate to admit this, but Nebraska was the pursuer back that.   Al… https://t.co/UIUJAbdie0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamario44 @CALLMEMRTIBBSS @JustRyCole @DekuSaiz You want a complete turn around in how long.  Two years?  We suppo… https://t.co/rV1OMwVXGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Hawkeyes win the Big Ten Tournament 90-76 over Maryland. Megan Gustafson had 45 points and 10 rebounds against a t… https://t.co/PAEG0A3LW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breida balled when he played. Kyle will find ways to get him the ball and keep him healthy. He isn't a workhorse be… https://t.co/WYGDUQE4XM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyRainbow “I was Donald’s bitch, man” sung by Michael Cohen to the tune of “If I was a Rich man”]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to define terms like "pro-business" and "pro-growth". This is how define these terms. If we didn't break up… https://t.co/kzJeiTHoTI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish this durag phase would pass, it’s not cute. Wear the shit at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NPowellFF @FFDynastyDan @DynoTradeCast @FFStompy Bennie &amp; The Jets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Entomologist friend uses leafcutter ant colonies, which cultivate fungus garden ecosystems, to start rainforest-bre… https://t.co/iz36sJksEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@facelesswook @Newsweek ...Should've been taught better before even thinking about joining the service]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTimefurlulz I have degrees in political science and criminal justice....and Trumpturdds cant understand logic and… https://t.co/utPtxlPCnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyTraditional Bte, the Afghanistan thing is a nice touch since one can’t even manufacture a color able reason Is… https://t.co/nApyIY3uOu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jane Mayer on the Revolving Door Between Fox News and the White House https://t.co/M43YMOExgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at this sunny beauty! SUN40 for 40% off. #SanDiego #procompressionambassador]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prydin You should shadow the #BeachOps crew that uses #wavefronthq to run Wavefront. That's some next level right there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got back on track today..  🏀Tennessee -2 🚫 🏀VMI +19 🚫 🏀North Carolina -4 ✅  🏀Michigan St. -3.5 ✅  🏀UCI -7 ✅  🏀Nevad… https://t.co/iMIdMN1ehc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisdelia @John_Quaintance Reminds me of when you dressed up like @MichaelLenoci 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC I wonder if Bernie Sanders, AOC, and the Democrats are watching a Sampling of the BS The New Green Deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillysDonutsHTX Just saw this story on khmermemes ig page and it definitely made me tear up a lil 😭. Being khmer a… https://t.co/NY9a7S0RrH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a meteorologist must be the easiest job. You get to make up random bullshit about the weather and get away with it 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humasqureshi  My dear huma qureshi Today  Ahmed malik Namaz prayer  India Bharat all is well  InshaAllh https://t.co/3nIBtwacsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump your silence on #CoastGuardTerrorist is deafening... did you not see it on @FoxNews, sir?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MichelleNgGong brings the #RealTalk: “Failure to execute never got you anywhere”  Volunteer + Follow Through]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realArovia I’ve moved since ordering my spud and need to change the address. This is the only way I’ve found to ge… https://t.co/qpsvhon157]]></document><document><![CDATA[TAMMI has gone thru life being totally confused....Ann and Laura are her role models...Therein lies the problem....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SP_Peterson6 No way Boyle is out of that lineup. Don’t know who the odd man out is but it wouldn’t be Boyle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsAlexMarshall He would have got paid if he had signed the contract which was offered.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing that would’ve made Bradley Cooper &amp; @ladygaga ‘s performance better is if he peed his pants after. #TheOscars2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EA_GZaro No motm for this weeks UCL and Europa games? Honestly seems like content team forgot the games were even… https://t.co/BecGONQmUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That shit was to funny, really try to pull some shit out ya ass today huh lord “niggas” never did anything like that ☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Richzeoli @SandyK648 @PhilaParking @DawnStensland @jimdonovancbs3 @CBSPhilly @LarryMendte @6abc It is a criminal e… https://t.co/ru3XmT4t9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I asked about a young Gears player who played in our events. Unfortunately, he no longer comes because his parents… https://t.co/vXRGgTrvuX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Seaforth Sportfishing - @seaforthboating in San Diego, CA https://t.co/e7BnkERaII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Yawn, why doesn't she just renew her subscription to the National Enquirer. #LeastEffectiveFLOTUSEver]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worth noting that she broke this story while simultaneously teaming with @stjbs covering rapid-fire developments in… https://t.co/khtAfcv3nS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 54 - 2/23/2019 - Maggiano’s and Beethoven’s 7th with one of my best friends tonight! Thanks for the invitation,… https://t.co/HWuiUfhuqJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomangell The hemp farmer will now grow close to a marijuana farmer. Or visa versa. Da two don’t mix. Make female@thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Over400ppm @DaxWarren1 @realDonaldTrump Obama released his tax returns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch The guy looks like his mommy is calling him to take out the garbage bag full of his Fruit-Loops!!!😜😂👍🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreNigeria @ogundamisi Same senatorial district with Kwankwaso, we wait !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it isn’t cool to praise @theresa_may but I can’t help but feel that she is trying her hardest. The dancing -… https://t.co/qPm4eOtBtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most dangerous dog walker. @ Pekin, Illinois https://t.co/ulyGIUqdOZ]]></document></documents></author>