<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Can my mom just lmk what I’m having cause I’m over having a gender reveal]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp;&amp; we have a date for our Field of Dreams family vacation!! So excited!! https://t.co/p1l4jQXjsb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on in and meet our friendly doctor! We would love to meet you and help you achieve your health and beauty goal… https://t.co/aV2paKVEMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mellyb1979 @ghenderson1013 @MarilynMassoud @catlovertamjo @cookiegigan @FlossieShelley]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love how many commercials during the Oscars are promoting perseverance! Plus, Gaga stating how it’s hard work and n… https://t.co/gPHwX29Vyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesMarstersOf @actordougjones @RealGDT @DCockle Yay!!!! 2 of my fav buffy dudes!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_com When demented lazy rich white know it alls have nothing better to do than bitch about non-exsistant situati… https://t.co/9cwfQUcEuP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarbonAtom6 @kjwallman @notwokieleaks @allahpundit @AOC That's not how incentives work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOT’S OF SURPRISES at my Seminar at 11:45 am Today #atljewelryshow Plus Watch 👩‍🎨 Artist  Ross take the notes 😲 https://t.co/BmzDp4eDm9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TannerKoomar @FilAmIAm — was it you who told me that Cali was a dairy state?! I always thought dairy = the Midwest… https://t.co/KRgnhAF9e0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please interrogate every "heartwarming" situation you see in the media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are way too many great quotes for education. This is just 1 of many. #sanangeloisdtweets19 #adobespark https://t.co/Kv562ZNqta]]></document><document><![CDATA[so here i am studying my ass off at 2 am getting hungry and come to find some one took my chicken tikki masala haha what the FACK #302cw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le SEUL avantage de revenir en voyage de l'Europe c'est que a 7am t'es dboute à vouloir faire ton ménage, ta vaisselle et legit un marathon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LIMALicensing looking forward tonight’s networking party at Toy Fair 2019. #Licensing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make that 3 now ☺️💜 @BTS_twt  #BTSxWembley #BTSxMETLIFE #BTSxStadeDeFrance  #BTS_WORLD_TOUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[These same Niggars that use mice in QP styling Gel work in supermarket &amp; your food there has mice &amp; rats in it too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWaduba @Harinzeyart @KevinHart4real @IAMQUEENLATIFAH @SAMKLEF @MoreReginaHall @MeaganGood @HeavenlyArtz… https://t.co/IpqUaUQVmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to have a food and wine oriented cooking show. I know I’d be really good at it so I won’t even waste everyon… https://t.co/SkvwQq9Fu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night for the Dorothy Height Dinner, wearelwd honored misstinalawson !! And in honor of her and her husband Ri… https://t.co/osXHdcH2di]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ts13ofmyheart @HBO @GameOfThrones @Maisie_Williams @SophieT @nikolajcw @lovegwendoline Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZNEWSNET Oh yea true, she is a Democratic Stalinist 🧐 #NeverVoteademocrat #MAGA #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FierceCheerMom I’m not really sad. It’s been a good ride! Lots of great memories and moments!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦🏻‍♀️ wow! I’m disappointed to hear that. So basically she’s just waiting to hear more lies and not hold him@accoun… https://t.co/pmwHJbMHXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskTarget I picked up my drive up order and there are 2 items missing. The app says to check back later to report a problem.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It would be nice if after 2 years + we had a president who knows how to use a teleprompter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm coming next Sat. To give a multi-sensory AI audiovisual piano concert @ucberkeley #cnmat #audiovisual #ai… https://t.co/28sD2v8sHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Social Work month to all of my amazing colleagues! Thanks to everyone of you for all you do! https://t.co/11dGFO9lPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[«Bang bang... my baby shot me down» 💥 . . . #AFOL #smallafol #lego #legobatman #legofans #batman #joker #bang… https://t.co/3UQLaol35W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman today and every day. Happy day to us ✊🏽👩🏻💜 @lisamarkuson thank you @strandbookstore @ Strand Book Store https://t.co/VMVDupIJWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRS7BTS @bts_armynana @BTS_twt Can’t believe I did it! I’m freaking out I actually posted it💜 ty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAdooGordon As long as they can get the false claim circulated is the goal. They have no moral decency and regard… https://t.co/D53opFs0L7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to rile up my Rockets people but I’d like to see the Celtics win just because they have been turrible lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein He's not using foil. Since he's on the toilet he's gonna use toilet paper &amp; the cardboard rolls it comes on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least pasok yung future Ateneo Lady Eagles natin na si Faith Nisperos and Angel Canino. Good Luck girls! #OBF 💙🇵🇭]]></document><document><![CDATA[My manfriend, who normally is critical of my choice to watch @markalfordkc and @fox4kc in the morning (I’ve explain… https://t.co/2WcsLh6Lyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boatoptional2 @JulieSummerman @canadiandaws83 @DoloresManley4 @alisoninsco @cathyhadenough @shannongailmc @howllr… https://t.co/ial2sWO7BK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti It's taking everything I have not to individually mock the people who aren't getting this right no… https://t.co/wpmMdqxRMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stronger, everyday. ☄️ That’s been my 2019 mantra.  There has not been one day that I haven’t said it to myself or… https://t.co/6fGEBDvXoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYFarmer Damn, too bad I live too far away to "just happen" to be in the neighborhood around dinnertime!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful sign from an old chapel @NeonMuseum @ The Neon Museum https://t.co/O9KmOpMvNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really excited for my dad to help me set up my new comp desk and chair this weekend. Today would have been a great day to work from home ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pairing nutrition with finances Community Mentorship Program @UMNExtFD @pdolson01 @BecherEmily @mceetweets… https://t.co/Dydme9KtYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man wakes me up just to talk to me for a bit and fall asleep 🙃 now I’m wide awake -_-]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMallicoatKTVU @ClaudineKTVU Good morning! You guys crack me up… I was hoping I’d be up to watch my cell phone tur… https://t.co/h66GWVABPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the day the new season of @AHWAmySedaris mmmmm DROPS! 🎉 🤘🏻📼 https://t.co/fjeBBVt6fV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel time with whoever this random fangirl is #captainmarvel @ AMC Shiloh 14 https://t.co/vHGMZ7VWAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have mitochondrial DNA 🧬 on my mind.  #RootsGroundYou #SeedsAllowYouToGrow #BalanceforBetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[if @TJ_Fisk_ still likes me after today i’ll be surprised, i’m giving him a little taste of what it’s like to be in a car with me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXACTLY! Let's not forget that young Student that was sent home in a coma to die  😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash AOC deBlasio the governor of New York all are to blame!  More and more are leaving that state.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cosby wins big over James River 72-49 in the 6A semifinals game.. Onto State Championship game this Wednesday!… https://t.co/eQDM3NtaDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are so many people trying to become the democratic nominee and I’m so confused. Who do I go with?! Who has th… https://t.co/grv9Rurh3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rant time: one thing that frustrates me about architecture is how unforgiving it is. You can be doing perfect work… https://t.co/KTQIo26RpM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of great moments at the Oscars last night.....this was my favorite.  #Oscar2019  #ItsOnlyCrazyTilYouDoIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[terror attacks in Europe, a report from Washington-based non-profit public policy organisation Bookings Institution… https://t.co/GDlSKwTtLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get a game show where the contestants just have to correctly pronounce Massachusetts towns?  The first one t… https://t.co/1gHjgLCZ7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikestore Nike outlet store in Marana, Arizona 6401 West Marana Center Blvd Tucson, AZ 85742 United States]]></document><document><![CDATA[MURPH!   Sean Murphy (12) taking a few swings today.  #AthleticsST  #BabyA https://t.co/D5K2dGxCXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAnimalRescue I’d like to do the same to him....and no one rescue him!!!! P.O.S.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @WalshFreedom Fake news tapper we the ppl do not trust you clown]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blerdgirlblue Every day! Full time job, single Mom w/three kids. And at this moment PMSing (sorry TMI). There are… https://t.co/9ZXQFvXals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dank Hill Wheat Double IPA by @NCBCBeer @ The Borough Brewhouse — https://t.co/8czaLKLGjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my one and only. Love you ❤️🎊🥳 https://t.co/dIs3PbOUTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoofMcFloof @KevasRobert Absolutely agree. I was furious with his Trumpian “no collusion” statement prior to the end of investigations]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be the Change 💜🙏🏼 @pRncssLyssa is absolutely beautiful inside and out and artistic to boot 🎨 May God continue to sh… https://t.co/i9mehSYDVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great watch! Am I a racist because I see our American culture and language being stolen by people who have no inten… https://t.co/Ck2g3sHFyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sabrina en Instagram Stories  #Goodwin #CutestPet #iHeartAwards https://t.co/n6R6rnjHJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abrázame, acércate un poquito y siénteme, pa’ cerrar bonito quiiiereme, lo demás solito se dará 😏 @iskanderlara]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bestseller   "A wonderful read, breathtaking in places with superb pacing."  "This book was well written. I couldn… https://t.co/ZIAhrSSiz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKevinGarcia @desiringGod I mean he could have saved some words and just wrote "I'm a misogynist" on a piece of… https://t.co/XT8Lw6YnhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a mom is not good for my anxiety. Everything has to be okay. I promise.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everytime i take a little sip of water at the gym it tastes like heaven 👅💧]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT jonasbrothers @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/MaPHZqAa2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏃‍♀️Con Sue Photography and Design🏃  🏃Like our photos...Follow our IG 🏃‍♀️  🏃‍♀️These designs were created by: Conn… https://t.co/8pQS6WacNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone take my debit card away!!! I can’t/won’t stop buying concert tickets 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speechless. This is a gross overreach of power. How did this Tuskegee-esque study ever get past an IRB or ethics re… https://t.co/er9hWktnit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NGDAverk @karels_jennifer @giulia_belvisi @curry9903 @Danielle21A @OncerHardy @StephanieR___ @RumpeGoldWeaver… https://t.co/kdUvr9Bz36]]></document><document><![CDATA[That being said, I'm not hiding from the world. I plan to show myself even as I use my pen name. What's important i… https://t.co/byKtS3t3Vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[U niggas better find yall worth! Don't let these bitches treat u like you're worthless king lol u deserve more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSearcaigh One could point out how much like his stepmommy she looks...]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Fridays, coffee keeps me alert until it's time to go home and be thoroughly unacceptable. ~Nanea Hoffman Court… https://t.co/Rrop9QxVx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every #nurse I know is strong, smart, and tough as heck 💜 8 celebrities you never  knew were once nurses https://t.co/SlsQlKHsQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wood on wood bottle opener. 🍆🍺😏   #wooden #bottleopener #wood #woodOnWood #peter #woody #morningWood #phallus https://t.co/8h84NWl74a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeAndriaJ I’m so happy to hear this!! Your honestly has always been something I loved about you!! I’m proud of you Le! 🙏🏽🙏🏽 keep going]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s day! 💪🏼I’m grateful for all the amazing women in my life! To my family, friends and col… https://t.co/iLkz3Jmbpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got help thanks to @midas after zero response or help from @avis. Thanks so much for the incredible custo… https://t.co/7ymjvQc8kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morris_Chestnut No, Keaton! That murderer is a terrorist! #TheEnemyWithin @nbcenemywithin https://t.co/GOEft86mfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notcapnamerica What is with this “Aunt Jemima” bullshit??!! Shame on them!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamescharles I think you should fill your wine rack with empty bottles with your own label 🍷🍾🥂💄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liz Story gives a shout out to @KateMessner and The Brilliant Deep #mra19 https://t.co/rVDYrRrBZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me tell you how fucking tired I am of cleaning every single damn day]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the night for some amazing #hockey in #ldnont at @BudGardens @TeamCanada Women vs some American team ... 🤷🏻‍♀️. Can’t wait!]]></document><document><![CDATA[’ve accepted the challenge to post covers of 7 Children’s books I LOVE: no explanations, no review - just cover. My… https://t.co/Wdkbc2AmG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then we put those little bits of liquid in a machine and see some weird shapes and feel either  really satisfied or… https://t.co/MlpYLQoW0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woman Dies After Exposing Bill Clinton tied Baby Slave Farm https://t.co/LqyKqjhU5n via @YouTube #Oprah #JohnOfGod… https://t.co/CV6d30lYsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the @browns for showing us such a good time last night!  : : #browns #cleveland #thisiscle #theagora… https://t.co/jC98IL46KW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Multiple fatalities as tornadoes hit Alabama and Georgia  https://t.co/YVJun45w9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@love_JMJ_love @MAFSLifetime Exactly.  If shes not feeling love and affection then shes not going to let him go pla… https://t.co/3TFuioVAh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colins' KARMA. Colin Kaepernick is doomed because Nike made this big mistake https://t.co/z8JzvEHZFj via @PatriotPulse]]></document></documents></author>