<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why yes I am seeing #ellendegeneres and sitting hella close. Happy Valentines mikeneffto @ Scotiabank Arena https://t.co/XVbNqbc9bi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every trip to mama's ends with flowers.!💖 @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/b6BwCOsoKJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noticia aún no confirmada, pero imaginamos sea cierta: Envío d 6 Buques d Armada Vzlana, a impedir q barco d nombre… https://t.co/yMTkq06YJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know when TV coverage will be announced for the Hockey East Quarterfinals? Assuming soon after tonight's fin… https://t.co/XE8INabQve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our little hometown paper had an article on the 10 “worst intersections” in our town. They are pretty much the busi… https://t.co/HEBfYelC8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruizmassieu @PRI_Nacional Que desaparezca el @PRI_Nacional del registro y juicio a @EPN https://t.co/1WNUucv6J6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Jim Jordan, you are a despicable asshole and a traitor.  Please resign your position and leave this country now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kishoreragi @GeraldKutney @Shemayah5 Absolutely no climate scientist does that. Modeling is in one sense a massive… https://t.co/0oL51fyJcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way I am changing diapers on my baby, it’s like I am already training them for a career in gymnastics or yoga t… https://t.co/465Vxfll5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wedge down screener, this is to find stocks that are in a downward wedge pattern and you can use this to catch reve… https://t.co/XB3dGGDe3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[First @anaupatree then @davey_kim , then @Adizah_E  and now @ascentofjazmin. Work with @WhatsRaySaying at… https://t.co/B3X7gssbL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[You carefully ignored my stories of sisters without gas/water, nephew without a job, ‘cause he’s not a commy. As a… https://t.co/sds6HYqEq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennSWhite It’s every day around here.  Sigh.  I hear a rumor that teenagers sleep in.  We will see eventually I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably one of the Most fulfilling thing we can do and it’s only the Beginning ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDK why people think Kawhi and them beating the 76ers in a 7 game series]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando me dicen porque le voy al @FuerzaMonarca escuchen esto. @ESPN_JorgeRamos lo dice perfecto.   Tal vez Morelia… https://t.co/RI79favsNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASaunders_PGH Something in my gut told me the Bills news was almost too good to be true. It did allow me to watch… https://t.co/fCVmolOi00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halikman912 @GmurphNBCS @Phillies @Pirates @TMacPhils @bendavisnbcs @JohnKruk Was very exciting to see them live i… https://t.co/fNcexVwoAj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelWxlf_ My speed comparisons between the two https://t.co/BvBZ5M2nf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevehosid @business @bopinion The graphic I shared is information compiled and released by the US Department of L… https://t.co/r925ptFrsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LastmansBadBoy who is great at customer service at the London Ontario location... NOOOOOOOOOOOBODY!!! #nobody]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saritam I’m not a scholar by any means either but that’s fishy as can be]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my favorite coxkring disintegrated. I'm devastated. Time to go on @FortTroff and buy some new toys 💅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dejo esto por aquí y me retiro lentamente en Alta en Charlotte Hornets https://t.co/iA5nZaiO8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Miss_Met @itsmilesbrah Now if @SNYtv could do something like this...... “https://t.co/3gbanTlLd1”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHCNM I am excited to help out in any way I can!  #smallbusiness #OneABQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YanksAreComing Seeing if my @ATLUTD can pick up where they left off of what the season will look like with changes… https://t.co/B8YtoM1qiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KopelmanWX @JeneeRyanCBS2 That's because you both never lost that childlike sense of wonder.  We adore that about you two.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Beach Haus® Parade Day by @beachhausbeer at @OldTownPubBtown — https://t.co/wvT09Nul8K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlravechespn great listening to the #bauercrest commercial! - 93 Waiter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Harden is playing defense like it’s a real game 😂 #NBAAllstar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even now, there are more parts of police reported narratives that aren’t making sense that are going viral. Such as… https://t.co/9rW57mcKRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kime106 @realDennisLynch @BarackObama You better learn the facts there buddy before you comment again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nike continues their “Dream Crazy” campaign with another brilliant video! ♥️♥️♥️ Nike - Dream Crazier https://t.co/nR57Gb7Vap via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[💙💙☁️☁️🎀🎀☁️☁️💙💙 #protecttranskids #TransRightsAreHumanRights https://t.co/hYVyBsQRN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you guys uncover something terrible about @BrotherNature that makes me dislike him I may have to quit the Internet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disney may be great, but it’s not sustainable. Maybe just for me. It was really hard to make the decision to leave… https://t.co/KBe7ggWfSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost oldglory_dc with get_repost ・・・ Our final combine will be held right here in our hometown. Come out to Cath… https://t.co/TqRQICjXfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Show Me the Meaning of Being Lonely is low-key one of the greatest pop songs ever done. Don't @ me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un film qui sera fort probablement sur ma liste de films à voir ce printemps !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YaleCEO @MikeNavarre73 @Everytown You're missing the point and putting words into my mouth. I've given plenty of f… https://t.co/90I5FpVn1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Petition to have @ramsaydubs be this guy for Halloween https://t.co/t4Z6oW1Qbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police have identified the man they’re searching for in the attempted rape and robbery of an 83-year-old woman in t… https://t.co/PnZHgffvhZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My high school is CLOSING so that everyone can go watch the girls’ basketball team at the state competition. THAT’S SO CRAZY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a killer find: a rare Horus, Prince o/t Sun poster from Thailand on Ebay. I found a photo online for use on… https://t.co/WPRF7FjCqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WFLAAvery @WFLA @WFLAMelissaM No kidding! culpable negligence on the part of the fire Captain which clearly is not… https://t.co/BmgHt7KiD1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wild up on Blues 1-0 after two periods. Whatever happens... just please no OT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never ask a friend for a discount, or a “pass.”  There’s a couple of reasons:  - It’s a low-class move.   - Your fr… https://t.co/hSGkhFwcpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CadeNoster5 I blocked this girl bc she was bragging about “beating up” 3 girls at once, and I never followed her o… https://t.co/4B7P8g7IJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see the end. Peace be still. @ Hagerstown, Maryland https://t.co/ah6bTP6VSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@megkelly92 @SensInsider because he will...without any argument.....do whatever his dumbass boss tells him to do...… https://t.co/DsaZluwZsM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I really want to know is what Jim Grant thinks of this after this weekend’s Barron’s column. Are cats better w… https://t.co/CpvPnTLSy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to build #ark for all the #tears 😭 when #Trump win in 2020 https://t.co/PNvCQBzGWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeforman21 @gphswildcats @SHS_PirateBball Regret that I missed you, Mike. It’s absolutely beautiful at the ballp… https://t.co/t9U4sektTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watching the Yokohama show AJPW did other day, skipped to top 4 matches and hot damn Nomura/James wasn't ba… https://t.co/bwB5kByXH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gsrandolph @fccincinnati Agreed completely, we have plenty of guys that belong. Just need to buuld chemistry and upgrade 2 or 3 spots.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SFGate and @BayCityNews for the shout-out for the @oceanfilmfest : SF’s 16th Annual International Ocean… https://t.co/C7bM2CX0w6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 10.22 km in 1h:15m:01s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/zt0G0MY48S]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday to meetups at @tgifridays with my bestbuy co-workers 🍻🍺 #FlashbackFridayWithFriends #FBF… https://t.co/T3JXF5UTfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another big batch o' shows coming to the #Detroit metro https://t.co/qHKxUSKdiK @313Presents @DTEEnergyMusic… https://t.co/DPFhSKM5kN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YoungAv0n @RavishinRUde @JonRothstein The point is St John's has lost at least one game to 6 different Big East te… https://t.co/4HA7fxVotY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If these waters could tell their stories .... Lower East River https://t.co/bsA09Kb7cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirRantAndRave @b_hubb21 @PastorTrey05 @BeasPodcast I think it's just one of those silly questions they like to throw out there]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well it sure beats THE BACK OF THE MOVING VAN. (No I cannot get over this. A child was riding unrestrained in the b… https://t.co/syvINjTrCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByMHarrington All words out of these clowns, same effort night after night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt old shot by daytonpaiva Taken in PA somewhere?  1996 perhaps.  Still have that bass @ New York, New York https://t.co/LczFsn2VUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Ferris says Mujey Dumbuya spent a lot of time at Quinn James home visiting her boyfriend Dequarius Bibbs. Mor… https://t.co/pIFRRYjMCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temp: 59.3°F Wind:1.5mph Pressure: 29.998hpa Falling Rapidly Rain Today 0.12in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foreordaine whatsoever comes to pass.—Appointed to accomplish, or to bring about whatever is good, and to permit what is evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFried_GDP @GSU_PAC @GeorgiaStateMBB Grew up near Brookhaven (went to Ashford Park Elem) and then Tucker (Class of… https://t.co/Nl1tcVPuZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gralger I remember this vividly bc me and my co-PA were so bummed it wasn't at millennium where that wouldn't have happened]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigersShs @Iam_kjj @MoneyyyMikeee @saintpresto @_1flyjay @thatboydarius01 @D3vo_ @thekidtj2 @SHS_HCS… https://t.co/QEBFfNb7ZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mathieudorval97 @ericforest Le PR s'est fait reviré de bord par un joueur fâché d'une défaite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeJo_1 Nah, it's a different version of this song https://t.co/uNXe4pIBdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matvelloso @TulipRide Not this new one. I ride it on my triumph Cafe racer / scrambler.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioSportsNet @Make_YourCase Have you heard of Santana and Kipnis? Bauers has a high power ceiling. Martin hits hi… https://t.co/Etp5YxExkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allJACE We had to put his head on that chopping block for him to come out and play. We welcome this new Ingram.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KendallJuly_ @PositibosiJ @ArianaGrindr26 Wag kana kasi mag alter mars para ma discover ka ng mg BBC.. makes your mama proud.. nu kba😋😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NationalAction Network salutes 4 women of the movement during #WomensHistoryMonth. Congrats Cynthia Davis, preside… https://t.co/9gGxRIHikZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smmrvl buang hahahahah basig nak limot nato sa imo yot kay naka limot na siyang Jae lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[me as @RealSkipBayless do the rockets even need james harden? #NBAonABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[FLN.... Big citrus. - Drinking an IX [deathstill] (Ghost 671) by @AdroitTheory @ Craig Brewing Company  — https://t.co/xoDZDUTjDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter Scotty, beam me up! This planet has strange leaders governing it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Money Laundering Tax fraud Treason Emoluments   violations Campaign finance crimes Countless RICO  crimes.  Let me… https://t.co/SXRjvw4Dff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Family. Know that God loves You more than You can fathom and........CRUSH IT today!God bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Ammonia in your beef, is not beef!  Know where your food comes from.  Read labels, ask questions and… https://t.co/yALRpZQfs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thejackatak99 😭😭😭😭wrong bald headed black dude in the NW lockerroom. Sorry wasnt me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoooo I just saw a dude drop off a ratchet girl at doghouse to get her car 😂😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jzanier468 I love fish and chips. Especially if it has a thick, flaky crust. And very pickly tarter sauce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laauraakaatee I don’t but from what I’ve heard from people coming in and out of the locker room isn’t good]]></document><document><![CDATA[#batteries #drained again https://t.co/8pvcJRLPU5 #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer… https://t.co/nenPmBXF1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff ...necessary to construct his wall/fence. He's too old to be able to see the project through. Too bad c… https://t.co/hdXiAz0TVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lsarsour @mehdirhasan @rafaelshimunov @WaywardWinifred @womensmarch @AOC @IlhanMN @imraansiddiqi @People4Bernie… https://t.co/gzGRjKCWXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 @maggieNYT Imagine that. A page from the despot/dictator handbook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just realized that @philly311 was celebrating today because it’s 3/11. That makes sense. It just took me 12 hours to process that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls tweet like this and wonder why they can’t find a man that wants more🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWilliams22 @thecoachvogt They compliment each other so well. Buck sweep is so intricate to run, which makes i… https://t.co/ryxOQqPltQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can Trump be impeached for not condemning extremists in his own base and openly attacking the media for calling them racists?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump So asking people to "...all mobilize...be on the right side of history...make the moral choice bet… https://t.co/RekBp0E4dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the problem with aides and assistants. They tell you what you want to hear]]></document></documents></author>