<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Im trying to right my wrongs, but its funny, them same wrongs helped me write this song... -=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=… https://t.co/z3bBoVcan8]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Music #entrepreneur @Camila_Cabello turned 22! #Entrepreneurs and other high-performing individuals often mature e… https://t.co/fpxqxKF5qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cunningham_kat Kat couldn't agree more, it has nothing to do with talent alone. A captains role obviously differs… https://t.co/LyEJ0rACcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SQUADUP The Bots are on high alert!!! Bond with your fellow #Resisters !!  Let's GOOOOOOOOO!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was a bit of a late comer to soccer but mine was definitely @TaylorTwellman. #NERevs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heymrneal @nowno1Gigi @BekiHughes @Jennifer_OHLITD @johnmacarthur No one is more surprised than me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are the people who when pestered  by squeegee kids or panhandlers demand and get police protection on private… https://t.co/ehh7kc9eTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[About time somebody called out the MSM for their 'reporting' fake news.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know @SufferinBa5tard , two things you dislike, I-95 and South Connecticut^^Carolina. It's going to be ok little… https://t.co/NS4tyxwXfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We, the writers of Morbidly Beautiful, took up the challenge of @PhilNobileJr to watch movies featured on… https://t.co/ioOurN58DE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taranoodle Not stupid at all. Vonnegut wrote about missing his mom his entire life. I’m older than you, and I miss mine too]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my history teacher that I’m anti vax as a joke and she almost about killed me sjkssj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pimping a ball that doesnt even go out? He getting a free base next AB lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wayne_tr3a @lynnerlou72 @DTrumpPoll @realDonaldTrump @POTUS And they call us SNOWFLAKES ??? https://t.co/OQqXSm4ovC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocjb825 @SheriffClarke @BreitbartNews @RedNationRising @chicksonright @johncardillo @larryelder @townhallcom @RitaPanahi Maybe a vet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thotpagnemami Once I leaned over that booth and they were out of my hand, that was all she wrote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackiembouvier @RadicalAlarmist @shaunking @BernieSanders Respectfully, they've both had 3 years to get these toge… https://t.co/sU26qcAQ8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NuanceBro @FreeSpeechAppar @realchristianob They contacted me. Then sent me on a goose chase connecting me to different departments.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SJPFISH @ALawRadio I had bosses and authority figures tell me 30 or 40 years ago, when I was a kid, that they woul… https://t.co/l2HoCArOAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such a fun time at Disneyland today!! 😊❤️ #disneyland #happiestplaceonearth #sister #friend #girlsday… https://t.co/cHwzVByJE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[20: Lo Inédito Sobre Los Evangelios Podcast - Las Bienaventuranzas: La Perfección es obligatoria?   https://t.co/6MfAqgkcDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lizzyskelter Yeah, pretty much..  I mean her fucken mother was banging him after he abducted her and married her!… https://t.co/pDD7pg5q1I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @Bakari_Sellers just skipped right over the other VA democrat who was “credibly accused” of rape. Vir… https://t.co/klYJ0kE8DL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh it should be fucking illegal to come into a closed ass bus smelling like mad cigarettes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatManDickman @WWayneMarlow @CheebaJones @YahooSportsNFL @Chiefs @Patriots if you go to college format then you h… https://t.co/hzgyhBI46S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lawyers close to the special counsel investigation say the Mueller report is nearing completion and will allege mul… https://t.co/tQeVPwYDvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintLeoVPJen @SaintLeoUniv Ash Wednesday is a day of fasting and abstinence. How tempting this is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeecoWang5 @AMBAMERICA @LindaMusgrove9 @TonyMalone7 @kathy101252 @nitsujreizarf @CraigChermside @VikingWilli… https://t.co/1k2aAuwqsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bonnie Banane - Statue  Kaytranada - LITE SPOTS I brought that shit to the table for my closest friends and these t… https://t.co/K7YiOvU1wm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was having such a shitty day, but after those squats I’m feeling hella better 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Asked: ''Should I Wear Gloves While Strength Training?'' @SparkPeople https://t.co/aqL7GQzixW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things have been weighing on me for awhile thinking about this day coming up, but then God spoke to me through this… https://t.co/GkVPX8Y6rA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alohigilman This dude just has that thing where he gets football. Reminds me of Troy. Just a tough dude who finds the ball @alohigilman]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @pltnun left me on read bc she with her lame boy toys 🤭.... millennials 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Samar3450 @Real_Whores @IsabellaSlut20 @Priya20539684 @Spanish_PornSt @snapdd61 @josepperezgaba1 @BetoRigoletto… https://t.co/srHtRo01ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heybowiee Qualifier for us is at canebrake. You’re gonna try for the Tennessee state am?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Walton has the hardest coaching job in sports history:  Imagine coaching a team that has a player who’s dad is… https://t.co/NPlex3dmHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abigarzaa_ @HCSOHonorGuard Exactly how I feel. https://t.co/hi45ftCn4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maryannbaldwin @hollyaiken Well said. Def helped inspire @runologie + many other retailers to invest in DTR. She will be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[political figures and celebs “dropping by” #SXSW2019 keynotes and talks only proves just how much #sxsw has already… https://t.co/YKZWD8aW4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[18 battle for the top of the podium tonight. Leave it on the mat! #MNstate #lovethefight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please do not disrespect any band or talented indie artist on my page , What you ought to know is we work hard to p… https://t.co/Zlqdy8ZNfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my city. I am to Seattle what New York is to Diddy. ... ... #seattle #kerrypark #porsche #cayman @ Kerry Pa… https://t.co/ILe9pJbAoC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@5tatergscottC We demand people FEED their kids too. Yet somehow we manage that without massive, dangerous, low qua… https://t.co/nXh8dat0oT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thought about trying this but then I got scurred. Cant imagine a beignet with a burger @ Old Town Sacramento https://t.co/03oSDckIdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truly I tell you, this is the greatest Coke of all. #orangevanilla @ Marble Falls, Texas https://t.co/2ArnaCtoxb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fly Fishing Film Tour 2019! https://t.co/ByIQRCqfDF https://t.co/CkZFLfojwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a 100% chance the girl I like is gonna get her shit wrecked tonight and I don’t know how to cope 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can take the weight up off your shoulder blades n try to store the pain inside of me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute things to do before heading to Toronto for our flight tonight to MEXICO!! Cabo, here we come!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RattusDaddus @MJJJusticePrjct Besides, innocent men don't make 23 Million dollar payouts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could listen to this over and over ... check out this amazing performance by @brandicarlile]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I decided to make #steamed #tilapia in tinfoil ! Watch the #cooking #video and you watch #culinary #magic !… https://t.co/XktSJj20Q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently if a steak doesn't have grill marks on it "it wasn't grilled and it was seared in a pan"..well that's news to me 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roundhoward @BriceIzyah And there is so much we don’t know; like the players! Not having seen Ep 3 yet, here are p… https://t.co/MAfsxwqxTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ripping set from Los Angeles’ @cherryglazerr tonight!! #CherryGlazerr #StuffedandReady @ Velvet Underground https://t.co/5ukmrqGKaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't touch my wife don't touch the Goldman Sachs we see your plot so that I stay poor and that you lead us all to mass extinction]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BestSaturdayParty with @DJExeQtive @tajlounge  @pquilter1972 @damonslist  @AnthonyPSmooth @NiteTables @MaCofBFEnt… https://t.co/n6A3BOggj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynnie_S4114 @admiralelite15 @alexxsmithh_ That's my dude...  Kill em with kindness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw Someone needs to invent a dual use comb-fork thing right now and start calling VCs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That's what the libtards are going to depend on..! Stupid assholes...!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t argue w Irvin, Smith &amp; Aikman, but Reed, Thomas &amp; Kelly are ALL Hall of Famers and a close 2nd !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's on! #PoliticalRevolution 2.0 $27 at a time! https://t.co/SdGyi64SQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[McDouble off the wall for Derek McCready to start off the inning! This prompts Wash U to change pitchers. https://t.co/LVhk42PsRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samuelT19 As for dealing with journalists who don't like or agree with you, again, that comes with the territory o… https://t.co/47U8IiVzbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you go see an @gunsnroses tribute band, you have to wear your GnR shirt. Nashville ‘16 with @ChrisStapleton… https://t.co/APLuoecxHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aye this is so cool, If you ask Google what song is playing it identifies My Song "Pocket My Niggas Lighter" when it plays.  😂😂👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein If true, it’ll bolster House Democrats’ attempt at impeachment of tRumP.  Now, just gotta find Republ… https://t.co/jX4nhof1jY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr bartender "my hands get purple spots and cold but my legs are on fire" Props whole ass leg on bar "Its not weird… https://t.co/aUhXukdhwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Hagelin out of the box and catches the lob pass and beats Hellebucyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumps support of white suppremacy has done considerable more damage to Jewish America than Omar ever could. Anti S… https://t.co/S1iv3d2xw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElRigel_ @victor_marin @SaraDessens @ARguezZapata @tibosanchez @Yadiracotalugo @SantiagoLunaG @ErnestoUribeC… https://t.co/fIm0Dn37EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pajuelo_10 Innecesaria en que sentido? En algun momento lo fue y luego ya no? Te aburrias por algo en especial??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lotusflowerom Authoritarian, racist, crony capitalist, hypocritical and immoral.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My neibor is a marine he is a old chopper sonar specialist knows codeing and lives with his computer his x girlfrie… https://t.co/3ABuhtLj9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not watching another laker game this season. This is legit the most heartless, least caring team I can remember wat… https://t.co/u8jCcFp2Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[The House PASSED the government funding deal legislation 300 to 128 to keep the government funded through the end o… https://t.co/QsxYoWCh7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Suprema by Industrias La Constancia at @pistoleros_htx — https://t.co/tzwK9vfMo9]]></document><document><![CDATA[843.302.1342 Call and let's get ya ready for spring!#westashley #chucktown #charleston #allnutrient #haircut… https://t.co/xPimIzsTCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the #Russians helped #trump get elected and #FauxNews became the Ministry of #PresidentialPropaganda that was… https://t.co/r27qgeRo7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3: I accepted a challenge from @power58karen to post covers of 7 books I love; no reviews, just the cover. Each… https://t.co/QGYYv0SMEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeLaSalle_BB advances to the @MHSAA District Final with a 74-38 win over @fitz_athletics here at Woods Tower HS.… https://t.co/qWPEnBmwDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich That’s just how petty of a politician you are @RepSwalwell sad really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump The quack is back looks like you ran  out of meds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGussA @LaundryQueen3 @allaboutAlixB @ChelleMarie25 @JamesleeMiles @BiasedBroncoFan @Dannystrong @JussieSmollett… https://t.co/bHPX2Q3Usu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MicahZeidman @realDonaldTrump I don’t hate, my man.....I’m for common decency and humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna do something so special for girls tonight who make me fall in love all over again every morning that i litera… https://t.co/aGBwuRFc79]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best way to fish? In a kayak and with a fly. Opinionated? Maybe. Either way it’s a blast. #famagogo #tetons… https://t.co/l7WFM8J2w7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doctor_bigs Asheville is cool. The town we were in on Alabama reminded me a ton of Asheville. Also, Husk has a Gre… https://t.co/H7QYoyEGC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Sharratt 2019... just because there may not be an oral component to standardized tests does not mean it should… https://t.co/AyIxEG6IeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manny_ottawa   Here's a question. Why didnt @JustinTrudeau immediately drop everything and chase Bezos?  Opportuni… https://t.co/GzaIzLZxAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Construction is progressing along nicely despite extremely challenging weather conditions this past month.. Footing… https://t.co/LRaSUI3XNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronecstasy @dddiaperrr @ellenvile Erin and I were talking about that recently. So many child murder tv shows and f… https://t.co/WRotSOZvy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be very careful not to define others based on our personal bias. https://t.co/Io3do649I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the day where boyfriend's ACTUALLY pay attention to what their girlfriend's want.   #ValentinesDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[These people are running the most influential country in the world and it’s wild]]></document><document><![CDATA[125 mil asesinatos en promedio anual desde que llegó la basura castristas a #venezuela, muchos asesinatos ejecutado… https://t.co/6iuR4R2gZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @1tc If her ancestors were of any stands beside slave in Jamacia during the 1700 or 1800 she is the… https://t.co/mAxSKqUXT9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Rastafari Is by @petertosh, from #SoundHound https://t.co/OYwWHAdOkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jan67438231 napisz do mnie Jan !,CZEKAM !.Czy na zdieciu to twoj penis ?.]]></document></documents></author>