<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@aladams75 @JFeinsteinBooks @JLEnterprises Lefty took the heat at the University of Maryland for things that were t… https://t.co/f0TZEIu2KH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tie game. Both 19s have scored, as Jordan Cornelison scores for Doherty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @DonaldJTrumpJr @TPUSA Hate crimes in the US (2016-2018): 21,000  Hate crime hoaxes in the US (2016-… https://t.co/Hv0xc1qciq]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve progressed from daily tweets about needing a man to a blunt &amp; i’m not embarrassed, not the slightest bit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My pink sea urchin soaps. Etsy 5 STAR REVIEW - “These are gorgeous!!! And thank you so much for the little goodies!… https://t.co/wsWTryXfqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgc6165 @ABC Also, it is hard to change the mind set of an older generation but never the less, God bless and have a great life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is your chance to tell a story about a moment where you decided to be a good human being...instead of a rage f… https://t.co/hH5jJOMhCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If shanna doesn’t bring me some subway I’m putting myself up for adoption]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do I buy now or do I have the will power to wait until I get my signed copy from @Lisa_See on 4/9? https://t.co/I99vXHachf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at these intramural basketball CHAMPIONS! 🏀🏆They had a goal from last year to take the basketball championship… https://t.co/AUgUKMA6wS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight shapers of minds! Tomorrow is another day! Stay positive and remember you are loved! 💛💚❤️🧡💜💙 #goodnight… https://t.co/TOMjtl6NPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gas has gone up 11 cents a litre overnight.  Do we give credit to Premier Ford for that?   @fordnation @SteveClarkPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigerWoodsNews maybe even your caddy .  I know My Husband would buy everything, t o Display in His Man Cave!  Just an Excellent Thought!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it From Paper students are so excited to finish their Lorax landscapes. We had so much fun making this artwork… https://t.co/U0VnQbqc3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s quite a sign!  Love the branding that you’ll be seeing sautéing the market and in a yard near you soon!  Hom… https://t.co/nbVctjUzYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's an awesome giveaway campaign by @brightechshop, they are giving away a really cool magnifier lamp! Join the… https://t.co/hP7w500EXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fucking love my Bitmoji #MondayMotivation #WritingCommnunity https://t.co/TR0iz7veg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only way this is corrected is if the people nominated for the other categories decide to boycott the show! Howe… https://t.co/wpmMBmOdJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson Love the “it wasa long time ago” excuse.   Child rape was never ok.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Increasing our collaboration capital! We are better together!!! #allmeansall]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunnflores @girlsmeg He's ugly in an alliance called the pretty face boys]]></document><document><![CDATA[ryans work partner told him that he's rude and he's a dick i'm ready to https://t.co/ofvwVx5seQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can watch someone true colors unfold from you saying 1 word they don’t like..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kindergarten teachers love dressing on costume every chance we get 😜 We all had a blast during Reading Under the St… https://t.co/EmmaefcEvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my dear friend and biggest cheerleader! I love you @TammyCoveney .. 💝 https://t.co/SmrBbP2Rz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing Magnetic Fun! Library Stations had several styles of MAGNET SETS to build settings with recently!… https://t.co/270rRo2nQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s so refreshing to hear someone acknowledge that midwesterners matter. And this guy is whip-smart!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Katie.....i would have loved to be in your pocket for this concert! Love them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[PETA DESERVES MORE THAN BACKLASH. I'M REALLY MAD BECAUSE ALL PETA DOES IS REPORTS AND TAKES PICTURES WITH NO ACTION… https://t.co/WS92l2Idh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amanderpus @sea_jaiden @Ibelievthehype nah I work at dicks sporting goods lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Simba would like more @finleysbarkery 😂😍 Good thing he can find them at @ChuckandDons now!!!  Simba is avai… https://t.co/rPNnpWl95K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love coming down to Tucson and being greeted warmly in Spanish when walking into certain places. It makes me feel… https://t.co/cB3QAWZMOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BryceMAHWilson @mollyburkhardt It’s not there for me to hit snooze it’s there to make sure I don’t sleep through it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people feel the need to sit at my desk, screw with things, then log me out of what I was doing?! Like wtf?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ibraaahim_ When u lookin through Becks phone and u have to murder someone again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@63BankStreet @StephScolaro @oldmanluvsmineo @Adbb037 @SwampysGhost @AGobsmack @ljcambria @ScottSkipworth2… https://t.co/mj1IX33Hir]]></document><document><![CDATA[feeling unconditionally cared about is something i havent felt in months]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Are you sure you don’t mean 8 years.   Your advice or perspective is warped]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy for my friends they went to Paris I’m a little jealous tho lmao. That’s definitely in my bucket list of places I want to visit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to know all things Beto? Follow @JeremySWallace who is all over it today and everyday, including right now whi… https://t.co/yoQEBV4crT]]></document><document><![CDATA[this has been the saddest week I’ve ever been through.. it might not look like it but it is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I hear my laugh in a recording I’m shook because I’m like damn that’s how I be laughing gross 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my life by K-Ci and jojo 😍😍😍 I know every beat, pause and word in that song]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever I have kids with is gonna have to have coin so I can stay home with my baby. Daycare is the wild west Wtf 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottSabolFOX8 @fox8news How awful to think the people of Alabama are plunged into these temperatures during rescue and clean-up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellymgorham @CentoFineFoods @pomara_matt @BillyGorham622 Can I borrow her???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hasanminhaj literally stayed up until now to wait for Netflix to upload your new ep! I finally get to watch the ep… https://t.co/Q6OCueqp5F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night at #q106storytellersjam #grangersmith #morganevans #tinelletownes #laurenalaina @ Monona Terrace Commun… https://t.co/l18PPBqjL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Strawberry 🍫 🍓  part of my #14daysofvalentines series I’ve been doing on my IG ✨ _MarkedByMichelle  —————… https://t.co/JB5ugKHNY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four years ago I was in Italy, three years ago I was in Canada and two years ago I was in Holland. Wow can’t wait t… https://t.co/F4doCW6hJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It wasn't meant to be serious, but while you are here..... 1) its not the dog. It's the owner. 2) my chihuahua has… https://t.co/lozHlbqWbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tk14_15_56 Wow!!! So glad to see y’all having FUN!!!!!! So refreshing ❤️   High School ball is like being in prison for some 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kept my whole class laughing. Maybe I was the class clown 🤣🤷🏻‍♀️ I also hated when I had to read out loud, we had… https://t.co/wKdwogL3yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was feeling bad for Khloe but being in her position myself once upon a fucking time. IT AINT EVER THE FEMALES FAU… https://t.co/vOKXO8OOfn]]></document><document><![CDATA[“life is a marathon, not a sprint” i mean that’s cool, but i hate them both 😬🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/luekEbdJe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile I’m waiting for a heart eyes emoji with soft pink hearts to match my aesthetic 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LolicOnion at 1630 the sun comes through tue window and blinds miki and I so we make dinner, watch @DraskylDota an… https://t.co/nKzALt5K6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have NEVER been able to figure this out! Guess I’m doomed to keep eating all of the popcorn forever 🤷🏼‍♀️🍿❤️🍿❤️🍿]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JcpLq2 @dilruba_lees @ArtsandScents @LiliRamos6 @ersu1880 @mabel_carrera @Jilliemary @susanWV309 @khanhakim_k… https://t.co/er1MlLMwti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TealHeather Good Morning Heather; hope you're having a lovely day. Enjoy the good weather and have a fun and relax… https://t.co/MWy7k0yQIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man I’m tired of crying over this relationship. At this point it is what it is. 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "CNA" at Laramie Care Center? Applicant tracking systems look for specific keywords. Use th… https://t.co/8e3YzpSVZL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day with @mjsteinle and Veruca Salt (Brewer’s Reserve)! A fine combination. @FreeStateBeer https://t.co/MaUTurW8Yj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ijames I’m so glad you found it useful! But yes the 2PC problem is definitely a concern esp when it comes to all t… https://t.co/1Bnm2d06hB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SajdaMughal A Child? Well those child’s that join Isis carry terrorism acts, wear bombs and kill people all over t… https://t.co/K7nlcqku82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattJDever @Morgan_Myler I only wish to help my son and eliminate negative behaviours. I do not wish to change him… https://t.co/QuGMwKRtEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Morning Sounds #az #moonvalley #sundaymorning #phoenix @ Moon Valley, Phoenix https://t.co/NB5KA42ufH]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE FUCKING POWER EYE #BTSISCOMING #MapOfTheSoul_PERSONA https://t.co/LDYtK0MzQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working with passionate leaders and providing onsite Eyecare and eyewear to our little scholars @Zone126Queens… https://t.co/RL4o5BUzbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalyaRobles13 Ugh seriously my bangs are a disaster and if they don’t grow out soon I’m gonna die]]></document><document><![CDATA[▪️◼️Every time I close my eyes, it’s like a dark Paradise ◼️▪️Cc: nickmeansphoto ▪️ H/MUA: daniellaviolet ▪️ bodysu… https://t.co/UvlUfXAhEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side-by-side photos: Same 3 kids 12 years earlier! #sohappy #myKids https://t.co/IK9Kie7GtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Reality is wrong, dreams are forreal” ✨ @ Eddie C. Moore Softball Complex https://t.co/xKFrDlInpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just fought my retired fed ass dad and pinned him down and slapped him hahahahaha what the actual fuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jilevin and he has to pay back legal fees due to his lawsuit in Scotland]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally just fed cheetah and he’s on the table with me tryna steal my chicken 😐😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out @CapitalFactory with @cisco_woi #seedlingmentors https://t.co/y4zPmOfUPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang. Should’ve been on that flight. I wouylrcr gotten a bag from Delta. 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KMosetti TRUMP: "Mothers who love their daughters give them massive amounts of birth control pills, because they k… https://t.co/fsyUEGfHnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did my man hype my mom up to go to max bar? Now i have to deal with these fools tonight 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no reason for Government to subsidize Planned Parenthood and allow PP to donate to political campaigns. The… https://t.co/RouVME1pS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las Vegas ranch style home for sale! RV parking, pool and spa oversized lot! Here is a glimpse of the formal dining… https://t.co/vKGPdcrYxE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s class theme is EMBODIMENT 🤩 and I’m pumped!! See y’all there 🧘🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet the Guardians...Shadows of Midnight, Equal Parts Mystery &amp; Beauty #cinderella #ballet #midnight #guardians… https://t.co/6FEafhaHb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oiselle_team @karagoucher @steph_willett @drlesko I’m Team Lesko re: the underwear question. What if I want to rew… https://t.co/3gyzfwOoJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE  Holy cow! Did I just see @BraunStrowman trash a #Camaro?? If he can do that, think of the chaos he'll inflict… https://t.co/1Ew5mcsSbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrinbergGabi @divohim So what I'm hearing is that you all WANT to just STOP Hamas once and for all, continue takin… https://t.co/iC8DWpeOy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy el Grinch del 14 de febrero, me causa conflicto que nos presuman a sus parejas aún cuando sabemos que ya les pu… https://t.co/TMDkATEaqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Botswana is considering instituting regular elephant culling in a misguided attempt to manage their elephant popula… https://t.co/GzClCnB191]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Donald @realDonaldTrump wouldn't even be qualified to sell Hot Dogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure id be honored to if I could just see you alive one more time Margret I swear]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duke_duke_goose @BSommerland @jessjarman @Charlotte_Stein @parlettscarrish @ruby_duvall @LJEvansBooks I’m pretty s… https://t.co/XSznXSd4yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simplicity  can be wonderful.  #handcrafted #shoplocal #madewithlove #diamondsandpearlsgreetings #giftideas… https://t.co/vGyGugYs7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canada must do more to help jailed Saudi women: Amnesty International https://t.co/eKHUHKUnzT  #cdnpoli @CdnPress]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely loved getting to spend some time with Laura, Norman, and Mackie this weekend! I’m so lucky I live in the… https://t.co/jyXAX64nVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[There comes a point in a boys life when he forgets how badass dinosaurs and pirates are BUT luckily, there is also the day he remembers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClifBar sponsor me pls i’m going to go broke trying keep up with my addiction to your bars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland That's the kind of PATTERN-icity and SYNCH-ronicity that freaks me out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Anzeige) Meine Gesichtspflege auf Weltreise 🙌 . Ich habe mir sehr genau überlegt, welche Hautpflege ich auf meine… https://t.co/sjWbL2DJ5p]]></document></documents></author>