<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'd also encourage us to meet people where they're at on their #MentalHealth journeys. Some are more educated and kРђд https://t.co/7KVNGIaUDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter-fuck is a disgrace to the womanРђЎs movement! A total monster. Imagine waking up next to that every morning. ItРђЎs Hell calling!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @Finextra @OneSpan and industry #subjectmatterexperts, like me, for a #webinar on 12 March 2019 at 15:00 UK tiРђд https://t.co/iPVhtUtRS3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcbridesworld @harrybelafonte Wow. Happy bday to the legend among legends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna be in the shop Sunday afternoon...hmu for some ink.  #tattoos #northstartattoo #Raleigh #NC #triangle #DurhamРђд https://t.co/LTks9uHxGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barney015 @PFTCommenter @BarstoolBigCat grit week. If you have two shoes you dont have one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocm11111 @MabwereL @LeonJuste @CEEAC_ECCAS @PostesTelecomcg @Grace_Patcheli @HarmonyOndombo @ARPCECongoРђд https://t.co/9FWGUWQXPO]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been more than 9 days since @ChrisCuomo used a deceptive edit to further the Charlottesville hoax, a damagingРђд https://t.co/f6iw809sVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So after watching Captain Marvel, my thoughts on the movie: Fantastic!   I want a Starforce movie. I cant wait to sРђд https://t.co/eWlSvpBfts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ROOFHOU @Q_fortheWIN @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Connect him to the crimes: Manafort (his campaign manager), Cohen (hiРђд https://t.co/1HGzoA76sT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Pittsburgh has to settle for a 3rd and a 5th round pick for AB. Mike Mayock swoops in and gives their РђюfranchiРђд https://t.co/bUdC56jUOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[He certainly showed it in CohenРђЎs Congressional testimony.   I donРђЎt know Cohen, but I know the Trump Organization.Рђд https://t.co/D4o3IfsFZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maxwelltani Put a purple mask on him and he would be Galactus here to devour the Earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of you all said @LoyolaMLAX gets the W. LetРђЎs see if the Greyhounds does indeed get the dub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MESanders Yes, but IРђЎm sworn to secrecy. Besides, I donРђЎt want to ruin it for you­Ъўі]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AikmanCMU @SinBinVegas @pahealy070 A lose is a lose. But losing 3-0 is far worse than losing 1-0. The turnovers in this game were killer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Kelley Craig kimbrel Kenley Jansen? I could get use to that #dodgers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stephen King once wrote, "Time takes it all whether you want it to or not, time takes it all. Time bares it away, aРђд https://t.co/XvytydB7HE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cailehb @RealHedwigBlack @LoganS33 This was like the Рђюyou know how I know youРђЎre gayРђЮ scene from the 40 year old vРђд https://t.co/3GFTFfDGy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюGet me outta here monРђЮ -Emil Hapanowitz @ Wayne State College https://t.co/lg77tdx00g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael JacksonРђЎs РђюTHRILLERРђЮ house! #thriller #michaeljackson #mj #olaray @ Michael Jackson's  Thriller  House (andРђд https://t.co/FlNZvn80Xf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OldJerseyDog04 @Bengals No I agree. Trade Williams for Rosen. Bates and Collins can both start and Bates can learnРђд https://t.co/TxFpB92juV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FEDESA809 @DiarioLibre Me met├Г a su Twitter y todos los relacionados al apag├│n son despu├Еs de que sucedi├│?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Success to me is not Being died or in jail at the age of 28 I can Speak To Kids About life and Even tho The Grind iРђд https://t.co/SA0SzOvrSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@country_skins doesnРђЎt look like IРђЎm gonna see you before your trip. Have a good time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RACIST CNN    CNN accused by National Association of Black Journalists of lacking diversity; Zucker refuses to meetРђд https://t.co/xloDbfmTj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fam bowling day. ­Ъј│ #pinsnstrikes #famtime @ Pins N Strikes https://t.co/GIqr28rFCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkNerdyWithUs Does Jackie still contribute to your blog? HavenРђЎt seen anything recent from her and would like toРђд https://t.co/HUskttuy9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Is that why the people who work for you make a fraction of what you make? They do ALL of the work why you buy clothes and grandstand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brynstole Rock formations and other nature things near Chattanooga. https://t.co/HKAabuDwK6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jenny, a Shepherd (Unknown Type) in CA, needs a home now! See her on https://t.co/YNgcSmYtj9 https://t.co/EY3VcJlV0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leadership: You get blamed for the negligence of the others that came before you. You try to pick the can up and trРђд https://t.co/NXbiPKvN6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChaseSupport stop blacklisting conservatives! IРђЎve been a customer for 30 yrs will close my accounts soon!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gibraltar is pronounced (j ih b - rAWl - tur) please stop the criminal mispronunciation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexBistonTV Aww thank you sweetheart I will stay dry. Doing laundry for the day with no outside work activities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews OHIO STOP VOTING REPUBLICAN. DONT VOTE FOR TRUMP. The only way to make a difference. ItРђЎs your fault.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aguilaroja63 @Reportero24 No se puede criticar y a la vez disfrutar al objeto de la cr├Гtica, es como despotricar dРђд https://t.co/mnnlkoxHC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TacoCabana Enjoying Some Tacos &amp; Personal Quesadilla This Morning. #hungry #tacos #quesadilla https://t.co/K5XwDN05YG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont tell dick jokes at work...just a tip.  PAGE: Chris to the HR office please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beltrandelrio NO PERO SER├ЇA TONTO QUE LOS MEDIOS QUE NO TIENEN UN N├џMERO SUFICIENTE DE SEGUIDORES RECIBAN REGALOSРђд https://t.co/azzvWmUDJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickBieker @GovHerbert @SpencerJCox @UtahReps @utahsenate BEER what a crime! LetРђЎs spend our time on somethingРђд https://t.co/0Pqb5QXPp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMisadventure @DougisRaw Love it. Really appreciate it! There was no way I couldnРђЎt bring attention to that toss ­Ъўѓ absolutely nuts]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite wrestler from the Monday Night Wars: Ultimo Dragon at Defy Wrestling in Seattle. He's incredible. https://t.co/f62Hd3Ce72]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulinaPresley1 Happy Birthday Paulina Presley! YouРђЎre 32 Years Old Now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want this team to get better! Lol #BUCS @gregauman @NFLSTROUD @JennaLaineESPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rare that a freshman lineman makes All-Conference, but 1st team???  Yep, he did that, too. #GoJackets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Neuropcity I find sleep apnea to be directly linked to AlziehiemerРђЎs. Also the lack of nrem first sleep stage. FatРђд https://t.co/ZZgRbNkwT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tahirqadeer @thefull40 @VUhoops CheekРђЎs another good call. I still say CremoРђЎs worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The way the TL screams РђюbeansРђЮ I wanted to ask who is lying now. ­Ъци­ЪЈ┐РђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ­Ъци­ЪЈ┐РђЇРЎѓ№ИЈ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobynOBrienUSA Over $6 million per year by Bayer/Monsanto and Crop Life. GMOРђЎs, herbicides, pesticides. Plus $3 miРђд https://t.co/OkM2NYusoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought a new chair for mah living room. @ Portland, Oregon https://t.co/mKYe6mYN9m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seehafer I love what it did to Luke, and the two things are related. The one thing Star Wars alt right fans have cРђд https://t.co/e7mSEUv0eB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My last three tweets should point out that this years team is on par w/ our Magic Teams who have won 3-5 BigXII ChaРђд https://t.co/gEKGyhIe8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love it when people singing acapella on a TV show have auto-tuned vocals ­Ъўѓ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PowerRangersBeastMorphers Just saw this got to check it out https://t.co/znW0w0JkMd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiperPerabo @SecretaryRoss On the face of it I would say, why should we count immigrants (assuming that they are iРђд https://t.co/JOQwloOUHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon Roils Freight Industry, Analysts Say.... https://t.co/sL2ZX4ykpA via @TransportTopics]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @TheAAF tonight. Slow sports night... #Singletary #DaBears https://t.co/5Vp5NP88DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foran HighРђЎs Mia Tunucci scored 13 points, with 18 rebounds and three blocked shots as the Lions defeated JonathanРђд https://t.co/Ih8OT6UgeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachryan82 @RobMcDonagh @AaronBlake Do we really think any dem voter would switch sides of any gop voter becomesРђд https://t.co/gqu07pNnXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealPaigeWWE @SashaKaestner @WWEAsuka @WWE I love when you walk down that ring you're so I Love The Way You Walk tРђд https://t.co/Fsl8TUrlvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StewartHaasRcng @ISMRaceway @StewartHaasRcng @ruckusnetworks @ITsavvyLLC @jimmyjohns @SmithfieldFoods Good MorningРђд https://t.co/eQ2f9Qxn7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dover defeats Oyster River 8-0 in DII action. Aiden McDonough with a hat trick and Trevor Gnall with a pair forРђд https://t.co/YktzKmNd47]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to be an extremely hateful person to watch this crap every night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Luck to our @UNLVRebelHockey  Team as they head out to Colorado for a few games!! They put in some hard practiРђд https://t.co/0vVVsEedWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the opportunity to chat with a #Madison, #Wisconsin-based entrepreneur and her new eatery, Pasture and PlentyРђд https://t.co/DTVfcnydpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an All 5th Anniversary Everything Imperial Stout W/ Coffee by @OtherHalfNYC @ Beerage Рђћ https://t.co/ivDbDsm3K6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachtaylor1987 @JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump @dbongino @SebGorka @McAllisterDen @RealJamesWoods https://t.co/EbMsnVm0S9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pilabuda @RossiF2018 Not weighing "justice" in one situation vs another (which I agree would be wrong), but weighiРђд https://t.co/TMPlfdH88P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Under the Stars ­Ъїа­ЪїЎ­Ъїа(Time lapse) San Carlos, Sonora, M├Еxico @metmex @chematierra @MuyInteresanteM @RevistaNatGeoРђд https://t.co/d1fwC2RdoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travel has been more than past Winters.  Can't think of a better way to spend the day than with Maura and her 1st tРђд https://t.co/bwcn7djZgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveTiger999 I gave a very basic answer. People who don't understand a discipline should avoid pretending that thРђд https://t.co/qfrsncXrLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saying AB killed the trade doesn't make sense. The steelers needed to get rid of him and would trade him to any teaРђд https://t.co/5KenMBh8ih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else got a friend who makes this face? This clip from #BoomerangBET gives me life.  #BoomerangOnBET https://t.co/Ef9CBgCo1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[so my girlfriend and i are now at a 69 (#nice) consecutive day streak on snapchat is that it now? did we win? did wРђд https://t.co/f4lEvk2Nkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[ThereРђЎs rarely any new women in rap bc yРђЎall donРђЎt let there be any new women in rap, every new artist that comes uРђд https://t.co/j7sjwgS71F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words fall short to describe the disappointment felt with such blatant discrimination towards the youth of our wondРђд https://t.co/rQLz3q8w31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonJeffries @mikeonitstuff @allenholub With that I agree. But how are these iterations Рђюuser storiesРђЮ? In this casРђд https://t.co/MQlnc8VkH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biannual vent that daylight savings time is moronic and should be prohibited. #kidsthrownofffordays]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialrolandb Lmao I ainРђЎt gonna knock they hustle tho ­Ъўѓ everybody got they preferences I guess ­Ъўѓ­Ъўѓ https://t.co/6TwPjnfmeu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @RiverdaleLW have the ball up 62-60 with 45.7 seconds left. #ArrowsUp @RHS_sports @cecil_joyce @WGNSSports @Mboro_Post]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SidneyPowell1 @realDonaldTrump @LouDobbs @POTUS @PressSec @jsolomonReports I agree100%. STOP IT ALL. Shut down theРђд https://t.co/bhk96UlpBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @Beantowndougish @chance4gardener @lynn_maryellen @wolflayla420 @TaggartRehnn @xpflyrРђд https://t.co/7sq3Yt6ZR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[TodayРђЎs Specials!!! @Rostovs_Rocks @CapitolPancake @DeanCanavos @VisitVaBch @VisitWmbg @ccanavos @VisitRichmondРђд https://t.co/hWrEgAMpjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acabou de publicar uma foto em The Griffin Observatory https://t.co/rCI2GSa7fw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The MCSS press release on the autism support changes. There is a lot of commentary from professionals in the field.Рђд https://t.co/IXcjUaCeoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[On another note, great season to the Cig boys b-ball team. They played with a lot of HEART tonight! Made us #toroproud #southlaredo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarciePadilla @marissjeannette So when we all going to this friends house? ­Ъцћ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesusEsc11 Ya lo habia visto, pero recuerda que hulk sale vatias veces y habla con bruce]]></document><document><![CDATA[His 2018 Director Reel: https://t.co/X003ogHEZ3 His Imbd: https://t.co/WjPyBRCUn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NPR reporter was talking about a new killer whale that biologists discovered, and said something like, РђюThis isРђд https://t.co/ECEcVjWRed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpenceMeekins @_stevenrod @tdgator9 What I find amazing is UGA shot almost 60% from the floor, to our 37%, they weРђд https://t.co/XigniAxIM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ledrew @WeAreinGodsPlan @lizfebry9 @AnnickNday @geshepjr @AddingtonSheron @EricJSwensson @Carole77777Рђд https://t.co/RPSy87s6dB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhismanSucks @Jimmypisfunny now he is just begging for yРђЎall to meet him  https://t.co/1iiu5ArqJ2 talk about a hell of a podcast!]]></document><document><![CDATA[HowРђЎd you know I was taking a bag full of stuffed bulldogs with me? https://t.co/xKnOyAr3SI]]></document><document><![CDATA[­ЪЉі­ЪЈ╝ @dudabeat ­ЪћЦ Meu Jeito de Amar ­ЪњЃ­ЪЈ╗https://t.co/auu0tCLR8u via @YouTube ­ЪЦЂ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NoT AlL wOmEn KnOw WhT tHeY DoIn ­ЪЦ┤... yea okay, but I do and if IРђЎm giving you that sloppy toppy, deep throat, nutsРђд https://t.co/wXTQxoRz3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[РђюDo you even mind that I Left flowers on the floor?РђЮ @ London, Ontario https://t.co/RGMyGqDxKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[IРђЎm 100% team nene #learnsomerespect #rhoa #neneleakes   https://t.co/cYvDsMpeb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickbaker80 @PeteLeida @DrPep24 @tjvari @josephjonessr @lancour28 @mdoubet87]]></document></documents></author>