<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Wegthorn @FightOwensFight Small Kevin is digging the graphic on the back of that big rig.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah, those things are my favorite. You better leave me enough money to get 2 more. When you borrow, there’s interes… https://t.co/yqtulEaQuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsCherieGrant @GennHutchison That’s honestly so frustrating, idk the ideas behind pocket design sometimes. (Also b… https://t.co/QHmMng3kBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueBoxDave Media is dividing us, this report is saying a community is divided over a display of nooses teachers p… https://t.co/bD7hRS7Cb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LTMHA2012 @HeyBenMcLean @queensgaels @QueensMHockey Game is on Saturday, 7:30 pm at the Memorial Centre against Guelph.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the amount of coaches that’s gone be in my sons life. This is going to be him to a T 😂🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltraRunnerPod @outsidemagazine I can’t actually smoke bc of my job but I’d be curious about the taste I think more than anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Ah?  And what does capitalism promote?  Not saying it's all bad, but capitalism is the epitome of compe… https://t.co/Pz5P2mYhPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samschreiberrr I’m sorry for your loss we are here for you if you need support]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacharrisWayne @JoyceWhiteVance YES  and the congress that supported him!  Shame!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess everyone is allowed to be happy except for me. So that’s cool 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tune in - @JoeNickPatoski on @WritingOnTheAir at 6pm/c. Listen at https://t.co/NtfB11HrAl &amp; 91.7fm atx. #austintoatx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Many people are saying that your obsession with Sec. Clinton is kinda creepy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GarmireGroup @RiceUniversity @NIEHS I texted her a pic of your tweet. Here's the response: That’s a nice tweet! Th… https://t.co/OVJuG26rNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @Tombx7M Because he's Jewish he can't openly support an anti- somatic Muslim]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might just cancel my Apple Music subscription 🤷🏾‍♀️ Spotify is where it’s at.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier She wants the Muslim Brotherhood to rule America,s  Goverment. That would make her very happy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everyone’s sitting down quietly watching avengers and then you hear @59_victoria eating]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would of been en la plaza hechandome unos tacos de bistec con una coca rn☹️ https://t.co/e0JIthgTFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cathy Rimer-Surles: because @DukePress works are distributed worldwide, may be more cautious with fair use if it ma… https://t.co/IkNOZsokWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj CEO's are the only ones making more than they did last year...The rest of us are all bent over pulling our… https://t.co/9Uwl8hLOCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m spiraling and i can’t stop. 911. Halp.   I need it to be 4pm. I GOTTA GET OUT OF THIS PLACE. https://t.co/DCujbUaXlR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny @Plasticdoe @badzoot7 @SueQuez @doritmi @BarbaraMcK42 @EmmaGPaley @boglethemind @Rosewind2007… https://t.co/SHBd3F67xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammynickalls I have a central nervous pain disorder that frequently leaves me in overwhelming pain. My dog, River… https://t.co/xexnKfSXTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@etnow This is the same story you keep posting with miss leading headline like there is new info.  Why keep regurgitating the same story?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better late in the day than not exercising the franchise. #democracy #vote @ West Side, New York https://t.co/6TfXoWZJMu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Triathlon race-day prep! Tomorrow my dad and I will toe the line at the @stanford Treeathlon Sprint, our very first… https://t.co/4hCXNzOynu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldAmbrosia @vir_geaux @cristinalaila1 @KamalaHarris I did explain myself. Why do I have to present evidence to… https://t.co/PrqnfhzCUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice out enough to finally wear flats. But not comfortable to wear while walking your dog in the morning and pick u… https://t.co/2YTSXAsygK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithboykin @breakfastclubam She is soo cool. N love CardiB.  KamalaB. B my presidential valentine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lynnfield DPW- for getting all of schools ready to open tomorrow, Tuesday, March 5th! #snowdays]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to make Friday morning sketching at my local cafe a regular thing.  The fact that their lemonade is The Best… https://t.co/AKPeERPVTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[STFU ! Your argument is ridiculous. He could have used a saw, a knife an ice pick. A bridge. I’d kill my self too i… https://t.co/SeqydJXAFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friday Night/Pizza Night! @Masterbuilt smoked BBQ rib meat, red onions and cheddar on @Dinosaur_BBQ sauce baked on… https://t.co/Vmb0VruSeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoogleDoodles @dmellieon That is so sweet ❤️ Brilliant, lovely family. Robert is surely missed by millions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super 7 New #Jobs Via @DMANF @FeedingAmerica @cityofhope @action4ifaw @LautmanDC @LukensPolitico @allegiancefrg https://t.co/M2RpU6Pbd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NPSMadness19 @ACKViking @MrLaredoNHS @ackpawsitive @nantucketISLE @janet3503 @latter_claire @NormandLCSW… https://t.co/S5TYJhBYAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#US goes on a parking lot yesterday night to #Tatiana. No FA. Only US affairs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republican Senator Mike Rounds really just said that Trump paid hush money to a porn star because he 'Loves His Fam… https://t.co/dyJWX2Yyci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nee_massey But you get to come to Philly! You’ll see me there bc I’ll claw my way through the vicious hipster crow… https://t.co/VTNiB8MuSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pa’lante siempre pa’lante!   El pueblo unido, jamás será vencido!  This is what I’m talking about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. @jack @twitter @TwitterSupport   Twitter no longer even tries to hide their psycho hyper-biased liberal agenda.… https://t.co/0bU9IyWlnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comparing apples and oranges.  The ME has for the most part been a shithole.  Venezuela has had a thriving economy… https://t.co/csPuUvrik0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hunkering down for the big storm about to hit Northern AZ. Bought a bunch of water bottles, chocolate milk, and lik… https://t.co/Z22d8Qpdv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My psychology professor is honestly so fucking funny dude. I’m literally the only one shouting out answers while mu… https://t.co/koBCJcbJ5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamesonandbeers @angrysatan6661 @HippieVol @Shawn172510 @The_Fool_Monty @8MillionML https://t.co/T1epSlTePp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@val_mccabe @hardball No kidding. What arrogance and what a waste of time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalamaTeddy Have an affair tonight! Find a no-strings-attached relationship tonight. https://t.co/D30OFvedLZ #us #uk #nz #ca #dating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump WE MUST STAND AGAINST A PRESIDENT WITH AN HITLERESQUE MENTALITY!!!!!!!!!!!! HE MUST BE VOTED OUT O… https://t.co/3xdy0dqyTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hair keeps getting stuck in my lip gloss. So I’m not going to stop wearing lip gloss. I’m going to shave my head.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HonoredValor @SEALofHonor @op_hawkeye @mjgranger1 @bigdawgjdub @SRex41563921 @dontcavitate @RickLRobbins… https://t.co/9ByqJxFjNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJRossReaders @drcaulder @NYorNothing I put no, but I was thinking like a celebrity, not someone you’ve actually i… https://t.co/Cp1VsPEOTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s awesome 👏 even me, in Indiana, has heard of St Cuthberts cave! 😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacyethan @AafLegends @CamNizguy @NFL He is the ONLY bright spot for the Legends today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guypbenson @DrZuhdiJasser Her apologies are meaningless, so personality I don't accept insincere, self serving apo… https://t.co/bG5Ld4K7R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJStevensAuthor Mine does the same, drives me crazy! It literally has a mind of its own, does what it wants, when it wants!🙄😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to call out my exceptionally well honed skill in picking out images to construct into a four-panel header im… https://t.co/h7zm4XSGez]]></document><document><![CDATA[More folks here now. Maybe about 40-50. #DurhamNC #ChapelHill #LightRail @DukeU 2/n]]></document><document><![CDATA[i want @joejonas @nickjonas @kevinjonas to give their opinions on this buzzfeed article immediately. https://t.co/RoiwXdBcR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting @genaustin tonight at their wonderful #galentinesgala supporting local girls! https://t.co/MIchSOtHca]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @lindacohn wait until you see the multi hoola hooper at Manhattan Beach Pier!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman is unstoppable. Her first college final exam is tomorrow and we did our own version of the Undie Run in… https://t.co/8KfStVL38B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pet owners share stories that prove the strength of their bonds 😭  https://t.co/fQrF2isLym]]></document><document><![CDATA[They have the most to lose and are scared to have to spend time on prison and lose all the money coming in.... They… https://t.co/YGIZJ1UnSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ramjet70512 @SocialPowerOne1 I think congress is going to let him "correct" the record as they did when Sessions c… https://t.co/C2azwJzNhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gerald Butts on the SNC-Lavalin decision according to @Puglaas testimony at the justice committee Wednesday: "There… https://t.co/FY8c7rTD2x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: he’s cute , but super tall  Giselle: he sure is.. but its okay trees are meant to be climbed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ostrov_A @JDVFL @NikkiHaley @UN_HRC I say sell the building &amp; send them all back to their countries.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I should stop drinking • I said stop smoking • I need to focus • I am the dopest •  you already know this • Chosen… https://t.co/m4N1CqVDGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really can’t (and won’t) finish watching that Yesjuls interview cause I already cringed so hard when that nigga w… https://t.co/jrhD8p6GvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaCAAlves17 Good morning Anna. Thank you for the beautiful picture and words to start our Sunday off in a wonder… https://t.co/EF2uYlzVjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway There; Tall Ship Details ‹ Sandra Hawkins Canadian Visual/Media Artist ‹ Reader — https://t.co/G1S2FDCdln. https://t.co/6q8laVWf15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is your commute better or worse than a little while ago? Hard to say, depends on where you live. The Northway to I-… https://t.co/TVfbFvFxUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS GOES FOR FRIENDSHIP TOO. LEAVE THAT TRASH ASS FRIEND WHO DOESN’T RESPECT YOU IN THE PAST.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My incredible niece, @oliviamac170 and her competitive cheer team took District Championship!  Wishing these strong… https://t.co/QV7sA1b4aT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hey_butter @ruthumstweets @DudekLinda @andrerucker51 @SarahGould_SA @Itridpm @evilgrrl @poppij @delgeo1 @dyny1bn… https://t.co/AcKENZoPJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bengalswim Ok Bengal Boys Swim you got this today.  The town of Barnegat is behind you !!!   Let's  bring it home… https://t.co/WCKJv1PMvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time, I asked the bartender at Temple for a root beer, and then he laughed at me. So I asked for an Arnold Palm… https://t.co/hVnPmYm3fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GiselleUgarte I use it! I don't have to work about it near as much as pads/tampons which is great, and less waste.… https://t.co/mevC5BxaHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[More details on the murder of #Refugee Camila turned back by US BPD and murdered in El Salvador https://t.co/bK9VEEUtod]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dig the message @chrisdelia Enjoyed hanging back in the HA HA days, doing the grind and watching you kick ass and… https://t.co/WPdbr7rVWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brought the sun back to my face thanks to @vitaliberata  With #vitaliberata  soothing and hydrating tanning product… https://t.co/ZtfhNOAbpV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not perfect, I have my days, I have my flaws, but I’m truly blessed for what I have and I never take it for granted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the morning at camp. We had visitors in February! Then Susan came over and we did more Trippin' videos in my… https://t.co/NgUzoLx9Cu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inesquecível... 🔥🔥🔥 Completely crowded!! 😱 Packed till the end of the room!! 🙏🏻❤️ Amazing audience!! Grande estreia… https://t.co/wGuiyisDdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh!! Its gonna be up to my waist when I get up there next week.  Still no place I'd rather be! https://t.co/Ls9bfvO7z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Lady #Supporters Asked Me To Release Some Music That They Can Vibe To 👸🏾💃🏾 So I’m Droppin “Trip Freestyle” Today… https://t.co/8Y5qUWFIJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bible teaches not to be lukewarm..it tells us what's rgt &amp; wrong.. to love the sinner but not the sin...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaira Hey @starblur did we give anyone that 6s (that has a perfect screen and a headphone jack)? Because it might have a home with K!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just saying... if someone surprised me by blindfolding and then telling me I’m skydiving, they would NEVER get… https://t.co/099SUDHx1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdolfoAguirreC Please have a safe trip, love. 😘 https://t.co/K6jOyPv3Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice conclusion to a presentation on payer partnerships: “And remember payers are people too” - Meredith Hein from… https://t.co/KBtkEcDaAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’ve lived in NC for 17 years, you really should have a favorite bb team. #BeatDook ? https://t.co/vENXZSpRpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely!!!🌸🌼🙌🏻 #bekind #showlove #bethelight @ Novi, Michigan https://t.co/wlIHotRbnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMattCouch @Solmemes1 I can't stand those folks but to each his own. 😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX This is the kind of show we need.  Don’t judge people by how they look. It was fun, silly, and eye opening ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dragon is on fire.., @MiamiHEAT #LetsGoHeat #LetsGoHeat #LetsGoHeat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Taco Tuesday!! #tacotuesday  ———————————— #exprealtyproud #exprealty #followmyheelshome #powerofthepumps👠… https://t.co/92ow3oG5TW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoloresOfCourse I asked you about money not about the floor people!!! These guys have been remodeling this SAME bu… https://t.co/wi16LvrPJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[cause I’m forever a thug ever a thug baby I’m forever in love ever in love]]></document></documents></author>