<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s weird seeing Facebook profile pictures because the ones who aren’t 21 have regular pictures while everyone ove… https://t.co/2zTa14o36E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just an FYI—I’ve spent the night listening to Vinegar Joe,Robert Palmer,Power Station, and @DuranDuran. What’s the… https://t.co/3ws88oINqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan Powell’s commentating makes Stephen Hawkin sound overly enthusiastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, @MarkMeadows this is how time works. With saying that is was racist in 2012 and it still is. https://t.co/dDq7Rwdmaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agoverningfrost I can relate to this. Sometimes when I have a couple good days in a row, I feel suspicious; like s… https://t.co/XbLXB7bAuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelpinkley_ No doubt! Looking at cities such as Boston, I'm sure it's already an area of interest.    For this… https://t.co/JtMnIuGO3o]]></document><document><![CDATA[🖤✨♥️  #bauhaus #petermurphy #davidjhaskins #40yearsofbauhaus @ TERMINAL 5 https://t.co/oS2WxdtvSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day at work someone was going to hand me a $5 bill but it was from 1990 and they said “this one is so old… https://t.co/wvp4QLxzsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We the American people do not support him and think he needs to be jailed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This bottle of wine said to let breathe for 30 minutes before drinking...Longest 5 minutes of my life. https://t.co/JQFQj9jf3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could re do my life from the past 10 years (maybe even 12) I would be the happiest girl ever lol I would have… https://t.co/3dGAQMtRph]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Happy Schatz's!! @ Westminster Dog Show (Best of Breeds) https://t.co/t0rpnPXNF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[👻Add Me!  Snapchat username : victorialomba1 Thx!! https://t.co/oDQA4wRrdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 14th Anniversary with megmal1021 @ The Well Bars https://t.co/5hyKA7Lspt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is one of my paintings from the 915 series. 915-5- Mixed Media, encaustic, collage, oil pigments on panel 6x10… https://t.co/AR72ky8hw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 @Heather_LPUK @realTuckFrumper @DanStirling3 Good one LeeLee! 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Floor - 8.0 4th place So I'm still trying to figure this one out.. I'm not sure if she was standing in solidarity t… https://t.co/O0EzBGR6fb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Days 1 &amp; 2 of #Slinkyacademy @ ‘Da Cuse.. great group of energetic, talented, and fun young athletes !! #future… https://t.co/UfUXlK5gAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPhelan31 Thanks! That’s a great idea. He’s letting me choose, but I want to make sure that’s ok with his fiancée—it’s her wedding, too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrChaeEd @HarlemGetsMoney @_beautyofegypt Haha. That dude deleted his tweets and blocked me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[women. you were born with the fire of queens in your soul, and the power of creation in your core. you are a force… https://t.co/WiUSL0A34s]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dressingaccordingtomarie trao3 #tonyrao #springbreakmiami @ The St. Regis Bal Harbour Resort https://t.co/ODXw62gpmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[like if you dislike valentine’s day because you’re not in a relationship you’re bitter and weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to get a selfie. #firstflightofthree #dave&amp;tim #mexico #ilovechaairport @ Chattanooga Airport https://t.co/HuM0IniAIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[WOOOOW. The last 15 years my non Spanish speaking ass thought he said “Culo”. It wasn’t until this video I realized… https://t.co/St3XRWg4hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoticiasRCN Ver estas imágenes me dan ganas de llorar por nuestros hermanos venezolanos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@republiconyos @BenjaminG302 @1zenbitch @Stuffits1 @RMConservative @realDonaldTrump Yes this proves if traffic is f… https://t.co/3EXMLBZvru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaydenSummerall @stevenrinella He literally just wants to hunt bc of Tegan lmfao]]></document><document><![CDATA[One time when I was 8, these two men on giant high wheels bikes (at least 5 foot tall) rode by my house dressed lik… https://t.co/TxzRqHS88u]]></document><document><![CDATA[s/o to the person who said i should be writing professionally. thanks for making me feel better ❤️🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD LUCK PAYING ME BACK ON YOUR ZERO DOLLARS A YEAR SALARY PLUS BENEFITS BABE !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @blainharber for give my “little sis” pro tips for jeans and picking on her with me tonight 😂 always good to see you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjamesnumber1 @OneBandwagonFan if they just accepted the L....  way better than being scammers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @ValeroEnergy and @CircleKStores for implementing touch to pay at the pumps! I love it! Will a zip code c… https://t.co/Pk11QUPk0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGildedJester @GoldenKnights “Arkan-sass” “Razorknight”... you give the best nicknames!  😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[“That’s how we have to play to win, we need to have all four lines going.” -Jonathan Huberdeau on tonight’s win ove… https://t.co/ENc2JTHcNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please #CALL your Reps at 202-224-3121 &amp; tell them to #SUPPORT these bills!  👇👇👇📱📱📱 https://t.co/umUrhnzqr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're at it again!! Love watching these two on my morning news @FBlankenshipWSB &amp; @MarkArum on @wsbtv! 😃😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CCBCMD at Essex...come talk to us about transferring to UD! We offer Fashion Merchandising, Criminal Justice,… https://t.co/2nafZ3Vdd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James46403 Lol, colonization???  I hope that's in jest - you sound like a creep or an idiot 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[new hair, who dis? [alt caption: look at this rad new haircut where I’m kinda trying to channel Beck minus the stal… https://t.co/576FV37gzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS, how is that anti-bullying campaign coming?  You are raising your son with a man that attacks someone dying… https://t.co/9xQJkGbcsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[at what point in my life did I start finding scrawny, stoner lookin’ boys attractive?]]></document><document><![CDATA[From: 40404 (1/3) @jhoandroit: RT @Luiselenu: Insólito, el Jefe de Consejo Comunal (2/3) de mi urbanización anoche… https://t.co/DG5ANNFnYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you no decency sir? He let thousands of gay men and women die and you want to talk about his optimism? This is… https://t.co/7cF4GIx3YW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SavageJoyMarie1 @HumanistReport @PSW_66 “Allow Me to Explain Why Beto Sucks” by Kathy Copeland Padden https://t.co/ITBTqTXd08]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starclusterr you’re right, but this was SO out of left field that even I was 👀 like I expected to hear we were a j… https://t.co/9AZtgI7S4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rowland72James @terrychristian @AuroraBlogspot Sorry for the late delay on the tweet but this is what we’ve been d… https://t.co/509u8MIVTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[nothing makes me happier than seeing people who i’ve been at the bottom with climb to the top]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hdz_edgar1 Yep and they’re just as cute as blues!! https://t.co/PfI1V6r4IG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnnoFarm @DawnVanstone I couldn't get my ram until January. No lambs for me until June. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the Democrats are trying to turn our christian country into an Islamic country...its getting time to stop t… https://t.co/Ng1XVuuwcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoVarnish1 @WriterRising I bought a copy of your book for my ___. They will love it as much as I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett paid the brothers $3500. Seems to me he could've saved his money and found someone who gladly would… https://t.co/XTkJio8485]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarcastic People Fixing Inspirational Images.  Perfect https://t.co/aEw6y1rMJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bougiehoolie I also thought it was a little different and I was in the meetings lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shall enter your house this morning with thanks giving LORD. I’m in need of a new beginning , healing and a new start!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost 4) Many lefties among Charlie. But not the Soviet type that follows a leader and a cult, the type t… https://t.co/zrzuRg3q94]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristosFloros Maybe you should do a PhD in global governance &amp; human security and think about these things more...]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Miss Allison turning 18 Tuesday…… Day 4 post ..... 🛍🎂🌻🌺🎁♥️🙏🏼😘🎉 @allihurddd I love you my HBBBB ♥️♥️♥️ https://t.co/HsKQ9B3dsr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillBissett @DAllenMoss You know you’re old when you’re the only people there concerned about the germs on all the… https://t.co/OkF1fda4PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@retrocrush is getting me into all kinds of trouble tonight.  Also, sonyta23 last shift. @ Pine Cove https://t.co/RSUFQtgIhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump I wonder if TRump is aware how much angst he is causing. I have a sick feeling in the… https://t.co/ubYPoS6ZFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Backstage at a #loveconnie show when tequila is involved 😂 this killing me!! #realhousewivesofatlanta @ The Cavern… https://t.co/4uTy8TmFZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also want more than anything is to be going to Dallas at the end of the month. Having a VERY hard time realizing ne… https://t.co/Kuv8iKmyyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @NBCNews I just can’t believe @GOP are ALL that stupid!! Considering I am one of them OR was !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting news from @Apollobecerra about upcoming student ANGLeS Challenge Workshop sponsored by @NASA on 3/30… https://t.co/OW94VBtraZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost So when other presidents declared a National Emergency I guess it was all about them https://t.co/GXYUSZVKkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Ex Phys teacher’s thought it was super smart to have two exams back to back on the HARDEST chapter, in the SAME week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blah. Blah. Blah. Joke. Joke. Joke. Commentary. - @KeithHabs @tryguys That is going to be my senior quote]]></document><document><![CDATA[Song in my head upon awakening edition 29: I Don't Care Sincerely ~ Timothy Seth Avett https://t.co/8yJjyMwqvC via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amazingjr87 @essayareayaitch @AnnMarieCFSS Go into the Disney store, and they’re doing it on the second floor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HLAurora63 @GroupHomepage Oh man.....I am right there with....pains my heart 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlineWH #DeadlineWH @MSNBC Michael and Claire are spot on about impeachment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GPM018 @dobermanmamma @BunkerGear_Gal @PokerDame Luv ya too Gary.. even though I don't know you well enough!! LOL  ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sore losers... maybe we should be more “Politically correct” since losing the election hurt their feelings. They ne… https://t.co/S5WsWKdP49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DemTeaParty2020 @ellievan65 Every trump family member. Liars &amp; frauds!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siadvance Making my own poll: Should I be mad at this mysterious “mds” for making me google the Khloe/Tristan news?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke didn’t disappoint! Thanks @sammyyhaven for inviting me and lost count of how many concerts this makes me and m… https://t.co/BknaDeWA0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Damn you just want to make a home right up trumps ass don’t you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @shortman5427 This woman is either greedy or mentally ill and does not care about the struggling Americans here today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Shut up ivanka you don’t know what real women go through each day you were born with a silver spoon in… https://t.co/bA3h9RxMeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[thesparrowparkcircle 730 Round 2 for Battle of the Bands! 🤘 @ The Sparrow https://t.co/dhH6nWO91K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophomores-check your emails for info on Ring Dinner Tickets! https://t.co/ddEpOlXtKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be the one to deadass wake up and feel like complete shit a day before i leave for vacation. Lml]]></document><document><![CDATA[The little girl crying at Costco because her mom said no to pizza is crying for both of us]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all ever compare instagram comments to see if you got a cuter response than everyone else who commented. yeah me either tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alamance Lax tourney pics are up ~ feel free to tag/share/download at will.  Enjoy!  @taguilar21 EA vs Williams at   https://t.co/YGun1LMUgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JxhnBinder Congress needs to get off their dead asses and start doing their JOBS, we need IMMIGRATION REFORMS stop… https://t.co/XTv9taxtOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am 25 and I just spent 30 minutes watching @jonasbrothers videos. I am more excited that they are back together t… https://t.co/Ts2mVMeiTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurenpoff @Healthynewlife2 A very confusing scene for me to watch as well Lauren! Not slow at all. Just being honest ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[10.138 - Nick Pivetta  All 3 starters could give me 250 Ks. Also could take a hit in ERA and WHIP #gobigorgohome https://t.co/Tv0dWxRVdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesselynCastro @ORLANDOSHINES @anthonyetuggle Jesslyn and I are shirt twins! Looks like you guys had a blast #TUGGLENATION]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeedYourFandomEntry https://t.co/477gVsjIGs ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜💘💘💘 Ends 7/31/19 ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Wallace was relentless in interrupting and grilling Steven Miller who handled Wallace like Wallace was a rook… https://t.co/DSl4OhxjUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinMeade note #2-It’s insane how bright eye’d an Razor Sharp ? 5:30 AM! Tell your dad I said thank you, SUNSHINE… https://t.co/xcw9Fp1fQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight I got to witness secretary @Michael_S_Regan sharing @NC_Governor's proclamation of April 2019 as #STEM… https://t.co/8y6ERE0R1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shanedawson @AndrewSiwicki I’m just saying now everyone in Grand Forks, ND know!! This was such an awesome series!… https://t.co/NVbhbQWXC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaBauz @kaci150 @Littlleome @TwistedOne96 @RodHillis1 @Jhwrr @mymynags @CaliRN619 @OLDFLACO @my3monkees… https://t.co/3nk8yvAde7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone else noticed how the contestants on the bachelor ONLY wear white nail polish?? Is there a reason for this?]]></document></documents></author>