<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I feel so proud of myself that my managers are actually arguing over me on where to place me at work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMcSallyAZ I disagree with you on almost every policy issue, but I am very sorry to hear this. I hope some good… https://t.co/qF3qM5Aba6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P2 @AB84 Awkward We actually are requesting a trade to send him there and get you our defense needs help 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[THREE INGREDIENT PROTEIN MUFFINS 😯 💪🏼  . . 6 grams of protein, 3 grams of fiber 🍌, and 0 added sugar (unless you wa… https://t.co/i6kLqgZ2oi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adam: “We’re gonna play a game that has to do with church.” @emily_faith217: “Jesus! Haha! I win. Where’s my prize?” Y’all 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[How ‘engaged’ journalism helped a community tackle suicide https://t.co/MSLkKeeVlb Check this out! Yes. Just do it! #spsm #AAS365]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Matt Gaetz is quite a little tick. What oath did he take and when is his term up? Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i literally watch jeopardy while I run at the gym and idk what I’m going to do without alex trebeck #Jeopardy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers appreciated for my father in law who is transitioning into eternal life. #saintkatherinedrexel #Eternalrest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some random guy is trying to sell Chris a vacuum and he’s in my fricken house right now are you kidding me. If I do… https://t.co/Bf1krQ7jnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMAOO “iTs JusT TwiTTer Ya FemaLes THink TOo MuCH” yeah yeah suck a dick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues la canción de los TXT me agrado mucho su tonito, vamos a esperar a ver mas presentaciones👀 todo va bien! ¡Felicidades por su debut!]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida me ah dado salud trabajo pero sobre todo amistades que te ofrecen confianza y un cariño que no compras con… https://t.co/vbNFTuUAdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despierten, el déficit por las altura, y los más ltibillonarios muy felices por el tremendo regalito que les hizo e… https://t.co/WtCm5vH0eS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonebeling @Echo4Resistance @MaeVic3 @Wtg4Gateau @WildChild69 @howloften @theladykatie @kenziebeck23… https://t.co/HedhF6REag]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found THREE spoons while #springcleaning out our cabinet! #mediatree #hyveetoday @ Hy-Vee https://t.co/wPM5e66Mic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Extended Barrel-Aged B.O.R.I.S. Oatmeal - Imperial Stout by @hoppinfrog @ The Bottle Shop — https://t.co/is0YjZEwht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaliarii @dyess_kelley @constancevaland @amvetsupport @realDonaldTrump There you have it #ATrueTantrum]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been trying to open these damn eye drops for the longest and i give up]]></document><document><![CDATA[This year we added the @Ravens @RavensCommunity to our #TackleReading team! Can’t wait to see your photos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It already sucks having to watch people die all the time, but it hits a whole lot harder when their loved ones are watching too]]></document><document><![CDATA[#anabelgonzalezfigueroa #miramealosojos #lookintomyeyes @ Miami, Florida https://t.co/RKJJxDn8q2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not getting caught if you talk about it.  Not illegal either since it us in the Constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenni_Meatballz 😂😂😂 omg yes lmao!! Jen, I use to gag at girls who’s bf’s gave them money bc I was “independent wom… https://t.co/sJAKpO9BZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help Me Title This Drawing Below 👇🏽  How does it make you feel?   ***PROFESSIONAL ILLUSTRATION***  #figureart #cold… https://t.co/bANRYNZ5wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kgreen_write @TeresaRobeson @ljrwritenow @PJMcIlvaine @writerjolene @iwriteforkidz @HannahSpuler @MelissaRicheson… https://t.co/szJPixK7Y1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando el dice que me merezco todo y yo sé que no, es cuando sonrío y le quiero dar mil besos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think about @tanamongeau ‘s video on makeup by people you hate and her impression of laura lee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thisisblayne When the parents have that glazed over look of defeat, you know that kid is gonna start screaming at… https://t.co/8QFkB6HYRD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DixonJay98 welp good thing i like everything besides nuts and cereal🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[My amazing husband helping some pets &amp; their owners this past weekend!   #AnimalWelfare #pets @AnimalPlanet https://t.co/V7ENi3AmK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I relish any opportunity to stay in my house for an entire day. If I’m also able to bake while in the house, it’s a… https://t.co/gaSkycLwJN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lushcosmetics Soaks into the skin so well!!! I was moisturized all day 👏👏 going to be adding this to my routine for sure. 🍌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoalieGearNerd Price like 99.9% of hockey players are real class!! 🏒❤️🏒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roblox almost there sabrina found and result is triggered becoming prisoners again like jake granddaughter Geegee9… https://t.co/cOMZmDUvho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoseKingOberon @jdo916 @Scottie713 @DylanJohnSeaton @GobAbiertoBOL @BernieSanders To me, it’s not even about being… https://t.co/cs8cqLSHtr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just about out of maroon and gold clothing for tonight’s @IonaGaelsMBB game vs Siena. (Sorry Saints ... family… https://t.co/UD9OZAWY1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[To see the rest of this video or future content click the link In my bio and don’t forget to subscribe to my channe… https://t.co/kJ0VWpgOXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an idiot, and a pig. Like depriving them of food will make them read better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My MIL was so into #LHHNY she sat down and asked why was @JoeBudden pissed about his ex being there. I had to fill… https://t.co/xIwQCytC7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019 Will Be a Great Year for Buyers AND Sellers https://t.co/8ueJtAqSvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a visitor, Dr. Jewell. 😁 She listened to the students' arguments and made the final decision.  Loving it!… https://t.co/fMFUWRUtLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @VernBuchanan for voting yes on HR8 (background checks) You just helped to make us all a little safer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Es un ser de luz este Pablo. Le está dando el apoyo que otros le han negado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar I’d probably just scream cry 😭 &amp; crash https://t.co/IQ3k3dMJFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@canklin @GinaMChaput I agree. This still sounds like an NMR question to me. What type have you tried so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Listed in #Manassas #VA. 7638 CHADDS LANDING WAY! Please retweet!  https://t.co/RC1CzevdCx  [For sale]]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who mix up "are" and "our" obviously never read for pleasure.  #grammarpolice]]></document><document><![CDATA[It has been a while since I had a flare-up, but today my body decided to remind me what they're like.  😣 #Spoonies… https://t.co/3XCzka96r2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 2.0 mph WNW. Barometer 30.328 in, Rising. Temperature 14.2 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 51%]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS MORNING she texted me i have a dolly you can use. So we go to pick up the uhaul. The extra help showed up at o… https://t.co/5BuFvT4IfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SongStuckinMyHead  is  “Rocky Top” and I don’t regret singing this song after this afternoon ‘s win, I’m gonna lea… https://t.co/Ov7XgiU7G4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YuriGomez22 @iamcardib @OffsetYRN @trvisXX @21savage Don’t lose me go hard 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed the Friends vs Southwestern game because I was out of town. Now ima miss it again on the 23rd cause I’ll b… https://t.co/sFMO64pr3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AddyDeww @emmaglezer depends, does your father talk about the hobbit nonstop??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it the night of the burglars #Livepd #LivePDNation https://t.co/j8PRKn5Ws4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aw crud. It’s arrived! Vaccinate your kids people. It might save their life, your life, and ANY immune compromised… https://t.co/jwUwxkjXyi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m havin’ a tough time with this cartoonist i hired for my assignment. I’m freakin’ out since last night bec i hav… https://t.co/rMmoMJpEqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We know you love to be peed on ,Can't wait for the tapes to be released 😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalisInk @jt_tauber13 @lauren_s_angelo @Orangelife_99 Good luck Frank!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with @tedcruz... it is time for #TERMLIMITSNOW Join the fight and support Ted's constitutional amendment --… https://t.co/ZCP0YiN0qs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My school is interested in doing an all-school read next year.  Any ideas for a book that will resonate with kids i… https://t.co/Va4umUVP9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner There is absolutely no abuse of power as our intelligent President Trump has declared a national state o… https://t.co/wk318dyQPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimSichko I’m not a priest, but as a woman that cares deeply and passionately about victims and abusers I do belie… https://t.co/5akS82X14h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SCJohnson @PlasticBank If you can do it -Just build as many as you can as fast as you can! Saving the earth is not… https://t.co/mO2Dv9qPnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @siadvance for sharing my story since Aprox 400 paintings done for #humanity for free updated First Time… https://t.co/NBe500IPwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Presidents Day and  National Drink Wine Day! So lift your glass to honor the previous 43...drink enough to for… https://t.co/026V7WH6AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know this information is important to know but I just wish I knew why it’s important to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[One thing I’m not going to miss from the cruise is their coffee. Literally tastes like ocean water.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch Buffett @ Wassabi #sogood #lunch #fridayvibes #letseat @ Wassabi Gastonia https://t.co/lM7Xjgnf5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found these super cute and fun Sallie Hansen @JellyBellyUK nail polish at Walgreens!! https://t.co/WVs4bmLJBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I far preferred Emily Blunt's version.   Unpopular opinion: never been that impressed by Bette Midler.   #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the stuff nightmares are made of!  Never had FB as it always made me nervous...thank God for that female intui… https://t.co/0iEemrY36J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamwandasykes @MMFlint The NRA likes Bernie! All other candidates get a big fat F.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best incentive trip by far. Kids loved skating, got to see the hockey team practice, I got most of my 6th grade sof… https://t.co/LtwnKYUXGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally demonic. He will be in Hell with the devil. I believe he is possessed with the devil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KeleeRingo @Mill_Edits @RecruitEdits @guccimax2x @slaterwolfcale #4sUp #8CLAP #BRUINS https://t.co/LMD5qRAj7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheyellszae I am bro💯I’m just waitin on this other single to drop first😈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lead_mbradley Thanks!! I needed a visual reminder of all those topics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amati9 @cbg_photos @victoriajbd @MeghaJC @Amy_Siskind I’m a lawyer and I would happily volunteer but I’m sure they… https://t.co/TvkJUHzD7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[also that fur shit i wore made a big ass mess and i never wanna work with that material ever again like...no.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 22 year old said I look like I turned 28 cause I came to the club with a sweater on 😭, it’s cold 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Hey! What’s wrong with being Looney? I’ve been a Looney my whole life. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SydneeReinhard @Precious_18 @21_melll CANT WAIT TO SEE YALLS FIT!!!! https://t.co/Nk7oTxvXlX]]></document><document><![CDATA[the internet hasn’t given me female!Andrew yet so I took matters into my own hands. 🖤✨ #LittleWitchAcademia #LWA_jp… https://t.co/LDUVThHHHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eeddieann96 Imma try soon! In like June. Or may. Or idk. But this summer some time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if u don’t give in to Benji and his cute ass face right now we gonna have a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[No wonder ash can never hear in real life. We’re in the sauna and I’m sitting at the other end and I can still hear her music.🤘🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile,you’re harping on how she wants to stay stagnant,&amp; not better herself,etc. That’s on you,playa’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A brilliant gala evening at @theRMG with friends supporting @AIDSDurham.  A fun night raising money to support… https://t.co/tmaje18ETd]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HouseDemocrats @SenateDems voted to allow MURDER!  As constituent is this ok?😳?  .@KansasDemocrats @KyDems… https://t.co/ngaMVDAA3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait. waiiiiiit. first of all, socialism isn’t a “bad” thing and it surely isn’t comparable to being a slaveowner o… https://t.co/njL18EmOYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[when it rains it pourssss @ The Schottenstein Center https://t.co/2e9GGqlAbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s crazy when you got to block somebody from every social media 🤷🏾‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelBa86419193 your gf lowkey look like coraline and u look like wybie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveinLC I would be shocked if he got that. 3/50 or 4/60 I think. I bet it’s only 3 years though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What it’s like to be the 1st one. Then welcome a 2nd like you. Then bring in more and more... thank you Pixar!   Pu… https://t.co/tOyQPYoZdK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning my friends😊  Today I choose joy 🌝how about you?  The beggining of your week, hve you done some self ca… https://t.co/BhyOmdCCL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shaycleaves @SiestaKey @chloe_trautman we are NOT rooting for you Carret]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj The big problem is they don't turn Fox off...They watch it all day...They don't want to see other news to… https://t.co/JOiaV95Bg5]]></document></documents></author>