<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Shower and getting ready and headed out!! Having a great week excited about what's to come]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paola_Dec1231 No. What’s to say she wouldn’t harm us. Untrustworthy enemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shireen818 Morality and lives of innocent people do not matter, everything comes down to MONEY in the #US corrupt… https://t.co/znlevDWJw3]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars Desde Monterrey NL México con mi esposo disfrutando Viva México Cuaronres TNT la mejor]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 page paper due tomorrow and I’m on the 2nd paragraph. Doing great honey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogsand cats living together – mass hysteria! #wine #drinkies #winenight #catwine #reisling #dogs… https://t.co/lHK5GFVhSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who tryna play pool in the game room tomorrow??! I promise I can beat everybody]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoadriii there are simply skipping a bunch of critical steps so they have to teach it. To me that compromises thei… https://t.co/1qxOwPMT0G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedroluisflores Huele raro con sello cubano! Hasta cuando? Y el pueblo ni por eso sale contundentemente!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The third rule of Ferengi rules of acquisition instructs careful handling of money.  contact with us 👉🔗… https://t.co/krcTKKNXgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RecomiendoLeer SONATA DE AMOR, de @Isacrisacu Una adictiva y emocionante historia, con personajes fuertes y pasion… https://t.co/qVep9pTvEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bald eagle weighed down by 8-pound ball of ice https://t.co/YrTPyF7jqB via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so excited to have a day without meetings....until I checked my email this morning and had a few Skype meeting invitations 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swear I’ll start feelin like school is going fine and then all of a sudden it’s like getting hit by a bus and you h… https://t.co/eLHV0tKboJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t have to be an a**hole to stop being so forgiving, but keep in mind ppl know wtf they be doing! Let that sh*t go. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Backupkidsfort1 @OpenSociety Clintom really trief to help haitian children right? Ask any Haitians, they’ll tell y… https://t.co/GBaWFz9qzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just need to keep this baby inside of me for another 2 weeks, and to make it home to ct this weekend 🙏🏻🙏🏻 positive thoughts guys]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you know 2 or more languages than you’re automatically smarter than the entirety of the American population nd that’s just the facts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#march 9th  mark yourself #busy 🗓 WITH #SELFCARE #SATURDAY ❤️🧠☮️💃🏽 from 11 am - 3 pm granitecitybrewery of course!… https://t.co/lHoqkoeo0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[since gallogly doesn’t wanna cancel school do i email all my teachers &amp; make a plea or.....?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been using @tula for about 2 weeks now (after hearing how amazing it is from a bunch of people), and my skin h… https://t.co/Gv4mtc0GVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@allyracing @JimmieJohnson @amsupdates Yes, he will get that win! Jimmie is still the best!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @mssmith_math to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Eac… https://t.co/01RRKDONH0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things that excite me: when the beat drops @3:05 listening to dance yrself clean by lcd soundsystem with headphones on]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take a Snow Day! @PGCJNJ Ski Weekend at @massresort #JNJ #GorgeousPrinceGeorges #JJOA @JackandJillInc https://t.co/aZc6Q147Dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast date at Gilbert's. @ Gilbert's El Indio Restaurant https://t.co/OvHJoDtSa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JensterGeek @topzepptraxx I like Mary too. I feel like people write her off for “abandoning” the boys after they g… https://t.co/oXvRGaCRV6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skkelleywrites I also hate TVs and mirrors at night. Anything reflective 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@riotgirlbrooke Or, hear me out, it’s not a trend and people are starting to feel better about who they are, feelin… https://t.co/w8BQAc9OWQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tempted.   #lentwithlifesprings, #lifespringswomen, #lifespringsintl, #lentphotoaday, #lentphotochallenge.    “...a… https://t.co/LqVVh5dQAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I (almost) cared about this Khloe/Tristan/Jordyn drama til I realized a new season of KUWTK was coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wavecrest Open Space - Macro shots (trees and clover horizontal) #wavecrest #wavecrestopenspace… https://t.co/dKywPcrUNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This filter really brings out our eyes 👀   Happy Friday-Eve!! https://t.co/iMGw1AZtCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking it all in #westcoast #LA @DrewDeHart @Andrea_DeHart_ @JedDehart https://t.co/jxToIJkMhw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Meditation!  I relax MY mind and body. Peacefulness spreads inside me overflowing to share with others… https://t.co/1qY9wXxUa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoloTamassi @IlhanMN @AOC Too bad @IlhanMN won’t read that editorial. Then again it won’t change the inherent anti… https://t.co/vEpUIDSZI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer You rig the system against “We the People”. You commit treason by doing so.  Is this why… https://t.co/Q3E84Em5pz]]></document><document><![CDATA[i might have just accidentally started some shit and i’m not even sorry 😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If Poor Baby can't stand the heat, Poor Baby should get out of the kitchen. Resign...before it all gets much worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone gotten a call from the Social Security Admin today? I called the number back and they said they’re close… https://t.co/L1y8P8KOPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick is on the CI team, and won’t be playing, but he will be there! And he would love to have everyone join us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes MJ  took his innocense  , but you Gladly Handed it to Him To take. For $$. Only sympathy for the boys, while th… https://t.co/zFIet0ho8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I managed to take 120 pictures before my phone died. #MardiGras #OakCliff #Parade @ Bishop Arts District, Dallas https://t.co/4LXGwtlSVc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar story niente male. La mia preferita però è quella di Judy Garland  candidata per A star is born che è in ospe… https://t.co/GRfeMZKME9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's another cool plane I learned about a while ago: The Super Guppy. It's the only one of its kind (excluding th… https://t.co/iTsXlo6RPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendly reminder that everyone is entitled to their own opinion and *maybe*  we should judge them based on their c… https://t.co/fg2bJRIJgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early am flights. 👎  Early am flights after daylight savings. 👎👎  Early am flights after daylight savings time and… https://t.co/CxDA3RR8Av]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudyJ31830202 @laura24fan @ToddTPrice24 @chevychevelle48 @JoePalmerJr @JLee418 @DaleJr88FanNate @jonesbrent570… https://t.co/h4haZUB8mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @TPUSA @charliekirk11 He should definitely press charges.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! Here are some pretty flowers for you! 🌹Whatever it means to you-I hope you get to tell someo… https://t.co/DWlcbZsgXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steelersdepot He doesn’t seem to want to be a Steeler with his recent tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vendo coisinhas nas lojas ontem e me coçando de vontade de comprar pro meu filho, o @flavionm https://t.co/sOQJoVqH8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have appointments this Saturday starting at 11am. You can schedule your appointment through the link in my bio.… https://t.co/u0kIjYWTzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super Cooper Friday! #heartawarenessmonth #congenitalheartdefect @ Rhinebeck, New York https://t.co/2TNaJjaeIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Swipe to see how bad I am at taking pictures with glasses on 🤷🏼‍♀️ @ Tennessee Aquarium https://t.co/lLu8eC5VL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do love when the bus is at the stop and there’s only one working fare machine and a woman gets OFF the bus, cuts… https://t.co/XwhXoLnsRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[oomf doesn’t find Kali Uchis attractive but has the the audacity to rub basic white women in my face... https://t.co/IKVVLqJxcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NotesFromNationalEmergency - I left my house for a manicure and haircut this weekend. Thank God I had my passport… https://t.co/C1vzlDGV4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[As usual, @realDonaldTrump is all show and no go. #TrumpFail #NorthKoreaSummit EMBARRASSING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 It seems that all republiscums think of is sex. Usually someone elses!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Egyptian soup over rice with onions in vinegar and toast.  Omg it's so yummy!!!  #oneloveya'll #foodporn #egyptian… https://t.co/kNTZcowJAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[do what you love and you'll never have a problem with monday! @Business3487 @YambagK #cna #na #work #dayshift #everydayisdifferent]]></document><document><![CDATA[If she didnt bash their head in to get them then serial killer is off the table]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful experience to see Nicotra Foundation grants used by @23Richmondtown @NYCSchools in such meaningful ways… https://t.co/TrFPVBbKk5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just realized I’ll never look like this again so I’m going to just post more pics of it 🤷🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/wtY7tFRm8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[rip me bc all the boyfriend material guys i know are people i’ve friendzoned and they’re getting into relationships… https://t.co/9FdjBeP167]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julesgarcia8 @austin2lamb @RyleighMata @hilliard_jaden @childssmaggie @TyBaker58 @maddyblake07 @rome_shubert17… https://t.co/dVGXTto5Lz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatclouthier MUCHO ÁNIMO TATIANA; TÚ SABES COMO HACERLO.  MEXICO REQUIERE DE PERSONAS QUE LO AMEN Y RESCATEN DEL A… https://t.co/exf0GypQZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smontney1969 I get it from all ages. Apparently they're all reading the same bad advice column.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eltonconte @luciano_hang Ah tá, então Mancha não é a torcida do Palmeira e Gaviões a torcida do Corinthians??? Ess… https://t.co/koFfIuATuA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another day at the office! Although, I will say the trade show for trade show people is much more fun than my… https://t.co/44YKIQGUTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nitenurse2 What about you, Rosemary? You're a generous retweeter which is a nice thing. But what about you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pidneyy That’s weird cuz we used to rock out to burnin up......... now I feel like that memory was just betrayed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it would’ve made for some good tv if Colton hadn’t jumped the fence so easily and struggled a bit #thebachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know where these statistics are coming from , but this doesn’t include all people of color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milkncherrios I just think saying “the past is the past” and disregarding the roots of racial classism is complete… https://t.co/43E3xYwH16]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msilvaazul Para gustos los colores, clasificar la música es un acto vacío, no lleva a ningún lado.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/uUr93gG3GJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@renato_mariotti @InSpiteOfTrump @CPAC @mercedesschlapp Those in power must find a way to stand up for Mueller. Enough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@avrgegrl81 @roywoodjr If i ever get a way but i have no way to get there i am anti social and i really don't talk… https://t.co/eBVm97J0I9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minimum wage laws can put low-income workers out of a job and raise prices for everyone else. My latest (and first!… https://t.co/OwVHI84Rup]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #internationalwomensday ♀lets take a look at some of lesser-know and very talented women behind the scenes on… https://t.co/YcYQZJm1Fo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshieecs Hmm, but there is this: Shakur began recording in 1987. It was his professional entertainment career tha… https://t.co/PurQ0X5TQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Catching up with an old friend over sushi is always a good idea. #sake #saba #sushi #nigiri #thatshowweroll… https://t.co/BBrjKw5efU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigifields1995 @WCPSSElemLit @wcpsselemela @SherriMiller06 @JamillahSimpson @trlipscomb @Ms_Smith1120 Saving this to read later!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why has it become a thing for girls to pull their jackets half way down off their shoulders for a picture? It annoys me so much..😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Espero en Dios que esta sea la última noche que pasamos en este hospital para comenzar un nuevo camino hacia la rec… https://t.co/WpYlj9M0r3]]></document><document><![CDATA[THATS NOT MY NAME IS A TIMELESS FUCKING BOP. WHY DOES THIS STILL GO SO HARD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got a new homeowner getting excited. We installed @cambriaquartz Brittanicca in her kitchen and Queen Anne in a… https://t.co/7oqWg7p2l4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this moved me to tears. @TheEllenShow you define #equality in the most basic terms. On… https://t.co/SjCIO6X4HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarleyRouda @FoxNews But have you co-sponsored the #GreenNewDealResolution yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I confirmed my course for Uni starts on September 23rd I’m so excited that means I get a month break for Christmas… https://t.co/lEHUSPt1tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accidentally texted Dale my tweet and he gone respond “What’s the problem”😂😂😂I’m all confused trying to figure out what’s going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Her name didn’t ring any bells but I do remember my granny telling me about a woman who died from TB when her son w… https://t.co/6d0jZ2QRaG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadByBHVR FIX YOUR FRIGGIN SERVERS. Me and my friend have been waiting an HOUR. Got in one and then killer dodged… https://t.co/S92GYOILjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StopthisBill @senatemajldr and #Rhinos in the @SenateGOP duped the @POTUS into agreeing to sign before he could se… https://t.co/lyVg0OgUE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeggyHarkins @stephen_rotich @AlchemicJourney @AlexRiedel10 @henrirousseau12 @GubbaRum @my_lennar @ManeatGrass… https://t.co/m0ReShkSEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All @Boyd_2650 This is.the party that gives you everything for nothing then raises your taxes to pay for it. A… https://t.co/oIH7zBddL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maceytayler @t__heg If I had a dollar for every time I have called y’all and you didn’t answer and then you text m… https://t.co/gJTwhqbTuK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XochitlGalvez @senadomexicano @CanalCongreso Xochitl, pregunteles: 1. Qué es el Código de Red? 2. Qué son las TICs… https://t.co/ZMrjTfLG70]]></document></documents></author>