<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@shitduosays #Queen much? #GreatSong #Duolingo #LOL https://t.co/2AfcXzPRJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dadank1 @brianstelter @ReliableSources here is a better shot of it  The opening of the park  9/18 https://t.co/7Ak5UpUmh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristopherAlph @scottsflights Just do it you will be amazed where you will go @scottsflights]]></document><document><![CDATA[We think 40℉ constitutes a trip to our local zoo; especially after a brutally cold winter, it's great to leave the… https://t.co/sbCNpadX8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitandrewking   “currently about 9 years into Cycle 24. The current peak makes Cycle 24 smaller than Cycle 14, wh… https://t.co/3CPjCsMo4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accept assistance; embrace camaraderie; flourish. #leadership #quote #HR https://t.co/fSWW92YRjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frequentbuyer1 @HeathMayo @AlliancePTY Haven’t heard from others. I don’t even know what state I will be in so I c… https://t.co/B8SafhL3oR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, man. It’s starting! #LemontLightning #baseball #lemont @ Lemont Police Department https://t.co/CmlzfO1bAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stinking New York City has billboard bad mouthing amazon leaving well amazon has lot more class than you asswipes i… https://t.co/rHEZqei0Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbykasch so so so awesome you made it to the voice. I know you are going to do great]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesUdland @BrianSozzi Every retailer is a great place to work when you can expand store count. No better place t… https://t.co/quJ0D8nKTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad but true.....once your out the cup  no ones arsed anymore....don’t even know who’s still in or care tbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even really be mad at men for being shitty because I ain’t shit either lmao 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAG4All We need 24 hour court at the border, with immediate deportation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillCastroAlves EEM/SPX perto da mínima desde a criação do ETF em 2003. Vai ter giro forte no jogo :) https://t.co/Xe7886k1pK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse LOL sure you are!  Everyone knows you tweet when you are taking your executive time dump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow You were in the Air Force. That doesn’t count. You probably did everything from home online.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yassybelle_ This must have been a good 5 years ago at this point, and I just thought about it and got heated all over again lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @KLongRobinson to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews ➡️ jus… https://t.co/1u3T185kRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Ever I Cease To Love : Church Hosts Mardi Gras Celebration https://t.co/OQr32Mu8mp https://t.co/Oac1EttQXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #WCW and my crushes are number 1 my wife... cuz she’s my forever and ever. And she puts up with my 💩. Number 2… https://t.co/QVUqZlXCx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leading my first faculty professional development today, webpage building, should be fun!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now we’re switching gears to PERS agency expenses... this slide made me sit-up... we’re the 3rd most complicated sy… https://t.co/B288V3brIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACHSBands THEY CANT BE SENIORS YET! Except that Den Adel Guy. He is too tall for high school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geigerpatty1 Ugh I cannot WAIT to go to Alaska this summer!! So beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gustafsson on his belly as the puck goes in. Picture perfect. #Blackhawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how I love this child. He’s grown up way too fast - wasn’t he 4 years old just yesterday?! 2 days til he turns 1… https://t.co/SafMNHYslT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s been a while@since I posted images. Here you go. Photo by Michael López   . . . . . #photojournalist… https://t.co/c21NCr0FdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoolStoryLu Dawg why nobody ever remember this song when I bring it up???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Noches de @karambaslc con alumnos en Club Karamba https://t.co/DLzXdeU1bc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Handsome Mick's Irish Stout by Vermont Pub &amp; Brewery @ Vermont Pub &amp; Brewery — https://t.co/r6vjYyRjEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC WHOSE THE LEADER OF OUR PRESIDENT ,WHOSE WAS MADE FOR YOU AND ME ,MUS SO LINI,,,IN OTHER WORDS WE HAVE MICKY… https://t.co/hAaFL73cix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dannykanell Outside of unforeseen injuries— I genuinely don’t understand why the “best of the best” wouldn’t want… https://t.co/aY3zZ3jKx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls say they like clingy but when I show up outside their window at 3 am suddenly I'm "obsessed" and "I need help"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboveTheMadness @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump Don’t take your kids to commit a crime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our top 5th graders doing the #APS Middle School #Math Competition.  Bring it Colt and Lilly!  @MorrisBrandonES… https://t.co/gEmPvwck6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhriGG @NBCBostonCraig @Max_Lederman Exactly he’s needs to go back to the bench and put Jaylen back in the starting line up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God  @powerhousegym save me life!!!!!!!! I just finished another amazing cardio workout @powerhousegym rockin… https://t.co/pYWMaHtg0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would be remiss if I didn’t mention Kemper was also cinematographer for 1991’s “F/X 2”, 1996’s “Eddie” *and* “Jin… https://t.co/GkcsjE923a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our dogs commitment this afternoon to get on the couch is level 9000...#dogsoftwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi #Toronto (👋 Queen's Park), please take note of Winnipeg taking note of Ottawa "spending billions on mass transit… https://t.co/3Bn9HbsNhm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Hollywood PR Peeps - I will go to your after Oscar’s party ~  $100 (DM me)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go!!! Time for  #OverdriveLiveBand to get the party started !!!! Come catch us tonight at The Flying Walrus!!! https://t.co/PQtmZ1ydh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good players are worth nothing if you don't have good chemistry. Good players are good teammates. - @JohnBeilein… https://t.co/vHcW4Xlzzk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blindboy and the CNI dawgs Live at Birdys in Indianapolis,Indiana. @ Birdy's Live https://t.co/Rb5FFKqhbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes I’ve started my beard journey and have a acquired a bit of hair on my face lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From a small area in Brooklyn called East Flatbush that music have some magic potion in the water that just creates… https://t.co/NV91NHS4eI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to welcome this 4 amazing chefs / friends from 4 continents to cook with me on March 10th for our 2… https://t.co/DXsTB0FtQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByYourLogic My IQ and waistline are synonymous https://t.co/CcLGhaitT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASUNTO DE TIEMPO, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/HQXWSWMOB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que chulada mis sobrinas, 💕💕 #nes #tmnt en Juárez, Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/N4SfWJphp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump You don't watch much real news....DO YOU??? https://t.co/ubWTmrbcmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamrussoxxx @ArmaniNicco @JakeNicolaX I hope you had a delicious Valentine’s Day..😜👊🏼 https://t.co/TyE57obSb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Arnold Began To Get Sick While Fishing 🎣 On The River And Ask Me To Pray For Him And We've Never Met Before, Bu… https://t.co/rfjOg91nLH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I have to confess, I watched fox fake news for a total of 3 minutes in my entire life. Trust me, I’m… https://t.co/G9BqOUmXD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranzkeLA If Adam Eaton has a WS ring, so should I. I’ve put up with a lot more in all my years]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stars &amp; Stripes - Pool A &amp; B (G3) - Michigan Mystics Kevin def. Michigan Premier White  42-6 #LBICERTIFIED @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robmurphyEMU @Bushleague22 @DerySpeaks @GregSteinerEMU @EMUHoops @J_T_IV2 New Season Starts On Monday Go Green Go… https://t.co/UFmmy1lwXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBreathe_Xenon @BOOOfficial @ChelseaGrinUT Hope u feel better. Try some heat for this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cr0sscheck @SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @9NEWS @WMUR9 @cogop @NHGOP @RealTT2020 @MikeTokes… https://t.co/RrwjUbSa8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[no more excuses, no more complaining just prayin’ hard with hard workin’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer Team Program directors looking at the same identical text a player gave them and another coach saying they w… https://t.co/FbPqYx7Xde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets vote for @DonaldJTrumpJr in 2024! He has a bright political future. @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends… https://t.co/Jz6VRKuWvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@futpicante @Beto_Murrieta @MauricioYmay @borgetti58 “Joven” Murrieta, porque cuando te toca referirte al equipo CA… https://t.co/nFdq8bKeSw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN turned you off!  Breaking news in Vietnam!  Historic implications.  Shame on you CNN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally!! I get back into @scottlay the #nooner for my 44th bday! Woohoo! Thanks for the #cakeday shout out… https://t.co/ydQ913CZ6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDK WTF we doing but it ain't nomore #InOzzieWeTrust our defense just leaving piece by piece. #SMFH @Ravens]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Os habéis enchufado la #guitarra al equipo #hifi #minicadena ? en Aberdeen, Washington https://t.co/hg7TaeZt3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ranchwilder86 Butcher block tried to shush the back bar while we were at diner and they responded with a very loud… https://t.co/YNyxioQRqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got too cocky thinking the weather would be perfect in SD so I didnt bring a jacket. I check the weather app and its pouring tomorrow 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dickfundy I wish I was in the room when this scene was pitched to the Jolly Rancher heads.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Please make the news, please make the news, please make the news! 🙏🏽🙏🏽🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Blavity This is what those in power try to provoke that children of color are only successful if they cheat not be… https://t.co/krpBlZfj3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my hair cut today and my mom told me I look like Sebastian from cruel intentions... I’ll take it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouiseCarduner In my heavy clay soil dry band is most efficient and proven for corn growing. I do not plan on usin… https://t.co/oChn2moiHe]]></document><document><![CDATA[!!!!!!!BE AWARE PAY ATTENTION TO WHAT YOUR KIDS ARE WATCHING!!!!!!!!! @ Lynn, Massachusetts https://t.co/dSGdX33odY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Class of 2020’ DB  Sean Fresch Jr. follow him at YoungFresch21 @YoungFresch21 @ASUCoachTW @CoachPopovich… https://t.co/wKl4XdiB6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1: I have accepted a challenge from @CoachB_Sprints to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no revie… https://t.co/m13FUvNqgM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in traffic and looked over, this lady had half of her finger in her damn nose 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[haha my friend group just discovered that Kevin Jonas’s first name is Paul and you can only imagine the havoc.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrisonBeeby @FEAS_Panthers @upnorthlive @LourinOnTV @CumlerHannah Didn’t get to that one.  Glad @upnorthlive was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Norm__Pelletier @noszyy @mwoodski Pretty sure you were waiting for me the second my wheels hit the grass off the t… https://t.co/y3yj0aAjK5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The NFL should require at least one FTM transgender per team. So should the NHL, MLB, NBA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDickCavett Some years ago, a Trump-like businessman in NYC said, "I'm no intellectual; I operate by my gut and… https://t.co/mlA4D6prms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t usually comment on media outlets because they’re all stupid but this is a bit beyond the pale intellectuall… https://t.co/tOW61k4069]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegas early morning is pretty cool. Watching the sunrise over this crazy busy city https://t.co/qHtJzJC05X]]></document><document><![CDATA[😲 LB on the #VoiceBlinds I’m calling it. He will at least make the finals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WisConsensus @WiscoPotitics Yeah me myself I don't see why cannabis cannot be cheaper than tobacco it don't have a… https://t.co/VjDkrSXOej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hats off to @jilldevries who runs a heck of an athletic program at Valley City State]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Paltz played aggressive defense  to hang tough. Should be a good second half! #mesports #goubears #d3hoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Felt like @eagles hockey from the last two seasons. Fun stuff https://t.co/oZPlhQMfoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[God bless Lara Logan for her honesty and sincerity and true love for truth and justice.   What a wonderful person with integrity and beauty!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny "Breaking Bad" Memes (27 pics) - Picture #21 - https://t.co/OoqjCTdMgD #hilarity #laugh #smile #funny https://t.co/jqyHLekzwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Gym, simple rule in life. When you see young men being sexually assaulted you do something besides watc… https://t.co/qzHBPyfJnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bossassRN No way. You took the time to send me(a person you don't know) info upon request. That tells me you're pretty f'n awesome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes good things just happen. #goodthings #kindness #pride #people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally feel as if I have finished adjusting into life here in Ohio... tonight I was recognized as a frequent cus… https://t.co/nKvtplVIoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW55 @ESPNMcGee @KyleBusch He is a great driver no doubt. But many other great drivers don’t have that many wins,w… https://t.co/DreR7bxPyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball: Final Pre-Season Practice footage https://t.co/0LfthWIUiR via @YouTube @LionUpBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got so bored looking at my phone I reached into my pocket to pull out my phone]]></document></documents></author>