<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you are scared of the outcome.  If you didn’t want to get out of bed.  If you were worried about what they’d say… https://t.co/3V15ls5wVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodnessBeauty @Downeyangel @janismcdonald_ @ladylafaye56 @MSF_USA Oh just f*ck off. You have no right to force yo… https://t.co/i5J18njnxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only people who appreciate life and flavor will understand how excited i am about my dinner tonight! :)… https://t.co/8b7Rt9tUQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 years already since my favourite aunt decided to leave us...if you need help, seek it. On pense encore à toi mat… https://t.co/SBZhisKZJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I legit don’t even care what happens for the rest of the day. The Jonas Brothers are back baby!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[will never fw you again  though gave you one to many chances to fuck over me stupid tahaha .. - to dat nigga lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS MAN-BOY IS ONLY 7 MONTHS OLDER THAN ME BUT IDC HE'S STILL A PRECIOUS GIANT BABY WHO WE SHOULD PROTECT AT ALL T… https://t.co/6yfX2o99dT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MarsHSHoops 🏀 for the opportunity to sit on the bench!  Had such a great time at the Pitt vs Notre Dame… https://t.co/T153HGrjkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Airport lighting is not flattering. #GoodMorningAmerica everyone! https://t.co/dLmp7L0V7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuppyNumber7 Hello Thomas    If you and Nan need anything let me know.  We wants her to be as comfortable as possi… https://t.co/uTp2El7z3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SW_Messenger my daughter started Flashback this morning. It was a snow day for her. She finished it today and now… https://t.co/C2OOEuQED1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LWszola @alanna_smolarz D’awwww!! I LOVE the name Penny (I also love that both of you HAVE a dog named Penny!)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great afternoon -   Welcome back Miss Bonnie!!! bonbononelove   #theysaidlifewouldbeboring #promisesdaily… https://t.co/rA5cYnGLOR]]></document><document><![CDATA[i just spent an hour writing out all 206 bones and their landmark.. rip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsarakaza @Samwyri I just imagined Jeff Bezos in a superhero Cape, as world vigilanti...killing corruption lead… https://t.co/kLzf5jEuLg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ngalindophoto @urbangorillas @wearegorillas @ladygorillas @digitalpoliticz @recapzine @BEACASSOMAG @ScumbMag 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to get to work and eat, ugh I’m so hungry it’s not even funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[This scene make my heart stop every single time still and if yours doesn't then we're not friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing but respect to @GayleKing for her strength and professionalism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjblakley @idehenje @hood_potus @CinquestMonet @PaIIahAbdul But nobody’s talking about natural bodies... they’re t… https://t.co/vLtOo1cVg2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JDOGGG_ LOLLLLLL bro you’re on the like other end of the city, it is on Decatur tho just like the south end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Manafort ripped off cleminick for 119 mil in 1999 2005 manafort said Russia could launder money thru his real estat… https://t.co/W0CCuZJg47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenLVick @aja1969 @HBStanko @ThunderMarg @louagb @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Prove it. Show me ONE source th… https://t.co/5ZPtTRv5E9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BachelorABC got me feeling ALL types of ways tonight 😭🥺😬😨 Definitely a finale worthy of two nights!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BiancaTylock @IFD_NEWS @DispatchDemon @IMPDnews @IFD_CHIEF @tomhanify @IAFF416 @IndianapolisEMS @FDIC @BobbyHalton… https://t.co/LD4Fsu4ZV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching all these snap memories from last years spring break is getting me so pumped! @tnknoeck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extraño a Bertha, Leslie, Estufa, Analore, Angie, Chori, Bernal, Piña, Ramirez, Piña y Dianis😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[The love in the room I just felt at Jellyrolls during Fantasmic is pretty much how I want my life to feel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amymaytrust @foodallergyuk @freefromfarm @GemmaEvans If you need any testimonials I have contacts for each and eve… https://t.co/46QJRrqRZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[every time i think about college i think about how much i’d love to go to binghamton university but they only have… https://t.co/ZiN3x6ZuPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom found a dog on Eastend between Chino Ave and Schaefer.  He/she looks like a chihuahua (no collar), very timi… https://t.co/CXHdYcscN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[On our way to Houston...We had to stop to see our favorite beaver! ⚽️♥️ https://t.co/h6rwufxy7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IKEAUSA @ToyotaFinancial @Aetna talk about #modernization customer requirements, integration and leading.… https://t.co/g51DcZTIa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isit time to be eating giant rainbow pizzas and drinking auntie Anne’s lemonade in LA yet? 🌈 🍕 🍋… https://t.co/asekA2zAtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[He redefines in every way what love is. She fell for him and hasn’t gotten up since.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the kinda stuff I love doing, what can I say...I’m a total goon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of people who send me snaps of them in Otis elevators kills me. Like ya we haven’t talked in years but t… https://t.co/64Zkz3h01A]]></document><document><![CDATA[all the time &amp; mfs swear something is wrong w me no just leave me alone.😭😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoreleeSiemens @deblindenas @MPCelina @ezralevant I don't .  Just the ones who are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope to see her and the @AppliedVRhealth team  at @virtualmedconf #VR #HITsm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our top priority to to teach our clients what their numbers mean and how to use them in making decisions to grow th… https://t.co/Y8twKKGYsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Rep. Gosar to Cohen. “ you are a pathological liar. “ with this too, yes this . “Liar , liar pants on fire.”@wbaltv11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cómo cuándo mí sexto sentido no me falla 🙊 sabía que Jarabo venía para acá USA 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i am in any given situation, i must ask myself: am i operating from my lower self (my ego, acting without… https://t.co/lFPebWe55w]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my friends think I be saying hella outta pocket shit and I— https://t.co/DL6wk4o7KO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kicranston @JayDesh93 @HuffPostPol At one time, both my sister and her husband were actively involved in the Dem.… https://t.co/6osOff64hE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deep cleaning leads to profound realization #loveacleanspace #lovenewbegannings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started wearing glasses a year and a half ago and I’m still really pissed about it https://t.co/Sa4QMsjTen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RNRKentucky @Boyd_2650 @RandPaul @tedcruz @POTUS Next election, all 10 get tossed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at our PTA meeting we were presented our first donation from @EDFirstFund Thank you for partnering with Gre… https://t.co/tnFwEc2e6v]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best things come in sparkly cowboy hats and Bud Light t-shirts   @paulina_las  @HopeNesbitt92 https://t.co/IniYohXJxN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrSpringer12301 @MsMarino_SMSD @mrssmith4en @_MerriamPark Dustin I would love to do a book study with people acros… https://t.co/03osiveLNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Understand what guns have done to our communities. This is my counterpart in Arkansas. ESCUCHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djkhaled @Kehlani Please do a song together for #fatherofasahd 😀 https://t.co/G14FQnLnAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the South Bay to the Valley From the West Side to the East Side Everybody's very happy 'Cause the sun is shini… https://t.co/zRIJXbRzv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ppl bitch when they spell your name wrong at Starbucks this guy at zaxbys dead ass thought I said my name was kiwi… https://t.co/Faflg3FazB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please investigate and prosecute the real criminals. America deserves to see justice. Out of control]]></document><document><![CDATA[paul klein's genius interview was amazing,, he's an actual lyrical... genius lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattHolihan @lizziellen Men in Tights is second. All other Robin Hoods not worth ranking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chip and Joanna Gaines Debuted a Bunch of New Dishes at Their Restaurant and We’re Already Hungry https://t.co/niUPcRHVv7 via @people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just played 3 games to 25 then demolished a number 2 @Whataburger #Balance #SoGood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heard it’s snow back home. The sunset on Coronado is pretty spectacular. #visitSD #sandiego #CAwx #sunset… https://t.co/u6PxXXYTd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamlevine #VoicePremiere you are awesome Adam hope you have a great season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couldn't sleep so here I am experimenting. Keto breakfast is served. Blueberry pancakes, sausage pancake pops, and… https://t.co/WVoPlRnMFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day!!! @ Bala Cynwyd, Pennsylvania https://t.co/ShsaCsjiQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tengo ganas de comer pizza pero no se a donde pedir como pedir y que pizza pedir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Police tell @KDKA that the victim, William Worry III, was carrying a Barbie Dream House through the front door when… https://t.co/w93QME4QMM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Una vez me dijeron:  "No pierdes nada. Total, el NO ya lo tienes ganado".  Y creo que ese fue el inicio de todo el cambio...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_M_Roth @adovadotchka Ok, but the key difference is that Telemachus is the WORST and you don’t want a son like that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet my Date for this weekend and Copernic Space, Lady Rocket Foundation And California Space Center have its momen… https://t.co/j1jHwGAhaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Battle of Scarif (RO)  2. Battle of Naboo (TPM) 3. Battle of Coruscant (ROTS)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardRSmithJr @JesseKellyDC @TwitchyTeam @LarryOConnor Actually that was my reaction when he said it's like a gu… https://t.co/xViNZJHSYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom drives me absolutely insane, but I love that lady more than anything ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH at SXSW: “don’t let the darkness blind you from the freebies”   i’ve been here for like 5 minutes ... 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you love when you get under someone’s skin so much they start acting stupid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our public dollars are fueling the worst humanitarian crisis on the globe. It's up to us to stop it. Urge Congress… https://t.co/MqPCVk0I02]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think she should stay the F away from them. It would be disingenuous of her to do anything of the kind!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qp que vienen bien arregladas jaja muy a huevo me dio tiempo de ponerme tenis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today must be National get behind people who can’t drive day. https://t.co/IGu3m8DiIa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC @JoeM_136 He was a little off in the beginning. NOT a singer. Totally okay though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrMAGA45 Praying Medic said it was legit. Pamphlet and Radix did a chapter for free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeavenzHalo30 Every spirit of oppression and fear l command you to loose her life in Jesus name. Father I ask for… https://t.co/U8b2ECXhZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What time does the camping store open and where is it located? @amsupdates]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shut up #WorstPresidentEver  Why bother? You're worthless! This white house is worthless. It's hard to come to grip… https://t.co/4ViotAFt6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodNetwork @duffgoldman Very deserved win.  I might be an episode behind not sure since I DVR it.  But I knew the… https://t.co/XYSPxPR02i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Activewear Orange Tank Top Manufacturers https://t.co/WQJ1IeGnP1 #activewear #apparel #clothing #wholesaleclothing… https://t.co/efQ8ph3x65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaydenPay1 @Jordanwelker25 Any specific needs restrictions or breed that you want?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChickfilA on Dublin in C/S, CO. Who makes y'all's tea? Seriously, it has always tasted watered down. Yes, I have h… https://t.co/O5OdjpCoOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Sweetland Chocolates and Coffee in Rockford, MI https://t.co/bWUhISFsNi]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Lansing, MI, check out this job: https://t.co/eIsgXFzGjh #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well you succeeded because flat-earthers are obviously idiots morons or imbeciles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thirst4dodgers I’ve never had measles as a child and I do not know of anyone that has. Now chickenpox is another story. But measles, NOPE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress @Liz_Cheney This is ridiculous to put all democrats into one container and use words to change messag… https://t.co/iBg0gMUKnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂😂 watching Black Books for the 3rd time. 😂❤️ Why did this show ever end? #BERNARDBLACK❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry I give you a lot of credit. It’s been really difficult for me to have any relationships with Democrats f… https://t.co/ToUAK9J8Zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GalindesPepe Are things really that bad in Venezuela? Just curious I don’t trust this administration. Especially w… https://t.co/GWf5B6RztU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WesLinda @askwpgirl @Kathy_Darling @companyofone Thanks! I do that with Suntrust as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I wish I had right now 1. A phone charger.                2. Snacks.                                       3… https://t.co/RphyIzeWFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[On a side note: I’m okay. Just need some time to process my emotions and adjust. Thank you for everyone who is chec… https://t.co/7pCW5vaioB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave the young lady alone with your hate of Muslims. You and Trump must be removed now]]></document></documents></author>