<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Omgggggggg. I’m so obsessed. #vegetarian #thali #indian #houston #maharajabhog maharajabhogtx @ Maharaja Bhog https://t.co/MpiUzwBJQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[May faith be the torch that illuminates, animates and sustains you, so that all your actions and sufferings may be… https://t.co/pz2RP0foz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Essa hora da manhã e eu conversando sobre college com o guri da minha portaria]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT Please: I’m proud to be serving on the Leadership and People committee. There are so many of you that I want to… https://t.co/OwfL3kxisI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic dinner to mark the end of this year’s Wine Writers Symposium. Deeply humbling and inspiring to participate—tha… https://t.co/gftI0Rf7rl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tacobell please tell me what I’m paying for because this ain’t it. https://t.co/Mn4v1PAyGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Championship game day!! Come out and support @REDSTEM_Magnet stingers as we compete against Valley West for 1st pla… https://t.co/aZYSLPdoZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WKQualls Jackson Galaxy has great advice and herbal sprays/essences that may help with anxiety. I’ve also heard fe… https://t.co/wkRDCd9fZ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I'm just gonna take a tab of this eye glitter and see how it looks   Ten minutes later, my apartment: https://t.co/6BxdRg15Vh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexMcDaniel @itsmelissabrown @MGMAdvertiser The conspiracy theories are like... I heard ridiculous shit when I wa… https://t.co/T4vjaZvUcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys my favorite part of the Oscars is watching you all be mad at the Oscars. #IMeanIt #ShineOn]]></document><document><![CDATA[All y’all care about is Twerking and showing off your body. It’s pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your life can't fall apart if you never had it together!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could say it was a fun practice round at the @SiGChamp ... gotta say I couldn’t give up any shots, as my match… https://t.co/clhkUd1rJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CandeGdl @KVajpayaee @Toda1VidaJuntos @MSpadine @BreakingKind @Edward733 @Carinalt_kaka @MikiMiyazaki13… https://t.co/nlrW9Q7OUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samitw33theart I mean if you wanna hangout and burn some crayons I’m down]]></document><document><![CDATA[My thought process is actually WYDD, what would David do.. @SchittsCreek]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many a tears have to drop written by Vice President Charles Gates Dawes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news4buffalo OMG, can't you find something really important to do with your time, NY is a mess financially and you… https://t.co/wl4JSujAD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[We out here in representing for Torie Lee with her wonderfully wreath at a pop up event. @ Donaldsonville, Louisiana https://t.co/j5toWDAzAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being someones choice of drunk text makes me so happy. Drunk words are sober thoughts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shed you not, this hebi-hitter is hissterical! (And deserving of 3 puns!) 🐍 The one and only @VoiceOfVegeta]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤦‍♀️🤦‍♀️I can't believe she even got them shorts on......Lawd help me!!!!!!!😂😂😂😂 @ dept of homeland security/tsa iah https://t.co/F2CnzaQsti]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also I will never ever compliment a guys appearance ever. If I tell you that you’re handsome or something that’s a BIG deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The line here is ridiculous. 11 mins so far and still about 10 people in front of me. All because I need a cat umbr… https://t.co/S2dbumB074]]></document><document><![CDATA[The amount of people that stopped and talked to me yesterday was unbelievable]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyBirthdayJHope @BTS_twt  #SunshineHobiDay #OurPieceofPeace #HappyJhopeDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaibiscuit12 @AshMcMichael @Flipgrid @DenboSchool https://t.co/92xueujhzA Thank you so much 📚❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[✨✨BOGO SALE!!💰$200 worth of wraps for just $59!💰😍 I am opening up FIVE spots for product testers 😍 😻 BUY ONE GET ON… https://t.co/h7gFKpftXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaymee Girl, how did either one of those things crack your tooth?! I once cracked my brand new crown, a week after… https://t.co/7VNH3yQbpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#quake predictions, https://t.co/RqBRl60J9J Via @TheRealS0s up to 3.14.19 M5 – M9  Radius: 200km,  Locations: Hsinc… https://t.co/9Wwi8K4Hxu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hadenbandlife What a privilege it was to be there to watch them today. SO proud and excited for you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jrue Holiday said “I’m a Nadal fan,” so by default I’m now a Holiday fan https://t.co/HPDSA6Whcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sis, not enough opinions like this on this situation lol. It was feeling like I was the only one]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alyssasconzo5 @SHAQ @aaroncarter You should have busted it out. It was good back in the 4th grade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way dude. But I do open every drawer in hopes that someone left behind a million dollars.. and all I find is a B… https://t.co/xmMQP5YOtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CapotostoKelly Can you please Retweet Donate, we need help his meds cost slot and so does the dr was denied for di… https://t.co/y1K8OYoh2L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!!! @kayla_manney miss you so so much pretty!! can’t wait for our annual tradition #CowDay 😋😁 https://t.co/GXHxt2uv9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta start looking for a new place this morning....I’m tired from working, but these bill dueeeee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got into an argument with someone &amp; accidentally deleted years worth of texts with them whoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. It's hella loud IRL. #CommunityPolicing #FuturePoliceOfficer #FamilyDay #CommunityEngagement #MomLife… https://t.co/NU6psSTZYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman You mean kidnapped children. This agency becomes an accessory to kidnapping if this is true.… https://t.co/99n9lqpFQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday, 2/28, 9pm EST please join us for a LIVE STREAMING CONCERT — from your phone! computer! tablet! See you Th… https://t.co/WpllQpJiaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do not like Self standing right next to official as he reviews video.. #SicEm https://t.co/5jcNXZLWSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[PHOTO GALLERY: Meteorologist Karen Minton through the years: https://t.co/Tk3bUVW3E1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beautybackpckr Make sure you choose good socks. I would also take a couple of different thickness socks. I'm assum… https://t.co/HlKk1QIoZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle @TODAYshow Absolutely wonderful to see  both of enjoying International Women's Day Stephanie!!🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Sylivia’s served green beans from the can when I dined there🤮Fake soul food; perfect for those two who have no soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KISDHeatherB @lklempnauer1 @msZotos @MrsColemanELA @mary_lindinger @KleinISDRiley @CoachAtkins27 @aggielgh… https://t.co/GSewY74Ixg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to dedicate this very amazing video to specifically two of my exes, thank u~]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna say THANK YOU to every single person who wished me a happy birthday!! I had the absolute BEST DAY, okurrrrr… https://t.co/v8iJZEFcmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #internationalwomensday2019 it is worthwhile noting that although 142 countries have laws that provide for gende… https://t.co/l4QubAcZCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the day 7 book cover(s), I selected two related books. I met Erin Gruwell at a @DiscoveryEd fall conference in… https://t.co/osRNJ1phBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetOfSpirit_ @1barryatkinson would be a far better president than the current occupant of the Oval Office.   We… https://t.co/iNHR6FG0Nc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bourbon Street / French Quarter https://t.co/Wt7MDj2ZHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BullsNation  @shaqharrison_11 @ChanHutch15 chicagobulls  🏀  #RunWithUs 🐂 #ChicagoBulls dpaxson5 @princesskk1210 @… https://t.co/ROfMFygrYD]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Operations Clerk 2" sound appealing to you, follow us to hear about these types of opport… https://t.co/srjFBvgppU]]></document><document><![CDATA[a little @timbersfc pre-game from afar. #RCTID #COLvPOR #MLS @ Winter Park, Florida https://t.co/fpcN7rAheH]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know shits about to hit the fan when hhh wears his leather jacket lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next hour on #SaturdayAM:   Police are searching this morning for a shooter they say opened fired and killed a man… https://t.co/Ripn4MirqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s still not too late.  PEACE AND BLESSINGS @ Central Indianapolis, Indianapolis, Indiana https://t.co/mG0xiuR3Qo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soy muy fan, la disciplina también es belleza @katelyn_ohashi gimnasta de 10 https://t.co/lw41yHF41h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would you take advice on how to kill your husband from your "INMATE" boyfriend?? Clearly he is not good at getting away with crimes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FunkyPhantum @Gazwilson041981 @DailyMail @MailOnline Yessss!!!! https://t.co/cpOLSPBfqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juddthestud_ I cried a little when I saw their tour dates I wanna go 😂😭😭 https://t.co/p3AXrmcC4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ow this is the inspirational comeback I needed right now | Bald baby penguin abandoned by parents: https://t.co/mQckI9fyhF # via @AOLdotUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValJ72 @willmenaker Dare and dare again, stop the murderous bs in its tracks]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 One of these things is not like the others  One of these things doesn’t belong🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciamalone You rocked it Alicia!  You should be very proud of yourself!  I was proud of you 🙏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽👏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[fell in love with these guys last night @TheNudeParty   https://t.co/6GetuLOuyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[That tiny vein life... 😝 #NoFilter #Ouch @ Kaiser Permanente Point West https://t.co/fu2yXxgXyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACMawards @coleswindell @ChrisStapleton @BebeRexha @FLAGALine @KaceyMusgraves @DanAndShay @russelled @THubbmusic… https://t.co/a81O6Q3kuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You didn’t comment when you heard it was two #MAGA supporters who carried the atta… https://t.co/oYs1Un1vUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrNickOFMConv Be safe! Your Guardian Angel will be with you! We will be praying for you! 🙏✝️😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaybennz How hard did you lie to Reg about who they actually were, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY 💦 What’s working with a personal trainer like? I did the research and spilled the beans on the blog today.… https://t.co/cGPIChLD4z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BravoAndy Mexican dynasties  is everything Bravo was missing.  Obsessed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anildash I'd like to start with a wifi signal that makes it to every room in my house (and no it isn't just buying… https://t.co/Jw5bQy68nu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elena_elinka @crazymom50 @ldavisusa @JenYeager6 @twdandmetal @Merve_TWD @justmel_li @emikoko896 @sparkle4meplz… https://t.co/CwDlgcO0iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worked Apple Retail in college and then I worked for minimum wage as a secretary at a fabric company that would c… https://t.co/jGfwNagln3]]></document><document><![CDATA[KellyAnn Conway and Sarah Sanders will go down in history as the worst women that supported a pathological liar and… https://t.co/gxPjLdiGQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexieecarbone @josieeeleigh Currently no one.  I'm sadly only speaking of with my exes. Sorry to disappoint.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialMonstaX BITCH YEEEEEEEEEEESSS YOU ALREADY KNOOOOW https://t.co/Sosak3ozXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up to knocking on my bathroom door (there is no one else here) at 3:33 am. Tell me I’m not haunted. I dare you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently Ariana Grande was within walking distance of me today but I was at work so me and the universe need to have a little talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The imbalance of justice in our country grows wider and deeper every year. How to combat this? That is the question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[literally no one:  any guy who sees me: damn is she a ps4 cuz I’m finna play dat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rise and Shine. 💅 Blasting @theestallion this morning because  #InternationalWomensDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennifer_Lugar @MomsDemand Thank you! You took your pain and channeled it positively. God Bless.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubianesJose @NBCNews I read there in Saudi Arabia Hmmm wonder what that could be all about?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A smooth ride or an adventurous journey on choppy waters, which one do you choose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Count down to spring!! Everything that’s left must go!  We are open. 12:30-5:30 today!  #ootd#boutique#shop#sale#st… https://t.co/9qSQB6TnGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWrightPhysio @Retlouping @adamdobson123 @ashjamesphysio @AshisArmyPhysio @BillingMartin @CombatSportPhys I think… https://t.co/ci7EFmnV3P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janrobinjackson @simplyrebecca8 @glennkirschner2 @MSNBC @MSNBCPR It’s not about removing him. It’s about the long… https://t.co/uqkUuJukZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get to train the new girl but want to go home after your 12 hr shift🤗 #Idontmind #WednesdayMorning Missing my 🛏🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bed at @GaylordOpryland is so comfy, I don't even mind that I woke up 2 hours before my alarm. That just means I… https://t.co/MavVeGX0TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy tratando de ocultarlo  Que no puedo controlarlo  Me controla y no me deja ver  Lo simple que puede ser… 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJuanVargas Israel is fine. It’s their government’s human rights violations that we’re all complaining about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometime I'm glad we live so far from anyone we know.  No drop ins!!!! Makes life quieter and less stressful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notbencarter Apparently it is more flexible than the people putting the stickers on knew....]]></document></documents></author>