<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Who'd like a nice, long #SundayBunday nap with the handsome @KristoferWeston? 💜💜 https://t.co/BHlqs75qLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan is a RACIST!  @RepEliotEngel  @RepJerryNadler @SpeakerPelosi  is @Ilhan going to be removed from Congress by… https://t.co/GHYlqlfJVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been doing a lot of praying lately for a lot of people, praying for health, jobs, prosperity, peace, life, mos… https://t.co/UiToMN9SQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just saw a snippet of the upcoming Deadwood movie in @HBO’s previews for the year and I might have squealed audibly at the sight. #itsreal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChazCasual I dig it! Miss working next to ya too #squad #LoveWhereYouWorked]]></document><document><![CDATA[First annual CANADA Trade Link International Women’s Day Event - a truly inspiring breakfast event!… https://t.co/wbTfAEpSFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[All jokes aside, y’all are coming after jordyn but y’all having friends who are doing the same shit and are okay with it. 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ok that you don’t understand, God knows! #Faithful #TrustTheProcess #BeBrave #ChooseWisely #ThankYouJesus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secretstranger9 @DoingRight1 If Harry wants his daughter to be a boy; go ahead... strange for a Prince...]]></document><document><![CDATA[this picture makes me giggle uncontrollably ... hahahahaha #humor #chuckle #smile #comic https://t.co/2LTWoLhdjf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love seeing people from the back rows win, and feeling that the award is so awkwardly new receiving it. #Oscars #underdog]]></document><document><![CDATA[YBe - Rumor In The Streets (Ft. Smilone &amp; Slowpoke) (With Lyrics On Screen) https://t.co/xkJpl57baZ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me [thoroughly], O God, and know my heart; Test me and know my anxious thoughts; And … https://t.co/QOwXgXukVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Worldwide GIVEAWAY! Enter for a chance to win this ORIGIN PC RTS NEURON w/ Pewdiepie! https://t.co/elslZWqNt1  #Sweepstakes #Giveaway]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins @SenatorTomUdall @lisamurkowski @SenatorShaheen Eff you, Susan, days are numbered. Bye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyKStewart @sherrilee7 There are no words for this. Not illegal fighting cancer and this. You know losing more… https://t.co/kWQSazYxZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @CorrineDodge I’ve had it with these clowns. Who is it and let’s get that person out. This is the USA… https://t.co/nDKDr9MMsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its a beautiful day to testify and let our legislator know the #STAAR does not show or value what teachers do in th… https://t.co/warZn91p3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eddieristo1 @AOC @saikatc @johniadarola @cenkuygur @AnaKasparian Maybe this will help you get through the breadlines faster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in History  February 18th 1929: First Academy Awards announced The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Science… https://t.co/fH0FuVkvJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Ok...nice try tho. I got my popcorn when it's your turn..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrismPalsDM Astrid whining to the God of the Moon upon seeing Defiance: why don’t I HAVE A DRAGON BROTHER?!??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good afternoon from your friendly neighborhood satanist https://t.co/0lTlfatCid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stone Tropic of Thunder cans now available. https://t.co/xOyQgPHDwb @StoneBrewingCo #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers for the safety of my family would be greatly appreciated right now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Study suggests humor could be an emotion regulation strategy for depression https://t.co/IvEwRhv0v8 via @PsyPost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you voyagedallas for featuring me and for including me in Arlington’s Rising Stars. Moving to Dallas was one… https://t.co/hyYzm5OPyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TabariWallace @NC_Governor Thank you again for joining us! You had our #SoaringEagles in the palm of your hand! He… https://t.co/HgxsIROCwJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BEST part of being a school administrator are the “other duties as assigned.” So proud of my job and school. https://t.co/8AazgKWZiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man + Po Boy Factory = perfect start to my birthday weekend! #hesthegift #lovethisman❤️ #lovemesomeshrimp🍤… https://t.co/yhY8UjFQI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asquerosa! Te veré corriendo como cucaracha. Ladrona, mal nacida... la justicia humana y divina caerán sobre ti.]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Maestro " ERNESTO PINEDA" en escena @the hottest place Guadalupe 10pm#freevaletparking🚘#ernestopineda #theplacet… https://t.co/36YKNRGHyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else is crying listening to Chris Cornell? Just me...oh. Go figure. Literally no one sings like he did. We lost… https://t.co/RHuTdzAEqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my friend to wake me up in 10. Minutes. So I can do homework...... why is it now 2:22am. Which is 5 hours pa… https://t.co/KW66BE8vM6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitchjccaylen Ugh I might miss the whole stream now ... oh well will still try to catch it! Hope everyone has an awesome night👍🏻💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett You started it all, there is no one to blame but you an your deplorable base]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then they'll  probably have a cocktail and go on with their worthless lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Desolation by Tremonti on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/Obz0clauyP https://t.co/6KcqBbwZFp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love that Nick is binge watching #glee and that the Creator of the show based the high school on Carmel!    Good lu… https://t.co/QzIrlaMzcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barelyliterate I think it’s a Canadian thing cause I was confused when I moved from PA to ON. Canadians would call… https://t.co/GFkuVomZFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheChrisDuarte @trailhead @cloudysan @swbjoyce @adamse @jimsinai It must be amazing to see how your child has grow… https://t.co/kCUgGFYfpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's hilarious. #hilarity #lol #smile #playful https://t.co/XJXtddgJqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any medical test that requires you to get up at 6:45 in the morning is evil. I’m so tired my arms hurt and my finge… https://t.co/3cdHWEBek0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timiamonet Cause he was lowkey already up but Kardashian’s do bring fame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peaceful desert run. Always so beautiful. #run #8miler #runner #Scottsdale #Arizona 🌵🌴 https://t.co/5GjqkSsigQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, join the #sangha at #bhaktiyogashala for #manta #medicine with #johannabeekmanmusic #dcstringer #jossjaffe… https://t.co/2Xi5SNyJ2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcal4HIM @JesusIsGod34 @2Samuel2222 @pj_hurt @Jetsta812 @PaulieD55 @Renatab55 @WTWTA63 @DianeHelp4pets… https://t.co/2uS4kLdhPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[To listen to me legit try for this song please listen to the cover over here~! 😎✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Demarcowinning @NeNeLeakes she did. she pulled her belt and this is why they didnt discuss it nor show it. they tr… https://t.co/NXXggMLvzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar Well he is a Narcissist and cant read above a 2nd grade level( constitution).]]></document><document><![CDATA[✍🏽 My love letter to the Women of Peloton: ✍🏽  Together, the women of Peloton flourish, conquer, and electrify. The… https://t.co/55B7GqH6cq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump let that sink in to all those 65 and older who are receiving MEDICARE bene… https://t.co/dMlsAf3hx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really gonna be out here giving a presentation in front of 600 people about mental health and my personal exper… https://t.co/e2mDPheW4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zacjanderson In your interesting Sarasota ACLU piece, you mentioned Gainesville w/regard to the Move the Date ball… https://t.co/3eAbRdEoX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 4th year students are amazing #proudtobeLBUSD https://t.co/zopAPJCF4t]]></document><document><![CDATA[BookShare @Miller12Shannon Challenged to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations, no reviews - just the cove… https://t.co/AAu6rkWL5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll get 3 steps forward with a guy then 7steps back... they never learn]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAGED HOMES • Staged To SELL • • • • #stagedhomes #stagedhome #styledhome #stagedesign #staged #homestaging… https://t.co/FCfFOS91Q3]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #warm moment of #calm before the coming #storm 🌅🌬🌊🌤🌥🌦 #floridalife #North Florida #Florida #weather @ Jacksonvill… https://t.co/JroKUP8wZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[People passed out and playing music and smoking on light rail train.... Thanks @MetroTransitMN ... I smell like a c… https://t.co/UMEpSScvfK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Free gift with purchase. Spend 3859027$ and get an itsy bitsy tiny mini sample for free. 🙄🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oonkeeta26 Barnum (one-way asymmetrical model) gains profits by hiring PR agents and making huge posters. Bernays… https://t.co/aJi0KNubz8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone say a quick prayer for @willcharper as we drive back to cypress later and he sits through 5 hours of old J… https://t.co/D3jBV5QpFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just teared up at an instrumental one direction song so my period is closer than I thought]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCIENCE PATTERNS AND CYCLES IN NATURE...✅ #3.11  #formativeassessment @quizizz #quizizz @scienceCCPS https://t.co/b6mQh7kHEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Road trip pit stop #jelloshotbreak next stop Washington coast and Seabrook #girlsweekend Oc @ McCleary, Washington https://t.co/cn4BioEAvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #Barnstable, MA! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Temporary Retail Team Mem… https://t.co/eg8U1IKeF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyWebbArt1 @senatemajldr McConnel is a dangerous traitor to this country...has been for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTRTRS Our Iconic heritage site #GolcondaFort. The heritage facelift can help more visitors. Golconda fort site se… https://t.co/56v3ztLxCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume I don’t worry about not enough people read my tweets for me to cause a social change]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PackagedLight It was a honey butter chicken biscuit from @Whataburger who wouldn’t drool over that?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr you know what your polls are very low you support a fraud man and  corruption administration]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WigtonRobert It’s unbelievable that he’s that stupid. So busy talking 💩 instead of looking ahead.… https://t.co/purMw057Za]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coldplay - Princess Of China ft. Rihanna https://t.co/ORGjly0OPs via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you veronnate  and the entire sysdschools for their recognition in fattonyprints  Victor Lopez elpollogrillbo… https://t.co/dLAEzDtXZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's budget heads for Congress with huge cuts to food, housing, and health—and a $174B slush fund  https://t.co/mkT5XcSPOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing @Skype with @CressidaCowell.  #FullerMeadow 2nd graders in @Mrslkennedy2, @mrsmulligangr2, @mrslevangie,… https://t.co/XZfzoDcOok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@williamlegate @realDonaldTrump All you have to do is listen to Trump speak to know that he is totally ignorant.  W… https://t.co/b1SheJEQV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gates and chains. #onlyinSF #sanfrancisco #goldengatebridge #coldAF #nofilter @ Golden Gate Bridge https://t.co/7qOokX5UXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting my good friend and fellow public servant, the great Assemblywoman from the 35th Legislative District Sha… https://t.co/0aR3nvUea1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h0t_p0ppy From LindseyFrank- “Their TopGen website is shutdown, however I found the name of the other executives a… https://t.co/OpKB7fXIeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never questioned it...NEVER in the last 3 years. Y’all just weak 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @Cressy777Jeri I'm very glad she is ineligible to run for president. It should also make her ineligible for Speaker position.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walked into Urban Outfitters for the first time and saw their "retro" clothes, similar to the ones that I actually… https://t.co/jrDI6rROkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMobile @SamsungMobileUS Samsung is the best phone I've had and I'm still on a Galaxy 7 ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking @CAMathCouncil Central Symposium at @ucmerced with @gfletchy! #CMCMath https://t.co/jrusRsZHJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rental car does not have seat warmers. It's 32. #newrequirement #firstworldproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSnook12 It’s a consequence that comes with having the circulation of an old person 😂🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[You couldn’t pay me to ever fw a hoe my nigga ever had dealings with ‼️PERIODTT 🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[REPORT: ICE arrests millionaire fugitives from Ecuador who donated to tens of thousands to Obama https://t.co/oMCFe7j12n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gisellevalenz speaking the truth about #payequality and how to get a salary worthy of your worth.   #AustinAnitaB… https://t.co/yI7V82USdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reader Question: Abbey Renovations @ThisIsWeHo https://t.co/fQMvvHtGXW https://t.co/etA91tYgxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueTrader84 It would also help if I would edit my tweets. Like EVER. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FORGOT TO UPDATE THIS!!! so I went back upstairs to get my clothes. as I got on the elevator to go up there was t… https://t.co/6mmKkGFu3N]]></document><document><![CDATA[6am and I’m fucking hyped !! Let’s go! #RaiderNation is BOOMIN!!! @AB84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day! May your home always be filled with love. 🏡❤️ Bonne St-Valentin! Que votre maison soit toujo… https://t.co/jGBdxijXML]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nativeesoul @DeeviousDenise One of the purest loves one can witness... the way my Carley searched for my Mama when… https://t.co/WOEUnVdXYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome work!!! James Martin Middle School is still waiting on that call! We are cougars too! #cougarpride… https://t.co/IKFG7gryTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[One picture, 20 takes, both post 19.1, with 2 kiddos there cheering on their parents — priceless and hilarious. Gre… https://t.co/aUyAT7B1Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 30% of you who voted LeeAnne are buggin. Queens @stephhollman @BrandiRedmond &amp; @dandrasimmons all the way 👑👑👑]]></document></documents></author>