<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[baby girl was getting some sun today!! @ Smith’s Farm https://t.co/6Gx9VFDnG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[STING!! IT'S STING!!!!!!!!!!!!!  THAT'S STING. AND IT'S NOT A PICTURE OF STING #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an honour to be Coaching against you @AmyfStuart Congrats on a successful Season and Good Luck in the Playoffs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you do any extra today? #gym #gymshark #gymmotivation #fit #fitnessmotivation #fitness #fitfam #awesome #bulk… https://t.co/l6jiZTyCk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shelton ends Louisa drought with a short jumper in the lane.  Louisa takes a timeout, trailing GW 43-34 with 3:28 remaining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An Intelligence Squared #debate: We should subsidize preschool.  A one-on-one debate, with IBM's Artificial Intelli… https://t.co/LTTJO1tb53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitney_shank Les Snead is an active guy. Then you insert new coach/systems &amp; that brings about player movement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackAftaThis Old Yankee Stadium. Although I haven’t been to enough to seriously compare. But I would say it would be hard to top]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loveGoldenHeart @AdamRogers2030 @dez_blanchfield @eldiablo0786 @Ceo_Branding @SuburbanMen @505Nomad @DioFavatas… https://t.co/hdEayVWzaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Lina4HC for organizing your Civic Saturday’s at our new @BakerRipley East Aldine Campus. Excellent oppor… https://t.co/KdH9Yik84E]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s @LawLakehead’s 2019 @OntarioTLA Cup Team: Alyssa Denley, Ryan Matson, Bryant Oakes, Justice Abrams, Sarah Nado… https://t.co/3P46VomTlS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @FiatChrysler_NA @michiganalumni https://t.co/C8LaWoHMLZ @ColgateCareers @CP_News @MI_ESGR… https://t.co/wXsglUU15l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBS12 HOW ABOUT THIS  STRAP HIM TOO  CAR AND DRAG HIM DOWN THE ROAD FOR A FEW MILES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory WTF is wrong with Louisiana politicians. Higgins, Kennedy bad examples for the rule of law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayGuest3 @DanMinkin1 @bollinger_david Nobody invited Minkin into this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenbergSez #CatsForGreenberg! Just ask Louie &amp; Scout, they’re with me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We coming for that Number 1 seed 👏🏽🔵⚪️🔵 #THEEiLove #Jackson_RYS19    #Jackson_RYS19  #Jackson_RYS19 #Jackson_RYS19… https://t.co/45P6E2pNTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger What lunatic fringe do you refer to? The strong of all Americans who support national health care, a… https://t.co/YlNl2bSBCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blackface, KKK hoods and mock lynchings: Review of 900 yearbooks finds blatant racism https://t.co/Mmo3lKp6wH via… https://t.co/0Ea2LJHSaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alpha_Grand @Ahmed_Alkhiary هو عشانه جاي من ينبع الي مافيها الا ستاربكس واحد فمش حاس بالفرق]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynn's Candle has produced The Minstrel In The Gallery. More Jethro Tull Please. My last Tull concert has this phot… https://t.co/LzmLXVFsE3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report of an intoxicated driver at a Burger King drive thru... I'm really not surprised.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrStahlerBC  to post covers of 7 books that I love.  No explanations, no reviews.  I’ll will c… https://t.co/WHDFUMCql8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@S_ATL_Wrestling @ApSnowball He likes to be the gatekeeper for news, and they basically reminded him that he's a do… https://t.co/vyTII1PeVD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just hate food prices at events?  Just went to Auto show in Toronto.  $7.75 for a hotdog, $18 for hamburg… https://t.co/Mo98BnS9EV]]></document><document><![CDATA[For My Beautiful Bestfriend @Angieebee__ God Loves you Your  Bestfriend loves You and your Bestfriends family alway… https://t.co/CxJupZhpBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNews Why oh WHY does Fox News continue to employ Geraldo Revera?? He is NOT an asset to you, I turn the channel… https://t.co/2s2KHguheJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suns_tutu_fan @brich44 I completely agree, but are the two mutually exclusive? You can add veteran pieces AND draf… https://t.co/8g5BUWKtzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[decisions that you make along the way to guide you in the right direction and push you forward. So appreciate the j… https://t.co/0IdweaFYMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also embarrassed bc I still know EVERY WORD to EVERY SONG that n any 1D album 😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[My name is Robert Kraft. My wife has passed away, I’m 77 years old. I had consensual sex with a young female- twice… https://t.co/zSYQMazl9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chet_Cannon why is she an embarrassment for calling out the criminal policys of isreal like the U.S., like philist… https://t.co/HzSoSwZdFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ordinarytallmom @janashortal You should really check out the Fort Collins, Colorado area.  I hear it's an amazing place to live... 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bagadeek @tinka_nichols @jasonburglar Baltimore home to weird goats https://t.co/9gXkdZW33M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Australia’s Senate has passed a bill banning cosmetic animal testing https://t.co/iCgeFmmeIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[si tuvieran la oportunidad de realizar una pregunta a algún misionero o misionera, cuál sería?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #JoyceStiverne is like watching someone hit the heavy bag in slow motion. And that’s what’s so dangerous f… https://t.co/jvEntUDjoZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savannahborn2 @conmomma the only on'es getting any play is those that benefit advertisers. the real people are suppressed badly!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brannonmc I’m not sure “guts” is the right word here... https://t.co/YmQ1YNdE2z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump partied at Mar-A-Lago with founder of Florida spa busted for human trafficking https://t.co/SJGWmyETDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you support armed teachers in the classroom? I voted Yes on WJAX. What's your vote? https://t.co/TYedcnRGqg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking: Emmy Awards, Colbert Get Massive Bad News After Award Show Turns Trump Hate Fest https://t.co/qYzj5LZbHq via @@conserv_tribune]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was said to me today by my former political science professor, mentor, and friend that we’re losing the republic… https://t.co/nW9BZWQFDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobgoff I love you! You’re posts really make me think and opens me up to what Holy Spirit wants to tell me. I appr… https://t.co/7qLaQdJqpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to put this back out there. There is zero correlation between the runtime of an Oscars ceremony and the r… https://t.co/75dE9hF5aK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an awesome moment with Niko driving home today. He turned off his phone and just listened to music with me. Doe… https://t.co/X5ztxg92z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good vibes only...#fridayjr  🔹 Snapchat📲 "kingfrost30" 🔹 #ChillyThoughts 🤔❄️💭 #chilly #ChillyVybz ❄️🌀 #king 👑… https://t.co/f6miPv7dkA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Now he is on to - trade deal with China and the billions and billions of dollars flowing into the Treasury]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glovingforbacon True. I switched out the halogens for LED last weekend so much better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skiptowne61 @FLMel69 @ProLifeTexanUSA @maxxx__power @MenaKyle @PrestonLane18 @heyk1967 @Zigurd @FifeTx @will10459… https://t.co/64xXc1zKRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eschwarzkopf We also have pothole season between now and then. I will be interested to see what people think in two months.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stayfrea_ Back always. They look at you sideways if you even try to open that passenger door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Liberty Twilight Capture ⠀ If you “Like” then “Comment” but “Follow” me on Instagram for a more unique and per… https://t.co/KLpQdmiS12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@junipermiilk My whole life. I doubt you will need surgery, my situation was a product of years of problems adding… https://t.co/MNlpV7xEab]]></document><document><![CDATA[my weekend. these brothers. this rock and roll..  #onlyincbus #atomicart03 https://t.co/p9WLHj8D0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PortChop305 @SamiXxx14 @Zaertlichkei @zankou89 @zacajavi11 @Happymodel2 @ngelLop06936892 @BLAYNQHUINNBRA… https://t.co/lMukTzOkzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe no Harper rumors unless coming from Rosenthal or Salisbury. #HarperWatch]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is so much wasted talent in this world, it’s sad to think about that #10xlife @grantcardone @JarrodGlandt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mad respect to @WayneLongSJ and @beynate for their principled votes on the NDP's motion calling for a juridical inq… https://t.co/qYzbtzl69A]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have got to consult my birth chart because (1) the imminent arrival of new Taylor music and (2) the announcement… https://t.co/IMLboZHe4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreakingNLive @MarieNoel45 Should be charged with manufacturing a hate crime. What a racist puke this guy is]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday March 5 - NBC Morning Rundown:    McConnell: 'There will be enough votes to pass the resolution of disappro… https://t.co/c8D3mHA1oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raleigh Egypt students speaking with TN State Senator Brian Kelsey #shelbystorm https://t.co/aw9epirSQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philorbanWSOC9 Should slipped the judges a bag. “Miles Bridges gets a 49 on his first dunk even though it didn’t go in!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @swosu and the refs on that win! @GACAthletics @SWOSUAthletics #WhatAShame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Toucherandrich when I hear @RochieWBZ it makes the  snow melt. I wish I loved anything that much. #steakandeggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson When you find out,tell us! I'm in Toronto. Why does President Dummyummy2x4 HATE us? Thought we were 'Friends'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't relate to @SingleParentsTV, but it's a nice show.  I quite enjoy it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning that we have unity in Christ using Legos...don’t you wish your church experience was like this? 😂 #legos… https://t.co/LdEk4CxE9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cobo_82 I can't imagine doing it long hand.  I would be in trouble without Quicken and Quickbooks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday sunrise. #oceangrovenj #sunrise #jerseyshore #itsabeautifulmorning #beachtown #february #wintersun… https://t.co/PWrrLOSU70]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theraghavbeat @ftweestu You hate Rakitic or is that the person who you think the majority of our fans hate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggreddslc thanks for the topps cubs set. You made my boys day. #gocubs]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s gonna be funny when we hear Brendan Rodgers telling us that Glentoran is his dream job and club lol. He’s gonn… https://t.co/H8wrffpTkg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halli - looking good with a great jeager. Huge step forward on her double layout. 9.825]]></document><document><![CDATA[With thanks to @annhandley of @MarketingProfs for highlighting this in her latest biweekly newsletter. Helpful!… https://t.co/bZX25tCQyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hdt_hugh I seriously can’t. I want someone to set it off and hack this bitch cuz it’s making everyone dumber for e… https://t.co/HGYvSI61Ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist My service in Toronto is thru Rogers-biggest in Canada-&amp; they are good but any week end the feed is slooooow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarinaHardy4 @ALFIEEP1 @jacabreracardio @crpisani @Dr_Santangeli @LuigiDiBiaseMD @adribaran @aalahmadmd… https://t.co/M6gyKmLV5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RT_Richardson @goekugolf @thewccpro @BestballCbd Happy Birthday RT, hope you got some fresh Js.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The second star to the right Shines in the night for you. To tell you that the dreams you plan Really can come tru… https://t.co/i5Jg7JQqLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RolandB3 Yeah.. Pac12 is an embarrassment for a P5 lol, they’re definitely worse than a few mid major conferences 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we’ve slept on Mary Poppin’s arm strength enough... honestly I’m sick of it.  She flew around gripped up on… https://t.co/mSW5nXEOBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @KurtWasilewski. Important insights on maximizing training events.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pull up at home and this truck pulls up next to me and I’m like was sup and this guy is like I got my eyes on you... bitchhhh wtf weirdo 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cooolllaazzoooo @KingLurchFit @mo_xdzn Legendary. I put it up there with the finale of dragon ball super]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @Walmart Supercenter in East Brunswick, NJ https://t.co/bjEgfISrke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisWGates Dick Blood would be more of a 90s gimmick than a 70s gimmick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boilers3212 @BoilerFanTalk @BSchmidt9 @ChrisForman12 @dewey_chris1 @mdavidbrown @CBBonFOX @HammerAndRails… https://t.co/3g4AKiEdD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do what you can, with what you have, where you are.  Theodore Roosevelt @ Swing State Strategies https://t.co/XcdCsjd2YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Managing other people, starts with managing *yourself* for effectiveness.  -Drucker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDom15104_ @Alyssa_Milano @PressSec @CNN I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Pre… https://t.co/MxnFCF1wX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USC1620 #DumbDebates Better drunk sports exec - Drunk Delany or Drunk Kraft? I’ve got to go with Delany now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Save the Tigers “ by Jake Henniger https://t.co/TJrQYabKch via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once we realize that Jesus has served us even to the depths of our meagerness, selfishness, and sin, nothing we enc… https://t.co/hauhfK9ftL]]></document><document><![CDATA[There no Connection than the #BossNHugConnection @SashaBanksWWE @itsBayleyWWE https://t.co/reIZe1imUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You moron, what evidence?Just saying there is evidence doesn’t make it so.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reggiewatts Might have been my favorite performance over the weekend. Absolutely threw downnn. #crssd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your world feels like it’s falling apart know that the reason will be revealed. Healing is possible.  There are… https://t.co/SOyq5U0TLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time with our special guests Dean DeBlois and Jay Baruchel for How To Train Your Dragon Hidden World… https://t.co/h2iBD4ZhVu]]></document></documents></author>