<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why Everyone Is Moving to Tampa Right Now (And You Might Want to Join Them) https://t.co/V6ktJWa6G2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agustinamcd @Obispo_Manuel @hectorlocutor @MayMartorelli Abrazo de luz 🙌🏼✨✨ https://t.co/RdPBE8RDN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always say I’m done listening to sad music, and then I go and listen to sad music. This is why I stay in my feelsss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Long story short, this man really got me in trouble (kinda ???) but then he sent me a whole ass friend request as i… https://t.co/zZU5pSFMRG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esglaude @Jim_Jordan He sounds deranged. He’d have to be to help cover up a sexual predator of teenage boys while a wrestling coach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna binge watch unauthorized living so bad but I gotta go to work tomorrow😭😭 it just keeps on getting better an… https://t.co/2IeRtGYXzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#harlemnights #slightwork #blackwomanmagic @ Foundation Room Dallas https://t.co/QMJTwfFoTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey I have a new art pic if some like art of some kind please add this as a good pic my friend sent me this yesterd… https://t.co/GxT6y2ZPbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[FDA states fluoroquinolone antibiotics have been found to increase risk of aortic aneurysm/dissection. This risk is… https://t.co/chKtemnwwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just take my money already 😂 I guess I know what I’ll be spending my @Scholastic rewards on next school year!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7 #ashtangahippies Gomukhasana @ In Balance Yoga https://t.co/2RExOzoAN3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not to be over dramatic, but I literally felt my soul leave my body when I saw The Rolling Stones peform Sympathy f… https://t.co/KdN4BSbKWj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well today was definitely different 😭 a really good different lol unfortunately she has 2 exams today so there’s my… https://t.co/tHygksgyhp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @AP @BW @ABC @CNN @CBSNews @FOXTV @ShepNewsTeam @maddow @NBCNews @NPR @AARP @USGAO @usgaolegal @Newsweek… https://t.co/5KBOowFz5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: i'm gonna study tonight   me: opens word, types 'integumentary system' into a document and immediately opens twitter on my phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@potus @realDonaldTrump becomes @JebBush follows Bush policies. No American friend in WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarekCristeros @Janusz1967 Dane kim są skazani pedofile:   900 osób z 1468 osadzonych nie ma zawodu.   70 było mur… https://t.co/tzqUEHW6EL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisitoazul007 @EllaCantaloupeH @cevalloslaura @Atolitoconelddo @rangel_tj @diprietonayeli @jomaiz @fernando__70… https://t.co/VKJIYTkQsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter And Coulter, you are winning us over one tweet at a time! "The other side" has been so pleased with you… https://t.co/DBy04zErmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet me at #yoga class tonight 🌟🌟🧡 at 8:30 Pm Find all the details in @namastetrey Story🌟🤸🏽‍♀️ #LA #SantaMonica @ L… https://t.co/0aEKzrWgh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[No I didn't start ripping up carpet or cleaning I want my oppressors to finish up before going to prison]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP @SenateGOP See, when you have had no moral voice for awhile, you lose the privilege of our belief you rea… https://t.co/POcJCzhBbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[1st practice for US Quidditch Cup 12 is in the books🚀🚀🚀  34 Days until Nationals #CosmosLiftoff #FatLife #quidditch… https://t.co/iG1N4Vs46F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rocky horror picture show 😥 I know the songs but never seem the movie 🤦🏻‍♀️😭 #AdmitMoviesYouveNeverSeen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeaveyDaniel ... you’re single... I’m single... https://t.co/60QNlOgIwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who are you to say the execution should be stopped I would love for the person who killed my sister 28 years ago ex… https://t.co/gaR6HUUK1A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Holly_A_K @AJentleson If you think the party that blocked Obama’s Supreme Court nomination will provide a single v… https://t.co/hT2HVk9vXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickmellamphy Well, I mean, a performance like that... you wanna get it right 😉😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianLandano @District31R @vgallassio @SIBOD31 @MLDonath @ChrisESerrano @staceyrappaport @sunflower1967 @JPatanio… https://t.co/RAAUu3B9tE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iwantmymomsfood Dont use the word check he wrote one to these guys lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for giving us your all! #superbowlchamps #EagleforLife #FlyEaglesFly]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Great! This is the most corrupt president ever! His Republican enablers are also corrupt and complic… https://t.co/h1JuSk3KYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy valentine’s day my boy gotta work until 11pm so i’ll see him for less than 1 hour total today ✌🏻 nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u find good lighting 😁✨♥️ @ Fairmount, Philadelphia https://t.co/DhWHxe2Ki1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CarlosRivera regresa a #Tampico con #GuerraTour el próximo 3 de Marzo @ExpoTampico Venta De Boletos… https://t.co/98mDApADUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @BTWFoundation for being a champion for youth mental health.  Let’s be the light that erases the unnecess… https://t.co/ECFwYlEw1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to help moderate this conversation and loved that parents received the equal footing and platform they dese… https://t.co/lMtUs24nEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socialenemy_ Lord my fans getting out of control! I love all my Erinators though!💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work texted me not to come in today, because of the snow madness, so I went out and spent almost 2hrs building snow… https://t.co/i74pDippje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinnXCII’s new album &amp; Nashville, Tennessee?  name a better bday combo 💙 https://t.co/VOHVTWYjUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[my future husband will be kickin it back with me at my family barbecues, no questions asked. 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uk_hazard Haha thanks man! Honestly Film for me is just about documenting/having fun, I feel like bringing around… https://t.co/k9IPDoTDyZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flashing my signature pearly-white smile fresh from the new dentist 💁🏻‍♀️ @ First Watch - Wesley Chapel https://t.co/8BkdrToHM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness hours @SantambroeusM  #happyhour #santambroeus #florida #palmbeach https://t.co/dE1YLscJpr]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dogs have this routine now where they take turns eating and who eats first- today Esther was first to eat, Kevin… https://t.co/4A1NpQhZRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misternineham @GDFW17 Would it be weird to wear a shirt with my own tweet on it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoriKnowsLuxury @LisaVanderpump @hawkchichi @Serabbi Dorit does not need a dog trainer, she needs a people trainer… https://t.co/51BIrmqzLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisygualberto1 I agree.  It is nice to hear other people besides me is very worried.  How those complicit GOP?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When everything's meant to be broken, I just want you to know who I am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MegCS22 Are you serious?! That’s ridiculous! We switched to Metronet a year ago and it’s the best decision we’ve m… https://t.co/p7U8QGe5zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las vainas que se ven en el tren de NYC creo que no se ven en ninguna parte del mundo 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thistallawkgirl @SaveAslave No it isn't. Its ONE JOKE TEN YEARS AGO THAT IN NO WAY represents Tucker's views. Demo… https://t.co/EtOouzlx0l]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at NCG Eastwood Cinemas for Alita: Battle Angel in Lansing, MI https://t.co/xIdobYKxjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Whole Foods Market - @wholefoodsrdu in Raleigh, NC https://t.co/7l35rdD9dT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to an audiobook about Chernobyl while home sick is strangely perfect. "I feel bad, but not as bad as *the… https://t.co/YizgTexUIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he play you then rule number 2 fuck his bestfriend and make em yes men..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yikes even if you're on bad terms airing someones medical history is raggedy and small minded. Gotta tighten up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE are Strong, WE are Beautiful, and WE are Bold!!! Happy International Womens Day to all the ladies who never say… https://t.co/SsRvS9lLvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[This applies to everything in our lives! It’s really tough sometimes, but fight to keep the faith in God’s plans! @… https://t.co/tVEpm5HcdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get me wrong I love Sunday dinners with my family, but I truly get a headache because it’s so loud and there’… https://t.co/ALBpXNsDne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsKrissy @JussieSmollett The Chicago PD Superintendent was outraged about the noose.]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 Life Hacks You'll Wish You Knew About Sooner  https://t.co/PFhRwe5WPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrowofJustice Walked into a room, said “hi” and then just shut my mouth for the next 30 minutes or so while the pa… https://t.co/bfdGt1EfBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traditionally Basotho blankets are manufactured from wool which offers protection from the wind and rain and provid… https://t.co/Cf6cGQw2BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The not to be missed panel @sxsw stay tuned for more updates @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/PDZYDhD745]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katebcochrane She may not have been a librarian...an aid or clerk maybe. It's a common misconception that all library staff are librarians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a guy not believe me about not  having a thing with his friend bc his friend is a hoe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to start drawing more faces and getting better at eyes/lips/noses!! if u want me to *attempt* to draw your a… https://t.co/pRCpMUI3AL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled for opening night! #ComeFromAway #BroadwayInPortland @BroadwayPDX @wecomefromaway https://t.co/pzQKlsjc67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleLyEaton @the7virtues @SohoHouse @TOmembers Love you Michelle. Can’t wait to see you!! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#chihuahuasofinstagram #chihuahua #winterfashion #needsummer #wednesday #dogsofinstagram #pictureoftheday… https://t.co/KrPFvHBZoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. President I’m 103 and I want you to make America great again. I will vote for you again in 2020! Thank you for… https://t.co/qoFDLSQSYe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics The office of president reveals who you are and trump has been revealed. Now it has been stated in wor… https://t.co/MfueE3aPIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 And they all paid big bucks for it. From $500 to $20,000. That's big bucks for someone who "supposedly" donates his paycheck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No citing sources just random numbers thrown around....more whoppers than Burger King]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @JanaMrszipfel and @mrsstellhorn - Thanks for an awesome few days at #ICE19! I’m proud to teach and lea… https://t.co/PqDFlAVflq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would I keep inviting you out if you repeatedly say you’re coming and then no show? 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 “If you are faithful in little things, you will be faithful in large ones. But if you are dishonest in little th… https://t.co/3tFqOCPzld]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Gi1Q8xRs6W #christianfiction #bibleverse #biblestudy #Bibles #Bibles #books #Christian #bookworms… https://t.co/o1vJYyRuxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[whenever i’m sad i just think of that video of the hedgehog stretching and i’m okay again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ariatnachantal @mi_venecia @susanWV309 @Jilliemary @Strictly_Chris @RasnawatiR @ArtsandScents @happy02013guy… https://t.co/rfoeTm327m]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you’re a journalist when the only excitement you get in 7 months is in CD format from ICE...2 weeks before… https://t.co/a30vRHSRck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Claydog_15 @PGSittenfeld @ChrisSeelbach @TDennard @GregLandsman Did you listen to my podcast yet I discuss how I'm… https://t.co/pHp50JGjle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAOC Are you happy that you lost 25,000 jobs for your state? At the rate you’re going, it appears that you ate n… https://t.co/WkZYdy9FDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know we have bilingual teachers too? Ms. Miller speaks Russian! 🌎 @HergetSchool #biliterateblackhawks… https://t.co/n7qEqldrRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! And just so you know, I’ve had way too much chocolate, so I’m switching to 🍷#Valentinesday #amwriting #Idolovemywine]]></document><document><![CDATA[At shell shack for the first time &amp; I can honestly say EL OH EL to these prices baby 😭😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pianopsycho2 @AOC You know, that famous Starbucks in New York, the one on the corner! Where he, a real New Yorker,… https://t.co/bHf1JVcp0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[your relationship with yourself sets the tone for every other relationship you have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gayle King needs to interview Donald Trump next but that needs to be shown at a movie theatre so we can get popcorn and drinks 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScarlettAWilson Maybe one day he will tell where he put her body.  He’s got ten years to think about it! Good job Charleston County SO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUN IS SHINING IN CALI &amp; I'M LIKE THIS HIGHWAY IS BEAUTIFUL THE CARS ARE BEAUTIFUL EVERYONE IS BEAUTIFUL https://t.co/HiRfYhDUje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee and Georgia be on the lookout for this phone stealing lowlife!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_on11 I think brain research says 21 times (don’t quote me) but you get the point... we need lots of chances to try again!!!! #teachpos]]></document><document><![CDATA[And he claimed it as cheating n like a dumbass I stayed with him n he held it against me for so long it was a month… https://t.co/l6zewJAPDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VCarranza_ USA no se queda atrás. Pero bueno creo que es de los más ágiles. 🙈]]></document><document><![CDATA[The man accused of shooting at deputies and setting fire to his own home is in custody. We’re in Union County this… https://t.co/9XR50gv3dC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigifields1995 @MehrerAllstars @ELeducation @harriscreekelem Ahh! You know how much I like Skittles! And bragging on people! 🥰👍🏼👩🏻‍🏫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GStuedler It will be interesting to see what happens next week when he's sentenced in Judge Amy Berman Jackson's c… https://t.co/vc0XkKYnUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. I have found what I want to do for Lenten discipline. #giveitupfortheearth #cpj #livingecojustice]]></document></documents></author>