<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dr. Oteng answering questions. We're abt 20 years behind where we should be in terms of trauma research in low-midd… https://t.co/aiYrmoX7CG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shroud I know you play on pc but what would your sensitivity translate to on console?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalliFugate @CIN_ROY91 I’d let that cat get way too fat. How couldn’t you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plenty of purple paisley on Park Ave . #onceandfutureluxury @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/upSMYuuzP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarilynM_Melo You look very nice. Still, I like your hair more when it's got that curly thing going! #omg love it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's disgusting and that both Democrats and Republicans in Congress won't give Money to secure our… https://t.co/IuXWsXaRPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on Unc you just makin it hard for niggas to fuck wit ya now . We love the big girls 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LincolnLouttit @DarcySeatonCTV @bradcoccimiglio @md_mackay @brendan_fyfe @tzacs21 @AllenRollin NHL -wise, Vanbiesb… https://t.co/vSLSmAUFeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@680NEWStraffic @1010traffic Toronto Police have shut down Castlefield between Locksley and Times Road. (Halfway be… https://t.co/3LE2eSvHLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbixoB Hey Bobbi and happy Valentine’s Day from my alternative music station 😘😘😘💖💖💖 will you be my valentine 💖💖💖😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreddieCampion It's kind of the reverse of some things. The process is fascinating, but the sausages it turns out are never very good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car calling the kettle black, or in this case racist. #Trump slams Cohen as a liar before he testifies presiden… https://t.co/63ouxzUzWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to the best girlfriend I could ever have @kimmykmorrison https://t.co/ukJsA2rg3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click Here to support the Rolesville HS Football Fundraiser and my son Byrum Brown https://t.co/L8qOXzr6RV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t get it @GOP. Unless perhaps the sense of power one feels being in charge (and having/keeping the ear/s… https://t.co/e35SI4wyty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJosh79 @MoxyTools @FilmToilet @losman94 @TWeirdling @cinema_strikes @danpullenbooks @Duugy13 @holli… https://t.co/YYfvXOB7O7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The president, you, clearly must've listened to The Goebbels Diaries many times over. Undoubtedly… https://t.co/01Yg8no6Ku]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueRyanBrewer @TommyHicksGOP @GOP @realDonaldTrump You’d think the @GOP are not human. Must be hater droids]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GetUpESPN @RealJayWilliams More like see what he’s worth somewhere else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BallBusterParty I would love to be bent over and used. Would fly out just for that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kd_bruins They got it 'DONE' didn't they KD.    I hope you feel better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezradio As someone who is forced to use public restrooms because of the nature of my job. People rarely courtesy flush.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeachMrReed In with yah. I teach in middle and high school but have the utmost respect for the teacher of littles... not for me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SBNation Roses are red Violets are blue The Hoosiers could use a shooter or two!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 @NotTooFondOfYou You hit a nerve with that guy. Holy hell, why was he so offended? Why was he so pa… https://t.co/0Aqdtj0PhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindaBr66944651 @BreitbartNews So are you, a loony. Cher, like Jim Carrey are telling, you stupid Trump supporter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWSMemphis Thanks for important info. I hope people take precautions now. Don't wait till it's too late 😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ruthieriley14 hey, i am 6 players short for jv game on 3/22 if you and the girls want to come play as an alumni ga… https://t.co/DDPBcKkJ6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wasn't ready to say goodbye to Toothless. Movie was so good though 😭❤️ #HowToTrainYourDragon #HTTYD #Toothless… https://t.co/4S8DBFqSPR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@len_stgelais @919sports @LPGeek @delorme_gilbert @simonrene01 https://t.co/99ElcJeHo6]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB-182, abolish death penalty in Colorado advances in committee 3-2, party line. Convicted killers get life while a… https://t.co/RcctCLMA1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#latergram #bts from last nights #screentest in #trenton #newjersey I performed some #monologues and worked the… https://t.co/Ce5mzPiIWf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Nut Crusher Peanut Butter Amber by @Kinkaiderbrew @ Kinkaider Brewing Co. — https://t.co/FaGEuJSmqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pirate0216 @Minges_Maniacs If there was an even bigger crowd I think there would have been more fans escorted out… https://t.co/zbj5MMq0gb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chase Cordia | Takedown at the buzzer! Cordia is heading to the semifinals. 7-5.  @SOTOsports @LakeSunSports @LakeNewsOnline]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maryville has had like two warm days since October and I’m so sick of it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupid morons.  Alaskans  wouldnt feed your flaky  pollack to there dogs (for real) Arby's  you got the bait..for sandwiches.]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the transitive property of basketball, San Jose State is better than Nevada.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimcramer Selling Program - Come on Jim the market is all Mom and Apple pie @SquawkCNBC  @jimcramer… https://t.co/qbGhuTGf7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AsaalamuAlaikumWahRahmantuillah #Alhamduillah #Allah #AllahUAkbar #ProphetMuhammad #PBUH #Quran #Hadith #Sunnah… https://t.co/a5i5Rj2JaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejgr @beaverbuildadam @manivmobility @autofleet_io Good post, well researched. Makes sense to go for longer tri… https://t.co/tHv9NF1Ksg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to connect with more college Coaches or just Great Coaches at every level of the game of basketball! #Network]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one asked for endorsement from @c22worldwide i don’t know where your information is coming from for us to all be… https://t.co/oKxodJUTtv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foxconn Frequency (no. 3): For Three Visibly Chinese Performers on Feb 22 and 23 - This is a real-time game mechani… https://t.co/LS4twK4i0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me put it more dramatically: The 40 million people of California have 55 electoral votes. But if the House deci… https://t.co/hNp49poUCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once you get used to eating so terribly, your craving for healthy foods just disappears. I used to want clean foods… https://t.co/TCPnoow4m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[there's planets in my palms, if you get bored of my skin. I mean you change with the moon.  habitual rituals. your… https://t.co/LTef1uierh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our state government just declared that we don't have a #right to work. #nmpol]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CalleOcho2019 #Setup #EarlyMorning #Before #The #Sunrise #USExecutiveProtection #EventSecurity #SecurityDetail… https://t.co/FeWLDRwS8x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanJKeefe @IDeclareClaire Great song. Timothy B. Schmidt’s big hit for the group.]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I unmitigatedly assure everyone that I do not take out any of my true person (physical or mental) out on ANYone.… https://t.co/t8g5zGWFWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HennoWilliam Henno, #GiftedBuddy! You Took A Classic Journey Song. And Rocked It Into. Henno-Mazing. Cover Gold!!!… https://t.co/LRlmbQOJjo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creative director and cleanup hitter at the MLB level. Hey, it’s a 𝘥𝘳𝘦𝘢𝘮 job, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaysintBB @JonAnthony7 @Riopedre31 @chance4gardener @woodywood1999 @wolflayla420 @FrankBenXXXOOO @MichaelZaker1… https://t.co/5PHpcM5PrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoe_veranda Honestly im about to go back to Guyana , we have a Marriott now , we doing big things now that wypipo… https://t.co/buMORswTIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear @LorenaSGonzalez i know this  is outta of your district, but hope you can help spread the word. SkateWorld has… https://t.co/Zx9ywZDpJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweeetMamaSue @DianneD03113533 @Voieinterieure @LavaletteAstrid @Lakisha19537166 @b_and_s_designs @michaelperez192… https://t.co/J4sWUVVfUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellpwtorch Such a waste of a feud between these two.  It deserves to start from a better place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieo_conn there was a tweet thread a little while back where someone who worked on the movie said everyone wor… https://t.co/i0RvHUyxVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GovIvey Too bad you did not give that order for Puerto Rico. Wait a minute. Are you implying that… https://t.co/pUXE7DhRWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondLynne1 @SayaraStClair @leftywitch @Icezia @CrispySea @cinathestrup @HairlessChimp @kitsonde @RealistDotNerd… https://t.co/Uv8yd9Hac9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24newstime @Javashots @jeffbailey69 @JewelsJones1 @JoanneColombo @jonmichaelolse1 @jskielb3 @judy_shwabe… https://t.co/LiRMvzi2Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pre-gaming Valentine’s Day with my special lady friend...mixing up a couple Rive Gauch cocktails. #GetFestive with… https://t.co/xaOhleWDVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elyse has decided to play both sides of the fence with our Ziploc bags. #ziploc #redskins #dallascowboys #httr… https://t.co/wtD7ePqMh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolPU Hahaha have fun getting bounced in the 2nd round of the tourney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listened to his @PodSaveAmerica interview — agree, he could be a sleeper. America really needs to see more of… https://t.co/oD0CowfVOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[dunkin iced espresso drinks are actually laced with crack instead of caffeine]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fireplace [Building a fire] https://t.co/ut3lD812Nt via @YouTube #solobroll @MattiHaapoja]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear there are infinite accounts of guys that look just like this that steal tweets from months ago and put “inf… https://t.co/hEY074VvR4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump What great photo opportunities for the narcissist in chief. I wouldn't have the courag… https://t.co/OJegEGgQ78]]></document><document><![CDATA[the holes dug in the ground for us are all the same size... stay humble 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyler Herro's first miss of the game comes on his eighth shot, a tough driving attempt. Ole Miss leads 53-50, 13:55… https://t.co/jhoRHJDWT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having trouble making that love connection? Consider sending in your mom. https://t.co/P7aK0umRn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humorandanimals Blocked for this playful joke?  I think you may have taken it wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky4Trump @tgradous @politico @natashakorecki @HillaryClinton @maddow @MSNBC We are ALL #TheMighty200. I follow… https://t.co/GnPHwclUYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero que lo vean bien, el será tu próximo presidente de la Rep. Dom. 2020 #PantojaConReinaldo  @ReinaldoPared https://t.co/g131qLkrQH]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good season with a Sweet 16 appearance. Good things ahead for @CHSbball56. Looking forward to 19-20 season alread… https://t.co/9BCnOiXfrf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jemelehill Really Jemel, I know what socialism is!! Do u?? Have u researched all the socialist governments that we… https://t.co/TK3ZZQ2hTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @Ash348 @DemonicAngel613 @xMelissaThomasx @JillSixx @alistasi @MeganLynnFilm @Horrorgirl1213 👻]]></document><document><![CDATA[#hondacvcc #1982 #hondacivic @ American Honda Motor Company, Inc. https://t.co/Ob5UOaeHs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night  @missmorenab sparkles in snakeskin projectrunwaybravo #premiere itsmatin #mu @cristinastylist easthartz… https://t.co/IWEi1LuLTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, McCabe stated that 45 told him that "I don’t care. I believe Putin." when he told the Orange Traitor about US… https://t.co/6Mi2hBzXs7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dynamo opening game lets go!!!!  Crawfish time and the town knows it !!!! en Houston Dynamo https://t.co/Bz7F15zLBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyndsay, you will not escape justice.  Remember "my parties gone bat shit crazy".  Whatever you're hiding will be d… https://t.co/vsuO1UfhGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergioB_ @AOC @washingtonpost @realDonaldTrump And yet..... https://t.co/2o5qwrxaXv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jakedello I am 41 &amp; this is the 1st movie I want to see in theaters since IT.... absolutely love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made some mods to my 2007 FJ Cruiser.  #joemaccarthy #conceptcar #sketch #illustration #fjcruiser #carart #toyota… https://t.co/WPVtgywjvO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luis5Xv @mauriciopedroza @jpedrerol @elchiringuitotv Jajajaja buena ésa😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookofshaders are the rest of the chapters out or available? From Image Processing to the end of the book]]></document><document><![CDATA[#7Mile Hill run to kickstart my “weekend” I use that term lightly because I work weekends haha! I think I’ve been r… https://t.co/pgE3AbttZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_tonyjefferson @CSteele32 @ALevine41 @untouchablejay4 @weddlesbeard Wtf u mean lol we a lottery team what did we ruin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incredible! @afthunderbirds  ・・・ U.S. Air Force #Thunderbirds flew over SoCal today. They kicked off the premiere o… https://t.co/0wUNY1Khmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiriWeather I like it, really strikes me as a day to remember how important love is, even if you are single never… https://t.co/kKqEv01AEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what's another great thing about @AlloFiber? In a blizzard such as this, we haven't had a single blip of s… https://t.co/Zl8kS1OUdW]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 SCOOBY-DOO IG ACCOUNTS HAVE STARTED FOLLOWING ME IN THE LAST 24 HOURS WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono @bend_time My brothers parish in El Paso needs help. They are helping emigrants dropped off by ICE. St… https://t.co/8AfSXr3uA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Volunteering 🇺🇸 (@ Perry Point VA Medical Center - @mdvagov in Perry Point, MD) https://t.co/IfhKbR0JzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great goal by Harry Kane to put @SpursOfficial on the board first. #COYS #SOUTOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Halocarterr @Deej253 I hope this is good because she been flopping lately 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xKhaoz You and your 37 followers! 😂 fuck out my mentions boi. Shit waaay outta style]]></document></documents></author>