<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Toasted Walnut Bourbon Porter by @OastHouseBeer at @oasthousebeer — https://t.co/CTUtyJNZek]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_s__h__a__e_ I had one done by a lady my friend recommended me to and I would 10/10 go to her again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He ain't answering you for a mother fucking REASON bitch! Fall the fuck back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntsyArtsy @agotoronto I saw it last week at the pre-view. Loved it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a Twitter DM group with Noah and Lia where all we do is send each other articles from the Onion]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸Con Sue Photography and Design🇺🇸   🇲🇼Like our photos...Follow our IG 🇲🇼  🇨🇱This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler 🇨🇱… https://t.co/tQg5y2JIeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__zoomm @TiffinXCTF Excited to see what you're gonna put down in outdoor sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My tears stained my cheeks. Freddie Highmores performance in tonight’s episode was moving, so much so I also had go… https://t.co/0M8eZk7JtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now there's a sequel:  Interrupting Chicken and the Elephant of Surprise!  Both on the shelves in the library… https://t.co/IgExwnHJBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexAndersonMD I’m all for hanging out with you in all forms... Twitter, Insta, FB, IRL, text, email etc. lucky to… https://t.co/dt34LwpYgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlreiner Carl, the US has arrested a Chinese tech magnate in Vancouver. and are bringing him back to the US. His… https://t.co/zFZvdL0CIV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the Larsens consider buying a house, we use math to determine how much light we will get during different seas… https://t.co/F9kTUfI283]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamL_Daily @adamlambert We’re freezing in Cali, so I’d stay in Mexico if I were you ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't been here for a long 14 hours 😂 (@ Miami International Airport - @iflymia in Miami, FL) https://t.co/eelEPlFLGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonG40210896 @jeanine_new @Valac666 @JaneColes2 @TeamSalBrian @735BlackSheep @JeannaMarie32 @Mary60053440… https://t.co/iv1uL3BgX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really appreciate creators who commit to working with integrity-even when it means walking away on a project. .… https://t.co/HwvA8AKLR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akarl_smith @PeteWilliamsNBC @KenDilanianNBC Mid February was last week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp I don’t understand if you have a baby delivered from a failed abortion why isn’t automatic adoption recomme… https://t.co/NiIEpuswbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyhughes50s Aww thanks Tony! I hope you do too! Did you have a good day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaltyFishTea @chanwalling @steam_games @larianstudios Who said anything about censoring? I’m talking about horribl… https://t.co/wFaR3RrSbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We arrive to the gym and the first thing my boyfriend says is, “mm, something smells like food.” Smh. Not now, please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/28/2019 • #Art • Wesley #UnitedMethodistChurch ⛪️ #allareWelcome #family #LoveLives ❤️ in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻… https://t.co/VI5quo3602]]></document><document><![CDATA[My grandsons 1st birthday. #winnercakeall #foodnetwork #mdvcustomcakes #alledible #anotherfavorite #food #cake… https://t.co/wObsrgzTFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also if they trade Kessel or Ashton-Reese I’m going to bandwagon another team because NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: I have accepted a challenge to post 7 books I love...just covers, no reviews or explanation. Each day I will… https://t.co/RhlHEF9x2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 100 Years, Katy ISD!!! 🥳🎉🎈🎊 _____________________ #KatyISD #Technology #100YearCelebration #KISD… https://t.co/93FP1gMDZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmclymer I try to give her the benefit of the doubt, but she just seems dumb to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Controversyz @ecclesias Tell him to come to the US and mansplain that one to Nancy Pelosi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couples therapy: the gift I give to me for my growth, for my chance to be the me I most long to be, the remastery o… https://t.co/P9lJeZS3DQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is my niece Katie’s 10th Birthday! We are going out to celebrate with her today. I can’t believe my younge… https://t.co/MZDSWCDPhq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt   This beauty, the Point Reyes now stands on mere boards that have been burnt and destroyed by partiers and va… https://t.co/8b7VMHHfaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WContreras40 This is a tragedy. Maduro is s monster. Sorry, Willson. It’s terrible v]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9hgkSxPtpd @ Maxine's Bistro &amp; Bar https://t.co/eocSG1XKb3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve officially made it- I’m in a group chat with 18 of bfs family members now lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t like when kids are treated like a liability. My goals is to show those who doubt I can do both. I know I can… https://t.co/XaGGL14kZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let Kofi win.  1. because he deserves it 2. The amount of whining if he doesn’t will be unbearable]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wake up everyday and know your worth don’t let no one treat you like Khloe Kardashian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DukeNBA @Jacksonator21 Cam Johnson played on a sprained ankle, Sterling Manly and Leaky Black have sat out the las… https://t.co/YB6ScdRTzO]]></document><document><![CDATA[After at least 15, 20 years I just found out today that my doctor was also born on March 7th.  Who knew. Yep, I did… https://t.co/BEpbvoGHfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[i found the warmest blanket in my house. also, might decide to sleep in my old room for a while, this bed is hella comfy!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the best fucking mom in the world why do I take her for granted sm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FactsFantasy #Amandaknox Whatever sounds good right? Take it run with it say it enough it comes true? 2 guilty ver… https://t.co/6txGgvvuGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[El Chapo likely off to 'Alcatraz of the Rockies,' the Supermax prison in Colorado. It's hardened buildings house th… https://t.co/xfjncCKMJd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet Daddy took me to prom this weekend and I felt so lucky. I even wore green. 🍀 @mattnathanson https://t.co/8kza1WVxz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastianbach @trailerparkboys @MSmithBubbles if you want to discuss it sometime ON THE AIR for Waxx Traxx to the… https://t.co/Bxt3LGhSUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww $#!T ... it just got real damn colorful up in this B!TC#... -Steve is damn 51years old today.... lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kbj_vi @ChrisHi19404803 We will always support and love YOU unconditionally- @genareagh @pendleton_jill You contin… https://t.co/BMdZj1Ebfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i believe you, would that make it stop         😜    👊/||\_      _/¯    ¯\_  if i told you i need you, is that wh… https://t.co/whnCVHuJLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXCUSE ME AMBULANCE COMPANY MY DAD HAS BEEN DEAD FOR YEARS AND WILL NOT BE PAYING YOU FOR THE AMBULANCE RIDE. GET OVER IT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paul__sullivan @grandmommy10 I’m truly not questioning her testimony now.  I’m questioning why she did not apply t… https://t.co/UuV1QFf2jC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And as Jesus was going up to Jerusalem, he took the twelve disciples aside, and on the way he said to them, https://t.co/qpy34ASFRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeaMichele Congratulations on your beautiful wedding! You deserve a lifetime of happiness and love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[As I said before if you went to the Arden mall to see that waste of life Jeffree rat you absolutely disgust me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll bet atleast half of the speech was repeating sentences multiple times.  Like many, many multiple times]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great speaker @ school today. Amanda Doyle, author “History of Civil Rights in St Louis” courtesy of… https://t.co/gt566dcXrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[And her best friend is a wannabe smartass and always talks during movies 😩😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter has made me gag twice in the last two minutes. My virgin eyes. Younger-me woulda retweeted these shits but nah. The world is sick.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then I volunteered to work a double Monday but hey that’s $100 added to my check 🤑💪🏾 bag is definitely being secured 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[The other day, someone told me their clinical instructor had 2 students sit in a bench bc they didn’t have enough p… https://t.co/YRzYy3XdZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Susan Sumners started the Cowtown Weekend Half Marathon P/B Sprint! https://t.co/5li8nt1N8d #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @awsten i miss you hope you’re doing good and drinking orange juice or something what’s it like being the best boy alive]]></document><document><![CDATA[#thethingsyouseetraveling #laughing #roadtrip #omg @ Booger Hollow Store https://t.co/ZtGGFWZMwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Presently, we should strengthen the ACA. Rebuild our failing infrastructure. Retrain workers in out… https://t.co/PSu34vZQrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[He did not spare his own Son but gave him for us all. So with Jesus, God will surely give us all things. Romans 8:32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmrxrn @doritkemsley1 Do these dumb bitches know LVP buried her brother, is taking care of sick Giggy, opened TomT… https://t.co/2FYfXil7Zc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stegobecksaurus It’s not beating you.... because you are here... you are fighting... because you deserve all the g… https://t.co/wxxc4dEFPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BezaTuga In undergrad I had to make a KBr pellet and I wasn’t strong enough to actually compact the pellet togethe… https://t.co/sjeFkVLL1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsell1023 @DonaldJTrumpJr Also you say you don't have a team, but you have already chosen a side by your own words ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Hilarious to watch Ivanka and Alexandria exchanges. Both immature and need to grow up. Tatiana]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t know how I got so lucky, so thankful ✊🏼♥️😋 ily baby https://t.co/GbWXa2H3cG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vicks Nyquil makes me hallucinate so hard. I just took a shot of it.  Good night y'all ❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every early riser needs a friend who will meet them for breakfast at 9am on DST Sunday without complaint. https://t.co/mFHcOEtV4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realAliTweets @metfan62 And yet those Republicans, who don't give a shit, care very much about the investigation b… https://t.co/RGSkDCfpjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jefequann Any guy that likes getting fucked in the ass is gay 😂🤦🏽‍♀️🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude in VA literally ran a woman down and you said there were good people on both sides. Should have kept that same… https://t.co/KgRtjslMjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtlantisMty @Joaquinsmarino 😳 ammmmm Es que ya no entiendo 🤔 en unos si hay y en otros no 😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning fun at Six Flags @ Six Flags Over Texas https://t.co/cSjtQawblx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diego_Diaz_U @NoUghhh I don’t either!! but my friends told me too and I instinctively put it in the microwave and they roasted me]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm such a baby when it comes to driving in the snow...and if you have a problem with that...GO TF AROUND ME MF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been 1 month since my world came crashing down. I miss what we had, I miss what our future held, I miss the wa… https://t.co/IyOQvoAqRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sumeet_Bahl @MountSinaiIR @Interventional2 @roblookstein @bonesz @SarahKantharia Yes! Yes! Yes!… https://t.co/JerPtzXfNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday! Monday! Men’s 🎾 on the road @RRHSAthletics 4:15 &amp; ⚾️ goes to @WilkesCentralHS 4:30 (no JV) hear “live”… https://t.co/vunugfzCa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m walking through the mall where I spent 6 years of my late teenage and early adult life. I remember feeling that… https://t.co/Xjh9ZBdLqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertsonElem counselor Mr. Rimey sets the example and encourages acts of kindness! https://t.co/VsbZVTwsxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t believe we still put up with each other after all these years.. will it continue for 5 more¿  ~stayed tuned~ https://t.co/a0UMuYJC8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I find odd is that I don’t see any #democrats or #liberals that claim to be #Patriots or have anything good to… https://t.co/PK8Lmcuvhe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep going to church then talking about others on the church steps, keep trying to break that happy couple up, keep… https://t.co/4AMYrzq8eC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennGlenndale @jbartos @MiaFarrow @JerryFalwellJr @AOC @CPAC If only those who claim to be Christian thought the same thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[CPAC ... has become the biggest 3 ring circus in the world. I have never laughed so much at what once was conservat… https://t.co/X8Q2GTjijg]]></document><document><![CDATA[He changes time and seasons; he removes Kong’s and sets up Kings; he gives wisdom to the wise and knowledge to thos… https://t.co/zeEYK8kVrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @starlandnj for such a great night with @brettyoungmusic No chance I have a voice tomorrow. Totally cool… https://t.co/Uoqf2ohrDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geovlm_ Como rompen las pantallas wtf, mi teléfono es un iPhone xr y pase casi un mes sin funda ni nada y se me ca… https://t.co/WAIZfUgi8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God I got home safely. I have got to stop getting into Uber’s super drunk by myself 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[So in case y’all didn’t know I spent my valentines in a fucking fox hole eating an mre......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MSNBC Since when do you believe anything in FAKE NEWS MSNBC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickygrichard @ChantalCarey @M_Normand @bigonadon Et pourquoi le fédéral promeut le 50e anniversaire de LA Loi? 🤔… https://t.co/k1B4CbKKDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida siempre se encarga de decirte  " oye no y oye si  "  🤗 , gracias vida!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday's recording sesh was a success! :) #hissmile #f**knowwhat #elizabethaddison #singer #recordingstudio… https://t.co/DSL9bsBqSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows the rest of the country saw you yesterday. all the things we have been saying in #NC11 for a long t… https://t.co/RIq3spbSl2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya. So. This is a problem.  1.5 weeks until I see ATEEZ 🥵 https://t.co/RlE8ho1XvV]]></document></documents></author>