<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Paycom is looking for teammates like you. See our latest #HR job openings, including "HR Business Partner - DFW", v… https://t.co/u1Hxx215Py]]></document><document><![CDATA[Northern Colorado Municipal leadership sharing insight into their lives and careers in City Management. #Careers… https://t.co/zocWUK1rpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyJeffro Thank you love ❤️❤️❤️ can’t wait to see you soon so we can celebrate our bdays ! ❤️ u ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tyler_105 @Change J Missouri. 10 machine Lan E Virginia.     5  S Space to wonder U United we Stand S Suggestion B… https://t.co/0bzRnVsjzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When u hear it snowed in LA and could only imagine what summer is going to be like in Florida. Looks like I'm staying up north.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Lied about progress with NK, he lied about Russia only to lift sanctions on Russians and about a Trump towel,… https://t.co/wInZu2Hn6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[A combined 17-1 the last 4 trips here.   This is what the 8th seed will get us.😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PaleoFest @PaleoBadger: Lots of cool faunal evidence of invertebrates and vertebrates in the newly discovered trac… https://t.co/tOscLSErJY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess I can call “pot/kettle” on this one for my damn self lol https://t.co/UYCDTuKZDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I DIDNT KNOW IT WAS DAYLIFHT SAVINGS AND I KWPT THE BAR OPWN AND EXTRA HOIR FUCKKKKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachETuck @CoachMills56 @CoachYoung41 @CraigYeast Appreciate it Coach!!! Glad to have been coached by the best WR COACH in the state‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KalomaCardwell @AfricanaCarr @HaasInstitute @rolandsmartin @AOC @briebriejoy @PaulaEdgar @Sifill_LDF ✊🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Six years ago today I met the nicest celebrity I’ve ever met. She was kind and very generous with the groupies, esp… https://t.co/JcEAKnnDfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Indian Wells Tennis Garden for BNP Paribas Open in Indian Wells, CA https://t.co/JLeXo51qLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathy_coppinger @Cali_J_ @AmberD___ @airbornliz @Robert_Daffern @LewisHom @AkinsMel @TaraTalleyTHD @gullatt_hd @KhariHeru 👊🏾💯💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bearded man who just asked @KamalaHarris a question is wearing @JeppsonsMalort jacket. 🤢#iapolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[PS. Yes I’m at work. Fee 24/7 secured parking FTW. Plus I had time to kill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On god if I ever got The Clap from a roll of toilet paper I’m going full Liam Neeson with the hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[I, too, am a Garbage Salad (at @PortillosHotdog in Chicago, IL w/ @jamlikescarrots) https://t.co/uVRY2aA9Jd https://t.co/Frf4EbCzDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope this photo ends up in the hands of every college admissions officer in the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTheil @derek_wgod Theil I got a kick out of this tweet, thank you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really interesting article and helps move towards organoids as a drug/nutrient absorption model]]></document><document><![CDATA[When we were in West Texas, 30miles from the nearest cell signal, I walked past a motorhome at sunset where I could… https://t.co/YrDBBMeBFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobBiertempfel Sadly, I will be attending work, most likely in a self driven vehicle. Not sure how I will get from… https://t.co/6qhN0irafn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@al_ambition @thisnorthernboy @PanterandHall Your galleries on your site are breathtaking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow All the Democrats AR Islam all of them want and only care for themselves.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smart ........but look at the dumbass that voted for them. Dam now that’s stupidity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tribelaw If that comes to pass, will the Joint Chiefs and the Pentagon protect him or eject him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValerieSprague I’ve eaten a whole loaf of bread. If it good bread and one is hungry, why not? I’ve never had anyone sit and watch, though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCapazario @Vikings I think it’s probably fair to say because of his broken fibula he endured during his college y… https://t.co/3CobfMsXlA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valintine's Day Tank Concert with Bae @ Saban Theatre https://t.co/CHKicGuTEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsTyler78 @Musings_of_wine @jwood7070 Ass was last month we’re working on our tummies now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow Spielberg sounds like he's taking sour grapes. Big screen /small, creativity is the story]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber @scooterbraun @taylorswift13 Saturday I am gone! You think you have to deal with this now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GotNoSperm @HalNiederman Eskin: Phillies will win &gt; 85 games even w/o Harper.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul The Leadership Institute has churned our Ralph Reed, Grover Norquist, Mike Pence, Mitch McConnell and Jam… https://t.co/fGFEdIEFGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My babies currently upset w me because I won’t let her run around the house with her bottle upside down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a PB &amp; J'ale'y by @elkbrewing @ Household de Batson — https://t.co/SeFdVhH1FI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SturgisSports Show him that South Carolina hospitality! I told him about the BBQ! If he only had the time to visit… https://t.co/Pl4j2kpqAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great fight from Urbandale. Just ran out of steam! Johnston on the semifinals 66-57]]></document><document><![CDATA[holga 135bc, lost roll #7. ••• #holga #holga135bc #film #filmphotography #ibelieveinfilm #slotcanyon… https://t.co/w8yPcEB62T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Custom wine rack by @EBrownCreations coming together. @ Temecula, California https://t.co/sjRcjx42EB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#workout #getfit  #getinshape #fitness #planetfitness @ Providence, Rhode Island https://t.co/yAKZptLD4y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey guys! First commission of the year! This was a really fun piece to work on. The character descriptions were so… https://t.co/m820auvFJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Notorious_J_v_G so if someone decides to idk...like clock someone in the face with 0.5 seconds left in  the they s… https://t.co/viv3dkGHCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when @SallyPancakes digs into #AI 👌🏻💯👌🏻!! @YahooFinance @blackstone @MIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out great videos from @DistribuTECH @SAP including my video of #Esri and @SAPInMemory - #BetterTogether https://t.co/9ipeaxN1Jm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like Region IV winner is going to have to somehow beat a DEEP 361 set of teams!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD @PascoSheriff @LivePDNation @LivePdFans @Sean_C_Larkin @TomMorrisJr1 @danabrams @PatrolPd… https://t.co/D6ipZWqoIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time discussing participatory budgeting and government accountability with Mayor Cheng Wen-Tsan 鄭文燦 fro… https://t.co/j666xXUdz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the reasons I suggested asking someone where they started is while it may result in survivor bias, it’s a he… https://t.co/rICZcaRTtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Triple Bock by @SBCbeer/@tworiversbrew @ Conway’s Bbq Pit — https://t.co/nBk3RWw5Pi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lcheslerclark @rrhoover @MugOfPaul @ProductHunt @rrhoover https://t.co/TxV3OHRewf! (h/t @bhadrasandeep)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gayGOPnews 2). Frankly, the idea that people don't ALWAYS say out loud when 'their guy' is f*cking up is one of th… https://t.co/qKO1hYho2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluishGecko Except the team is scattered across three primary locations w/ manager in a fourth, so in-person is nearly impossible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeanne826 @Franklin_Graham @ChickfilA Only a fool hates what God chooses!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr and neuropsychologist Micky Collins giving the Athlete Keynote Address at #gfeller2019 https://t.co/W3F1jNvT4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazon thought they had a deal but wasn't prepared for pushback.  Everyone as plan until they punched in the mouth.… https://t.co/ql3RcaIWEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MetaFlaelli You probably needed to find someone’s cat so they’d join your party, so they’d open a cave, so you can… https://t.co/66LhcIfIph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @schmoyoho can you #songify the #RKelly interview? https://t.co/WfyZpL4z49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBC @CNBCMakeIt Here comes the BitCoins! Bob Morton https://t.co/mnEB9rwfGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haha, I hear you. This is awesome. Great looking out, I appreciate the compliment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuse would have Mcnabb, Harrison, Monk, Jim Brown, John Mackey, Daryl Johnston, Dwight Freeney, Chandler Jones, Wil… https://t.co/T4bY34EnEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of our job at @plasticity and _herogeneration is to increase the accuracy of people’s understanding of things… https://t.co/TcYy8fb4cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[me watching all the drama going down about senior assassination on my timeline like https://t.co/JxQEvJSW1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tyrone Fowler of Bishop McDevitt (Wyncote) majors Pequea Valley's Joey Coblentz for 5th at 220, 11-1. @LancasterSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maramcewin @afaduln2 Why should NK give up their nuclear deterrence. I’m an american and I have seen how our gover… https://t.co/uQxiqG5CpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[No school tomorrow Sachems...but there virtually will be at your house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just imagine the facts we would have if Oprah hadn't edited out the good stuff. 60 min McCabe report]]></document><document><![CDATA[He said “on some faggot bullshit” on his most enduring song, what sort of]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but THIS IS ALL IM GOING TO BE TALKING ABOUT FOR THE NEXT EVER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @TWITMO_INMATE @JohnnyB371 @4RANDALL1 @TexaLonestar @ZyroFoxtrot @cindy_nurse @Maggieb1B @Lady_Vi_2U… https://t.co/PTpQXziYHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Padres_Farm @poglankford @ParkAtThePark This build has been focused on building a staff to compete for a WS. If th… https://t.co/vxOr3xsLLU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all realize this is going to be @PeytonRoyceWWE first Championship match since that what I call Screwjob at wargames 2 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonotabot_ @CandiceBergenMP Yes that shit show of a justice committee shows that. That justice committee is an ass… https://t.co/dY5Wmcq3Ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go watch #CaptainMarvel You will LOVE IT! Stay for end credits. OMG!!! #Marvel #AvengersEndgame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ran into majestic on my commute home. #bridge #baybridge #sanfrancisco #rushhour #cars #street #embarcadero… https://t.co/VMJVKwC2ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are the odds on this cunt being the next Dennis Hastert? Might have to put a tenner on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieAndelman He’ll make much more money earlier with NFL...prob a four year guarantee of about $20m. He’s a long… https://t.co/PAttMHgdpB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hangin’ with the King: @fox12oregon @TimbersFC Preseason Special kicks off this Friday at 6:30 ⚽️ 📺 🌵 https://t.co/yvpiV2R8SU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Mouser Electronics team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/HiUwNG9ESk #IT #Mansfield, TX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Santiago getting some work in on a Friday night. #PTF #SlidersBaseball #EmbraceTheGrind @pistokache_PT https://t.co/894sgOAt8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraRBelin @JonesChrisA @RobSandIA @RandyFeenstra The first words I said was that Feenstra was wrong! Why is this hard?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Beer J by @GrandRoundsBrew @ Grand Rounds Brewpub — https://t.co/dbvvTytJc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say after me. . Baseball is back, baseball is back. Presenting the SJALL (San Jose American Little League) PIZZA. M… https://t.co/31lKhP5bvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CindyStarfall @the2livecrew Looking so Fucking hot ass up I love to to have sum of that ass so Fucking super sexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMA Home 10 Year Old Transgender Sexual Dancer @michaelstrahan Approves @FCC @TheJusticeDept @FBI @ThomasPKennedy3… https://t.co/9ElGIAINuZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry to be corny and ppl say it a lot but don’t actually do it you want more you have got to do more! You can’t co… https://t.co/ewR7LztJq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a very simple way for women's sports to bring in more revenue, and it has nothing to do with winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@csdPagan @LindseyGrahamSC @senjudiciary I think that was the one and only time I ever heard the word portieres use… https://t.co/IGQ65IKaZm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Linden Yard Fleet Operations in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/st5W9mDvf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SMGHF It's the least we can do to support you supporting our community! 💝 #support #circleoffriends #ThankYou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@24To23 I'm in Technology and I'm done with the class I finished in November]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made an FRQ about how my id/ego/superego would interact with the decision making of me buying a new sweater. one… https://t.co/ZOSAjo0VRH]]></document><document><![CDATA[They close schools for THIS in New York? If one “can make it here” one “can make it anywhere?”     Not so much. Clo… https://t.co/jm0bf7Kj8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarpeDonktum @DonaldJTrumpJr @donlemon How far is your head up your ass?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s path is different. What they left out of the article is that he navigated his path with an unrivaled wor… https://t.co/Sx7rQwlW2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[.... systemic oppression, socioeconomic disadvantage, ableism, sexism, institutional racism...  There are a lot of… https://t.co/Ol7O9SNwf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[May you begin this day with a smile on your face, and with happiness for your soul to embrace. Good morning friends… https://t.co/q5j1cxcizO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austal Supplier Fair on full swing! #SSIUSA #shipbuilding @SSI_CAD https://t.co/W7coxdjWdo]]></document></documents></author>