<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My favorite part of senior day 😊♥️🏀🐏 #letsgoVCU @VCU_Hoops https://t.co/uvUKVhbsa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my...This essay from Braden Holtby is so so charming. I love the anecdote about the kids tossing hand written no… https://t.co/9ZI4cyDpVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[What you've been waiting for is coming ahead of schedule!!!!!! #YurExpectancyPushIt4ward]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahpaasch I am a 4, which is why I cry while watching commercials. I am my emotions!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TayyIsabelle @OfficialRezz @hbrooksz @tbellard0625 They would lose their minds!!!🤫🤤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is so weird I swear. I didn’t know anyone including my bio dad until I was about 15-16 when my sis found me on… https://t.co/I9wOM6b219]]></document><document><![CDATA[HEROS! Bus drivers navigate winter roadways to get athletes to events; Some drivers routinely make trips from Centr… https://t.co/2IK3yKwHJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mans couldn’t resist no matter how many times I was promised “I will not nut in you”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#livingdeadgirl #dragqueen #dragula out in weho sowing undead oats for y’all to feel. I should make a series with t… https://t.co/GCbAZzBx9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[😏😈 https://t.co/RVvJEip1NA use promo code NOVA10 for a 10% discount on your purchases! 🔥🔥🔥 #fitness gear online!… https://t.co/NX1Ohpv1aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Precalc Links It Up with Trig Functions.... #GoBeyondLampasas  @HopkinsMath  #lampasashs https://t.co/h0j7wZZzor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Pleasant Hill Baptist Church https://t.co/fbPh8cc1Xm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meet #Alba, an intelligent and gentle mother #pig who spent most of her life behind rusty metal bars.   She… https://t.co/Rc6aRkAPi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of International Women’s Day, celebrating the slew of #badass women who slayed, prayed and sashayed with m… https://t.co/YDJWdODexy]]></document><document><![CDATA[One size does not fit all #SaveCDPA from @NYGovCuomo because we need to stay in our homes not institutions… https://t.co/ZLup6SmtC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of which road you choose to follow: the perfect will of God or the Permissive will of God; never make giving up on God an option.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardinal George Pell found guilty of child sex abuse  https://t.co/IXOeSB2Xc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this idea for kids New Years' Eve wishing wands - a fun way to make... #funniness #tee-hee #smirk #merry https://t.co/xjvTPisw1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SteveJohnson_ @ThabitiAnyabwil @MeganRegina Oh yes and if I’m not mistaken, the largest is right down the road fr… https://t.co/Dls84kTtjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fortressfin @MAGAgirly @PaulMer70053201 @1PatriotRealtor @John_R_Berna @AngeleStar11 @MissILmom @leftovergravy… https://t.co/ORT9zrRADj]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s the bench at the top of the NW side of round valley at the radman/TM/pulp friction intersection... #snow… https://t.co/HpwNYVUbCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow Fox contributor says it all. He's gotta be crazy or an opportunist. #resignnow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewMusPrincess @aidancramsay @OliviaKieffer The allure of making beef stew is that you can throw a cheap cut of be… https://t.co/TKpRgEG7iX]]></document><document><![CDATA[A year ago I hated the one single job I had, dreaded going to work everyday. Now I have 3 jobs and I love every sin… https://t.co/s55E4UbOnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to represent my great place to work &amp; collect learnings at the @GPTW_US Summit this week. #CollabieLife https://t.co/N2p7p9xrlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[being a region rat has its perks... like going to the beach when it’s 30 degrees outside 🤩 #219Day https://t.co/foUURZCy4g]]></document><document><![CDATA[3,000+ pieces of world class art coming to Fishtown. Nice temporary popup until it’s built too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder that I spent two years I. High school making everyone call me Max.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ St George Community/Parkway https://t.co/dFdKXDOGiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trench_notalone I love your parents for how much they care about you. Tell them thank you from me for worrying abo… https://t.co/iLAGI5wq4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Irma46977582 @DontBuyMurder @MattEdw12312749 @Cynwel73 @JanuaryBabies01 @Dave06031956 @jadeo09 @sailorfawnie… https://t.co/gKSFgBfprj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NJ tryin to do away the basic democracy the country is built on. Never fear tho...we gonna nominate #Trump again a… https://t.co/GFWA2dp18g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielBrasilia @wecanmag @PrezesPan @DavidLogan2020 @XandraXandraBX @GiselleMarks1 @TO31771 @enriquillo2… https://t.co/Tg11mPnwqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barrieshelter So sad. Prayers and condolences to her mother and family. No More!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKenavam @cher Cher is rich, but wasn’t born that way. She worked for it. She wasn’t given $$ by dear ‘ol daddy. O… https://t.co/vTZsMpjc3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year I keep tabs on people that don’t wish me happy birthday. Just know I’m petty and watching. https://t.co/qCGETGr4ix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insanely amazing performance by the “Firecrackers” Jump Rope Squad at #ukbasketball game today! Wow! #justaskmelia https://t.co/DIoeQv3Pi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost died of embarrassment that time someone brought Zima to a high school kegger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attorney General files lawsuit against Pike County home improvement business | Milford PA | Local News https://t.co/s8mVBWSb8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I use to take valentines so serious when I was younger but now it’s like you have the whole year to show me you car… https://t.co/aAjuc7x2Kz]]></document><document><![CDATA[on GOD. I b tryna be a better person &amp; everything, meanwhile bitches out here thinking being crazy is cute 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HiKei_Bi Oh em gee! Finally finished taking them out! 6 hrs later! 😱 Oiled and combed through...now time to start… https://t.co/W6bopu3JlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not had any coffee today and I think I’m dying. #TuesdayThoughts https://t.co/JK4JBwtIUK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seguro estoy que se marcho pensando que la quiero, yo fui campeón en el amor y ahora que perdí, no debe de saberloooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecNielsen @DHSgov @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @PressSec @GOP @SarahHuckabee @KellyannePolls @LindseyGrahamSC… https://t.co/HPtfCI5GEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1990chevyman @realDonaldTrump Its so hard to say this to our president, but you act like a 8th grader does any one feel the same?]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA if a man tells you he’s only seeing you just don’t believe him and save yourself the trouble. Also applies to “… https://t.co/2shQZbNHmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boulder_Barbara @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump Do you live in a border state?  Because I do and I disagree with y… https://t.co/x2O8qyVKPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ranger letting it all hang out 😂 Oh the life of a dog 🐾💙 #ranger #dane #danelifeistough #babyboy @ Mabank, Texas https://t.co/0E0lVm8bTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight don’t forget to set your clocks ahead one hour so you’re not late for yoga tomorrow! Sunday 8am Vinyasa awa… https://t.co/npm6dQ59zX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyJasonSchultz Don’t you just love how @NASCARONFOX keeps using Tom Brady with all these comparisons they are tal… https://t.co/DMW4zKRb9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[These two cuties had a ball helping  their Mommy and other Chancey teachers navigate the city delivering food to st… https://t.co/lFbWlFizyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nick_LGrant @Rocioceja_ I feel like they’re kinda hurting themselves by doing that lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[My coworker stopped coming to work!  Gonna work my butt off today. Too bad I’ll be sitting down the whole time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX please let me guest judge!! Normal mom normal pet sitter..but funny and would LOVE to be a part of… https://t.co/xyHUG2AP75]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seems like Trump and several of the GOP needed a "hand" from the owner of the Asian Spa's in Florida.  Wonder how m… https://t.co/KJGzKLuswm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bulletin board has earbuds on it but I know they look like shower massagers https://t.co/bfRBtfGwvA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhopesgalaxy @Crystal_592 @BTS_twt Literally what happened to me when I tried to get the love yourself Seoul conce… https://t.co/3Xpm6IGpl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Bend people are the most different people in Indiana. They hear about everywhere else but no ones hears about… https://t.co/d7v6cUJLuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stepped off the plane in Orlando like 🧨🧨🧨😬  shakethegroundcomp  I give myself Elite Platinum Gold Fairy Dust Prince… https://t.co/927RUfqQdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[to all of my indy and west lafayette college friends— sitting made simple is hiring! rates starting @ $10 an hour.… https://t.co/Scn1HcwIQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX I mean, Mormon “apostle” Bruce R McConkie taught this about Mormon missionaries: “I would rather have you c… https://t.co/k4XxdqVpy3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Time to Make Sure Our Kids Are No Longer Bound, Shackled, or Locked Away When They’re at School https://t.co/YErwfRawtr via @aclu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm proud of you, @cathymcmorris!! We have 3 branches of government for a reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HighSchoolMeVsAdultMe  High school me: Is a huge dork who finds out about this weird new thing called the internet… https://t.co/DBSho9W0WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorningBmore #ViewFromMyPerch #BlessedInBmore #DayIsDawning @ Christ Church Harbor Apartments Inc https://t.co/xzwdzvfRLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe instead of signing Bibles, President Trump should actually open one up and read it. How about Matthew 19:24 to start? #justsaying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honey highlights 🍯🍯🍯 yummy!! #hairinspo #fromdarktolight #olaplex #beautifulhair @ San Jose, California https://t.co/udrj2Mktzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great day to #chooseCSU! Enjoyed meeting with Assemblymember Monique Limón. Thank you for your support of higher… https://t.co/06gn7U337b]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that I deleted every old picture of my obsession with nick jonas and Hannah Montana looking back now I hate myself for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Life Of A Stranger by Nadia. https://t.co/MsuDtlpQjQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Returning to God in the midst of ashes: Benedict XVI’s final homily as pope https://t.co/3Rq608OagN #PPBXVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shergiggles @TangnikaiA That’s good to hear that you have an a good day. I was also shocked to hear about Luke Per… https://t.co/g3GYop3Tzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne It's too funny. I love it. Have you ever even been to Africa? You are ours and we are keeping you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minha vó ontem me mandou uma mensagem de voz falando q uma menina do centro espírita parece mto comigo, mas ela é m… https://t.co/0pB9KZ47mc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @DonaldJTrumpJr Junior tries his Dad’s outrageous deflection tweets, but they just fall flat. He t… https://t.co/JQEm2ukg7f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanalda Will Arlene ever kindly grace us as a guest as I’m rediscovering her ‘From the Bronx’ audio book?… https://t.co/DlbCpSlWKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantasy Suites and Women Tell All – The Bachelor https://t.co/up7KRttbUy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorkmanEric @Rosie Of course he does. That way he can get back to running his corrupt company and sleeping with Putin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secret stairs led by Tour Guide @adamboggs_bts 🛤 #hike #secretstairs #hollywood #hollywoodland 📸 chrissihernandez @… https://t.co/zuHDNizge1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Para de mamar. Las calificadoras no califican la corrupción pinche ignorante, califican decisiones económicas, algo… https://t.co/l5M76ZVLkW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Coffeeshop#NYC#motivation @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/DXx9ysjRC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Cummings is a man with a soul unlike the GOP. He will hear his name called out from the book of the Lamb on ju… https://t.co/o1Pk6oAMix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBJohansen @SundlingJH @Sundling_Burton @Rachbland @StuartRPaddock Interesting! Ha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xan_desanctis I understand if you’ve never been in this situation it seems monstrous. But if I believe I put my tw… https://t.co/dTqGwNDb9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[KC Moms Blog night out at Top Golf. Sarah is such a pro @ Topgolf https://t.co/NC8ULENqcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckyUF @CMFord24 @4thegatorgood @Rob_Dodd @C_Robbins97 @CJ_Clarke1 @SeanSteed Awwww thank you 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenwearmouth So what’s been going on on your special day any exciting gifts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When a #snowday gets called at night so you stay up late perfecting your closet door #dunk! 😂🏀@scttrmac https://t.co/J6X9J03R7T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I had a very large bug bite on the back of my neck that unfortunately didn’t end up being a bug bite but inst… https://t.co/X6HYStvXbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TossUrOwnSalad Forgot about the vitamix!! That’s on the counter. Food processor and juicer are in a cabinet. And i… https://t.co/ZOTYxTdpEw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leighmlorien And then the next thing you know you're pouring all your time into your etsy shop and you haven't fin… https://t.co/3P5oLpDAXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[well, I mean I can do it for my job but I could never do it about Sacred Scripture]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the Oscars are finally over we can start preparing for the Met Gala!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SSherylyn @PS26Travis @ps68si1 @Ps78Stapleton @PS54si @Ps316S @PS11SI @PS44ShineOn @ps5huguenot @PS41R @ps65si… https://t.co/1zEHGqhh4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyTucker_Wyo interested in a friendly wager?? Sabres win, Pendleton on me. Hawks win, Titos on you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Big Idea:  The ones whom you love the most can hurt you the most. Love them anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[omfg while sitting here waiting for this stupid mon to spawn a car just went by and blew through every red light se… https://t.co/aRPFjZbPKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CynthiaNewman Thank you for standing up against #ReligiousDiscrimination You are right.Being pro traditional marri… https://t.co/1oI35xeUer]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beach #keepingBeachesClean #cleanBeachesBitches #leaveNatureBe #followforfollowback #instapicture #instagramers… https://t.co/Po4BB9w7jA]]></document></documents></author>