<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DayleSmithPhD @Anna_ohlala @ashtonpittman @MJMcKean also, his voting record was aligned republican all the way lea… https://t.co/SCa3HnnNSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Atlanta i need y’all to tune in at 12am Midnight #Callmeup will be aired on the radio!! 🎬🎬 @ Pennsylvania https://t.co/NYXgTh8x6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are lots of opportunities here at RBG to learn more about the invasive common carp and see the #Fishway in ac… https://t.co/MpOigURhbG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertAWiseman @CanadensisMax You see when you  make a comment that implies someone is too stupid to know what hap… https://t.co/Xmkd89M0xK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top of the morning 😉🙏🏿😛 another day another dollar 💵 remember I said it 😚😚😚😚😚😂🙏🏿😛 @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/FpayiEmNcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KidsDeserveIt Checking in late! Nathan here, 4th grade @CooperEagles260 inDerby KS.  #KidsDeserveIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man. Wonder how many people making a living from writing were powerfully inspired by #Tolkien. More than a few.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best triples I've had, thanks Ramsey. - Drinking a Belly Dance by BlackStack Brewing @ Ryan's Refuge  — https://t.co/EjOHvhKX9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshanejo87 #joshanejo #art #photography #love #belove #nature #findyourart #glitchart #glitchstockphoto #beach… https://t.co/BGOmz9mMnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[SORRY my #WelshTerrier Maddie just ate it "Madden 19 releases one more Michael Vick card"  https://t.co/EgOV9onvYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because the “Shape up or we’ll trade you to the #Browns” threat doesn’t have quite the same punch as it used to...… https://t.co/VjjHXPNrsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎵🎶Trust &amp; Obey...for There’s no other way...to be happy in Jesus...but to Trust &amp; Obey. 🎵🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite part is when the little Uber car slides sideways across buildings on the map. Wheee!! 🚙]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy is so full of shit. He spent 8 years dismantling the Green tech and renewable energy progs @Ted_Strickland… https://t.co/8IE9hFhjpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueJaysFan1532 @Cooper2Timez @SupercrossLIVE @MonsterEnergy @cooperwebb_2 @KTMUSA Oh yea he won San Diego as well… https://t.co/fZDclNZ22i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StarbucksCanada So today after a couple of 📱 calls and some emails I finally received the bonus ⭐️’s that should h… https://t.co/cA7sbJ1DW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[who gave my 9 year old sister a phone and who let her harass me when i don’t remember her roblox password . https://t.co/LK06Amv0fh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Broker’s Open House. Friday, February 15- 11am to 2pm.  $1,399,000 20312 Strelna Place, Woodland Hills  Stunning si… https://t.co/lclWGMfd5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first official assist with @Vol_Baseball.  Thanks to @SeanBarows for allowing me to help straighten out some of… https://t.co/hpYRdzQYe0]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Dixon BBB plays Trask tonight in Coastal 8 semifinal. Here’s highlights from Bulldogs’ win Tuesday.… https://t.co/Z4Ny8oVje6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jennydan26 @CassandraRules Oh no, a panel where she wasn’t even sharing the guy’s views. What a total shock and scare!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbrannanarchive @tomscott 🤣🤣🤣🤣 I’m flying a friend to Edinburgh next month and soon I’ll have enough miles again t… https://t.co/kKOMNCzKLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[15 games left! LETS GO CANES! #ohsaycanyousee #nationalanthemsinger 🇺🇸 #ohcanada 🇨🇦 @ PNC Arena https://t.co/OZak9spbwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@newmsportscards @CardConnector Might as well make cards out of it he couldn’t hit with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unless It Changes, Capitalism Will Starve Humanity By 2050 via @forbes https://t.co/nFXElpDJV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SL1733 @ruth_moyer @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @senatemajldr @SteveScalise @DevinNunes @Jim_Jordan @GOPLeader @VP… https://t.co/cFq81YE65j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisTye3 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ldrrn04 @IlhanMN https://t.co/GRnWN1Laaa #IStandWithIllhan it’s not anti Semitic to criticize a war criminal soooo… https://t.co/qPETTqJBSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomjwebb A worthy endeavour perhaps we can brainstorm a solution during the next deep-sea expedition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND THAT’S 2,000!!!  @SolehiSpartans senior Olivia Snyder drills a 3-pointer with 4:50 left to surpass 2,000 career… https://t.co/voypqHPcid]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally choked up reading this, it means a lot to have hardwork recognized. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bmorrisonusm @SouthernMissMBB So happy to meet you and enjoyed watching the Game and THE TEAM beating ODU! #SMTTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How blessed are those who observe His testimonies, Who seek Him with all their heart. Psalms 119:2 NASB https://t.co/Al014BFHX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenBeschloss @SenFeinstein - question - when do you start listening to constituents rather than massive PACs? Y… https://t.co/nMUoGaJemM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max is a freakin’ saint. A truly compassionate and empathetic human being.  #NakedAndAfraid]]></document><document><![CDATA['Pay your rent and stay in your bum ass place' is probably my favorite Nicki bar to date 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertbenzie @reggcohn @TorontoStar @OntarioPCParty How can premier ford say he’s looking out For workers one just… https://t.co/uFeLuIPrC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[egyszer egy sárkány 🐲 egyszer egy kyrájlány 👸 💕🎶  https://t.co/LfQDZUqdqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajajaja el discurso de "wey mamo al rival porque no soy fanático"  me da un vergo de risa, no es de a huevo… https://t.co/6t4ImJrMwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chirinos gives up a pair of HRs to RF. #Orioles and #Rays tied 3-3, T5. Ricardo Pinto is warming in the pen. Chirin… https://t.co/vwF7wrVAj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAMSCORECREW @robert_carder @TherealHaas2 @NationPenguins @NHL In the end I will always take Crosby (slight bias b… https://t.co/qSTijwRm0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[First sheepshead! Fisherbae is getting better, @chrissyisf out-fished me today! @ Jensen Beach, Florida https://t.co/FKjINwyFBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I work with the same 9 ppl everyday. I know they’re names, their spouses names, their kids names, their weeken… https://t.co/N3lUBpzSTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hinrichfdn @StephenOlsonHF @Diplomat_APAC @UNCTAD @USTradeRep #TariffsAreTaxes https://t.co/P3ht673DmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two new members of the family. Arrived this morning. https://t.co/hPlAIeWp0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was that Saturday night live No it was Wednesday morning An very bad script writing But we all were forced to watch… https://t.co/bvnnYRXo4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxxxy27 @SpeakerPelosi @JussieSmollett Media divides country with constant lies and false narratives. Obama set division up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox Back before the country was flooded with low skilled illegal aliens and collapsed the wages, people co… https://t.co/BqZxO7rTv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your smart decisions , your bright future. #invest #realestate #realtor #orlandorealtor #orlando #florida… https://t.co/Q6URkxZgUo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RayMaraj @ChallengeTea411 @iammikeyp You will all will be disappointed when you see it. Not even close to as bad a… https://t.co/RNyk6iyEc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnG927 @MarshaPatriot @joey_beavers @Brenderm1 @Maggieb1B @ArmyOfTrump1 @OutOfRegister @PauWitkowski… https://t.co/huJxkN7OT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The average 16 year old has literally no sense of what the real world is like, u are on crack if you think they should vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s great! Go team!  You deserve a reward for all the miles you’ve traveled already!  And for good stories!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SF_BrodieHurtad I guess it sort of worked, I mean work sucks, but I think normally I’d be a lot more pissed off no… https://t.co/t3fLYmuXTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters Duh, Mueller can’t just get up and say, “the Republicans have been right all along this was a fraudulent i… https://t.co/Jv6M3NXdrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soft capture achieved at 05:51 EST, 04:51 CST, 03:51 MST, 02:51 PST, and 10:51 UTC.  #spacex #crewdragon #nasa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hughhewitt Bro since when has it been that it’s cool to be repub and know the @FBI?  Huh?  Mueller is Repub.  he a… https://t.co/z45LBRjlBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excelente, no pierda la perspectiva de la realidad nacional. En Colombia hay miles de problemas aún sin solución y… https://t.co/hIr7un9ujd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ADESA Charlotte - @adesaauction in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/Jw6h1z2RSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keydrep901 The lrg wasn’t bad but y’all was always wrong for them fat leg ass levis 💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Statements made out of ignorance quickly gain the approval of the ignorant. Don’t be ignorant, know truth, be freed by it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man arrested in connection with slaying of 11-year-old Inglewood boy in 1990 cold case: A 50-year-old man was charg… https://t.co/AZ1vDQLUYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanJorEl looking forward to reading First 30 Days! Good read this morning from @CharlotteFive about @CLTDadsGroup. Appreciate ya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 1924, hundreds of Filipino soldiers in the U.S. Army mutinied, because they weren't receiving the same pay as white soldiers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Allen is dealing with hip soreness per Helton. Hope to have him (and Dominic Davis) back after spring break]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome : FaceTiming with my sister and my 7 month old niece in NY   Not Awesome : My niece pulling my sisters hair… https://t.co/cX9pjWtGnd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inclement weather plan tomorrow for @siloamassembly .  If you feel safe coming we’ll be there.  #aplaceofhope https://t.co/U04tDNsu55]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a difficult first year living in the city.  This journey was a necessary one for me to grow and evolve in… https://t.co/SEiyTtBrgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary  #thingsDanielthinks #Twitter https://t.co/1Qys9nnQJ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cartwright2 I used to feel like this regularly. Thankfully I discovered #Carnivory Lost all my lifelong depression… https://t.co/ADLLVXeSSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyManMyMelo @OnlyInBOS @grovehall True. The Post Office says I live in Dorchester, but most maps tell me I live in… https://t.co/YIV6La7lux]]></document><document><![CDATA[No porqué siempre se esté sonriendo, significa que uno esté bien por dentro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before graduating from a National Blue Ribbon High School, I nearly lost my life as a victim of gang violence.… https://t.co/gD0XomEwmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep. Krishnamoorthi (D) on Using El Chapo’s Money to Pay for Border Security Deal: ‘Why Not?’ via @freebeacon… https://t.co/P4w2Zb0Ggn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/aPU9860yNR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepHaleyStevens Proud to be in the front row, tuned in!  Thanks for representing #MI11 so well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[FED UP IN NEWRO: Still No School Budget, No Plans to Present One https://t.co/NuQZfo5Qkw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentee Dan Li describes the "Arti Hurria" effect on his career. #DrHurriasLight https://t.co/4ASy0cO4nr]]></document><document><![CDATA[they: "so you're telling me you're not interested because we host with godaddy and you have to use ftp to update th… https://t.co/SoCKa0650u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rogerwaters hey u pompous pos,  what nationality are u?The English have more blood on their hands then most Countr… https://t.co/B2n6MfKro2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trumpy my pal. Just say the words "Economic" and "Powerhouse" when you tweet about my boy Kim dawg… https://t.co/C9wSOXJysj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CW_Arrow redefined what superhero TV can do with epic storytelling, fantastic characters and gripping action. Way… https://t.co/6O4AxK6LAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewillbaldauf  in progress @ Erie Art Gallery https://t.co/QuUgpx0HUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attaboy, Trevor.   Now take that blueprint to the ink shop to make it permanent, my steel-gutted brother #AllIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelseyycm @lukebrown_6415 @teal_colby @mak_enzie0 @DrLeanaWen https://t.co/9q5cpJUmI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the last 7 days parts of the South got a foot of rain! Wow! @DanManWX @danpeckwx @SamWnek @Ginger_Zee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smfehir Dad abused Mom,Dad internationally embarrassed Canada, Dad gave Canadians the finger https://t.co/HprYOIbY32]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEET @DJSCREAM THE CAMPION NIGGA WE EINNIN SALUTE THE A1 MOVEMENT I GOTO PLUTO THATS A SIGN THAT MY ICE ALL REAL @WILLAFOOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wthisagigawatt Netflix raised fees because it is becoming more expensive for them to exist - as you said just as t… https://t.co/6qRpqq5r8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graffitiwriter1 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @grafitiwriter1 Are they wearing costumes so the FBI doesn't recognize them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBrookhiser Once the pact was signed such a song would have had to wait for BARBAROSSA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a pity these people can’t be turned against capitalism but that’s why they get for not coming to Happy Hour at… https://t.co/9AEkBUyFWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[“He is more a fat white slug. A Jabba the Hutt of privilege. And worse, he is that most unforgivable of all things… https://t.co/C4yfHPDsey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s the poll about dipping your scrambled eggs in ketchup with your hands?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rodriguez @JimCameron @AlitaMovie Just got out of #AlitaBattleAngel A new sci-fi classic! Loved it!!! Now Robert,… https://t.co/KgixrRWfQK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get to know one of our software developers, Sean Widmer! Sean is discussing the power of ALMobile’s approving capab… https://t.co/ZxQ5rHBSHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking this coffee so slow this am! My cousin was like damn  you act like you won’t get anymore 🤣🤣🤣 #coffeeplease… https://t.co/a89XE2NrOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer A tax refund is the government returning money to you because they took too much from you during the pr… https://t.co/wMZXfjAbLS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hopevacc I am   and I can’t stress this enough  VERY disappointed I can’t retweet this for the masses]]></document><document><![CDATA[One awesome thing about the @usopen was how easy it is to buy/sell get last minute tickets on Ticketmaster app. At… https://t.co/cPEohYipMs]]></document></documents></author>