<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Had the best captain ever on @united flight 15 from Heathrow! Put everybody in a great mood!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZumbawithCat @mrsmaris "Sweety" is neither sexist nor gross, It's affectionate! Age has given me a clear understan… https://t.co/9RjBBybSrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IServeCoffee  Crossroads of the #Coffee industry at the @nationalcoffee  #DrinkCoffeeEarlyAndOften… https://t.co/b747ZF83yN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmeliaRayno Some good frinds have spent the past week in Belize. They go there regularly and love it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathleenVelas11 @seanhannity Partially true also, the economy is booming due in part in part to the corporate tax… https://t.co/GdnbM9TVLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[You sent pick and choose when to hide behind what the constitution says !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[and the Jussie Smollett hoax backfired on them badly. The Christine Blasey Ford fantasy is taking on water rapidly.… https://t.co/cV3ZCw8D87]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrandgar @victoraraiza You arent gonna force ppl into coming but their outreach needs to be larger. Difficult to… https://t.co/Hg7jE2HTjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tuckahoetommy Little extra love for someone who gives you 30 million guaranteed for no real reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time tasting bourbon and rye at @whiskeyacres make sure you have Lisa makes some drinks from her “secret” men… https://t.co/IjaY1CXsAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dangers of the trending keto diet https://t.co/dNnoioJKPO via @TullahomaNews   This article is a lie. #keto @KenDBerryMD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all’s parents didn’t make you get a job the day you turned 16 and it SHOWS. My GOD it SHOWS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[52 of 365 ————————————————— A very special opportunity was presented to me recently that has now come to fruition.… https://t.co/yEZYw6RRwI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllenKate14 I'm glad at least one people ok Twitter can match my energy on this 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gfstarr1 It’s supposed to be say “who has the second best uniforms in the AL east?” they forgot a key word. They a… https://t.co/tlhyShHXDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Actions speak louder than your tweets. So far, your tweets about automobile companies or air-condi… https://t.co/zoA5hkVKbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDeDomenico @sgallman96 @SteveScalise sorry to hear about (True tho) Trudeau sorry that most governments or of… https://t.co/UTexWO2SEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump is accused of Russian collusion, then it must be true but if Obama was accused of the same from the republ… https://t.co/jCmsmOi77J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmfishbowlcom @andyhre I also am curious on the booster take.. you can’t reallocate restricted funds from boosters… https://t.co/1b3Af6AQXE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had a constant raging headache for a month now someone put me out of my misery]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brhodes What do you know about this plan Benny?  Were you in on the Ohr Aug 2016 meeting where he advised you guys… https://t.co/VmccKAWK7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good educators are heroes, angels &amp; a powerful force of change. Show an educator some love today. Shout out to:… https://t.co/LQd32gCQi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum Just watched your interview with Tim Tebow. Really enjoyed it. Very entertaining. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a guy you know you’ve got a best friend if you guys get into a fight and start beating the shit out of ea… https://t.co/eqDlpJ4WkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neddy montes with his second huge match of the day, this time bumping up to 182 and getting the pin in 1:16 to put west Sioux up 18-9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last bottle. The beer is great, but the memories of a really fun day are even better. - Drinking a Mornin' Delight… https://t.co/erB7HzxJzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emeraldireland1 You law breaker! Using a straw! How devious you are!😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonDavies Oh Don wrong argument. Just show Canadians you'll be better than this mess. He is a disaster on his own]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsTranceyPants @nowthisnews @BernieSanders We are https://t.co/k1gIONHTEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GQMagazine Maybe time to retract your rather abrasive, and frankly EVIL wrong article here. At least the title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinMcKnight37 He was 7-31 last night, in a game to clinch an outright title.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never dull moment. Dogs being dogs got in a scrap and I got hit as it tried to intervene and pull them apart.  Hope… https://t.co/AubtZhYKKj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone on Trump's side of the fence put out the same proposals they would be accused of plagiarism by the lefti… https://t.co/kuU5dUHcAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t even question the foul count when your opponent out hustles you, out plays you and puts the ball in the littl… https://t.co/u4Rfzw7sHQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DixieNadine @globalnews does anyone find it odd we got three more amber alerts the morning after the child was alr… https://t.co/J1z7w3ye60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VillalobosE @Iwori07 @ConsultaPara @PartidoMorenaMx @PRI_Nacional @AccionNacional @VicenteFoxQue @FelipeCalderon P… https://t.co/ziIyC3Xt2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chilling with Littlebank! @ The Bigbank Mansion! https://t.co/IFKHwgaWD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Spoaty Oaty by @AMBrewery at @hmshost — https://t.co/FFFgmOM6o1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Other than the night he was in the ring with @RealMelina this is the other night I envied @RandyOrton in at #11 the… https://t.co/4nAVRTraPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_barillas @WGNNews You can blame Trump for everything and anything apparently! 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaggartRehnn @Riopedre31 @someone_1958 @JonAnthony7 @chance4gardener @woodywood1999 @MichaelZaker1 @wolflayla420… https://t.co/STo2bwR2e2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FilamentFrenzy @joeltelling @MatterHackers @monoprice @Kijaidesign @makersmuse Honestly it's been pretty good on t… https://t.co/9xBf7oI9fK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at American Airlines Catering Facility in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/Cxov9oe90e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sad to see my friend David Preciado leave as the Consul of Mexico here in Fresno. I’m proud of the great partne… https://t.co/6sz7bGN5Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amber_Marshall @CBC @HeartlandOnCBC Heading out to do my “Chore Board” before sun up. The things we do for our “Fur Babies” 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fred_TheSavage @TalentedSlacker @MichaelKeaton https://t.co/vhvWCqcGc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The oldschool is dead. I CANNOT. 😭#TheChallange33 https://t.co/J3S3OB6hFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenacallest @ABurgos1706 DON HUGO YA PASARON LAS ELECCIONES Y PERDIO POR PIJIADA HELLO NO HABRA SEGUNDA VUELTA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria and I at the St Francis de Sales Mardi Gras auction. Good food, good friends and good times. @ St Francis De… https://t.co/LfzRGDtVvr]]></document><document><![CDATA[juice wrld is easily my favorite artist as of rn. idc that y’all made some of his music mainstream i’m mostly talki… https://t.co/eSkxiZLgxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do other designers notice the smallest imperfections in their work that no one else notices? @TKDesignz @kevinc_sr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayday22 I can’t make anything stick for a week, much less 3 1/2 months!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are the only school in the Treasure Valley with a Jumbotron. Got to pay for it somehow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, we all know about Dick Cheney and how many wars we can thank him for. Go bird hunting Mr VP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/jWsHpDEGac]]></document><document><![CDATA[That @mulaney opening monologue was hilarious. Maybe I'm late to the thing. Goodnight.  @nbcsnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philsturgeon @apisyouwonthate Done and done! But I keep trying to PUT the tires on the jet and it looks like it's DELETE-ing them?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stalking is when two people go for a romantic walk together but only one of them knows about it...  • • • •… https://t.co/Ebr1ILUfGv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I woke up out of a dead sleep and thought of something I didnt do at work and now I’m annoyed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@totallyrad_liz Haha yeah that’s not a good thing at the same time but oh well 🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avec un neuf c’est différent @jheyraud prolonge stp https://t.co/cfCmDA6O0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[A nice 5am pre-surgery #sotd yoresh_pottery shave bowl 💈 @omegabrush boat brush 💈 nancyboyinc shave cream 💈 gillett… https://t.co/nh0S4VVIwp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing down to our competition yet again, and getting outworked by a college team.. Torts switching the lines all… https://t.co/BcWq5xLbge]]></document><document><![CDATA[During halftime of the Lehighton 5/6 Grade Travel teams game, the entire Tamaqua team came out to play ball 🏀 with… https://t.co/ka20RUFx8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew? Great tool for sometimes small and/or incomplete biopsies...#pedipath]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markdpfan @SICKBASTARD3 @ProgRockGrandad @basiajarecka1 @Holloway_girl @vinylofilo @ingercarola @Lady_Rock_11… https://t.co/4qyYygyv7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ethanalcorn7 @DYoungRivals @CoachKlanderman @isiah_childs @amyd0120 #EMAW20]]></document><document><![CDATA[After taking an L earlier this week, my roommates and I finally took our first collective academic L together 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias Amigo! Appreciate the kind review.  @realvision is an amazing format and talking to @ttmygh for an hour wou… https://t.co/JbykBlPlhx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincentmel @FOX29philly @BGordonFox29 That’s what we did all morning.  We said in every report that waste manageme… https://t.co/q9tEYTg6XA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amedgarces @CarlaMorotoli @ADemocratica Todas las élites de todos los países, desde que se inventaron los países a… https://t.co/1XIaM64Pe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Mision Marielena Hotel Cuatro Cienegas in Cuatro Cienegas https://t.co/IaDQRr6uyo]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few thoughts after this morning's 1-hr commute. ⚫ As daily-driveable as a 911. ⚫ Impressive, unbothered ride qual… https://t.co/zdE2XtPzdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tebow15believer @AprilLaJune Don't we get to keep illegals out who (some) are killing Americans in your world?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting in @HarvardIOP on @AndrewGillum’s class; his guest speaker today: @MsLaToshaBrown  With my good friend, for… https://t.co/CYbhnHSvdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I could see it Right from the start Right from the start That you would be Be my light in the dark Light in the… https://t.co/WCZlV3Kr86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jomar0383 @DonJuanitoTopo @GraficoTigres @MLS Por lo que gana aqui y en la ciudad que vive debe estar feliz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mount Si gets the win over Curtis punching its ticket in the championship.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Johnnycake @cadej4686 . @cadej4686 @Badassgreaser @sodabitx @GreenLuffy26 https://t.co/KAGFjmLuyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PattyJenks @GalGadot Classy and talented ladies! thank you for your examples of promoting positive and empowered m… https://t.co/KmkZn0BtaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EntrenamientoDeCiclismoDeSalón jueves 8 am #OverTrainFitness #WeAreOverTrain #LaCasaDeLosCampeones… https://t.co/t6ucawEXQy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomrollman @seatimespreps His family moved so nothing illegal but I hear you. He did start there his freshman year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The drink @ASoloski and I had this summer was super fun and illuminating]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just chillin by the space heater. @ Boothwyn, Pennsylvania https://t.co/gH3inDF322]]></document><document><![CDATA[@romanmars Dude  It used to work   Pre 12 iOS upgrade   Then   It   Stopped   Cc @tim_cook]]></document><document><![CDATA[#epic #failures https://t.co/7qIxFGO8wp #Jesus #Christ #God #Spirit #Faith #love #grace #poem #prayer #hope… https://t.co/sAoGavS62b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I’ve practically got kick in the arse by Don Juan, all I want is mint chocolate chip ice cream #kthanksbye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dad2136 @Rifleman4WVU @AllProAnalytics Murray won’t make it either.  Grier is the best most well Rounded in this d… https://t.co/knFAXkWZM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GordonVoit It's JV.. until they develop a JV state title process, no need for 4OT to determine a "winner". Everyon… https://t.co/Iq6i64h3dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbehre @DanClarkSports Why would he need to go there? He knew the Orioles were dirt and not going anywhere, esp wi… https://t.co/Z6TSf2wFTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[100T beginning to look very scary. 4 wins in a row and CWL Forth Worth around the corner...]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most egregious cases of #GOP #electionfraud in recent memory was just verified in #NorthCarolina.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One more arturia_official #minibrute 2s jam before I practice my #dungeonsynth set for the show at @Towerbarsd on T… https://t.co/12vobokZ2u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EshwarEswaran @RomeenSheth @_waleedshahid @AOC @BillNye Inequality is growing and the American people have woken u… https://t.co/IlUmE9ZIZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dancing your Wedding night away with Red Bottom Shoes!!!  Tashana and Eric were fierce on the floor!!! . . . . . .… https://t.co/pJuVEmIflI]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I don’t leave you on read in the middle of the convo just know I care]]></document><document><![CDATA[While archiving some 📼I found an old #AirThisSideOfCaution show at @MetroChicago that I’d never seen https://t.co/1nUT3vvGTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the pleasure of catching a little #baseball with @sarahmichele5 in #tampa this week #springtraining2019… https://t.co/N0pp1Ur1KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beelovermegs I retook a placement test and I got placed into Algebra one from Pre-calc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OohMyNose @BrettHamil @HowardSchultz Uh, yeah, if you're a Republican or Libertarian. Or just an idiot who wants t… https://t.co/dgF6VmHBkG]]></document></documents></author>