<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DKPghSports @Dejan_Kovacevic @dlolley_pgh @HunterAHomistek @mattsunday @CarterCritiques @btsteelcurtain… https://t.co/jDGvu0f83n]]></document><document><![CDATA[What friends do. Keep your head and chin up and always push your way through your obstacles. I know sometimes it's… https://t.co/E5CEPRJaGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We have now gone from “Russian collusion” to “Emoluments” and I’m sure all these people shouting i… https://t.co/gnKSmiCNlT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The car in front of me in the Taco Bell line just opened the door, got out, and shot gunned a beer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVDemForum @cupw @CanadianLabour @cupenat @jcallaghan2 @Tony_Tracy @JohnOCAP @tonimaca @FTT_np @neatsie66… https://t.co/5C9whNOdqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timkawakami everyone on the bench has shown flashes of solid/good play say you get a good game from each one on a… https://t.co/3ozqzjd3R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScienceIsMetal I think Bill and Ted used it differently?  Memory is fading though]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time he shuffles the card into the deck. I ask him if he knows about the dangers of time travel. No he says. A… https://t.co/Lkdku9nD0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[did this bitch just try to justify the genocide of native americans?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hope_Carter @beysgiselle I agree with this statement, mine is just a fun exaggerated version of this. In my eyes B… https://t.co/IGXY67oLka]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glad to be able to get in work on these rainy days. @ByrnesRebelGolf https://t.co/pGmUMK9QuS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I killed another person in the ring.... ALLEGEDLY! 🔫 https://t.co/kivCXZK5PC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying LA tonight with a long overdue date night with the wife. It's been years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SotehPR You make a good point. Trout will be 29 when he goes FA. Still think the starting bid is $350m.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watch Ant-Man for the second time last night. It's way better than I remembered even though it's still a lot like Iron Man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALGhammer I believe we all just watched an episode of corner gas, this episode tells the story of an idiot under i… https://t.co/VY5NSMLQns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve done so much research on this topic that I’m changing my middle name to Gerrymandering. I think it will flow n… https://t.co/VrAtZuB3Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@COL_EJERCITO @mluciaramirez @IvanDuque @infopresidencia @FuerzasMilCol @mindefensa @COMANDANTE_EJC @Ejercito_Div4… https://t.co/UiaCPRutdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just binged “More Than An Athlete” on @espn + - feeling incredibly inspired.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh I enjoy watching @McJuggerNuggets and @Lance210 but why not just say y'all are gonna be collabing together to d… https://t.co/28FxdtjXIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnHeilbron @StonyBrookMBB @StonyBrookWBB Understand the commitment for sure, but how can you be so flat against Binghamton at home?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our series continues: Big Jewish Question On My Mind: Where Am I Complicit in Perpetuating Bias?… https://t.co/LjVDHXg5Vu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take My Heart ( You Can Have it If You Want It) Kool &amp; Gang (JB &amp;The R... WATCH https://t.co/zTNO6a6Dh1 via… https://t.co/N8T9HdSWbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Show off -&gt; @jeancase   Get your CD's off the table   They aren't coasters   Get on the BUS 🎟🚌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AxaltaRacing @AlexBowman88 @WilliamByron @LibertyU https://t.co/409UP7hWjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Mardi Gras, here’s one of the most inspirational songs I know. Written shortly after Hurricane Katrina… https://t.co/jB8sr9I6gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JAGERSLAYER @AprilDawnR1974 @wolfast @freefanaddict @Doucette82 @IfIwassomething @Original_king79 @Pastabowl2… https://t.co/LCW09xJZht]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would you thrive in a role crafting and deploying a sustained, high-quality facilities services program for our Nor… https://t.co/O5gZ7bCRUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[They are building a Target   Literally right across from my house..  I’m be too grand for you wal mart shoppin ass hoes lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealTayRoc Goodz tried every vet move in the book....and it didn't work lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s nothing like telling someone you aren’t leaving your parking spot and watching them drive off all frustrated 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great talk by @developerxio on machine learning in JS kicking off my #developerweek2019 experience! Great audience engagement too 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homosmakemepuke @seanhannity I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy… https://t.co/mjcKHRnsoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@burnside4141 @skicrestedbutte @AdaptiveCB Saw the video. Looked like y'all were having a blast.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Indianapolis International Airport - @indairport in Indianapolis, IN https://t.co/80kMmCMdgG]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lM9pkViJiz Dry for any evening plans today but showers will be around during the morning on Friday. Mi… https://t.co/tkfoLViquW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This story seems extra relevant tonight... https://t.co/jDfF4n5bT4 https://t.co/Atm7gsynKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday score! Shout out to my social-media-defiant lil sis for making it happen #hearmeRohr #universalchrist… https://t.co/tyh0VlRcx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[repprosports ... x king gang x meech x @dwyanewade 💪🏾 @ One Last Dance https://t.co/9ChLFvBBdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoiraiOW Yeah, I'm not a huge fan of TPP. It has its uses, but like you said, free cam is the significantly better option!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggamejames36 @IraSchoffel 200 is a magic number that unlocks another ball, then it turns into a big game of halfcourt knockout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danidonovan It scared me to hear nothing but quiet. I didn’t know how to handle locking in like that. It felt obse… https://t.co/ZjJ3J6v37N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t dumb, I know what you thinking. This dude (me) is a sucker.  Give me a chance and I’ll prove you wrong. I’v… https://t.co/onfgAYPSbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American left and right continue to do significant damage to victims of sexual viloence, both men and women.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EnglishBob1 @AliceLfc4 @brecollier @FlatBack_Four @binkymarsh29 @DanteFlorence @Peej_Jones @TheAnalog_Kid… https://t.co/vkCUMOz5SE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarmenYulinCruz @BernieSanders @Latinos4Bernie Este idiota no sabe lo que habla.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreasuryMog @TreasuryMog , Vice Lt Governor Boogie of all Animal Affairs in Nevada is gathering all world Educatio… https://t.co/9MrliQaLcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for the perfect ring for that perfect person? Your search is over! Check out brilliantearth for some of the… https://t.co/HModcbe78r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Free_236 @Drdanks49 I’ll definitely let you know when we make our way down to Murrs dude!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilsonFrontier @StaticWarpBubbl The guy that responded to your post on “Just Star Trek”’s tweet calling DSC a step… https://t.co/kYlTlwWTjz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cenewman0 Eek. I rode out an EF-3 or 4 in my roommate’s bathtub in our 3rd floor cardboard college apartment with… https://t.co/AGaoRUH2Jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last Call was one of Kanye's most slept on songs by far.  #Yeezy #SundayService]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PStalpes51 Thats like saying Giroud wasnt consistently the most average striker in the top 6 tho for years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manriquehector Propongo que ya habian miles de razones mas que suficientes para que salgamos y acabemos con esta vaina!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Halfway through #DPC19 and it’s still trending! Gonna be tough to overtake the Trump stuff on the national trending list though...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateWr That last tweet could stand in for @culanth’s mission statement! Thanks for this far-seeing perspective and… https://t.co/a8n1vmCow6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“When the legislative and executive powers are united in the same person or in the same body of magistrates, there… https://t.co/nnOVXuDBBW]]></document><document><![CDATA[STARTERS VS NON STARTERS: Do not root against your own teammates for your own benefit. Negativity, inwardly or outw… https://t.co/UJjq4Pl5Vp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WineInBlonde @dubblecounter Yep it’s 57 right now in #FtLauderdale - PERFECT TEMP for storing #RedWine 🍷In a bit -… https://t.co/yhBIi2JoIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I been meaning to ask, what is going on with Britney and why is no one worried or asking? #AccessLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitMarieox He has a degree in mechanical engineering from Cornell (Ivy League). She’s a US congresswoman (which m… https://t.co/3IPkqorVHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@houston_trill98 Help a kid out though I’m flying to Houston and may shoot all the cool spots to go to]]></document><document><![CDATA[gonna get you to tee-hee. Sydney is a Tumblr user who has been posting her text conversations with her mother onlin… https://t.co/OSXAkNDDFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still not over this trip!!! Not sure I ever will be. ❤️ #brothers #nature #optoutside #grandcanyon #hiking #explore… https://t.co/YaHtTnIECV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @Todd_Gutner temp in Topsham is 8 we have clear skies and no wind. Hope you have a great day and  weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@23Tressa Did you send me this one? One of my faves. https://t.co/K2pmOQMXai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chatelainedc @HeerJeet @Patbagley The history of Mostly F and D- ratings from the NRA, voting for the assault weap… https://t.co/KAgCUmfavj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this. Bob Dylan’s “Tangled Up In Blue” explored.. https://t.co/NvWNfj2lSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ziggysmith1415 @Martina Good brother! Yep, Wimbledon is the biggest of the majors.  @Martina absolutely owned, "Th… https://t.co/I4TQ2ZdDbv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickedPictures @WCA_Reviews I wish I could believe her.  But her support of SESTA/FOSTA makes me question her intentions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Airess @LLinWood @realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @RealJamesWoods I'm still waiting for mine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine if the Knicks are able develop Frank’s offensive game to resemble  Khris Middleton’s game!!! 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plattsburgh Cloverleaf Plattsburgh on 5/6/18 https://t.co/9s4ShiPx31 https://t.co/0QpdqwK7Zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wiser words were never spoken...the Coach is worth the pain, @EricOligny]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Your off the wall the planet is gonna change no matter what it is evolving as it spins the polar ice ca… https://t.co/psE84Owyqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump : are you finally announcing that Mexico will pay for the wall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chase anyone else have issues with Chase rewards or Chase support team  .. in responsive is the theme . https://t.co/NLzYIpTMRt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Criterion @nyrbclassics I'd like to win these. Count me in. #BerlinAlexanderplatz]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are on day 5 is the longest stretch so far don't let me f*** it up @emmyFbabyyy  at least give me a text or some… https://t.co/lzVeCskLoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cincyredsteve @McAdamsJustin @Jamieblog @baseball_ref @Reds Good move my man you don’t need that negativity on you… https://t.co/IRuL2KNmiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap it is cold here! (@ Mammoth Lakes, CA in CA) https://t.co/EWPWuMUD45 https://t.co/tQAByA7bgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrLeanaWen You lobby to kill the most innocent of human beings who have no say in being torn/ripped apart like a u… https://t.co/4cqTDGNnGL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast checking out this #VR game but can't remember the name. Help!  It's like #BeatSaber but much more full… https://t.co/1F2xAcVxjL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sampled some of my DNA and used PCR (polymerase chain reaction) to cut (and replicate) a small segment of it that… https://t.co/0sRopddaXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_ballin @KaylaAndersonTV I will NOT get betting advice from you sir lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright @BrianWFoster, I finished up Wolves of Calla today...I thought going in that this was gonna be the “lull” b… https://t.co/SIg0r9SYCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhsrangerbsb It’s Time!!!!!  Get after it fellas! #B4L #RangerPride https://t.co/pyuFrgLcWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Db406Dustin @VeldaMcConnell2 @codeofvets @Lrihendry Might want to look at Flint, Michigan. I grew up in Minneapoli… https://t.co/ci4LzRBscD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't deny it, you've been waiting on me to post a cat pic https://t.co/m64vWpbign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson @DemRN1974 Kneeling next to each other in Federal Prison as the suck big fat meaty hate cock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Watch👇🏾 “What Do U Mean”  (Official Music Video) Latest Single out now #linkinbio “SHINE” Prod. By @MontereyJakk… https://t.co/IR9xvUnOPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bertramschulte @SAP @SAPDigital Great team Bertram! Nice to see @RobertDNA in this photo, he's our brilliant "Tech… https://t.co/8gDABvJMXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leeleeb50 Frick Frigging Funny Fellatio Fart Fat Fisting Fishy Fringering Foolish Flagellating Freak Fleet Famous… https://t.co/oeoILh0iQX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos a orar por todos aquellos que están en los hospitales y clínicas sin electricidad en estos momentos. Niños, m… https://t.co/jw7Sec8I5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mini Vader &amp; Mini Mankind vs Mini Goldust &amp; Mascarita Sagrada Jr on WWF Raw 1997. Crowd loved these guys!!… https://t.co/FGnNZy9snd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyMcKinless If this happens, I will be holding you two responsible... @zacdayvis]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m soooooooooo beyond excited #lookatthosestops #royalcarribean #floridabeforehand https://t.co/szBGEg1FHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pataltschul I heard the premier will air sometime later this year. Ugh. Hoping sooner than later. @Pataltschul… https://t.co/PysQhgF4II]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember i couldn’t go a day without smoking I’m glad i broke that habit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__gabbymiller @mmfa Trump pays porn stars, not pawn star. Go home Rick.]]></document></documents></author>