<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir can someone tell someone in San Diego to put my misplaced bag in one of these flights to SFO? I did the… https://t.co/7fX5rxyHw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Gee Governor just tear down the walls and let the illegals all come into yours, Pelosi’s, Waters, Fein… https://t.co/4DvfIQT8Ai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holleyr It's like Christmas morning but with evidence. I need more covfefe before all this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JenniferBrody @victorlavalle We turned your room into an office, sorry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Feeding the never-ending, Mother-of-All-conspiracy theories that Trump is a Russian agent because Warner a… https://t.co/H4IhAzC9ip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb Black people are regular people, same as you &amp; I.  Meaning, they're not spared insults just because of their skin color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jraymer15 The things we do for our children! You are making great memories with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come #celebrate my #debutnovel #bookbirthday SKATER'S WALTZ turns 4 on 3.4.19 From 3/1-3/15 it's #onsale for… https://t.co/Ar1t8z7hZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sensational #saturday #butfirstcoffee #watchingmybabies #horses #coffeeholic #horsesinmybackyard #coffee… https://t.co/9Hvd60pzb0]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: Norfolk D.A. says man killed was Haki Sanders, 33.  Suspect Justin Gaston still at-large, considered armed… https://t.co/XAYPIbzSho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women Crush Wednesday by lifting weights! Wahoo! Thank you greatdaywash @kristenberset &amp; @super_markette… https://t.co/LDbmCdykqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDonnnieSharp @DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump Donnie you are very sharp dude  and you feed us with your words.  Thanks Deplorable. 🌴😎🌴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jay-Z is throwing another epic Oscars party https://t.co/1y0ZU3gjyU via @pagesix... If we had 1 1Oth of his Scratch… https://t.co/3yo6rTQS7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[In my line of work, you’re never told good job and it never seems like you’re appreciated and that shit really sucks 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[“You know what I’ve never needed at 51? Algebra.” 😂 Missy Grynkiewicz Hall has the room roaring. https://t.co/zb5pbA4poQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 years ago my left kidney went to live with my sister. Blood, liver, bone marrow can also be donated while you’re… https://t.co/afUFyFgGE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[’tis mighty fine here. celebrating @designlovefest’s impending love nuptials in laguna hoteljoaquin. i like it. i l… https://t.co/Y7cGVSURFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabigibson Good luck to my sweet friends at @ChampionCheerAS Hope y’all have safe travels and a great weekend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see @aaron_watson and @kyle_park tomorrow night and I don’t know when I was last this excited!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost rear end someone✅ Spill coffee all over myself✅ Leave computer charger at home✅ https://t.co/OK8Ju1aqbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day thereal_maryjblige @DJBEEBLACK 2019 Remix. #beeblackremix  #beeblackbeats  #maryjblige… https://t.co/t3jaMrFZvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in pole vault, there is a clinic at Aquinas College on Saturday, March 16th at 2-6, around $65 if… https://t.co/v9Tb7YyAfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swistle I have been known to scream THIS IS NOT A TRUCK STOP I SHOULD NOT HAVE TO WIPE THE SEAT BEFORE SITTING ON… https://t.co/ZxdTWR1zxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrAdame @juanpueblo2012 @ClaudiaPavlovic @lopezobrador_ @bienestarmx @JorgeTaddeiB Es solo de la presentación del… https://t.co/Bm6K0H5CXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took some of the clients out to eat. And my shorty a drunkie after two glasses 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[First attempt at oil painting (without liquid white, might I add!)  I'm no Bob Ross, but honestly, following along… https://t.co/yTQjrwOX4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rd58Ronald @texaszeller @offensiveloons @TrueNorthElite @MNDarkClouds @MNUFC For real, Ronald. Paint some tifo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are you going to put someone down who is deceased??? Fuck you @peta]]></document><document><![CDATA[here i am enameled with my son, ponyboy. i got him today and i adore him. this is what motherhood feels like i assu… https://t.co/gQywcniX9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoyLauraRivas @informador_JAL Hermosa Bendiciones un excelente día para ti ! 😘😘😘 Te quiero Mi lau ! 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[#floridarealestate #floridarealtor #floridahomes #firsttimehomebuyer #newhomeowner #florida #floridarealtors… https://t.co/O9xq5jqsXH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kayakgirl27 I haven't paid attention to any of you until this year.  And I saw how vulgar you are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would have been in to see Carol and Michone join in that fight #TheWalkingDead]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wesleystromberg My lights in my house went out and it's completely dark I can't turn my lights on at all so I have… https://t.co/VCQ2Od4SgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mirror mirror on the wall🌸#French #mirrors #wall #cottage #fashiononashoestring @ Talladega, Alabama https://t.co/v3smFTQ0Lp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t stand Dr. Avery.... I REPEAT I can’t stand Dr. Avery. Idk why but I don’t like him #GreysAnatomy #takehimaway #whydoesheexist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dalianata Mario Abdo, pero al menos aquí en Twitter usa el diminutivo (Marito).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunny @ABC Our community ( lesbian/black) has enough 💩 to deal with. We don’t need this guy making 💩 up for attent… https://t.co/iZQhOazML6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @adoptabledog with get_repost ・・・ Scarlet is so ready to find her forever home. She is well cared for, but… https://t.co/XdXLy9iCH1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time Shelby and I talked in the Uber last night, the driver turned the music up a little bit more]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shit. I really need to start saving those Marriott loyalty points 😂 #oscarsweek https://t.co/mvOEfoeWLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amber Carr is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $797.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $25 b… https://t.co/gKMdEN9oMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Tweetbox69 No because if it’s Thursday and I’m talking abut this upcoming Monday I’m not going to say “next Mo… https://t.co/aRtuk4bb5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Build Your Voice Team is ready to go. Get The Voice Official App to play. https://t.co/hYrYuZ2Kb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve only bought like 4 things for the condo in total and dropped $300 today only like 🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have accepted a challenge from @MrsMagillBCPS to post #7BooksILove- no explanation, no review- just cover(s). Eac… https://t.co/rOy1gID6nS]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people can’t prove a point in their own beliefs, so they start commenting on what you look like...  #CantRelate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheZidar Ohhh, I really like that—both the stripes and the blues with that buttery yellow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Odland I feel naked without earrings. I keep an emergency pair in my car!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #aldineUMC retreat is one crazy good experience! Honored to speak, sing and act like a nut, for this is what we… https://t.co/Gxa707Raq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a weekend! The cork is back in the bottle. #PNV19 #napavintners $3.7 million reasons to raise your glass.… https://t.co/bcFhiXSupA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recent batch.   Did something change?  Thinner than before, dim flavor.  Not what I remember. - Drinking a Moon Sho… https://t.co/c4jIpsxuYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk Cause dear ladies they are as full of crap as the next Dem...the darn Republicans need to get some… https://t.co/1Tey08fg5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris STOP lying! There is no trauma whatsoever! Get a grip!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generally, Minneapolis and St. Paul @MomsDemand members stand together in frozen solidarity. But on Sunday, I’m tea… https://t.co/Mgrq635ePP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I can understand why some people pronounce Rosalindo’s name like “Roz a lindo” because of Rosalind chocolat… https://t.co/BpHT2zxqcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shhh 🤫 I am launching a coffee collection! It’s not in stores until March 7, but you can get it online here now 🙌… https://t.co/xtOP1sGhmF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samjulien 😃 do you already have a place to stay? My Airbnb host was amazing 🙌🏼. Would recommend if you're looking for something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all for play based, child centred learning! ABA is not that. There is no "good" ABA as autism therapy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The follow up trial was stopped for futility: no difference in vent free days. 🙁🙁 https://t.co/BGbm0RZLEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am enjoying watching the @HC_ladyD on @PrepSpin on this snowy Sunday afternoon!!!! Let’s go Clay!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisAllen02 Everything! Everyone except the the Republicans that are his”kiss-ups”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really thought Lady Gaga was going to sit down at that piano and start a cover of “Radioactive” because that would explain her spray tan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhenIs2001 @chick_in_kiev I feel you, brother. Tweeting you from my hospital bed 4 days after having lymphoma tumo… https://t.co/mvBHEGxIwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[missymisdemeanorelliott @ Lauderdale Lakes, Florida https://t.co/efLBkFKaGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today begins @AmplifyAustin day! Schedule your donation now for our 9 PM power hour. #ILiveHereIGiveHere #amplifyTrinityCDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not much new to see here. I added more joint compound today. #unfsculpture #hometown #shelbyvilleky #havicstudios… https://t.co/GjGdbofKlB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despite @WisconsinDOT saying 41SB crash at Richmond exit being cleared, traffic is still not really moving. #WBAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cut spending and budget. We don’t have the $$$ also NO 2 #illegalimmigrants getting free tuition-costs $$ we don’t… https://t.co/AIUYq4XqU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we’re not going to address the fact that Kanye got KENNY G to play for you alright then]]></document><document><![CDATA[@____1UP___ @thinkprogress Her plan that gave them &amp; asked them to comment on is superb  Have you read it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a BEAUTIFUL day in SW Florida ☀️🌴⚾️❤️ @ JetBlue Park at Fenway South https://t.co/FCIdrYqd3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING A woman struck by a red pickup truck has died.   @CincyPD say the driver fled the scene and it’s an ongoi… https://t.co/KzU6jMAJT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stepping up Taco Tuesday on this Taco Thursday with elevated Tex Mex paired with adult-rated slushies... 🌮🍹 Kicking… https://t.co/yX9uxNITbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only 90s kids-“ Me: Excuse me but I am a 2000s kid and I experienced all of these things]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating Black History Month at #RoyAyers Jazz is Dead with @ArtDontSleep 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_franico Thanks for sharing. I think I found our other friend Craig Fox doing dog handling duties 🐾🐺🐾🐺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congressman Mast asking that public not be left out of the new schedule of discharges or operating system like they have been before. @WPTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️💯😘#thatface #bulldog #lovedogs #lovinglife #happy @ Great Falls, Montana https://t.co/uZeCACFrlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having had the pleasure to be part of the #InternationalWomensDay podcast last year then you should all definitely… https://t.co/T9IQ3X3CjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are coming in with their coffee for some Facebook Ads training here at #DSSEA! If you’re sick of tearing you… https://t.co/AkkkBJIKjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceCordall @startrekcbs I don't think they're 'secret secret'. Just a different division. In season 1 when Burnh… https://t.co/EqstQPFMp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y NADA MÁS!! #historia #leyenda #supéralo #miequipo #orgullo https://t.co/AlXsQTbkpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was/is still me. It's a constant work-in-progress. There are good days and hard days. There are days where I d… https://t.co/kVOm75nbMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women’s Day!! #cocktailvixens #mobilebartendingservice #bookus @ New York, New York https://t.co/fZPEnCYGil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dance Mom Mode: Activate! Love getting to see my favorite dancer perform ❤️ Always so proud of her hard work.… https://t.co/QvHADAhyzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @AOC @CPAC You're disgraceful. She is an elected official and you were born with a microphone in yo… https://t.co/IE800Vilff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abbeytheshadow @PositivWarriors She can't be blocked now unless you follow her #SaveShadowhunters #Shadowhunters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaksicNenad @abraham777888 Hur många härskartekniker får plats i en enda tweet? Du måste ha slagit rekord. Googla… https://t.co/XouX5UErv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislaing @JenDevor Is this the place we agreed to meet at for dinner in 15 (now 14) years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FeelingAllTheFeels in my happy place with my #GermanFamily 🥰 #Austin #Texas #HowWeRoll @ Torchy's Tacos https://t.co/tuEbMwwCT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Intelligent &amp; young with some extra on the side. Undervalued but to me you’d be a prize!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @HuntsmanAbby  @BillSpadea @MattRooneyNJ U ppl really R Chock Full O Nuts! Don't tell me that Conserv… https://t.co/ziqzn9QgJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s wrong with the other Supreme Court Justices. Why are the allowing this????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeptofDefense @USMC @MCIWPendletonCA Our prayers to God on their behalf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuzzy bat!  This is the size of the brown bats we have in my area.  They are still in hibernation now, but will com… https://t.co/P4ALZSNiFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexHeider1 @JesseKnutsonNC5 It is! haha we looked it up. His name is Alex Call]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rihanna serving looks on your birthday is the horoscope of modern times  https://t.co/ILSqwYnwV7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WahooRubio1809 I know I had so much hope for him when he first came up it’s a shame he got hit with tommy john whe… https://t.co/XbnAgLOlNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hellbent 💯😈 (@vicesbrnd) @kalanattila @ATTILAga 👽 . . . . . . . #photographer #photography #machinegunkelly… https://t.co/XwNtEKOKqq]]></document></documents></author>