<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So I make her leave the room to doublecheck my efforts won’t be in vain because if it’s not #FortheThrone then I ca… https://t.co/Wi2awDK7jF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJWineandBeer @EightSandBeer @ACBeerFest @WhatsOnTap_TV @garymonterosso Trying to make it happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@woohoo9 @TrumpCat04 @sc08960854 @rnlynn1958 @2501Wolf @misspunk63 @kidgolferman @low_riding @justjessie226… https://t.co/CzZ9k4ZUuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got my @whydontwemusic tickets for August 3rd. Can’t wait to see them @ImZachHerron @JonahMarais @SeaveyDaniel… https://t.co/H4gKGNTNIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spent my life hunting and exploring hunting is NOT KILLING I DO NOT LIKE THE FACT THAT PEPOLE AQUIRE A GUN TO BE… https://t.co/DqUQQziXrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[and everyone was so happy about lindholm mocking it on OUR ice while the some of the canes were still on the ice...… https://t.co/vDfPipzHuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adapt to your customers needs but don’t lose the essence of who you are in the process]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just because someone works in sports doesn't mean they can get you free tickets/apparel/etc. We don't even get that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorsPEU Next week #NYCVotes for Public Advocate so get out there and do it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an unhealthy obsession with Mitchell Tenpenny ... can’t wait to see him in June! 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kid is only 4 1/2 months old and I got people asking me when I’m having another .... chill Gloria. I’d like to keep my sanity, thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[since the jonas brothers are coming back together, we need another camp rock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dumb teen in Lincoln Memorial protest sues Washington Post for absurd $250 million https://t.co/CsczZG1ywK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that Governor Janet Mills has formally presented her two-year, $8 billion budget, lawmakers are already digging… https://t.co/Lc5xvoqeCu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Bryson is at it again!! Students are using technology to graph the parabola made by mentos and Diet Coke! @ Wal… https://t.co/51KNMeS0VG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCAviation a Boeing Max 150+ on board within minutes of take off ... someone mentioned noticing speed changes...… https://t.co/p61MwQ4Tkn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LoveYourPetDay Moseley the Greatest of the Great Pyr. Been a steadfast Resistor since Nov 2016 https://t.co/1hL4X79k0S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daily Chess Improvement: Clever Chess Endgame! Info here: https://t.co/NXTNtZlAfQ @FIDE_chess @EuropeEchecs… https://t.co/bLJzQKlQFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHeathensDay May I mention the recusal/non-recusal of Devin Nunez, who leaked confidential information on FBI inve… https://t.co/Z3mtoaSLFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was so happy to catch up with Roula from @woodlandhistory tonight and see the team get presented the award. Proud… https://t.co/5P2ho7bM6k]]></document><document><![CDATA[The iniquity of Ephraim is bound up; his sin is hid. https://t.co/vqgUwmlqR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just left the gym and now I’m on Amazon deciding is I wanna Prime order Girl Scout cookies..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photoshoots on the yard... But make it PROFESSIONAL! 📸 Meet us on the yard TODAY from 3pm to 5pm, where we will be… https://t.co/s7fA93hj4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ronlee1975 Nice to see some old man game in a sport being ruined by hired guns.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every flight I’ve ever taken with them has never gone smoothly. There’s always a delay, cancellation or some shit g… https://t.co/XGR4hAiOle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @FoxNews @CBSNews @ABC @NBCNews @MSNBC  @ananavarro @GeraldoRivera  @jorgeramosnews  @SenSanders @SenBooker… https://t.co/5MCLMuTaZn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'm thinking you haven't heard from Otto's parents today, they're a little upset with you, that yo… https://t.co/jOyfsgrTRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lunaastef hell yes every year you cry on everyone’s birthday because you don’t want them to get old 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mosqueda199 Thats it Im using these as inspiration! Y’all are too cute!😻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeeJayStark Like yeah anyone who goes to Sade to learn how to act is a fucktard, no argent there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The producer of the ring and the final destination movies are following my dad and he’s so happy about it it’s so cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattAnders17 Can't follow anyone  at this time... TWITTER RULES...RULES 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarpad &amp; #spn &amp; #spnfamily always fighting for good mental health &amp; supporting each other 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@visitmendocino Mendocino #movies #moviesset #hillhouse #travel #california #mendocinocounty en The Hill House Inn https://t.co/d6nzbg9eFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @KevinMFerrara @hoppinmama5 @Patti_Sc60 @jonz970 @Serremmy @Chris_A10_USA @Bigbillshater @CaliRN619… https://t.co/CxsIgGzznh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please find this person and Ararat him for assault, hate crimes, and for any other charge you can bring upon him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212  keep the faith and keep telling the truth. I understand how and why you did things for the mob bo… https://t.co/P0UJO5CWPJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beer time! (at @BadBeatBrewing in Henderson, NV w/ @wolnisty) https://t.co/iRWBCnu1bd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atu2comSherry I'm picturing a random video of you dancing with the veggies in the produce isle!!!😄😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND Hillary. Let’s not forget the sorest loser in the universe, Hillary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 I think it has a lot to do with fucked up patriarchal religion. Teaches women to rely on the words an… https://t.co/FNPEtwUjps]]></document><document><![CDATA[La fotografía de calle es mi pasión. Sony A7iii |50mm| f1.8 |1/60 s | ISO 100 en Chicago, Illinois https://t.co/mxJFf8hXS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieG74195935 @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You are kidding right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[These were their names: Ben-hur, in the hill country of Ephraim; https://t.co/jD1UpkWZ6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[100th Day of School!  Moving and counting to 100! https://t.co/KWGa1E8zud]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tutorials The Secrets To Taking Awesome Dog Portraits #funniness #giggle #grin #merry https://t.co/FtDzBODJy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have had the good fortune of having both female and male mentors that toot my horn and sing my praises. It would… https://t.co/r7pxB3raf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this sweater! Size 8-10 for my g'bby Joana. Pattern is Harvest by @tincanknits  Yarn is Mighty Stitch from k… https://t.co/82F4UhjXSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of the day business is business and no matter how good you are to people they’re still gonna do what’s b… https://t.co/ixYu0xbqn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a year and a half dry streak(no sex) and I just had my ass grabbed by a porn star.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hang on I'm committing murder! ... BECAUSE IT'S ALL I KNOW!-Vik #lifeinmurray101]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deb_k_alex @codeorg The workshops are offered all over. Check out the PD map. We all use the same curriculum. The… https://t.co/eqLvktXK8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherJones Trump is slowly attempting to establish a dictatorship.  Kim Jung Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk who needs to see this but pulling full coverage bikini bottoms up your ass so it can show it off doesn't look g… https://t.co/dFzjdNGkhC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPLukePerry you were too young to leave us- a piece of my adolescence goes with you #90210 #Dylan4Ever 💔… https://t.co/VKP1Au8X9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Knowing a student's reading level is not the same as knowing the student as a reader. How do you get to know your r… https://t.co/wXiSjZjDza]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BorderNarcotics Great! She shacked up with three isis terrorists.  She is a danger to Americans]]></document><document><![CDATA[How bout them Hoosiers *cough cough* @CarsonScheer   LoL I live 20 minutes from IU ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My biggest Cancer problem is I’m scared to be too far from home so traveling freaks me out. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aliya313 Hahaha .. meri cat meri goud mein aa kr so jati hy https://t.co/2FnrBKsrDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashvalentinex I'm that girl who could listen to nothing but 5sos and still be happy, lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[H/t to @LauraSell for making me aware of this thread. #rechargeyoursoul]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's been tested, we have a sure foundation in Christ Jesus https://t.co/yjqwL2ubok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellen Hyde from @WalmartInc Foundation thanking us for stepping back, coming together, listening to each other - so… https://t.co/cfVTGwktD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've known precious_healinghaircare since junior high school... I was so happy to see her at my Erica's… https://t.co/IxjicK1vW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it normal for steam to come out of ones ears?  Covington Catholic teen and his parents sue the Washington Post  https://t.co/ltSbfCRpXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything about this is beautiful though - Kid feeling emotions  - Parent holding space for kid to work things out… https://t.co/XxCCa2iyrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@health_xl @DreamItHealth @Healthbox @TechCrunch @Rock_Health @rvalighthouse @theStartupVA @startuphealth]]></document><document><![CDATA[My adorable handsome Lad. #persiancat #purebred #catsofinstagram #CatsOfTwitter #CutenessOverload #gremlins https://t.co/m1U0c4v8LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is interesting that if I take high school students in a field trip I need a chaperone for every 10 kids to help… https://t.co/D6BWqJXlCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please STOP all the hate on Justin NOW he doesn't deserve it he deserves only love ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dustinlynch Haha I missed the socks the first time seems each time I watch it I catch something different]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confession.... I like wearing my backpack because it feels like someone is hugging me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most exhausting weekend of the year is Ice Bowl Weekend, but sooooo worth it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday #ReadMoreWomen #Recommended https://t.co/f8tvzUTIe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, Grammy. Miss you every single day and love you always. https://t.co/VbTLNuFipw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check put these two during the Deposition of Testimony on Immigration,Customs and Enforcement's . https://t.co/NfUKS75g3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy first rehearsal day for @stratfest #sfNeverendingStory. I’m there in spirit today, see you soon! Xoxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarenMorris @MarissaRMoss Wait wait wait, so y’all are saying we women have an imagination? And we can use it and be creative? 🤔 Seems fake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond They take themselves way to seriously. No one cares about them and so they have to pretend someone does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveholland1 @PhilipRucker Being in "really good shape" is something Donald Trump knows NOTHING about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlliniHQ @clikasNG @STMoreADs @Redbirdwbb @adzilis @ParklandMBB @Tatelines @IlliniMBB @ngphotostaff… https://t.co/q8NcQPSzN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a look at this clients gorgeous upholstered walls. LOVE IT!   #GardenCity #Design #GailCiprianoDesignStudios… https://t.co/kTy1wxRepQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[dad : what time do you want up  me : not 6 in the morning  * he always wakes me up every day at 5 in the morning *… https://t.co/XTwM0TmfIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyTakata I was only there for like 30 minutes because I had a flight to catch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone for making it out to Little Village for a final Election-eve rally! #TeamSusana is fired up and… https://t.co/eyOnUBywHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[What say you now @LindseyGrahamSC @mattgaetz @Jim_Jordan @MarkMeadows @ChuckGrassley @HouseGOP @SenateGOP… https://t.co/FsCtyZd8iz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having seen part of this - the excitement that a univ here had offered Prof Salaita a position, the subsequent atta… https://t.co/ontbNZqqkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Port St Lucie Featured Community. https://t.co/usSxtc9f4O 772-224-1634 #portstlucie #stluciecounty #homeforsale… https://t.co/BpBllA0Xlq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nlbmprez @JPosnanski @Royals @MLB @MLB_PLAYERS @fox4kc @Sut_ESPN @MLBNetwork @vgregorian @mellinger The greatest!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lord guides the steps of a man and makes safe the path of the one he loves. Though he stumble he shall never fa… https://t.co/NWEXbVmXSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy to be with favorite guys and waiting to see The Crabb Family! @ Charlotte, North Carolina https://t.co/0lHbFJfR1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed a nice game of spring training for my tigers yesterday.   . . . . . .  #selfie #baseball #springtraining… https://t.co/1jSa3WL8Tf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Settled in for an afternoon nap AKA not actually sleeping, overthinking that awkward interaction from 2 weeks ago and ordering @UberEats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Trump has committed others.....there is just too much on Trump!!!!Republicans can not save him!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two thoughts. 1. @AlyssaMastro44 has Amazing Scarf game.  2. Her new book, So Here’s The Thing is sooo good that I… https://t.co/KHF9MmwOk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayCarney @RonaldKlain Thank you Ron and everyone involved. We are very grateful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly truly. I wish I could pop out a few kids right now then rip out my ovaries &amp; all that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be among this group of evangelists! I’m not a techie but I know this sector will be as key a driver to… https://t.co/qQKksVqodj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SassyKadiK Had my 1st two shots of espresso. Hesding out to work FOH at super busy coffee shop on the beach that s… https://t.co/1Mx4uujkLD]]></document></documents></author>