<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#AMEN and God bless WORLD have a great day don't forget to SMILE @DennisJBolt 🔱⚡BOLTIBOLTZ CAN'T STOP WON'T STOP Be… https://t.co/pjMfUffOs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @benshapiro Where is the follow up question..  you had less info the first time you commented]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the world needs to realize is that it's 2019 and guilt-tripping doesn't work on me anymore lol. I know my wort… https://t.co/A3Q88sp8PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickygervais I’m watching your new show, Afterlife....you have no idea the kind of effect you can have on a comple… https://t.co/aC1y5HGzOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bikes are off to Daytona Beach 😊😊😊 @ SL NYC Inc. https://t.co/SHm69JrV2d]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FirstMan had the best sound design I have ever heard in a movie ever. #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well.. I may not catch Angus and his 382-Day Fast, but this is a good start! @ Delray Beach, Florida https://t.co/pyrgK1Jlec]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@GovHolcomb @IN_gov @SenToddYoung @UCSUSA @ChispaLcv @EarthjusticeDC @GreenLatinos @HUDgov https://t.co/ZrlvRCgV4r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone laughed at dining and dancing at the @tacobell in demolition man but it's happening in Vegas! @ Taco Bell https://t.co/l2yn1pneal]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shall now be known as the @Leinenkugels curse, too soon for Summer Shandy in NJ https://t.co/4Mfm0MQqlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The finals of the @beyondwrestling #TreasureHunt. @dirtydickinson v. @callmeklizav for a shot at the @PowerbombTV c… https://t.co/1t6PShePaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC HERE I COME!!! Excited for Antigone in Ferguson NYC Phase II 🤗 looking forward to another great experience in N… https://t.co/qmi5rZxqvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#smb #entrepreneurs #technologynews #mom #dad #family #wife #husband #teens #Chevrolet finally adds ‘find my #car’… https://t.co/vNRWvaj40O]]></document><document><![CDATA[One for the road (we walked here) (@ Gold Cane Cocktail Lounge in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/6nADDPNSne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gunnerblog We’ll prolly never know why Sven left, but if we land Mochi, at least that means we’re still an attractive job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It could’ve be worse. You could’ve become David Spade. https://t.co/DYSNFb0dDE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrekCore @datalore_tv @jonathansfrakes Is Fantasy Island where Riker learned how to sit? #StarTrekTNG https://t.co/7W3K3j8Vc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @lukecombs can you do me a favor and make sure “Houston, We Got a Problem” is on the set list for tomorrow night in Cbus?]]></document><document><![CDATA[lol says the one who threw my only spare key on top of my apartment roof. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can't hang with me mofo @garyvee you are getting old fucker I see it. Quite frankly idk how you #doit for that… https://t.co/KMDZE8Mix4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Mommy! Today I started a kindness club at recess!!” 🥰😍❤️ @goMercerEagles @Walkergirl66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stormy_succubus I hate asswipes that think they are alpha males who are nothing more than weak ass shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @guardian That is what you believe.  Stop thinking you are the owner of the truth. You don’t know what millions of Americans are doing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just ridiculous !! Invasion?  # Down 20% Gang members? 0.1% Criminals? 4%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Suckaby is a worthless POS. Lies more than the liar-in-chief. 😠😠😠😠😠 Fire Sarah #FireSarah]]></document><document><![CDATA[YATES COACH GREG WISE  AFTER BIG WIN OVER SILSBEE LIONS HEADED TO SAN ANTONIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Lowell: broken clouds, 33°F 29% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1023mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PariahSojourner @nancyann1968 @AnnMoti3 @MontyFowler @realDonaldTrump FYI I love Costa Rica! Vacationed there great place. High tide soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two more photos from Hausermann’s open house orchid show. This place is enormous! Next weekend is your last chance… https://t.co/HkZOxgVIIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[as if we weren’t the EXACT same type of edgy but w different words like come on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 @Tnmountainhome She should know this subject pretty well!! @KamalaHarris]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero sexo oral y anal contigo amor bello a love ❤ me gustas mucho sexy boy Hot simpático blonde amor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vijaya @kayvz soon you'll ban ME for asking you legitimate questions :( a word of advice... quit lawyering for twi… https://t.co/OCOxBHnVNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jair3D No me hables de 21 años. Háblame de lo que viviste en la semi de vuelta y el volver a una final después de… https://t.co/CNEwz8F8GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[New to the list @faustobrooklyn   #winewednesday #huet #pettilant #wine #loirevalley #brovia #arneis… https://t.co/R3nFrhF49e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KirkDrakeIII @LenderClose @RedboardApp @Ogo_Cuso @live_survey Looking fwd to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wow internet and cable is out once again it was out 2 days ago and now its been out for 4 hrs since 1:30 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loading the last video of this 4 video shoot my friend Nick in Ocean City, MD recorded back in 2014 for me. I will… https://t.co/3KOWdJsJ73]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoCalPro @DamianDrakeLV @mattvanda209 please bring damian drake and matt vandagriff to so cal pro to wrestle please]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_C_Campbell Person with addiction should take personal responsibility for the life they chose. Get a job and p… https://t.co/zu0cKdi6xA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don't even all experience looking at that stone the same.  Some of you will be offended by the words, some will… https://t.co/l04vs12sgC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bubbles with the wife @ Atlantis Casino Resort Spa https://t.co/MXHRk0dil1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOXER36 @CSCtweets84 @therealroseanne @TheConnersABC @THEsaragilbert Bot]]></document><document><![CDATA[First night at Disney! Supper at Boardwalk! #Italian @WaltDisneyWorld https://t.co/QRZ1gdAsDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuvaDre You said Dane so yeah she'll be good and he's bigger than Dobermans uglasses]]></document><document><![CDATA[broken clouds -&gt; clear sky temperature down 55°F -&gt; 49°F humidity up 62% -&gt; 87% wind 6mph -&gt; 3mph]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can safely say it’s been about 16 years since I ran a mile without stopping....thanks otf_astoria #imtired… https://t.co/ICBuOSJaN8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Frfr i take great offense to sick😤1 nobody got time for that and 2 what you ain’t gonna do is be lurking around in… https://t.co/5LU2y8YQye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be a warrior when it comes to delivering on your ambitions. And a saint when it comes to treating people with respe… https://t.co/7EmAjo4my1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glasprojoe @Notverycon @SenateGOP @GOP Your mother didn’t complain about my dickhead]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @ElevationChurch - Raleigh in Raleigh, North Carolina https://t.co/SUfN3dFQ9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump How sweet!!!!  And in the shortest month of the year! https://t.co/PMK4PURC7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you believe this? From The NY Times?  If even partially correct, it is frightening!  This must be stopped!!  An… https://t.co/kv7iZfERW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#follow_me #follow4followback #followmenow #followtrain #followforfollowback #followback #follow #followtrick… https://t.co/fri7ybwpKR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Those are very beautiful ear rings. I’m very sorry for your loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeidiGolznig You look nice but i would get rid of the breast implants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrKMcGee @DisneyBooks @Spanish_Broom Thank ✏️__you__ Kris for this and for all you do for teachers and readers each day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think one of my biggest regrets in life is gonna be me not having a son...🤔😥 #latenightthoughts]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkMBC @JoaquinCastrotx @JohnCornyn @tedcruz I have faith that someone will help me eventually I pray to God I th… https://t.co/LdVtANzleI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night went from connect four to my Uber getting a flat tire at 3am on 465]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be clear: I will not let Jussie stop me from believing the victim. I’d rather be wrong about that than not belie… https://t.co/RlNlris8GP]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it’s Thursday...we’ll be on-air from 6-9 @Thunder102 #havaneseofinstagram #havanese #countrymusic #countryboy… https://t.co/yvkdgbDOaS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spratto9 Rory with the cocky walk.  #AnyoneButRory https://t.co/gdzaGI9wBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[verse or hook features $100 for the next 7 days  send the track to pierreanthonyproductions@gmail.com   send paymen… https://t.co/Jsy6gedIJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carolyn_1228 The funny part is it’s not even my family! It’s someone else and they feel the need to post every lit… https://t.co/gHpZGWciWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The real story would be him saying that he’s not looking forward to playing for him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSchnecker Thank you to all our mentors.  Supporting our future leaders.  @ossiningMBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, help us not to raise a new generation of children with high intellectual quotients and low caring and compassi… https://t.co/dZrMHVCjOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey bro my juul broke can I have urs? I need it when I wake up in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chuck1one @OotyMac @Woodshed_1914 @Nykterryandtray @PreZnyc621 @BklynGM @RisKOutlawS @2ForgetUs @knickanator… https://t.co/DRaSBMgPwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erdayastronaut I am interested in one of those hoodies if you get them up on the store.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg I used to live paycheck to paycheck until I quit overspending on unnecessary things like cable tv,… https://t.co/DsRQZB0Z3Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, @espn needs to quit dick riding @KingJames. Jordan led teams to championships, Lebron was led by… https://t.co/Cx9CwEdLSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JIMBO_SOLAR @PaulRMQ @TheOrville @SethMacFarlane I’m definitely excited &amp; open to give it a real shot! Nice to have something new!]]></document><document><![CDATA[There was many nights I watched this in @bMann_10 basement for hours on hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaylaRimpson Congratulations on your accomplishment. See you don’t need no man. Your a independent women 👍🏽💪🏼👩🏻‍🦰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrewingTalks @tayyyibahhh @Houthi_hunter @Brutal_SK @NOFACEN0CASE Got a Hadith 💁🏽‍♂️ https://t.co/VObPkULrha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavKat43 Alot is not all.I dont take it https://t.co/jiz9AKIJM4 not begging for your acceptance.I have fought prej… https://t.co/lMuyB3cGqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHEELING/OHIO CO.,WV (HLG) ASOS reports gust of 53 knots (61.0 mph) from W @ 1711Z -- KHLG 241711Z 27029G53KT 10SM… https://t.co/3RmmCmSvle]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m dying with these reply’s to @khloekardashian recent tweets! 😂😂😂😂 they are dragging sis! https://t.co/nKvcYmCFv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 5th anniversary @FallonTonight! thank you for all the laughs and for always making me smile, even on bad days… https://t.co/niUcZzLDWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brian Wilson, Pet Sounds Live @ Bardavon 1869 Opera House https://t.co/NRRdCOsmOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthewherper @barttels2 @venkmurthy @SteveJoffe @VPrasadMDMPH People also speak of the impact Hal Barron has had… https://t.co/DPHOhrmDVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_War_Economy @JackPosobiec A little stretch there @NikkiHaley Brennan should be in jail without a future.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My left side of my face is fast asleep. Why my right side wide awake? The fuck is this nonsense?]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is why you shouldn’t reproduce with your second cousin. You get little shits like this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My partner in crime as well as favorite co-caster is headed back to Vegas for another round of @MWEsportsSeries   S… https://t.co/4vJbYK1ser]]></document><document><![CDATA[I downloaded Apex Legends last night, partied up with my homies from high school and we played for six hours til 2… https://t.co/Eld5hajCuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoloProtection @BernieSanders Bernie makes below average income for a Senator and saved his money from a 40 year c… https://t.co/mQdy9wXHbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doubtless any new policies raise potentially new problems, but it seems a mistake to say that these potential new p… https://t.co/o72UoeLuPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll see you in Toronto this weekend! We’re playing at the EFS Social club this Friday!   #toronto #gradybrothers… https://t.co/kzWN6e9Twm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alotaibi_a899 @SashaBanksWWE Belly I'm glad to see y'all be World Tag Team Champions I hope you all still keep the world belts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que la vida era más bonita, más romántica, divertida, llena de ilusiones etc... cuando solo salía con niñas    🙇🏻‍♂️💫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Relax [it's just a hazy IPA] by @offshootbeerco @ Table 301 — https://t.co/1GCqvjW31r]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Internet nutrition battle wages on.  Some say carbs are the cause of our fat gain.  Others say (or have said) i… https://t.co/PzjRy7FjiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews Not a coup but a conversation dummy. You fired the FBI director, then in the… https://t.co/otiOMGQ8nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are an anomaly if you aren't trolling. Not saying that in a bad way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msewelldesign @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Well then you can just kick throw a fit and cry, I don’t care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure Coach K liked that call. Something about a truck and his mom? https://t.co/pSAZM7hQgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wondered that last time. Non of the other alternative parties did that.]]></document></documents></author>