<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[HELL YEAH! 🎃🤘🏼🖤  Can’t wait to get my spook on 🦇 https://t.co/5XmmGT7dyA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffChody The week before Christmas oh, I lost my 17 year old cat Sooner. I don't care how old they are it's hard to lose a fur baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are glad to be there!   Warmer weather is coming and tea of all sorts will bloom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything I do is for them! I work my but off to make sure they have a better life then I did! I spoil them often… https://t.co/S8qVtQunIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @joncoopertweets But will our nation survive the Trump era? Congress should curtail his authority 2 prevent it.#getdtoutmyWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uglybitcheric Just watched it again last night and while it's great I think the episode after it is better. It's t… https://t.co/STqPtvXsJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Meloni My favorite team is the NY Giants and our biggest need is a QB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes Time for Bernie to accept his role as elder statesman and advisor in 2020 campaign]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALKentBooks Wow. Thank you so much for this beautiful message. Kids always remind me that I’m surrounded by love,… https://t.co/OF9psuUMHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[My after workout weekday breakfast.  Unsweetened almond milk, celery, broccoli sprouts, blueberries, a banana, huel… https://t.co/OfO7Rp75zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kirapractor I didn’t have a special ringtone but my alarm to wake up used to be t-pain chopped n skrewed😥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating love and lovers with @kylieminogue’s All the Lovers as our (unusually upbeat) finale to last weekend’s… https://t.co/Q70ADmdE0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lovingmyself #sexyselfie @ Grand Prairie, Texas https://t.co/uWZFXE2Ra3]]></document><document><![CDATA[No upper eyelashes on one eye. Had to read who it was.  Def does not look like AOC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trixiemattel @bdanielcole I'm no one because I want all the fucking honeydew. 👀🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@valeriepineiro @e_schwags @Bridget_magee @EM_and_Ms I thought Greenday by Greenday was a little valid. I’m not in… https://t.co/LuCph3LMWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN is devoting HUGE amounts of airtime to #JussieSmollett. Classic distraction from bigger news #MuellerReport "Lo… https://t.co/94gTkbIjnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[tell me why I’m still the person that would drop anything for people I love even if I know they wouldn’t give half a thought for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re home alone and someone knocks on the door https://t.co/8Rc8bBJ34a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Iyanla to get into Kadeem ass #FixMyLife https://t.co/ee14KULPLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[A bird doesn't worry about the branch it lands on because it trusts its ability to fly. It's been a hard-fought bat… https://t.co/Hc4lMkxulH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedbauer2003 Don’t know if I really remember any conf rooms. But I think one had a big glass wall with a view of t… https://t.co/1ogg5AWUG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rebelpride32 @staceyaugmon @JordanCornish5_ @m_cornish Tell him to be careful on that thing Lesley! Be safe!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertDRoseJr1 @DrPhilRoe @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @LizMacDonaldFOX @DanLairdMD @Pharmaciststeve You’re wasting you… https://t.co/sjtwswcZ8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vintage_vendor @VABVOX Loved Jane Curtin since the SNL days.  And sometimes you have to pop things. But not like t… https://t.co/imdoeOnF2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthAnna77 @mcspocky I am laid back too! It takes a lot to get under my skin.  But some people will be testy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I’m going to my favorite coffee shop. 🥰  Going home for a day.❤️😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennyWillard Super cute!  You should crochet something like a cute little purse,people would buy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly Raybould-Wilson felt pressured. But she was making the wrong decision. Her real pressure was internal. #SNCLavalin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see the creature in 3D on the big screen today 😍 I'm also super excited to read @malloryomeara's book on Mil… https://t.co/BZ7OySa3Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your Mind is a powerful thing⚡️When you fill it with positive thoughts, your life will start to change 💫 - - - - -… https://t.co/9hQhzAY0RU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fill in the blank....who would use my services?! #bios #photography #interviews #networking #industryevents… https://t.co/OE3GPhH3pY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@180gradosweb Hola, me podrían complacer con el nuevo sencillo de @julionalvarez #CuandoTeAmé 🎵🎶❤ @ChulasDeJA… https://t.co/SEPOm376cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannahtasker @Gina_Caro @Jessicarosewil @caitflanders @CathElizGordon @clairewantless Thanks for this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gracias porque me has dado mucho más de lo que esperé que me fuera cualquier persona en esta vida. ¡Feliz cumpleaño… https://t.co/gqx2IK8dMj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Laurel Canyon love story tonight on Valentine’s Day ❤️🌸☮️☯️ @ Pace Restaurant https://t.co/mhbcGvyiUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a “watching golf” setting on my Apple Watch. It keeps alerting me to breathe and that my heart rate seems higher than normal. 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DystopiaMoon Facts he was also a misogynist he told me to take my tit out just one lmao like wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how I'm already planning our dates but I haven't finished my hw due today 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially when she feels like she’s trying to come out.... girl CHILL IN THERE. It’s not time!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julia’s Tinder Adventures continue with this absolute gem... https://t.co/sE29r0Cv0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OkeAyodeji10 @pattygilli @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Lots and lots of pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highs of the day: fixing the printer and remembering to bring my lunch to work.    Low of the day: theoretically I… https://t.co/onym8TjKdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed an urgent petition: Revoke Trump's national emergency declaration. Add your name here: https://t.co/4HB4DqJLdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@humbertto_lopez @ford1026 @AllTTV2015 @123456Ray @Dodgers @Bharper3407 @kayyharper8 @camelbackranch https://t.co/HzbLVMJBqu]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Yes, these are my real eyes.. no I do not wear contacts❤️ pink and red roses make me… https://t.co/8XCuqdAKB9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video extended. I have the full video on @YouTube and my blog if y'all want to see it. @McDonalds ... you need to r… https://t.co/uComOejYI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Climbing up from there now. #abetterme #thisknee #beautifuldisaster #growingoldgracefully #rockbottom… https://t.co/rEFBvUay7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melanienidhuinn @AssocTeacherEd @SchoolofEdTCD @TeachingCouncil So wonderful to have here for the 2019 CFS #clinicaledfellows]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods You cannot TAKE a man from a woman if he’s loyal.. the man wouldn’t allow it (again..IF HES LOYAL)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidanHenri Congratulations!  I'm so happy for you!  A one at contest yesterday and now this!  You're on fire man🔥W… https://t.co/WX2bU70S6f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wolv54b1 @cellmavin @PlatformBeers @badhopper @RJellyman @cedarflats @JohanBBT @JonMontag @Just4BeerLovers… https://t.co/IWOEwpmyUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my phone was also sitting in a bucket of water tonight for who knows how long.. only thing that doesn’t work any… https://t.co/Xr9JaBctbp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I finished watching Parks and Rec. Today I realized my boss is Leslie Knope to my April Ludgate and that… https://t.co/wokjxZySxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so easy to buy, but did you know it's also really easy to make your own refreshing STRAWBERRY LEMONADE?With th… https://t.co/fcHeaA1P5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TremorBD She can rock her old look and young look. Just like Johnny does his?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DD733 @Mayacama707 @DalyPolitics @ZerlinaMaxwell @MollyJongFast You’re so lame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anniejarr No I like the flare plane that's costs 200 million, seems really efficient at problem solving]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most intelligent and funniest person I know. Wouldn’t of passed Latin or Economics without your vigorous encour… https://t.co/nSspGA69C0]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow that women literally tried her best and y’all still bash her yet she did nothing at all wrong ? ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @Mr_Jitters I love Shepard Smith. He actually is fair and balanced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I normally don’t complain about school, but a quiz? The Monday after spring forward? At 8AM?!!!!! 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[A member of a family within a cult structure is what I born into. They wont let me leave and they keep me locked on the outside.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The natural progression of Charley's first professional sporting event. #FCDallas #LAGalaxy #dtid… https://t.co/xoF2N9Ui4Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me after finishing 19.2 tomorrow ... @CrossFitGames #InTheOpen #crossfit #thatescalatedquickly https://t.co/0JC2aBFlWg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never understood girls that fell for guys so quickly but now I do and I think I’m crazy but it feels right all at the same time 💘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iconic Oscars Vibe! 🤩Sophia’s Iconic curves were just the beginning then..😍Ready for tonight’s 🌟Oscars!❤️👏🏼 #curvy… https://t.co/BBvsHwIiUl]]></document><document><![CDATA[you democrats, they want to be able to kill a newborn. I don't have an agenda, it's the liberals that do. And I fee… https://t.co/wyBma9q0df]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I FINALLY ordered my cap &amp; gown- graduation is 2 months &amp; 22 days away now! (not that I’m counting haha)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great win tonight. Celebrating With my girl @lynnegoknights https://t.co/uLikiwKytQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only my third time selling this house and what do you know? Multiple offers again! ☘️☘️☘️I leveraged the offers aga… https://t.co/mkrqOLk6Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ElvisAllStarTribute 2 hours and only @carrieunderwood could even come close!!! Awesome.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I’ll never have a cooler parenting moment than the time @Ninja gave my son 10/10 on his artwork 🎮💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NytheBOSS It was dreams and nightmares intro before a dreams and nightmares intro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temptation Island is the dumbest fucking show I’ve ever seen and I’ve only watched it like twice and not even all t… https://t.co/SOJXLyirZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Go2HuntsvilleAL @DowntownHSV Definitely SiP for the best crafted cocktails #iHeartHsv 💖 https://t.co/NIigq8O1EJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@findingfletcher you bring light to many people, your fans, family. Thank you for your music that has helped me a l… https://t.co/yBDnsEgBD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shotgunsmoke12 @rebrokerjoe @Kert200 @ShSherrer @PigglyAGoGoMAGA @flowerpot197 @GraftedInByLove @BatzelKathy… https://t.co/Kl4J4HUQyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello VR Artists . @ARize_AR is a great way to showcase your #tiltbrush art #vrolga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHorrorGuru Dude, your health is more important than anything. I'd rather wait months for a video and have you b… https://t.co/kZAOlQEkf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day number one of vacation, and not pointing any fingers but Cameron got up and pissed all over my carry on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can no longer feel your tongue. #SignsYouNeedANewHobby https://t.co/LozV0SEbpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This good be REAL good. She could shed light on why she was hired and for what!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes and most end up dying or suffering life long consequences that are irreversible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why would she do something that she knew would ruin their friendship? Kylie is OBVIOUSLY going to be on her sisters… https://t.co/5GQJ14SeJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really actually pissed that me and @kayraecruz live too far away to be friends. I really find better friends on… https://t.co/L9Fqmnvfjp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyrusMMcQueen excellent sorcery, indeed. but is has to be sharp cheddar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maryland filmmakers Krista Parris (Fallston), Martha Shane (Towson) and David Lawson (Towson) are all showing films… https://t.co/YKc2MqdUED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenwhitmer You Didn’t address Ur Poverty Stricken Residents!! #HomelessnessMentalHealthBrokenCommunities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spanishcvndy i don’t know if i don’t know how to read or if that was really a comment]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wCFPoYMExQ WOW!!!!! What is wrong with this picture, he was the best besides Dave Lee]]></document><document><![CDATA[left the hair salon crying, and they were not tears of joy https://t.co/MGuFsKXAdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved all the music from #CaptinMarvel movie #myjams #Marvel #MarvelStudios]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rain, Sleet or Shine 🌞🌧❄️💨🌪 Lets go find a home for you!  Look at this Beauty I’m showing with a fabulous pool and… https://t.co/xtLqbpJowk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate “I bet you wont share this” or “I know you wont read this” posts...shut the fuck up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Everyone in Hollywood needs mental health care. Jussie Smollett needs his backside in jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinWLOS @WxRobBradley ROB!!!! Half asleep listening to @WLOS_13  and there it was... the voice...and the beard!… https://t.co/2kqudVFXRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always a fun time on the red carpet when I’m around!!! 😝😋🙌🏼 Been busy these past couple weeks working on this… https://t.co/uQDrNL62QJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best thing about a long commute is listening to @Jimmypisfunny and @WhismanSucks there and back. Laughter keeps… https://t.co/jAD0k7PuTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This afternoon's workout in the gym 💪🏋️ #getfit #gymlife #fitfam https://t.co/c97V6Zk2pP]]></document></documents></author>