<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The giants let @TheHumble_21 walk? I cannot understand how this puts them in a position to get better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a diehard @aafstallions fan, I can speak for all of us - we’d love to have you @JManziel2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Da Baby videos remind me of the 106 &amp; Park days when niggas actually put fun and thought into visuals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now's the Time☝🏿#rockyoursoul #newmusic #nola300 #offbeat #wwoz #mardigras2019 #zuluball @ Ellis Marsalis Center Fo… https://t.co/rvLEXsQ7tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ducks win their first game in their last 7 and just their 3rd in 22. Me as a Ducks fan: A good win last night. Glad… https://t.co/Ydljj3uGm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[10 years ago this would not have been a penalty https://t.co/h7btue4pv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[After reading some of the wonderful hateful comments I receaved this weekend. Especially for supporting Trump. No w… https://t.co/qe0qedEUkj]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEIPA smacks you with a ton of  Pineapple! #homebrewing https://t.co/Ovmr05tex5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BHSPINFEST thanks for the ❤️ all the competitors 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 you all were 🔥 BOOMIN @BarleyHouseCLE https://t.co/A1Fl4MmPJV]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone know of any pixel art apps that aren’t like. those colour by number ones. because i wanna get back into… https://t.co/Hn3DL3NMSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Where was I? Oh yes, your change sir...would you like to donate $1 for the Little Girls Ninja Club?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calallen492 @jonrosenberg @AlexNotPhalix @DiscussingFilm but rose isnt for 80% of the fanbase .. so logic lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time lapse from the 4th. Not sure how much IG will keep. @ East Caddo Creek https://t.co/N5k2LJ0Ly0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Generico I believe he is okay it’s just kinda funny lol.  Be aware though: my only source so far is my mom who h… https://t.co/0JSpHjfgFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorAnnMarieB HA you thought😂 that’s how you are going to support us in our old age😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when you least expect it.❄ @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/c87Jn8d2Tu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nervzndepizza @NBA @NBATV Solid 7th tonight, just a few games from 5th.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaroDuarteArte @IvanDuque 👏👏👏👏👏 Muchos horrores han hecho esos psicopatas no más impunidad!! Te apoyo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCHS_CoachWill @GrantMyers44 @PickensHighGa @pickensad @chris_parker222 Congrats Coach!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Clerical job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. Billing Associate -… https://t.co/uWZIbRHzVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Jersey teen arrested for beating elderly man over MAGA hat https://t.co/8hxFybvHsz via @nypost   I’ll bet you d… https://t.co/oWToPhAGzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisOD65316390 You must admit the quote is right on point.   Rarely mentioned anymore is he?]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you forget to make a fucking payment and gotta pay the pass due fee https://t.co/3q9O3kGAdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got this sooooo cute souvenir from the advance screening.👩🏻🗡😍👍🏼👍🏼 #Alita #AlitaBattleAngel #TwoThumbsUp #SoCal #AMC… https://t.co/NZMRgBrYlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s perfectly Christian of you to tell @KamalaHarris to “hush.” More people should, particularly CA voters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feelin’ fresh and clean with my crew at Trivia after our haircuts today. @ Tijuana Flats https://t.co/sE3GRUkAQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Retweeting this. If you can't afford to donate, a RT would help too. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACTBrigitte Performing next week at Madison square garden, performing their latest album "open borders, green will… https://t.co/21rSfR4gCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[L.A. will become biggest city in the U.S. to ban fur sales: Los Angeles will become the biggest city in the United… https://t.co/s9wFtqJDN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing smash in the work break room after hours with everybody reminded me of hanging out with friends in high sch… https://t.co/ntmxeLmSbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Trump Chat (@TrumpitC): https://t.co/bMqMj4zxK9 Best place to be #Maga]]></document><document><![CDATA[hilarity for me today. SHOE QUOTES - or cartoons in this case - Red Soles Rule! - #Fashion #Quotes #NICCI...… https://t.co/fRFPdJX05c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elite Bracket Championship Final  #IENationals @InsiderExposure   @WestridgeBBall 56  VS.   @blairbucs 47… https://t.co/VlLlTypsAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShayllasH @Sam_Levine @realDonaldTrump Yeah, and the Holocaust was a joke, too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rank-and-file Dems revolt against Pelosi over resolution to condemn anti-Semitism  https://t.co/k3BlfVClUn https://t.co/85CAZI5TkE]]></document><document><![CDATA[These @CPAC folks are so frightened of losing privilege and improving America through fairness that they have becom… https://t.co/8C9jiRpmCG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittMcHenry I'm a semi-retired Pit Boss and i know that Men, those with the XY chromosome, and women XX are diffe… https://t.co/gARLiPqzhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Great idea Bernie; just stop arresting criminals that cant afford bail;  skip the whole courts releasing them !]]></document><document><![CDATA[90s Night with Ja Rule was 🔥 . . . #FearTheDeer #LightItUp #90sNight #FyreFestival @ Fiserv Forum https://t.co/uOYZoTPlrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBsBigHouse1 @ShroomyBloom @SECNetwork @Vol_Hoops I clearly stated we have to start somewhere. Tennessee’s not bee… https://t.co/lDZjpM8rfe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tayah_irvin @maleajacks22 @mollywalton__ @amaya_hamilton This is a great memory that last a lifetime]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisxaaron_ it’s valentine’s day &amp; my car isn’t moving side to side :(((((]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WajahatAli @FrankLuntz He's a large part for the polarizing nature of America today because of his "work" for @newtgingrich in the 90s.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Count Nibula Chocolate Milk Stout by @FountainSqrBrew @ Ale Emporium — https://t.co/xZNKWr6Mgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[US firm returns $400m fund to Saudi Arabia over Khashoggi murder, at least some have principles!  https://t.co/r5creEGiOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@syorston @GeorgeTakei I just need five minutes on this phone.  I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. Day1… https://t.co/q9kDZjcgvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattB_WOF I think the Twins are better than everyone thinks.  We will know who was right at the end of the year. I… https://t.co/Y7fGFbtESG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TylerDumontNews @AngelicaKATU @boston25 That’s awesome, Tyler!  Angelica Rocks! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[The BEST way to spend the morning! #goodmorning #wakeupcall #happybaby #thatsmyboy #thatsmile @ Firefly Farm https://t.co/sDHaXLqIzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[My short film Keep “Your American Dream” was a success @spenational. Good conversations good people. I love being i… https://t.co/Owrs0ViGck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, @MarkHerringVA for standing up to this #FakeNationalEmergency declared by @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/s5FGP0QAuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the Jonathan Kelly murder trial, three morning witnesses positively identify Kelly as the shooter in a downtown… https://t.co/Nm7RkccX4G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truckingwithgnw Nope. Paid out of pocket for a company I signed on with. Did the required 3 weeks in school then 1… https://t.co/9E5HaafNaD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations Chris! Great role model for all young student-athletes! Non Vox Sed Votum.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got out of the shower and my roommate was standing outside the door just waiting and then proceeded to get mad… https://t.co/eFE3lZD5rQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_JeanPierre Your blame is in the wrong place, people of this country voted him in and your congress allows him to… https://t.co/mvu7kDvAsF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going on now @hs_woods the Performing Arts: Showcase of Bands! #warriorpride #performingarts https://t.co/3gUgUdj2cx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NateLull @DelhiBroncos @payt_dean34 @DelhiMensBball Congratulations Coach Thomsen!! You were a coach on the floor… https://t.co/d1G3a2glEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @Kris_Sacrebleu Trump is playing 3 card monte and America is the mark! We will never pick the right c… https://t.co/AIOQ4l3hzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @7Eleven in Woodland Hills, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/L7sPFnRuwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The edibles kicked in with the tincture and I’m hanging out with my family rn. https://t.co/9egHZNZi5u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come drop by for a lovely afternoon in Los Olivos at the gorgeous and tasty @zinkewines - Kids and small animals we… https://t.co/JR2mJcljAz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand up for the truth—and get updates on important #TrumpRussia news—with @StandUpAmerica's Trump-Russia Roundup: https://t.co/nEqAurerQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bud_cann @OCNaNa2013 It tells me running an illegal money laundering operation and using those resources to target… https://t.co/Cf6dP8mvFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trophies Figuires,HomeDepotInpaintareaAskforRattelCanSprayHandle,2minSEOfBunkhouseByBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just told this chick bout shmoke &amp; she said ew...Lmfaoo that’s a dub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don’t think people doing business with a foreign power should be investigated, but a televisio… https://t.co/DIdpskDrJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know many of us rarely watch all the way to the end of a #video - so here is the last 60 seconds from EP 116 -… https://t.co/BZ8hmFtlSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the text after hanging saying how much fun they had &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[It happened. It finally happened.  I know what my next short film is going to be. 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregSteinick Haha Kim and I are watching the movies too since it’s the fastest way to get her the story. That’s th… https://t.co/Pmk27e0Szw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw your face in a crowded place🌹 @ Drury Plaza Hotel Pittsburgh Downtown https://t.co/Jq2QbjVhHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the Floating Markets in Thailand! 🍜 🥘 https://t.co/vPk9sRAaD8   #floatingmarket #Thailand #travel #southeastasia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don’t exactly have the right to say you fought or served in any military. Remember those born spurs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to see Reggie go he is a man with so much personality and charisma and was good for a company I love… https://t.co/xLLK36o5tp]]></document><document><![CDATA[starbucksreserve_mil #starbucks #starbucksreserveroasterynyc #starbucksreserve #coffee #coffeenation #reserve… https://t.co/fpDlBTL93h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__katrinarenee Pretty much the same here. I am a psychiatric nurse. At first, I did my master for professional dev… https://t.co/Fp0y1e2Mg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachWhitsett I want to see what happened after he went over that 'jump'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing " Eleven Rose's " by Hank William's Jr. @ Grandstand's Bar &amp; Grill https://t.co/ty90xxu2VP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moms are the best thing to happen in this world. Try to prove me wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoteshockey Well,  of course.  And #GoPats while we're at it.  LA sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn “streaming live on the espn app”. Unless the content is blocked.  Thanks espn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr10 @ArizonaKayte @KAG4All @ReneeCarrollAZ @KatTheHammer1 @TrumpOrBust2020 @bbusa617 @buzzman888… https://t.co/v1xdsSqHtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ZacAttack was Student Of The Week at  oceanviewelementaryschool in Mrs Johnson's  ocean_view_room_24 class.  When… https://t.co/FSPjuZjrkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffborek Wonderful advice - For those outside the paywall - TL;DR:  Rule 1: It’s not about you 2: There is no bri… https://t.co/FhzXgV2uSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can We Find The Name Brand? (GAME) https://t.co/CGY1TjSRl8 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hagaman_kl I have a standard set out thought out plan if I ever need to too and I made this plan 20 years ago.  It… https://t.co/vrJIs4PUy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the amazing Rickey! . We have some truly amazing humans in our organization! . Giving opens the door to receiv… https://t.co/Zi5iUEtAOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIVEAWAY ALERT!!! For a chance to win a free copy of Brazyl Ward's Safe Ventures and an opportunity to support my f… https://t.co/F1grrfDX1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@npdgroup you should employ people who have a sense of maturity, and brains. @MatPiscatella lacks both, and when he… https://t.co/Y8HPfuLeTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bestnaunieever @MaryOsb36485285 @bigleaguepol CORRECT.ALLSOCONFLICTINTEREST,CUMMINGS ?- COHN BEFORE HEARING.ALLABOVELAW IT SEEMS.OPINION]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NotatRootsTech connecting vintage photo finds with their families and long lost relatives. While watching live thi… https://t.co/PQkHIBJNBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LcPepin @La12tuittera @TanoAngelici Exacto, estaba jugando bien Carlitos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Postgame: Mahtomedi Zephyrs Joe Paradise, J.D. Metz, coach Jeff Poeschl, Tom Paradise. #mshsl https://t.co/d4hk6eLVKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBrandon84 I'll take Jordan hicks over barr but I hear ya! #OnePride 🦁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ottawa has now officially traded their top-three scorers, let the long rebuild begin #TradeCentre #Senators]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Doom1776 @2020WinAgain @seanhannity Um, I'm scared. Ok, not really.  How much is the annual membership for #cult45 membership?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c_a_israel @AUCLAiTech I had a slight panic when all of my meetings seemed to be cleared from my calander! Happy to report they are back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starters for @MayfieldHoops: Michael Favazzo (JR), Michael Huss (SO), Denzel Seawood (JR), Neshawn Brown (SR), Hayden Nahra (FR)]]></document><document><![CDATA[How I pass 2 border patrol check points, and got searched my a police check point an still ain’t find the wax pen😂🧠😉]]></document></documents></author>