<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JBOpi1 And infuriating.  I absolutely LOATHE the patronizing attitude toward Bernie.  There is a real problem with… https://t.co/OlrtvTwtSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ricardorossello @pnp_pr @NatlGovsAssoc @MassGovernor @GovHawaii @LouisianaGov Gobe, almost ending February, and lo… https://t.co/5YK8M4Urv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[To those going through heartbreak. Or still dealing with an ex. Don’t give them a reason for leaving. Or cheating.… https://t.co/0Dmleob0wu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry I had a little photo shoot yesterday @ Lakewood, Ohio https://t.co/3fRwsW8l7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #chef #apron in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa https://t.co/Nbn6gAKXG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr Wilson is an an amazing educator that inspires greatness! @TampaBaySTEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @FRESL1brary to post 7 covers of books I LOVE with no explanations why. Each time I… https://t.co/bUCV9PNoaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[just moved to salt lake and i need some friends!!! HMU, a bitch is lonley out here &lt;/3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realTrumpForce @JudgeJeanine So what do we do?  How do we have them removed or handle this B. S.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triple6ixbangin swallow three times then stick your tongue out for 30 seconds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealLucyDavis @kimberlyaboltin Fuck! Happy Birthday sweet lady! May this year bring you all the joy you can handle… https://t.co/Mg8JN7vmtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[And then i thought about how @ClobberingTime7 and I had the DJ play this song at our wedding and how riled JenJen got 😂😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisamatonm jajaja ya viste el video de ayer de @maurg1 en YouTube? Sale la nota de luí oro comunica que hicieron hace como dos semanas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's day friends!! 💖💖 @backstreetboys @nickcarter @howied @aj_mclean @brian_littrell @kevinrichardson… https://t.co/ge1obzFHwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd section game!!  Nice job ladies!  Final section game in princeton on Thursday at 7!! @ Forest Lake Area High Sc… https://t.co/6tpBYCtbcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@omertene Ugh you are being so Omer right now. This is worse than when you asked me “what do you think?” At 9 am wh… https://t.co/glOlhU3Yg1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It happens everyday Yout going to ruin your life waiting around a fictional man His name may e Shawn Nothing he tol… https://t.co/pGfCHcw9Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a shower to wash this day (and night) away.  #ksautophagy here I come. @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/aFNC1VKN37]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katiebugg82714 @SCdeerseeker @Liibbbaa @MayBuhhLean @Jo_Rager You are so confused as to who you are talking to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FBI @CBP @ICEgov @TheJusticeDept : this Newsweek article raises some serious questions about #Nationalsecurity . R… https://t.co/Rhk7xEljBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate explaining a story .. I could care less if you don’t choose my side]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could not agree more and this is why I love #myMKlife #MaryKayCares @MaryKayGlobal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to be done with work. I can’t fight the tears anymore today. FML]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast day drinking in sunny San Diego today☀️🍹 https://t.co/hENZPUPAsY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s almost as good as watching rattle snakes 🐍 in trump administration turn on each other!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard butterfly on my shuffle and it gave me the craziest feeling. My heart did the craziest jump... i love u Kehlani ur beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls At least we know George is the one with the brains and the honest one.  https://t.co/ItjCcx3i0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an honour to be the fill in for the fill in when the fill in is @jannarden   See you today at 1PM on… https://t.co/Imf0sQqERw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all don’t get along with your boyfriend’s kid’s mom??? Can’t relate. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tag who comes up for each letter and spread some #FF kindness!  k @HellbenderHecht i @biologistimo  n @PlethodoNick… https://t.co/4A3LI0H6lI]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Til the day I die.” tobymac #hitsdeeptour @ Ted Constant Convocation Center https://t.co/3yZA4ozLzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[didn’t wanna drop these on ig vibes 🦁🖤 #yourfavpeliroja #akalanarca https://t.co/9JgZ5yzxka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nflnetwork @Terrell_Davis @MJD @NFLTotalAccess H-NO!!! What is @johnelway thinking???🧐🧐🧐😫😫🥺🤷🏻‍♀️💙🧡🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gehem007 @BleachedRatTail @KillaColls @Amjie @jakedgoode @BakerSullivan @IlhanMN Are you stupid? These “scientists… https://t.co/xdTmyJDHAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great seeing my kids play!! @SJHSTrojans #sjhstrojans https://t.co/y6BpepfU5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fighting with my family was such a great movie!!! @RealPaigeWWE @TheRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y usted se va de trabajo de campo el lunes para no ponernos la cara con la vergüenza de la JEP , o se va a hacer el… https://t.co/dvER2loSyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisEvans Those are my mothers words. I swear. She said exactly the same thing when we watched you tonight! 👏🏻💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell And please stop with the gross air “fresheners” that make me want to hang my head out the window in the rain!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to reunite with aj like he literally is my whole happiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chris Syler - Contigo siempre (Con letra) https://t.co/sj9zF2YjpW via @YouTube🙏🏻😇😍😘🥰🙌🏻☝🏻☝🏻☝🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[global warming just cancelled nearly all of my classes for the week 🤷🏻‍♀️🤘🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarrisonSmith85 @DeathHouseMovie @JasonMcFiggins @TriCoastEnt Shit get Fosters to sponsor Death House! It will even up the sales!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You simply aren’t  facing your own racism and bias.  Still making it about the right!  You’re a sad woman !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks and @WeAreTheWrecks are the only things getting me through this work day]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot text me and say oh I don’t wanna say it now.. like then don’t bring it up at all that pisses me off when people do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh fuck i am NOT ready for all these couple pics I’m about to see all over insta 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stonington hangs on to a 42-39 win over Griswold. Bears get 12 points each from Zach Scott and Cooper Wall, advance… https://t.co/PhETjVXFpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanCottenWF  Our picture with Coach Manning made Baptist Hospital webpage. https://t.co/xm3E3GxuRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[in 3rd grade i ate a tomato clump at lunch and i literally thought i was going to die so i went and laid in the bed… https://t.co/7h3piN3oyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NumbersMuncher Or when DJT doesn't get his Big Mac as ordered.......sexist much??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyV178 I do ! I love when they start insulting me or when they go into a MAGA live  feed and start insulting me… https://t.co/ZeCJb17mp9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Old Homestead has been around to see it all. Established in 1868, by a German immigrant family, the restaurant… https://t.co/VTtGQMH44t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like he is but at the same time he seems to just be conservative with it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to just sleep. I need my responsibilities to go away so I can just sleep this feeling away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I see you baby, shaking’ that ass” 😍😍😍😍😍 @ Rabbit Lake Township, Crow Wing County, Minnesota https://t.co/np9IxwaUu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I’m not going to do today is compare all of the health and wellness I’ve achieved to someone else’s. I will no… https://t.co/UsUHBbHHOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad used to throw all of us like this at the lake, it was fun 🤷🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MEDITECH Congrats @MEDITECH Digital Marketing Team  @cparent44 @CarolMarkets @JPatnode @NerdyWriting and your team… https://t.co/5M6sBXDqpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the heart pain I was scared to go see a doctor about for the past three months which turhed out to be costo… https://t.co/7BDClymkrN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor @OriginalBarryJ had to work later than expected so we couldn't make it out to Turkey Creek. 😞 But then fortune… https://t.co/7vFced6tYz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fly2mebutterfly @Dpuccini_5 @GodsGirl1989 @AlphaWolf2018 @iNorMel @grech_samantha @JennSurvivoraav @Coreenfw5… https://t.co/eJodEqR7BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylamsturkey @itsNICKSNIDER @GlamLifeGuru @HaloBeauty It be,so with redness! I have rosacea and it flares up less… https://t.co/lQfs4g6492]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @Holly2360 Mr.McFeely Pedo is a disgrace to this Country https://t.co/wmo5bDJWK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlashiKat @collette04 @smoking_reedus @leedusme1227 @uoklilbrother @BethHeartP @Walkingdeadluv3 @OeverDaphne… https://t.co/iqwHWE2zYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LIZ_khal_ifa @Car1yFr1es  has! I’m dying to watch... tomorrow’s the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealOddTodd @CNN Donald Trump's pipeline of undocumented workers https://t.co/sGRInXXR5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just gave me goosebumps. Go @PeteButtigieg - if you haven’t seriously looked at this guy for President - PLEAS… https://t.co/KjAoWgGLKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blake Shelton Tells Cody Alan New Music Is Coming Soon https://t.co/jAIVKwoxhQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit y'all I forgot to set an alarm and woke up at the last possible minute. And I made it to work on time! 🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic 6 bedroom 3 full bath home! Many upgrades is this wonderful home close to houses of worship! Listed at 49… https://t.co/cDQZE3oZ93]]></document><document><![CDATA[ok I'm watching leaving neverland and like yea this is how you groom a child and their parents. this is how rich ppl get away with this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a true honor to come to the @Qualtrics Experience Management Summit. @jennykutz @RennyArensberg and I hav… https://t.co/7RWg8Ods30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Woke up late &amp; still took my time getting ready. I give no fucks today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I couldn’t think of a better way to celebrate #InternationalWomensDay with these amazing women of @NASAKepler at… https://t.co/PQgMDR726y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning! Thought it would be a good idea to watch Lebanon &amp; now I’m crying before 8 am. 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que está haciendo estos malandros con los apagones,es neutralizar a nuestro presidente Guaidó,sin importarles cu… https://t.co/jeUqO38RXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[STILL PRAYING JASON JORDAN RETURNS TO THE RING VERY SOON, THAT MAN BELONGS IN THAT #WWE RING #RAW #RAWPhiladelphia… https://t.co/J0DePq2K0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is outstanding. This is why we fight @IDWPublishing @IDWEntertain @netflix #FightForWynnona #Earpers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so a state senator (who is a former Harris County prosecutor and judge) filed a bill that would make it a *felon… https://t.co/ASvPufaX00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morgmorgan25 WELL I DON'T SEE YOUR LOOSE SKIN BRAH!!! https://t.co/JE4kKEFZLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson Pelosi and her “COVEN “! Trying too hard, Pelosi! You are still just an old battle axe!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy March everyone !!! And a very happy Friday !! https://t.co/Mn3ZKy1nZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Can't Handle Olivia Colman's Upset Oscar Win Over Glenn Close | W Magazine https://t.co/xCt6csggWu via @wmag]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk what to wear for international badge day tomorrow, so i’m not going.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone took my Lyft ride last night and charged over $100 to my bank account for damages... WHOEVER YOU ARE YOU REALLY SUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 2 😉 @danmillerotown @iamerikestrada at Starbucks in Nashville   have a great show tonight Guys wishing I coul… https://t.co/Aco0J37dUB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kare_kari I'll take one and am sending one back. It has been a tough week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish people could forgive as much as they want forgiveness!! My son has aspergers and sometimes says things that… https://t.co/mAog9vq3Je]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch so hard mimosas wanna find me 🍍🕶🥂 @ EJ's Bayfront Cafe https://t.co/brk9n3GdfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 8.0 mph WNW. Barometer 30.181 in, Rising. Temperature 11.5 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 64%]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday afternoon dreams... 😴😌🤔🥰 #lazyday #napping #dreams https://t.co/iDrle8vPaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muslimfireman And watch the hole in the net above you head, sometimes pucks come through there! Makes a nice little souvenir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @BSkoobie @foxnewspolitics  Why has Fox been so quiet about this scandal.   https://t.co/8eVl6mK7JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[rly though me and @alysegundo have gone through so much life together it’s dumb ILY https://t.co/EXEv9vBhRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seconding shooting a wedding today...   conquering all my fears this year, so don’t be surprised if I quit my job t… https://t.co/tHWdJhl3ME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Return to sender (@ US Post Office in Johnson City, TN) https://t.co/5j1KH3CvH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinFarmerWSB This is... disturbing. I live on poverty pay and have zero intention of being this disruptive over… https://t.co/0u3DsCkEcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friend: “how’s your Friday night? “.          Me: oh. Just another bloody nose. Nbd.                 #canwebedonewiththeheatersyet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Umbralwalker I'm sure I have so so so many more, but it is late. I will try to add then tomorrow ❤]]></document></documents></author>