<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tkweaveractor *Happy Saturday* TK! #ActorBuddy 😎👍🌈☀️ https://t.co/sbcLAumcJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magic Treat yourself to https://t.co/VE9rWuqnWj from magicalbutter these cannabis infused #tri berry ! #lasvegas… https://t.co/U1RTTvJnHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinNewsom People need to wake up Congress is becoming a anti security for our Americans. Gavin and company are t… https://t.co/dg33cZxgf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[These “moderate “ voices will be the death of us. We’re looking at the most corrupt administration in modern histor… https://t.co/MyAUymU9g9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good advice. Check smoke and carbon monoxide alarms today. I’ve seen them save lives.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliesurely She just got re-elected possibly to her last term. She’s finally free! 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSMT88 @anypigslft @brassman66 @briantcairns @pavone120 @SallyAlbright Hey IT, quit trying to impersonate an Ameri… https://t.co/OOXyq8NiWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜🦋 Fighting for the #lupus cure starts with learning more about the #disease Raise your awareness 🙌💜📚💜 #educate you… https://t.co/W841Z6drHl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m incredibly thankful to women like @ChristinaKahrl who helped pave the way for trans women like me to work in th… https://t.co/WCD1mcbrdf]]></document><document><![CDATA[shout out to the @jonasbrothers for being my motivation to get through these midterms xoxo u the best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arruda_j What is it and where can you get it. And kudos for riding in Oshawa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right after confirmed touchdown of tornado in Columbus, MS #WCBI #MSWX https://t.co/SPwQpd61oe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElNacionalWeb Lamentablemente estamos a 1 paso de una situación caótica con saqueos y agresiones a la propiedad privadas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you start getting dressed after  few drinks and finish after a joint ... https://t.co/ZBtRecAeaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secupp @SpeakerPelosi @Ilhan If she doesn’t understand then maybe foreign affairs is the perfect committee. No one… https://t.co/3RLQoRP8j7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatTheBerner @Bananas4Bernie IMO the surest way to get Bernie elected would be to slip sodium pentathol into the w… https://t.co/OO1oSR5wow]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just a mama’s boy ❤️ frame it #WHPSheInspiresMe @Instagram  #Me 👉🏽😂✌🏽🐦 @Sixp8ck - 📷📹 #ShreddedBeyondABSolute… https://t.co/j2NzNnBTs3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emily_singer “Athleisure, in any case, means different things for different people. I tend to think of it as activ… https://t.co/gxwVv7rZRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[wait wait im now a joke to you but yet yo family and you said other wise 🤧 can’t hurt me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts with Coach Boeheim and everyone involved. Some things transcend sports.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta stop waking up every morning and the first thing I think about is skipping class https://t.co/58wxEIh98c]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KnowlegeIsPower #Dexcom #DexcomG6 #CapitalismIsGood #T1D #FirstWorldProblems #Insights #Diabetes #Wisdom #Fatigue… https://t.co/vfbkSSkcIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dooglaaone @wbz I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Presidents Quincy HOME Day1 US… https://t.co/P7plDNahe9]]></document><document><![CDATA[also all of this screams @kyleknudson, give my man a follow as he is very clearly helping hearthstone out in a big way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/z8Olwe78Gz Nate and Cheryl along with coach Dillon Nelson are getting closer to being ready for the Ma… https://t.co/ky9g6vyNh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MHanson62 17 and 71 are also retired. Could I interest you in a medi-evil times 'Z'?"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't expect @WWERomanReigns to be in action this soon. So glad he is back and will get to be involved in #WrestleMania #WWEFastlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you do your taxes and they say you need to pay this year 💀😂😂😭😭😭 alv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JFranimal1989 @SarahSpain CD was scratched or something. It is a 90’s celebration lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jav174 @BlackTonyStark_ I can dig it. I’m still shocked that people are saying J Cole &gt; 2Pac....new generation I guess.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coolmaccags56 A-Mac, would appear as if you encountered a mental enema, in the form of a 9 shot swing.  Steady the… https://t.co/AAUh8c1ubv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The blind leading the deaf dumb and blind. No not really. Just the 2 dumbest piles of toxic waist. You've the White… https://t.co/cdi3M2Zneu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dany_bahar @JShellinsky @IlhanMN You want him to be held "accountable," but you are throwing a hissy fit over 10 m… https://t.co/ZTBkecL2TL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at AMC Veterans 24 - @amctheatres in Tampa, FL https://t.co/xY5txcBQld]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was a long journey from 258 lbs to 182. Y’all don’t understand how much better I feel physically but most important… https://t.co/AOnwvNJdaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be clear I’m not offended, though I can understand why others would be. I’m just BORED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDCLBlog Nice giving folks a few chances to go on Fantasy without paying 7 night pricing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCM @MindiMink @karleegreyxxx @RachelStarrxxx @Zoeyfoxx @SummerDayXXX @JillKassidyy @onlyjennafoxx @APOLONIAPORN… https://t.co/cfJ4d7lk1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maryland_Sam Any Ravens fan who doesn’t love Joe wasn’t a fan before 2014, no other explanation. Guy was a killer… https://t.co/uKfHBXMLJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIIDeaton Forgive me, I was wrong 4 saying that. It's not 4 me to judge a person's salvation—one or more of them m… https://t.co/7Isjay8oue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamierodr14 @smalltownandrew Democrats and Republicans will always say what you want to hear Trump's the only one… https://t.co/LTkOFSX2h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 In that case there’s no need to watch the Olympic Games....... it’s over!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the other Double-A 4/5 game, SE5 @Baldwin__Hockey defeated NW4 @MoonHockey 3-0  The Highlanders advance to play… https://t.co/x1EZ7bhOld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bnw852 @summershamrock @josephspencer00 @Kieran_IsAGod @BeckyLynchWWE Yeah your right but in the eyes of WWE I thi… https://t.co/OYn9WuSWSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OwenMcCain @aylex519 @LukeWolly I would hope so since it is a hairless cat LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the 44 presidents whose elections were not stolen by a foreign power, I went (again) Russian bot huntin… https://t.co/xFfB9ysSgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you see someone hurting, pray with them. If you see something good thank God for it. If you are going through so… https://t.co/YRsEConwgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izzyrz @YouNicks @58isthenew40 Made by infowars Alex Jones. Too funny. No conspiracy too goofy for that guy. This… https://t.co/P1F8PvUQGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work with Kevin for the past 15 years  His community involvement is an example for all of us @GawthropLaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[For anyone who hasn't submitted to San Japan's lottery-jury Artist Alley, you have a few hours left:  https://t.co/myItoXLfQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catharxis_ @twentyonepilots Ahhhh! Josh is shirtless again! LoL Italy got to hear some great music!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasVegetarian Do you always remember it as Chick-fil-a or do you have memories of it being Chic-fil-a?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Chicago reflected in #LakeMichigan as seen from an airplane https://t.co/AGPzmkD6WK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMus_Ed @EL_ASCD @CraigCMartin12 @thelearningloop @Krista_Leh @NameyEquityHCPS @KyleHamstra @bamameghan @ASCDconf… https://t.co/jqMugGJ1QO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jensmith207 @andreapatrick @jodimac99 @StephanieMoshe8 Thanks for the shout Jennifer!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/8/2019 - 05:51 Temp: 47.5F   Hum:  89% Wind: 0.0 mph Baro: 29.953in. &amp; Falling Rain: 0.04 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@higlaud2 @mattgaetz @TulsiGabbard @CNN 😂😂😂 With a recommendation from him... No thanks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is not about being rich, being popular, being highly educated or being perfect. It is about being smart, being… https://t.co/HeTmpII8ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[People need to realize that the Democratic’s are the racist. Think MIRROR. Whatever they left says to the right it’… https://t.co/8dxvVEgR0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @WattersWorld @JesseBWatters @foxnation Lmmfao clown you are a Non Factor you audience is nothing but a… https://t.co/XyNpM3POnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southernwayjim @KatTheHammer1 She didn’t even know the district she was to represent when she filed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To be fair, Real Madrid looked way inferior to Ajax and Barcelona did not set the world ablaze against a Lyon side.… https://t.co/RNJUiM98JP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juxtapaused @RickSantorum Is there anyone who would side with Trump on this? Aside from his family? And Sarah Slanders?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ninja warrior summer camp. #taekwondouniversity #liveyourpotential #taekwondo #ninja @ Taekwondo University Olive B… https://t.co/0DnxypZM9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KPRC2AdamW @KPRC2 Nothing about a 6 foot 8 250 pound man going flying to the floor?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManMadeMoon @asano_tadanobu Can I be in it too? I can be cardboard box #3 or hot guy #2 in the background. 🙋🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briantheguppie @coupdebanks I've seen that done in NJPW &amp; ROH &amp; its a sick move if done right]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Linda Ronstadt leads kids to the intersection of arts and understanding across the border: Rosa Ar… https://t.co/oN4wCpmwhr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chump's in Vietnam, finally. That's nice, maybe he won't come back.  #CohenTestimony https://t.co/el20aYWPni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @EMluvsPibbles @Jr3597 @ChaliceGarden @BCWildfireToday… https://t.co/SaYfJfYDYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerweber Even if no one does remember...it is part of Congressional history now...so no excuse for not proving the facts and truth! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got a @MSUHatch student pitching here at #SXSW19 in the Student Startup Madness Finals!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ferdoval Incluye "Todas las anteriores" para que tengas un 100% en esa.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimserwan @RepSwalwell @volvocars You, sir, are a fucking pussy.  Grow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's like saying Bill Daley's endorsement of Barack Obama defies the legacy of Chicago's white politicians disenfra… https://t.co/LpZg0MNtSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ndnpro64 @RunADZ_ CP gonna get hurt again this year, whats the big F-n deal]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dæmonium by @RoyalDocksBrew at @RoyalDocksBrew — https://t.co/asdVFO1Dy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking Yay! Now there are enough for a #TIGger football team! @SkyNews @BBCNews @tnewtondunn @Peston… https://t.co/DZxET9AVVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PADI So I’m going to add octopus the food I don’t eat anymore now, this guys are smart and have awareness, I don’t… https://t.co/Z8xaGCRodS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@votevets Not surprising since his Government shutdown proved he is unconcerned that military members go without pay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 seeds are good, but as we saw last year with Titanic, 1 seeds can fall. Looking forward to the match-ups.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastAndrew @NBCSGiants @PavlovicNBCS Think they’d shell out another $200 mil+ for machado?😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Sing Me Away by Night Ranger https://t.co/V1f27dJYC0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just had a beer with my close personal friend, Mayor Bill De Blasio. It's an Iowa thing. In a blizzard.… https://t.co/0gpb2ay694]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daughter Sara covered the President's trip to the Alabama tornado site. https://t.co/hUGsa6pGqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jazzmenlanae @RalphsGrocery @kroger @SimpleTruth4U Lmfao Jaz no. It could’ve been poisonous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RafaelAPolanco @jordigarciatv @Sitvrd @Chapuli56617913 @radafil_diaz @ljpaulino @angrudo88 @CONCACAFDOMINI… https://t.co/IScSlTR7Rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeVeonBell the Path to the New Green Jersey is set for you! Free Agency off to a great start @jamisoncrowder and… https://t.co/ctApEWyb18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I finished the book of Exodus. Now getting ready to take the challenge of Leviticus. Smile!]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m at Dunkin Donuts picking up breakfast and then I’m going to walk my dogs.  Pretty sure my day is already be… https://t.co/83T9UsNGET]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I see this.... the best thing ever to see the final play of the last game of my 4 years😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[McCaleb Wise with a big double today in the bottom of the 6th to put the game winning run at 2nd. Beat Boswell 4-3… https://t.co/n7D9kJjPBX]]></document><document><![CDATA[my favorite parts of the #gerryandersonpodcast: 1) @RichardNJames singing “that was the news,” 2) the twinkly music… https://t.co/rLdcGTPsnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was thinking about finding a date for valentine’s day (which would be easy considering how hot and cool i am 😎),… https://t.co/ChG1EVAiuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you include the women who were "working"  at the massage parlor that your dear friend Kraft visited?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cowards_are_us @Jim_Jordan @Morning_Joe @SpeakerRyan @senatemajldr I forgot about that https://t.co/hNyy0i0Fch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @raulv48 @bryanMackSC @Tesla This is literally you right now... https://t.co/52VzAZufF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MNVikesCentral @hungryamerican As a @Braves fan and @Vikings fan, I say yes!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only @llizzzieee would answer my text messages😒 https://t.co/O33hlbcYUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the convention of states ending illegal immigration for the preservation of OUR nation must be addressed]]></document></documents></author>