<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Here is my first art, done while I wait for airplane parts to do interference checks. It reminds me of those weird… https://t.co/ZxupiGuMZz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JSDMusic3000 @Yascha_Mounk No it's not. Rep. Omar is not afraid to express herself. She's been critical of the Sau… https://t.co/iajmLNMH7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaslhorrocks I’m in one but barely use mine so ¯\_(ツ)_/¯ (recently I’ve been thinking about whether it would do… https://t.co/uZ7vsWXYpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UofSC_SJMC @Michaela_Baker @HarrisPastides I understand...  but it still hurts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone with some juice start a campaign to ban the word “porno” from the world’s vocabulary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No west wind blow torch, Big US model bust as GFS had temps surging to upper  30s. We stayed at  32.  Bought a few extra hours of no melt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I'm really stoked that @trey_tatum and my #podcast 'Off the Record' has over 300 plays for the past several mo… https://t.co/CfqNdL3km3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LongHornSteaks #LongHornSteaks Ate with some good people today.  Great stuff. https://t.co/ERDeSmkwKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brooklyncowboy1 They don't call them 40 mph couch potatoes for nothing lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaginMaginl @SlenderSherbet She really didn’t have to flex on em that hard]]></document><document><![CDATA[We don’t have much time left.  Prepare.  Organize.  Make contingency plans.  Love your family, neighbors, your coun… https://t.co/KLV0964uXp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se dan cuenta que gracias a @lacademiaazteca aprendimos geografía, gracias a ellos aprendimos donde esta Tantoyuca… https://t.co/mlMkZHnclk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa. #Brexit is like a showcase of the cost of accumulating estimation errors. Underestimate option value, then un… https://t.co/45rIY5fd8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscars without a host is great so far. Tina Fey, Maya Rudolph, and Amy Poehler should host the ceremony next year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimcramer Is this another fake merger to drive up price?  Like RAD or Sprint and on and on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichDevitaIII @tradestreetpost @BaconDwayne1000 @Devonte4Graham @hornets Or they know they are benched in CLT and… https://t.co/udAQXUJb0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[This economic cycle will soon top the '90s and be the longest ever.   But old doesn't mean it has to end. In fact,… https://t.co/6GAyLsGQpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers @conecora1 @realAliTweets It says everything I need to know about Bernie. I regret supporting him.… https://t.co/HRMznzYmjO]]></document><document><![CDATA['A Hit Dog Will Holler': Trump Lashes Out At Spike Lee's Oscar Acceptanc... https://t.co/Fu7XH8NbP3 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why more guys don’t try this. I think this is more impressive than throwing it in the bleachers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhostOfTick @Raider_Hayter @BuddhaKatze @UncleJoe5465 @Mharris888H @Trumpbane1969 @AbrahamAlyzah @cowboys20041… https://t.co/DFBj8r3Njl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oahu_Raider808 It’s nice to know I’m not alone. Go Irish!☘️ Go Raiders! 🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PolskieRadio24 @jakubiak_marek Koniczyna wiedla, wiedla i zrobila sie teczowa...Witos w grobie wiruje gdy pedaly z… https://t.co/sMvT7u0xmj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@playfairdata signed up for the email list/free ebook a while ago. How long should should it to receive welcome email? @ryanvizzes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to ghost write a series of medical texts under the name Angie O'Plasty]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, @ChrisLevel, we aren’t having fun yet. #Stress #Championship #PleaseWin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yamiche when discussing Bernie pledging to be one a Democrat on @Morning_Joe with @morningmika   Why didn’t you me… https://t.co/EvWXefBPO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is good. - Drinking a Here &amp; There: MegaBlend by @tiredhandsbeer/@SideProjectBrew at @tiredhandsbeer  — https://t.co/yRMwOqTGoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxBusiness @FOX2News @foxandfriends Game changer- SUV out Cars in. New .50 per gallon gas tax needs aerodynamic andight weight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@asia_ilse @PEPFAR @jpatadams 1 million people die of HIV each year. Funding and implementing @WHO #AdvancedHIV pac… https://t.co/XSAc07IHUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alfonso___7 Let’s take your terrible predictions to Vegas and cash out 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[UGH! Team Blue won the competition 28 to 20! This means @iamkellsmcc and I have to be PIED in the face at our next… https://t.co/arBJc8Mf52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThtWrestleClub I thought that wrestling club was no more and now turning into prowrestling crate because I was jus… https://t.co/lnDMp1RJol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrcoEsquandolas @CincyToLondon I don’t doubt that! Next time phish plays Walnut Creek I’ll bring barbecue &amp; Brunswick stew to lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phu Quoc is now a global destination. Is that a good thing?: There are times, as your plane swoops down over somepl… https://t.co/og8qw43GKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[we salute  #Electronica #tecnomusic  #industrialmusic .@SynthoElectro  .@WeatnuRecords #weatnu CHEERS respect… https://t.co/h2oMfaFapS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow! Quite impressive! Congrats ladies, Coach Robinson, and the rest of the staff! #HowardPride]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alagrandslammer The ERA and fielding are particularly encouraging.If we can keep that in the upper 7 or 8 of the league we've got a chance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Glenn Ligon #glennligon #regenprojects @regenprojects @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/xmXcaoYITP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Blackhawks. Dylan Strome was absolutely non-existent in the shootout!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay strong my love, LOVE CONQUERS ALL!  It's difficult to remember this simple idea when you're surrounded by 'rea… https://t.co/hM3CuzKiDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awilkinson It makes me want to smash something every time I get a message interrupting me somewhere embarrassing b… https://t.co/msr5MifAzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdomenech @JohnFeehery If this chart is true, why do Republicans want to ban all abortions??? 60% approve 1st trimester]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaSeasn 1/2 Last time I checked, Poirier served Holloway his first L in the UFC. Yeah, he lost to Conor, but Dus… https://t.co/MFKOTAhiqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dominikhonnef @Gladpus Nice work! @Gladpus could I please contract your services for some Gopher related illustrations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MJP1313 @jamiedupree Mr. Whataboutism, here’s the answer. None of them look made up like the “Emergency at the boa… https://t.co/ahUBEnRbWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to see another day @jimmbsc @VannagrammyLiz @RareCat @PicBallot @HariG_IN @JAclouds @BrendaFlournoy1… https://t.co/ULIolJCt1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat is so fat.  I moved all the furniture so I could mop the house today and this is what I came back to. https://t.co/GG9ZtykPTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Lol Adam u on some good dumb drugs with all your corruption Democrats investigate All nothing there… https://t.co/kuU3aj0C2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update on Mopac Fire.  Truck is located at 11600 Blk of Mopac Southbound just south of Duval overpass. The only lan… https://t.co/rDHWzcWMzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[varsity boys soccer is under way at MISD Stadium McKinney North Bulldogs vs Denison Yellowjackets]]></document><document><![CDATA[Say what you want about Bush senior he could at least take a freaking joke. Trump is a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gregclauson @HowardSchultz @CNN Because of how much Starbucks is mentioned]]></document><document><![CDATA[i thought i was the onlynone going thru this omg, i been trying everyday for the last week and it’s been gray area]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @KamalaHarris @SenSchumer @RepMaxineWaters @DNC #DemocratsArePoison #DemocratsAreCorrupt… https://t.co/rUFcuRsHtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto @Trumpsters45 Save CPD time and taxpayers money, set him loose with some real rednecks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNTOGETHER Trailer | 2019 (Jamie Dornan, Billy Crystal, Alice Eve, Ben M... https://t.co/ylSNILQJCX via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngeldebritoOk La verdad kudos x la entrevista de ayer con todo el caso Jaitt - los veo x YouTube ( me encanto la corbata )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darialebedeva They share the blame, but they’re just following Apple’s lead here :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OpTicHitch I like some of the changes they made. I like BO4 though. I’m a fan boy. But that’s Optics fault]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever disrespect me or one of my roommates in our house and u will get ur shit knocked. motherfuckers always tryna act bigger then they are 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[told my mom about that momo thing and everything else that’s going on in the world   my mom: making sure she cast d… https://t.co/VOf2sABJnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why didn’t Twitter delete @KDTrey5 twitter account for using fake ones defending himself? 😂 @Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully not too many more mornings like this. Ready to do some #bassfishing c’mon spring @ Churchville, Maryland https://t.co/4eTIM10HiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMHague13 @rmayemsinger If you believe our president, we're not getting much news about America, either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the volume down in preparation to falling asleep, and then the last two rounds happened #DirrellYildirim]]></document><document><![CDATA[More exciting news @WyffelsHybrids meeting today!🌽💪 On the home front, the hibernating hounds were dreaming about s… https://t.co/jY8Gseak6u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pistons have been the most efficient team with the best offense in basketball since the beginning of February and h… https://t.co/3jSrAVq3F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love when the spirit Moves 6 1st time Salvations 5 rededications and many kids praying for healing over sickness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaredStansbury What about Uncle Rob? We’ve had some good times (and terrible pizza).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hintze_steve @LittleMissFlint @realDonaldTrump We used to have a clean water and air act before Trump cut the provisions. 🥴🥴🥴🥴🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh what could’ve been if Ty Griggs completed this putback dunk. #nebpreps https://t.co/wWt0Ok5LWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @wsternks It always worth fighting for Justice even if you loose!  #Impeachment]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Michigan #PureMichigan #US @Kaleidoband w/ also @ChristinaChriss #Leadsinger in #Band on #Facebook @  To head to V… https://t.co/VeAAE3SyxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this news to you? Stay current with all the news from ASU and earn Pitchforks toward great rewards! https://t.co/afvYNMvFg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaliaSchlanger @MorningEdition And that she first asked him to join her in having tea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natnewswatch As if Peter MacKay has a clue about how this PMO operates!! Give me a break. You can do better this t… https://t.co/bLk3FajZ7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 hours of audio that’s sure to melt your brain https://t.co/QZyi6anF5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember wiping your ass with those fingers and getting potato chips afterwards without washing them? How's that "c… https://t.co/LDmIOp68DS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @__ctack__ can’t wait for my Cincy visit https://t.co/TQhs5gqTvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillReporter I think paranoia has set in the American way of life. God Bless America!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think #putin has unfavorable information on #trump and that’s why trump always favors Putin, or do you think… https://t.co/Gl2QY0IOkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully @derraleves hour long video about the YouTube algorithm will help me understand what's going on here. Can… https://t.co/Vle2bAV69J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonKyle00 @ZerlinaMaxwell @Russian_Starr @TheRoot My mother was who hipped me to Julian Castro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1) The other night I got assaulted at work. This clingy, over-sharing 50 year old woman is a regular at my work. Sh… https://t.co/MW5aJkg8RP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mhodg89 @RealJayWilliams Lottery picks are supposed to be cornerstones of your franchise aka a Dwayne Wade type.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima get me one of those fury ass two pieces with the mini skit from fashion nova]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are some glaring historical inaccuracies in the article (e.g., history of panoramas) but the contextualizario… https://t.co/owglXnZYCN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t watched A Star is Born yet but thanks to @melissavcomedy on SNL and @ladygaga last night at the Oscars, I… https://t.co/Kny9TXfpKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @VZWSupport why is it when I lose 4g service my phone won't pick it back up until I turn airplane mode on and then back off?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good bye #towerclimber #telecommunications #211ft #att #fun #grateful #done #rru #antenna bishop #vagabond #✊🏽 had… https://t.co/1lQ2uV6k47]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @nytimes @realDonaldTrump Nothing matters anymore.  We are fucked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your debt is your own problem but imo the government should create a program to where students can take out as many… https://t.co/FNK72Fsq2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping you’re the reason why, searching for eternal high. Someone to save me take me off this rollercoaster ride. I… https://t.co/4mS52Nt2iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA Live useta be sooo much better than NBA 2K. NBA Live 2005 was a cultural shift. Real gamers know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @TheRealSambora heads up. USAF thunderbirds are flying over Malibu and Pepperdine and SMO and Hollywood Monday… https://t.co/DGGfZrGFh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey are you laughing now at you boy Juessie Karma is a bitch LOL Karma watch out for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will be signing tomorrow, 2 pm in the lobby at JC! Everyone is welcome to come!! https://t.co/95iAh61TTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donalfonso1890 Two Stars Michelin Chef Ernesto Iaccarino will be joining us tomorrow night to introduce some of hi… https://t.co/TuhbGa6935]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SurlyNotAWalrus @nytopinion @FrankBruni What do you think experts could have done differently to educate the masses?]]></document></documents></author>