<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If someone is stupid enough to walk away from you, be smart enough to let them go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nkotbgal21 @NKOTB_LV @SportsCenter First they are deflating balls, now paying for sex!?! 😉🤔🙈🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImDonaldJTrump happy to celebrate my President's day...so proud to have a great leader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndersonNickee @JackCDLee @proturnedexvax @Dreadpirate42 @4everleather1 @Flwrgirl66x @Charbrevolution @CplBart… https://t.co/y6Xv9AtpPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fam and Phillip are having bacon wrapped steaks w baked potatoes and salad &amp; what do I get?????? Grits... :’) #OverThisTonsillectomy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mla28 Wait...what? Girl, close your eyes and listen to the interview. That way you won’t see what color the jackas… https://t.co/EGr0B4Oojv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nthandamanduwi Trust me there will be more laughter because s/he will be a blend of both of you plus their own per… https://t.co/7Lxz1Xfa4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riddick_5 @OFemmeFataleZ @DelSchilling Well you think that all white males are bad  based on a couple of bad white… https://t.co/z6l1PxHc3c]]></document><document><![CDATA[When everyone is held accountable the W’s become the norm —- as a Coach , if you let one player slide and just do w… https://t.co/JotxqeqfnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@i_kevsl Cant see the video. Dammit. Ur caption made me want to see whats going on.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same goes for "your" and "you're"...oh, and "then" and "than"...let's not forget "it's" and "its"...sheesh...… https://t.co/IY63Lb0u9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk if it was a car in front of me, or an employee, or @tacobell itself that paid for me tonight, but regardless, thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I could have more friends if I wasn’t such an antisocial asshole, ya feel?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤑 Florida massage parlor owner has been selling Chinese execs access to Trump at Mar-a-Lago https://t.co/yOmamHJzta via @MotherJones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here comes that  amazing “hall” fight. Which won’t be equaled until season 3. #savedaredevil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pithywidow though that too had a vaguely mafioso feel (like he's the guy who would scare the shit out of the ER su… https://t.co/Hj52224nZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weisenburger says Hardeman was cured of hepatitis C in 2006 and any abnormal cells caused by the virus would have d… https://t.co/P2CSQtR4ro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting @dimash_official with all my heart! Because he is #worldsbest! Team #TWBDimash https://t.co/0YfeBRJk3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@REDDEZNInterior Oh NO!!!! Next time I see you, I’m going to give you a time out!😉😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all better take notice of this unconstitutional overreach! New York now, what state is next, and so on...]]></document><document><![CDATA[They had fun with “roll to 100” with dice and a 100’s chart! #minermoments #JBWatkinsES https://t.co/1bqbIWnKID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LCNM99 Phil, scumbag is too light of a term for Trump.  As for how many tax dollars were wasted?  Millions, as is… https://t.co/yrIOy64Phh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna be annoying and cliche with a #TheBachelor tweet... I feel bad for @colton bc he's ended up with a final… https://t.co/O8k8Cp6udi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just to manage my expectations @DeltaAssist if my companion and I upgraded to Delta One leaving SFO to JFK will we… https://t.co/TEke1W3pSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokerpami71 @KarenSoutar1 I really have too, hell, I've even defended him in the past. I'm.over that now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TARZAN AT BIRTHDAY PARTY! ♫ Giant Pinata ROMPE Song ♬FUNnel Family Finge... https://t.co/LeFqNyqhAQ via @YouTubtt #abdl by jsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipfranklin @Jim_Jordan Mitch McConnell : alien life form !!!!!! Bwwaaaaahhh! I’m dying !!!!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[New #fogglisting  10703 Colebrook Street Shadow Hills 6+5 Estate see tour for more details https://t.co/0UuJsmSwyr… https://t.co/SX1oDu4tow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay but if this is a lie and they don’t show the fence jump tonight, I am rioting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine @realDonaldTrump And he’s still speaking!!! #historicspeech]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aliciavitarelli @duciswild I love Ducis ! Esp when he cracks Jim up ! https://t.co/Ux1U0hPj5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[It bothers me when people ask me for free tarrot readings, free paintings, free drawings.. it takes alot of time an… https://t.co/vL68PgqAD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pulled a white and called the police because the towing ppl wouldn’t release my car... but it worked. Sorry everyone 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nick Bosa and Dre’Mont Jones meet with the media today and bench press.   WR’s Terry McLaurin, Parris Campbell, Joh… https://t.co/JReip3dYbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FionaMorgan79 @ccatmpt @SLBriscoe @thatsVeryKari @Cbp8Cindy @joneill55 @suziday123 @cowineco @AkronWineGuru… https://t.co/3VCvT4z4ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best clean/dirty dishwasher magnets ever. I co-sign. 😉 @kimberlymagness @ New York, New York https://t.co/s5LIEqTPFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson We have so many people with useless college degrees working in McDonald’s expecting high wages, becau… https://t.co/xvrTfWZ0Nq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be still my heart!!! #auntlife #avenclaire #freyaelizabeth #thatssoaven #freyaalldaya @ East Ridge, Tennessee https://t.co/PR3kaZhiq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanMajdali I haven't. Well, not since I can remember. Vague memories as a 4 year old. Mom and I may Thelma and Louise it out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I’m sorry I am the unpopular opinion but in what world is Shawn Mendes sexy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Isn’t planning ahead and making sure you have the means to care for and raise a child part of good and responsible… https://t.co/2EQOJmcHUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 39 percent of the nation's 2.1 million farms receive subsidies, with the lion's share of the handouts going t… https://t.co/y7urYCKzyr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lblee58 @Pty46 @NASCARONFOX The one @KyleBusch smashed was a one of a kind. Couldn't be replaced and if you know a… https://t.co/87j2NDFe38]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnni So the mess our country is in is your fucking fault! What fucking hole did you crawl out of, where ever it is… https://t.co/8FuzoYQalh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This 👇👇👇 Was at a high school basketball game and they announced the score. Place went crazy! #USAUSAUSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever said money can't solve your problems Must not have had enough money to solve 'em]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandiz2 @KathyDutton16 @flowerchild2017 @ElkeHansen7 @KimelPenny @Karrasamelia5 @sainz3203 @army_bc @Mopor777… https://t.co/qiLysvq1Ql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeubGod happy birthday Bryant!! I hope you have an amazing day you deserve it! thanks for helping a girl out when… https://t.co/kUeifNLs7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[So brave. Heartbreaking. Empowering. #SelmaBlair https://t.co/U6z6INe1Lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for a new #guessthebreed ! And no, not another Berner (but a similar shape).  A more recently created breed, I… https://t.co/Zz7gyZVWMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to #JRRTolkien, #CSLewis and #AnneMcCaffrey for helping me "escape" the teen years! Reading gave me HOPE… https://t.co/Vty0edETBw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another brewery and beer I had never heard of before. It’s very good! #craftbeer #beer https://t.co/uuZdGKHcDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls on the Run is so much Fun! 💚Luxford Girls💜 https://t.co/YzYqBAq1bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti Michael now ur responding like Donnie  Don’t lower yourself to that level]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find the kind of beauty that makes you feel small... @ Angels Landing Trail https://t.co/4wbHJJhfrc]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a woman, that felt really awesome - guess I needed that 💥🔥👏🙌 Go, ladies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to be healthy and bought fruit bars that are super chewy and I took one bite and started to choke, like air… https://t.co/QfuPiAh5Kp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRexSteele @itsjustj355 To clarify: while I think underage drinking is bad, the stings seem vindictive and intense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbylee Heh, the blue and the red Powerade are the only ones I can stand, and you’re so right about them being key… https://t.co/SaPGoFnoCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BxglL @72cricket @sharon_schwan @CSonafelt @rosemoczulski1 @sannbs @RidenerTina @MrsSpuds @ACog1984 That’d be great!! 🐧💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever is releasing these sources need to get their facts right before they post]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniversalORL you are so right about that, But I will be there in 177 days with my then husband, our Adventure star… https://t.co/cV2urmxrpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @TheFlaBar  pretty obvious to those with a brain this wasnt a threat but a spoof on Cohen's pretense… https://t.co/5BO7IeJgWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never ever saw #walmartfashions dresses @Walmart like the ones on #RedCarpetLive @TheAcademy #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want To Throw Your Ultimate Dream Party From Party City? https://t.co/9KfWRvJt6O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey look, the co-worker of a neocon mass murderer is trying to say neocon is actually code for being Jewish https://t.co/LVXBdoMEZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A vote for Trump and Pence has put our daughter’s future health care in jeopardy - no woman Democrat or Republican… https://t.co/eyYp8TABud]]></document><document><![CDATA[On* Amazon. Former EDC planning intern of 1.5 years. Shoutout to the Marilyn Lee protogés!!! 👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DevinNunes @FoxNews Does Spanky McDotard appreciate that Robert Mueller‘s office notified Roger S… https://t.co/yu1hJAkTQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @zumbawithlindar with get_repost ・・・ #pilates #matpilates #trainhard #commitment #staystrong #pickeringmoms… https://t.co/kUp19uc70d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJNewsflash He didn’t say what they wanted him to say before, so they called him a liar. Now he’s promising to tel… https://t.co/kzzRdIBjSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ChristiansSpeakUp against abortion. There is no justification for murdering babies. #Godhatesbabykillers… https://t.co/76VCW0r4Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leonor tkm pero QUE NIERDA ESE VESTIDO POR LA CTM  #PartyChilensisFtGala]]></document><document><![CDATA[More from yesterday’s Flower &amp; Garden Festival preview 🌼 #FreshEpcot https://t.co/vIgcXZfciO]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that Republicans seem to care more about Cohen lies than they do about the lies Trump tells Americans eve… https://t.co/lavcKSSjeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I make my living doing what I love. I’m proud of the things I make, I’m thankful for every opportunity, and I’m hum… https://t.co/IZUCo3JtXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEST PRICED 2BR ISLA! OPEN TODAY 1-3PM. 5736 La Puerta Del Sol Blvd. #151, St. Petersburg, Florida. David Estabrook… https://t.co/0B8cUTnMnf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 8: THE KINDS OF PHOTOS YOU’LL FIND ON MY PHONE/CAMERA ... March 30daysoflists . #idocument #photojournal… https://t.co/iF8rVNZ2wc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would do anything if it meant I woke up with india’s titties tomorrow 😭😭😭😭 wtf they’re BOMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieFinberg @Eryn The bottom is sooo much easier and you don’t mash the banana trying to open it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iwrite4u2 @KeyaMorgan @Corey_Feldman The guy is a fraud https://t.co/YnxMaZmooH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox, you forget I could care less what these people say about me. Brian there’s no way you could ever look into tha… https://t.co/doUxjCUZQp]]></document><document><![CDATA[New way to move!  #t3learns @ Baltimore Marriott Waterfront https://t.co/x8P4fE8hwk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most amazing thing I’ll see this week. ❤️ The most heartbreaking thing I’ll see this week. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to realization that you truly DID NOT have me like no one else had me. And with that, I’m finally released😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ann_dibella @knott_michele @auntierez @Kpteach5 @mrsmelanieroy @Beth_Parmer @m_simpson5 @NikiOhsBarnes @JerryCraft… https://t.co/J6D2CCy5B9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @MarkyMa66695246 @SpeakerPelosi Its like whoopi saying Roman Polanski wasn't Rape-Rape....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter is live now making some emotes and sub badges!!! Come give him some love and hang with me in chat!  https://t.co/m1s9swMUD6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Presidente llegan al Puente Tienditas  Fuente: Embajada https://t.co/D9x5e2KD02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boost Your Mental Performance: By Taking A Nap  https://t.co/qUjLET0UZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckRoast10 @nicoleedeuter @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse You can talk with my autocorrect, it always happens when is set in… https://t.co/lOH81hAj5E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if the sky is the limit sweet souls!!! Today, we are believing in ourselves and our dreams!! Xx 🙌🏻… https://t.co/tmPJxQb7xO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chuck E. Cheese is the first place i’m at in the morning &amp; last place i’m at before I go to bed....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had high expectations for the show tonight, and they were exceeded. Thank you, @macklemore. You are pure joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arixthankunext @masoniswokenup @L_E_4 He's been reported they have all the ss and in talking to you mykie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vitruvian_plan @pkoonce Thanks for the connection! Peter, let’s get coffee?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeMorrisPE is killin' it right now at #ncties19! Dude. Thank you!! https://t.co/eynLDI2PDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lean_dragon_ @heybro_then holy shit the lil vampire was such a good movie i loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's hard to have a bad day when presents are waiting for you at home. 🤘🤘🤘🤘🤘🤘  @aggretsuko #Aggretsuko https://t.co/dttSZLVn6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow will make 7 years my uncle been gone. #AJD https://t.co/zG7ZPSAZXT]]></document></documents></author>