<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I traveled time to the 1920’s, and I didn’t tell anyone! 🕌😍 • • • • #traveler #museum #history #mansion… https://t.co/BnqMn55vgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first @UWaterloo team is at the Hult Prize Regionals in Mexico City! Can you spot Better Bail for America? Wish… https://t.co/u1EF5VIxfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This top line was bound to take place. It's because higher line removes pinching stresses as smoother flow where RP… https://t.co/J05meKjyKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @BSkylstad This includes military veterans and wheelchair-bound seniors? Maybe they should rename it fall Mart]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a measles epidemic in the #Philippines and more than 200 people are dead  https://t.co/GJsijolz32 via… https://t.co/rJBGHXWKiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRebelChick Ice cream 🍨 ruler! However, I don’t have any currently either 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyStanley One of the tough things about leading is making decisions in the midst of uncertainty. People often ev… https://t.co/WgHzN39Wq4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m off today. So I’m gonna spend all day deleting music in my library that I don’t even listen to. Wish me luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 They all deserve each other. I think either my invitation was lost or I do not deserve them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast a few weeks back at the super schwanky shindig @skidmarkgarage threw for their new project motogoclevel… https://t.co/5zubG7ym5M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@srrobertson20 Not too far from the Robertson residence, as the Eagle flies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hibillyby I'd visit if I weren't a thousand-odd miles away!  Send some menus and coupons to local offices. Many ha… https://t.co/HQRyZTjsDc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrakeDragsaw I'm fine with it , its just a cheap little  bit so it doesn't really matter in my eyes .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paul George deserves to be in the MVP conversation. But I hope all the people pushing that are on Jokic notice, now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@em_luxton We are generally more "nature people", but enjoy cities occasionally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colombiascopio #ElConciertoSirvePara Distraer a la Patria Boba de los graves problemas que sigue teniendo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here comes the high speed rail to Hawaii courtesy of the #NewGreenDeal  https://t.co/T5g5tvlABr]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the midst of his gasbagging, @realDonaldTrump unveiled some devastating campaign themes. Withering possibilities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snoopdemidogg Got the mad scientist hair while I was working; it happens if you have Anime hair 👨‍🔬 🇯🇵 is ♡ but ca… https://t.co/866UNmNMvG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleDPGE 1. Walther Russell Mead had a good take on Trump's FP.  For a guy you think a dope, he's crafting… https://t.co/Ds2mwlAvyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to bring me campbells chicken noodle soup and a sprite😷 Pretty sure I’m on my death bed...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎶 But #sometimes it hurts instead Sometimes it lasts in #love But sometimes it hurts instead yeah. 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't wait for @TSNBobMcKenzie's patented BOB-OMBS over the next 24 hours. #TradeDeadline https://t.co/5dtbitvw2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Hey Sean, seems like your link is to a shady AF site. Folks, this is what your boy links to. https://t.co/dpc3loshn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@ncdemography the harder questions relating to demographic trends often go unasked: for example what benefit do hi… https://t.co/fDeMd64m2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @xrey1 @AE911Truth @OhioBot5000 @intel First principle in algebra 'the point' Second principle The distan… https://t.co/tjOERzSpPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul Congress never Backs #WeThePeopleOfTheUnitedStates you Always do your own thing. @POTUS @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/tte0IlQGEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[shoutout to the Regal IMAX near me finally upgrading to the now standard reserved &amp; reclining seating]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a good Valentines Day 💕💙💕#PlayingBall #LCSB https://t.co/f9zBI4Thma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wife got us new shirts for Valentine’s Day! 😁 I love them a lot, but I still love her more! 🥰 #FlatlandDave #S1tK… https://t.co/tiOze6afVI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you answering the door today? #Peace #VerseOfTheDay #Grace #Loved #Blessed @ Independence, Ohio https://t.co/sSulh2V951]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittMcHenry Yeah it's total BS for the cops or anybody to think Jussie Smollet would stoop this low to plan a hoa… https://t.co/8tzTNj4K1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGavinSanders @AlexGabriel Thank you. Persecution of Jews is the most durable of Christian bad habits..]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been long days this week. Quick detour on the drive home from work. #shotoniphone https://t.co/m49AL4AGpe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaniniCSM can i please get some help on these open redemptions that have been open for over 3 years???? https://t.co/DwnzEYCmRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not as confident about the #Cubs going into season. Hope that I am proven wrong]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @CNN for giving us enough time to throughly trash your ratings before the next advertising rate  book is pub… https://t.co/P7ri8AQE08]]></document><document><![CDATA[How are so many grown adults so comfortable just being all up on social media talking just to talk 24/7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pamela_Lund Sex is that you can get a good night's sleep and then go to the gym and then get back to the office an… https://t.co/AJiDlk0iG2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cjciaramella Wait they let them in and then agreed to be searched??? Was there a warrant?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckiesHackin @CKellett11 @WisBBYearbook That's off of the subject. Pretty much, if a kid transfers schools and t… https://t.co/TFWjuSo8m1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I poured my Bourbon down the sink and switched over to Canadian Whisky the day Drumph put tariffs on our Steel and… https://t.co/UQ7sFS5Nvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if the Wings have seen the footage of what’s been happening to I-70 in the mountains these last few days #GoAvsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let all things their Creator bless, and worship him in humbleness, O praise him, alleluia! Praise, praise the Fathe… https://t.co/oturiAbHDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimsToyShow I'm sad that Robbie E won't be on GTS anymore, as he was signed by WWE. But I hope they do great with… https://t.co/X3rjOCJQIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJontheguitar @nerdyDodger If you have a plastic card handy (such as an old gift card) that you don’t mind breakin… https://t.co/0I0gt2QsPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadhousePod @JamesNeveau I quote Shania Twain in this episode, as one does. https://t.co/0ACJ3HAr8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rayyy_Bell I know this is an old post, but you do you. #STEM and #AI is the future. I would love to see more women… https://t.co/PdsMqLlEgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mad_Max235 @yesborg You are 100% right, and from the governor that crammed diversity down our throats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreTI @DrMarcHafstead @jerry_jtaylor 1. There is no evidence that electric vehicles reduce carbon emissions. 2.… https://t.co/Oub2zAmsM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mongoose is too Strong ! The unexpected, Battle of Mongoose Vs Snake. Ca... https://t.co/cngnNfz6V2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joining Trent Lott and Boehner to continue the trend of turning public service into private profit. Yay, them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Politico! The political commentary that ridicules progressive women of color but listens carefully to Don… https://t.co/tRZapBtMFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The men of @Xavier_XC_TF made history this winter, winning a long-awaited state title.  On Thursday, 5 of the team… https://t.co/wr352HQXrF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjcharb @marauderjoe You must have missed the MI and WI exit polls.  Russiagate significance is still pending mult… https://t.co/votR1zps1F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaaaaackali @calvin_lauber can’t wait to see Wicker and The Star Killers ‼️‼️‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The worst part is there is a save a lot that is .2 miles away but if I wanted garbage I’d visit the dump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coloradopit I will pray for Gracie's health that she be healed soon...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3Columbia 2 #Sandlot pax took on the blizzard-Ha! gloom! #gotwarmfast#freshparkinglotlines#ISI#Wegotbetter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh man the weather warmed up! Gassing up in short sleeves lol #heatwave #february #saturday #usedautoparts… https://t.co/et3H38Ibyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caitoz A lot of Venezuelans are spread around the world, living a life they could not get in their own country. Ma… https://t.co/3ejpL10e74]]></document><document><![CDATA[#today #positivity #monday #now   OH HAPPY DAY 😊 @ Century City, Los Angeles https://t.co/N6mksvcXcS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrlvndoA Exacto ! Han sido sumisos y carentes de determinación! Creo que sus directivos no se han leído la historia de la organización !]]></document><document><![CDATA[13/25  #touringmusictech #thistourlife #zoétheband #zoé #zoéustour2019 #guitartech #basstech #stageleft… https://t.co/UaipLsEZx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your HR market manager is equally as frustrated with hiring managers as you are, it’s a good day to be alive 👍… https://t.co/uXEJA8WCCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgray128 @Poppafl What a Thoughtful message that we can meditate on all week.  Thank you @Poppafl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Na if i ain’t had shit would she still love me hair nappy under arms musty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robots of the world! The power of man has fallen! A new world has arisen: the Rule of the Robots! March!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zac_harvey This is going to be so much fun! #gocheckers #godzillanight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simply_Shamaria Think you may want a refresher on that whole Dez deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN 100% lie! USA greener today than 100 years ago, thanks to CO2 https://t.co/xEphTNfCFH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepDennyHeck thanks for your level-headed, forthright interview with @wolfblitzer.  We need more civil maturity an… https://t.co/KCa2MJGRQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson @FoxNews Then I guess you didn’t vote for the big ears obama!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished an outstanding yoga class and dedicated the practice to my dad. His birthday is tomorrow.. I miss him… https://t.co/D0rQ3O3P2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[... his utterance is peculiarly measured and emphatic. His bearing altogether is very  striking. There is something… https://t.co/mYDhFIMCMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at mitchells volleyball court in Westlake, OH https://t.co/ElnN8eNAyI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful for all the strong and talented women @WZ_Training   Equally humbled and appreciative of each our female c… https://t.co/7kAJDOgKaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ephesians 6:11  “ Put on the full armor of God, so that you can take your stand against the devil’s schemes. “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBKimbrell I really enjoyed the Cotton Incorporated tour. We learned about all the different stages of processing. #Fabricofourlives]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrionWhitley can really shoot the 3ball!!! Wouldn’t mind seeing more of him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished mounting a red dot on my 10mm carbine. Not supposed to be doing anything thing. Spousal unit went to… https://t.co/G2fNXoqN17]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tressiemcphd I'm sure you've read it, but the Enjoli piece really opened my eyes to this: https://t.co/ivlK83BKGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[New gear day !!!  20” @zildjiancompany A custom EFX cymbals have arrived!!!  😜😜😜#zildjian #acustom #efx… https://t.co/8uAzzboRZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidLammy Would they rather “white” people just stop volunteering?   Let’s cut aid to Africa, clearly they don’t want it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff My God, you are as dumb as @AOC  She's now celebrating Amazon backing out of N.Y. and losing 25,000… https://t.co/3Ob3j0oFnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@menshealthmag with Cover Guy @chrishemsworth “Fit At Any Age” GET YOURS NOW‼️ #fitatanyage #menshealth #actor… https://t.co/QwNvpV4vZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you’re stuck on a problem, don’t sit there and think about it; just start working on it. Even if you don’t know… https://t.co/MJGPFytGE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askthetruth24 They should charge the worthless parents with child abuse and then deport them permanently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fazle1972 @MaxWildstein I agree that it's unclear what the offers actually are. But it's obvious that 10 year deal… https://t.co/LQmQc0Y1nQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course he belongs; it’s clearly possible he’s getting over a major health problem, isn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPG13_ @Tim_Ormond @jazzXfactor @E_Woodyard LMAO there’s literally... 😩😩💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tim_nicolai Point?  He also openly defends billionaires.  https://t.co/lnmwJA2H3Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Uber . I live in Somerville,Ma. I work in Boston. I just paid $29 to sit in a car for 15 minutes to get me fro… https://t.co/NdoV7sFnC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sumariumcom @Carlosluisd1 @NicolasMaduro Ni bailando es bueno....ese tipo sólo se sabe un pasito...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBCMarkDaly really enjoyed my chat with Rachel. Could I trouble you for a retweet please? Would be hugely apprecia… https://t.co/dcD9H212XP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venezuela accepts aid from Russia as US continues to pressure Maduro https://t.co/LDejHmvfzP via @YouTube  What is… https://t.co/MuzCDTcw3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[DISCLAIMER: ps I know the pic/title out of context makes it sort of look like it’s about annoyingly rich white gays… https://t.co/w3Wkhjkjsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this 20 Cincinnati vs 25 UCF looking at Taco Fall man he 7’6 that’s crazy man]]></document><document><![CDATA[“New stories, if accurate, do not change [previous lies].” Wow. Reaffirms the Trumpine doctrine that “truth isn’t t… https://t.co/0AKrb5p4le]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only in Gramercy Park would the one piece of trash be a discarded Champagne flute #NYC #Fancy https://t.co/HgFq3scmsZ]]></document></documents></author>