<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @RepGregoryMeeks And praying, that while POTUS is distracting Congress over this STUPID WALL, we don… https://t.co/zJ3hWzpVrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Month of March, Direct from Wikipedia! https://t.co/LChuKDuNAe https://t.co/oRInvUjdbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FreeThePeople 🙏🆓👥 . . #StreetArt #StickerArt #StickerPorn #StickerPoem #StickerPoems . . #buzzed#iphonesia #ig… https://t.co/s4nstbs04h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayingPolitix @momgladewater @lajorkm @HoneyMcReynolds @rieth_damon @Analisa_Swan @coleyworld @ed_in_NOVA… https://t.co/iyAFzEoox9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recap of Gym Jordan’s performance today 👇#michaelcohen #JIMJordan #GymJordan https://t.co/NePMJ3cGfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @ClaraJeffery @BylineTimes @jack @Twitter @TwitterGov need to block these anti vax lunatics. Their spew is… https://t.co/7ORj2ZAoHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinLea7 @Darth_Pingu I feel like a smuck when I stare at them waiting... for a big nothing 🙄🤬😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing Paul and Ines a very Happy Valentine's day! Have an awesome day we love you both]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn172510 @HippieVol @jamesonandbeers @The_Fool_Monty @8MillionML I bet!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Creeds_Crew @readerroberts @WaltDisneyWorld @AnimalKingdom @DisneyStudios Sorry to hear! I'm convinced that when… https://t.co/daHehnY8hA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump's #FAKE 'national emergency' is an #ILLEGAL power grab and there are #TWO THINGS you can #demand Congress do… https://t.co/U95FUrb3dk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda522 @BoyslnBIue Haha isn’t this the same thing that happened to Strip during photo day at the ASG??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agricultural Subsidies | Downsizing the Federal Government https://t.co/4Yy6jSmsZc by C Edwards - 2018 -    Apr 16,… https://t.co/b12yCs7cYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning sweet Peeps! Wishing you a fantastic week 😘💋💋💞 https://t.co/iITs1nC9rp]]></document><document><![CDATA[the mars rover is the mother I never had. she is the sister everybody would want. she is the friend that everybody… https://t.co/16pDBDmDA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooh I think I'm going to LOVE the book fair that's being set up right now. I 🖤Dino's! @MrsDonnaAcosta… https://t.co/ELE03zvLrD]]></document><document><![CDATA[she wailing like that with a little puncture? girl get up. you lucky you didn’t die.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hellolanemoore Never say it buuuut I think it though https://t.co/oNXgP2q3Rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHERE THE FUCK IS THE FENCE JUMP??! We got 10 mins left dammit!!!! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@influensterjen1 Thanks! We both are following you on IG and entered the giveaway! Fingers and toes crossed! Have a wonderful day!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump The only way we succeed if he gets hanged for treason or resigns, whichever gets the most Fox News ratings]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madagaingirl @CommonColo @KamalaHarris The root cause is they are fed a B's crock and are told they can get free s… https://t.co/TvVVOpyJSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibepacheco Vamos bien, es la respuesta al venezolano que deseaba seguir a un líder como Guaidó]]></document><document><![CDATA[Security line our to the concourse on the morning I’m running late. And all the people asking if this is TSA. It’s all TSA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go @chaseelliott  💛💙 #di9 #NAPA9 #TeamHendrick #HendrickMotorsports #ChaseElliot #NASCARonFOX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Warehouse Order Selector" in #Baraboo, WI. Go on informational interviews. The be… https://t.co/o9QkgNFARw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OriginalFunko Don't make me go wild if I don't win this pop LOL https://t.co/niuQVLNf4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cecilia is over here trying to pop open a Martinelli and takes a sip like a bad bitch and then we broke her vibe an… https://t.co/tGg1hSponp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @RealMattCouch Would not put it past Obama to do something this sleezy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OptimisimLives @HoarseWisperer Thank you!! I love getting another year older. Sure beats the alternative.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for Sarah who listens to me babble about anything and everything with no judgement. Thx Facebook and Br… https://t.co/nmWzsUzS0P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaytonZeringue Remember when MCR and Coheed and Cambria came on though? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God, Your will.  Nothing more, nothing less, nothing else.  Amen  #umc #umcgc #gc2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Packerpenguin @EBraeden @DougDavidsonYR I certainly hope they do and I'm happy he's back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your expression of #nonbinary identity, whatever it looks like, is changing popular understanding of gender. And it… https://t.co/eYcjLu5WzG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have not forgotten to look on with you all it's been impossible to do as much on air wave connection and everyone… https://t.co/bdQqYejIfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHADOWHUNTERS - MALEC SNEAK PEEK + 3B NETFLIX TRAILER REACTION https://t.co/x4oJKasVXZ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradAnderson_WX I’m so mad! I still have to go to work today! Healthcare (just like the weather man) doesn’t get a day off 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Handing out @Moda_Health #CJMcCollum cards at the @trailblazers game 🙌🏽 #RipCity https://t.co/dzktllESy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lovely bridal shower for Rachel today! Just 2 more weeks till she's a Mrs!🍷 @ Rowe Ridge Vineyard &amp; Winery https://t.co/45sAKHxuuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Maybe because most of America knows we have an imposter in the Oval Office.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya les platiqué que aún no puedo correr?? La semana pasada lo intenté y todavía me duele el muslo... ah pero lo cor… https://t.co/R0GyxniLiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god my family is talking politics and won’t stop they’re giving me a headache 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Either Murray forged Adam's handwriting or Bev can't recognize handwriting. #TheGoldbergs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessbeforedawn had to sell at least 2 major organs for pink tickets to surprise my sister]]></document><document><![CDATA[el fin le hice un postre a mi novio por que cumplimos mes y (cabe resaltar que en la vida me ha salido uno bien) yo… https://t.co/1Cz5b7ThA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The place a steer belongs. #richardson #tx #steer @ State Farm CityLine Building 2 https://t.co/w2uPS08Ml7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great media introduction to across.the.pond tonight with delicious bites like the escolar with soy-marinated… https://t.co/gXcMqCHUTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@21centarmy @USBTSARMY @BTSGALAXYOT7 @BTS_twt @ultrarecords Where is this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree. Had one AMAZING woman of color that came to mind and she and I have been friends forever. I. Just. Don’t.… https://t.co/SLwizeWE2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starofthesea007 @Campbell71Helen @ClevelandCeltic @kevinwalsh1964 @RCeltic1888 @Montreal_Celtic @_Larsson7 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿🇺🇸👍💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m still doing all the things I used to do, plus more. People do return my calls faster.” Idaho Gov. Brad Little,… https://t.co/MyyX77LU9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JetBlue It won’t save or upload or download or copy. When I try tosend to Dropbox or tweet it comes up with a blank page.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheriehu42 @bellocollective this is fantastic — so glad you’re covering/exploring this territory!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okstate needs to cancel school tomorrow bc i’m not walking to class in 15 degree weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceJe00776494 Sorry, didn’t mean to be rude, just being careful.  Had a couple seriously unpleasant encounters l… https://t.co/7eZBPDiyDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reserve your child’s spot in school next year! Return your Intent to Return Form no later than Tuesday, February 26. https://t.co/w4EK2EMHNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trustrestored @tuesdayskirt The DRats are into HATE. Don't cooperate or give to them anything without the fight!… https://t.co/5r9bXVSxDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The quality of athlete in the game today is far superior than the past. But these dudes were just men. So much toug… https://t.co/fc6QQRb19J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra length shouldn’t cost more because the shorter you cutting them the more nail you wasting 🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MommaMarks20 @ljbraf1313 @IDWPublishing @SYFY Earpers are FAMILY! We are here and We stay! NoChill 👊💕 #WynonnaEarp… https://t.co/bOEQEZeGGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we to believe you want us to pay special attention to the word green there LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol Saleena, you’re nothing but trash. You, your mom, your friends. Your poor child. Keep talking shit, cause I can… https://t.co/W2uA8tSFnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well... HAPPY VALENTINES TO ME! 🥰😍😘 I love you devinlong789  #valentines #uncleduties @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/CEkNWAoxbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald It does not surprise me when he dropped bombs in Syria they said that he looked presidential.  They hav… https://t.co/8IJ4BNLlr6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wrap  my mind around the fact that #petertork is now 77 years old.  He turned me on to some cool classic fi… https://t.co/CgYkO26EKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm soooooo mad at JP. He said we were watching a rom com and here I am watching a thriller w Jesse mcCartney.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cimorelliband what was the best and worst phase in your life and how did you overcome it? @Cimorelliband]]></document><document><![CDATA[TONIGHT: Collab Celebration w/ @crystallakebrewing! We will debut the latest beer “Unfashionable” , and a cask of “… https://t.co/62gCeUud7E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamGrasya016 @simplyZzzaida Oh i heard sila din doon toxic ang iba. Ayaw ko i mention baka magalit hehe. The guy i… https://t.co/CSvh7DXd8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@techie_teacher1 @nearpod @NicandSully @KaliThompson2nd @smilelearning @PeppyZestyTeach @joangore @Hazbo214… https://t.co/u7OWBB6hB0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @Martina That LGBT group lost one if it's greatest ambassadors.  Their loss.  She's right about the unf… https://t.co/Oo5KfHliGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does everyone else get to have "bad days" but the second I do, it's like the world is ending and I am the sole cause?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd be interested in seeing a collaboration between the new membership-based coworking spaces and public libraries… https://t.co/vvXa4nLnfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should you upgrade to BoxyLuxe?? Watch my unboxing video to help you decide!! Amberrific or No?? 👍… https://t.co/LpwT5QQOr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[why did one bitch at my job have a whole ass emotional breakdown and told the owners god daughter to “ talk to her… https://t.co/VU1WHupUIL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devoptimus @Metrolinx Giving @GOtransit @GOtransitBus a heads up. Much thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phanerozoic11 Awww thank u doc sahiba 😍😍 I love yr purani dp too jis mein apki apni picture hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abbeysy Sadly, some Fil fams are like that as well. Parents would just rub it in other people’s faces how their ki… https://t.co/crD4cgqSfV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me lol when customers say I need some coffee. I work in the coffee industry, I need ALOT more than coffee]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️🍣 (@ Umami Umami Japanese Restaurant in Dresher, PA) https://t.co/mPsri1rHPi https://t.co/osyfaGntr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ash_est92 He wasn’t right for the Super Bowl but he is https://t.co/KFEKoSvrRq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belangelyn Guardias corruptos! La vi hace casi un año atrás y wow, qué coraje!!🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoDoubter2383 @gwenstefani Good luck! I that would be awesome! Are you dressing up? I'm still finalizing my outfits!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's going on @RyanMcPikeKMTV ? #overit @3NewsNowOmaha https://t.co/NXhoiTXwZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving my new Marley Lilly pink pullover! Fits perfect! @marleylilly https://t.co/WYzihKvydB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not just any old Starbucks but Seattle HQ the Rostery. Off to see @BDO_USA #Seattle team this afternoon. Glad of a… https://t.co/BWka5W1Kdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaraotaDigital Lo mejor de todo esto es q cuando salgan estos bichos no tendremos que volver a oir más  nunca a es… https://t.co/yewCHsdbVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vueling Ya he hecho todo eso y me sigue dando error. Me podéis ayudar?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like a Saturday #brunch for a little #keto experimentation. I give you #eggchalupas—so tasty! #ketoaf… https://t.co/soxl1sHnAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NLavison @daisy_chandra I was just gonna say Tomorrowland ugh the dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s very unfortunate that #stopSOP has taken over the discourse in relation to the upcoming… https://t.co/BYDqbGxrmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bex_gay @CMoran709 @ohyeaChris I just woke up for a work meeting. I need you to get off the plane and immediately… https://t.co/r9sJWiRdkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@milindsuhasprad @MengiKuldip @Jungle_View @better_delhincr @PNRATHOD1 @Rahul42420890 @chutorjan @ajitsinghpundir… https://t.co/Giv547LeFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[All lives are equally worthwhile @soledadobrien really inspired 👏👏👏 we must raise these issues now as part of our r… https://t.co/1gFK3R8h8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReasonAwareness @ClintonServer @mebeandreaaolco @Carpophores @yankeeproud1 @Gram247 @WHurensohn @Robjenk07Robert… https://t.co/0qblq0UjjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most ppl that I know go straight from the heat to AC and do never bother to open the windows. That's why so many pp… https://t.co/7qKqqOx0wk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daisychangeblog Leadership - Lifestyle - Fashion - Travel 💕 https://t.co/mUYoEu2S1O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msnicole1124 @TnNationalist @STAND_For_FLAG_ @KBesosa @ernie_plumley @michaelwweston @brainburp13 @BellaInxs2… https://t.co/Ql696pRamO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to cancel my Grand Canyon vacation but I’m still off of work for a week, where should I go instead? 🤔]]></document></documents></author>