<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@SnapLensStudio @JinneTheWew @svrf @ka5sh @ali3jackson Thank you for all the great memories, now that she’s gone I… https://t.co/D2kjyeT1xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know what they say.. when life gives ya lemons.. throw a brick at your boss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been workin hard since the Fall to crush the past! #BlueHens @DelawareTFXC are movin fast don’t blink 👀💪🐔🏃‍♀️💨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get you a friend like @kevjumba__ Love you too😂 https://t.co/E2ekhIQdYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate the rest of the peanut butter at the bottom of the jar which didn't seem like much, but it was definitely eno… https://t.co/1INfLXSl7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall ever go on the activity page of IG &amp; see your fuck ass nigga blow up some female page with likes lmaoooothatshithurtedooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnBrennan Excuse me, sir. Fuck this guy! He is seriously an asshole. He knows damn well the ONLY reason he’s in… https://t.co/Ck8m1YsfUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arquitectura Objeto VS Arquitectura Social. #porqueesimportanteplaticar Los esperamos en la @faunam_mx  Teatro Carl… https://t.co/hCDiUTcs6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Biebercome2me Amen to that you are absolutely right he definitely hasn't been the best father 👍👍👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great day and night of musical hangs in LA. Great to catch up with @mattmusty and themichel, smash a few be… https://t.co/wjxjnENu70]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo can we show you our mad bowling skills? @EarlyEyesBand @livviegrace123]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the best classroom management tools has nothing to do with “points” or rewards, but instead is about differe… https://t.co/0xfwwtgWxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph WNW. Barometer 29.799 in, Falling. Temperature 30.3 °F. Rain today 0.00 in. Humidity 94%]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weekend I saw vintage cameras, the first Simpson's published, many rad comics, hiked, tried new tea and got in… https://t.co/NHPoyihl13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of @DrMelanieMiller and @DrDonnaWrightd7 for being such exemplary educators and leaders in our great state!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/11/2019 • #Art • #nachos &amp; #YuenglingLager 🍺 for #supper 😋 in #Conway #Arkansas 🙏🏻 #blessed @ Conway, Arkansas https://t.co/QVV0upWuVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandy_styers You tell Tim that pop tarts are ass and if she wants to fight then heres my address]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcruz73 And I’ll just be crying happy tears like this for a bit longer... https://t.co/XLBFtPzxJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[USMNT statement on WNT Players lawsuit | US Soccer Players https://t.co/mHsDEcflnt via @ussoccerplayers @USWNT #equalpay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcp90 @ShannonNutt @billpeduto I have been doing my taxes for 25 years. I am FAR from the only person I know wh… https://t.co/blD93Xw4Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rumours are true!  And it’s a beauty!! #OpenHouse today and tomorrow 2-4!!! See ya there!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today a company guy came to talk to us &amp; told us they had PET INSURANCE. Yes, PET INSURANCE! 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the middle of an intense game of #Tetris99 and my nose started itching. Even worse, no one to scratch it😖Torture I tell ya! 😵🤕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hipEchik I had been out there maybe 2 hours before they showed up. They were all but 1 sitting on the rug to enter… https://t.co/M5e8SrgcOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎶🎶The fortune queen of New Orleans, Was brushing her cat in her black limousine On the backseat were scratches fro… https://t.co/8mCfq4ZzSE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nada más no veo a Leslie en 2 o 3 días y ya siento feo en mi corazoncito :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Stephanie!! I hope you have a fabulous day and that the coming year is super positive for you! 😁🎂🎉🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exciting !! New things to come ! Y’all stay tuned !! #mainstreetadventures #queenannslace #queenscourt… https://t.co/j6rfhzn2bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️Today at The Poem Farm, a work of art from Kindergarten Artist Ava in @WymansWonders's class...and a poem I wrote… https://t.co/m8QniKpxGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindishurum Hi Lindis I read your chapter in ‘The Politics of Fear’ and I would love to speak with you for an upco… https://t.co/lrnPrAXJV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 years ago today, my grandmother passed away. We sent off balloons to heaven for her. Today, a short brunette woma… https://t.co/4aKPKagRqI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of this 4th grade class for independently reading rhythms and beatboxing in two parts! #tacomamusic… https://t.co/2ngm2Cgyzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Report: Freeda Foreman, daughter of George Foreman, dead at 42 https://t.co/bo6AfwdPYt via @YahooSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexthetvterrier Oh, very nice!  Flowery smelling Cigar tree. That’s a special branch. 👍🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I sign up for things that I know I will procrastinate on?¿?¿? 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachelvmckinnon thoughts? I mean, if cis-females can catch up to, match, and even beat cis-male competitors...does… https://t.co/G7IdvtHOht]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepJoeKennedy Is anyone surprised? Is this being shown on fox news? #traitortrump will lose some supporters on thi… https://t.co/CsQOB32KoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get outside #Reflection #Patagonia #affirmation #MondayMotivation #mondaythoughts https://t.co/frhC3tVFlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomohawk1989 @caffeine @Minecraft @Tomohawk1989 stream was fun! I went onto your server and left you with a little… https://t.co/qTwvqLheMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiet mornings in beautiful places may in fact be the reason for it all.  • • • #accioadventure #optoutside… https://t.co/ysGWfvOiqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @smalltownandrew Hey John lewis did you ask American citizens what they want?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We were in line behind a very nice couple from Buffalo, NY for the 5K . They said they had been in town for 12 hour… https://t.co/vbeQ2EsI12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmazonChique The more TERFS and transphobes get into the weeds of ”bone density”, T levels, etc the crazier and mo… https://t.co/5q7AQqbIYm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonGarcia_3 @PBR_Texas @MOJO_HARDBALL Kid is going places!! 💪🏻⚾️ Love this dude!!❤️ #talent #immafan @MccrayGann]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxineWaters You are mentally ill and should commit yourself to an insane asylum immediately! You’re ignorant as hell to boot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jessica knows I’ve been wanting tapatío &amp; she deadass just got me some 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[KINK Abbey Leather Night https://t.co/LxnyTaLw6X https://t.co/KEme3485wO]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, thank you for all the hard times in my life, I turned the unthinkable too possible, because of you❤️.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iran and Russia both require that employers pay women on maternity leave for at least 26 weeks (possibly more)  Ame… https://t.co/PEb4vl4ZgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[im watching peaky blinders and wow.......tom hardy.........the power he has.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAYMENT‼️ did he just say he needs to do mouth exercises &amp; can feel the saliva coming up from his stomach???… https://t.co/eicVHzoy2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuando te reciben con esto en la universidad... #GoHuskies https://t.co/L0mfV0Wknc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“i’d like to know what really be running thru your head” 😂😂😂🤧 No you wouldn’t lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asian spinach salad with salmon with a side of broccoli 🥦  #LIFEOFADUCHESS @ Miller's Ale House https://t.co/RweVWn8ARW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie I think he meant despots. That’s their 2020 theme, isn’t it? That somehow people who believe in free… https://t.co/7yyHaZOeTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhaleesiKirkley My favorite books....too many to count but anything by @AndreaHonigsfel @MariaGDove @Jechev… https://t.co/vcQ6xFG8E4]]></document><document><![CDATA[but I can’t help but struggle, when the person that I am is the person I don’t knowwwww🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fbriandeuces I'm curious, Francis.  Are you the person who finally came forward to claim their $1.6 Billion lotter… https://t.co/RtR6nZuQdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure to emcee Care Canada's Walk in Her Shoes event to raise awareness about equality for women and girl… https://t.co/jk3E56s5Qj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Use your heart ❤️ #useyourheart #sidewalkart #kc #kansascity #spraypaint #❤️️ #city #urban #concretejungle #stencil… https://t.co/QPQ3dvKFMx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The camera at Target is designed to make you look your worst so if you get caught stealing you’ll look like not onl… https://t.co/H3QEfX7xpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itismyemail @ShannonBream If you were the father should you have a say?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when ppl try to tell me how to raise my son like if they’re kids came out so special]]></document><document><![CDATA[MINE!!  haven’t bought myself a palette in forever, but looks like that’s over 🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[PED 4126 making motors for electricity and magnetism! Homemade kit all the way! #hackingphysics @uOttawaBEd https://t.co/jU5kKCAfxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theblaze If you think @RepAOC @AOC is few crayons short of a kindergartner you should be ecstatic we didn’t end up with THIS as a @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's nice to see the House doing real work after nearly a decade of GOP stagnation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey New Mexico, would you like red or green chile sauce with that L tonight?    #USU #AggiesAllTheWay #GATA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an attempt to move to a cashless society in set up for the mark of the beast in order to buy goods.… https://t.co/CwoYHeKZGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I generally also run through the Portuguese countryside when I don’t feel adequately loved]]></document><document><![CDATA[@locdupshawty I know. Negativity sells. Usually it gets people to look at things (unfortunately):..I see now this w… https://t.co/uBztuUBGNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realdonaldtrump, you have no right to control my body or my decisions. Your gag rule keeps patients who get care… https://t.co/HPxWFHvg3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seyiamakinde  is the governor elect of Oyo State!!!!!!💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castro @soulcycle and diner as @manny_seth and I kibitz on the next @welcometomannys live Recode Decode podcast in… https://t.co/yldCYDDSd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bianka just roasted the SHIT out of our other roommate for me.. like I’m talking about the best roast I’ve ever see… https://t.co/C12gqQJIed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump Tells His Lawyers: Stay for the Coming Legal Hellscape https://t.co/FRBpPgCwUe via @thedailybeast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvnewinfo @Lady_Vi_2U @NRAHillbilly @ChrisBragdon @ruby58293 @RL9631 @harjo111 @horse1157 @KarmicPlurality… https://t.co/pcvbuE0U23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicaonairtalk I hear Georgia will be voting on similar heartbeat bill]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tabuckner5 @KimQuigley311 We appreciate YOU @KimQuigley311 for advocating for technology integration for students… https://t.co/r3Gr4UoK62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoaoRafaelV_ Pior q eu tava vendo pelo pc tb e puta q pariu, travando toda hr! insuportável]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always good for a reset.   #NOLA #AndroidPhotography #LowLightPhotography #SeeSomeCountry #Happy #ThankYou… https://t.co/mXKkX0tBFl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great, now your #MAGA zombies are going to be against Spike Lee. Like we care and what else is new?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paberk42 @AdamParkhomenko Totally agree, but the word perfect in connection w turtle face is an oxymoron.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 18th birthday to one of my best friends @AlliHaugh 🎉🎉🎉 hope you have an amazing day today love ya lots and en… https://t.co/WLKXMguSWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@physedlove @GopherSport What happens if you get hit with the ball, do you switch places with the striker?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very special thank you to Dean @mbountrogianni for taking the time to recognize the value of the @SpanningTheGaps… https://t.co/mWb8BPg3P9]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Happy Black History Month. It’s no secret what God can do in America. He turn things around in the spur of a momen… https://t.co/J7jwcdwztB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamBfelt @GCSAA @BIGGALtd @Jeopardy You’ve gotta answer in the form of a question, Adam!! 😃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Kamala Harris part of the Jussie Smollett hoax? https://t.co/WsMXNllqtW via @AmericanThinker A SPIDER'S WEB....… https://t.co/wQTmgBR0Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luziliya @PaulaUsero @ManuBaqueiro @A3AmarSiempre @DiagonalTV #Luimelia https://t.co/UmXiCw9Bud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was telling Ian a story that involved @PEEPSANDCOMPANY at which point he told me “they’re horrible” and now I’m c… https://t.co/kG3f1wzNmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ordered my #GalaxyS10. Now I have to figure how I'll be able to afford tuition next semester. 🤔 #Priorities]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA 🌴 LB 🌊 OC 🍊 • Video, Photography, Digital Media • anamelissavideo@gmail.com FOLLOW US! IG:… https://t.co/oEDb28jloO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews So you're a mind reader too, I knew the house was bad but a leader like you I am sure it can achieve new lows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flower_tender @JosephNSanberg I am not saying you won’t but you could also get shot and there is nothing from prev… https://t.co/S8ewoe7Pzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viewsfromdan @JeffreyGuterman @paulsperry_ @realDonaldTrump I was pleased when Trump tried to reduce tension with… https://t.co/cNA0laOkfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tammys85 We are hanging in there.  It's hitting my sister's today tho.  This is my adopted mom, lost my own mom wh… https://t.co/XjsaTEkukj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @MitchellMeeks11 Show us you grew a pair! Someone lock Mitch McConnell in a closet, quick! Before he figures it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the craziness in my life, sometimes getting outside to enjoy an amazing day is just what the doctor ordere… https://t.co/ZTOrjD0leD]]></document><document><![CDATA[ITS PAJAMA NIGHT   So I broke out my carrot onesie and will be singing “Ur the 1z” all night 🥕 https://t.co/TeJoUA3rpY]]></document></documents></author>