<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave @POTUS @realDonaldTrump I'd recommend he sign it. I'm sure he doesn't want another shut down, and, it'… https://t.co/pbjJowjhnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to receive an offer from The University of Tennessee 🍊! #GBO https://t.co/ywF6fkrrL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Current Readings :  2/25/19, 07:15:36 AM Deg: 57.1°F R.H.: 42.0% H.I: 54.0°F D.P.: 34.2°F S.P.: 30.29inHg D.A.: -467ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I used to know you back when you was young Your brother brought me through, you saw me That made me think of you s… https://t.co/q7EueN8V2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little sister getting her ears Pierce for the first time. I'm going to 24 and she 12. She growing up to fast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brooksidefilms @super7store Classics size! I don’t know about the hood, but it’d be great if he had an alternate head...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dreaded QuickBooks update. Something is not going to work correctly after installing the update. If you call su… https://t.co/Go0ZdY7ll4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought this cup at my first visit to amazon.go to remind myself that every day is an opportunity to think differe… https://t.co/9ftsipbuvc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'll be there! WiFi should work there but, technology, ya never know. Looking forward to seeing @EAHSBoys again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VHFCD @ehcampanita @MariaCorinaYA Le regaló el 100% de poder regional al chavismo, y tu le celebras la gracia. Es… https://t.co/r14JioBRBs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eric__Smith @FAN590 @Sportsnet @DGreen_14 @NBA @GreenRoomInside @Raptors You are too funny, a class act though!  L… https://t.co/3Tapfs406S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @BADNEWZBROWN13 😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 #ButIsItPettyTho @ Carrboro, North Carolina https://t.co/iPiTJsYLUZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[May actually buy my first White House Christmas Ornament this year as I appreciate the tribute, and design.  Thanks… https://t.co/xmCEj9gm28]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the most important game of the year, the Leafs are wilting. When push comes to shove, we get run over, and that… https://t.co/wAPj9pjkAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichOToole @TheDrewLynch You look like Little Finger from Game of Thrones]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TheThinkers #AirPlants #AdamsAndSonGardens @ Adams and Sons Garden Center https://t.co/XXIIKNlsXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murdochchat @BrettLe66628669 @charlie_adler "GOOOO!" - Also also @charlie_adler]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is doing the best they can with what they have. Let’s try to remember that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mloxton @NeuCare @matthewtaber @ballardsigns @moylubimykroko @physicianswkly @stephaniemedira @streetglide12… https://t.co/tt1B2HLpPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heFADESme @JMurphFB @jimmykimmel @VitalVegas @Christi196155 @damarkts @LasVegasLocally @HalleTheQueen @Thirdothy… https://t.co/RJERpS4b7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portageville leads Campbell 23-17 at the end of the 1Q. Bulldogs go on an 8-0 run before the end of the quarter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MTA @NYCTSubway why are A trains incapable of going faster than 2mph between 42nd &amp; 59th?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Holding Back the Years (Symphonic Version) by @SimplyRedHQ on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/l9rXIWklxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Take Five - Dave Brubeck https://t.co/IZmgZsAbYM @ Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park https://t.co/bDZq2JCypZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cushbomb any way y’all can interview Gov. Cuomo again regarding Amazon pulling out of its plans for their LIC camp… https://t.co/ZeMzVeZ6kE]]></document><document><![CDATA[31 minutes and change into the game and the #NHLDucks have 8 shots on goal.  They do own a 1-0 lead though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeHillerEsq Post link to argument please and index number of SC case]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceFan23 True, Bosa is obvious then it sounds like Allen. I also believe some team will come up with one of the to… https://t.co/X4YnKiSl0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Vini's Discount Liquors in Carol Stream, IL https://t.co/Fkn6l9SpL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[A sneak peek at a new series/ set I’ve been working on. Should have everything all set by the end of April at the l… https://t.co/ZUqHgSQx9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorMenendez   for the people of venezuela we should have a massive air drop all over the country of food and m… https://t.co/4acCl3FM6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when “experts” like @stephenasmith handed the Larry O’Brien Trophy to the Lakers before the season began b… https://t.co/bkj8WP3EH4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally got an instagram 😅 feel free to follow but just a heads up...haven’t posted a thing.  alecbertsch13]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree!  How about we add a little spice to that mix?  I’m all for not just charging all employers who hire illega… https://t.co/EPNog0OUJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fox8news I’m wondering if it’s a catholic school? I went to school with people with blue hair and guy liner. But it is Texas...]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a new month!! Let’s make the most of it! #la #hollywood #bernarddavidjones #actor #actorslife #writer… https://t.co/KlCw79a7Jh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AletheiaAtheos @scottsantens @paulkrugman Totally agree on both points. Glad Scott tweeted that out. My only point… https://t.co/B7LluSmPnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who appears on tv with @AlanDersh should refuse to debate him and just say “Google Jeffrey Epstein” over and over again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICYMI:   Judge sets R. Kelly's bail at $1 million  https://t.co/sL7Ply1zzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early service at Midtowne Church ⛪ Continuing our series: Without.  Without Jesus we have no rest. #Midtowne… https://t.co/ezWpayZsfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @stmarkcs for hosting the Knights of Columbus Basketball Free Throw Competition! A great morning for all… https://t.co/unxXwGasnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Your the great divider Donnie not socialism you and your klyptocracy. Your are nothing but a con man]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is an example of what HS students are capable of. They'll remember THIS class long after they have graduated,… https://t.co/1WFQ3PqN1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a song for you… Take Me Home Tonight (Re-Recorded) by Eddie Money https://t.co/ARxqch5S06]]></document><document><![CDATA[This coach was out of football for what, 5 years and that’s his evaluation of Bobby Hart? It wasn’t the bullying th… https://t.co/Q7AglqHL69]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rjballinbias One lucky punch and 10k feet elevation stops him from being undefeated! The rest of ALL his fight he… https://t.co/N5wuLP3U03]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made myself French toast using brioche bread, turkey bacon, eggs and a apple for breakfast and I feel so accompli… https://t.co/JgLqkuWZZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want help with promoting events for your company, a SALE, or products, or whatever helps you more. We have the BEST… https://t.co/3wbuxTYtVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom really woke me up before 9 AM i’m really going to be tired all fucking day now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ct-  would you change the music? C- fine Ct-  what are you? C- I got what you all wanted then sobered up Ct-  that… https://t.co/ZyzhRL3vKk]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@aceshoops and @RomanBasketball also met in the state playoffs in 2012 with Lower Merion taking that matchup, 67-4… https://t.co/wxSuQUz9bx]]></document><document><![CDATA[my name is Taylor i was born in a new way  my age is still not over  i like to see her and y’all get better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creachadair I might die from folks who refuse to silence notifications.]]></document><document><![CDATA[17 Things to Never, Ever, EVER Do to Your House Keep the vintage wallpaper, but upgrade that time- and money-draini… https://t.co/9zNVarAwif]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the people that are in my life. Especially my niggas that I have I wouldn’t want it another way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[May your dreams be sweet and your nightmares be spooky monster scary and not grandma died scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work (@ The Stewpot's Second Chance Cafe - @thestewpot in Dallas, TX) https://t.co/8qOzA9x3bv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfpelosi @freeandclear1 And maybe freshmen reps like her and a few others should learn the ropes about messaging b… https://t.co/PkoCIxLrCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amberella06 When they advertise it on the window that's pretty bad... LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@haan_singh91 @jerrytheazzman @bebinabraham @gabekapler Not RT-ing but it’s RT worthy, saving it for when the Flyer… https://t.co/HWyHw4g0jl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If he makes this event all about himself, it will end up with one of the smaller turnouts of DC July 4th events, si… https://t.co/OY9u3e13ks]]></document><document><![CDATA[ha ha saving the earth day 95.all is calm and im sitting in a little ray of sunshine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanNotTheKiller Now is not the time to be risky and be fresh and new because that just might not work, Now is the… https://t.co/A2OZ2a5l8u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jefoson7 @KyleClark Give examples please, three would do. Please remember attribution before assertion. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to the realization that 90 percent of my music comes from having heard it on TV or Film and buying it. Th… https://t.co/dmPfvfKFaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solferx It’s like you haven’t been paying attention in the least. It is not a “customer revolt”. It is revolting customers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliGreenKFrog True..he should be like “give me names or else you’re just a snitch” lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[New entry on the medal stand for beer names that I’ve had:  Lord Hobo Boomsauce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gonzalogrank @FelixCaldera60 Mmmmmm.....medio español.....mmmmm.....cuéntaselo a mamá, renegado😞😞😞😞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraMcOutdoors @RepFrankLucas @quail4ever @pheasants4ever Can’t wait to catch you on Saturday! 😁 https://t.co/lScsh61IWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's ok @PoseOnFX they didnt nominate me either, but we know you're the best, so all love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Responsibility #BeDependable #DoTheRightThing #DoYourBest #Integrity #DailyEzeDose #DailyQuotes #QuotesDaily @ Uni… https://t.co/g3BAX4CN28]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattPunkArt I’m seeing it on Monday. Kind of excited. I’ve heard it’s a mixed bag. I do say that if someone like a… https://t.co/mwZRexUzw4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So for instance, a company issued equity shares. Forever they will be kept on the books at the price they were sold… https://t.co/fyJzkfS8y2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clark College is hiring! Click to apply: Part-time Philosophy Instructor - Education #PDX #VancouverWA https://t.co/hcADhUHs16]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what happens when leftists control our schools. Instead of being taught civics, mathematics, or history, ou… https://t.co/N17BPvRZsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaniceDean I’m doing the same. I just had a hummus and mezze salad celery juice, some sort of green juice and a sh… https://t.co/SX46I0T675]]></document><document><![CDATA[you think she would get the point that i’m NOT interested in buying her makeup after the 7 times i IGNORED her.   p… https://t.co/gtV5KsyHO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PerdigueroSIPEp @merece_saberlo Alfredoooooooo.....y mira q no tenía ganas de vomitar😉😉😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders The top 20% (those making more than $150K) pay 87% off all income tax.   How much should they pay?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come to the show tonight at the @wickyards on YSU campus ima be performing wit some other great artists  🐏🎤 @ Young… https://t.co/fkQ8xIA1s4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobCairns @JohnLusher @HaleyVeturis @cu2uc @AlbertCavazos @windowsot @Charlenemay @TalentedInk @acoracle Amen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask Your Body a Different Question... What's Your Next BOLD Move? #getfitbetrue #trainforchange  #motivation… https://t.co/q3mMY7WS01]]></document><document><![CDATA[sharing this because I love the fact that Tito Puente is here to tell you that there is no such thing as salsa in 5… https://t.co/E1CPntax51]]></document><document><![CDATA[I suspect the TAM signings will come quickly after this is official. Of note is that TFC has a bye in week 2. With… https://t.co/QB0QP8gVqU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysteryman113 @DGSkilla23 @MeganHickeyCBS2 @cbschicago Also the lawyers are there not with the hope of being paid… https://t.co/CPesnLE4Kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Birdseye1 @chriswaslight @Truth2Dj @The_DNELSON @AMERICAOF1 @imaxmeon @MargaretMcgui16 @BrettHuntoon… https://t.co/o6b9LzKsl5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I change dirty diapers.  I pick up dog shit  ... https://t.co/z97M8pKBvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uribe2525 Muy buenos días para ti también Evelyn y feliz jueves cuídate mucho saludos cordiales y Bendiciones ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IF IT CAN MELT STEEL BEAMS HOW CAN IT BURN IN A JET ENGINE FOR A FIVE HOUR FLIGHT FROM PHOENIX TO BOSTON WITHOUT ME… https://t.co/iJUfDeKyc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s another night at work where I watch these young escorts trynna pick up guys walking through the casino]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoJoz_World_ Contact my daughter for leads. She always has/knows/uses the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So that’s what she was doing in the bathroom so quietly https://t.co/YWKemBvnVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might want to look up the definition of “photographer.” And also learn the difference between the terms “photograph… https://t.co/vL9k8bisRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_N_DMT Ajajajaja! Chi! Muy iluminada! Redentora! Inmaculada! Sin zapatos...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us tomorrow as we experience the LAVISH LOVE OF GOD in our study of Psalm 22 @roswellstreetbc / 10:30 am Worsh… https://t.co/WkvhXETDKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, 8 inches of snow aint going to stop me. #MinneSNOWta @NoLayingUp @GolfChannel https://t.co/ILNOkn9hF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @cristinalaila1 "Can't recall" It is called the Obama/Holder/Clinton defense @paulsperry_ @TomFitton… https://t.co/JWaQzGqOoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebateBrexit @netflix But Elvis is alive! I just saw him and Biggie and Tupac at Burger King the other day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trenttl_ This happened at my high school too, except this girl posted sonogram pictures on instagram then deleted… https://t.co/tOkEhJRiVL]]></document></documents></author>