<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[the tv show the office is government propaganda created to reenforce capitalist ideals by conceptualizing the workp… https://t.co/xi8oHicMki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closing on the house set for next Friday - feeling excited https://t.co/gk2GwiKpPl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me applying for single occupancy next year and the housing application crashes https://t.co/syeUQgXrIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KAliceCompeau The Ladykillers remake by (gulp) the Coen Bros. Hard to admit because I otherwise celebrate their entire catalog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basketball hubs 🏀☀️🌭 • #miamiheat ##letsgoheat #defense #alltheballs #propertourists @ AmericanAirlines Arena https://t.co/KCZCEuziHx]]></document><document><![CDATA[that we need to get the state test off  these school children they do not get a grade they are all over the place t… https://t.co/XMxSb6KrSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Treason!!  Trump @realDonaldTrump should declare ‘Martial Law,’ and arrest the Treasonous Perpetuators.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Unbelievable!!  Sounds like this is Canada’s version of ‘trumpeters!!’]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amypeck2011 @SsJamieDornan @Elenaandherword @MissJulieBehave @50shadesofdandj @50Shades_JD @truefan50shades… https://t.co/wW7sjXpKnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanbehar I’ve had the same experience.  I echo the others who recommend blocking. I’m trying my best not to enga… https://t.co/HczJgyR6Vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djc27osu @SKonwinski You don’t know me ... Plus the trailer got me really hype 🙌🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy international women’s day! All three of these girls are so talented and amazing i’m so happy to cosplay this… https://t.co/buEW5Fwf2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[CFA, you’re slipping. I shouldn’t have to call everytime I come bc you forget half my shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First and Fourth celebrate Dr. Seuss  for #ReadAcrossAmericaDay @SouthwestES https://t.co/sy57FEGB6F]]></document><document><![CDATA[When it rains, Something new grows In all the spaces The sun could never reach #pavanareddy 💚💚💚 @ Palace of Fine Ar… https://t.co/hCGjVNOZ9r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Great Plains Regional Medical Center https://t.co/eZgoEqqYbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you haven’t checked out @AaronSlone’s blog you’re missing out people!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does everyone in denver call crab rangoons, “cheese wontons” ???!!!! i’m pizzed]]></document><document><![CDATA[royal street. new orleans. louisiana. @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/WLST9gFFQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nyalain lokesyen karena lagi luar negeri. Kalau lagi di rumah mah moal da.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m starting to hurt to the point where i just want him here now and to have my body back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cause I'm not just a Porn Star you know 😅😅😅  Anyway, this shit is about to go down!! 😎👊🏽🤘🏽 #gamer #wannabe… https://t.co/yDxrwvkzcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhh you mean I have too....🙄😬Okay, one day I will. Not tonight, too much activity on the go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell You ARE your dog. Energetic. Curious. Etc. #peoplewhoareliketheirdogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[y’all really got kim kardashian saying period with a t i just- https://t.co/MyAHPXbyhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amethyst_leon It’s not actually called Ocean Avenue sadly but imma try to remember to snag you a pic when I go visit in September. 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perlmutations Yeah...so there is that.  Maybe it’s all those meds again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruce lovin "it's a small world"  #bruceharrison #itsasmallworld #magickingdom #iloveyou #family @ Walt Disney's Ma… https://t.co/UdQtPKYe5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[None of my friends are awake and I have practice in 20 what a boring morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway men are shit dont touch people unless they give u consent to why is that such a hard concept]]></document><document><![CDATA[The opportunity that @norvina1 and @ABHcosmetics are giving to micro influencers it’s amazing! That is one of my bi… https://t.co/BWJKaSHsE1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yepp_itsBee Being positive and thinking about having a flat stomach literally it’s sounds dumb but it’s really not… https://t.co/L7jAGzfXiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEI certified dentist Silver amalgam fillings are made of approximately 50 percent mercury and when hated from chew… https://t.co/dH91oOAT2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elakdawalla I use Mendeley. Love the desktop app (for Mac) and it’s relatively easy for Word citations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still can’t get over that fight scene with Daryl and Beta😳 They couldn’t have matched up two better peeps💪 I’m re… https://t.co/5eF0D033HK]]></document><document><![CDATA[that semi-stranger you see at the gas station every time you fill up? i bet there’s someone out there who prays for… https://t.co/3S9MQEiDsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtsArt @CCES_Principal @CCES_AP Thank you for creating our shirt design!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ShoMarket Sip and Slime crew spent yesterday afternoon at the annual Eta Sigma Chapter of Sigma Gamma Rho Soror… https://t.co/GmbM7F0cOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It baffles me that some don’t understand this is a pretty “duh” endorsement. Then again, most don’t get California.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vegan Egg Rolls #veganfood #vegan @ Icy Donut Spring Park https://t.co/u4rAWStGbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to need to find something adorable for Larkin to wear for Easter 🐣 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieGump @MKGenest I love hearing that at Christmas as well.  Story draws you in.  ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s the day! Take this flyer into Jersey Mike’s in Stow and help support our RHS Cheerleaders!!!! @alyson_judith]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be one of those #LoserTeachers that teaches students to think critically, question sources, and foster cur… https://t.co/Hbb7u9aJBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sitting here tight hot ass tears down my face cause my nigga I’m entirely too fucking real to be lied to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 @StigallPat That’s what Trump likes about him. He’s always attracted to scum and tyrants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson I think you’re the one that scared because we’re winning and we’re woke 🇺🇸💃 #TheGreatAwakening https://t.co/dvWJkED7py]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imaginarymargo @EdonaGKrasniqi @trUeLOVEdatsME @_starpostgroup_ Yes! Look Maurice can go I twerked for Jesus when… https://t.co/GA0XSCdTDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfbj FYI @ChowenBollock I heard they are selling there stormy Daniels tapes for $7 each, get down there !!😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sherifflamb1 @Vivaciousveter1 #60DaysIn #ArtsAndEntertainment  y’all need 2take booking photos w/help of makeup ar… https://t.co/jgQESy9q4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shiloh feels good about the Rollercoaster 🎢 competition #ScienceOlympiad #ProudTeacher https://t.co/rEzRFsHA8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JOHN__JUAN Couldn’t make it past 20 mins? I’ll give the season a try tho. What did you think of it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bucket List ✅ Visit Cousin Gina @  Washington State Capital in Olympia  She’s Bj’s cousin on his mom’s side of the… https://t.co/BFWubF8jWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone remember when a certain someone called the cops on a party just for clout]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost sandeesoulsista (with report.for.insta) ... Celebrating #internationalwomensday  tomorrow at muchmoresnyc w… https://t.co/Pxwxq4r1rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[HUGE props 🙌🏻 to the Graduate in Minneapolis for eliminating single-use plastic! Think about the amount of plastic… https://t.co/deU2poivUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this #girls #handbag #onsale in my Etsy shop #etsyaaa https://t.co/WAn44f4B30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmikinzC @MauraWest This weekend!! Em I wish you could fly across the ocean to join in on the fun! 🍾😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emerging Technologies in Journalism and Media: International Perspectives on Their Nature and Impact @CogitatioMaC… https://t.co/BNnwkECnXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FAX_online @RealJamesWoods It’s racist regardless of the skin tone of the one who says it.  Imagine “I hope the in… https://t.co/fxkC7qCFBO]]></document><document><![CDATA[supply regulations, import barriers, and crop insurance. These programs have been expanded, modified, and added to… https://t.co/MfCqmAG5kB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto Just like he takes MBS "at his word" that he didn't order the killing of Jamal Khashoggi.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EasyEarl @EpochTimes Thanking God, for leading to the @GaHouseHub to pass #HB481, the Living Infants Fairness and… https://t.co/bbgX1oRIej]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMail What the hell is wrong with the US, opening and now closing the consulate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s literally margs any time of the day/night with this guy and I can’t play this game this often😶🙃🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amigo En Venezuela la derecha no existe, nunca existió.  Solo izquierda Entiendalo.   Ahora se pelea con un régimen… https://t.co/whaoyGIPRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[In 6 days Eddie and I will be enjoying this view while awaiting our departure on Monday for our 5 day cruise 🚢 to t… https://t.co/SW21y6ApWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_christinaaaxox @mrscrankshaft Probably a good idea 🤷🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/4fPs6Q1gfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryWarnedUs Maybe just ignore him and his cult, and let the people vote? Democrats don't want him. Only his ba… https://t.co/lRPH9eOPPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Children Who Experience Early Childhood Trauma Do Not ‘Just Get Over It’ https://t.co/wrsRhX7Eu6 via @swhelperorg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please thank the blunt I just had for making me more positive 💙💙💙 https://t.co/Axvl6Ot5m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sign Jon Stewart's petition to support 9/11 survivors https://t.co/RR53xberdU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why Bernie Sanders’ top campaign strategist is caught up in the Paul Manafort trial, via @mic https://t.co/4h8sVc3ztX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to create a new FB account... lol dont even know why. I’ll delete it in a few days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In protest of this past weekend’s daylight savings time, combined with her human’s schedule and 4:30 am alarm, Will… https://t.co/DHSm1deg0W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhyllisNef @grendelsmumm I’m too old to sell my vagina eggs for cash dammit]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bernie #handsoffmymoney  NO FREE ANYTHING.  WHY SHOULD I PAY FOR FREE STUFF FOR OTHER PEOPLE, WHEN THEY CAN WORK T… https://t.co/OLbFeBpfct]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyBirthday grace_gris...love you! 😘 @ Pasquini's Fine Italian Food https://t.co/gIdwENobNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes @realDonaldTrump I don't follow Trump but I still see his tweets from others who either like or RT th… https://t.co/288k9eegM7]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOT TO HAND IT TO MA MAKING.SOME IMPRESSIVE HAY. BUT REALLY A DOPE DEALER IN MOONLIGHT??? IF YOU REALLY HAD BEEN ON… https://t.co/j6ujqDOHop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgoess96 That’s what I did!!! When we got home he didn’t even greet us, he was so invested.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenSJacobsCA @chrisderose @emilymiskel Ummm and all he did was answer the question. Smdh it just so happened that it was about a female]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @whitney_bauer10 for setting the Elm Creek Season Assist Record with 107 assists! https://t.co/mRCuWPP1iE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been on a Fleetwood Mac, kacey musgraves, and heart kick lately and this is a mood that I need rn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BaggooAlan @tasha_wodak @onlytshepo_ @Sabelo912 @Leachimblue @BBCSport Well said 👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[The journalist in me is impressed, but the 12-year-old in me is super excited about that scholastic books series.… https://t.co/uAAfIEXOpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Really? A lot must be going on behind the scenes that us mere mortals aren’t privy to!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPTeamRafa @ppteamcynthia_ @RafaelMySmile @smileforlesslie https://t.co/ZENXakCXPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @vanderkitten ・・・ New for 2019 is an evolution of our industry-leading, hand-built, Pro Series Cycling Jers… https://t.co/CzO74nGxpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dani09_83 I need to watch it about 80 more times just to catch everything]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuarón talks about his love for @Cruz_Azul_FC!! Great piece, @Carlos_Film 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPThrio they can, although idk how often they do. so when you search a hashtag below will be the posts but if you… https://t.co/waqqmoEBTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is fucking HARD and lonely to be such a sensitive creature on this planet. 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t miss out on this great deal shop with me today online at https://t.co/ZSOFD0gHfr https://t.co/B5fUINsWq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like such a bird being so intrigued in this celebrity drama. They got me good this time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fa2Chainz For me it was the illusion that true love exists and could somehow be found on the internet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republic reporters receive prestigious Polk Award for #charter-school reporting https://t.co/9iMEkXJm4C via @azcentral #txlege #txed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrFly187 @beccas1434 Hannity is “big brother” from 1984. Can’t wait till he’s in jail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to get back home....so I can watch the ##RHONJ reunion!  My @BravoTV app wouldn’t load so I could watch and… https://t.co/Gx1xgBDI8Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[⏰Few more days to registration dateline! ⏰ Make sure you sign up for the pre-CSW youth dialogues where we will disc… https://t.co/406USJuzAI]]></document></documents></author>