<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Stuttsy @WWERetroStars What is odd is I never saw Ric Flair retro in any store but Five Below. I saw about 10 of t… https://t.co/eHGtERJP5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week is your last chance to get tickets before @ogjellybean jettredrocket and myself go out and put on a show… https://t.co/zCnZ93epWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone was screaming in the library because someone"stole" her laptop. No one wants your 2005 Dell, Karen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Grandson Easton ready for Senior Night at Sacred Heart Sedalia w Karen Connors Enloe https://t.co/fr1HYpysEi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freedomcaucus @Jim_Jordan @RepAndyBiggsAZ @RepMarkMeadows The @freedomcaucus version of freedom is that everyone i… https://t.co/oalGvN5BsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The behavior and reputations of founders and principals is linked to that of their company's. This affects both cus… https://t.co/utzOqW0WCY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexsalvinews @OANN What does this have to do with the Donald Trump Presidency. Total witch hunt instigated by Mue… https://t.co/aIj1HThv31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treykook @natemcdermott @shaunking She was opposed by the Russians and the Bernie Bots— both singing the same tune.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CascadiaSoccer I pre-ordered a home jersey last year and I still haven't received my order. Can I get some help with that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lightning36 @Robvegaspoker Did you think about another woman while eating it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @Mavandspark @rkelly He should get rid of all of them I get two charges out of his big mouth, those co… https://t.co/r6mgwrP13L]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chocolate Guinness brownie with stout butter frosting recipe https://t.co/nkNmNEaAfV via @IrishCentral]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JennyLynnBrdar Apparently I’m to old for that 😂 I just want my phone to ring like a normal phone]]></document><document><![CDATA[I read it about her while living in Korea. #Remember1919 #WomensHistoryMonth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBrandonMorse i need serious hog control at my lease. Come on down. #CodeMonkeys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyMcGrathKY Once the president vetos it and it gets sent back, then we will see the true colors. Right now it is… https://t.co/Jv1DWZ2Tl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[skeler. - ＷＯＲＬＤＳ ＡＷＡＹ https://t.co/R9GlJToPZf via @YouTube their this series of songs on YouTube for 3 -4 years I’m… https://t.co/7nkstwOxC6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RhondaMcMahon24 Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tennesseine You get all types,I'm afraid. There were fanatics in every camp. They may also be bots. Did you chk their follower count?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constant harassment by the left. This man deserves to shop in peace. I wonder if someone like this would do somethi… https://t.co/hkYXtgKtUx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news for my firm. We just added a group of almost 20 litigation attorneys, many of whom are ERISA litigators,… https://t.co/WI90U0wXWs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats must cry themselves to sleep nightly, Every day I wake up I smile knowing the man leading out country for… https://t.co/onrQv9I9Ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[One last Post as I go to bed Every single Word said to Russ last night was heard by children and by Donovan Mitchel… https://t.co/DLLiPAk1G2]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's currently 34° F and light fog in Harrisburg with active alerts. Visit https://t.co/D0EYeDbBdR  From  1Weather… https://t.co/QpTb6RDBel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRichMaclone Heard of it. But I only see Rob Lowe as one person. https://t.co/i5mloi1bKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sales Call Mistakes:  You’re too nervous. Sales calls require confidence. But if you’re sounding anxious and stumbl… https://t.co/f6GvCpnFWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lasassinate @Amandaeldracher @TSetnicky @BillMarra98 I’m a pretty happy guy honestly. Life’s great except for my t… https://t.co/Ef2tepDkBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the Doc while eating on Valentine's date. @drdisrespect https://t.co/A5H2iStAN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[March in #MyMaine:  Day 1:  40F and you get 8 inches of snow Day 2: brightest sunshine you've seen in 5 months and its 18F.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to be in for @hughhewitt!  Up next: @mikeallen of @axios on the hot stories to start the week.  Listen at… https://t.co/diZRRaRaNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Steele is an idiot and stoking fear with this BS ..... just STFU!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @yahoomail @Yahoo @Microsoft @CERN @NSAGov @CIA @WhiteHouse EVER GET PO'd when dragon speak says you just… https://t.co/6WbATdMq5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I get older, I hope I age as well as @JColeNC’s 2014 Forest Hills Drive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColBannister @NaveedAJamali @chrislhayes @MrJonCryer Let's not forget that if god created us and he kills people a… https://t.co/QlPAWH9krV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simonsnake70 Is there a reason you are?  I have plenty of reason why I'm not. and I just listed a few of them. He'… https://t.co/1bVQspmmmG]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Increíble!  Pasan de una luminaria de LED -de esas que costaron más de 45 millones de pesos la pasada administraci… https://t.co/q6T0uN1C22]]></document><document><![CDATA[The upright man is the one who fears  God--and turns away from evil." Job 1:8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissquire6 @RyanAFournier Why isn't that substitute teacher prosecuted this is the f****** problem do something… https://t.co/5TkhOqrpa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattDancigers Much like his other book, “The obstacle is the way”, there are many stories and anecdotes that are e… https://t.co/Q0iZHKa7CZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO Glen Grant! That’s my favorite. First had it in Scotland when in in the Navy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s not even close to the pro-Trump book https://t.co/MFK3hABnZN #maga #DeepState #trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to catch my attention while I’m DJing? Just give me an inflatable flamingo 🤪🙌🔥 #FlamingoLove https://t.co/YekGUJtfZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpvguerrier Mwen konn kotem kanpe👊🏾... mwen pa gen esplikasyon poum fè pèsonn ke Granmèt la. Si gen moun ki vle pr… https://t.co/yddy8hk0Ak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Irish Eyes by @TrueRespite at @TrueRespite — https://t.co/3E5bMlVbJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATs are health care no matter the school #Pac12Swim #pac12dive #NATM2019 ⁦@pac12⁩ ⁦@NATA1950⁩ https://t.co/oQKFzIJK0Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clarisamadruga4 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joeywolf44 Stop it! I love East Shore restaurants and you’re making me crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the trump administration is going to allow highly toxic pesticides to be sprayed which will kill off a large amount… https://t.co/cGbnFnc43V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love Will Get You Through Times with no Money, but Money Wont Get u Through Times With No Love]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWVS #NEWYORK POSTED 📈 #X @ Brooklyn, New York https://t.co/NZKFA5i2GW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bro how did you get verified?  It’s called next man up the other guys will score more than their averages because t… https://t.co/JTBZfTxufM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just tore this whole contraption apart. I hope I don’t have to put it back together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sporting the snow blown look....... #snow #snowday #snowblower #sunday #sundayfunday #thelook #lakesherwood #lake… https://t.co/O6E83dbHcW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new rim ready for action here at St Joseph’s, replacing the bent one that has delayed tonight’s game https://t.co/0pmGGFw39k]]></document><document><![CDATA[We gave up Khalil Mack and amari cooper for a 30 yr old who wants half of the cap space and now the raiders have 5… https://t.co/rbxk1FoU52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finished this one last week on the homie Kirk. Outline and Bull are healed and shading is fresh. Thanks again for l… https://t.co/xQ1jBVQYiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's those no big deal things that matter the most https://t.co/Nr8JIcoY2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@printtemps Even this car? All electric, same displacement as a Honda Goldwing ... https://t.co/oiXtB35SpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXACTLY how I feel. He’s going to a game and a league with zero loyalty when he could’ve been regarded as one of th… https://t.co/51xNpe6h78]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump @SteveKBannon @StephenMillerAL My apologies (autocorrect) to parody account… https://t.co/MQI4fuHVxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The Book ," everything Trump touches dies." Is the best read . It is all true.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The racial divide in Ms is nowhere near what many are led to believe. We live together, work together, raise our ki… https://t.co/HZ855qE4fz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spike Lee on the Knicks at the Oscars: &amp;#8216;We&amp;#8217;re trying to tank!&amp;#8217; https://t.co/giPGr8rRYK]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the paper's implication makes me nervous. What if advancing knowledge requires you to know more and more and th… https://t.co/lrSXBIgF7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damnshes_feisty @nxtstvp @Gabriel_MWilson @shaunacoralee She acts like god gave her a list of shit to do and not to do. 🤦🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweet Jesus, do I look good in a suit or what! #KidVicious💪🏽😏👊🏽 #Dragon💪🏽🐲👊🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandyMom4 When I told @asullins81 my idea, she was like “absolutely not, I’d be throw the remote thru the TV mad a… https://t.co/6TwZuuYm9q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Axios: How Big Pharma's research budgets stack up to its profits. https://t.co/qg07iSXdKe  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sí... del imperio castrista. O sea, el pueblo impide la acción imperialista, unilateral, neo-castro- fascista, de l… https://t.co/vJiSqtbpFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is anybody else thinking that William Barr is shutting down the Mueller #TrumpRussia investigation rn?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My skull is in serious pain, but at I'm not puking out of my mouth or my B U T rn so that is a plus https://t.co/uNltSCGGrs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind What? He's not aloud to hold hands with his girlfriend (mistress).]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ugh why do I always get so emotionally invested in getting Democrats to not suck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the day! FREE crawfish and @HailStateBB today at 3 PM.  Come enjoy crawfish (and heaters) while you watch… https://t.co/A46BgFLdfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClaireBLang hey Claire will you guys be doing a live Q&amp;A like last year? Lots of laughs #NASCAR… https://t.co/BwWlo77WxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think so much, that I’ll be driving w no music on for minutes on end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[With #TheCatONineTails, #Argento’s most Hitchcokian film, we see a blind man and a little girl trying to solve a my… https://t.co/iLLoCswJez]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who EXPAND your knowledge, potential, and capabilities... not those who try to restrict them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cowgirls4Trump @MislaMelissa @jklslayer258 @racephenom @TrumpLoverTina @lupieleslie @KCLibertyAvenge @Mamma_Kel… https://t.co/UpHmwtsC3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smilon713 @MollyJongFast These kids and the reefer madness. I tell you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bonnhere I've got news...the adults aren't any better. If I'm tailgated now, I slowly come to a complete stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relive the action from @rungasparilla with this banger from @StephenKersh   @HOKAONEONE @PolarGlobal @GUEnergyLabs… https://t.co/KjOtxGZYiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cevangelista413 I STILL argue that we really need a revamp of Buffy the Vampire Slayer, not a reboot, but continui… https://t.co/VmrHJ97ISe]]></document><document><![CDATA[That said, I did see the movie like four times and I’m not gonna pretend like I didn’t enjoy it or anything. I’m si… https://t.co/1LxppmdDkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicklap_ @KingKohle83 would not wanna be in the lane this week if the balls in his hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Info: https://t.co/H9oTMwmbWA … 2019 #ProductionAllianceGroup300 #Livestream Event: 2019 #NASCAR #XfinitySeries Loc… https://t.co/jPsJfNtH7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Franky_P_ Soto, Robles, 🎒🎒, Zim,  Trea and the pitching staff. I’ll take everyday. #3 is gonna need a helmet stand… https://t.co/C1sRVpxEsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaiyanaBrief @AshleyBel84 @SeanSchemmel @Rialisms @iantweeting @VoiceOfVegeta @FUNimation Technique babies. Technique.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Letting the people of NK build an economy to feed themselves seems like a good way t… https://t.co/WzjtbvFfb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The refs handling of this game has been T E R R I B L E #LAFCvSKC #ForGloryForCity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Republicans Already Are Demonizing Democrats as Socialists and Baby Killers https://t.co/EIPMHfR8xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Temporal Purgatory by @18thStreetBrew @ City Social Kitchen &amp; Bar — https://t.co/EirPtq4tHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fact 2 - 75% of people say they have been affected by bullying. Children who have been bullied are at risk of suici… https://t.co/XmlSnBKCbW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s be honest here..Omar has deep seated grievances against Israel. It will not go away.  If she continues to ser… https://t.co/iApGCoFTrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Um2X7BdFU8  https://t.co/8sXq1RELFh  "My 1st copy I sold of my new book, Dead Phone, arrived today; an… https://t.co/htcc2edzck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright cool that’s officially enough internet for today and probably forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a handle for filming skate clips. LETS GOOOOO! https://t.co/BAk0b3IzE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Winston-Salem, North Carolina https://t.co/oCPFGqjeju]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also available from the government: ICE Babysitters, IRS Bank Accounts, DMV Time Management Courses, and EPA Plasti… https://t.co/P697Nz1gaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I CAN NOT STRESS THIS ENOUGH!! THIS IS A VERY TRUE STATEMENT. DONT @ ME]]></document></documents></author>