<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0Jnx60dIjx 🚀  https://t.co/wtSCp3QhG9  #rickrockbeats #RickRockBeatsTheAlbum   #RocketTheAlbum… https://t.co/764bsuGOWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@traciemac_Bmore @ZevShalev @NarativLive I counted at least 3 suitcases! 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeanMotionMedia @NWSPaducah @WEHTWTVWlocal Probably will be here in Owensboro soon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of 7 favorite book challenge. Today I nominate @munson_math to post her top seven over as many days! https://t.co/dCMZTl02RH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a nice little visit and cool performance from @kaitlynbristowe (Season 11 @bacheloretteabc) with us here ton… https://t.co/pRd2ETNDKr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este es mi libro ,de cabecera así le llamo yo , ya lo conocen hace años ,que se los muestro y recomiendo ,lo pueden… https://t.co/IHn8hcI88O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your guide is the FARCE the Leftist Media has fabricated on ALL PPL around Trump.Ya all loved him when he was throw… https://t.co/Pm4rdbtani]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt Casal fino no Museu de Finas Artes 🎭 #sds em Museum of Fine Arts, Boston https://t.co/faTodkt1P6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyZuker @hwinkler4real He's been blind from birth.  He might be a jerk, but let's not make fun of his disability.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me to any film that takes away awards from @the_favourite #Oscars https://t.co/ReQ8oJjrAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CzarGorski @ImTheMarigold @OriolesFanGirl @bethamph3tamine @JohnnyT4 @ErikStafira @aaronpmccray I love free queso....just sayin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exciting news James! Nothing like a camp invite from SMU!  Not that Im biased or anything!  #ponyup #classof89]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 @ProudResister I flat out REFUSE TO celebrate A CHILD RAPIST A WIFE BEATER A pussy-grabber a pervert a sa… https://t.co/ByNPVdO6Aq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only watch the most professional documentaries https://t.co/GQwtz74EIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Psa to all the guys who can’t take a hint sending 🍆🍆🍆💦💦💦 is not going to change anyone’s opinion about wanting to “hook up” with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @realDonaldTrump Don’t have to be disabled to get Medicaid. Slot of people need to get a job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuperEliteTexan @trucknation13 And why weren’t they arrested. That is threats against people’s lives and threats t… https://t.co/zfsQeOY0Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I let anyone knock me up he’s gonna be Jamaican and if he’s not he’s going to have to accept the fact that my ch… https://t.co/i5oOYKrVfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and tell regulators it is time to break up Facebook and make the internet safe for democracy and privacy… https://t.co/lYONutr6gP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SyydNee_ Lol. Last minute tickets be wild. DC to ATL this Saturday smh. Won’t be me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FixesItself @phyllisj1003 @NAudrey_ST @AussieDebBell @ItsMeCandiceTh1 @callkurt @pam_brundige @fit_gb… https://t.co/XMySb1WXMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[im finally off tomorrow &amp; all i can think about is how excited i am to clean the house]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not even a minute outside and I have enough static electricity to keep the building running for a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was wondering maybe could I make you my baby? If we do the unthinkable, would it make us look crazy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jarpad @realGpad You guys make suck a adorable couple looking forward to the next 9 years .. ❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my Springbreak: snow, streaks of sunshine and sticks. #babyitiscoldoutside #isitsummeryet @ Lower Saucon https://t.co/2art6izDcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my! Tennessee man accused of dipping testicles in customer's salsa https://t.co/dO0zTO5Bjy #FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Starbucks tough day for everyone, or is just my phone/app that doesn’t want be caffeinated. #paidwithsparechange]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If she’s not a hustler, she’s a bill” Everything in my life is a byproduct of my work ethic and failure never bein… https://t.co/77rDt971MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreyes37 He knocked over my dehumidifier with lots of water because he was trying to attack the steam 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting the results from that crazy test I took the other day #praying for good #results #amen @ Cumberland Car… https://t.co/HmnkL8xkkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing like being told to come in for your shift at 12, getting all excited to sleep in, then getting a call to co… https://t.co/eS14llvc2i]]></document><document><![CDATA[EAT SHIT DIE BITCH WITHHOLDING INFORMATION FROM ME ABOUT MY LIFE LEADING TO DESTRUCTION OF;ALL SERPENT OUT OF BOUND… https://t.co/xlCUWhucli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RustyLord Hey! It feels GREAT today AND the sun is shining! We'll take what we can get and enjoy it while it's here! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Jacey Hammond (Hammy) @jacehammy2 Proud Australian 🇦🇺   for retweeting the show! Happy day friend! 💙💜☮️🙏🏻 https://t.co/NE4PPUoJNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Disco Inferno by @50cent on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/vPS9udCS4u Sunday Night Fever]]></document><document><![CDATA[But tmrw is my appt and I’m SO READY FOR IT IVE BEEN WAITING 2 MONTHS FOR THIS SHIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peggy_blair @davidgourlay Sounds fun!  Many times during 1st year university when I lived on campus at @Carleton_U… https://t.co/zOPxCismnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Your a crook!!!!! Can't wait for the Mueller full report! Only Republicans would tweet this! Spoken… https://t.co/1nHOH86zQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahPalinUSA Let’s dig deeper into her Russian collusion!!!! Let Trump do his job  without all this phony investi… https://t.co/kGvXjED8We]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @Jesus_Luvs_Us @JackConnie @xaaNrdZvSp8Iyaa @MelindaYoe @karenslinn43 @Peeperpea29… https://t.co/tGDJrdEZAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Sorry for twitter ignorance. I've been banned for talking out to a few ignorant people. No one missed m… https://t.co/OIZHkLwVf2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quinncy 2. Besides, you need someone to take you to the show, to the theater, to act like a 2 year old with. That'… https://t.co/mVy78oh2nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebestjasmine I got tired of boring old hair bands so I bought a bunch of floral scrunchies! https://t.co/xatA9KYR8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rather fail many times than not try at all ‼️ #DailyInspiration #dailymotivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI “Creating the Future of Rehabilitation Medicine” #rehabilitation @upmc @upmc_pmr @drjaimeyu @SuzanneRastrick… https://t.co/x8xU9WjA5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoodMorning (@ The Forbidden Forrest in Hogwarts, VA w/ @bryan_warren) https://t.co/v6R80I2iBa https://t.co/ez4idZTCYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Beyondthebigidea is a great forum — “Look at Oprah, her authenticity. She was offered a huge deal recently because… https://t.co/NnOgf9Xm8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[More on this guy...   Runner who suffocated mountain lion with his foot describes the attack - CNN https://t.co/xAfo3c5gGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[1915 Ford Model T touring car. #ford #fordmodelt #modelt #modeltford #vintage #vintagelove #vintagecar #classiccars… https://t.co/X8z8uPnyA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mulitplyherby4 I love your enthusiasm for life. You're not afraid to be yourself and you fight for what you love.… https://t.co/ULZjvBs3WL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholasBrendon so has anyone met you and been shocked you have two eyes? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte and Reggie sharing a moment this morning. #mvlittles #MVPSchool https://t.co/ppmtan5OYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscars 2019: Spike Lee urges crowd to 'do the right thing' in charged plea ahead of 2020 presidential election… https://t.co/Yl1kvv8G4Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[this morning the sun rose and with it came the birth of my niece magnolia paige baughman - being present at her bir… https://t.co/cGSeArcEta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelBoudreau27 @maggiereilly15 @OfficialLivePD Dude I can’t fucking wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande @ArianaGrande - My patients don’t get a ton of celebrity visitors because we don’t have a separate pe… https://t.co/jKq93749KB]]></document><document><![CDATA[These girls had the choice to sleep in or practice this morning. I’m proud they chose to work. #tmshurdlers… https://t.co/QqTaS8lpQb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy writing about cats this morning, but fluffy dog appreciation post:   "This is Jagger. He’s an incredibly hands… https://t.co/ETiWuikQGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh we have some beautiful vintage items coming my friends!!   Comment MINE when you find your Vintage Love 💗 and di… https://t.co/QBQkwKsvb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand How insulting to our collective intelligence. Unbelievable. Both the clearance and this lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an @ImpossibleFoods #impossibleburger for the first time today. I inhaled it. It was “impossibly” delicious. I’… https://t.co/0WgPx82Wzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s best to be thought a fool and remain silent  than to speak and remove all doubt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@29rain I guess  soo mr legend  or maybe  u do  I perceive  case its impossible  for u to live ur life just working  baby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ted_sahl I hope so too man I’m gonna adopt a African kid On life I already told my girl 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, I stand somewhat corrected: the panel that calls itself “all male” actually includes one woman, whose defense o… https://t.co/V332AGTvTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnzer61 If this is ok with R’s, then so is this https://t.co/hQXwOl9SyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck anyone that thinks any breed of dog is naturally vicious. These are the purest of creatures😭💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[with all this crazy stuff going on in the world , make sure you got your heart right with god 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just had a #Chocopie and a glass of #OrangeJuice - citrus goes well with chocolate, right? https://t.co/9jwo49Jexd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monitorLATINO Voto x #CuandoTeAmé de @julionalvarez para el 1° lugar en #TopCentro @SAPSGrupero @ChulasDeJA @EEnrique_F 2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nationalMTB @GUEnergyLabs @migchapulin @GeoffKabush @AMTetrick @assos_com @NinerBikes @atomcomposites @CamelBak… https://t.co/j6nRJ2F5UA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @Satchalistic1 @_AstroAmerican @MAGA friends Please give @_AstroAmerican a lift and follow him !! Thanks every one !! 😊👋👋👋❤️😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si ven a @marthacedillo felicítela, hoy es su cumpleaños!!  Que Dios siempre cuide tu camino, te guíe  y te bendiga… https://t.co/3g8284Ggic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GheyYu @QLover18 This is a Disgrace!! The poor white child picks up trash, and the damn black bitches throw the trash back out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday! I’m so loving my new hair😍 haleyxhair is the https://t.co/3OTam9RUCw, go see her if you’re local!♥️ I… https://t.co/QNYjFE5pCt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I looked up this great web link with this handy hints about Twitter use, written by Laura Walubengo who lives in Ke… https://t.co/BiSsa3FmEB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevinJames Need you in Florida! Otherwise we have to go all the way to Bethlehem, PA to see you back in our hometown 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are your top priorities this week? 1. Personally  2. Professionally  .... and, how will you feel once you've a… https://t.co/cHeCVRvrVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halcyon_keiran @AttackBunny1970 @Conservative_VW @AOC Just pointing out mistakes I could have made. My bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a rule that if someone is venting to you and you are there 100% listening and being there for them that fo… https://t.co/uMu1vwTKjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chefrocky413 @ivyjofreeman @doctoralexa @ElleWibble @FredMertzReal @JuliaKozuschnik @Grabsback2 @rdnk_grl @efocuss… https://t.co/95qZRk717f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett is one of those crybabies who would pay someone to beat him in a heavyweight market steer class wit… https://t.co/3vNlnkg5EZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always loved Valentine’s Day 💕 show someone you care about them today!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cougars live to have fun. ♥️ @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/Yvur26PPiH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to LIVE on @CHCHTV @morninglive in 20 mins. Sharing some tips to help you get back on track. Tune in!… https://t.co/MBosWNBSqA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieSLalonde Excellent point. Also, so glad I had a childhood that didn't include social media. https://t.co/LSaVs4ehy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Agree. But it will never happen. Democrats will NEVER let themselves be punished or held accountable for… https://t.co/gPcY3MjaKU]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDK, maybe he’s depressed cuz his family doesn’t wanna see him. His balding, wrinkled, traitorous, treasonous ass i… https://t.co/O8nTHkVcK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all the lucky @nycmarathon  lottery winners : have a great time and congrats ! This Marathon , the whole day and… https://t.co/NlG95Qn0rV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now for the big match!  St. pete Vinoy  vs Chelsea Piers CT. Who will win?   #tennisfun @ Vinoy Park https://t.co/vzyG0LMiMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savin’ lives, savin’ lives, ah, ah, ah, ah, savin’ lives, savin’ lives @GreenwoodKISD @KleinISD #CPRTraining by… https://t.co/2UOu7P0l0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zammit_marc @BBFC thank you Marc.  Have a great week!!  Kudos to your success in this film]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJakeStrait @rkrome @SMSUMustangsMBB I’m supporting him now!  But his spirit needs to be a little bigger!]]></document><document><![CDATA[college so far has been me going to three classes, sleeping in my car for an hour and a half and then going to my last class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @realDonaldTrump @reaDonaldTurnip This is why we #LearnToRead]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve got a spot for you at #Xooma’s National Event - April 5th &amp; 6th  For more details, visit… https://t.co/vJ9bBc0XMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[On my way to #Nashville for #WaterYPSummit🚰 and Leadership Training, which is my @awwa event of the year! Very grea… https://t.co/q6eOoKEDZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book 29 of the school year: “So Brave, Young, and Handsome” by my favorite author, Leif Enger. https://t.co/t4qG18txoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for saving this sweetie,  many would not have. Blessings on all of you.]]></document></documents></author>