<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Something has been thumping in my upstairs neighbors apartment for over an hour. I’m very close to going and knocki… https://t.co/3QiscAJlPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta make a phone call about an apt.  so I can set up an appointment for my case manager... I ain't gettin' paid f… https://t.co/kLH5JVyqGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mendo I don't imagine you being beaten given object gliding is removed. Maybe if they used infinite flight but then it'd be null.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EddieAndelman Understood, but other than the $4.5m Oak gave him to sign, the NFL will dwarf MLB earnings in early… https://t.co/ADdB8ghnAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[nashville has decided to become seattle with how much it’s been raining recently, please send ur thoughts and prayers to my hair k thnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Five Definitive Reasons Trump Has Already Won On The Border Wall! https://t.co/EGL23bivXk #war]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a baby my mother gripped me by the heel and dipped me in sugar and now nobody will kiss my sour ass heel, gee thanks Mom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[See a virtual tour of my newest #listing 3644 E 3300 N #Eden #UT  https://t.co/X9EtcN3Kd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend @chrissyteigen @annawilding Coming this week, to Netflix: The Mystery of John and Chrissy’s Oscar Party that wasn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebdub77 @BiggerTen @JodyPorter I was at that game and I know who won !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak @steph93065 @ChrisCuomo @CuomoPrimeTime @CNN @brianstelter @CNNPR @BreitbartNews Network of lies and trash!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Wonder if @PrisonPlanet was trolling for a date when he stumbled over this ..... 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillReme @MarkDice Views are also not changed by harassment and bullying.  #Discourse doesn't have those as founda… https://t.co/lN3YvN31rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxMaysville Too close together using the same characters, you are right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LordOfAlabama @thecjpearson LOL . Whatever, Brandon. Keep on believing what you are told to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[shit would be kinda cool to be laid up with a boo right about now but shit... i don’t got one :-/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it possible to have a pre commit hook that formats C# files?   In Javascript, this is easy to do with… https://t.co/Y4jOhsypQM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great to know wonderful people @ Gammage Auditorium https://t.co/47Yt4HW4Lw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish her every success.  @TheRoot @KFOX14 @abc7breaking @SkepticNikki @RodneyAnon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donavinestep14 @bigorangetix Sitting on the website at 9. Spent 13 minutes trying to get a ticket until finally the phase ended.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back home for 2019! (@ The Gulch Area in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/1gOHL1EZM2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kris emailing TMZ some more fake stories when she sees people ain’t buying the Jordyn and Khloé drama https://t.co/g2POxn9A6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwsymphony tuning speakers 🎼 @ Wallcast at Soundscape Park https://t.co/eOIPaKqZDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[is it normal to hate yourself when #editing your own footage? #shakyhands]]></document><document><![CDATA[Branding is your attempt to harness relationships. @ Miami, Florida, USA https://t.co/MjSDpdEgud]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why anybody would say people are obsessed with AOC, I just don’t see it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sneakersqueaks @TSNCurling Hahaha!! I saw the same thing! Pushing and shoving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes @HollywoodInToto @WashTimesOpEd The reason nobody watches anymore is because all the so-called "movies"… https://t.co/z3lqkX6GNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Side note I’ve been craving enchiladas and you know what.... I’m fucking getting enchiladas!  #mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was going slow and bumped into this small curb on the driveway. The scooter stopped suddenly and flipped forward. L… https://t.co/crfDNOGhZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jmenglish_ @realDonaldTrump What rock did you crawl out from under? Donnie Boy's as useful as broken wind in an el… https://t.co/m7uTYZvVUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shermanburdette checking out @RebellionDough 🍩🤘🏾 https://t.co/iiSaS0Afgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marine Corps steps up winter-warfare training as global threat shifts https://t.co/0v7EOau6a4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sassy9374 @JesseRodriguez @selectedwisdom A deal doesn’t have to be made on your schedule? The Korean issues has b… https://t.co/iQ5es6UBZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GLegoy @TylerJBrown192 @enlow_kenny I am not anti-tax, which is why I said “keep MORE of what they earn”. I think… https://t.co/A0uH6Iin3D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProLifeAction @iamsambee @FullFrontalSamB @SarahKSilverman @LadyPJustice @michelleisawolf @robinmarty 🖕🏻you. Mind your business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRedMantisEye @jacobinmag @IlhanMN 1) Pretty sure "Central Bank Tyranny" is one of those whatchamallem, anti-Sem… https://t.co/cF4ckmxjnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[WLAX: Hall getting tricky! Terriers lead 8-2 at the half. https://t.co/Zt5KbxDJuU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicashram @standatlantic @jonnoatlantic @BonAtlantic @PotterAtlantic @MikiSFTF YASSSSSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Thattinyassgirl @penelop06848466 @bri_sacks This is Indiana where I can take you for a fact that you can get a thr… https://t.co/Dkdb6QOxJj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trust me buddy you don’t want to fight me. My dads a hurtz rental car gold member]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still can't believe Hannah B made it to the family round, crazy as she is #BachelorMonday #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @soledadobrien ANA, I thought you were married with 2 kids. Congratulations and happy days ahead. Who h… https://t.co/SoVf1CmXaj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinceMcMahon    I didn't know Bruce pritchard didn't work for the WWE anymore although I should have suspected it… https://t.co/S5OCyDTzeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBADonaldTrump @IndiansTrump @TrumpOSU @Indians @TheRealSlamtana You guys are dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[ISO 3 tickets to see @BobWeir &amp; @wolfbrothers  tonight at the #BlueNote for me and the kiddos. It’s right down the street!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lovrega @tatclouthier ¿Y como que ha hecho Tatiana para el 2024? No ha dado un golpe de autoridad en el Congreso,… https://t.co/ptl5weInVB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes they are playing baseball at Newman Park.6th inning. Catawba 1 Anderson 0. Bryan Ketchie doing it again on the… https://t.co/jhIr2zjaAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL:  @WWUMBB takes down #HGLU 66-63 and are one step closer to a #2 or #3 seed in the #AMCTournament.  An absolu… https://t.co/ciWilEFJSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Itsjustrigo @pinchetwink No one has ever stole a girl from me except your fatass at edc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nascarman_rr Yes I was there. But not sure I can share Big E photos from Feb. #TooSad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader Would this also apply if President Obama paid hush money? Just asking https://t.co/7sgKcpRuOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drjohnm @EdwardTufte @CSHeartResearch @bmj_latest @fgodlee Unnecessary Genome Sequencing is like WebMD on steroids 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemme think about that... Amanda said something similar but idk I think there’s a better answer here]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harper’s slash line is .268/.365/.564 in 179 at bats at Citizens. #mlb #phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[33.1005° N, 116.3013° W #joshuatree #california #desert @ Joshua Tree, California https://t.co/ZoAJwqa9Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outside of the video this is retweeting, I just discovered that "Jesus pole vaulting christ" is my new saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieXHunter Page count varies based on interior settings (font type and size). The most consistent story tellin… https://t.co/Of7tk9kjxa]]></document><document><![CDATA[#valentinesdaynyc 😘🖤♠️ #allevilthings 💜♠️😈 #pleaseme #cakesss @ Electric Room https://t.co/KB39A7Mvx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@madddie818 My ex fiancé and my ex that told me to kill myself while I was going through an episode both popped up… https://t.co/MOEusXVkdL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump needs to shut down for more than 30 days &amp; then have a "reduction in force".]]></document><document><![CDATA[I genuinely think people may not understand or think about this. I'm not trying to scold. Please, just think about… https://t.co/fAgUCEmFLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT @MUTGuru @EA_KRAELO @Jstein2469 @Schautz47 @Sgibs7 @MaddenBible really though where is warren moon? S… https://t.co/OrygZRJtKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy @bdomenech Irish car bombs are stupidly low ABV.  Guinness is 4.2% abv  Jameson is like 40, but 1/2… https://t.co/RTrfvhn0gT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TBT + #30YearChallenge. Todavía mantengo intacto el look de aquella época. #ChandlerEsMiPastor… https://t.co/g3iEQD649y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sensory OverloaDDH (Nelson) by @Ologybrewing @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/nzqwzkInxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like you either end up being on Live PD. Or you sit at home watching and making fun of people who end up on Live PD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP GT-4586 : Ferrari-Powered Toyota drifts a Portland Touge https://t.co/5EZJKEJG4M via @YouTube 🤭🤭]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my very first best friend. you da 💣 @MaJorTosino https://t.co/bCE5XDz3oM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baumanelise Awe you’re the best! I’m so happy for you. I have a feeling that KimCon will come soon. Looking at you @Kimbits416!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xfoster6 You're pretty butthurt this whole AB thing. Just wait till the Steelers start losing to the Brown's twice a year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT The Mueller report? Is this how deluded @HillaryClinton is now? She actually thinks there will be someth… https://t.co/2lZAv8V6nT]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Section925 where's the pod? We need someone unfiltered to dissect Cal Hoops and to provide some gold linings... #gobears]]></document><document><![CDATA[My old stomping grounds in East Alabama/West Georgia. Damage looks bad down that way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro me and @23_elmore  would be on zombies and anytime one of us went down we’d pause the game and put “take it to… https://t.co/Ytx4hews3p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday Brunch at both #jbjsoulkitchen 's today 11:30-2 https://t.co/SJ5AssmXCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC @SpeakerPelosi Isn’t this comparable to saying if someone breaks into your house their menu requests should not be ignored?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane John Taveras and the Leafs will go deeper in the playoffs!!! Guarantee it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do bitches treat me like I'm ugly but behind my back they love to discuss me....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your are in the perfect time. With all the Tools And all the abilities you need! Goooooooo!!!!! @ 92Q https://t.co/BviAd9O9S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trouble &amp; reflections #love #IceTrekking #RoughCollie #DogsOfInstagram @ Turner Reservoir Loop Trail https://t.co/qWFmuYUyTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the presence of greatness @the_amazing_raj @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/jO5BtvfBvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tangotiger @steamerpro Weird another MVP season projected for Mike Trout.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomasJTobin1 You probably had an N router and a modem with less than Docsis 3.0. It’s the Gift of Finest Wheat of internet setups.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started on a pint of chocolate Häagen-Dazs today. I am not aware of a better chocolate ice cream.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As McCabe so Eloquently put it, POTUS May be a Russian! I say , accusers Usually accuse others, of exactly of What… https://t.co/9c0DOLOx5V]]></document><document><![CDATA[So here I am twitter, asking you what you think I should do? Should I confront the situation or should i just let it go?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump “The Democrat Plantation”, The Party Of Bias, Racist, And The KKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @SykesCharlie False accusations are dangerous. Look what's happening to our president. There needs to be… https://t.co/5x68n45HFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CCINDYT7 @Mediaite Trump and his supporters have set the bar pretty low for what is considered acceptable behavior,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LyAHandmade @C104Weaver @Country104 @HunterBros @jamesbarkerband @WesMackMusic @sonsofdaughters @HIGHVALLEY… https://t.co/GrquGeA5n2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet primitive people in ancient cultures thought skywriting was a message from god.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just realized i can’t get certain piercing if i still want to comfortably wear earbuds and now i’m ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[GALLERY: @MTHSAthletics1 vs. Manchester Township in South Jersey final  https://t.co/J6qquMKQjv  (Via Press of AC)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ryan and Cristina’s little love bug @ Kona Kai Resort Hotel &amp; Marina https://t.co/g1jIlKCj1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffreycwood @pakman888 @billyjoel @SCSU_hockey_pbp @deanthibodeau Captain Jack did make a couple of lists, but di… https://t.co/j4IJ2sORD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cory42413558 @VictorGOATipo @NFL @TheNickShook @Colts @Browns @ChicagoBears @Giants @JABergman Idk why you sent that to me. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[$45,000 por el capricho de cambiarle el color a los camiones de basura. Este Neto es un inepto.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KylePorterCBS Rors physical skill set is off the charts but he needs to rehab his wedge game.  DJ, tiger and JT al… https://t.co/k5IbRjrpRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zelenny Buenos días Zelenny, que tengas un excelente viernes 😀. Saludos!!]]></document></documents></author>