<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_ChristinaChang @TGDsquad @GoodDoctorABC @shorez @ABCNetwork @IamNickGonzalez Ok one more question because I hate… https://t.co/WWCRmu58WR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another useless think of DNA tunning for repuglican seat in Congress. Just what we need. NOT!]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ll always be Daddy’s little girl that stole my heart. Happy Birthday Angel, me and Daddy love you❤️ https://t.co/hiKhYzVhO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgressAlberta Obviously from the get go the name was meant to mock us, how people never saw that and don't see '… https://t.co/Jc87sFUFZ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 @TwistedTwittler @TeamTrump Obama May have kept us out of depression but his horrible policy the UnaFo… https://t.co/w3nvG1t9p7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalbertSwan @AlbertMotta_ Good grief, pointing to bad behavior to justify bad behavior is insane. Thank God (and I… https://t.co/TpXmbXppoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenRayMorris @motelsiren Comfy Puma Rihanna for 1/23 https://t.co/GyUz9ZBmRU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out of this world performance last night!!!  You are above sensational!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help find @ConnieBritton missing pup Santos last seen in Lincoln Height a part of Los Angeles. 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YouTube Why is it that when @PhillyD does a video that is critical of you... I don’t get a notification and it doe… https://t.co/uqboHOOfpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The people with the money don’t care if something is good but if it will sell. Sometimes that’s the same thing. Who… https://t.co/j2hrCrUGHX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibertarianBlue What does Google plan to do? Destroy CNN? NO, CNN has already done this to themselves. Expose the… https://t.co/nsApaiNXL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the anniversary of when @kariiinaa and I started exposing people on depop for selling Brandy Melville stickers you could get for free🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[“By detective agency hired by the school”. BIAS ALERT!!  Fixed it. And who cares, the agency isn’t a decision maker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpaceXFleet Hopefully Mr Steven will get new arms and the fleet will get shore time qith their families during downtime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acobasi @Nori_NYC @GCRebel21 @YouTube @NomikiKonst Apparently Bezos is not fully out of NYC....buying lots of prop… https://t.co/vjTnx9CIBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad to say none of my exes are happy or married 😭😭 im in. Whole new relationship happy af ☝🏽🌹]]></document><document><![CDATA[With nationwide opportunities and a growing book of #business, looking for your next career move is never far away.… https://t.co/f3GlwH3WQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The difference between "I can" and "I can't" is not an apostrophe and a "t", Its the motivation and effort to succeed. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[GRACE: These are moment that fulfill me... helping to nourish the largest organ of your body. The same rules that a… https://t.co/YAAxCNZFrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The robot stepford wife in @UmbrellaAcad is bat s$!% creepy tied for first only with the bizarre mannequin love affair with 5.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@onelovechild13 @Fred61276798 @TimRunsHisMouth and actually there is no "hate" in my tweets - just a heavy dose of… https://t.co/RFfrJfpzMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breefeighner Seriously! It’s becoming more appealing to me. I finally hit him with a pillow and said “Okay it’s my… https://t.co/9grb8GNTm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thatoneVAjumper Honestly dropping out of college was the best decision I ever made]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buddhist goddesses are very often what we today might call extra.  https://t.co/ShoU8RfWcZ https://t.co/eXpVLN9q62]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bom dia! Pra um dia de muito trabalho, lhe desejo gratidão, orações, fé e disposição! Pra as dificuldades lhe desej… https://t.co/L2kZqg6ZEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichelleZhuWACH Finally! It's the best time of the year! https://t.co/jwsLDnSZEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all stopped talking and were overrun with traitors, crooks, murderers, pedophiles and well, you get the point! N… https://t.co/yVX7QpGaEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Trump wanted to be out of country while hearing being held. He created perfect ba… https://t.co/zzETp8FHwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorNikolai @RealYungCripp How dare you ruin a disabled man’s day like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cherese_cobb Hey Girl!  The bot changed my password.  I don’t know if it changed  my email address too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreamcatcher5 @nc_turn @joncoopertweets These quotes are from the 1980s, the DNC is letting him run, and bashing D… https://t.co/Ja6xRkmwTJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s Day from the awesome Christina St branch where we all thrive because of gender equality… https://t.co/ZzkrrSiAeE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momjeansca Wanted to see yall in chapel hill but by the time I got money it was too late :////]]></document><document><![CDATA[So anyone just wake up from the sound of hail trying to break into your house to get you or was that just me? 🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[When did this iPhone 8 come out? Bc I’ve had it since then WITHOUT A CASE and it’s been perfectly happy and fine an… https://t.co/Vx6G762Z49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tbird765 They are usually Baked on there so you lucky at least they found clothes to wear!  Normally, they wear 5-6X they say]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrykerRocket @funder Oh good at least I wasn’t the only one, our current situation is exhausting, and his speech… https://t.co/7QEebGLrWq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great thought provoking questions!  I am excited to hear the answers shared on Saturday @AffinitoLit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fluffy sun angel. #leoandgrace #cat #nofilter @ Plymouth, Massachusetts https://t.co/aFnGOgA60U]]></document><document><![CDATA[for the majority of het men its not something they would do. which is fine. but its not gay lol being attracted to… https://t.co/dN4q0S88wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColeWoody88 Not at all unfortunately. I’m thinking the best bet is if Sam slips up with a random :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you love dinosaurs so much that you could just hug their leg bone. #stellasboys #wacotexas… https://t.co/yHs2hUdYV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Voter ID cards are the answer. I show mine along with my license each time I go to vote. Guess what? I don't mine at all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How about the picture the Phillies use for this promotion? https://t.co/5Mfxbhk4JE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just glad these bdays are over time to dedicate my weekends at home ☺️☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#francisbacon #threestudiesforacrucifixion #triptych #1963 #solomonrguggenheimmuseum #nyc #emotions #art… https://t.co/8axRNMYSqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES. And I need to go back to my comfort zone so I can plunge into telling America how Cohen lied about everything.… https://t.co/eSgpXeghoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vatican dismisses top US cardinal McCarrick over sexual abuse allegations  https://t.co/vGoRh424c6]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is doing to Hannah G  exactly what Cassie just did to him.  He’s not into her just like Cassie’s not into him!!… https://t.co/fHOF8PrPAy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dearkristiina GIRL I NEED TO GO BAD. But I’ll bring this chunker with us so you have a good reason 😉 https://t.co/CjMeIgC6Va]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, Kiana, (and Jason?) getting on FaceTime to practice our tagalog lessons https://t.co/wbmDnhLA8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's First-Gen Fest week, y'all! Don't miss all of the festivities this week! #firstgenutsa #ais1203howell… https://t.co/sHkDrjmWzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraK93322487 @NTCR @CatRescueTweets @austinpetsalive @StreetCatRescue]]></document><document><![CDATA[My former professors @Jordan_Ragusa and @GibbsKnotts write “the South Carolina primary will serve as a corrective m… https://t.co/lA2cEfOZX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my boys out there y’all are all gonna succeed in whatever area you choose. Keep grinding and don’t let anyone stop you. Goodnight 💤🌙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just reading about all the shoveling people are doing back home is making me so thirsty. #SpringTraining… https://t.co/ZTCWCLETTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not my first #robin of the year but I saw several today so I took a picture #flocking #robins #spring2019 @ Magnoli… https://t.co/wKLKgvI0ji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your personal style should reflect in the decor keeping it characteristic and appealing instead of being trendy  Ar… https://t.co/vuWJJRLAlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time you speak on ANY topic you show the world how uneducated you are !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fui de compras y vi vestidos súper bonitos ☹️☹️☹️ lastima que no puedo comprarlos jajajajaa por qué aquí el invierno dura casi todo el año]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Basic Leggings Guide For Women Over 40’s https://t.co/InOI1HchhR #Workout #Leggings #Wholesale #WorkoutLeggings https://t.co/5M98qyIN6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AboutElizabethM @AOC Me to my kids: someone else being great doesn’t subtract from you being great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Friends!!! Happy #Thursday !! Tonight, I am hosting a webinar for those who have no idea where, how, a… https://t.co/zx8REOoBDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“when the ‘weird’ person’s talking shit on you ‘ “ - Alexa(2019) https://t.co/ZDX5fSaH0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 episodes in on #TheWidow on @PrimeVideo 🤯🤯🤯there’s so many layers to this show and one is more surprising than th… https://t.co/ON5X5dLnvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3: of having 2 jobs. Last night I checked my schedule. PH manager scheduled me on the days I’m not available. S… https://t.co/1cZwn9uMXO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel has a rockin’ 90’s playlist. @nerdist compiled the songs here: https://t.co/T8tzeEO57s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Search me, O God, and know my heart: try me, and know my thoughts - Psalms 139:23]]></document><document><![CDATA[saturday’s are for morning workouts, cleaning my whole apt &amp; spending quality time with Lilo ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ @jasonrileywsj Was the media supposed to call him a liar right off the bat?  That would not be reporting.  How… https://t.co/OpaA6K9gZv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, the Zakim Bridge will be blue to kick of #ColonCancerAwareness month. We're grateful to the city of Boston… https://t.co/qRDoY1RrUq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonz970 @happydays72711 @ImabitcSumtimes @clovis1931 @sappermartin @John_R_Berna @OrenIShiKiddo @my3monkees… https://t.co/WVmdQkPzuy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gents, let it be known @lindseyannkri  is now a country fan.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the heart of Kondo-ing is letting go of what’s holding you in the past and making room for living and working wi… https://t.co/6jB0oKPkgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalmargaritaday @applebees @ Applebee's Grill + Bar https://t.co/0L21HfVDEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliVelshi Tulsi doesn’t have a snowballs chance in HELL of winning the nomination! What’s her end game! She disres… https://t.co/n8HnKPK0u8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gorgeous but hope you’re visiting someone or working and not staying there!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePDNation Heartbreaking.. RIP Sir, thank you for your service.  God Bless You 💙💙💙💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Warehouse Worker - Univ. of GA - Conc./Sanford Stadium" at Aramark? Apply even if… https://t.co/tyrCWb3Wfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que difícil es querer discutir en inglés, me escucho como Sofía Vergara pero lento porque proceso las palabras 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Phoenixville, Pennsylvania https://t.co/7hoDVpu5l7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slpwlkr1863 @KenDilanianNBC And to have the illegitimate president on your side to save his own skin! Trump would… https://t.co/P9G7iFVxwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que nadie me diga que me baje de los stilettos, menos aún por falta de 'sororidad'.  Si me lo tiene que decir algui… https://t.co/ND5k1TWu3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #nationalmeatballday with dwightmontoyagram #southphilly  #meatballs #nonna #grandmom @ Girard Estate, Philad… https://t.co/n685PDnZaw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattnathanson @mattnathanson so wanted to rock this poster my 13 year old make for me last night. Wasn’t feeling i… https://t.co/y06SfN5stc]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who sing on snap or insta but obviously don’t know the words annoy me so much &amp; I don’t even know why but it bothers me to no end]]></document><document><![CDATA[i wanna go back to my happiest place on earth @magnolia also i miss my long hair so much and i want it back https://t.co/UjnvozfPkU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated #InternationalWomensDay a bit early last night with these two brilliant ladies @AlyssaMastro44… https://t.co/7SULcvSKaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj If all you need to make money is money...You need to be taxed at a higher rate...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewPollackFL 3) thanks to Gov. Murphy, there is money set aside for Illegal kids to get free schooling while ci… https://t.co/0M2PixKbdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FyreFestival is exactly what monique was saying, you need to keep integrity as you secure the bag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vocês precisam ouvir os áudios das véia elitizada de #SJC desesperada com a galera pulando carnaval na Vila Ema (ba… https://t.co/kJoUcIFqQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto she knows this for a fact. Not. We are pretty sick of her lunacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC: THIS is the state of American #Conservatives: your movement is cheering on a xenophobic imbecile who threw… https://t.co/i3iv7mzIwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolBelmont I’m assuming mocking the opposing dance team not #TheBelmontWay #BeBetterThanThat #GoRacers https://t.co/D4B5Tg4iJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting a head start on Neos, #Woonsocket's newest #Greek restaurant, before their grand opening tomorrow! Read mor… https://t.co/2VXelzUwwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was honored to share the @RedCross Hurricane Harvey Disaster Public Affairs story with these young girls from Nat… https://t.co/h4HQTr8nlI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@d_ast777 @DavidHarris707 @RosaDeliadelos1 @ArleneKowalczyk @SeptemberJulie @PrayHard972 @carmelitequotes… https://t.co/OzAasSVBng]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Ebay Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below 👇  Clic… https://t.co/EwKQtOeHba]]></document></documents></author>