<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’ve got to move to a place where I don’t know a single soul. Is it May yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[⚡️Haunted by Memories ~ #TheUnholy⚡️ https://t.co/NS7wySG5tH #iartg #asmsg #bookboost #horror #suspense #thriller https://t.co/gXuoxrUAyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night off... game ON (@ The Shire in East Islip, NY) https://t.co/uW0JxxcRk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddds0 @kodykpelham11 Those are literally all Blood signs. Y’all ain’t got a damn sign. Y’all are an after school club. Not a gang.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make it a coffee mill Saturday. #bestcupofcoffeeintown #seeyouatthemill @ Coffee Mill https://t.co/Wvbwgetd4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MyBaby #Daughter getting #Braces Today.  🙏🏽⛓⛓⛓🤣🤣😁😁😁🤑🦷🦷🦷😷 #beforeshots ✌🏽🔴🎙🎥🌎💪🏽🛸 #dentist @ Southeast Houston, Hous… https://t.co/sWTZAGoHgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been keeping up with @brycevine since my freshman year in HS (6 years ago) and I’ve been able to watch this… https://t.co/gXpdf67smQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooh, I'm on a wave with Fremont Fred. I've never been with such a celebrity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can they bring back craigslist personals but only for breakfast dates. #m4eggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is worth every minute of your time. And it won’t take you more than five.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AHSMaplesAD It’s really sad that more people don’t know about Hoagie Man!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's #nationalwomensday and I like to draw women who can smash your face in.  #boudicca #wonderwoman #bigbarda… https://t.co/iIy5brUuEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[50 minutes from our apartment in #DTLA is another universe. Los Angeles is the greatest place to live on earth don’… https://t.co/XWUuoqIidq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Questionable Origins #3 by @cellarmakerbeer @ Highland Park Brewery Chinatown — https://t.co/H7GhcSfIdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 5 Central Michigan University Chippewas  Seniors also got recognized at the Cardinals Senior Day...Fire Up Chip… https://t.co/FHL6OjaDhI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you looking for shit you can never find it.. but when you not worried about it tho 🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al chile yo decía eso pero amor a uno mismo y el total rechazo a la heteronomatividad hoy me hacen decir que si vue… https://t.co/4QWMt6xaGT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby Maci Needs Your Help! Everyone Please Retweet. Baby girl needs a lifesaving marrow donor!… https://t.co/xJ1u1pMvRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Neal Brown consulted with some data companies before, and he's bringing analytics with him to #WVU.   "We've been a… https://t.co/OQI8fapS8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddyflako88 Nah, stay the way u are, other can learn to be less of a pussy lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me why Tommy Genesis is out here delivering bars, and people cant get off the Nicki vs. Cardi bandwagon just to hear her?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found The Rocks star and his hand and shoe prints... Also found Micheal Jacksons star and hand and shoe prints....… https://t.co/Im0rueihgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats want bill passed so they won't find themselves swinging from the nearest oak tree!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to need it to stop snowing because my winter jackets can’t zip over this bump anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've read six of them. I wouldn't have put one of them on this list, but what do I know?  https://t.co/XZcv8voTOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the @Angels keep on doing what they do, out of nowhere signing of @DanJennings30. Welcome to the team! #surprise]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadameNole I'm no #chile 😂 and I tell #thetruth https://t.co/KKl7boz1Kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy is the man who finds a true friend, and far happier is he who finds that true friend in his wife.  #memphis… https://t.co/z7MTF344ck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twice the meat! Spicing up life at the Hard Rock! Before seeing Alita. All the things! #hardrock #alitabattleangel… https://t.co/hIM9VTNy0r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamVTV @tina_MAGA2020 Sounds like a challenge. Prove the moron wrong TX @SpeakerPelosi]]></document><document><![CDATA[And y’all thought white cops killing black people was bad 🤦🏽‍♂️ delete me if you support your racist president]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s my mini kanye meltdown for the week thank you for tuning in to my little digi-rant]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @KelleyBouchard if we are putting only two people on the flag don’t you think one ought to be a woman? #mepolitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York City's @NYCMayor has done such a wonderful job improving transit and bike safety and police reform, he sho… https://t.co/qs5nqueHNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t know if I should be offended or appreciative someone recognize the realness in me. Either way I’m wearing Ad… https://t.co/Zr1MKNqgzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickkokonas hospitality flows both ways and a “celebrity cook” should know as such and not take to ig with a child… https://t.co/6qqpko0LXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to following Dr. Baxter’s journey. Thanks @ThePeakTV @asr_media @AshleySRusso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DamienW3 @chrisnau @AOC @jockowillink No, that's like saying a historian's words are as valid as someone who lived it. Not close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobaqueer Sis everyone isn’t built to hide their emotions until they can’t function anymore like virgos, Chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol y’all really act like staying up till 5 am on a Saturday is a character trait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WalterSobchak79 @SherryKumar4 @EduMontesin @kadelia @AOC Look out, folks, we have a regular Ben Shapiro here with the "facts."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeeban88 more than likely it will be there tuesday paired with a boys game, but they have to wait until tonight an… https://t.co/F5lROQHFnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made this last night and it’s so clean. I love it https://t.co/j7PVE2uoh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtonLHaynes Waahhh didnt know you are into #PoGo too! Happy! A fan here since Teen Wolf! :D Shiny swinub is a cu… https://t.co/cdKJawRm7S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TiboDMZ Definitely another thread -- it's true we're sorting much more than in the past.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeastPode The guff, regardless of the hour, get it off my timeline chief]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PtboMinorLax @yourtvptbo Thank you for the response. Now my next good question is why does it cost $95 more for a… https://t.co/jXwoJIVixd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d rather see a map that shows key frequent and/or express routes along with the subway, something like Vancouver… https://t.co/HBoJbyFVxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtBusiek I was disappointed when he started going on about 'family values'.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t smoked since New Year’s Eve but ima have to make an exception for that jungle boys!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to draw for 1 of 2 autographed jerseys courtesy of our host Kitchener Rangers for @GKWCC  Annual Rang… https://t.co/L7RoyZXc5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @RowShurn to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations—just the covers. 1 cover… https://t.co/jagXsUjhKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[INBOX: In a statement to KOCO, the OK2A foundation President reacted to Chief Citty’s press conference yesterday https://t.co/9goztlTTnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine you're Taggert possibly coaching for your job and your recruiting Hornibrook. Yikes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoganJames It’s not even just Astrology. Believing that Mercury can go in retrograde means you believe the Sun and… https://t.co/zB2cbj6dRi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJKDblog Nonsynthetic cannabinoid preparations, particularly smoked cannabis, can pose significant health risks an… https://t.co/RWq4Cwzncb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchgarber @postmedianet @TheTorontoSun @winnipegsun https://t.co/efbYsyLgpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrickDMcNult1 @BradThor @FoxNews If it's got Brit Hume or Bret Baier on it, you can bank on it. But Sean Hannity… https://t.co/opwWHr6imO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exiting @mbta station to call a @lyft because I didn’t think I needed to budget an entire fucking hour to get into… https://t.co/MqxOSfCNLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crisco_r Staying at MGM. We're driving out so we'll see how the weather is. We might leave Tuesday night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch that effing obama was consistently guilty on that account.  Pls continue investigating soros. He is our enemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Complex @Bucks It’s not fraud it’s false advertising  🤣🤣🤣 jk I love you Ja]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a night with these great friends as well as super talented celebrating @TCremisini ’s birthday. . #friends… https://t.co/SSFF6itYMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USC1620 a birthday drink Friday. #OneBeerFriday https://t.co/VqYu4BKu1V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Appointments available now for JKTV! Book your appointment today! 706-392-0532 @ Phenix City, Alabama https://t.co/2QV7bURdmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just landed in Miami (Florida USA) and the flight attendant, for the assist, goes “welcome to Miami” and - I kid yo… https://t.co/McbBwRBJsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Flickanelde @notquiteold I certainly agree Flikanelde, but my sweet puppy , Koda, loves kids and will suffer in si… https://t.co/uiXoa7L6e8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jttrw @amesimmons @DaveHogue @shoobe01 I’ll be in this hole until further notice. https://t.co/1vJ5TjsNDJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JcRuizMty @CongresoNL @DiputadosPANNL Aquí sigo esperando la invitación a la Carnita Asada se va hacer o no se va hacer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta say it over and over again  about centralized crypto projects: there is a very realWar going on, fullafuckery… https://t.co/OITcIcJ1xJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In response to several #DemocraticParty candidates in #Campaign2020 shifting more toward his progressive policy vie… https://t.co/ANM9ZKmQll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SutterD @cannaworldsite @EmeraldZoo @OneFallenAngelM @realmedicineMI @SmoknSara420 @johnnyrebel907 @Raymosaki… https://t.co/kuflUdC7bP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great night at #CirqueduSoleilVolta my family enjoyed the show!!! @Cirque]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sec1968 Plot Twist: Simmonds scores in OT To win the game &amp; is Traded Tomorrow to Tampa Bay. #PITvsPHI… https://t.co/KrpFPiOEOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trumper2020 @celeste_abeytia @MyronTsosieLD7 Ultimately, I do believe Sowell’s argument has some merit when viewin… https://t.co/MQR7tur9kt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viet_t_nguyen @drain_tim Yes, and against which colonizers? The 130 yrs of French rule? The 300+ years of Ottoman… https://t.co/X0DlIZYO5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[you have to be one of the finest woman i’ve ever seen for me to shoot my shot in the DMs lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nah fucc that if she can’t tell you yo breff stank or yo outfit ugly , hair an easy one lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachDubs_EBHS @EB_CoachLo @BigCountyPreps1 I will have to work on getting ours there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_sharonnpadilla Turn “one day” into “day one”. You’ll get it back in no time 💪🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took my Guy jak.e1 to eustisskatepark For his first trip out there🛹🙏🏽👽🖖🏽🛸 👀 it‼️ 📹 filmed 1/5/19 📹 Proceed to Get L… https://t.co/KUODbGFoOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normal dilated veins During and after exercise Hour indoor cycling class Half hour lap swim Fins paddles kickboard… https://t.co/HHn9IGCwhA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daigneault1212 My hooman sez ima jack shih zoo.  Am not a zoo.  Just a fuzzy little doggie.  But I hear lots of am… https://t.co/o1cjkjYgTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTideAustin @ChipotleTweets tell them to give us black cards where we can eat Chipotle as much as we want without damaging our finances!😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excellent move! Now our defense has a solid foundation and they're young.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks, Brooks ! I wasn't aware of that fact. I Determinedly avoided all news of The kenyan when he was in office.… https://t.co/1vYaDSPvyk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@love_jesus1st @realDonaldTrump You know the relevant congressional committees could have called for a special coun… https://t.co/Cqe2y7q4JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When one season of basketball comes to an end, another one starts! Going to miss WFW Lady Bearcats, but excited for… https://t.co/I6em3Um3Nv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things looking challenging at #borealridge #borealmountain @borealmtn #monsterdump #dumptown #dumpsville #snowscape… https://t.co/YuMiot13xv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sir, you will never be forgotten in Cincinnati! Pure magic and still chills. 💪⚽️🔥 @fccincinnati 🔶🔷]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este thread se lo tienen que leer todos los genios que aún defienden al chavismo en Venezuela.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone remember this one show with this black guy who was like a hall monitor/detective thing with a delinquen… https://t.co/U4PutOwUZr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unlike those other people, I believe you have potential to be great. Unfortunate that you wrestle on the ground, bu… https://t.co/WgidYzVJwK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out today’s @BtBScore issue. There’s some good stuff in it! 😉⚾️☕️ #MorningMoundVisit https://t.co/e1tT2NtbX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Logando_5 @EnebongEphraim @JUDDERMANG How many times has Atlanta beaten RBNY...? They got one win, by a few goals,… https://t.co/0Gtpt1xBUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh he’s thinking about it.  He just doesn’t want anyone else thinking about it right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, it's after we find out that Trump was with the Russians,  all his clones gang members are in jail or indicated.… https://t.co/MHLeTyM53e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wait, you just have to do an “other” workout and name it “dance”, and voila, Disco Stu is back. https://t.co/olv0FKueIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fairview_XC @jennifer_dahler Which meet was that from and I’ll send you the FinishLynx image]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t stand being around people who look for problems... ima just smoke my bowl over here then!!]]></document></documents></author>