<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Nick just said, “I can’t be there for the good days if I’m not there for the bad days,” yallllll when I tell you I… https://t.co/3ntMMUu4fa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Levendaki17 I’m the same Eureka. I have no trouble saying when I’m wrong. ✊🏻💕✊🏻💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RubinReport @jo_ooxo How does he know aliens don't have nipples? Maybe they have twenty nipples. Maybe he should add nipples.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep Huebert, who chairs House Ed, asks for a summary of differences between HB 2257 and 2233 to assist both committees. #ksleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My apartment smells like burned popcorn. And I didn’t burn the popcorn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i was gonna tweet cute shit about chris but he just called me a cheater   1 rt and i’ll bite his dicc off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quoting the great Paul Simon, but changing it a bit: "still useful after all these years". Thank you @benforta for… https://t.co/5uGQzTD74D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Facebook Backtracks After Removing Warren Ads https://t.co/iVznOIiX1v https://t.co/ARYFmnE2oY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Art of Heikala: Works and Thoughts is EVERYTHING! And absolutely essential to my art book collection! 💜 • • •… https://t.co/FBz4EPSKff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast of Champs! @ New York - New York Hotel &amp; Casino Las Vegas https://t.co/y4aFD2buog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starbucksgirl51 @MSNBC #BernieTheBossFromHell  #BernieIsARageAholic  #BernieBeratesHisStaff… https://t.co/LSH14MFnam]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 2 jobs, a busy Etsy, volunteering - and I still decided to try two new hobbies this week! I’ll sleep when I’… https://t.co/jzkBWfMgm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Naked Security: Mega-crackers back with nearly 100 million new stolen data records. https://t.co/nBIRJF2SV2  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[apparently it’s national margarita day and I just wanna know who is going to join me for one 😋😋😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belated Birthday Lunch at amumanu for my bestie J'macon Luvv... free Ginger Creme Brulee too!!! Summer sat with us… https://t.co/jjbuxBE69H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickjonas still makes my heart skip a beat. 😍 I can’t believe that the @jonasbrothers have came back into our live… https://t.co/061Bd6238F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TikiRose @GovHowardDean Although I think everyone should carry a first-aid kit in their car and know basic firs-ai… https://t.co/dqiEznaMkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I tell y’all that on Napoleon’s birthday someone asked me what I will do when he dies? https://t.co/bJhnmeHs2w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thieriot_news @SEALTeamCBS @SEALTeamWriters @CBS @SEALteamFansUK @SealTeamcbsfans @SEALTeamMIA @SEALteamFans 🙏🏿🙏🏿🙏🏿🙏🏿🙏🏿]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is gross #LEGALIZEIT  #fuckcancer  #MedicalMarijuana #medicalcannabis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can a human chimp who is deaf, hear the heart of stars and lead the way to freedom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAndyKimNJ @VVSaichek @HouseDemocrats This is how you get corruption out of elections.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @jonz970 @paulbhb @bigstellsr @Aug1405 @garway95 @tlewis417 @MauiPugs @geo_hazel @pjbowles4 @ERINN1331… https://t.co/7lbOjMZSfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the only Odell trade I will support. Baker... throwin dimes to Odell? Yes please!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite tweet of the day! #GOPCriminals #TrumpIsARussianAsset #MAGAts #Treason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris And the mendacious Mitch McConnell will not comply. Best to Trump he is the biggest cancer on our Country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[From Azmeena Bhimani's Mehndi Night!!! #AzmeenaKhan #GoingToTheChapel https://t.co/ak3Uwu9BMw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein What God do they serve? Certainly not the God of love my Bible speaks of. God is probably scratching… https://t.co/usp0Zkp1jS]]></document><document><![CDATA[THANK YOU FOR FOLLOWING ME @KanesDonuts!!! YOU ARE MY FAVORITE DONUTS IN BOSTON!!! Everyone knows I am OBSESSED with donuts!!! 💜💜💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PLTWSummit #PLTW #CSIM After a long day of PD and networking, we are having a great time at the PLTW CEO reception… https://t.co/ZSTlteZmzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[4am and I get to sit in the labor and delivery with my patient. Come on baby girl! 💓💓💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HailStateWBK @lashe5_ Interesting to watch the people in their seats when the eating contest is happening.  No one… https://t.co/73HxDnb2qG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Legally blonde last night was amazing!!- @ Georgia Southern University Performing Arts Center https://t.co/roZTd6tIsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@declaneo, I have just seen pictures! Congrats! I wish you a lifetime of love and happiness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorTomUdall No everyone must show ID!  Like finger print or retina scans!  Fake IDS  for illegal Aliens are gi… https://t.co/vLLsDZJTlC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Decided to create a Fantasy Baseball league. If you want to join, message me and I’ll invite you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanTAnd @GeorgeEliseo Someone needs to help this girl. She is brainwashed by society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Rainbows #weeds #borregosprings @ Rams Hill Community in Borrego Springs https://t.co/qyZOZ92EQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I get special glasses for staring at a screen all day. Price point for them is like $40-$60.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vibrating high with gypsyrosewellness at hairazer_robyn_scott ‘s organic wellness salon! Pisces ♓️ Power!!!!! 😍💜💜💜💜… https://t.co/hwNvVDip7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[The lone girl in the bay.... they’ve got a new Manager, Juan. Major improvements although one of his little asshole… https://t.co/QxyD7BquQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah in Russia and in other dictatorship countries that's all right. But not here in the U.S. you Southern dumb f**… https://t.co/t29yUWhe7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[M (@ 33 Bus Toward Inner Richmond in San Francisco, CA) https://t.co/BXm6O4VKts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drama filled game vs Portland last night leads to $25,000 fine for Head coach Steve Kerr. @957thegame]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nmfishbowlcom You won't see THAT at UNM or NMSU! And Ole Miss has had a very sad tradition of racism. Props to the… https://t.co/EM1dsZA7lk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Adam_K_Levin These SCAMMERS Seem 2 Pick On Elderly. I Get Calls@LEAST ONCE A MONTH. I REPORT THEM. IRS NEVER CALLS… https://t.co/iaZFHBXnHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed out for snow coverage, tag teaming with @MRossNews! Keep it with @News12BX for the lastest 📍 @GiannaGelosi a… https://t.co/1W2NpGSEj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CASSI3W @eBrambino99 I’m more in love w u than Emma is 😂😩😍 why’re u like this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Portraying a positive image,remaining well-groomed,and consistent with ur personality are the characteristics of a… https://t.co/Vt7cyi7vIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[The skill to not cough like I'm dying in a public place is something I don't have.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks Like The Shittler Is Storing Up Treason Turds In Those Sagging Undies To Shart Out Later For His Deplorable B… https://t.co/sXbUyOGkJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the U.S. Census send their employees to ask building tenants to let them in to ask questions, because that see… https://t.co/3CQEHHbdJ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just boarded the train to Penn Station, headed to the @UpYourMorning spring national college media convention in NY… https://t.co/2rHTxvLkn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got a new journal for bullet journaling because the Moleskein I have just didn't feel right. Working on my March sp… https://t.co/QoesHmUFw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@volmom2 @RobertKazinsky Robert took three tweets supporting true victims, not defending Jessie. I think the point… https://t.co/1OPEoyTU41]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I did not cry sexism ! If we don't like u ,we just don't. If we don't think u r smart enough, u proved it with… https://t.co/2X03yR6Gsw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTtoronto how can you celebrate Toronto's birthday without the @TorontoArgos? Don't get me wrong. I totally suppor… https://t.co/2gzDfMYzqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJCoastExp I know but was being amused. I wasn’t even in a cheese tray attempt mood in part cuz seat mate. Can try… https://t.co/T41BCIUhyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @MicheleAtTriad to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations or reviews, just t… https://t.co/2dECAbAN2r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artimus_of_war @NightCulture @diplo @Stereo_Live @ohsomoisty @JayAreBo https://t.co/3b3Op83rdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreamsUnderfoot @DineshDSouza @old_mum Nope!  He is screaming to the people to wake up and see the truth!  You sho… https://t.co/XnVjXtSDuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[100 BAD DAYS MAKE 100 GOOD STORIES. 100 GOOD STORIES MAKE ME INTERESTING AT PARTIES.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Edgar A. Smith Family @YMCAHouston in Houston, TX https://t.co/Goo7hWC9r2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BandB_CBS However, I do know it has something to do with "Fat Tuesday" 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm only getting a half screen n a pix of my boots but I'm having fun!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If @ChuckECheeses did an after hours thing where it was like a club/rave thing after hours...I’d get a fake to go there every night.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do people think they look cool wearing sunglasses outside even though it’s super cloudy? Like it’s not cool sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UToledo Nice photo but didn’t UT police recommend not posting pictures until you get back home https://t.co/zplPH9L1tc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wore open toed heels for the sale of my outfit &amp; now I’m about to catch frostbite 😖🥶]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing 80s Quizzo and this is my team name @midgeure1   #80s #80smovies #80strivia https://t.co/i0WSWpTWsf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathglasgow I preorered on @audible_com  so that you can help me fold laundry. 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout-out to the cashier at Mel's diner for having a full on Rocket Man sing-along with me as I bought four boxes o… https://t.co/gmG7Lt3DfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Their goal was to remove those things and keep them out and by the grace of god they did. He looks and sounds so mu… https://t.co/c4ixVeZPam]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CeleryCaraway @VelshiRuhle #VelshiRuhle It’s not just #Thug45 it’s the entire GOP! After they gained congressional… https://t.co/vTIXz3G1eB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Eric_Clarkson @PerryNBCBoston @Notre_Josh @NBC10Boston And nuns are being accused too!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight!! Classical coffee tonight!! Come enjoy great music by great musicians! https://t.co/LFEkTr80ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is true. It’s a brief moment that’s easily missed, but a piece of #spacejunk started the zombie contagion (and… https://t.co/tEFR2f69lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickFoles @lululemonmen While you’re at it can you be the @Redskins new quarterback? Please🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[The article says "illegally obtained" the word we're looking for is stolen-- over 42,000 cultural heritage items fr… https://t.co/JF3zAgvThW]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 2 years of this administration, I’ve decided that being law abiding is just silly. I’m thinking of turning over a new leaf 🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kids World Dance Is back at the studio starting today at 4:30 PM! March will be dedicated to learning dances from t… https://t.co/6YcTU3r1mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guapofalbq @MalcolmNance I can completely understand that I'm on the same time lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the half, it’s @trinity_titans 34 and @HermannBearcats 11 - keep it up Titans! #TitanPride #TCHS https://t.co/kJa2dCUQVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FNSRockyHorror tonight was amazing. What a fucking cast! You bring your A game to this park.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VeraMBergen @GitmoWatch @carolrosenberg @nytimes @oldmanluvsmineo uh oh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[do I fully swipe in to the terrace room to sit and drink Coke Zero frequently : yes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows They haven’t done their job in almost 3 years but the Americans people is loving it they see hate and that’s it!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to ADORE this man 👇 Now I hope he stays in there and rots! I have 2 daughters and could not even imagine wha… https://t.co/ABfrF5g4rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[All that to say, be easy on people that tremendous L's. Don't just disregard the fact they took a L, but definitely… https://t.co/Dtc25fHfoI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValentinoAndy77 @Anton47492193 @ssyamanov @stevedespain @SteveDunfee @_maddiemueller_ @BamilMusic @social_stars… https://t.co/lMtIdrrlSm]]></document><document><![CDATA[he did not do it, he did noooottt.....  oh hi mark https://t.co/tsxgCicGM1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Govjerrybrown @KamalaHarris @SpeakerPelosi ??  Maybe a #Gofundme maybe use some of #ChristineBlaseyFord $$??]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEDIA MALPRACTICE: New York Times Says Border at ‘Breaking Point’ Weeks After Claiming ‘No Emergency’ | Sean Hannity https://t.co/u9MvwuGOdY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HallmarkHubby Everyone has preferences. I know kids who don’t like ice cream. Adults who can’t stand the smell or… https://t.co/3LDKomLISQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianmckown1 @MattLoveless @JessicaDobsonWX Ahhh! I think I was trying to recreate what the wind sounds like overnight lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okWessler5 @TodKAGWarrior @USASTAYFREE @scarletteskyMT @Deplorable_Man @JoeRile11516053 @KellsBellsSC @fortressfin… https://t.co/2Ep1M8WvW0]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s dogs allowed in this bar and I  content. A good ol golden boy. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[FF Haiku:  Dirty snow in piles A scattered snow and rain mix Gray skies all around  #HumpdayHaiku #GreyOrGray?… https://t.co/iWzpnnIqMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important read (the whole thread) Seth is the best explainer of things:)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate a handful of peanut M&amp;Ms while walking into the rec. Compromise.]]></document></documents></author>