<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The most grammatically-infuriating holiday of the year https://t.co/oESQQ8sVah]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colts need to take a look at @Ziggy_Ansah for sure.  Colts have the most money, pay him and @TheHumble_21.  PLEASE!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really don’t understand how the Canadian media isn’t making more of a big deal how the Conservative parties in th… https://t.co/SPMSXv2KDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidN1027 @cymruisrael @EylonALevy Maybe part of the problem is how well the Gaza withdrawal worked out? Maybe?]]></document><document><![CDATA[im tight I ordered uber eats and fell asleep before it even got to my crib]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilandmc @YardHouse First time on the whole trip. She is looking at cowboy boots. She told me to come upstairs as it could be an hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know they don’t give a fuck about me , I promise I’ll be happy alone 🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great time performing #jazz harriganscafewinedeck in #Johnstown yesterday with #JazzTrip.  Today my #guitar… https://t.co/jVLxI7O1hs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Joe I am so sorry for your loss, I recently lost my mother as well I talk to her every day I miss her extra… https://t.co/gbKKcu2wwB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tanyaeiserer Spoke with the IRS. They are very interested in your story.  Nice job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyRhodes What white one looks like Pharoh. That needs to be a printed T.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Games will be played on two consecutive weekends at the conclusion of the season at regional sites with multiple ga… https://t.co/8biGS2N6xn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Motorcycle was sold today.  Kind of sad but glad that's one less thing in my life I do that can get me killed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Innovation in Higher Ed is happening in Vocational Schools. Traditional Universities and Colleges have deep cultura… https://t.co/TjWStvw0xw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very glad the baseball players are going to places not Seattle. I want a rebuild so bad. Stay dedicated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UM1124 @umphreysmcgee When in doubt, I’m assuming it’s Wappy Sprayberry but I’ll spell it differently each rime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GM gadsdencountyfootball2019 I need all y'all to show tomorrow and bring a friend. @AntonioBrown @twse5… https://t.co/Eslwq8KM9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday Who's going to pay for the wall?  If you have to ask, it's probably you. Unless you are Mexico.  #NotesFromNationalEmergency]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uh...so is this the point where sad dad is living in a van by the river...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@michball⁩ with Heart of Destiny at Hurstland Farm ⁦@KYHorseCountry⁩ #kentucky https://t.co/PIKlpIKEh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine being a playoff contending team giving Isaiah Thomas meaningful mins. And letting him shoot 10+ times a game. #Nuggets #nba]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissarogers @jackmjenkins This is so awesome. "It’s a class on C.S. Lewis. We just finished The Screwtape Letter… https://t.co/2hwXtmmXyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters What she says is so stupifyingly dumb.  I need to go listen to some Mozart now, to repair my IQ.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN on your description of you you left off incestuous deceiver of immigration.  You are an anti-Semite POS an… https://t.co/ODMaQvRXv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SF_ArleneLester @prsageorgia Ha! Great to have met you and so glad you enjoyed the session, Arlene!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m in the hospital and need blood, I wouldn’t care if it came from a man, woman or non-binary individual. This… https://t.co/W8gP8BpCXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if anyone would notice if I walked out the door with this painting.  Good stuff 👍🏻 #shawscrabhouse @ Shaw'… https://t.co/cakiJtGGf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSUCoachMeyer @TheTerry_25 need more Hoosier Buckeyes coach.  Always the most coachable kids here. #gobucks #hoosierbuckeyes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@primestew As a Lakers fan it’s all karma for trading Lou Williams and Zubac]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m alive... one in a million chance! #thankgod #blessed @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/SGAbBqOccz]]></document><document><![CDATA[So — former Georgia gubernatorial candidate and potential Presidential contender @staceyabrams is not only inspired… https://t.co/6uoPEBMVPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PEforlife @SHAPE_America @Jamie_Seiler @5210DSM Always hashtag your #Vegetables!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertoSmithP Estoy totalmente de acuerdo. Estos animales no salen de allí sino a punta de balas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump  @SecNielsen   #ReleaseAllTheVisas   @POTUS  Please support a legal work force in sea… https://t.co/B41gaW3Py7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 Meet with your nearest City councilman  Whichever party he is,he will always be ready to take credit… https://t.co/mDATnHnC06]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/zNfOuNgJdt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FfurryStud @HungerFF Would like to see you guys making passionate love!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinnbass @DrAseemMalhotra Not a surprise. Along with @DrGundry, distorting, ignoring and revising science is the… https://t.co/F2FzGzjBwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mastering attrition momentum, timing fracturing praise are key elements of sports success. You got it !  @CSUNBaseball]]></document><document><![CDATA[This shit is soo funny! 😂😂 Barkley fried on Jussie Smollett and Liam Neeson https://t.co/DOIAkN2lYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grossman4NJ Why should they? If you want to model your life after life of the Prophet, you would think the same wa… https://t.co/5Ma8QCGpI8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #InternationalWomensDay19 and thankful for all the great #strongwomen #Mentors I have had - 280 charact… https://t.co/pYlRKAQdrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachIsHere That would be beautiful. But I also think that a bowl of Rieger Pork Soup would make for a masterpiece. @TheRieger @howardamosa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABELS0N @seacoastonline @ENLNews Where won't I be?   Planning on The Rinks for boys hockey alongside @DoubleDSMG,… https://t.co/U45PRqrZTU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ali Kumbaya I Must Be The Greatest Man 🥊🏅🛫💫 • https://t.co/Nrv2TzEvTZ 💻 • #Significant #xxl #JordonEdward… https://t.co/5icCvtG7D4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Classic moment on my fave show! Wonder if Greg’s in trouble?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZekeDaHefe The saying "it takes a village" really rings true in that story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019: This the year I started doing me, for me; to become a better ME. And Honestly? It’s just me living my best li… https://t.co/lCEpcEaZa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[After 13 years of dating and 8 years of marriage. She's still my valentine, best friend, muse, and amazing partner… https://t.co/0GngGHce1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR Absolutely not! Young Hollywood has ruined the Oscars. @TheAcademy adding new and younger people to vote was d… https://t.co/pOOrJ0GebT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ne0liberal Didn't the Mercers pulling support tank Milo? Tucker is probably even more sensitive to loss of advertisers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look 👀 for a Venezuelan flag pin 🇻🇪 on @GustavoDudamel’s lapel this evening on the #Oscars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved seeing Coach Keady so fired up yesterday. Big win for the Boilers. 🚂 https://t.co/3N4uL4xoSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[ﺍﻟﻤﺰﺍﻣﻴﺮ 39:12-13  Arabic Bible:      12 اسْمَعْ صَلاتِي يا اللهُ، وَإلَى صُراخِي أَصْغِ. لا تَتَجاهَلْ دُمُوعِي.… https://t.co/PjqJ6mtRYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dairy Product Consumption &amp; Metabolic Diseases in the Di@bet.es Study https://t.co/V3kvc0seaR  @Nutrients_MDPI… https://t.co/9jqdNVBKbB]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you possibly blame Machado for taking 30 mil per year to live in San Diego!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love me some funniness. Insanely cool wedding invites/engagement photographic announcements based on famous movie p… https://t.co/rS9TJ7NrSx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redwings5ever @askrohan @helmerroids @GrindLinePod LMFAO https://t.co/722Ph87fr5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booth 1! Come visit us at @26shirts and @chargebflo! #SoupFest19 (@ Buffalo Soup-Fest in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/qN08PLbP3V]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Surprise is the greatest gift which life can grant us.” —- Boris Pasternak]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the mainstream media expressing regret/apologizing for initially perpetuating devise hysteria ov… https://t.co/Eh9cwP59Du]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rise of tech-worker activism https://t.co/ZyLy3cJcIK #security #hacktivism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayStation hey #sony you guys should bring back #PlayStationHome I think would be a great time to  #gamer #gaming… https://t.co/OP7grCaCOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A challenge I face is that students are willing to lie about what they said in a room full of 7 adults and gets awa… https://t.co/KrHZia1wau]]></document><document><![CDATA[Powerful and uplifting words on inclusion and diversity from @SimuLiu last night in SF: "It's never been a better t… https://t.co/8KzbLF9HCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a bad thing that the Coyotes killed so much clock on that delayed penalty. They'll get almost a full PP to star… https://t.co/9kjCNNDIs1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamasaurusof2 @FLOTUS @WhiteHouse @POTUS @Kaepernick7 https://t.co/jFajnMWcmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlatinumPerry and I having some fun sparring #axekick #capoeira #sparring #ufc #mma https://t.co/jAIorQiDTq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I owe my foundation to clinical trials research design to this avail workshop course #radonc @ARRO_org @S_W_R_O… https://t.co/ns140xJOhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got me all tongue tied and mesmerized.💛😌 #mondaze https://t.co/3znWICmD7q]]></document><document><![CDATA[The motion to subpoena @pweiser to get his legal opinion on popular vote bill fails. #coleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lungar13 @alexgleitman @BrianDohn247 @RivalsFriedman A local Basking Ridge family would Love to see you in Clemson w Dabo. 💯👍🙏🏈]]></document><document><![CDATA[heading to the lab to 3-D print some slices of cheese to throw at people]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers Looking to Bust Loose vs Eden Prairie today. @thelakepl @PLLakers #TheLakerWay https://t.co/MIJMdvp0ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a firm believer that everyone who is addicted to vape runs on Red Bull and cries diesel]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s so much physical strength in Bianca Andreescu’s game. The base is so solid and allows her to do whatever sh… https://t.co/sFdzZYKgOl]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥⚡️⭐️🌟💥I Present The Photo Of The Day!!!💥🌟⭐️⚡️🔥 . . Photo by @mygolfinggirls  . Greenery scaling the front of a tre… https://t.co/4gjQcXDwNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is completely untrue because pregnancy and hormones change the size of your boobs regularly....]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NEAMedia Fight for the public schools students deserve!  @PGCEA_PR Art Build for Public Education in preparation… https://t.co/NonG6Bz2JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJKustoms Should've just used the current Escalade or just the new Tahoe RST]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving through #vermont and stopped by to see my old school. Great memories at @worldlearning #SIT. #tesol… https://t.co/98eEAysO6T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Let him check the bus schedule, the one headed to prison. Perhaps he will step in front of it. Wishful thinking.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concerning for the Johnnies that they are lacking any ball movement on offense.  Very stagnant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like big buns and I cannot lie, especially these buns that are made in-house daily along with the ketchup, mayo,… https://t.co/nOOOxDMUWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @USMC Its NOT about 'hearts and minds' Any more...hasnt been since ww2  Lend lease was just exchanging de… https://t.co/SAWJezyrRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDanielStern thank you for being a member of the https://t.co/wG5YzZI00F am I.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smoker 1995 40” X 30” oil on canvas   Michael Hafftka is an American figurative expressionist painter living in NYC… https://t.co/aiGj5kIRth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleClark Considering whoever you're subtweeting already has me blocked, I'm sure they're full of incredible insig… https://t.co/jtYQhZLu1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Off to Brazil in a bit ✈️ (@ John F. Kennedy International Airport in Queens, NY) https://t.co/FA9CAeH3wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking news:  Apple has discovered the secret to anti-gravity and is building a new transportation system.  That… https://t.co/XU6vVM5tFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last film session/shootaround with my six seniors. I really appreciate their sacrifices and dedication they display… https://t.co/Cc44bZiv7F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m behind and just saw Seth coming out for Roman . My heart 😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😭😩 #Raw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to Barclays Center staff for the love to platinum selling artist Fulanito and myself DJ Leche as the cele… https://t.co/mohqtQqdxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a drug addict, got it all wrong. I’m just a love addict, til my hearts gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a 3 hour nap yesterday, fell asleep again an hour later for 12 hours, and then took an hour nap after I woke… https://t.co/JbnHyxLj19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Andover pulled their goalie there for a little bit after the power-play goal. Tried to take advantage of another Fa… https://t.co/ZfdyTaZxL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is my neighbor gonna Facebook message me asking if I’m home at 1:51am and then not answer me]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ff check it out @Gaudomatic @ConvoComedy @madflavor @somethingplanet @stevebyrnelive @Funkghost @GentlemansDojo… https://t.co/jzNCIj3aeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[This woman is both Bold and Brave. She’s taken life changing adventures, she’s rescued dogs from horrible condition… https://t.co/eYpMAewclp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've done  a ton of zero budget B-movies and that's exactly how we dress up a PA to play a bodyguard in the backgro… https://t.co/QXDyH9QtnL]]></document></documents></author>