<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@zerowondering Ugh just back off please. Now everyone is gonna play random online. You only main random because you… https://t.co/UwSQtrGPFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Education in North Carolina is such an aggressive dumpster fire.  How about investing more in our teachers and stud… https://t.co/G5cvpT2rLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adivinen a quien nos encontramos en la #calle8 drbrooklyn yo? eldante507 #elcomandante en Calle Ocho https://t.co/uKvSVswODr]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s something about good blues music and the harp playing that makes my dick tingle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave for my trip tomorrow for OBS sales! Looks like I’ll finally be dressed appropriately and can break out my Ita… https://t.co/W85EhnCt7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember waiting for the subway in LA after the Arctic Monkeys show and there was this dude playing (and singing)… https://t.co/iOFwcuSROC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCrocker @hookupsonly100 @hot_connection Next time you’re in nyc it’s my treat 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@duckman_31 @AndrewDBailey I feel like I scrolled through way too many replies to get to Dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t watch the @E60 story on Enes Kanter from this morning, then you missed out.   Wow. This is incredible… https://t.co/iHberPbLaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@buying_girls Wyoming has the second lowest population per square mile, first being Alaska  so no one pretty much]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is definitely the best Rock Version of The Star Spangled Banner, hands down. Jimi stayed with the purity of the… https://t.co/AqamuFZp4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilplntlady I’m so so in, unless there’s unforeseen circumstances. It’s only a 4 hour drive from me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satan knows your name but calls you by your sin.  God knows your sin but calls you by name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rep John Rogers at Podium talking about creating a Lottery to Fund Infrastructure improvements. He is also talking… https://t.co/0jHvpogeQZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consider this your invitation to join a growing movement in NWMO. We are hosting the Family and Children’s Center t… https://t.co/t3rekRGqLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phaily_ @VioTCZ @GFuelEnergy Fruit Punch and Green Apple best flavors #Gfuel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 @YahooNews #Must be why he walked away early . Just like those before him . Kim is a Dictator]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinisreal @jfc_3_ @jlowin @Jfc_2_ C'mon Justin. https://t.co/lNhbJXftF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThisWeatherIn4Words California doesn’t like snow https://t.co/Jsq41MRJb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Let them bark .!!! 16 out of 51 only 1/3 of the state . The same amount of falling angel that Sata… https://t.co/YDTZBCk9TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: How Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Won the Cohen Hearing: Too many representatives chose to bloviate ins… https://t.co/t8XHHN3Vbr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forever squinting in my photos  #squint #couple #bestfriend #wife #roadtrippin #sanfrancisco #fishermanswharf… https://t.co/tIm1Viv03H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VHSiTeam kids training a group of teachers on using @BloxelsBuilder at today’s #SchoolofRock mini con in… https://t.co/7tm0GnLGON]]></document><document><![CDATA[because they’ve been duped by the liberal media is where I differ with him. That statement is an insult to Black pe… https://t.co/ZVJ3ppbi7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only went back to college so I could use the meal plan to buy frosted lemonades from @ChickfilA on campus]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an incredible night with the gents from #thechershow at #broadwaysessions . #talent beyond belief. Thank you… https://t.co/rsggAUM1ea]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some hilarity. minions with sayings | Despicable Me 2 Minions Funny Sayings #laughter #giggle #grin… https://t.co/rMpwedY2ZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re ba-ack. New #trumpincpodcast focuses on Trump friend Tom Barrack, who chaired the Inauguration and hoped to c… https://t.co/CbN2FOdN12]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodyRoarkNFL That’s not what you said and it’s irrelevant how you consider the game. It is officially Super Bowl 4… https://t.co/KDfXHyOq0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only republican my parents ever voted for (because his opponent, Silber, was crazy)]]></document><document><![CDATA[So day 1 of 14 days of being on vacation has been complete. Still dont know what to do with my self for the next 13😂🤦🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a playlist for you… One Fine Day by Nathan Jones https://t.co/Oxv0PUaIMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Syd_Love_ @SetItOff @DannySIO on god I saw the tweet and not your handle and got pissed like “wtf this girl disrespecting syd”]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @manscaped giveaway arrived the other day!  So surreal that I won their giveaway and own their products! Their #… https://t.co/iRGy3s0c1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm worried about my good-good buddy @alexdgreenfield getting himself body-slammed one of these days...and by one of his own wrasslers!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_teagaaan I know your probably not going write back or anything but I really hope you have a truly lovely and amaz… https://t.co/S2KrdIVsiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annvandersteel @BreitbartNews Jussie Smollett was probably paid more per episode of @EmpireFOX than many people ma… https://t.co/Sauo079xCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManuelSkyexxx @MusculoDuroBlog @gayporncrushes @new_gaywanking @OliGaySexPornX @QueerMeNow @MarkkoXXX… https://t.co/vdLMpL7O64]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnwrittenRul3s Going left! Stan Van Grundy said on broadcast he can’t really go left yet.. he did this for the game with 7 on the clock]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not going to lie, I saw "women's strawweight" and expected a decision. That was awesome. #UFCPhoenix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok, that's all I got--as far as what I've heard this year that I like/love. #musicjunkie #bestmusic #albumoftheyear… https://t.co/dCh1NMPtg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s a crazy theory:   Let Kyrie walk.  They’re better without him   #celtics]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care what @drnadolsky says, #3 totally should be #1 IMO 🤷🏾‍♂️...  #nutrition #supplements #magicpill… https://t.co/WgevotEQXo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The food was amazing, the drinks were incredible, and the people I got to share it with - even better.  Can't wait… https://t.co/SqJs5FVFYg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@libertarianinja @clever_n_witty @Mojo50Radio @stuntbrain @TheCartelMatt @RealRonPhillips @RantsOfIzzo No]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWyden @MarilynRMarks1 What do you expect when the republican sec of state retains control of his own election /… https://t.co/3gSIStianb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else out here getting they shit ROCKED by life rn or is it just me 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging backstage with my Mr Olympia friends and idol Lee Haney. Always good catching up with these guys. We’re get… https://t.co/Ou05P2QM1q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ethics watchdogs sound alarm over Trump tweet on Scotland golf course #Topbuzz https://t.co/dQLNFS3KyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to eat in between working this event! Starving! 😋😋😂 https://t.co/kNnbHniuZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best part about the zoo is the Leopard’s companion golden retriever :0p @ San Diego, California https://t.co/5t9S3RoEmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RBReich I hear there’s a Presidents’ Day sale. Let’s sell Trump back to the Russians.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BJ_DeGroot @Brian_Butch my first ever red bobber https://t.co/o4LpzPEAeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Observer2541 @ITDave2 @Atheist_Dragon @deelane @YeshuaLover1970 @DB_Grimwalker @kneadinghands @Elinor27652146… https://t.co/TDp33aHBU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HartnettHockey This is an excellent match.  Glad to see my MUN guys are competitive with the club that Inthink is… https://t.co/we75lARojy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer She's the left's version of Donald  Trump. Unlike others who just criticize him, I think she's studie… https://t.co/U6Eoy3TK3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EclipZe31 @credibIes @Oath_011 @TriggzB2 @ItsSxndy @ImGlorify https://t.co/IAQ0oFR6hq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @realDonaldTrump @nbcsnl He. Doesn’t. Understand. Freedom. Of. Speech.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No MORE APOLOGIES to racists like Mark Meadows @MarkMeadows time to call them out on their racists tropes and actio… https://t.co/C0jJWW48Wz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddHerzman I figured out how to end my novel!  It will probably end around  120k words.  #amwriting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Real24_ You all the way healed up? Much love. Pulling for you like it aint no tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shell-on lao gan ma spicy chili crisp shrimp over roasted cauliflower and sugar snap… https://t.co/xUCjValywk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FerMoralesdice ¡Feliz cumpleaños, querido amigo y que sigan los éxitos! 🎉🎂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarstoolChief We need a instagram live inbetween periods to wake the boaz up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnelaTannante @tvanouvelles Coudons, c tu la première année qu’il neige au Québec  ?  Les commerçants devraient d… https://t.co/MvsYEw4xQ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremySickel I agree 100%! Too bad Vermeil didn’t get a chance to coach him earlier in his career or he would have made the Hall of Fame!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the Stars of the Industry at the Governor’s Conference on Tourism. #migovconf19 #pmgct19 #puremichigan… https://t.co/KxS41tpM4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would frfr love a documentary or biopic on this mans life. He went from a poor child, to coming to America and wi… https://t.co/94Pnyjuorl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always awesome seeing @_kimms_ at the Ballpark! Have an amazing time in Japan! #Athletics #RootedInOakland… https://t.co/YtIcnY9wBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I’ve been catching up on Atlanta while on the treadmill in the morning before work. Watching this ep at 6am Tues… https://t.co/oaZj0g4h9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Except for the liberal clowns, who in my estimation haven't got an ounce of common… https://t.co/dEMXm6vUn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib That bill won't get pass Our President Trump. The bill is that tge House of Representatives aporoved… https://t.co/NAA0CQqIsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[The most illustrative proof demonstrating how great Tiger Woods was. He STILL (after 5 lost years due to injury/sca… https://t.co/U1eg9BaCzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I see every time I’m around @coachforce @blaze_teach_42 @coachtklein @Klynn_Force @lynseyengle thank y… https://t.co/Rt4TfBapqQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[A beautiful sign 💜#SpringIsComing in Syracuse. #TheColorPurple https://t.co/IlJmtZ5zbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShoodTheDude Hahah it does have that feel it now that I read it with that lens lol #NelsForOffice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Lord for another 24. If your not getting better daily your are getting worse. #AttackTheDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Después de éste resultado, se paseará por la zona mixta el jeque de lentes oscuros que describía  @martinainstein ?… https://t.co/idhTRoHtkx]]></document><document><![CDATA[&amp; in the end Arkansas... Did. The. Right. Thing‼️ I love @SenatorFlowers- SHE “stood” HER ground‼️ I’m a… https://t.co/eXALO2MiiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamie2181 The salutation should be to put pants on before going outside...but call me crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muhhfuckers watch one episode of criminal minds and all of sudden “narcissist” is in their everyday vocabulary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually start off with strong words like collide, rattle, or Love. Too bad, we are loyal 2 only one option.  https://t.co/CEPQGttM7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[As an 18 YO, you see LeBron being an (almost) billionaire, putting his boys on, and living life like you couldn’t b… https://t.co/01HVaMuCrX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My manager basically told me yesterday that I got like the best shoe game at the job and she been noticing the type… https://t.co/Pf40AjOFL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aidan meeting Conor... #HappyOut #CRC @ Valley Hospital https://t.co/y0VouuCR5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadicalSeraph @ShawnMilne What I mean is that world peace won't be won with guns, but with the blood of the Savior… https://t.co/xEkX10ohBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know one thing if me and my 6”0 and up friends pull up to the club and they don’t let me in they better be right behind me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattWalkup @CardConnector The newest 330 million dollar man and @Phillies player, Number 3, right fielder, Bryce Harper]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just gonna keep working out and stack my paper , some people aren’t worth my attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short answer. No. 🙄 @JussieSmollett you disgust all of us. Not by your lifestyle but your judgement! This is ridicu… https://t.co/0KazSyq6dE]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Read about our latest job opening here: Registered Nurse- ICU- Night shift - https://t.co/J7ngUZyYoY #hospitaljobs #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really do adore finishing my runs in downtown @KCMO, There's something about staring off at the skyline after a h… https://t.co/eMxHHgm0x8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we get the video wider so I can see my guy @CoachE32 reaction?  Well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyuKaiser29 @clairlemon Don’t feel bad. I started life as a Republican, then the religious right absconded with th… https://t.co/RsYNaWP5bQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Always And Forever by Luther Vandross, from #SoundHound with LiveLyr… https://t.co/7S16KfvNgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my Friday evening at the softball tournament in Iowa Park. The baseball/softball facilities are on point for… https://t.co/Sq8NWi4fEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrMatthewLC Democrats think people cause global warming. So the less people the better in their minds. Also, As Fe… https://t.co/KpBr5btJWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun night in Chapmanville, hated to see our sectional team fall but a great game between the Lady Tigers and Sisson… https://t.co/FeKbpTs3A3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirLarr @NSSteph Is the best way to watch to subscribe to the know on YouTube? It’ll be posted there not funhaus ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My unpopular opinion: Most technical debt isn’t due to “rushing delivery” but is because the problems/users evolved… https://t.co/Z06sAgtCSW]]></document></documents></author>