<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’ve been working 7 days straight w 8 hour shifts and my manager doesn’t wanna give me a break FUCK I WANNA QUIT SO FKN BAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to move into my house I keep driving by to see what they have done so far lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCOntarioToday @TorontoStar In 2018, there were over 90K new DXs of cancer in Ontario.  8 weeks of (not always cu… https://t.co/e5swoOT25h]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Facebook page is filled with this Momo character.  What is wrong with people!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LukeBaines I think hes got u beat their @Kat_McNamara ..... #SaveShadowhunters #ShadowhuntersLegacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How old are you? You are such an embarrassment to our country!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but this story is wild I really can’t wrap my head around it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree, we cannot wait to take measures after Trump leave office. He must be taken out of office now]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is nothing worse than the few days after you get in a little spit with your best friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God I have family present bc I’d be losing my mind right about now ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS IN THE WHOLE UNIVERSE @graymustfall!!!! https://t.co/9yPkPfr4FA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#monday #tgit Make it a GREAT day - it’s your choice!! https://t.co/eQcSIxDxpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian This reminds me of the time @KimKardashian used her daughter as an excuse when she was too chicken… https://t.co/lOVg7VjfHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Growth requires change, changes challenge the status quo, leaving our comfort zone causes fear of the uncertain ...… https://t.co/IQjWtGIgt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPORTANT SCHOOL BOARD MEETING TO ATTEND ON MARCH 5th at 11:15AM at 600 SE 3rd Ave, Ft Laud  School Board members w… https://t.co/Dd8UOtquMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TucsonVoice28 I didn't say there was anything wrong about condemning all forms of racism. I know the GOP has antis… https://t.co/2K7qt1Ky7M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hannah_rfh @NickSacco55 I wonder if there is a way to incorporate that whole process into tourist time constraints… https://t.co/omMYDHn9bs]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a night of going ham I took care of someone and got myself home. #Master #getlikeme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacobAWohl @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett He'll be stopped all right when he gets to prison where he belongs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real people. Real results! My next challenge starts Monday! It’s not too late to sign up! 🌱🙃 #HealthyLiving #arbonne https://t.co/0szTSyiNnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanobles @GregJKrieg @BernieSanders Did he finally join the party then??]]></document><document><![CDATA[They gave me these leggings, so what they say must be true. 💛 #lovebeingyourauntie #LVtoLA #cutenessoverload @ Los… https://t.co/OpNfLUsMI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A dark day for Israel was the day your buddy Netanyahu was indicted yes, INDICTED for corruption.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colton was way more emotional in his Hannah breakup but I feel like we didn’t get to see enough of their love story!! #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 10 yr old sister got all nervous when my 14 yr old sister got out a visa gift card to buy something on their gam… https://t.co/1FiQWdkGrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PJCanuck @Fffeisty @Sportsnet Toronto proper is only like 2.7 million. I was going with the lowest figures to real… https://t.co/1ogbnwr7ms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsTheWater Oh G. You are missing the whole point. Sigh. (But yes by all means do so).]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night: “guys suck i dropped my boy he’s not coming to see me anymore”  this morning: https://t.co/FKxx3jGVnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Searched for a good goat pun for a solid hour... I goat nothing @ Lucky Weather Ranch https://t.co/YBJWuBzZzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[You fall down one stair...... I swear to god no one lets you forget it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanBanks21 @AB84 Why are you destroying your career?!? #assclown #ABdrama]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever wondered why we cut those little slots in the footrings of our pots?#albertapotteryvideos @ Greenville, South… https://t.co/WWiP3beabf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maria Iman Santoso crossed 3.1. Time 00:35:26, pace 11:24 min/mile, est. finish 11:11 am https://t.co/0sOApTW5NO #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaPenney @locobolo1 @grumpy_grannie More than that .  Why would it  be a problem]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just ❤ 🤗 mi amigo's music.  Do yourself a favor and go follow.  He da, best]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s snow (1/2 inch) on the ground in Arkansas! People are FREAKING out! When in ROME... https://t.co/e4KwBWNBcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tara Hills CA Thu Feb 21st PM Forecast: TONIGHT Clear Lo 31 FRIDAY Sunny Hi 55]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biggsdaanimal @HBCUfessions It don’t but it your man isn’t getting you where you hand can ...it’s even sadder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellen Prager discusses her books revolving climate change here at the St. Petersburg Conference on World Affairs at… https://t.co/Zht0dseprc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring Ways to Say So Long to Traditional Letter Grades https://t.co/gFcvbCPAm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like if you can’t park, you shouldn’t be allowed to drive a huge truck. Y’all either need to stop taking up… https://t.co/iiCfpFJHAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather What I wouldn’t give for 15 minutes of news from you or Walter every evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Max_n_Ruby @LHVanhorn @Beatlemaniac201 @Michael28710212 @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @danabrams Rewatching video No… https://t.co/OyBcqrq2X0]]></document><document><![CDATA[no matter what ur opinion on who can say dyke is all wlw must come together to defeat the real evil: billie eilish… https://t.co/WpBpiIHJDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFRSH757 They leave you be. They might say hi. The Carytown location has 4 meeting spaces that nonprofits and comm… https://t.co/l7l8IbEkPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot fall asleep until my person is already halfway asleep. (a struggle)  Can some1 tell her to stop doing her… https://t.co/xLLCqdMw1Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[i will truly never forget the amount of lunch periods i spent playing this mixtape from my ipod touch in my sixth g… https://t.co/tlDQwSNNxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaVanderpump sitting here watching RHOBH and I am getting more upset by the second. You are dealing with so much… https://t.co/LQmmKcLsBN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesssssssss I am here for the summer...whose with me to get my summer bod in shape with the Tracy diet!? #LoveAfterLockup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realPatriotDrew @fev7777777 A battle to get there, but 🙏 we will. We must support our POTUS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to bed at 11:30 and I just woke up expecting it to be 8am but no it’s 2. Wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SweeetMamaSue @LindaLeeKing @SweetetMamaSue @Kimberl38218406 y’all please thank your friends family for your praye… https://t.co/iVOqrK0WOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Already we argue over whether to call them climate deniers, skeptics or doubters. @AOC might have hit on a more dev… https://t.co/xl0tyYzuD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel opens today on International Women’s Day. Coincidence? I think not. 💪🏽💫👊🏼💥 @captainmarvel… https://t.co/G9ZS4y5C8c]]></document><document><![CDATA[So apparently when you favorite items on Etsy, it becomes a part of your public images on google. I am obsessed wit… https://t.co/o4frr25yVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie @Markwil50187274 @RollingStone We know already Jim, Cohen hasn’t always told the truth.  But people who live… https://t.co/EgwP9zIJm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DontMindIfIDoob Not 900 on one pair..however much you’d spend on a pair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi 👋 I work for the Associated Press. And I also went to a no name university with a non-existent J school. Strong… https://t.co/4By1kZkVk8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billdowns2013 @gardnerwebb Congrats! Super excited for you Bill! Well done! Look forward to following your success!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my school plays music every friday morning and sucker just played and i freaked out @jonasbrothers @kevinjonas @joejonas @nickjonas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susanasilvi58 @L_Boop @BlancaNayelyNT3 @3gcry @gerardo_hedez @salakill @EllaCantaloupeH @cevalloslaura… https://t.co/hrFmrnPrwG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third grade is kicking off their unit with a @RightQuestion strategy of close reading a picture from the Great Chic… https://t.co/iW9JNz49lj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanRKnight I’m so happy spring forward. I can’t wait to start to warm up and it’s a sign that it’s coming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That time when @DierksBentley @mirandalambert and @KeithUrban started singing @BrdgstoneArena !!! https://t.co/SmtorTA37P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar @MomsThoughts Trump looks like he's using the flag pole to hold himself up -- the opposite of revering the flag.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence Lord, I am near  Baltimore , in Columbia, do you have prople with you to hrlp you.?]]></document><document><![CDATA[coolest pregnancy photo haha So have to do this when I get bigger https://t.co/2NIkf1nGSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melody_mcgowan @Truthseeker126 @KAG4All @ArizonaKayte @michaelbeatty3 @Rampage95_ @bbusa617 @Mr_Common_Cents… https://t.co/nJr0JLOB0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your having a great hair and makeup day... take photos as proof! #goodhairday #curlyhair #lovemymakeup @ Belle… https://t.co/4VMMF90d8y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmykimmel Really big fan of your show! I have a request to make if it's possible I would like to see… https://t.co/2XVJssEbfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker I was waiting...who is tackaling criminal justice REFORM. GET PEOPLE OUT OF JAIL ....$5-$10 BAGS OF MAR… https://t.co/2mx99bw7wl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews The only one obsessed with racism is Sharpton who makes his living from it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sofyoule L'alcool c'est bon pour elle et pour toi aussi mon amie qui me fait le plus rire.  😂😂😂😂🤘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer @realDonaldTrump is all of the above. #IllegitimatePresident @POTUS aka #PresidentPantsonFire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_granata @296_cool @loveujustinjb5 @BhanuRajput33 @kulsgrace @Monika_Kapoor19 @curly_bug @Bizzlex8… https://t.co/bV7LhAxumo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Break a leg all the actors opening in Betrayal at the Pinter theater today. This goes double for @twhiddleston.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easymoney_slum Yeah... pretty weird.... Zach.... https://t.co/j6bH0YlY9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe I’m starting to really like @colton. How did this happen?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join St. Peter’s Episcopal Church for the #U2Charist — a music-filled worship service on Sat., 3/2 at 7 PM —  featu… https://t.co/BcR3vmuQuL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My newest energy forecast has been uploaded to my YouTube channel. The link is in my pin tweet under the reply sect… https://t.co/Uhk2fxe6XJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent the Day Shopping 🛍 ✨🤪 #BeverlyHills #RodeoDrive https://t.co/R7zMsJAnSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that I know the truth, all of the things I questioned are making sense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GayleKing great job with R Kelly. So very proud of you, you didn't let him intimidate you, you showed strength and a unshakable demeanor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t watch many youtubers but I really love #karinakaboom . She loves saying weird made up words like… https://t.co/dzdG3GXRMV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Vi_2U There pay should be cut to $55,000 per year! Why are the newcomers getting $175,000 a year when they’re… https://t.co/7P4t9W267t]]></document><document><![CDATA[💛 #bookstagram #books #funkopop #harrypotter @ Ooltewah, Tennessee https://t.co/LbrqKA5zRk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someday, this will be considered your classic early work and has the potential to sell for millions. Keep going. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maritza_neboyia OMG Neboyia now I'm gonna have "Ice Ice Baby" stuck in my head all day LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t even imagine all the other lies that have escaped news coverage or were buried by some other breaking news!… https://t.co/jnq7Sl3rx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DomajorReminor @MirrorRoyal Meghan or her " anonymous " friends do that all the time. That's why KP is having such… https://t.co/ZsJpnbiWAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MusicFunAndFood @VeganRobs Loved the puffed Brussels sprouts! #fcs2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewellLab But see, in your case, you were likely texting about science, not crafts for your Mardi Gras costume. I… https://t.co/m6ap5poYLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in my room and alla sudden I hear my brother playing fortnite screaming,  “You’re a lil bitch, you know that?? You a lil pussy bitch!” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of immunotherapy combinations coming down the pipeline = good for cancer but more irAEs! #ImmunoOnc19… https://t.co/FiH9Raf4kD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun, fresh, and talented! That’s the team you will work with at Ulta Beauty! We are currently hiring for exceptiona… https://t.co/vpUumklsgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sthornburgg I already know I'm in trouble. Karma came in the form of someone who looks and acts exactly like me 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super excited to join @TheBOSSNetwork as a featured keynote speaker sharing my #ProtectedByPurpose journey at… https://t.co/R0snz6Je1g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna know how the fuck these bitches live on a MT salary, work a couple days a week, support their kidS and stil… https://t.co/PKaLBGVaVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, Roger Stone has some creepy friends.  Is he asking Russia to send poison?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hendrick9Team @Hooters Petty? Yep.  I’m not being serious. Joking is allowed on twitter, right?]]></document></documents></author>