<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I hesitate to compare the two because today’s creative is largely garbage, but the Flair birthday segment is WWE’s… https://t.co/YaAHEHWCXz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackDixonXX @HotMaleStuds @gayporncrushes @Gay4Gayporn2018 @GayBearDaddyXXX @gaybearcave @theo17110 @L_K_4… https://t.co/L8pQODKmNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep! #abouttogetdown #livemusic #countryconcerts #instagood #countrymusic 8pm startup @ Knuckleheads https://t.co/pn1VW9MwoB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bainard @Passionweiss Silas has been in heavy rotation for many moons now, ever since Thoroughbreds came out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed checking out the DI tourney. Championship level Kids, sponsors, and parents working hard today! https://t.co/vk7RrfNv3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GreenRangur91 Welcome!  Have you checked out the LAST BLOCKBUSTER episode of TALKBUSTET yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBB_RunThePoint Thats insane. Surprised he didn't cut his hand wide open.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanBragg I know it’s far fetch and 1000% not happening but I just made that head cannon and I feel like a gen… https://t.co/nLs91OmyAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand by for live-tweeted review of Applebee’s delivery. Riblets edition... https://t.co/J26SKUJZaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greta Hey Greta why not have classes cost more or less depending on their relevance?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my beautiful, badass, amazing cyborg mom. Now that you're half robot you'll probably outlive us a… https://t.co/6BIS1AzqoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mind-altering, ketamine-like drug OK'd for severe depression https://t.co/7JeZNUtrZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneNightStanzas No one should have to argue for, or explain, why they believe in equal rights.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenMajLdr remember this when a democratic president declares a national emergency on guns, health care or climate… https://t.co/0r4GFuwhXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad, but true. The abuse of women and children represented by the EC’s decision to assist in the coverup of abused… https://t.co/LizCRp5VkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Basically I take on more projects than I can handle and when you’re already constantly stressed, adding all of this… https://t.co/DG3Ix60gyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loc Retwist  Cut.  Color. Fade. Razor Finish. Style.  #locs #dreads #retwist #cut #color #razor #fade #style… https://t.co/Lz3FEaMKOm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HazelwoodDan @labour My bad grammar strikes again. I meant, “Communism kills, Comrade”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tim Rogers is doing some beautiful work at Kotaku dot com @108   Dragon Quest XI: The Kotaku Review https://t.co/G9FfznuMP6 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tip looking real lame right now bro. 1) he still salty cause Floyd fucked his bitch. "Fuck niggas" get mad at the… https://t.co/V05cdkWBrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codyythehuman @UmbrellaAcad @netflix The universe is really giving us everything we want.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC AND THERE BY THE GRACE OF MY GOD GO I " FOR ONE BROTHER FOR ONE GOD ,, FOR ONE NATION UNDER GOD ,, THE TRUTH… https://t.co/kdGkXaRb0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗳Voted YEA on #GAHB228 to raise marriage age in GA from 16 to emancipated 17 year olds. Passed 158-13 #garepvotes… https://t.co/ghcxa02gWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 0.0 mph N. Barometer 29.652 in, Falling quickly. Temperature 30.5 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 94%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctanner3 @AlwaysVoteGOP @Thkngofthenorth @CaliRN619 @Plena007 @ImabitcSumtimes @FairyQ15 @garway95 @mtdudette… https://t.co/DxjGZwySKl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qian Magwood with a steal and he throws it down at the other end   Walnut Ridge leads 10-2 with with 4:33 to go in the first]]></document><document><![CDATA[@capehog @SharpTusk Wait.... where them pizza rolls from? Old Chicago has the best.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kadet_Athletics @kadetbball Thanks @Kadet_Athletics ! I can’t wait to stop by the old stomping grounds #Kadet4Life]]></document><document><![CDATA[PlayBig ... Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez: U.S. Congresswoman on Fixing the Country – Rolling Stone https://t.co/dYDL3uvrmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dreamt of adopting a puppy golden retriever. 😭😭 where’s my puppy?? https://t.co/MWQUgAzaw6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derek_mafs @AOC Democrats are very good at that. When they point the finger three of them are pointing right back… https://t.co/A1qTFU6b8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mimi4meyerboys 65 and 56 throughout. 56 &gt;&gt; 11. Not sure what 56 means.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuned in to @noshoesradio this morning and cried the whole way to work listening to the tribute to #RememberingKristi . So beautifully done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chocolate_Coupl Mmmm yes lay back and relax 💋💋💋🌹🌹💕👅👅👅👅 and ride my face]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuckfaceVonClo5 @MontyFowler @realDonaldTrump But again your comment only strengthens my point- application of sta… https://t.co/OAV7L7HEQg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Glenn_XLVIII @brianstelter @ReliableSources I got fake news,called freedom Most valuable thing on Earth City of Pr… https://t.co/L1CUlh5vso]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the @americanair app says that I am still at my original seat !!!  And we are already flying and I am at anothe… https://t.co/py63z2iXyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boneitis @SlanderBob I've loved every one of these recommendations so far, may attempt to hit you up for Preacher… https://t.co/lY8rXvHySt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boonefor3 @couchandtherube @Graham_Couch Sports are a zero sum game.  Results are literally all that matter.  Unle… https://t.co/ciTEBwMtcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danmall @zeldman Mixture of the two. Nav/header and page title follows grid, but non-card sub-items follow internal grid. ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Any reason will work fine for me . As long as your not the president]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @Sunstruk Many truths are finally beginning to surface and even break through the MSM dogma.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FLOTUS @ericbolling @WestgateVegas You’re charging admission?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnGaltJunior3 I used to make my own weed vape from glycerine and the other stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun Day 😎🌴#floridawinter 🌝⛄️🌴 @ Fort Lauderdale, Florida https://t.co/EpTmNb7QDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone’s in the south March-April and wants to know more about the show—a queer love story set in a fantasy tech… https://t.co/gAtQniC0CH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just as @SueSerioFox29 predicted!!  Waking up to #snow and the @FOX29philly #fox29goodday team! https://t.co/DE6EgYegxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaBoz28 @Ramcgreg @vivahate46 @benshapiro @CommerceGov That will lead to war lords... How American of you...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I shared an elevator with the UK mascots.  Nice fellas...didn’t talk much...I offered em popcorn the 1/2 Wildcat gu… https://t.co/Qg01DSyDO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington helped forge the framework of freedom that allows each of us to pursue happiness and create better futur… https://t.co/VRT3Mt2xd0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even animals are talking to me. It’s just such a beautiful thing to be gracefully in tune with the world and wishin… https://t.co/kREBjtxxB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final at St. Raymonds| @step_basketball 72, @MsgrScanlanHS 60 Stepinac moves on to face @StRaysAthletics in the cla… https://t.co/XrWSliUSkq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s the weekend. But I can’t stop thinking how this action figure in our writer’s room looks exactly like P… https://t.co/ZvNe4BsOqB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvonomicsMag @yanisvaroufakis Thanks for the credit! Was great working on this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jadler1969 @Twittersupport my list of tweets is once again including replies to tweets.  How come?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larwrd bless I thought I was watching @PriceIsRight on @NBCTheVoice tonight with @kelly_clarkson when Jej Vincent p… https://t.co/33JS7YXPcU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go figure. Back those fuckers up. They're basically sitting at the out of bounce line, ridiculous. @ncaa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ricky Morgan’s Freshman year, LE called a timeout in our first exhibition game.   Ricky walked to the huddle.   LE… https://t.co/SM4eETIEZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AztecBailVegas @DriveSafeNV I appreciate you attaching an example this time. If you have a stack of these that you… https://t.co/qDKCIYFtct]]></document><document><![CDATA[NBA Jam/WWE mashup: Moustache Mountain vs. Street Profits, Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic Rd. 1 (via @ceehawk)… https://t.co/UEkOS2ygRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump NOW YOU'LL WISE-UP....HUH ASSHOLE!!! HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dame_Lillard @hulu Did he scratch off the raider logo or did Hulu did 🤔🧐🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[Obviously, an honest evaluation will tell you that it’s borderline insulting to compare Nylander to that group, now… https://t.co/0dJG0pONrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[It won’t be easy but it is possible. Ways to help with that is prayer and surrounding yourself with things that say… https://t.co/NnjJDmKb5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy bday to my day one!! The big 1️⃣8️⃣have a great day boss❤️ @minton2313 https://t.co/pCBDROUAnK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very weak call. You’re looking for something to call hard to put your arm up for that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so envious of the people who got up this morning to go for a run.  How do you find that motivation?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always wanna know my side of the story because dey know with these words that come out of me ppl judge my ca… https://t.co/JxKVU2GZXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertLaurie That’s a nice box to hold your LPs. Did you make that or can one find that online?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A good read for cosplayers desiring to become Cosplay Guests. Having met some of the most known Guests multiple tim… https://t.co/w2s3TLizpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I'm saying is   Bernie marched with MLK.  Kamala would have arrested MLK.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medon1165 @JoySamms1 @The_Mitchman @davidcicilline https://t.co/OIu3Rgm0ll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Felix_Sicard I think that's good for the ducks, but it will be nice to see him play]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wingoz. #KylerMurry is VICK 2020 R G 3 Athlete,not reading coverage you can't be in two sports and be invested enough to be NFL QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MimiSandrock78 Her district is full of Somali settled refugees by Obama. Sound fishy yet?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskCapitalOne Thanks! I figured I’d have to stop by a location... I have one identified in Highland Village TX. I’… https://t.co/ymyV4C9E7b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Russmoore713 @rhodeislander Nobody thinks that. I just think you act like they should be as successful as Duke bec… https://t.co/fdpuVV0UBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tholzerman But also I’d rather a show end at 1015 and leave people off than end at midnight so we can get everyone… https://t.co/KEVhuauAYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I donated blood with a different medical organization than I normally use and I feel dirty about it. 🤦🏻‍♂️💉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margcellent @realDonaldTrump Elf is a Trump hater !  And also an illegal so he can’t vote on Trump issues! Deport!]]></document><document><![CDATA[...and at the hotel lobby in Palo Alto! ☺ #WelcomeToStanford https://t.co/WulL9XSCUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egrette @AngryBlackLady @magi_jay Wow, I was a high school sophomore back then! But even I know that sometimes sta… https://t.co/Yyujt8Bzp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a while! Bringing my Coworkers here! (@ Sciortino's Harbor Lights in South Amboy, NJ) https://t.co/QQQGAH1kKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhecht @PolitiFact @SenRickScott @AOC OK, truce terms: we’ll agree to stop using fringe statements as represent… https://t.co/3DqIaXGW9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[All of the feels... Tears were shed. A decade well waited, now hop to it and get going with what's next!! #KH3… https://t.co/8P9ybOm5Xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuarushing 1) Repent!  2) only if you add the eagles to that statement  3) no opinion. https://t.co/93GN3BvEJt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Non_Symmetry Woah, so I’m down too chop off hunans but sultan wok? Had them a couple weeks ago and it had my stomach set tripping 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[The American problem with illegal drugs has an American solution and that is to reduce the demand for drugs. When t… https://t.co/f5ENwfjMA8]]></document><document><![CDATA[CBS suborns McCabe perjury.  Indict McCabe, Comey, Clinton and CBS.  @SixtyMinutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnAsplund1 @ScottKuffel I’ve accepted the challenge from @JohnAsplund1 to post an album cover a day for ten days… https://t.co/WHzN3wJBYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrotherJoe18 @marklevinshow Speaking of Reelection Guaranteed: please help us Dems n 2020 by not supporting RINO'S… https://t.co/g5DsYqfJc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like not enough people are talking about this https://t.co/Rz4StSSr51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our newest #rialto #california listing! Highly sought after, prestigious neighborhood awaits your customization to… https://t.co/QrDf0rKLLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SocialMediaIn4Words: always chasing those clicks! Big happy guy Brian is chasing a loving home. Want to help him o… https://t.co/KYNdfbEu4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you living comfy you dont respect money. #billspaid #stillgotmoneyinthebank]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyons_Indiana win 137-125! 8 straight wins!  Thanks for a fun day of basketball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimRunsHisMouth He'll get about 3 or 4 months of probation if he keeps his mouth shut.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apple needs to add two hands 🖕🏽 flipping you off emoji   That’s a different type of energy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 30th birthday @callencudmore!!! Apparently twitter is cool again now so here we are. 🎉🎂🎈🍻🎊 https://t.co/dwC2oIoMNW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarasLab @sgi_dna @SynGenomeInc Wow, how you getting along with the A.I. Keras?  ...Or should I not even mention it...]]></document></documents></author>