<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[When I was working in LIC back in the80's it was being gentrified then. They were renovating and retrofitting many… https://t.co/9gWLgXf3iR]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they don’t have anyone up there to wipe down the solar panel to let the battery charge up...]]></document><document><![CDATA[This time Friday I’ll be in Nashville soooo this will probably be the longest school week ever]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go see this great free Appalachian Studies conference at #UKY! Hosted by @UKYAppCenter and #GARC. https://t.co/JPhoUBKXlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:33 am y mis vecinos tienen música de cartel de santa, o sea  que les pasaaaaa como no estudian o trabajan se pued… https://t.co/SJGLBJ0n4C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elyh - Quiero decir algo pero me da miedo que luego el Karma venga por mi.   Betty - No pasa nada, dilo y luego te… https://t.co/uO66LB5Il5]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Now that they’ve returned the money they stole from me, I wanted to let everyone know that they should avoid sta… https://t.co/HIlIfo8xWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[These snap memories got me fucked up :( I used to be so skinny and so tiny wtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THILL0810 So sorry to hear. My condolences and prayers of strength and comfort to you and your loved ones. 🙏🏽💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#macro shot inside of the #orange #poppy #LA #superbloom #nofilter @ Lake Elsinore, California https://t.co/hF4Ma3r9Zh]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait to be ina healthy loving relationship where i don’t doubt every single thing my boyfriend does]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachSueG @UMCoachHutch I accept the 7 day challenge from @CoachSueG to post covers of 7 meaningful books. I chall… https://t.co/zxym3KInkB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Silsbycarr @cbcaron I think BJs sells a box mix, but I’ve never tried either to know to compare and/or what I’m missing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing at @AIA_SFA tonight, so be prepared for hearing the Bible, and also: #mightyducks https://t.co/9gMpdsL9MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun at Ripleys Aquarium! #marchbreak #toronto @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/tj0pkn0dIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[RAPHAEL!!!!!! Rnt u the good samaritan lol #SaveShadowhunters #ShadowhuntersLegacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had plans for the evening, but they turned into a trip to the ER. I’m fine, but I have a stomach virus which trigge… https://t.co/e2sLpfQD0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys!! Its that time again!! Join me at 1030am at Dancing the Soul for Zumba class!! Start your Sunday Fun Day… https://t.co/b8DxdLp5z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr Of course they will listen to you Bernie , u r so wise, fraud]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @FoxNews Why are you SO pathetic!! You are the poorest excuse for a congressman that has ever represe… https://t.co/jTCEC38ftH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So exciting! I love mine! I can't wait for someone to win this and fall in love with it like I have with my student… https://t.co/oSZioW3N4n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha when your husband wakes you up cause he had a nightmare about the number 3 &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCornyn @SenBobCorker @SenatorCollins @ChuckGrassley @LindseyGrahamSC @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @Jim_Jordan… https://t.co/Ca2dkNFpdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freedom2713 @msnicole1124 @DaveSchreiber3 @RL9631 @45Quickdraw4 @nancy_hamm1 @PsychoMetalHed @SealeyGerald… https://t.co/c2hBQToAFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome Jannah Shields Miss Muslimah USA 2019 contestant. _ Name: Jannah Shields Age: 22 Occupation: Student/Botani… https://t.co/RJd8rlWRiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[16 shots, 9 in the back of unarmed black boy, he's getting what he deserves. Chicagoans will not allow this, period!https://t.co/aZ6azEE2l4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brunch with a friend, and mimosas 🥰 @ Montreal, Quebec https://t.co/Ea9m1ODCDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Trump finally hits the dust, believe it will be because of his financial life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seven years ago we answered God's call to adopt. Obedience isn't always easy but I wouldn't change a thing.… https://t.co/wkg4tlxFNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m sorry but it is absolute blasphemy that Step Up only received 20% on Rotten Tomatoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished five weeks of five day (some six day!!) a week 5am workouts. Honestly, those are words I NEVER thou… https://t.co/L0Aw6IjiNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Honest_Hillary1 @CNN @realDonaldTrump I personally don’t believe a wall is going to stop drugs from coming across… https://t.co/8BQVTXqrTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[God daughter so cute , go vote for her   https://t.co/bfKYzNoNNL https://t.co/3Ig98eVhko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arunwithaview Whew! I paid in enough in estimated taxes. Too much actually, so I’m getting a refund!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon_Reiss @ifpfilm @CalArts @Tribeca @larajeangal @BoraKimNews @LostBayouFilm @AndrewAhnFilms @JeanieFinlay Thank… https://t.co/wWdVrznbQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please listen &amp; help this family effected by PSD, Vet.   https://t.co/AFXRjblijN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MMAWeeklycom @ICICLES_USA @SusanCingari @JeffJetro @MMAjunkie @PsychoJoeBKF @CombatInsiders @BloodyElbow M1 Global… https://t.co/LARwJfIMKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ten things only coaches’ daughters will understand https://t.co/49Awfq0Gmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baptism   Nacho Libre https://t.co/oE99pkR2hF via @YouTube @IamMannyMans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and a wonderful panel of #landuse lawyers discussing all the best cases from last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boot scooting boogie #rodeohouston #boots #western #family #houston @ NRG Stadium https://t.co/o9AztlfGyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing and fun Pit Orchestra performing 7 shows of "The Wizard of Oz" and performed by the talented students of Bl… https://t.co/y71jI0vL1Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganStoneCT It was good. I should have stirred the caramel around a bit. Would have again]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jamiattenberg @JenAshleyWright Had you been asleep? Could be a hypnagogic hallucination. I’ve had several of those… https://t.co/VyvykCyyw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[giggle with me for a bit. Picture Book Lessons: The Summarizing Hokey Pokey: That's What It's All About. pictureboo… https://t.co/ZgADHSO93U]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Brampton! Join me today 1-3pm! Image credit: Knowledge Bookstore @harperchildrens @harpercollinsca… https://t.co/msJjPdb2X6]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an event! Thank you, @dougblandry, for bringing us all together for #AdvanceCamp!   Now, let’s… https://t.co/lIpgBBW0j8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeMusicYT Check out ‘Duller Star’ for some Noir &amp; B vibes 💫:  https://t.co/aTIaXwfDb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to you @KimFCoates Hope you had an epic day!! See you next month in Niagara xoxo (a day late because… https://t.co/46C9sNWC4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[And russia, and Saudi....any Man who killed, raped, beat their wife, pedophile....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MariaK46861456 @lamphieryeg For a Candidate to run for election in a riding, they must have the endorsement of the… https://t.co/PEJGlU344z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sure Do.... Multiples of Multiples playing with 🔥 with the Chief Comptroller’s in Nam 🎳👎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum And, I have dumped them. In many ways CNN has become a moderate Fox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @girlscouts in Corvallis, Oregon!  The S’Mores cookies almost beat out frozen Thin Mints.  Throw back… https://t.co/vbPmHFIVYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[jariatu gon call me at 5:51am talmbout some “i was just saying hi” like bitch ??😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I met my baby fitfeministmama for Tacos and Beer last night!  Photo cred: 1_000_one_000 it literally took him like… https://t.co/4vkk5f4tY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManaByte People say the same about Tom Hiddleston as Loki.....like seriously, it’s crazy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chezhdchick @gbindyjilly @WhatRUTinkin @ceallaigh_k So.... instead of haunting US just MAYBE she'll haunt him, Che… https://t.co/qTEQHS84eR]]></document><document><![CDATA[While this won’t be a common answer: There’s a part of Do Androids Dream if Electric Sheep by Philip K Dick that ca… https://t.co/DBN92Ja6Wi]]></document><document><![CDATA[757 Booking✨ Follow my IG @NailsBy_Kiy  #newportnews #hampton #757nailtech #bethelhigh #757nails #hamptonuniversity… https://t.co/B0Kwdtv48F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win a Trip to See The String Cheese Incident's in Las Vegas, NV! https://t.co/44VlXVKlKh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Herfurth_Bronco @BrewerDodge @GISDArts Overall Day https://t.co/hPCrZgzBvQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow men really ain’t shit. They can’t bring anything to the table besides the fucking audacity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPEN_DAWN @JannealFranklyn @OfficerMorton @ayerscg497 https://t.co/otHqecOMG9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to #rallython2019 on raising a record-shattering $117,530.29 for the #UVMChildrensHospital #movemountains… https://t.co/vBvVlIwyxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FebruaryContest Will you be mine? I want to ply you with books galore in @NNP_W_Light’s Be Mine Bookish Giveaway… https://t.co/LFMS7OfnzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer And I used to think all 2A nuts did was to shoot their mouths off... https://t.co/ga0dz1qJYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how it’s feeling. #blizzard #snow #longwinter #lauraingallswilder @ Autumn House At Toad Hill https://t.co/KwtQ5m2oG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all you AEW jumpers out there, listen to 4:58! Doesn't sound like a guy who's interested in jumping ship https://t.co/X5wZO33ER8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin Salud no hay nada... 🙅🏼‍♀️ . Come daño para que tengas: Mas Energía  Mas tiempo para disfrutar de tus seres que… https://t.co/yxKzan77St]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chantalrochelle How did we not discuss Keto in our catchup today?! 😭 I’ve tried it a few times and failed. For our… https://t.co/LMFdkXfTwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #bully, #fraud, #liar, #LockHimUp    Maybe have a look at your reality... https://t.co/ADrc1yyyBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CISNational #mosaicchallenge #WhatWeAreMadeOf #SXSWEdu https://t.co/AzrSXGlioX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we supposed to just let the Democrats allow illegal aliens to vote just so that they can win?   Isn’t anybody g… https://t.co/DGix4SDiMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you meet @NESZLO at adventure club but your phone ran out of photo storage😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaththeWineLady @DivaVinophile @chelelife @pietrosd @ricasoli99 @magee333 @SteveKubota @cuvee_corner @jflorez… https://t.co/dksnTDofs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends 81 entities should plead the fifth!!! And no recollection at all just like Hillary!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green eggs ready to go to school to kick off Read Across America Week!  Love days like this that are filled with fu… https://t.co/nUaGFQvHCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[16 days til Spring Break 👙🕶☀️🍹🛳 #cruisin #timetorelax #letsgetshipfaced #SB19 @CarnivalCruise]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach said he can tell I’ve been losing weight because it’s easier to hug me. Which is a great compliment by someone who sees me everyday]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can tell you don’t got the matching hoodie to go w these sweats just by the kicks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tell Eric Trump to keep JFK’s name out his mouth. I would but he blocked me because I asked that he apologized for… https://t.co/t0kFDDf0zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj America has used Afghanistan like Afghani's don't have anything to say about their country...Are the Rare… https://t.co/PZRY6VwJcJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alphak9p I woulda smacked the shit outta every one of those bounce shots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VarsityAllStar I wish we could have seen battle. It's a long drive from WV, didnt quite get here in time. But we a… https://t.co/x5lwilBx1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resharing this video in honor of #InternationalWomensDay 🙌🏼💪🏼 #WomenAT4ALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeanetteSMB @FireDiscCookers @USChamber Finding your #CompetitiveEdge: “The Jaggard brothers spotted an unmet need… https://t.co/QwJvmITE4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elenamtre I try to get a head start and leave him sleeping in his recliner but tonight it didn’t work. 😂😐]]></document><document><![CDATA[We read books with our kindergarten buddies in Mrs. Fritel’s class today! #comfyspots @sgrspuds @MoorheadSchools https://t.co/X1yUbnouxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day baby!💕 I love you! @joseph_kn17 https://t.co/0Uyk13ATS6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lulu_says2 I didn't want to believe him....but I actually do. And every republican in that room is afraid the public believes him too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it possible that @Bertuccis has not seen this toddler marketing coup?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Moore07 @urmomsluver @ethanmilford1 @penguins I’ve been watching hockey for over 30 years. Believe me, I know… https://t.co/aaLN6l0yTM]]></document><document><![CDATA[True about the caps especially when my head is too big to fit in almost any of them. I think I also have way too ma… https://t.co/QuyrmgFKcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someonetell me what language they are speaking? Twi? #BeastOfNoNation #SundayBlackFilmTwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Maria_Giesela my company makes a 1mg kids melatonin chewable and we joke about carrying them around to hand out to parents bc YEAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are all just pure hearted animals who want love &amp; to be told “you’re doing really great.” @Remember_Sarah… https://t.co/en22LQtWsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[stolen from my everyone lol reply with ♡s please   ❤️- you consider us friends 🧡- you want to be friends  💛- you th… https://t.co/pmrQUJiAqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to the inclusive culture @eesalbnl and amazing scientists with whom I study mountain watersheds.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please give blood, every city in America in running short. I depend on it for my treatment for a very rare auto imm… https://t.co/c6OEK5frOK]]></document></documents></author>