<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Accounts Payable Analyst, PO" in #Centennial, CO. Go on informational interviews.… https://t.co/037tZuylfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[why’d you let me go on thinking i was the only one?   you knew i loved you more than i’d loved anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatrioticCindy @ReneeCarrollAZ America will say “no” to Bernie.  Done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far this #Oscar2019 opening is far preferable to some cheesy monologue. (Though Adam Lambert will never be Fredd… https://t.co/jp5wy4GgkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whitneydlw10 @sparksjn @EdKrassen You’re cute, but I said one of the most respected men in the Justice Dept. will… https://t.co/rKkZJ9LMkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatHarty Iowa’s 5-5 over last 10 B10 games. Only Mich(7-3) Wisconsin (7-3) Purdue (8-2) are better than 6-4. Obvio… https://t.co/K0HYUrpkJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midway through the first half:  Odessa High 0, Amarillo Tascosa 0  @OA_Sports #oavarsity]]></document><document><![CDATA[drop as most don’t even have sand to practice in. 3) have teams station volunteer ball sighters each hole. 75% of p… https://t.co/TG2j2jSFIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which track did the public school system place you on?  https://t.co/6aOa7kUdie #freaksandgeeks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Build with family I know lately mines has been talking about investments ownership and building a solid foundation for future generations]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lya9_ Pues siga descansando , buenos días Lya y feliz domingo familiar saludos cordiales,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super strength? Super fast? Move things with your mind? Nah. If I had a super power I want to dive into people mind… https://t.co/mFxGm7TOCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Backdoor Funk With Guava And Peach by @deBineBrews at @deBineBrews — https://t.co/tKDjKZEc1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ocasio2018 I don’t agree with all of your ideas and policy, but I like your making the statues q. Anxious. This OP… https://t.co/qXfTbXMGOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza Ask Ann Coulter she has become the expert on liberal hate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeyalfieri @TheFarrarSide Tough challenge tonight .. #Habs need to pick up pts cause other teams are coming up fa… https://t.co/VgjDb4NSHb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, “I believe Putin” “I believe the Prince (MBS) NOW, “I believe Kim (about a dead American College Student’s d… https://t.co/rm8EefemQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINALLY: Rosenstein to Leave DOJ Next Month https://t.co/TyLmlFpGXk #war]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Classy Work Shirt by @3magbrewing/@Culminationbrew @ City of Fontana — https://t.co/MfNDRnytmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suspendedsoon1 @EyeLikeFax @indystar Ur sword is the most expensive health care in the world....  Got another exam… https://t.co/grM7Fvp1v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book lovers! Check out this new book by 10 young women from the @BarackObama White House. With a foreword by… https://t.co/g7Pp2ELeIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajajajajajajaja!!! Ya voy a ver a mas de uno así!!! en AmericanAirlines Arena https://t.co/OnW9MhWnzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BurlingtonBees @FisherCats @MiracleBaseball @OremOwlz @MiLB Big jokes from the team with a tiny little bee 🐝 .....… https://t.co/mC8sudjwrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery Obama already covered that under his communist-style " Community Reinvestment Act".]]></document><document><![CDATA[More like Bugging Ouuuuut! #GameofThronesSeason8  . The best part Is not having a clue of how this beautiful monste… https://t.co/DyQlxH3yKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XMan1932 @kamalelallam1 @KrusherKovalev J’adore ! C’est un peu moi aussi . Les bons combats se font rares]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JideLambo 🤣🤣🤣 good request bro! Didn’t think of that but i’ll let them know once i come across one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delcosportsBob Awesome stuff!! According to my record John is the first-ever Strath Haven wrestler to advance to the PIAA Final Four!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkewayman Plus a new guaranteed contract right? That’s what he said he wants. I’ll pass. Spend on defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyKappell Thanks for this update, Jeremy. I’ve got to head this way in about 10 minutes.  🚙💨 ❄️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day is tomorrow, everybody gonna be waking up to paragraph with picture and Imma wake up to 100% charged😂😭🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the @kyliehnsn !! We may be a little psycho, but we sure know how to have a good time😘 have the b… https://t.co/H5Dp2jarj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc what anyone says soccer skin gives you powers https://t.co/eY3ABOR4Nl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another wonderful morning in Malvern @ Willistown https://t.co/XusyaC3kHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump will really lose it if Michael Cohen crosses this ‘big, red line,’ Omarosa says  #DictatorDonnie… https://t.co/nm7d4HLEu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kennedyquinn5 Tagging someone in a tweet after they’ve already seen it dude... HELL NO]]></document><document><![CDATA[[My NEW Blog Post] Windows Server 2019 – Active Directory Installation Beginners Guide. Sure you can use a hydratio… https://t.co/03qwxsgtjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlonaABC13 "I disagree!!!", Says this Detroit Lions fan. @Texans are a playoff team with plenty o' upside.  Detroi… https://t.co/LbldgFDJ3O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRoderickI SMU already has a berth, vacant berth as Dal was in regardless as host, so the “AUS Champ” berth goes to SMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidBHayter I was wondering what all the helicopters we're about earlier. Stay safe man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight presenting best supporting Whactor @TheToscars 🎥🥂💃🏻 great evening full of laughs and love 💕 https://t.co/JqIdvFnHx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @Puglaas I’m AMAZED he let her speak; perhaps he thought he had a “deal”, not to implicate him. This lady has a ton of guts!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@g_ack @CapitalOne @AntonesNightclb YEAH! We got on the list…thank you so much! We cannot wait for the gig!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Instead of celebrating how long you’ve been on Twitter,  let’s celebrate how much more transparent our government h… https://t.co/KuObLt4hsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now who did this nonsense???  I love Snoopy! #NotFunny https://t.co/sqq3bOneJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Evacuation orders in Guerneville to be lifted after worst storm in 22 years - San Francisco Chroni… https://t.co/wBiUU85tSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see this headline the intro to ultralight beam plays in my head]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, because either @HamillHimself would use the Force or @MarkRuffalo would get angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe @undisputed Only 1 game plan calls for @TG3II to get less than 20 touches; the one where he is injured.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @trashtvaddict @pitsagainst @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_… https://t.co/dBiGe1CXM5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Turgeon in 0-19 when coaching on the road against ranked teams. Tonight would be a great night to end that str… https://t.co/YgdJMe6hQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metsandnesfan @FScopers @RealTarone @FullyPoseable #figurebath https://t.co/90lrWemuFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[walked out of wawa with 3 quesadillas, picture 3 quesadillas and myself eating concrete.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy This is a end of the great wall of China! The tide still rises and falls at the exact same height t… https://t.co/3HfBTCKRIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Hey good for you. Did someone on your staff tell you the difference between a city and a state?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeJessAriane But he's the emergency contact for lots of random kids.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because I know for a fact that #AlyssaMilano is an ally for both #POC and the #LGBTQ community. People need to do s… https://t.co/lQQVF9aHSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people can’t get actual shivers down their spine when they listen to music and I feel SO BAD for you, like damn you really missing out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathalieR71 @RyanBJackson1 If you add a #microbit on your knees and "when it is level plus one".  It would be a gr… https://t.co/MXcEuomBHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join me and party with me in honor of my birthday. I will have bottles and tables at my party festivities EVERY nig… https://t.co/idHXyalDcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@breee_castilllo oof why you changing? then might aswell hope to Verizon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@makemecumplz Nailing that hole and ain't holding back is it good to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be @100blackmen!! @ Paris Hotel and Casino Resort https://t.co/mqna7Aq5vB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Parma, OH? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/ZtTRoOmySz #Marketing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arretche13 @ESLRainbowSix @Soto650 @EquinsuOcha650 BRUHHHHHHHHHHHHHSJSKXGDJS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is the difference in black power! And white supremest! They both are Racist! We need. More Native Americans in… https://t.co/NBla3uRyKT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tailgate—1948-1953 series Chevy five-window https://t.co/rl9VVzU4zi @hotrodmagazine https://t.co/dLejXaVWbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[People can have their opinion and beliefs on being a vegan/vegetarian, but nothing irks me more than the constant i… https://t.co/iPcChOOYTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking news Harper will sign with  @SFGiants and not @whisox or @Phillies  8yrs for $320 million]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DwyaneWade really retiring after this season...? https://t.co/of8txyQ1yO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Cheney @DineshDSouza @IlhanMN Don't play sanctimonious with us #AOC, your obvious effort to reverse blame won'… https://t.co/bi9meXSXHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr As long as the GOP suffers from "Oval Sphere Disfunction" don't hold your breath waiting for someth… https://t.co/W7fR5l0mma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds thank you for sharing the tribute of John Candy. Have been binge watching him today. #MaximumEffort #ImaMog]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now abideth faith, hope, charity, these three; but the greatest of these is charity. 1 Corinthi… https://t.co/pxMYoNfTzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[nvm crisis averted... and it was truly a crisis because the guy in front of me has already made two separate compla… https://t.co/v4WOFzz0Yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every speaker today giving shout outs to @AndreaSCousins. All well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WaqarVick True, but the good news is that most of what passes as legal writing sucks. So don’t ignore all your old… https://t.co/IchpEdtGQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consistency produces Understanding. Your regular? Indeed King.#freetrenton @ Health is Wealth https://t.co/hyUpynX3zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A wonderful reminder that even in the darkest of times, light still prevails. Happy Sunday from Charleston. https://t.co/yYMGZ7vF7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masrod @dannysullivan I ordered fries animal style once... my cardiologist was not impressed. I think he ordered a… https://t.co/LTrpyxsLSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful day for a rescue with SARA, @PimaSheriff and @RuralMetroSo_Az! https://t.co/WHwydFCnLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[No way they’re getting Machado or Harper, those dudes are expensive as fuck, they want those 10+ year contracts, pl… https://t.co/8Wnh9OkMEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a blast at @PlaylistLive!  Make sure you go follow my IG: TheRobRyan to see tons of Picts and vids with my f… https://t.co/E5nO3wnOvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BackwardsHatTim @sheamccormick Joe Izzo? Bob Izzo? Not sure about them. Don’t quote me, but I’m pretty sure Tom Iz… https://t.co/nUOgekv9PI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBallScientistX @xsnyderman @BNets247 @DaRealDom15 @TJmiranda @NBACycle5 @IloveBa96385444 You have to exchange ban… https://t.co/gAyJiFkP6Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oie @AztecaDeportes @AztecaSiete  x k los juegos de @chivas de local en el azteca 7 Hd no tiene sonido 😤🤔🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[#happybirthday 🎂🎉#elizabethtaylor @elizabethtaylor @ETAForg @ Hancock Park, Los Angeles https://t.co/R4U9ZFNtu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who are psycho: bites ice cream, eats jelly filled donuts, likes spam, reformed horse girls, doesn’t like pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent my morning with two icons in the sports world @juliefoudy @Simone_Biles and #funfact between all three of us… https://t.co/UtexMHHpI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JojoV2005 @RealitySteve Let’s see if they are together in a month when this shit show ends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC’s Mind Is "Blown" Over Not Being Allowed To Receive Gifts https://t.co/m3IoO3ovP3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley @BrunkerCyn @realDonaldTrump #He’s stacked the deck there]]></document><document><![CDATA[#art #supportlocalart #printmaking #printmakingstudio #bigoakpress #fargo #northdakota #nodak #moorheadproud… https://t.co/fR2A6IqWpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, the thick heavy fog last night along with temperatures in the teens make for a beautiful sight today. I'm grat… https://t.co/hCwinhRPda]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alex Bacevicius day is done with 5 2/3 innings of work! Frank Morales checks in on the hill.  8-3 Eagles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moon Rise over the Napa Valley #tombrichta #tombrichtaphotography #tombrichtaworkshops #travel #travelphotography… https://t.co/uhpgbMHZne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnmarianony @WilliamBibbiani @bryantchirper @CanceledCast Can't forget their small, yet inane parts in #DCCab lo… https://t.co/PJ8Q6Eb40T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JokkeNevalainen @FinnProspects What do you think his NHL ceiling can be for fantasy? Points only? 80+?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#storytelling The Human Superpower - Georgina Cooper Friedlos  https://t.co/2K1VAjzlq8 via @TEDTalks #journalism… https://t.co/M2NQzDy8wH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scrufacejean That may have been the *weakest* apology I have ever seen! @thatsdax not sorry he’s just trying to sa… https://t.co/brcxQb0atf]]></document></documents></author>