<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@madisongtaylor1 Apply for UCA housing &amp; you’ll start feeling a lot better...recommended by 10/10 doctors. Or use some essential oils]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was hard. Depression kept me in bed for a lot of it. But I got things done and took care of my dogs and made… https://t.co/1u7ujPWEFM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snapchatbabies part 2! #filters #snapchat #snapchatfilters #twins #twinlife #babies #instababy #instagood… https://t.co/bB6FNgzc10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barkbox I’ve written a few polite requests re:status of an order that should have been delivered at least two days… https://t.co/Q0H1jIk5i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg @marcorubio Good question !!  He certainly did NOT show much sympathy for the families of the slai… https://t.co/Q46fKrSpp8]]></document><document><![CDATA[got to spend the morning with the woman I’m seeing and now have two articles about sodomy to write happy #PresidentsDay]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #US. It seems like not a big news. But it is. 😁. I lived on the base. Food opinions for our military folks are… https://t.co/ARzRZCYcE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm two fucking seconds away from naming my next dog Goose. Like this has gotten ridiculous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliezapata_ Im convinced this whole Jordyn thing is a publicity stunt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@savefacenj do you think someone would call corporate if i played merci in this starbucks it’s my las day]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that you are focusing on her butt is clearly showing that SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH YOU NOT HER. Sweetie sto… https://t.co/OlNTX6x94G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Various California shelters: DNA/DNR/Ban Jonny Preston! - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/DWO4qPbHN5 via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Saturday Night (DJ Pezz Urban Mix) by @aaroncarter on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/E5Ez8uvMqz https://t.co/phmqI1E9F8]]></document><document><![CDATA[So basically the other two girls are going to be 2nd favorite....awkwardddd #TheBachelor https://t.co/2dQEOMgOH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is corny but whenever I’m not feeling well, mentally or physically - I find so much comfort in looking at vide… https://t.co/0EzGY0J85M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to meet this beautiful lady at the airport in Austin! We were both on the same flight to Chicago heading to see… https://t.co/uyplzYxXmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took my hair out of the twists #naturalhair #kinkycurly #blackhair #hairtexture #twostrandtwist #selfie #smile @… https://t.co/9syGjAkP7D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twins boys as this week’s Tuesday feature! 💕 I may just over share this week (I love twins!) 👬 @ Boston, Massachuse… https://t.co/SnOjw3LtUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonSandler3 I'm in Henderson, by the airport, it's snowing but not sticking... yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 Look, he IS fat! I don’t care what he weighs as long as he quits lying about it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheToyInsider @JAKKStoys Thanks for the chance. Happy Valentine's Day guys !! #tweets4toys #JAKKSToys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalesforceMing @jenwlee @cloudysan @trailhead @SalesforceMing So if I understand you correctly, I can updated one… https://t.co/pn4AIrzqSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow him and do what you need to do and welcome him to the family #ohyeahyeah @Brayden04331461]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting impatiently for this picture! This is labelvevents ❤️🦄🌱 @ The Asbury Hotel https://t.co/3Ovpt8nf2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ermd2000 @jeffdow @Sizzler_USA @SadiesNewMexico Sadie’s overrides a lot of places!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the outside world these tests need to go and for god sakes I wish some politician or even if the president had t… https://t.co/18gqjjZrPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Would have loved a job paying 6 figures where I produced no results for 2 years.... 🤷‍♀️🤗🤗.  I know I can do it👍.… https://t.co/QnUMyUKheT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaVigeland @Bakari_Sellers Wow when will these out of touch pundits just stop with the BS ..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna do like 2 hours of cardio to make up for all of my poor decisions on food lately 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donetodeath @nancyjosales @garage_magazine Real Nancy Jo Sales heads only.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so proud of these amazing teens who spoke truth to power today. I kvelled like a mama during their speeches.… https://t.co/lyeYWq3iOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm spreading the word and helping my buddy who also loves 🌮. 3 years is longer than I was without a family. Let's… https://t.co/lIDHbWO23h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero ir de compras soo baaaad pero tambien tengo que ahorrar para europa ptm]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re off from work for ONE day and you come back and people beg you not to take off again.... really makes you feel needed ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edutopia We watched the 5 Keys to Rigorous Project-Based Learning. #pblchat #nccat #nccatpbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried 🍊 #orangevanillacoke twas good 🌩🌧🐸🍀🌴🌳🌲🌉 #March #Mandarinmuseum #MandarinPark #JAX #Florida #betseyjohnson pur… https://t.co/Q6v3Xx16sP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You were never there! You are too chicken shit to fight for your country, even as the @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phyllisj1003 @PollyPapaya @CandiceRoyer @AussieDebBell @NAudrey_ST @chefrocky413 @CunningSq16 @BlkSantaX… https://t.co/KpUxssMWWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess my uterine lining is extra juicy 🤷🏻‍♀️ lmao some guys are so fucking dumb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@samtwomilton I have mine through 4 years of college and haven’t had a storage issue!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump How can you run from Prison? And, she is probably sick of you bringing up the same old stuff, that… https://t.co/AH4MKk5825]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidSabourin72 you are still amazing after all these years. You are a part of the puzzle that @FromWilliamE is a… https://t.co/x8RRQOuthh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now is Norm Spaulding, “riffing” off of this article “Paradoxes of Constituitonal Faith” (3 Critical Analysis of La… https://t.co/C1g76IM2GQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@John_F_Kennnedy @VectorSigma4 @StormIsUponUs @BusyElves What is this? It showed up in my list on You Tube? https://youtube/0caht81PqhM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divIIbaseball @TusculumBSB @DeltaStateBSB @UNGBaseball @NGUBaseball @FleetBaseball @NMHU_Athletics @ChowanBaseball… https://t.co/hM4nd5XAPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SWDAChat A2- School leadership need to make instructional rounds on a regular basis- with the help of a strong lea… https://t.co/sPv2kEX9IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@datinaaa Lmaoooooo no ma’am I’m a submissive lmao and if it’s not sexual I’m not with it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@syswarren I have something that can help you, me, your company, and the world. Contact me!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to bed a little after midnight. Just woke up. Realized it doesn’t smelled like corn beef in my apartment (I wa… https://t.co/AcNrTknux5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StressFreeKids @AmyMorinLCSW @TwinningatHome @LoveEdMovement @FRCenters @YourTrvlHndbk @RootsOfAction… https://t.co/I8xy0jEa9p]]></document><document><![CDATA[ME ESTOY CAGANDO VERGACION PERO SEGURO VOY A CAGAR Y SALE RICARDO MONTANER #VeneuelaAidLive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goerahyuck @8675309Carson @Accounttoreado1 I never said you were heartless? I said your comment was disheartening.… https://t.co/5bgds7ofvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman “Let’s go, Fatty”. This works occasionally on my husband.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, couldn't help it... @ Elkins Cleaning https://t.co/m2PKGblq04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KereshmaGhani I was about to reply to your tweet with this exact sentence 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not Deja vu we are back for Pond Hockey weekend ✌🏼#FargoPondHockey https://t.co/4S7W9hogIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ask my daughter Claire to choose between pink or purple nail polish, she always says both. 💅 Then she adds g… https://t.co/H3xPtATkj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you pay your own phone bill, you don't HAVE to talk to anybody. If the bill ain't paid you ain't hearing from me either way soooo 🤷🏾‍♂️♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[DonorsChoose twitter friends check out this wonderful giving page 😁👏🥳⭐️⭐️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoishesMom PLS HELP KUDO, #nycacc! https://t.co/Hb8BxMZyRL or mustlovedogsnyc@gmail.com or PM 4 asst 2 #foster or… https://t.co/BixKMdpY48]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pte @jguaido aplique artículo 187 #11 de la Constitución Nacional. Intervención humanitaria Ya.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend and I  enjoying some together time in the snow.  #HeIsMyHeart  ❄️🌈☀️🥰🐕🐾 @ Edenbrook Conservation Area https://t.co/kMtie01Zqv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngryDem1 @rolandscahill @tonic516 He only watches Fox Not News don't need the remote for that!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calebryantt @DeansGir1 AGREED!! No one should be made to feel less of a person just bcz of something or someone th… https://t.co/SmP6yCzeKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskPlayStaion  when ever I turn on my PSVR on the PSVR box flashes red]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #gorow @orangetheory today. Currently sitting a top the Female leaderboard at my studio with 1156m. Going to s… https://t.co/1hGa0hKgu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[ever notice how when your happy you jam to the beat but when your sad you listen to the lyrics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @CA_DMV Please thank and congratulate Angie working window 2 in your Culver City office today for being profess… https://t.co/u2jP5wd0ge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lavozsandinista Gracias a Dios, de vos no hay NADA que aprender, por que sos mala sangre, mala madre, mala persona… https://t.co/rgaQp8iOUh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Trump contradicts himself - if he's building the wall already why the emergency - he never makes sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s been a crazy season full of ups and downs but I’m so so ready for nationals with my girls and my team… https://t.co/qWFwJ1fTtD]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s because her and her family are evil that some of the stuff she learned from her crooked family another waste]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RocketShip726 @rebeccaalpert1 Exactly Gwen's dress. Also she ripped off Miley Cyrus' short blonde haircut (from wh… https://t.co/W1I1m2VVQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe the journey isn't so much about becoming anything. Maybe it's about unbecoming everything that isn't really y… https://t.co/PJ4U1Wo0nS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zack_Moody32 Bred by Neff Livestock. This little dude is pretty nice! #showlambgeekhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schroeder has other plans... #catsofinstagram #schroeder #streaming #daburntbisket #twitch #twitchstreamer… https://t.co/qxO7QazXbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to land a job like "Food Service Lead Worker - UPMC Susquehanna -- Lock Haven Food" at Aramark? Applicant trac… https://t.co/9s8w1fXP4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[My thumb is the only finger twitching on my whole hand wtf. That’s not normal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another one of our favorite eateries here on the island. 😋🍽🎉 https://t.co/QThS13fUlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please someone do a feature on hand knits of the Iditarod. @ravelry @ClaraParkes]]></document><document><![CDATA[mine and @WesleyyBoles’s new baby, our sweet boy sure did steal our hearts!🐾💙 #bluepit #bolespartyof3 https://t.co/03PbQ5NLfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[saturday night plans: figure out how the pats can extend brady, pay flowers, win the draft and land a top threat re… https://t.co/4lrTRUEdWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TarynDeVere @beannfatale @Lady_FMP Training doesn’t work, I don’t think. They need therapy and support and supervi… https://t.co/xOzNVKFqGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean painful to watch. Im glad I watched out of order bc I never would have continued to watch this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyLevi I just watched the full trailer and it is amazing. Definitely the best part of my day so far. Everyone… https://t.co/SkOePUe2CF]]></document><document><![CDATA[no one :  colton to everyone: i think i’m falling in love with you  #TheBachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[WE'RE OPEN!  COME ON IN! @ In A Pickle Restaurant https://t.co/cCN7w0XSIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I kept waiting for everything to come crashing down today, but guess what? It didn't. In fact, today went suprising… https://t.co/qcqUHrQ8uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[when u get excited to find a sports bra on sale to match ur leggings but it’s lowkey a little different of a patter… https://t.co/TOc1p9k5lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers are back and life is good again (also still obsessed with Joe) ❤️ https://t.co/bLSCEkef5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[interpreter services. The demand was huge and we felt we could make a difference.”  Makaram said, “We have a team o… https://t.co/PdnksChPxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grubhub get your shit together. I love you in the city, but you suck in the suburbs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yazzy_Music @JohnAdamsMusic1 If I were there I would come to the show for sure lioness angel]]></document><document><![CDATA[#teambucay #lovewhatwedo #happyvalentinesday @ Dr. Vivian W. Bucay https://t.co/1hgctw1Hj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalRadioDay Spent many years immersed in the world of radio, most of my childhood, and later in life th… https://t.co/T9OkEq6hpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Sandmann should seriously consider hiring a different lawyer who's more interested in presenting the s… https://t.co/uM6AaXlWqo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#needed #ourfavorite #myhidingplace @ Taqueria Don Pepe https://t.co/cBfJZENCVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I said it once, and I’ll say it again. NOTHING GOOD EVER HAPPENS AFTER 3 AM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missbadexample You’ll keep going and if you don’t there are non-gym ways to stay active; doesn’t make you a quitter in any sense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning. 🌞 Not to overshadow the excellence of last night, but it took Spike Lee 30 years to win an Oscar. I’m… https://t.co/pmU77iGkqz]]></document></documents></author>