<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[.@MichiganDEQ close to issuing permit to start pumping in Texas Township.  Permit could come as early as next week… https://t.co/M6ZlKA2oRj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorrorMOfficial @sabotek @capitalyoga @Ont_Ombudsman @PeelPoliceMedia They didn't need to send a second alert sayi… https://t.co/B5hI8yUJ6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last ski day for the season! @ Catamount Mountain Resort https://t.co/ulbdRYYjmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Golf simmy (@ Sydney R. Marovitz Golf Course in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/mjt3sEUMk6 https://t.co/kf1tmJpCIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rbpothier @murphymike JFK and #AOC would disagree a on social and other issues , but both proposed 70% tax on high… https://t.co/75oy9Npkrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliandrews73 Me, hopefully. And I don't know who you've been hanging around up there, but you should keep better company 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[Outstanding piece by Kim-Mai Cutler on the latest salvo in San Francisco's long-running battle over housing, develo… https://t.co/ZTpUXlwTSe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muensterman coming up clutch down the stretch. The Bruin guard hits a mid range shot in the paint to give Belmont a… https://t.co/mL7LcA0K2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @CaptainMarvel #movie review:  Go see this film! Stop getting hung up on the politics. Do yourself a favor and g… https://t.co/ZyM90KGNT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[We also shouldn't have to pay several million dollars for each of Trump's many many golfing trips. Since his office… https://t.co/bd4W24mZWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coreyplatt @Redistrict Right, if they still ID/reg as GOP will they vote in D primary?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alcohol! This cocktail is called an "Okinawan Woodpecker"; Patron Blanco, Prickly pear, lime, Sparkling Mojave Grap… https://t.co/GbGmPf3MBM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chaos erupts, 2 arrested during Texas execution   https://t.co/ATQdAAixfJ via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProgressNow_NC And have an independent review of prior voting data. Not the first rodeo for @NCGOP and absentee ballot fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow @PRG_Golf for your chance to win limited-edition Arnold Palmer-themed gear. @MyGolfSpy https://t.co/spJ9Ymuuda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyTaylorRock  can't wait for Aug 28th to gett good brother corey but the real question is will you be on… https://t.co/G4OBhx5gCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AuthNJMcConnell You’re still holding on to that? He stood there politely, while that activist got in his face?  An… https://t.co/ND4znD0lEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww yeah! These Max's took me to the stage for the #divastrong show tonight. Killer show! #killerkicks… https://t.co/850mFwXA9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckettL @etanthomas36 @krassenstein No, you, like Smollett, have created a fantasy n narrative in which you belie… https://t.co/jfBJtQIKqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you ever get so high that you think if you refresh your checking account balance enough times that a large sum o… https://t.co/nrMvmo5E5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BRG_66 @TarrinAlmanza @undisputed @RealSkipBayless And you're a Republican. That says it all. Why do you even root… https://t.co/7b9ublhQNy]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the wise words of uncle Kenny Chesney, "I never wanted nothing more"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bingo! And the rest of the Trump crime family are all guilty of raping our country as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee Question is when they go to @amsupdates will they still be upfront or struggle like Chevy did last year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulZeise Forget about all this launch angle crap and just teach timing and contact, Shortening the swing, etc. if… https://t.co/b2BYt3823D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luminiux Las coronado de cajeta, si me descuidan cinco minutos me acabo la tira]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr. President, no one believes you brought up this subject with Vietnam leaders. What a pure self serving claim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthanOPry @Flirt4Free @Flirt4FreeGuys @F4Fmodels @belamionline @Belamichat @QueerMeNow Ethan, you are extraordinary]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Worship Leader Roadshow made a stop at First Baptist Church, Alexandria, VA, where Pastor Roger McGee led a glo… https://t.co/rATQuuZhgl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a really good idea:  Optional separate time zone feeds for @twitter. For example: you have your regular feed… https://t.co/UoMDBYnEqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgeller @rez512 @ChuckWendig It's really amazing that other people are alone on Valentine's Day and we aren't tbqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Jetside and off to #Vegas with my lady! remax, ARE YOU READY!? Looking forward to dropping the mic for both the… https://t.co/ZOXAPYkR5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united it’s been a miserable day at the gate here at MBS...but it would’ve been unbearable without Jane and the gr… https://t.co/sbApL2gcgZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormNondo Totally get it dude! Thanks for inquiring and sharing :) please don’t hesitate to let me know if you nee… https://t.co/WA6ryIzTLa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesertEaglet9 Get a milkshake from the ice cream place across from the coffee shop #SnaxManRecommendation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vote for Paul.  Even my rwnutjob friends. If only so KWT loses   https://t.co/jRPlcojA5k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw Maelyn five years ago in NYC. I knew she was magic then. I’m glad @johnlegend agrees. Good luck Maelyn!… https://t.co/ebRQgrHNUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AC360 @andersoncooper Hallelujah..Since when they kept any promise except Building a Wall, Democrats will be Stupi… https://t.co/UvIYqmVJKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlieDaniels No surprise to us who have good ole common cowboy logic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missp14 You’re one of those rare Bama fans who support all their teams?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MickShuran South Dakota! Here is what this looks like https://t.co/xJDCbwR3hS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelastpinkcar @realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Dershowitz went to the dark side years ago.  Just a shill for Trump and Israel these days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrisco113 @deptulahasrage This has nothing to do with football, Chris.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioAttolini Amigo Antonio.. no se desgaste con el 18 % de la población ya que el 82% tenemos gracias a dios ..… https://t.co/0ydzuCFTDN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me vs Me. All other factors are external. @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/oMj3THfiZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deadlynitshade If you like rock five finger death punch!!!! Great group!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today 12 years ago, this little man came into my life. Love watching the man you are growing into. Love you buddy. https://t.co/ljw6s1khaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anastasjoy @MuiMui2010 @nytpolitics Ovanka biggest fan remains Cilizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[See you in LA... ☀️😎✈️🌇#NASPA19 #SAPros #Clemson #UNCSA @ JW Marriott Los Angeles L.A. LIVE https://t.co/ehzhId7oV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Raiders are a halfway house for past-their-prime veterans and problem children.  Oh, they’re perfectly capable… https://t.co/FYFpbkvw2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I agree with Jeff Greenfield's argument that it's a missed opportunity to have @FoxNews host a Dem debate.… https://t.co/tGGZlAjj6Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My headlight would Go out soon as I get to chesterfield 🤦🏽‍♂️ Wrong place to be riding round with no L’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enchanted_wx Not a bad low-level environment up there. Some short CAPE and 15kts of 0-1km shear. 0-1 SRH in excess… https://t.co/PRDE2k24Hd]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my expectations for #Oscars2019 are low. Between no host and a leading contender whose highlight was a 15-minute… https://t.co/Cs8sHmLlX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is truth that hides the fact that there is none. Simulacrum. April 2019. https://t.co/dGNIgWroCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GMPaiella @Thymbraeus I would not understand the desire, but I'd try to be supportive of their life choices... Wai… https://t.co/LoYZwRXL7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[45 Day Dry Aged Ribeye, Beluga Lentils, Sweet Pickled Peppers, Bordelaise  #tuccis  #steak  #steakfordinner… https://t.co/PqeptoaRmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s moments like these that warm my ❤️ heart... this is what I live for... nothing better than putting a smile on… https://t.co/2enkZJ6zIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THR @EllenPage Sounds like someone isn’t getting enough attention at home so she has to be the center of attention… https://t.co/sSX6knT0Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Auckland Art Gallery director Gregory Burke under investigation for alleged workplace harassment | Newshub https://t.co/UAhCh6rSJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNBCJosh @benedictevans Seriously lol I was reading this trying to find the joke but then I realized he was serious]]></document><document><![CDATA[The humorous effect of thusly was wise but some may overlook and take this post seriously.]]></document><document><![CDATA[aye what wrong with you?   nothing.  aye shawty what’s wrong with you?!  i SAID nothing.   ight.  I JUST THINK ITS FUNNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AMoffRetail Thought I was safe...(cred @rtmccombs) https://t.co/zOR7cHzX0L]]></document><document><![CDATA[#baby #babynames #babyshower #pickaname #bornon #birthday #hate #hatepeople #delivery #specialdelivery… https://t.co/uTtkZwzJUN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BarackObama the Florida army national guard used me to take out the secret service at 19.  For TT shit judgement d… https://t.co/YWnaY1NWMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm getting my Patty Melt with #RegularFries. Patty deserves it she's been sideless for TOO LONG.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coffee Station set up ready to go 💯💯💯☝🏻☝🏻✅✅😜😜😜🤘🏻🤘🏻👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻☕️☕️😋😋😋😋 @ Comfort Inn &amp; Suites https://t.co/AT8d95XcUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACollinsPhoto @WPFFA_481 @NiagRegPolice @FCWFES That’s right next to the post office, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Met the First Black Woman to have her own show on thetravel_channel ! The epitome of a Lifeaholik, she gets it in.… https://t.co/l4vgtVTZat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo  https://t.co/QAlD7JTQ0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to my first body pump class in over a year. Having a lot of anxiety about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidacoil @phylogenomics @ryneches Awesome. Could we get some system details? Being used for experiments for MoBE… https://t.co/IVxvQpjrZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarleeDanielle2 I’ve had a girlfriend at one point in time  or another]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheNotoriousMMA @propertwelve1 got me through it! Can't find anymore @TheNotoriousMMA send me a case of that… https://t.co/xS53EODpde]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @CobosInsCenter Post-Match Interview with @WrestlingElyria junior @mickburnett02 after he won the 132-pound sta… https://t.co/ysk5XutwF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mkraju Oh, and for being a 'senior Congressional Correspondent' sure sounds like editorializing as opposed to "journalism"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how easy spoilers are to find on the internet. Additionally, I hate how dumb I am for reading them. Sigh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics @RightHookUSA The Dems do that to themselves without Trumps help...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLWARREN526 @the_travis_bull @VOL_de_MORE @KySportsRadio Is that your cousin? If so I’m just curious which side of… https://t.co/WUmeJMEMxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 @ImabitcSumtimes There u go killing children .on yur backs. Govt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ckparrot It’s would be ok. We won’t be competitive next year. We have time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job @Viborgs4395 in your @FRCTeams competition at Belleville HS today! Good luck the rest of your day and hop… https://t.co/VVH9vx34PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyArmagh Best news I’ve heard all week. “Freedom of speech” does NOT mean freedom from consequences. #cdnpoli #abpoli #ConvoyOfStupidity]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Brian Solis book release of #lifescale (@ The Eleanor in Austin, TX w/ @frankgruber @dberkowitz)… https://t.co/GO3LCzNtEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 Mariota,Corey Davis,Taywan Taylor,Dion Lewis, Walker, Henry!!!!!! With you added to this group would be impec… https://t.co/AYB6eLxaGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VividVivka It’s your fucking birthday and he’s asking YOU to give him a gift?!? Man fuck that guy and his bullshit]]></document><document><![CDATA[She's so cute and fierce just like her grandmother n the rest of the Kardashian]]></document><document><![CDATA[@page88 @latimesopinion Not necessarily. Lots of Hitler's supporters went to the gallows after WWII in terminal loy… https://t.co/J4JO209Iwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGBT community got me suspended and now they’re either silent about Jussie Smollett after being VERY LOUD AND WRONG… https://t.co/uKWRIs1eDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@movement_speech @MikeStuchbery_ MIKE WAS NOT THERE. You're a lying sack of shit. And why didn't he answer? at 11pm… https://t.co/x66J51O9b8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I setup a VPC with both public and private subnets today with a bastion host to link them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grumpy_Pudding It’s almost certainly going to turn to ice at some point tonight and I am displeased. https://t.co/ZXHDgheSjg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #VAMISSIONAct should be implemented in a way that puts veterans first! Learn more &amp; tell lawmakers here: … https://t.co/v2BnA8uG53]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snixxrivers @buknerd @katyknowskungfu and I will come and give that person a stern talking to]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xjaketylerx @SpencerWDMW I mean, to be fair, I’m completely biased here. I was born in California so In-N-Out is l… https://t.co/EWWZVWSGHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bugaboo_baller That's one of my fav bands, and that song is from one of my fav albums 🍀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcknight0 You got this! The good news, I don’t think readers will get tired of sex anytime soon!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJA_Cortes To your credit, you’re doing a better job in the selfie game than @HunterDrewTFA, but that’s mostly due… https://t.co/1oSmv2pTEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally have no words.  @whitesox you better call Scott boras and tell him to name a freaking price for @Bharper3407]]></document></documents></author>