<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HeyMo517 @AntoniaSchmitt4 @BethHeartP @wwwbigbaldhead @emikoko896 @SuzieSaysPlease @smoking_reedus @Cheryl_W61… https://t.co/rvvke0fvjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new guard of VC at SXSW @HeatherHartnett @suzywillow @marinanicolah on how they raised their funds, sectors the… https://t.co/KqICu3BDa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im getting frustrated with myself. This is literally impossible to pick 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagotribune look at #ClarencePage #author #columist #pulitzerprizewinner  @fox32news #spincycle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackie Litynski wins her semi-final bout 15-13 and will now be fencing in the final round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@linkedinselling Thanks. Got in eventially. The session started about 6 minutes late. Seemed to be a canned session… https://t.co/up936fgbHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fuxinchen @WinnieWoo17 @Sweetdr17415074 @JoeyJoyful @HoudiniDancing @lynnsterlyn @CuriousMonty @BeatrixAnn1… https://t.co/tkIdQihYPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bdew @1Unaturalsoul @ACTBrigitte @TheDemocrats I'm going to have to study up on the Constitution. You, my friend,… https://t.co/cSKiZD3gF3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaNaGsFunkyJunk @Tolltac lee county Alabama. Primarily smiths station and Beauregard. Many are still missing, home… https://t.co/xGuAQu52e6]]></document><document><![CDATA[tax refund: deposited  savings account: alive and well speeding ticket: paid mental health: slightly less stressed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJTBurton @coachzachholt @CoachHiggz @sisto Great win for our Men's program!!!  💪👍😊❤🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory Susan Collins can never just " make up" for getting us the sexual predator Kavanaugh in the first place. Inexcusable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estamos entendiendo mal a Alberto, el problema es que no hay cascos a su medida.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenJaneNelson  and the Texas Senate for the amendment including librarians in the raise.  #txlege… https://t.co/0KJ8eDMMOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to go home and see my dogs stupid fat face w all it’s wrinkles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st to my favorite person in the world! I love you more each day, and I could never have asked for a better… https://t.co/2IhQ8MsUiU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjbowles4 @ChrisBragdon @joseph_alberson @somethingfun08 @Raymond52842250 @Sweeetchis @CherylAndrews59… https://t.co/RNAnpItM74]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MandyluvNj Joe didn’t answer the question so I don’t know where *NSYNC would’ve been on the list. Hopefully the top.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaitlynMKE Have you ever tried adding cinnamon to your coffee? I’ve found that it sweetens it up just enough witho… https://t.co/fIrllu4OIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sorry I didn't get to tweet like I wanted to had to lay down but I must say I enjoyed #RAW tonight I knew two w… https://t.co/PxAEqGOUnV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t need to tell@them it’s #NationalNapDay @CatsOfRAWdance https://t.co/7lOY2HSuuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was a BEAUTIFUL day‼️ ✖️Eyeliner on FLEEK✖️ @GerardCosmetics Eternal Eyeliner is where it’s at🙌🏾🧡  #makeup… https://t.co/uDc1g5lMgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was für eine Nacht!  Dinner mit Gwyneth Paltrow, Party bei Snapchat, Tanzen zu Live-Musik, Nachtgespräche im Hotelg… https://t.co/gQNRV7Oafo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what day it is??!!! #Daytona500 #daytonaday 😎🏁❤🇺🇸🍻  we are having a party! Walking tacos on the menu!!! Who a… https://t.co/4Ok1JmaMoj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for an amazing teacher to win $500, and you can, too. Please vote! @RUSDInstruction  @PrincipalTicha https://t.co/PXnJIsyyB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta read this book! My son has been asking lots of questions about our “blended” racial identities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MessMinchin3 @burochaw14 @JSumagaysay07 Okay forgiven. Haha. At least typo. Hindi parang hatred na inulit pa 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrittBakerTV I love love love ur take on this!!   What?!? What!?!  🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #ThirtyThursday! Help support the campaign of Vanessa Joseph for North Miami City Clerk. Vanessa is passionat… https://t.co/0yDg5ohqNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool morning in Maine today. Cat is active trying to warm up I bet! Not much on the docket for this fine day. Colde… https://t.co/0bGerOpIKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[stand in front of a shelf of history, he asked where the non-fiction was.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I am F-I get screaming and ripping out my hair by the roots! When will this madness end?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorriefencil @muttoo_sharon Ok now you need a office too so you can escape lol!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StateDept @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo I feel so ashamed of they way Congress behaved today. Your doing a gr… https://t.co/FC9gbhZHYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacquelineDax @savannahhraine @chrisulmer I still dont see how turning off the comments is going to keep pedophile… https://t.co/DrlQMLrQXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello, 21 year old self! @DiverStar asked our panel at @Omnicom Most Promising University to give our best advice t… https://t.co/c92Zg5JxkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaBaracCardio @AAHFN @MedStarHeart @LombardiCancer We are so happy you will be there !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Tulsa, OK? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/QbC85gQ0Kb #FacilitiesMgmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump The IRS is corrupt, Mueller is corrupt, it sounds like you believe Pres Trump is the on… https://t.co/1S9OKX5Oj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@batmaaaannnn @racegearcom I have been bashed for “making fun of something so serious as sex trafficking”... 😳 it’s… https://t.co/34CsIv1szE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link : https://t.co/jQ8YSAibcK  to check out this article featuring The cast of @SirensoftRealms ! I love… https://t.co/iFClk2Tdrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnoopyG7 @Zak_Bagans No slappy needs to grow up  he likes to ? #Zakbagans]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mummu1951 @WMAR2News Exactly..so sick of this...I can SEE..well, I guess they don't care..on 2 #netflix &amp;… https://t.co/UYls03erQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJackEdwards Becareful, you’re not as young as you used to be! We don’t want to be without you during Bruins games!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ripped the bottom of my shoe off as I was leaving the gym... if that’s not a sign]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 5 o’clock in the morning and conversation got boring! Because it wasn’t with @BradleyJames #goodnight]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slacker_ga01 @joegooding @Lady_Vi_2U @Barracuda_Bella @Jamierodr14 @LaylaAlisha11 @KAG4All @ArchKennedy… https://t.co/RDYXg5lSB3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@callin_bull I’m coming to @UW in two weeks to visit my son - hope we might be able to catch up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nobody has a collection of amazing human friends like @anniefryman has a collection of amazing human friends. Thank… https://t.co/lgYesOzaNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When adding new tiers to the worm bin, it's important to control your mite population. Giving it a good cleaning to… https://t.co/dPvw2e3MET]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamie_Weinstein Peter said his email from Avenatti was unsolicited. Yours was not. I generally think email, DMs, t… https://t.co/d287pzj634]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Marbles I heard you like watching people’s dogs...here a some photos of Jet 😂 🐶 https://t.co/bwk3cZ8Gao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost “Look honey! A pretty kitty!” Driving by I’ve watched people get right next to fence to watch buffa… https://t.co/oFMY6eA0Ju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdDept I live in central TX so we rarely see snow, y'all can send it down here so we can play in for a day or two. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[The drug bust at the port in Newark of $77 million of cocaine! I hate that place, it's desolate and dirty and unsafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @FRESL1brary to post 7 covers of books I LOVE with no explanations why. Each time I… https://t.co/unBVZg43CZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The public favors coming to the rescue of #science to break the infinite cycle in Washington DC of ‘cutting, cancel… https://t.co/74dTlO4r2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@classiclib3ral @ffish In the era of Trump, too many people don’t care about actual data. They have impressions and… https://t.co/9DwxgXw91K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@belladevil @Rayterrill I tried to log in and ended up locked out of my gmail, so that’s a neat trick. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baby I was on your phone when I miss your call....nahh you were in the backseat sweating like an athlete..... doing… https://t.co/nuZ9oQB5vb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got new bedding today and boiii when I tell you I might never wanna get out of bed now ... I mean it. If thought it was bad before, lmao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Tastings in the Library! The students “tasted” different books as their Appetizer, Salad, Entrée and Dessert a… https://t.co/hdZ7zqMN49]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrumpyReviewer2 A psychoanalytical Marxist analysis? The feminist in me is rolling my eyes. Especially about the “… https://t.co/J2hg2ayMb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all have those days that we just don’t eat right, or the just because. This is always in my purse and ready to g… https://t.co/ajbKMwKDzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Kate Beckinsale make out with Pete Davidson has turned my lesbianism into an act of protest, to be frank]]></document><document><![CDATA[Complaints allege horses in Wells Fargo’s iconic stagecoach program were drugged, abused.  @JStricklandWSB speaks w… https://t.co/iljG0oveJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedDoberman @Cass_C7 Her brothers &amp; sisters are bomb sniffing dogs, Iraq &amp; Afghanistan Our Troops n been adopted by handlers❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me starting to fall asleep at 11:23 after looking at my phone for hours and remembering I have an assignment on can… https://t.co/Pz2v1km580]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IncorrectPacey @KamalaHarris 1 I don't understand, 2 police need access to the secret registration files in gun re… https://t.co/nR6K6i1fTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk @BuzzFeed @colbertlateshow @Alyssa_Milano @AOC @maddow @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @BernieSanders]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been awake since 4 am.   Just got home. Can't stop thinking about a to-Do list I'm too tired to tackle. To go… https://t.co/pY6JYkH9Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allahs_SonOfMan @khamenei_ir @Pontifex @netanyahu #Witnessed #TAMFOUR #TaraAnnMoons in Jesus Name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Liver LACERATION (laceration = blunt force trauma) graded 1-5 ... lower grades can be monitored in CCU #CCRN https://t.co/9pseGtawyE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will sit through 45 minutes of inept executives trying to do regular jobs just to watch them give their money to… https://t.co/JG9SJ7cRm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jk it’s not. But I remember one time I lied to everyone that it was my birthday and they all brought me presents to school. I was DEAD 😂💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five Netflix shows everyone should watch:  5.) @NailedIt  4.) @DearWhitePeople  3.) @MakingAMurderer  2.)… https://t.co/MDdn2KxsYH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Especially not by no mf who probably don't even pay their own bill 😂🏌🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I entered the https://t.co/hFWV4WZHDA #Giveaway for a chance to win awesome prizes! https://t.co/hHY9nu57gO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relationship or friendship... my loyalty runs so deep. That’s if you give the same to me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marthatoddharv @Jessie092859463 @keanothedog @unbrokeMs1 @JCoker13 @clairermassey @nereid_niobi @ghost_kitty… https://t.co/XmtMlvLUfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belle’s first trip to the beach! 🐾🌊☀️ @ Pismo Beach, California https://t.co/DzicPPkpkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ever photograph toddlers you need to read this! Get Ready: 10 Tips for Photographing... https://t.co/Ss2n1BiKjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[My poor guy woke up with his cough even worse and now hes running a fever!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCJO_LABMOM889 @lisa_nor @Nancyb157988 @pmodlin69 @SniperK78 @Twitter I saw the new ride sis got it's a beauty!! I… https://t.co/FzUztOVPW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Young men that were innocent just a few years ago. Your not funny when you try to be and your not smart when you sh… https://t.co/5l4EdFXg2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Starbucks A homeless man was so kind to open the door and greet your customers this morning. Now he’s being sh… https://t.co/CCNSqAQX1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Autobiography of an Unrepentant Geezer  2:30 AM: Wakes up 2:35 AM: Drinks beer and whiskey 2:40 AM: Drafts dail… https://t.co/nNvWXcDEBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxcarolinanews I have always hated plastic bags. Now they want to to back to paper bags.]]></document><document><![CDATA[this truly makes my stomach turn and my blood BOIL. no one deserves to be a parent if they aren’t willing to accept… https://t.co/ulhr0t8mFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad bunnys ni bien ni mal music video is just him massaging some chick im so dead i cant stop laughing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Galentines Day!! 💪🏽🦵🏽💋🥰🤩🥳  . . #bootyday #legday #bootyandlegs #tiu #tiuteam #tiugirl #tiufa #falife… https://t.co/TxdbPwxZdR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iam_AyHole Butt, Ass, Glutes, Behind, Bottom, Culo, Bounda, Buttocks ******* https://t.co/5mZHqgUAhP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@willyofsteel Now when she brings it up to laugh at me she starts with “i know you don’t like it when we bring it u… https://t.co/cv6PRg36SS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I always feel bad for my man on Saturdays. He never gets enough sleep the night before and then has to work from op… https://t.co/ttAN2FtImo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCPandolfo They know!  You're right.  They don't care.  It's saying one person's rights are valuable than the others.  That's scary!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving this @WhovaSupport deal, great call by @SAHMtweets! Makes communicating so much easier given spotty texting… https://t.co/iF7yhkvqu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__nicole_ I only wear pink. I am a Gemini vegetarian. And so is my dog.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Im going to be single forever   Also me: curves every guy ever, doesn’t sign up for a dating website, hates men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PREACH🗣 My family came here legally, BUT we’re the same as the illegals only difference is my family had money and… https://t.co/deSF2eQMx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DorisRuffcorn @BLHSTrackField @BLXCbobcats @JoeRuffcorn Way to go Joe!]]></document></documents></author>