<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@rjprimeau @AOC Why would they? I live in Florida where there is no state income tax, we are selling our state to y… https://t.co/rfT8MkBScq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcm @the_60s_at_50 Nobody Knows is devastating. https://t.co/TtJX6p0VTu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Several @SMBaseball players on this list for Week 3 Top Performers! Go Knights! Thank you to Richard Obert for the… https://t.co/fMfrUPjvaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took 2 exams today and I’m pretty sure I bombed both of them.. good thing they’re the first exams 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahkendzior Right, while receiving $billions in free advertising from US media, Trump hooks up with the Kremlin… https://t.co/iDNqibM1h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[We would JiJi to come visit Moline! Can we set it up?  @STMath @bhatiadankur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenFox29  Good Morning.  So u like my little trailer idea? I think it would be neat. See the country then decide where to retire.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSharkDaymond I love Monday's ! Tuesday is not ready ! These are the JumpBall Pivots ! Limited Editions dropping… https://t.co/U7TrWx5MNg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big night at @nathanbillsefp tonight! I’m gonna be there a little earlier than normal, Trivia will be close to sche… https://t.co/qKbqj8Rilw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to hit the ground running. #225 #MundayFunday #NoImNotCrazy #LetsGetThisStarted #LSO #JustGetHereAlready @ Da… https://t.co/EyzQ4KrSxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I actually meet a woman I like it’s always sum that fucks it up for us.🤦🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure if I've ever had this many instruments in the place, at one time. #Saturday #ThunderBay #Music @ Thunder B… https://t.co/mXhGFesxUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nreilly_24_01 Bro we fucked! We got three players and Kuzma aint 1. We got no coach!  We gonna get some depth to o… https://t.co/dBzgTq9nrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReviveOurHearts @jenniferwilkin Needed to hear this podcast as the same goes for men of the Word.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of the 1st quarter @OssiningSchools 33 @AHSAdmiral_Al 16 @Zacchio_LoHud @KDJmedia1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cursing the T wolves is easy. Put a curse on the Warriors and put something on the line scared boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Waldo4Cy I think I still have a Mellow Johnny’s t-shirt somewhere.  Back in my Lance fandom days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s why i always do my best to make our rallies the best. i’m super satisfied with our last night rally we had a… https://t.co/406xBGdd9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBlueNovember Ahh....trickle down economics lives on, huh? Hey @dexcom as a customer (2X) of yours, this is poor f… https://t.co/3AGWhQPy9E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoreyRForrester Hehe in fairness I've heard of him, but I wouldn't know who he was if I fell over him.  I don't ev… https://t.co/kShiM28wHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations LeBron,   @KingJames   #MichaelJordan   #LakeShow   #Lakers   #NBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manoj_bansal26 @aartic02 @ArvindKejriwal @nramind @the_hindu Bloody pimps and treason artists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarolineFB I’ve never understood that. And I’m not a good guy or white knight, I just never understood how strong,… https://t.co/gOlHsSBF1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakeshelton #VoiceBlinds you’re so dang cool it’s HOT! Thanks country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The tracks are being laid.  #AutonomousVehicle challenge. #xs20109 #GameOn @vb_mehta https://t.co/SJEQ1bnpKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurdOnTheHill You are going down. Texans want border security and you sided with Dimms. You will be voted out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidkroll @DukeMBB @oskarblues Yeah, a 1 lb. small bite does not compute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#jump #lapd #lafd #la #losangeles #ca #california #drama #suicide @ South Central LA https://t.co/Vtje0jSZSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just another reason why @mcuban is one of the best owners in the @NBA and well you see who isn’t! How pompous]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicolle: "This is a masterful chess move by Andrew McCabe. He added the pres. to their open counter intelligence ca… https://t.co/8k6rYhUJAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You could see that goal coming from a mile away. Atl only chance is to get 1 goal over next 10 minutes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walmart @WalmartInc always something with @WalmartWorld. 24hr Walmart closes. So much for buying a blankets for th… https://t.co/OUCL39LsZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pretty nice hazy IPA.  On Thursdays they turn the taps over to a different brewer, and I was all in. - Drinking a… https://t.co/kcTOXwhGvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinerbocker Sounds better than a dry bowl of Great Grains and my supplements 🙄🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! I hope it’s as F-A-B-U-L-O-U-S as @CarmellaWWE is! https://t.co/NCar556ViJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok politics aside... Cant blame Donny on this one, I want one of those in my house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@americanrivers @KatePooleNRDC   @saveSFbay @SFEstuaryFriend @SFEstuary @SierraClubLP @sfner This is also an intere… https://t.co/eFlHkgnboK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man, I am wicked glad that I'm not trying to make a living off of YouTube, because it's basically impossible, espec… https://t.co/gj5IQ00YGN]]></document><document><![CDATA[And Saturday night lavacantinatc  with Desperado - A tribute to the Eagles! @ Lava Cantina The Colony https://t.co/SnRHd79qEs]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoriUrecheG @sisigolgol @AtlanticoEmi Siempre apoyando a Papá. Abrazos desde Canadá. Nos pillamos en #Carnaval2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slipped into @JoshuaTreeNPS before work started on my latest video shoot for @MoarlyCreative. https://t.co/ktTCiM50wv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming to you this April, #TheMasters ⛳️🏌️  Also, s/o to @PatMcAfeeShow and the boys for this ELECTRIC shirt. https://t.co/1jVX5c0Vl7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #MAGA #JobsNotMobs #BuildTheWall https://t.co/XgST9jN7Kv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vizekonig @JC00011 @michellemalkin Hey did you notice on your cute chart how the Dow started gaining after the Dem… https://t.co/2bmQUb2Q0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Days...for me it’s felt like a lifetime since we last dropped music or went on tour. In 4 days...I take my first… https://t.co/QDsRF657dW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vrichardson444 @RRiotReport Very nice! Appreciate the work. Would be happy with this mock!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bryce Harper agreed to a 13-year, $330 million deal -- the biggest overall free-agent contract in North American sp… https://t.co/rcKDbGNcLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does this hurt UK's chance at a 1 seed? Calipari, as he's leaving the podium: "Nah. No. Because other teams have lo… https://t.co/kuXRC0iEXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachOsterman The difference. He attacked the rim. Archie also gave him some screening action to help move the defender. Well done by both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Venice canals and we had some laughs about the past. Some things never change 😂 #bromance #venice… https://t.co/5OodBqqr8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upon further reflection and learning I have been informed that it’s spelled “putz”.  I apologize to all who may hav… https://t.co/5Y2ScKYuwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay tuned for my latest on @TheFanVerdict about the latest @TennisCanada sensation @BraydenSchnur, who, despite ob… https://t.co/kqiIFPzi9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveclay9 @jtkantor @Lucky_Diaz No apology needed! I’m always delighted to talk about Pianosaurus. Or Josh. Or Lu… https://t.co/5MBwo6xCci]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RMontea4 @CNN @jaketapper was trrump's mentor a kkk leader? https://t.co/qfUu8tUkZM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marie_yiki @PonceCanto @PsicologaDra @MuySuFrida @TuitEmil @fariasdojl1 @Jackie2theworld @Laloban62… https://t.co/L82gknP4fK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngleseyReds @BennyDSquirrel @PepitaBumper @CurlySquirrly @Pwookey @kit_orihara @TheOnionMaid @mandycrn @pyretta5… https://t.co/RSCSQkmoPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight banger here between @tadpoleslimj and @Antnyhenry @WrestleACTION1 For Super Nova]]></document><document><![CDATA[HIPÓLITO MEJÍA EL PRÓXIMO PRESIDENTE DE LA REPÚBLICA DOMINICANA, EL TODOPODEROSO ESTÁ CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en… https://t.co/Vgn4z27oDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtinctionRebe6 @MLifeforce has begun independent investigation into climatechange inaction by Dutch Minister of E… https://t.co/h74ap859VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Resorts Casino Hotel in Atlantic City, NJ https://t.co/pBhefCJJK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of Presidents Day - Which President was most influential to our Manifest Destiny? #history #presidentsday #CFISDspirit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Truth, only lies in the eyes of the beholder  Therefore, you’ll never get my pain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Unicorns Driving Army Tanks by @sauconybeer at @sauconycreek — https://t.co/S4tlr6BYkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[No Excuses! Don’t wait any longer 🙌🏼 Let’s take your business to the next level ! DM us today ! ⠀ ⠀ #BenAnderson365… https://t.co/leIUouDPFo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missy_ryan @LucasFoxNews 200 is 10% of the total number of US troops now in Syria, right? That's a significant difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bennyjohnson @AnnCoulter @TPUSA When is this piece of crap going to be arrested and thrown in jail?]]></document><document><![CDATA[3402 Rodd Field rd Church Unlimited   Come join us for some networking and education! @ Corpus Christi, Texas https://t.co/IM3BoUuhgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Golfer_Jake_78 @LegalHooks @1beardedgolfer @tonyjdear @MichaelClayto15 @gfordgolf @feedtheball A fine list of gent… https://t.co/qVNVGyw1Y5]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Only thing on Right Now like a Night Light” 🔥 Forgotten Fire https://t.co/qUkAPeUJBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting the day started on this rainy day in Los Angeles. #humday #imup #LikeABoss  . . . . #LivingForTheApplause… https://t.co/RZomxV9ZTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeBroah_ You think he’s messing up the chemistry or something? Last like 6 games have all been rough for them smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Closed out February with an easy 5.25 mile run on the #dreadmill w another hour of weight lifting (biceps n triceps… https://t.co/mIj1AMMvLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will remember those who didn't help me and those who did in my time of need. Pettyness is for the poor, but for t… https://t.co/YHMBZXIvKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the feedback on Authenticator apps! I’m now using 1Password’s 2FA feature and wow, it’s magic! Love the… https://t.co/PzFtHIVUAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why they think just bc your sick 🤒 we can’t have sex, the fuck nothing wrong with my dick #hello #morningsex #ove… https://t.co/AM62kvI1oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s Friday the Friday outta this Fridayin’ Friday 🥃 😏 https://t.co/fwSuaIGKlF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DolfDietrich Politics are personal.  I don’t ask unless I know someone well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@libertyladyusa How about those little kids with running noses,old ladies coughing,]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gunna eventually eat my words for saying this.. but for the meantime id rather have a 100 degree weather than t… https://t.co/JCOaRskE00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Empowerment Through Awareness  A Joel NR Powell film.  A documentary that showcases visible minorities that have br… https://t.co/nuf4BjQ7Uf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVED Fighting With My Family- smartly written, great performances and a true story to boot- what a fun movie! https://t.co/jRMCsi0vmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Crowdsurf In A Rubber Dinghy by @Troubadourbeer at @maxstaphouse — https://t.co/a0UEJtiQws]]></document><document><![CDATA[ck really just spit horchata all over my face...she about to get socked out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposeto be in the 80s the next couple days but then back into the 60s so they won't be out in drives yet. But a m… https://t.co/pN0E5iSNQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[So seriously @wingoz is a mastermind. Who else in media has a show named after them that they only have to show up… https://t.co/3cMWJMhI4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just look at the comments to shits crazy how they can gun up close and mid range and sometimes at long range. First… https://t.co/x278xs8oii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnYon9a @launchbasezone @samusisawesome @antiidiot5 @Firlows @Slasher No, if it hasn't grown yet, it's not gonna.… https://t.co/nv771fJKDw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueMarlon_ Man, when all is said and done, I hope Ronda gets the credit she deserves for presumably being cool wit… https://t.co/U82TmBj0yf]]></document><document><![CDATA[JV Dogs take on Bartram Trail in a Friday night tilt @ Hugh Donovan Field.  @BollesSchool #BulldogProud https://t.co/XGwLFztc7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[FINAL:  @GopherWBB beats Penn State in a blowout 97-67!  #Gophers https://t.co/Of9Jx3yk94]]></document><document><![CDATA[i understand the frustration with her, but this didnt accomplish shit. talk to her, get her to understand why shes… https://t.co/cOdrsvQMrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[CAN PEOPLE PLEASE LEARN WHAT ROOM THEY LIVE IN AND STOP TRYNA GET INTO MINE i’m abt to fuck a bitch up 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vancepantsdance I dont think so. Theres a few players that use bauer sticks dressed as easton sticks. Its bizarre,… https://t.co/jkyIO4FD8C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacMcKinseyIV @ItsMeCathi Hired these pooches to make the tRump family look more human.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A caller on @cspan acts like crooked Hillary could make a better trade deal.  He is a paid back obviously.  #maga]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just think it’s funny how you could love someone since u came out the womb but they’ll chose  a dog they found in the street over u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GatorRyan Are they on sale right now? If so I need some Tagalongs ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big Tom McClain! Always a great show! @ Oxnard Levity Live Comedy Club https://t.co/WSzccsEnmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you start walking the wrong way but you have to finish walking the block because you don’t want to go back and… https://t.co/hQ0oxHcJl3]]></document></documents></author>