<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Why do banks charge a "non sufficient fund" fee on money they know you don't have?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have 4 kids..I usually took a minimum of a week off and I don’t do nada expect hold hands, feed her ice chips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeviStraussCo  Lost my business.. after 20+ years... https://t.co/Qjo1qcaTw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcTague3 @CBSThisMorning @BernieSanders @CBSNews @docbuckley It's the 2016 election all over again..America h… https://t.co/yFBvtWInEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tbh I really couldn't pay attention to anything else going on in that scene bc HIS FACE 😵]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guy sitting in the middle of the @HOBMB parking lot: “they won’t let me in the @DropkickMurphys show ‘cuz they say… https://t.co/9MIqBK6hhV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ed Trainer at RTTF 3.0 (Roadmap To The Future) discussing our movement to the cloud at the State of Colorado. @ Low… https://t.co/R8acCAWPDr]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH.. I know how to push they buttons.. I got 'em standing up ready to hook and jab and I'm just grinning.. it drives them bananas.. :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re off. . . @ St. Louis Lambert International Airport https://t.co/NBz38viuqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[These small conferences tournament champ games reveal true passion and genuine love for the game. Just seems like i… https://t.co/wmuApgqnif]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still a little time left #LSU fans to take advantage of this offer https://t.co/xZ2uLJRH8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dwaynetanner @RailYardDawgs How did we do so well against the same team 24 hours earlier?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lead changes on each of the last seven possessions. Clemons has 21, but hs'e getting help from his friends. Eudy wi… https://t.co/cW39bOXiwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[BREAKING:  OPP asking public to avoid Moffatt St area in Pembroke because of an ongoing investigation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn't always use trigger warnings. I used to think they were a limitation on the free exchange of ideas. I start… https://t.co/tVkLU5QL59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: (minding my business walking to class 🚶) Freshman girls on the second floor: https://t.co/PcDH6mUSRX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vandyktra Seems to be a good experience for you? https://t.co/fZzS4C2KFj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourmumspants @mikenedie @zypisfy @paulmpet1 @PrinceOfAtheism @Wolfpak561 @DB_Grimwalker @AtheistsRead @Cern_lXXl… https://t.co/PSWahFSppR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like a river meets the sea, Stronger than it's ever been. We've come so far since that day And I thought I loved you then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Westward Wind by England Dan &amp; John Ford Coley, from #SoundHound https://t.co/o5MHePtvv4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come see our show come see our show come see our show!! https://t.co/IyvAlonQur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nataliauci16 Robó robó robolucionario ,te atrapé en faltas de ortografía]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would try this lineup   Guentzel.      Crosby.      Rust.    Kessel.          Malkin.       ZAR.   Blueger.… https://t.co/CxdglbifBg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seb_awyong @crystalhylai @berricha @Smolthie @piyopiyofighto @act102_to Here too: https://t.co/eUkiV7bZXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NiskayunaCSD Brian Liu wins the 100-yard backstroke @Sect2athletics boys swimming and diving championships… https://t.co/CzaroW3ZA5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau says he “should have been aware” of the erosion of trust between his office and @Puglaas.  But then… https://t.co/FVtGM0Jmvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[running but our emotions are driven, smoking to overcome that thought slowly that my mind will slowly rot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wish to take this moment to say thank you. You know what for. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of the young guns are seeing their great runs going down the tubes #NASCAR #Strat200]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NEDRPE2E Day 2 of great learning  @AndersonMillEl @tsallen2016 @ElizaJaneGordon https://t.co/XpBohsqQKO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending out Valentines Day reminder "we love Him because He first loved us"...cause and effect. 1 Jn 4:19 Works for… https://t.co/PmDmNehB2h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@j_pauleen Or we can go to country music festivals and sell pbr to white trash women who wear non ironic daisy duke… https://t.co/z2oOiMnTcc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I burned off like 1/4 of my lunch 🤔😂 #fitbit #fitbitionic #gymflow @ XSport Fitness https://t.co/0j2c8zjYVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorningJoey @WYEP Uncertain Smile THE the is a must!!!! https://t.co/XcvVct5K3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KitCorcoran @EllenCohen1 Very true Kit. There's a lot of ways to save money but for some reason Turner hates the Firefighters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KTHopkins Obama bent over backwards to give us the Muslim community votes.  That’s how you gain power. Apparently… https://t.co/mKwoO58qvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkFishkin Hey Mark any idea why they have to wait until very last minute to finalize their local tv coverage?]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re black kids caught with an ounce of weed sentenced to more prison time than Paul Manafort.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ain’t petty enough to wait until next year to thrive off an “I told you so” tweet so I’ll leave it right here]]></document><document><![CDATA[As @rachel_shorey notes, we won’t see the receipts until later. ActBlue, which processes these, has to report every… https://t.co/7HQZByu2j2]]></document><document><![CDATA[According NYPD 42 complaints of some kind of Racial or homophobic attacks 31 were proven to be fake or staged and t… https://t.co/vnSjUZ6l3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Mr President some of our elected senators and congressman have proven they are mentally unfit to h… https://t.co/qkCp2ivCJH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This national emergency bullshit is a direct attack on the separation of powers and the constitution. America is fucked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First ep of Doom Patrol was as ridiculous and as irreverent and as awesome as I expected it to be. This one could end up being a classic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @BrooklynNets players in the @barclayscenter for the #TravisScott concert are enjoying the show as much as anyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you gotta repeat your order for the third time to the cashier https://t.co/uZ1Ip5HRqM]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @DillonFrancis said “I can’t believe it’s not butter” I really felt that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She might have mixed feelings. About the Sixers losing not about me waking her up. She would feel strongly against that. But she likes Steph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma start a GoFundMe to become president. Just for fucks. Get enough support so I can make it to the CNN debates, what y'all think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a while since I’ve posted anything about Jeff Deyo. He is making such a huge impact on so many of our stu… https://t.co/pVmeArZ1RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[LNC LAVELIN PROCEEDINGS EXCUSED BECAUSE OF A DELAY IN HEARINGS! THE VERY SAME REASON ANY ADM NORMAN PROCEEDINGS MUST BE EXCUSED! NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Ya ven? Por estar burlandose de Mana, ya anunciaron nueva gira. A ver si le siguen jugando al vergas xD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to let go of who I used to be so I could become who God called me to be 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paises potenciales compradores de petroleo temen a sanciones de gobierno de EUA, ayudando a estrangulamiento financ… https://t.co/A3c4fS5OvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion No offense but you share the first name of a major league pitcher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Moore_Darnell @tressiemcphd @thenewpress @BoldTypeBooks @nytimes Thank you, Darnell! And congratulations to Dr.… https://t.co/9UC0lYcOPs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilianaVeli @cristiancrespoj @Democracia2017 PERO,LOS VA ACORRALANDO y se van quedando SIN OPCIONES! El mundo, la… https://t.co/owpCtyOyPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TigresDeNegro Yo la neta pensé que estaría más complicado, no salió y pues a chingarle en la vuelta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which of course led to the playing of several Charlie Pride and Darrius Rucker songs. Some days this job is really fun! 2/2 @DolsonPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought some golf apparel from @WMurrayGolf and there is no better combination than Bill Murray and golf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic fail by @marcorubio Thanks for calling him out @davidhogg111  Lame 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ohhhhhh yeah 😋😋😋https://t.co/5X40I5K9RW: Miley Cyrus shares racy Valentine's Day pic for Liam Hemsworth.… https://t.co/7IPSqnObda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump.… https://t.co/Pa1iTH66Ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[Survive and advance! @UMDWomensBBall onto the next round! 🏀🏀🏀 https://t.co/gRG0zrBrdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TYEGUYSMUSIC Yo hands down all I hear from u is good music bro keep doing what ur doing man so much respect can’t… https://t.co/OE9lCJWmsq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please explain how you can be in fear of your own safety when the dude you shot is sleeping and there’s SIX of you!… https://t.co/Zcy6VlPadZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simon_Kim45 @SRosencrance87 Yea I was joking lol. I don’t think the eagles would give up a lot for him anyways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mixed feelings about the big radio news today...glad we’re expanding the @Entercom NY family but thoughts are with… https://t.co/M6M8TUPCJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am. Gov. CP: Tomorrow is final day to work on Ch. 8 &amp; 9 Presidency Packets during class  GOPO: Artwork and Workbook Ch. 14 Due]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiamStults @CameronBrin @PFTCommenter @BarstoolBigCat Nah that’s Josh Beckett]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drink single barrel whiskey. There’s no time for anything else. 🥃 @kovaldistillery #Koval #4Grain #ChicagoDistilled https://t.co/WgWHrtWVOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know it’s going to be a good day when Dunkin gives ya free breakfast sandwich! #GOODMORNING]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senators of the 62nd Texas Legislature. Barbara Jordan, my Political Values and Ethics professor at the LBJ School… https://t.co/WO7XceEH1l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChelseaNorthru Lolol. People always offer the casserole thing and I’m like nooooo. Really. No. @Grubhub exists.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got so excited when I found out my grocery store offers a pick six, six pack that I forgot to get dinner and now… https://t.co/KB8RfFfbF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump is so good at being arrogant that he does play the best corn ever I mean think about it I want to be mobster… https://t.co/7S0wc69se3]]></document><document><![CDATA[📅Open House: Sunday, March 10th 2-4PM📅  Check website for more info.  Welcome to 341 Cobden St. located in Central… https://t.co/I2alQzox5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birdman was on the floor for the majority of that 4Q in G6 of the 2006 finals. Didn’t score but was a big defensive… https://t.co/egDDbPEB8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women need to quit this shit. Stop being so insecure. You literally look insane with these random messages. NOBODY… https://t.co/NC4z4UOWfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Numbers grossly inflated, DJ! You’ll be long gone before there’s a dent in any number. Do you realize that under th… https://t.co/djS0kQWD78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small Group Personal Training: Morning workouts have never been better! Check it out 6:30 am with Coach Ray.  -… https://t.co/GoQZgJDS0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paradox: Here's why white evangelical women love Donald Trump https://t.co/58D0K34sIl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LA_Sparks I Love the WNBA!!!!!! I’ll be honest women shot the ball better than men!!! I got 5 on it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez at her finest!! @ Prescott, Wisconsin https://t.co/HbydmeGFIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1pissedPolack @BaileyShatney Sending you and your family thoughts of comfort and peace, your mom will be missed, I mourn with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Iowa, you should know that we pass slow moving machinery thats half on the road.]]></document><document><![CDATA[going straight to work after getting off the plane from vacation  https://t.co/uda4EUEZjy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dgoarmando Mal, Meza esto gratis los últimos 10 minutos, y dió oportunidad al cambio, no le digan a los tigres por… https://t.co/20YlnDkpTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at the Canadian Podcast Awards. I've heard this is the second year of the awards. Hashtag Trending is up for th… https://t.co/G66EO5ecMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[An agreement has been reached for Pevely police Chief Tony Moutray to resign. He’s been on paid administrative leav… https://t.co/BbxPv3G4s5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheesy NYC souvenir! #nycsouvenir @ Midtown East https://t.co/oG6iXRPBZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you plan the baby shower but you still gotta work at the strip club right after 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it bad that I’m trying to figure out how to make it to Texas to see @cantswim_ even though I’ve already seen them twice on this tour lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Potcy @arkellsmusic @IrvingPlaza DO IT! My fourth Arkells New York show and my 24th in the US overall!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today my advisor told me: Stop beating yourself up. You want this and you want it for the right reasons. You made a… https://t.co/NA9S5j7W5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ Did they not specifically confess to being paid for the staged crime? This is crazy 😂 #unsolvedmysteries]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uhlyssaaaaaa Can this come on @hulu or something. I need more positivity in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASU president Michael Crow, "The College is the core of the university." #ASUHumanities https://t.co/wMYCiJ8dCc]]></document><document><![CDATA[PUT it on @VisitQuadCities @IntheQ2030 and OWN it QC! @MelanieSpring knows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_tark @MTGCritic @nappiestNate There are a few that do more then that.]]></document></documents></author>