<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PinaCocoTweets @RickGriffin @MattsRoadTrip @MadHattersNYC @CharlesMcCool @VISITFLORIDA @VisitPCBeach @DanaHFreeman… https://t.co/IioMGKQ3kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The responses to “can you build a house” tweets is how I know you niggas can’t think past the surface]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Sound of Music should be #1...the cinematography in the opening scene, with the expanse of mountains… https://t.co/UbHfk2lzkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couple of crappy work days. A follow from @DonnieWahlberg sure would be a nice surprise ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#build your #dreamhome on this #private 6+ #acre #building #lot in #eastlyme with a #pond on Rocco Drive… https://t.co/0whzHqLKEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[God - thank you for these moments of happiness and security.  I do not take them for granted 🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m leaving as soon as I find something better, and I know of at least two others who are as well. And we are alrea… https://t.co/9VwnFoceXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is happening to you because you broke the law on so many levels.  So.Many.Levels.… https://t.co/s9WMC9VfF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, check out this amazing game! Join me and win awesome prizes! https://t.co/gfKLoFSbA6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKTelecomFaker Hi Faker! My name is Chong, I’m on the NA server, my ID is cal elephant!]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG IM IN TEARS I FREAKING LOVE EWF AND THIS IS ONE IF MY FAVE SONGS 😩😩😩😩 SANG @IAmSteveHarvey!!!   https://t.co/a7cZwQdBCh]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICY ICY BABY! The temp is starting to drop and road ways are getting a bit slick. If you’re out on your morning com… https://t.co/Sl5pGTBrq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hubby interrupted my watching of @SHO_TheCircus to show me @DropTheMicTNT with @ThatKevinSmith @JayMewes… https://t.co/V7pfkaQRVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewJeffCT @smoking_reedus @collette04 @leedusme1227 @OeverDaphne @L777Lobo @kevkye @TinaTWD @sachi_j @reni_89… https://t.co/LKVNXzuHzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jr4science I’ve sat in so many defenses thinking yea im going to do mine like that! Then i completely forget what i liked about them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s our lucky day in @StaggAthletics every day having you as our main gal!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRiffle @MEPFuller @JessicaTCahill Why would anyone think Hill staffers were activists? That’s a shocking part o… https://t.co/4YziplwRAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies i hate to break it to you but my mom lives in the same apartment building/hangs out with Colton Underwood and he’s a douche. 🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need you guys too give me random things advertised on youtube for a upcoming video I’m working on I know it sound… https://t.co/8erMmWhbcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brotnoff Sadly I can save I’ve definitely been here... but with coffee. Multiple times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Movie Review: #RubenBrandtCollector Is Visually Stunning But Lacks Depth https://t.co/5lTsKPS3Rp @sonyclassics… https://t.co/RN2KVPWH7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews 💜💙👰🏼🕍🤵🏻💙💜l love you FOREVER FOREVER MY LOVE FOREVER TOM CRUISE FOREVER MY LOVE💜💙👰🏼🤵🏻💙💜Me Facebook Lyhada S… https://t.co/hHYKrtJ0sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders No regime change in Venezuela.  UN and Red Cross refuse to help this covert right-wing coup. Diplomacy needed!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my daughter Julia for appearing in her first high school musical!  Kenmore West cast says farewell with… https://t.co/cWG4Da7kAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day of the week (@ KTEC West in Kenosha, WI) https://t.co/KCv6nk6fMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueFoxo @ScribeUndead I kind of think I should do that for a few people too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dega_boy_87 @joshbilicki @DrSquatchSoapCo @DannyLeBlanc24 @4judyblue @Cobraswife4life @Varightone1 @Jbriggsy_14… https://t.co/7ZQmagWYHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all my single people out there!!!   We all deserve some love on this made up holiday!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[was goin back through pictures to delete for phone space and ended up having a crisis because i cant even be happy… https://t.co/G8ENkSoGUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Calling all Brooklyn residents! Today, 2/15, is the deadline to apply to be on your local community board. It’s a g… https://t.co/Hot7MzRCLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMobTalk7 Okaaaa~~~ I’ll go on (FB) 😏~ personally I don’t frequent it lol.. tho,  for you..it’s a must ~!! ✔️🖤✔️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tentonheart Hawthorne Elementary has free pre-K 😊 must be county funded]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StopPC101 @AOC @RepAOC I was the first one to say she is the new Lolita Lebron ( look it up in Wikipedia ) = KILLERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inspiretowander Q4: A very moving historical place was the many graveyards in Belgium and France such as Tynecot t… https://t.co/gWGDFgsHls]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommacherri I love your videos!  I can’t seem to find your recipe for your Cajun seasoning that you keep using.  H… https://t.co/b9luJsSqme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@armac2010 @CoachMikeLotief @KarenWeekly Where could we send equipment?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg lol all blockheads agree... You could be more than one 😂 but your not 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read Across America School Spirit is happening at AES today!! #AESLLC #read https://t.co/Eg4EOApQPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSpeerHauser @SarahKSilverman It’s on  video.  Twitter went after her the next day. So there’s that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we ever meet in person, be prepared for me to tell "May I Please Hug You???"  Because, excitement. But also, consent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @alfranken I’ve always said that whole fiasco with Franken was ridiculous. He should never have resigned an… https://t.co/pe6L2mVxs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baseballyouth @warstic @txusssa @OU_Baseball @CenTexBaseball Yes sir...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I see Hailey she always reminds me that she got her ears pierced... My heart 😭😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianaa_alfaro I have been lucky to find professional mentors from various backgrounds that I can look up to and… https://t.co/cy9p6o60Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr . Redding posted these quotes.   They are true.                                        You can't be what you can… https://t.co/AuDpVQddgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abimbolaxbee @150Bison @soulthepoet @franklyalex_ It was definitely IN the room (not someone next door), and we ch… https://t.co/jFgOnvaJ1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏗Con Sue Photography and Design🌃  🛣Like our photos...Follow our IG 🌆  🚘This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/ljlLtdNGdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your kids don’t want to play with Aiden and make him feel left out, i will out loud say “they don’t want to play… https://t.co/z5H7Yva1B4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Relationships matter! Relationships are unsinkable!” - @ChrisSuarezPDX #KWFR19 #KWYP #XperienceGrowth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelschweitz @CNN @jaketapper Damn!!!!!!!👍👏👊🏻This guy knows what he’s doing!!   How refreshing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skate fish with lemon and capers @lebaratin. . wildediblesseafood #instafood #nycfoodie #lebaratinnyc… https://t.co/yohhKIBAro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pénitencier de Donnacona: 15 mois de plus à l'ombre pour du cannabis dissimulé dans son rectum (@Cote_Sophie) #JDQ https://t.co/HVxgREVLhK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This winner with 33 whole followers doesn’t think women know anything about hockey. Perhaps he should be educated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoArquette No we won’t! Everyone needs to stick together! Who ever it is no matter if you like him or her! That wi… https://t.co/lFRWWSXng4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried this a couple years ago. I found that it worked well for a few, but wasn’t best for everyone. I want to try… https://t.co/rA8EBgaqRN]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, he just is so full of hubris that he thinks he is untouchable. He’s already threatened the judge,with WHAT repe… https://t.co/QmO31TFCbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[S T Y L E L O G U E⁣⁣ M A R C H  I S S U E :⁣⁣ GARDEN BLUES⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ Is now live on the blog (link in bio).⁣⁣ ⁣⁣ Talkin… https://t.co/R2CblmbZ8Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 94-year-old grandmother. She worked as a journalist, a mother of 9; served on the PTA, the school board; read to… https://t.co/27dO2k7owa]]></document><document><![CDATA[the most toxic shit ever is a female that claims she loves u but can’t SHOW u she does]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously can.not with this basketball team tonight 😑 I was tired before. Now I’m tired AND grumpy. https://t.co/gI2BorJCc6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great opportunity for fund development professionals! 5 courses from @blackbaud University are now available to all… https://t.co/QW8ZhYeVSs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌞😜👩‍❤️‍💋‍👨💙#husbandandwife #exploringtogether #winterinusa #solanabeach #california @ Solana Beach, California https://t.co/hBlMbiCPcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@RepBradWenstrup: Oppose changes to Medicare Part D that restrict health care access and fail to reduce drug costs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[we live in the most annoying, SENSITIVE society. i almost want to delete all my media accounts. i’m sick of express… https://t.co/ALyqJdUvlV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyGMartinez I’m really sorry. I made the choice to live with my family, and then I wasn’t an academic for a lon… https://t.co/XpCG6HezMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could afford to move away, there is way to much out there to be stuck in this shit town with shit people :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s just say Ashley and @maadelynnnn always make my day better when I feel down 🥰🤧 https://t.co/uR5eONmfxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[In  him was life, &amp; that life was the light of all mankind. The light shines in the darkness, &amp; the darkness has not overcome it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You niggas put up with chicks/fuck chicks you don’t like,so meh to that statement.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow falls away from the curved blocks of a retaining wall in thick ruffles, like the full skirts of a fair country… https://t.co/oKso65toej]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning from vacation! See ya in a bit....!! https://t.co/FexHaLYRyf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @hmcghee She was brilliant.  I applauded her for not backing down this is a crisis and we MUST ACT NOW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[my uncle and I 4 years ago meeting @piercetheveil and @SWStheband crazy how fast the time goes! https://t.co/6r9MpeEBJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @SweetChickLife in Brooklyn, NY https://t.co/1xMkhdMYSW https://t.co/uPX7FuPfct]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today we play tunes at parkwayprime 5-8pm stop on out for some drinks, great food and tunes! #SupportLiveMusic… https://t.co/eIzOoVLHtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bby_grl_jackie I feel for you. They don’t got an Instagram or something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bull###!!!!! She knew what she was saying! No body is buying what you are selling!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning in Ft Lauderdale.  Staying in downtown close to Las Olas Blvd allows you to relax, enjoy the beau… https://t.co/OiGSPFA2gl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you use bumble BFF to solicit your personal training business,  Stop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Yes indeed Trump is a maniac we do not need a national emergency declared he is a moron no wall for Donnie]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bella &amp; the General🐱♥️ #waitingfortreats #workingtheheadtilt #weeklyfluff #fortheloveofpets #love #chewy… https://t.co/mvrAI8FPyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What is holding you back?  To a extra income, freedom, be with family and still make money. Or purchase great quali… https://t.co/9NBT1NR3q4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all say “Go Demarcus” but what about that poor little girl he had pushed up against the wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the loudest voices against President Trump is a liar and a fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday Dinner meagandrohan 🥂 @ STK - Toronto https://t.co/gjHMf7RGgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews @sparks_randi He should be indicted and tried, impeachment wouldn't get him out of office, only the courts can do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate how my family always wants to eat their little tacos every time we go out]]></document><document><![CDATA[....lmao 🤦🏻‍♀️ why is this me? I nannies and was alright but my OWN kid? 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[She doesn’t even have the kids ncentive to look it up before she opens her mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahLeCount1 My pleasure! I’d like to go back for fun and not just work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffTarlo @FLOTUS @Nicklaus4Kids Obama proved that it's not affordable. Why should anyone pay for someone else's?… https://t.co/odBabSH2Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lagniappism Never had fried clams, but the chicken tacos 🌮 were delicious! That is what I miss most from @PopeyesChicken 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why is the president of the US trying to help a dictator who kills his own people, become an econo… https://t.co/gXrkagyPzT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quntut13 @Pearce2389 @LaKeithiaL @tee_da_trainiac @deb10deb @jonipawlikowski @CowboyBart333 @NovaO @GeorgineBauer… https://t.co/6uNszuL7sE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@acoyne is just killing it this week..how long are Canadians going to put up with this government?? #cdnpoli… https://t.co/Rojh3ypoKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealHughJackman You are amazing! Even when you’re sweating your ass off! 💜 https://t.co/5zkiE0zAGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s just proves to me that once again, even when you’re a good person, and you are trying to do things the right way, it doesn’t matter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because networking isn’t just for people... Cruiser’s elevator pitch is on point! Thank you @Erica_Keswin for conne… https://t.co/jZNBcfb4yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[To trabalhando muito pra ser aquela “tia rica” que todo mundo tem sabe. “-Eu tenho uma tia que eh rica sabe, ai .....”]]></document><document><![CDATA[North Carolina to hold new election in 9th Congressional District amid election fraud scandal.… https://t.co/wZjzBim48N]]></document></documents></author>