<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@peterboykin We don’t like her because she’s a piece of Shit @kathygriffin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir Yeah Rocky NO. My flight was cancelled and I have no alternative. I’ve lost my parking Groupon, my ai… https://t.co/8FgKJifVL7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelaBelcamino @realDonaldTrump Who lost 6billion as Secretary of State??? Who sent billions to our enemies in Ir… https://t.co/ZzA4z1JE32]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! 😥My fav in 90210! Condolences to Luke's family. https://t.co/jGMG82abMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wrong. Yes, it saves money, but the savings it amounts to is FAR outweighed by the independence it provides… https://t.co/bOMYFtMbEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllaAgneau @mackenz35566664 @Kierabridget Hi plz find me a new big fans]]></document><document><![CDATA[Samuel Johnson said, “Great works are performed not by strength but by perseverance.” Remember why you started and… https://t.co/oBddte2CAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told myself I can’t finish GoT season 1 until I finish my homework and my desire to binge vs do work is highly disproportionate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSignorile I don't want to stop enjoying Jackson music.  Don't ban him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esa gente envidiosa que o que?  Sean felices con lo que tienen, sea mucho o poco...  Hakuna Matata ✌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look back and smile or look back and cry but keep moving! 😊❤️😢#livelovelaugh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Nintendo eShop Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Bel… https://t.co/rVPzsEco2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great panel of #womenintech for #InternationalWomensDay⁠ ⁠ #innovationeconony @Bullhorn @klaviyo @CarbonBlack_Inc… https://t.co/ldg985wyFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachbetterteam It’s one of my “go to” ways of introducing new science #phenomena #NGSS 💙👍🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[International Women's Day 2019: Celebrate women of history https://t.co/Qd4ehDZau3 # via @ABC11_WTVD  #IWD2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reginatames @RamirezClaudia_ Noooo, si le importan, el criminal mas famoso del mundo va a recibir a sus hermanitas… https://t.co/v0lXnm7hjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleMc420 @AllVape3 Yes. I prefer a pipe, but to each their own. Enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My students think it’s sooooo funny to shove bananas in my face when they have them for snack knowing I 100% do not like them :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[💞🎉Last night was inçredible!!Thank you so, so much to all of you for every part you played in the relaunch of the s… https://t.co/nkSME0wGD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jillianne_gray @MadHattersNYC @MyVirtualVaca @monstervoyage @suziday123 @Sostraveluk @always5star @FunInFairfax… https://t.co/toYqLJxog1]]></document><document><![CDATA[A #yarnbombing for those in need of a warm hat &amp; a snack ! https://t.co/yMhtqWfivZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Wounderful Husband surprise me on Valentine's times day thank you baby I love you https://t.co/ciEooAAbLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResourcefulMom A9 The illuminations thing you mentioned sounds perfect. Any night time fun activity or fun at a fu… https://t.co/0HIErRkrEP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2:  for teaching, I find that reflection is key.  It’s so easy to ‘slip’ if you aren’t intentional and don’t follo… https://t.co/f6zzElseUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaraCarterDC Joe Biden is the embarrassment-right! How dare he say that about a country who gave this moron everyt… https://t.co/bisiYXYkOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know your coworker is a real one when she warns you that they put mango in the juice 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[This weather is acting upppppppppp!! And I’m laying here not charging my phone like this electricity might not cut out 🥴🥴🥴🥴🥴!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Morrill Act of 1862 established the land-grant colleges to teach agriculture and other subjects. The Hatch Act… https://t.co/jy72quv8NG]]></document><document><![CDATA[WARNING: Your doorbell camera might make you feel safe, but who else can see what you see? We investigate how priva… https://t.co/YAQvYkQ83X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #US, you can find these delicious snacks on #Amazon. I tried it last night - delicious 😋 ! #Tatiana https://t.co/8De9g7bA4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream i met @LanaDelRey on the train and we took selfies but the selfies didnt save and i cried]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiturgicalFolk @laitylodge If ever I go missing, @laitylodge is one of the first places people should start lookin… https://t.co/fg2mBip8XR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scientists may have discovered a new killer whale https://t.co/8bq32iblm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TotalWireless wants to send you to the @iHeartRadio Music Awards! Enter daily for your chance to #win!… https://t.co/SBmVDMYucQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Booked flights last night, got an email today that they’re $100 cheaper. GOOD.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylornation13 @taylorswift13 @ELLEmagazine Lesson 14 hit home hard. love our girl for putting our feelings into words ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somedays, life makes perfect sense and I have it all figured out. It makes me feel accomplished. Then somedays I co… https://t.co/BskyhHF2Ci]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully stocked with beautiful little somethings...#newclothes #freshmerch #saylavie #retailtherapy #myhappyplace @ S… https://t.co/aRrfgwf5oQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stlukesportsmom @PhinsTweets @SportsTalkBarry @AOC Im a RN as well!!   Marijuana does lead to harder drugs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished vampire diaries and I’m not sure what i should do with my life now but i appreciate this tweet v much]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolument formidable. @ADoumara de @AlvfNord est une héroïne féministe pour nous tous! Je suis tellement fière d’e… https://t.co/K23x9AFhQ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Real Slick, Diarrhea.. That’s Real Shit ... I’m Having Fun at this Point  🎥 @PeepTheSneaks  @ilovekicks23… https://t.co/7GmdGx7qnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Will Ripley be joined by another #CrewDragon member for this Demo 1 flight to simulate weight distributio… https://t.co/VcGGEuXNXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen Now iam sorry. That is the funniest FN thing I heard all day. My neb.same HE,s 30!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it me or did madden curse win again Antonio Brown balled no playoffs and know on block]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can't believe the level of dishonesty in the @WhiteHouse with the #TrumpCrimeFamily   Loosers!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vlonelykt @JackiieSmacks I was about to say the same thing!!! Child lock his ass up!!! Immediately!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just heard Pence say he thinks trump is the same as McCain in the way he runs his administration. Good Grief! Expec… https://t.co/Em3qrCxgkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[What??😂😂😂 @joshsteverson ...”Okay, NOW you can go play with your LEGO’s.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarthSkyWrecker @yonex1us @realDonaldTrump @darthskywrecker  I’m passionate about not killing American babies. I h… https://t.co/bJCrjwNcqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kitobuddha Omggg, I JUST put mine back in after a 3 day break with it out :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you need a tan, a nap, and a workout but it doesn’t matter because the #stage makes you forget everything,… https://t.co/X0Cr5KhMRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunch before I head back to NJ. #ayearinthelife @ Empanada Mama LES https://t.co/6gv6U41l3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland Hey.  Didja know this Guv'ner was born in 1957? https://t.co/MblwqAkbjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MacUidhir @MidweekMinute @WillPresti I have 2 grown sons who have told me the same thing. I really should watch it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Less than 20 days left to get your limited vinyl edition❗️ Get yours before time runs out ⏱ Your support always mea… https://t.co/34rrg51WEW]]></document><document><![CDATA[can u imagine being this perfect knowing every boy is obesssd w u ... lol must b nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burger King @BurgerKing Crispy Chicken Tenders TV Commercial, 'Food Court'  @HereBeDragons3 Styling @GabrielleGabby… https://t.co/s5kp2gt5Ir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Not only that, but I don't think she has a clue what she's talking about. A minimum wage job never supported a family of 3....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for the confirmations @mychalwynn! Looking forward to your breakout session!! #ensureaccess #ensureequity https://t.co/pAaOoV6Z01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the recommendation. Will be checking them out. Maybe this weekend! 🍕]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GoVols #BeatKentucky #SEC #oneidaladyindians #statebound #Murfreesboro #theglasshouse #tssaa @Vol_Hoops… https://t.co/dWCLOaYqFv]]></document><document><![CDATA[無事にパネルディスカッション終わりましたの。英語でのパネルなんて初めてなので緊張するかと思いきや、めっちゃ楽しめました！ #think2019 https://t.co/HJZ1AxFjX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReeceDominique omg I just heard “Scotty doesn’t know” what a bad mom letting you girls listen to that. 😂😂 literall… https://t.co/3ijECMbjxs]]></document><document><![CDATA[My response to anyone who says, “I don’t see color” (first) are you color blind? Because all that means is that you… https://t.co/Ff0iC48fE7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to win 1 of 24 Truly Wireless headphones from @crutchfield, and you can too #gggentry  https://t.co/4fDlZeuNXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this song by #EricClapton or #GeorgeHarrison #WhileMyGuitarGentlyWeeps 💙🌈💙🌻]]></document><document><![CDATA[One move of God will change EVERYTHING!  Trust and Believe!    • • • • • • • • • • • • •  #hopedealer #worldchanger… https://t.co/HA80yDcFBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeyischillin @BornChamp92 Too honest. Makes sense. People ain’t ready for that real 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Democrats want a smarter fix not some criminal hateful antiquated fix... If course Trump isn't smart so… https://t.co/9sZ7t5rmXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before they do their taxes, they still argue that they'll save.  After they do their taxes, SILENCE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Your party kills babies AFTER THEY  ARE BORN         A L I V E ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maya Angelou, said that “People will forget the things you do, and people will forget the things you say. But peopl… https://t.co/Cz2SRA9cxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 The average American is getting really tired of the desperation of the DFL Trump haters. He has 90% ap… https://t.co/jtl8mAhLjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for this @annkpowers! It’s never Solange vs Beyoncé around here, but I have to admit I’m partial to the f… https://t.co/tYMrmFX1OF]]></document><document><![CDATA[When my human valentine is away, my furry valentines hold me down.  ✨💕🐱 🐶 💕✨ https://t.co/vVqHG0unVt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you not know DNC hasn't allowed Fox to host a Dem debate in 15 years? Nothing newsworthy here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganRadford Morgan this has been going on for a long time. I hope these women get justice. Thank you for your always excellent reporting!]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANYONE who believes tRump is NOT a racist is so stupid they are dangerous.]]></document><document><![CDATA[*Gets home from the Arnold  Me: OK no more spending money, gotta get my save on  *notification from PayPal about my… https://t.co/6xrwP98ldI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrmartinEDU @dtangred @Roosloan @thekylekitchen @GoslinK123 @MrSoclassroom @TeatherBoard @lizbonn @curatecuriosity… https://t.co/gGSQwfJedH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@caranorth11 @mzrascoff @profoyarzun Yes!!!! Love this.  I think I’ll take the job description and put it on my vis… https://t.co/Xk1EreLDJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rgay @tressiemcphd Darn so sad I won’t be in your audience tonight. (I was in Santa Fe,NM and thoroughly enjoyed y… https://t.co/Iws3q3YIiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThrowbackThursday to one of my favorite #makeuplooks from @chicstudios  #redlips #makeup #50s #madmenstyle… https://t.co/ov4DFs9EC1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilhimself Oh I thought that said Sam Ash. Must be all those Cornford Amps I just had to wade through to find out… https://t.co/2ErsUUpmFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leighmadz_ thank you madz 🥰 i’m glad i got to see you as soon as 12 hit. i love u.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clydetombaugh @kevinandbean ☹️ You realize you’re leaving the Trump dystopia for the Brexit dystopia, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland It's NOSTALGIA because I was skinny back then. https://t.co/M4nXZQ3WLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join us at our March Madness adoption event tomorrow (Sat, 3/2) from 11am-2pm at @k9dergarten in downtown… https://t.co/rKArNGyxno]]></document><document><![CDATA[HI GUYS CHECK OUT MY FIRST OF MANY DISNEY VLOGS!! #WaltDisneyWorld #WDWBesfDayEver #travelvlog   https://t.co/exh4pAHWTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4-I have accepted the challenge from @zackmmartin to post covers of 7 books I love. No explanations or reviews,… https://t.co/PwcRuolUWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we have real sick people who need the medical help instead of someone who needs a life CHANGE with GOD...]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m gonna make a thread of the tommyxzendaya pop up bc i took and edited such great pics uwu the art heaux jumped out this weekend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClappSandra @KamalaHarris The worst president ever? Where is your brain? Thanks to Trump we have a booming economy… https://t.co/xMWKHyoxvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[That face 🥰💕 Not only a billionaire, but look what she does for humanity.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realityaddictx Yea I noticed that with the prices too. I grew up on their shoes. I am sure going to miss them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PressSec @AprilDRyan @realDonaldTrump I guess if most Americans were in your income bracket they would agree. Have… https://t.co/EiGk08s490]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvptvinmarvel @basixcoffeeboy @lexirenep @UniversalORL Haha, we paint warstripes at every single sporting event. I… https://t.co/SHT6xkUgEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m told 400 to 500 people have signed up to testify for and against #SB181, the oil and gas reform bill. Each pers… https://t.co/osNi0g3zy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[He is a very creepy old man. The mainstream media should have extensively reported on this prior to the election. I… https://t.co/QFaPCJLUae]]></document></documents></author>