<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[neadsdogs service dog in training, Emmitt, chillin with his BFFs (Best Frozen Friends) after raising his paw and vo… https://t.co/KGnATfdNtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like im the only one who filed my taxs &amp; havin a kids got there money lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harper_coach LOL so your coming to southern Oregon Coast? https://t.co/2BPGTL6Epy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wondering why @anthonymbertram is messing with me while I’m trying to #self #tape?!? #working #actors #havingfun… https://t.co/XJ4dS6V4AA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any and all crisis and problems do not automatically amount to national emergencies. A national emergency is for wh… https://t.co/BEK1gCeCh8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC looking forward to Bernie rally on historic BOSTON COMMON....expect record breaking crowd...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to put lebron out to pasture tonight. Celtics put a whooping on the lakers lebron will call it a season mark it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abbyhondo @B_Ingram13 I don’t think people doubt his talent, but it’s the consistency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting. Feel like I need another to figure out how I really feel about this - Drinking a Sangria SWheat Tart b… https://t.co/Piwfmc9t9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Alameda You’re in Clearwater?  Wow!!  The girls would have loved to come watch you guy play. @TheQuinn44]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes you can say a thing that even before speaking you are certain will change the entire course of your life… https://t.co/XYV5wn3ZHO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fantastic_Nami Nope I’m all caught up now, and I still support your message 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of this life – which is sure to come much sooner than we’d like – it is unlikely we'll ask if we accompl… https://t.co/hyJ56eubTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeleisTheKing @seanie_doyle Mike email me and we can arrange a time to chat StevieGrieve@hotmail.com]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried something new for this weeks #WallpaperWednesday https://t.co/YEVXEzcELQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriteLikeUTalk I’d say just as bad: “A fire claims a man’s life.” Heard this earlier today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGT - Damn, the ventriloquist girl over Susan Boyle And John Dorenbos?  The world is in trouble.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexiaStevens01 You all are so kind and sweet people as well as awesome writers! Have a wonderful weekend Alexia! ✍️😇📚💕🌞🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VTBShomie nah trae deserves it his skill set is actually useful in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dayanar29 Define socialism and tell me what countries do you consider to be socialist]]></document><document><![CDATA[@torinomonty Wow!  WTH is wrong with people nowadays?  If they’ve really been following you that long, they should… https://t.co/rn8I6GDt5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuji and Kepler grab morning sun. #snoutofafrica #barklessdog #basenjisofinstagram #basenji #newyorkcity @ Manhatta… https://t.co/fjmsJiXueS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry On the one hand, she’d be a great life insurance policy for whoever was president... on the other hand,… https://t.co/Wu66Su2Vpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh it’s losses like this that are frustrating. Lakers played well enough to pull off an upset win tonight. Too man… https://t.co/4o9g6gvnhX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAFromBK @SabreKevin1639 @JustPlainT @SandiMarie79 @TheNotriousBob @DragonMom98 @Jordandelmont2 @Crazy4OReilly90… https://t.co/ccJUV8e2sN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump has another meltdown on Twitter with accusation that Hillary colluded with Russia https://t.co/ZB70W5JCRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talmage_lisa @SenKamalaHarris @alaskarebel Not a bit of it. They are all highly principled liberal judges. No hack… https://t.co/Fx4euzDJCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CptCrowley @cmnandy *infield shifted 3 players to the right, thus making it an illegal formation*]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what? All those crap DC comics MOVIES?  The comic books... THEY'RE FANTASTIC!  It's like... Something gets… https://t.co/MWanjyG314]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ocalderoff Thank you Olivia, you always know what to say to cheer me up and I definitely know every word he used t… https://t.co/3sFuA8GthX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the early bird gets the worm, where's the fucking tequila? #truckerlife #peterbilt #rollingnorth @ Morningside H… https://t.co/nL3kvcwDoN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bama_world Yeah that’s about where we were, they had Conti and Dearborn taped off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asheville, NC just keeps getting better with every trip. Had a great recording session today at Landslide Studios w… https://t.co/hnJJecFLCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[2:22am. in bed. eating a spicy @SlimJim. this ain’t the life i chose this the life that chose me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManInTheHoody @RandilynIsIn Just whipping up a quick batch of Botox before sleepy time]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonBippus @PerryJuDo4ever @TeamChabby @billymflynn @MarciMiller @TeamMarci @hintofmccartney Well if you got th… https://t.co/xJf8SyKerf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dope times at the Smif N Wessun album listening party. Salute to @generalsteele and @teksmokeelah for a fire album.… https://t.co/BVFkt1aSNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@moarxbt the  term is now used as a weapon not only by the political Left, but  also  by far too many on the politi… https://t.co/sWaXjzkMPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday February 16 - Your Saturday 6:    Payless shoe stores will shutter;     More wintry STL weather;     RBG i… https://t.co/rBNyq39i3w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Decentman282 @TomiLahren All green of skin... 800 centuries ago, their bodily fluids include the birth of half-bre… https://t.co/Nmlq9DXhIb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HerringLiz @charliekirk11 I'll admit I'm not sure what that has to do with what we were talking about but the poss… https://t.co/KBgGxhN15O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for an assistant baseball coach at Godwin (PAID)! If anyone knows anybody who can be there at 3:30 everyday, please let me know.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A successful showing today...and as always there fun and games! #Repost @LordByronEmpire (get_repost) ・・・… https://t.co/M0kOdlS9tM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alcoholikaust it's a global unlock so I don't have to https://t.co/M4m6Cmmg3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cast bonding doesn't get any better than sharing bacon and booze. Cheers! 🍷🍺🐖 #simplejoys #foodie #bacon #mmm… https://t.co/lb6oCcbYqG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dabernathy89 @codebyjeff Pretty cool! Learned about this stuff in dev psych in school but haven’t thought about it in a long time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FMInman @ChickfilA I broke poor Logan’s heart Sunday when he didn’t understand why they weren’t open]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omaha picked up 7.5" of #snow on Saturday, so it's a tie with 5 days to go!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Redpainter1 @TuckerCarlson So sad that you are so stupid he didn’t call women anything he called a particular pers… https://t.co/yV32zLffzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VanceTallman $NSPX as far as the dip I am responsible. I accidentally passed on old info to my group. I was readin… https://t.co/35tpKChBhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SLCScanner @dannahyer Taking off at SLC Airport. Caught some open shots just east of the Wasatch, then some good p… https://t.co/h9xTV9DzVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@do6SON @TheDirtyBirdFan Yeah. But at least we’ll put an effort towards making the playoffs before stomping on your heart.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen I have a question for you , what happened to Hillary Clinton's emails? Oh I'm sorry that's a sore subject isn't it, my bad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JussieSmollett Chicago police is one of the most corrupt law enforcement agencies in America. Let's not forget tha… https://t.co/8pa04rmYEL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway It amazes me that Fox News reports the emergency way down the list as a headline on their web page.  This… https://t.co/HFR6tKY411]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayasax @ejdickson @TaylorLorenz Forget that Momo, look at this Momo: https://t.co/ArqrlXNqdY! She’s a lovely seni… https://t.co/GXh0mlIpv3]]></document><document><![CDATA[LLEGÓ EL MOMENTO, LLEGÓ PAPÁ EL PRESIDENTE 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/vyEmsmW6eF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bayanwang @SunDevilHoops I really hope that doesn’t add another juggling ball 😦]]></document><document><![CDATA[Partido MONUMENTAL, Luis S. rompiendo sequía de 5 partidos y Messi? es el de siempre 👑 #ViscaElBarça]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The problem is it affects more than just the nitwits that voted for her. All of the socialist ideal… https://t.co/FNTwRYWXzD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@natekostelnik @AaronWatson59 @PiperCreativeP AND he's helping VLOG the book launch and cut up content fast (our "S… https://t.co/LuBh5kP8Oo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boston, MA: the Customs House in Boston, by the way of the UK + the Dutch. Why shouldn't I have faith + trust in th… https://t.co/Kg9XPnvys2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yuge size aggregates. 35.4F and rising. Tremendous battle just off the surface for hydrometeor supremacy. #wvwx https://t.co/RP7SvQMhH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenWhitehouse @nbcsnl @FBI We do not wonder about the President.  But you whitehouse are another story.  If you su… https://t.co/5ZNsr0LF9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Fri., March 29, in #Cary, NC., and Sat., March 30 in #Greensboro, @Humana will sponsor #VietnamWar commemoration… https://t.co/brRSkdcjur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TitaniaMcGrath Paperback punishes trees and the ozone, Kindle punishes retina and causes floater showers. I am sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RKamagawa @TheBubbleBubble @hmacbe The great prophet @MikeJudge foretold this situation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thankful Thursday from the Men of Hiram: I am thankful for our birthday boy today. Thankful for my wife, family and colleagues.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hickenlooper 100 yards from the capital, thanks Hickie https://t.co/PuGVbh0KEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Today would be a good day for you to release your taxes.  #Corrupt45]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You know what else we **really** need?  A Space Farce. #SpaceFarce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SIENNAWESTLAND Just wanted to give you a "heads up"...Instagram has been blocking comments to your posts. It looks… https://t.co/xNFcR7Bw9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to attend the annual meeting of Community Action Pioneer Valley, ably led by my friend and former Mayor of… https://t.co/xD7ZTz2g3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminder that while the @mplsfoundation builds deliberately segregated charter schools in areas on concentrated rac… https://t.co/ly9Wb9KX1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to start a streak @UCDavisMBB 3 now, 3 more then #thebigdance #MarchMadness let's go @SilerJoe5 @G_Goode15… https://t.co/5aMt7h2SVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can enjoy my homemade chicken noodle soup knowing that it never suffered the cruelty of being locked up in a cage… https://t.co/L3Mhepu2hT]]></document><document><![CDATA[6A Area Hoops: after 1Q @BrotherhoodNet and @LFHSHoops are tied at 18. #RGVHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mlramsdale_law @bradyqg I was in college at 15 ... I was a Democrat and they made me vote without ID or being registered]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday @SecPompeo She don’t need to be BACK ON USA 🇺🇸 SOUL @SecPompeo good JOB @realDonaldTrump @PressSec… https://t.co/ZockiTeHz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport @kylegoon He got some of that born ready juice from lance]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeavyMetalTeddy took me to the Stanley Cup. That’s as real as it gets! Go @NJDevils #BBceleb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #Germany watch out for your young daughters @JoeBiden is in town and he likes to fondle children #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Forest Height Entrance Waterfall in Portland, OR https://t.co/gnx705qkQB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewingsnation I just watched it and was praying Jensen was on the ice for it 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nerevsfan I'm more interested in hearing you all do the "cows, churches and motels" chant against OCFC.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ozinho10 @ftbIOscar @RidSwayy @GoatVarane__ @MxrtialSZN Anyone who disagrees, YouTube Ronaldinho volleys against c… https://t.co/HcaYLsR1Ch]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you propose to a chick and she start hugging you like you’re cousins then take that ring back bro, she don’t lov… https://t.co/8HmVKHigWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LexiReyne1523 @tr3v_15 Even if he touched his back moe put his whole elbow in the rim.]]></document><document><![CDATA[..@MorningAnswer @DanProft @AmyJacobson Sixteen year olds are absolutely concerned about "the Iraq and the such as,… https://t.co/imgXIgVL2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[In austin, we feed them at 3 am, but I guess 1 is ok. Always forget the time and solar distance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to go support @_YungBleu show! He brought one of mobile #goats @Afori251 out 🙏🏾🙏🏾 now that’s the way you bring… https://t.co/xgNgAAQsa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fear no death claw lol ok maybe a little @ Ogden, Utah https://t.co/49OxLT8Usq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandomTweetName Yikes. Well, may they give you a great multitude of only the best classes of painkillers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pamfoundation god bless you pam your truly a great American love you so much thank you for all you do god bless]]></document><document><![CDATA[ANIMAL REUNIONS - 7 MOST HEARTWARMING ANIMAL REUNIONS WITH OWNERS https://t.co/hBLgmSMvRy via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dr_athenamac @ParkerPhonics LOL that's true I've seen the others but that one...bonkies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisatoluna @GuyverI @EnzosReviews @KirkMcCall3 https://t.co/qW41tMiz9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public Open Houses for the #EglintoWestLRT are coming up tomorrow at York Humber and Thursday at Martingrove. Have… https://t.co/YuJwOhQaG7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hitler's Gestapo Chief Heinrich Mueller. Thank GOD we don't have a Gestapo Chief in America! https://t.co/n5lfwATpYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmfm This should come as no surprise, as the 1% tend to be insulated from these problems. What is astonishing i… https://t.co/MYH4T6ww8d]]></document></documents></author>