<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@redshirts1701 @TrekCore Clearly not cause you keep replying. 😂 https://t.co/AmzYiUqYK3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate when people don’t answer my phone calls/text/emails in the time of crisis... if you don’t care, idc. Let’s b… https://t.co/8fvuHc359V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought myself some tulips today.... I can’t wait for blooming flowers and spring to arrive #spring #flowers… https://t.co/IvUHaNVePd]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever dance with the devil in the pale moon light? Streaming Devil May Cry 5 tonight at 8 pm CST. I'll also be d… https://t.co/jqy27rifap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMadison Pllllleeeaaassssse! I’m begging you! I have to know your favorite Van Halen song!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great two games today with Travis Hiett of Tabletop CP on YouTube.  Although I managed to lose twice both games wer… https://t.co/PMky9jFjpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up, these Brooklyn Boxing ads look like CrossFit ads.  #DirrellYildirim #PBConFS1 #Minneapolis #boxing #MonteroOnBoxing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SofyChan22 @AristemoFans @NeonBreaker @Pukerainbows7 @SCorcega18 @GIOVANICORSA @JessYaoi @MomentosDAmorHD… https://t.co/XslQWhOjqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfarnsworth beautiful and elegaic. sounds like the inside of my soul today...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connection between home energy efficiency and respiratory health in low-income homes  https://t.co/RGDsDzjdwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoffinMJC @SammyLev I like the new “handle”. Congratulations again Prince @SammyLev.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danthd3848 @McFarrenGary @AsalazarHD3848 Way to go team!!!  Thank you for delivering excellent customer service th… https://t.co/ahNUQnndDe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Those were because you’re a vile asshole, nothing to do with your religion.  Do you not see the irony in… https://t.co/Yk4RZWLWLD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellykeegs Thought this said SCONES and I was like WOW west elm made the right move here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachchitty Milner probably would take a hack at his ankles as well if he came on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Teach_619 Remember 9th tryouts at 1:00 today. We can discuss the sweep.😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrickPony @Timcast It isn't racist to say that white privilege exists. It's a proven fact. And yes, colonialism is… https://t.co/Z1bG0NLiki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming on the market this weekend in the heart of Germantown! Rare opportunity to build your dream home in an alrea… https://t.co/kVtzITfap1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiaYim @TheModern_Myth Still waiting to meet you next month. I was sooooo nervous the first time and didnt want Ke… https://t.co/xoMkLNDKcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Messthetics, Helen Money, Thee Thee's ($12/$14, all ages) 7pm (at @AceofCupsBar in Columbus, OH) https://t.co/LU4T5PedLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Happiness Comes From Within by @BrainDeadBrew at @oakstdrafthouse — https://t.co/TI9Hvqyfuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zen_Moments Never put off until tomorrow what you can put off until the next day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LogicalDame @EvilBobJ Saw Elton John in St Louis, No in 1973. Billy Joel was the opening act!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, come to Mobile and let’s us show you what southern hospitality is all about!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BCDreyer the proper title of the 1942 Rogers and Hammerstein musical is ‘Oklahoma!’; if it comes at the end of a s… https://t.co/ND5tIAyXJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitBabcock @Bluegrass504 @ArtscenteratVT @HokiesWrestling THAT is so cool! I have not been to a wrestling meet in years! Gotta go]]></document><document><![CDATA[8.6 billion for the wall that no one wants. Increase in military budget. Cuts to Medicare, Medicaid, and social sec… https://t.co/xfJB709pb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Iddybud @thehill Hey, don't make The Hill into the bad guy here. Someone wants to say dumb things? Media will and should report on it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@citizencohn Excellent piece in the @HuffPost @HuffPostPol on Sen Warren’s universal child care prop.   As you ment… https://t.co/YkFleqCQjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The work I’m about to put in when I get to college everyone is going to regret saying he’s to big to slow his feet… https://t.co/KV0fITGQtZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kcdoubleok @wb_thorne @Derek4943 @robinhanson @John_Hempton I am reminded of work on the cause of type 1 diabetes.… https://t.co/nEVIEztHU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before @AmyDumas was Lita with The Hardys she was Lita with essa Rios and basically as popular as heel @RealDDP was]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FINALLEVEL Ice T's the only dirty cop in the SVU!!!😝 KINDA like the pedefile that works @ Disneyland!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Loyola at Southern Illinois: How Clayton Got His Groove Back. #MVCHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DestinyTheGame I’m so close to getting Luna’s howl and I’m worried that I won’t be able to continue with the steps during season 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sigh*   I'm gonna let @piagnone @ebruenig @DeanDettloff handle this one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Funny how you now want to believe Cohen is lying, you know the LAWYER OF THE PRESIDENT… https://t.co/SrdvcxujfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sitting here at work mdeposiaking a list of everything I have to do over the next 8 days. Paying the deposit, signi… https://t.co/srCyJ3TxHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Donnie dumpo is a complete ignoramus and piece of totally useless shit too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#internationalwomensday⁠ ⁠ #iwd2019⁠ ⁠ #tgif #fridayfeeling i'm live right now use my #FREE link #CAMWITHTAY. COM o… https://t.co/EV8OzarRlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[your a total sweetheart and I look forward to seeing more of you on Twitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[They got some bomb voices together, for real. I waiting for them to say “Sarafina!!!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hasdrubal_ Well it looks like the democrats have taken up the policies he's talked about for decades. That is a ma… https://t.co/CHgIiIlSAd]]></document><document><![CDATA[843.302.1342 #raymercerdoeshair #allnutrient #balayage #colormelt #hairgod #ilovehaircolor #westashley… https://t.co/PFFJXfwbXV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every midwesterner thinks his or her weather is wacky. It's all wacky. "But it was like 60 yesterday and it's cold… https://t.co/VNgpwLNLmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to have Heatherlee Bailey MD as 48th President of @SCCM #CCC48 @SCCMPresident https://t.co/r1ao9e81Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[@People4Bernie Yes..crazy loser settle for a pay off from Hillary Sanders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamerJayG LOL. Ended up splitting it into 3 parts, I’ll make 3 deposits over 3 weeks to make it work better 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s mad because he spent all his money and got nothing in return and never will. Scott jus take this L and start d… https://t.co/bqOsBiVjSg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture this:  You wake up and you look like a mushroom. You go to work and hate your job because your boss is an a… https://t.co/ySFQCR4FLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BostonGlobe Paper or phone? WBCN 14 YR I got fake news. Most valuable thing on Earth. 249 yr ago today  Day1USA HI… https://t.co/sRXggCKu15]]></document><document><![CDATA[YALL THEY CALL OKLAHOMATHE AMERICAN SKILLET..............I’M DECEASED💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladyHELLacious Not sure what’s turning me on more bondage elephant is pretty hot🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyReiser @azfamily Then she should get fined for being a selfish dipshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SectatorGaming Birthday parties are always fun! Hope you enjoyed your time with your fam over the weekend! Mines w… https://t.co/l4bfnOgCWI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm telling you . they are coming for u they are going to criticize and pick apart everything u do and say. Stay st… https://t.co/aX8GQWh3Fe]]></document><document><![CDATA[got something cool coming friday 🕰  @sunsleepband https://t.co/Y2Di7LXs5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ronda Rousey looked good and mean tonight but don't like the way she made Dana Brooke land on that last move. #RAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The boys were buzzin today 🐝🐝 (couldn’t ride it out tho) https://t.co/jSX07lBgsK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'm celebrating every @POTUS except you and @barackobama You because well you know and #Obummer because he gave us you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[one genius of the biblical prophets is to dream not only solutions to problems in the world, but to dream entirely… https://t.co/ZmVvIqeUZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey... that’s my best friend!!!! 💙💙 @KAMADUNG words cant express how proud of you I am 💙💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[someone reposted something i edited on instagram without tagging me or even liking the tweet it was from??? https://t.co/NS9zIzu8R5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson @AOC Young man, you misunderstand the meaning of the word. Go look up the word racist, read some book… https://t.co/bvnmi78qyV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exactly they will all reap the worlwind of Justice,eventually this new DOJ will see to it!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay to my favorite racing analyst @WoodbineDawn who has helped me picked tons of winners… https://t.co/jBKQAzHvjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Expecting better performance tonight from @FriarsHockey, hosting Hockey East leader @UMassHockey, than that of… https://t.co/YbC1J2DzRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese When I was a kid, John, I learned that the leader of KKK Police Officers who tortured and murdered coll… https://t.co/W9RvSepmt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[God, Help us weed out our spiritual lives because of our love for You. #Amen 🙏🏽  #StandFirm 💪🏽 Are the weeds sneaki… https://t.co/uriN5yeB7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesPearceEcho Not so much in their hands as by their fingertips. Let’s continue to hope they get back their form. #YNWA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods See kids that’s what Botox does to your brain screws you up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been playing $IQ ALL morning again started buying puts this AM bought 25 of the weekly $26.5 puts at $.48 avg bough… https://t.co/efP6pDrzCT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wright_blake @Ren_Daxt @TampaBayTre @ZacOnTheMic In the economics of the NFL, it isn’t so much about how much some… https://t.co/7XlC9LgAq1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smaller Tax Refunds Surprise Those Expecting More Relief: Many early filers under President Trump’s tax plan are su… https://t.co/KnCewLOKCE]]></document><document><![CDATA[vegasgoldenknights take notes: this is how you win a championship in an inaugural season #mambonumber5 @ Hockey Hou… https://t.co/3GBXcwxWZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CTV_PowerPlay @GerryNic @salhousser this story is well beyond the Ottawa bubble that is wishful thinking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYWFP @AOC @BernieSanders @ewarren @SenSchumer @SenGillibrand @andrewcuomo @SenGianaris ...and there is no money t… https://t.co/nUJiHKFQTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffwolfe206 @NBA @Pacers Great to meet you and thanks for making the trip!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eden Prairie vs. Edina for the Class AA Championship has me like... https://t.co/qXffHM5rcE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steigerworld @cabot_phillips Oh, and I am NOT a Bernie supporter.  Never was. Peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone just told a why did the chicken cross the road joke. I almost smashed my face into the desk and walked out… https://t.co/js1YTO6Em4]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can also do an en-dash in Word by using the em-dash and letting copy editors fix it at the proof stage!… https://t.co/DTkIsDiLNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a HUGE Kobe fan. But stop with the comparisons between Bron and Kobe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJerseyPics @southladyeagles I’m not going to lie, I teared up watching this yesterday. The bond you two have as… https://t.co/jv7gdsi5uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Hazy Sexy Cool New England Style IPA by @BirdsongBrewing @ Ferguson's Bottles &amp; Taps — https://t.co/ji8DBntogN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Story with @AmericanAir gets better. The flight they didn't let me on? They put my luggage on it. So I landed at te… https://t.co/DEOzWzwAjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome night tonight in Nashville with @ubcomer and @deandralk as we enjoyed great BBQ and some great music. Looki… https://t.co/392HMhzceO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNCLE__WOO @Gab_alexxis @d_edwards24 @a_fierce_flower Bro said pip squeak lmfaoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Witches used to grind the fairies, did you know that? Abominable. Superstitious rubbish, and highly unscientific.… https://t.co/Q5O6d8GlBf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccnomad @Silvara75 @jbouie L.A. would be okay, but for the driving. Really don't like all the driving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rich_L_O The check they cut him was the least they could do for keeping the guy from making his money. And you’re… https://t.co/0uuKC6C36U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigolfoot @gypsyglutton @TheEliza2 @CynChamplin @MikeroHonky @HamLibertarian @Merica_Media To the gulag with you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft told me years ago at the super bowl that he’d love to come back in another life as Gronk......but clea… https://t.co/yr2wjmt5X6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aberg had nothing to do but retrieve that puck, he wasn't barely aware what he should do...what a waste.  #mnwild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendono Campanello’s was so fantastic.  Loved the sauce and pastas.   The ambiance was too cool.  Sad to see it go.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this what it has come to - we cage the youth of the world where we use to welcome them with open arms! I cry for… https://t.co/Ri89Sn8maj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two words that I wouldn’t mind not hearing again for the rest of this year: “Atmosheric River”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnOwning Fant has the athletic profile of Aaron Hernandez and Hock has the athletic profile of Gronk. Just not as big.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShimonPro @Cernovich Which means that the two Nigerians were part of a fake hate crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wire2wirewendy icymi my .20 pk4 R8. 2,5,7 R9. 1,2,6,9 R10. 5,6,7 R11. 1,5,6,7 $28.80 good luck]]></document></documents></author>