<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#TherapyDog Congrats @BarkAndreFurry! cc @docanton @missrachelgrant @WinstonDaDoodle @GoldenKnights… https://t.co/xkGJcppfu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chipfranklin No reason to pardon anyone because evidence of any crime doesn’t exist. Your hate has caused you all… https://t.co/1cltUFynaf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday was so fun except for the fact that I ate McDonald’s, Wendy’s and Skyline for breakfast, lunch and dinner!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Re evaluate your life if you have never been alone on certain holidays ...because some people have it worse then yo… https://t.co/mBVJU5KX2v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blessyouboys Might it be considered risky to use your utility player as the DH?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idc who gets mad but there is NOT going to be any alcohol or beer at MY baby shower &amp; if you can't respect that then DONT show up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CGProgram the ‘9er’s biggest needs are definitely on defense and almost any deal for Brown would be an act of inco… https://t.co/hV4MHvTbCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Curculiunculus @infernoxv Count on you to catch that! I did consider adding that right behind my tweet – all the m… https://t.co/MaNZleN8zJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just saw someone at work put mayo on their bacon egg and cheese sandwich. Not gonna lie, I considered reporting him to the police!🤮]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4YrsToday It is NOT a coincidence that THIS "president", #45, is surrounded by nothing but SEEDY, SHADOWY individu… https://t.co/EUe2u9miF5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You’re right. Russia investigating 120 million to your foundation while you were running for Presid… https://t.co/ZQXbbEc6yQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@librofilos @maqroll30 La escalera del conocimiento es más reconfortante que la escalera de la fama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 most important remaining games  March 1st @ Islanders March 10th vs. Winnipeg  March 12th @ Pittsburgh  March 16t… https://t.co/TefHK6HEbU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to come over and suck some of that big beautiful black thick cock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DifferentFight That video really got me interested in the game, I just don't have people to play with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fantastic @scunleashed #podcast with our interview w @keatingcarguy plus a great story on how his team watc… https://t.co/HsHBQtfzxn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/RTiC2d4t9x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@extrabaggs So does this mean @knbrmurph &amp; Mac won’t play “his bat is alive, his number is 5, and he’s Hundley like a wolf” anymore?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! Actor's Foundation Class Tuesdays at 630 pm. Working on the Actor's instrument and creating a process for… https://t.co/tSzakTmvxI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at Omlid DR 13 #Springfield #OR  #realestate https://t.co/vf1l0KtOFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning - anyone know where the buffet is?  #photography #naturephotography #chipmonk #breakfast… https://t.co/9KNr1Jjed7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't sell out your constituents. You are a lame lowlife if you do because you are as corrupt as Democrats for not… https://t.co/Fz0dhBFRZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnkriesel I had that joy flying into MSP today. Drinking at lift bridge is helping me get over it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC @MarkDice Poor Wussie. Needs a big hug. Kinda falls into the snowflake category!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention ALL MEN ACROSS EVERY CAMPUS of @JefferyPortmann We have an incredible wknd planned for you this coming Ma… https://t.co/oNirhnUrdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder how Steve Miller reacted the first time someone called him the Gangster Of Love]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kfippin @christinadunnn @patronusisotter I'm not really speaking for myself here, nor am I encouraging ever abstai… https://t.co/qm9zr8G97w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mango3000 @Phillies I wasn’t a Bowa guy. More into Ivan Dejesus. Bake for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe Yeah,,cause the rest of crew brown nosing everything Skip is saying 😂🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanMenley @CoachSigne @NAIA @Sooner_Athletic We don’t, the book keeper does! People not doing their jobs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Walt Disney Attractions Technology at Kirkman Point in Orlando, FL https://t.co/Py8f32D3v1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenbaLamb @scott_seiver @Joeingram1 No. Patience and extreme discipline obv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to @schutzandleaves for always pushing me to chase precisely the correct word. I’m a far better writer an… https://t.co/9qcwkCOYf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[E! NEWS: Alex Rodriguez Posts About Soulmates as He and Jennifer Lopez Enjoy Beach Getaway. https://t.co/6kBc5DJM6d  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're a Reds fan and don't like Joey votto, you're searching for reasons in life to be mad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my little buddy traveling with me today.  Have the honor of speaking at the 2 year anniversary celebration of t… https://t.co/4JMeJssQpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[it is so hot in my room but i’m too scared to sleep w the windows open send help]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forest Hills NY Thu Feb 28th PM Forecast: TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 31 SATURDAY Sunny Hi 41]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Or they are totally on to something.  One of the two sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeoEdResearch @PSBROOKES @drugmonkeyblog @mholder_conklin @Rick_Frausto @jenheemstra @sbarolo @dnatarheel You said… https://t.co/UZVPYwXX7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askck Tienes razón, será porque esa conducta debe ser lo normal. Tenemos que hacer que sea general. Saludos! 🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do all these rich white guys look like slobs who don’t spend any money on clothes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders In these dark times of our nation, you are the light at the end of that long tunnel. I will do all I… https://t.co/CVpfGgzlm6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m gettin older bc I’ve started to watch full series shows instead of just movies 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@holbrook @xiruxi @Karoli I for one was blown away by the number of independent candidates who ran and won in 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bad, bro. I was actually ya know, living life. I just jump on here every now and then to clown a fool. You clear… https://t.co/xm3nDD2Xt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fortressfin @GrrrGraphics Talk about unoriginal mocking. I heard that in 1st grade. Speaks more about your level o… https://t.co/SSwbqZzQcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN One of the greatest scenes in movie history to be honest.  ".....The Queen, the Vatican, the Gettys, t… https://t.co/ymiS2OGzvm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just rewatch the Shallow performance for the 7th time? Yes I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My picks are out for today’s games. Lot of interesting action going on today so take a look! ⬇️⬇️⬇️⬇️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out Jake Arrieta on Twitter. Athlete, outdoor enthusiast, husband, father/life coach. Philadelphia Phillies https://t.co/TOSwAIWPpg ⚾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me see if I understand. Neither #Purdue nor #Indiana can score 50 points, yet #PennState scores 95. #Nebraska c… https://t.co/ebTrG1tqPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nowplaying Drip Or Drown 2 by Gunna feat: Lil Baby, Young Thug, Playboi Carti via the @audiomack app https://t.co/zgxb7yZn9h. @1GunnaGunna]]></document><document><![CDATA[Horrible game by K-State, still in first, but man they did absolutely nothing positive tonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to announce the studio picked up a couple of ADDY Design Awards. One for a @JohnPrineMusic piece for The… https://t.co/NtK4eJUXbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t get enough of “The Red White and Blue of Samford U” @JamesHardyPBP . Don’t ever stop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s neat is that each park has the team’s local brewer.  So Surprise has Boulevard.  Not sure about Milwaukee yet.  I’m gonna check]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlamoOnTheRise Glad to see another blue San Antonian. We will make this state BLUE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got so many dirty jokes to tweet bout these photos. Imma stop myself cause I’m an adult]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to see the breakdown of the answers to this poll question by generation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WashTimes Change the narrative of YOUR @POTUS and @GOP making a fool of themselves on national TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um, besides the fact that he's been promoted up levels in the minors based on ticket sales and not merit? Look at h… https://t.co/56NG4ev8N2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Lamp by @ocelotbrewing at @OcelotBrewing — https://t.co/luBKnRQv3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  IT is NOT a Eight to Own a @NFL team.. sure u have to have  city and a large location with a population base.… https://t.co/MHALTSZjBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationWomensDay #amotherslove #mamasboy #imissyou #iloveyou https://t.co/tM9pFsjMKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kchonyc @honglaklee @adampaulcoates To give credit, I was also very influenced by Michele Banko and Eric Brill's c… https://t.co/vWPHpk0gyN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO We! We! Does She have a Mouse in her Pocket?!?! Along with that Fried Bologna Sammich!🙄🔫]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epcot #waltdisneyworld #prajznersinvadedisney #werehome #epcot #ball @ Epcot - Walt Disney World https://t.co/AAKMiAyby2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetrishakelly Hang in their. And stay in love with your story. Love conquors all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I keep having waves of anxiety and panic all night. I’m really having a rough time and my self esteem is really low… https://t.co/MOEyRujlJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanawrites Lorelei Gilmore, Raven Reyes, Emma Swan, Temperance Brennan, Leslie Knope, Elena Alvarez, Rosa Diaz, Am… https://t.co/O692x8eCQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crikey! Today's #google #doodle took my on an emotional journey.   RIP #SteveIrwin]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of my team, wish i had been at sunyac. But you fam for life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_DopeLolo But what happened two days ago? I saw a body bag but got no reports]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not a sports related tweet but @abc7ashley I love your dress haha #WhatsBrewing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FerAlvarez #SOSVenezuela vamos chamos, adelante. El mundo tiene los ojos en ustedes. #SOSNICARAGUA estamos en el círculo de espera]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StevenWThomas1 @RealJamesWoods Mr Garrison ... https://t.co/c5mbxhIXOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sesttle,WA:- A walk up and down the market, a gum wall, a beautiful view and some wine tasting. A busy and fun firs… https://t.co/OVYpgGjalS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SimplyMARAvelousMitzvah @ Independence Grove Forest Preserve https://t.co/aoNy8ap5JL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day today: @AlabamaMBB @aafiron @bhmlegion all have home games. @AuburnMBB @UAB_MBB all playing away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[xaviergonzalesbmx @blackoutbmx kinkbmx @evssports @officialleatt @fuelclothing proteus_bmx demonunited bfmwbmx… https://t.co/ivxL1HRTy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Behavioral Resource Technician, Nights - https://t.co/kVisJJWCaw #Springfield, MA #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejschaefer @gotchasaurus @JacobPadilla_ Played for that coach and we were given pizza for holding a opponent un… https://t.co/XraaEZRjKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“One for all and all for one!” The Three Musketeers opens TONIGHT at @LincolnParkArts ! ⚔️ Break a leg everyone 👏 https://t.co/dPrEKbPjvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @Espngreeny Tell the truth! @ZionW32 has to do what’s best for him, not what everyone else thinks he should do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good news. Procedure worked. Now hope it holds. At least I no longer feel quite so exhausted. #goodoutcomes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zachary J. Cook: Removal of Governor Michelle Lujan Grisham from office - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/aEX3yUZjCE via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[I set my cruise control to 65 because there was a cop behind me, he got annoyed and passed me so now I’m comfortably going 80]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anything for my ❤️ lawanafreeman Love you Mrs. Freeman #happyvalentinesday @ Freeman Music Production https://t.co/hbzdALecRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Centralising and harmonising data across these large cohort studies and across brain disorders is going to be an im… https://t.co/9JvwbdM1vO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching the #ElvisAllStarTribute with my 13 yr old daughter. There’s no age to be an @ElvisPresley fan. He’ll alwa… https://t.co/RhMvlt1WMa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Biography of Alicia Keys Written by: SPC Joel L. York https://t.co/DnjUgnG9Nt (Ret.) Military Police Corps 501st Mi… https://t.co/XQfkgSnWll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisVanHollen You have a lot of nerve about not being able to trust William Barr you worthless POS! You sir are a… https://t.co/irsbQBbvhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[La esperanza o por lo menos la mía y siempre confiando en Dios, es que de los días más duros puede venir un cambio… https://t.co/zS4MuMfz4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gave a stranger a ride to school this morning. Got my good deed for the day out of the way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Double Blazed Orange Milkshake by @HopButcher @ MyZoomZoom — https://t.co/TBoBufovki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TourSportsman @tfisher44 @AlanShipnuck I think you’ll like my new video Vignettes on here and cool,older stuff I w… https://t.co/HEtvmhjcyj]]></document><document><![CDATA[It never gets old...hearing "Welcome to Cleveland" when I land...I'm home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Foutsy_96 It’s not, sorry you can’t handle reality of a situation. If you’re in a relationship where you are takin… https://t.co/PPvPVahxUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to UM. I can’t wait for the Penn’s Peak show. That is all, carry on.]]></document></documents></author>