<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@steveaustinBSR @SCOTTHALLNWO @FightOwensFight @DickTubs You need to give credit where it's due. @ChicoElLuchador taught you how to do that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tech Xplore: Wave device could deliver clean energy to thousands of homes. https://t.co/rPOeHOWlNJ  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early look at tomorrow’s Detroit Free Press front page. https://t.co/VahARWgjZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick work handcheck with some @blackhatvapors Bandits Bourbon  duvo.usa_mods V3 @528customs Goon 1.5 #thursday… https://t.co/4FL318VTMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pbcmike98 The Belgic Confession  The Doctrine of Original Sin (Article 15)  We believe that by the disobedience of… https://t.co/ed65OzRPnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColumbusCrewSC when are we getting our season tickets? A week out a still haven’t seen them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When cleaning up the rubble everyone needs to grab one of those bibles and READ THEM!   🙏we ALL NEED TO READ THE BI… https://t.co/0xqvNCgBvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachShawnQuinn Your Christian faith will guide you every step of the way. The Lord opened this position for you t… https://t.co/MtjdT44lU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is executive time. Trump’s watching the news and twitter. This is executive time. He’ll soon… https://t.co/FiMLAKCh1z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plainville MA new municipal complex open house @ Plainville, Massachusetts https://t.co/hH75twRb7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@egoltz @stephietweets @DraftDiamonds @Billsfan1516 @thedudeadam101 @lno09281978 @Crazy4OReilly90 @only_flip_flops… https://t.co/1OYXB4OGb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[So Will I (Do It Again) - Cross Worship feat. Osby Berry https://t.co/2wqBYEmiKt via @YouTube As you speak a hundre… https://t.co/m10fFF9Han]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Don't forget the ending of bussing, thus effectively re-segregating schools, the vilification of so called "we… https://t.co/WQFMDNTU4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyFull @Kyle_Bauer @Bobosphere You don’t get to lecture someone on quibbling about bullshit when you’re the o… https://t.co/nDnbRtOkte]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to the Facebook community living in Scenery Hill and going to Bentworth High School does not make you a l… https://t.co/lvTOmYRfyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@get_it_maggie @bonaevolentatis @lcby @images_mc @djinnxxi @JenSutt6971 @texbrodave1 @mch19600 @aarostew… https://t.co/Ks1cKcQ7cU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jstrachm This is bad and there are no signs of life on the horizon either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[happiest of birthdays to my girl bjthomas416. you are truly a sister to me, and I wouldn’t be half the man I am tod… https://t.co/EbTJU7EmjD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was at the self check out at target and the lady next to me scanned these cheap sunglasses and then called a work… https://t.co/Sdr8h9f0Ov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pedrioa will be what slows the 2019 Sox down, he needs to just go away. Zero respect for for him. #BadTeammate… https://t.co/dUr9zsCpaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forrest Gump because I want to recite all the lines and I don't need anyone seeing me cry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who watches better porn, Girls or Guys? #dinglebarrydoesitagain #standupcomedy #paperheroescomics #comedy #porn… https://t.co/7RrNRyTh30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cancunbound2022 @cowboys20041 @Mharris888H @AbrahamAlyzah @bushie200 @Black_is_back5 @schjoe1 @AlexMLeo… https://t.co/PXr3hHIXRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Raiders trade Kelechi Osmele to the #Jets | #NFLFreeAgency https://t.co/PnJCMRVYDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@137pm One more hr a day is like two or three yrs longer in life! Definitely life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealBrianWatt This country is about to learn a brutal lesson about weed, if you carry that addictive gene and are… https://t.co/WjbRR2QCNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shayn_Mikel @IndianaJedi Fair enough. Was only thinking of Red Squadron. The default one in my head canon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luvnewinfo @IPOBPill2 @1GaryBernstein @seashorewoman @VanidaPeters @1776KAG @Hiqutipie @kwilli1046 @QmagaMike… https://t.co/ZzN7aTT3F9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if our #Commodore64 still runs? @Schoolisaswamp, we could play a round of Carmen San Diego or print a cool… https://t.co/Rg9RFWNkEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@christmas_nel @OnigiriJikook @BTS_twt @Adonis_Hoseok @AHOPE218 Holy smokes! At first I thought I was looking at a… https://t.co/jJPrz3aCye]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenciadeideas El peor olor de la vida. Prenda alguna candela con aroma o esencias.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s on! Live @ThisMightBeAPod watching Don’t Let’s Start video. @NoisyChairs https://t.co/hi0PamQ3DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@leesargent I don’t think I’ve seen it since the theatre. Thankfully, I’ve forgotten most of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Massvwatches @LAKauffman @POkoumou And my point is, if it’s against the law, should they just ignore it? If the po… https://t.co/gdpzuwL1Un]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just remembered I tried to teach someone to salsa last night I DONT KNOW HOW TO SALSA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home inspections are generally inexpensive compared to the kind of repairs they can uncover. If you wait to find ou… https://t.co/Q1ECDyxMpZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I heard once that all that spirituality is is learning how to SEE ... Inwardly and outwardly. . . In thinking about… https://t.co/U3ebPP3AAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen’s authenticity pounded Jordan. Trump having a bad day. His GOP lap dogs look pathetic. #BlueWave2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamYanetGarcia Yanet , te ves preciosa , espectacular y súper sexy en Hoy te amo me encantas besos 😍😘😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I actually happy? Or is this a figment of my imagination ? https://t.co/FObd7sYub9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Best Websites and Web Apps for Making Use of Exactly One Hour of Free Time&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; https://t.co/u168zIgAk9 via @gizmodo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@11hullinger @larry_mowry is one of the best! Sharp eye and great communication]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morganhousel Fixed low debt cost vs rising wages with very little to no exotic debt structures post 2010. Also, a… https://t.co/zgDYSICc9X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCalvisi FYI, the PG in Nike PG 2.5 does not stand for point guard, it stands for Paul George. @DougandWolf987]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been standing in her yard with this milkshake for over three hours. I'm starting to think that my dyslexia has foiled me once again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBCHereandNow people with children think that study was for you? Lol. It’s for informed consent of childless people 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeDunham Awesome using “When the Curtain Falls” on return this morning! Keep supporting Greta Van Fleet!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarperMitchell @Mxjhymz1 @sapinker @DemSocialists It seems like a far-fetched dystopia to me. Reality is messier.… https://t.co/cG7Htba07g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when @gop invited this criminal to rebuke the president of the United States at the time @BarackObama ?  Y… https://t.co/AfBcCf5zmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheeWham @OhSoDev Boy you better pray some game cause you have none. Thank you next.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JycYNqzRhQ it's because she nuts and she admited it oh and she not human this she admited is that crazy or what]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RatCatcherMpls This is going to be your “Paulie Sparing video” isn’t it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a big one. #IAWild beat @griffinshockey 4-3 in OT. Big Bart on a feed from Capt. Cal. Right guys, right place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Forego137 Might have just felt the sooner he got him out of Santa Anita the better]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marco Roy, in his first game back from Laval of the higher-level American Hockey League, tied it at 2 by snapping a… https://t.co/vqnb5uGllp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @ACONNECTIONTV Made by image.downloader · · · · https://t.co/O41sKAtQy1 is the world's new diverse internet… https://t.co/fUnRb7UyHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takes a strong and confident person to stand up for what you believe in and not follow the masses.   Follow what yo… https://t.co/htIsPfijZP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Litty? 🎉 @myfabolouslife at #draisnightclub Celebrating @nascar We Out here lasvegas https://t.co/GsRH3fKzfL Joi… https://t.co/aCCiji0V3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeftwardSwing She has a background as an environmentalist, so she probably has some legit concerns. I wouldn't hold it against her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UltraHDBluray @DeshanRandika @engadget @PlayStation Which mistake. Not including a 4k player? If so i believe at t… https://t.co/DgA10Pfofo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ken McElrath a jumper from the right side. @raidersofshaker 45, @TwinsburgTigers 39 #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyJazzSux @TMLutas @jckennedy70 @solomon_rotty @Higashi6969 @househound007 @RepMcGovern @realDonaldTrump I enjo… https://t.co/Rba6u6apmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gainesm @annietheblank @adamvanho @KaraCalavera @AOC To me, it's like healthcare or education. The rest of the wor… https://t.co/OSABAcBVW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodPrevails17 @MarylFaunda @POTUS I’m just sayin... https://t.co/EzUJVRrWIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roger Stone Says Michael Cohen Is Lying, After Stone Was Ordered Not To Comment On The Mueller Investigation https://t.co/OZfwJZau9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@giantsprospects @Garcia_Daniel30 In recorded games anyway. He should be playing fairly consistently up until that… https://t.co/HPWBJMMC6i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time #creeper @ Fort Zachary Taylor Historic State Park https://t.co/r6HjwNdvOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CodeMageHattraz Ah, it's a milestone for one of my classes this semester. Building a simple AI with movement, targ… https://t.co/FsBF7g8aim]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beloved grandmother about 5 years old. #restinpeace @ Simi Valley, California https://t.co/WgSPy8tlvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidKPiano Totally agree. It was declared here so it would be available in React context under the object object… https://t.co/Z8mZ3P8qrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DreadheadTWill He is better than Zeke, sorry. He had 91 catches 700 receiving yards and 1300 rushing yards behind… https://t.co/hyoiS5ucYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dang 8 years ago yesterday I some how ended up in the front row. Pat  Healy vs Lyle Beerbohm.  What ever happened t… https://t.co/M4oxh8ldIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am a Cancer and that's why i'm so fresh in the next couple of us sitting in the middle of a bitch.  HELLO WHAT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Same As It Ever Was same as it ever was water flowing Underground, you may ask yourself where is my huge Cadillac c… https://t.co/sFsJuNPDI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OmarLopez0207 @Procreate @Ian_Barnard Impressive! #EveryoneCanSketch #EveryoneCanCreate 🎨🖌]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part of the smarter, more economical way of getting work done. No need to put in a 3-4 hour workout if you do it th… https://t.co/Ot61HJQc3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenmatichuk @biscuitpancakes Literally biscuit pancakes.  I'll see myself out now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Former @nyknicks guard @LangGalloway10 with the sick Rocket Power kicks. Shoobie. https://t.co/gwQ8MmFutN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be kind to the causes that you fight.  Be kind to the contributors of light. Be kind to the people who just might.… https://t.co/tAUsXMKaMf]]></document><document><![CDATA[LHS Bowling in State Championship Match today. Get it done Dores! Leave no pin standing. ⚓️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke_johnson100 @milosevans Wait you don’t have papers how we gonna go to pro events]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey friends 👋🏻 The parking lots will probably be full at your favorite resort this weekend. It’s another great reas… https://t.co/EQ5q75x92p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/1XanWydb2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts are the real hustlers of this country, 4 different scouts have hustled me for 6 boxes of cookies.... respect @girlscouts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure that discrediting Cohen by calling him a lying scumbag will work when it's clear that Trump kept him aroun… https://t.co/lbc6x0sVyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@info7mty Es un problema en ese rio, siempre hay gente estupida que mete sus camionetas por todo el rio contaminand… https://t.co/GwKigudNll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DPWelles @jdholland @scottrileyx Aww, thats nice of you to say! It was nice running into you in Vegas btw:-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treeman233 @MysticDragonMxr Aww your supporting your friends!!! Good job!!! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @Write_the_World Question for you: Top of your head do you know of teen writing programs in Atlanta? Perhaps a… https://t.co/GkUUoemoS1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, everybody. Warmer temps are coming by Sunday. March is a crazy month. Have a great Friday and weekend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimIversenShow @4everquestion @dawnbro98968959 @DraftTulsi @jimmy_dore @RonPlacone @KyleKulinski @HumanistReport… https://t.co/MyWqJzDdaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀 this thread on what we should think of when we think of “density” and “urbanism”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it SOUP yet? Wonderful wall of Warhol...part of an awesome Whitney Museum retrospective of  the POP ART phenomen… https://t.co/jrkXdlFvmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreyJfrey @CoachHelmer @WorldExposureWB Hill!!! Like no disrespect to their players and coaches I’m sure they work… https://t.co/I0LJZTm5ie]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what makes shows like @OfficialLivePD special!  Being able to see how things are done all over! #livePD… https://t.co/lVwFd3FQGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there a way to stop Google Amp resultss from showing in search results on Android other than the obvious not using Google?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCJ10 No real reason to post this except I hate the Yankees https://t.co/s1gPa0bidj]]></document><document><![CDATA[High growth is high stress. Or at least high pressure. It just is.  The key is having a boss that has your back.  Go find that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We know he doesn’t hold his tongue, that’s obvious, and he’s a moron, that’s a fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBauer81 I'm not on a pro-or-anti climate warming crisis change payroll. Climate is and always will change. Con… https://t.co/aPEjRmWZNh]]></document></documents></author>