<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[So sad for his family. Way to young. RIP @ Upper West Side https://t.co/pIZy9TDwdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinhenny I can bake brownies but dont have a masters degree lol. The main thing is do exactly what the directions. say.( no shorcuts lol)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @EZ_Lerner Makes you want to laugh at these people until you think about all the harm they are doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuaTheFoxy @grendelsmumm I kill the spiders at my house but Pete has asked me not to at his, so the tradeoff there… https://t.co/kbytKpNznM]]></document><document><![CDATA[That game was exhausting to watch even before the final fifteen seconds. Really tough loss in Lincoln. Hope the… https://t.co/rzKYArmYUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to buy a PrePaid Visa Gift Card to convert cash to bitcoin but unknowingly bought a debit card and accidentall… https://t.co/4JQDFzueTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for Joy, Sunny, Abby and Meghan (get well Whoopi) @ ABC Television https://t.co/zr1codb3bT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your purpose seems to be just insulting folks instead of talking about legislation. Calling someone a shit head ill… https://t.co/WUdCuzJ38p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I submit to you your evening plans (assuming you live in the Cville area). We love this place for its beer and food… https://t.co/h9kTVua8LW]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I know its a different time in his career but just seems that he isn't staying in the moment anymore. Its as if… https://t.co/qvhz9mgM9W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went 3-1 in our tournament to place third overall in points. @borahdawson #hockey @ Lou &amp; Gib Reese Ice Arena https://t.co/eLoK7zxQVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esto acaba de suceder en la #Daytona500.  @FOXDeportes #NASCARenFD https://t.co/ibKGyov4h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kubedex Thanks for the follow! Please check out my blog:   https://t.co/BPzKPSRj1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Nightingale Plaza - @nightingale_la in West Hollywood, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/Tm0v4ggz2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elijah_Reaves @ryanhunt00 @YoungDonDeity Texas will release your inner cowboy 🤠]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t realize how bad it was in Venezuela until I saw pictures of kids eating out of a garbage truck smh wow and… https://t.co/oYpDVcyQrg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaGConnell Her and Kathy Griffin on tech was really comforting to hear. (Kathy dragged senate committees for not knowing anything)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 going to the Raiders is great! He will be in a crap town, play in a crap stadium, play for a coach that's pas… https://t.co/2zYzi2MlhY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kali and I twinned today without even planning it 🤘🏼 @ Platos Closet - Canton, OH https://t.co/LVnztgqzdb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“New York, New York. A city so nice they named it twice.” 🌇 ———————————————————————— #weekend #NYC #Manhattan #love… https://t.co/Hlyjo0f0pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar @karenhunter @GayleKing Handle it with poise and intellect. Definitely a woman of the year!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your chancleta breaks at Jungle Island and there is a lighting crew near by that has tie wraps🤣😂… https://t.co/WB7HGpiBBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BitsieTulloch @mistergiuntoli Y’all look like a famous pair I’ve seen before. https://t.co/KsoZLj8wjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 Long beach hospital new jersey, in the USA, when politics were civil, and no such thing as social media, and Howdy Doody was on TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoverRadio @RMGCharlie are you not on today or did they take you off Dayton, Ohio @AltDayton ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EastDistrictAB This is BS and you know it! I’ll donate a map if you need!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnv378 @HillaryClinton @MichelleObama @mayawiley @MHarrisPerry @soledadobrien @JoyAnnReid @Sifill_LDF… https://t.co/XvQV1269Id]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve seen it all. i’ve just seen stephen a. smith live on ESPN w a jean jacket and a turtle neck on]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #InternationalWomenDay celebrating some of the most inspiring people I know @ros_harvey @theyield]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Free #American Stands for all #Human #God Given #Rights #Freedoms &amp; #Liberties Guaranteed under the US… https://t.co/obRDbbT6g4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not asking this cause ion wanna judge you I’m just curious. What is your sexuality? Gay, bisexual or lesbian? 🌈💯 I’m bi 🌈💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnaValenciaIL Thank you Anna for coming out today in support of the men &amp; women of the Chicago Police Department.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffsleasman @Lrochellew Advocates deserve ALOT of credit on what has been achieved so far. Years of collaboration and education.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aqui led va mi #tbt con @themusicpimp de @laxmasmusica @UribeDJ https://t.co/vt8HB6TgqO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ElChapo: c’est incroyable comme ce procès est sujet d’intérêt autour du monde. J’ai vu des journalistes français,… https://t.co/6NIdWAF1BB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacer0317 @southcarolinafb Wofford cause granddaddy went there  Presbyterian cause name is blue hose Citadel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live on STREAMING THE MAGIC⠀ and https://t.co/0SPSvvt42P⠀ https://t.co/1oZIhodN4X⠀ @ Celebration, Florida https://t.co/GzXzMzQMMH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoRichardsKent @moonrakerkih @margarethodge @thetimes the level of control in which one institution has over anoth… https://t.co/tnvrCqmYqS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Spencermusic1 @madisoniseman That’s some funny sh.... there madison !! Love that kitty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nina &amp; I are celebrating my daughter in law's birthday remotely. Wish you were here. Happy 30th Ellie! #family… https://t.co/xamUU7lxTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Songs sound better to me when other people play it lol I think that’s just me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not 1 tweet about C. Hasson and what he was planning for the Dem Senators. You our the biggest 💩 to live in the WH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tú eres quien voló adentro del sol yo sólo vine a asegurarme de que ardas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I strongly feel I would be significantly less attractive without my beard and thus, I will never shave it off]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EJames9029 Althougg you will need some knowledge to do this right.  Or ask any 10 year old. 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[He needed to step down a long time ago! Plus his pizza’s terrible anyway.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Farcmolkman @jacobdpuck @CJMcCollum Home is actually canton for him but close enough. Cavs bound]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYPDDetectives @NYPDnews @NYPDChiefofDept @NYPDONeill @NYPDChiefPatrol @NYPDCommAffairs @NYPD102Pct @NYCPDDEA… https://t.co/4yLDG9hgLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul @penndragonArt True, since 2012 &amp; 0 followers, 0 following, BLOCKED!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really annoyed because as much as I knew Jussie been lying, and I been mad at him, the logic part of my brain i… https://t.co/fkfS9H5swQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t feel like absolute shit after eating McDonald’s you didn’t succeed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cocalico to eliminate valedictorian and salutatorian in shift away from class rank competition https://t.co/7b43ypYDcx via @lancasteronline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Riley_King412 Today I ate: Italian bread with sauce, a cookie, Swedish fish, pretzels, cake and probably some more bad stuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toro628 As I said, you've confirmed a lot. And, sadly, lines were crossed. Best to you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sushi heaven.. Thank you Chef Jackson Yu &amp; your staff for the dope experience!!! jacksonyu_omakase @omakase_sf… https://t.co/1gCwDt6YzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GWPattie @jdavey_2 @Jayfan34 @bruce_arthur I really hope one day we can have a right-of-center party that doesn’t… https://t.co/m5X5xKYOGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Headed home for the last time on this project!  Feeling good. (@ Newark Liberty International Airport in Newark, NJ) https://t.co/u5SdsEj8kM]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 miles down. 17 more to go. The sunrise was nice. #charitywater https://t.co/DVVWzRsfeP https://t.co/WUt4F50Jew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@physicianswkly T6 Getting off the hamster wheel. Taking way better care of patients. Practicing medicine the way y… https://t.co/edzr0U7qFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@opusken1215 @realDonaldTrump Nice of trump to save Mueller the cost of digging his own grave  Read WSJ story on *f… https://t.co/Bu3haFdwzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScoopMiller @brockmealer Wrong. Maybe 1 out of a hundred but generally the more gifted athlete prevails.]]></document><document><![CDATA[End of Report. Y'all let Mr. Mueller go to bed.  #LightsOut https://t.co/WMv5DGHAF6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft a plaidé non coupable   Moi je le crois  Me semble ça marche pas  Kraft qui paye pour se faire manger… https://t.co/vnOjmxmNyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL You think he won , let’s see what happens this year it’s going to be funny shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[I show students the ways that systems track us, and then we visualize stuff in class like our iTunes listens or Net… https://t.co/ZaB10cjGXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khaIeesi_ i’ll make you the most flame sam hamwich ur eyes have ever seen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again, West was the best player on the pitch. I may have a new crush... #S04SCF https://t.co/hYfXQBbsCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first episode of @DocumentaryNow season 3 is a two parter and it is beyond incredible. Part two is quite possib… https://t.co/kptznILn2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Women is held in Montana and  arrested for speaking Spanish in a grocery store, was arrested by border agents. Is t… https://t.co/JqbdRfdxld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MPerlman4 Damn another one from channel 4!! Good luck, luved watching u on channel 4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to meet @RoastLox online in WWE so I could throw he off a ladder]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can't believe Torrie got in the HOF before Sterling Sharpe and Leroy Butler. #Raw #GoPackGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cat just rolled off my chest asleep; emergency landing gear deployed on way down. I was considering having my nippl… https://t.co/xRDdJ5kjdX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gpeal8 @joannezchen @tonal Love deadlifting, and leg press. This is super cool, but I would still need a large weight set.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been a big LeBron fan but one thing I’ve always admired about him is his efficiency this is a guy that w… https://t.co/ux2ho80W52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyMusgraves @shaylynnmzigler @RedRocksCO @paramountdenver Gorgeous eyes..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kendra Scott is hiring in #Austin, TX! Read about our latest #BusinessMgmt job opening via the link in our bio: Vice President Wholesale]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like an adult I have $31 in my saving and I’m not tempted to touch it]]></document><document><![CDATA[There will be two #HR1 panels. The first has a lineup that includes some great democracy champions like… https://t.co/mRkekAmsSC]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao be grateful that they actually care 😂🤦🏾‍♂️ wish my parents were on my case ab mine]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏡Open House: Sunday, March 3rd, 12-2pm  718 Grand Street, Hoboken #OpenHouse #Sunday #March #starter #starterhome… https://t.co/mjNmhDPmjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Alex Trebek, I wish you the very best, may God heel you and protect you.  Sending prayers your way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flores_carlos08 @porlagoma Dudamel nunca fue empleado público y efectivamente le hacía lobby al chavismo para que… https://t.co/7GERtE8Jgz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thenameisito Stay up homie! Self awareness is the key and you have it. I'm not a professional or anything but if y… https://t.co/ZGN1lrf3Ba]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m out of ideas @cityofbarrie - the apt. across the street pushes their snow to my side. The plow pushes it in our… https://t.co/xOL3s2b2Pv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@priored @BlakePriceTSN Because anything that contradicts your opinion MUST be wrong.  It’s an echo chamber.  So I… https://t.co/2E3H6pQU5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachLashSr Richmond Sr. had become stale before Coach Till came in. He brought a new mindset to the program. He d… https://t.co/OyHDUry8bT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKidPoker @NHLHockeyBets 2 questions sir, who are you cheering for TML/VGK and what casinos take the grand sala… https://t.co/osexATerLA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bharper3407 Make today the day please. Philly is ready to embrace you and buy some jerseys #BeBold]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RingFalcon All I can say is that we are human. It’s our nature to look for something else once we have achieved wh… https://t.co/vZC8PElgVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattlarimer @andreanogarry @DrJoshMadden @CorbyAmos It's years out. Right now it's just in my head. Gotta get book #1 out first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope all you Trump supporters walk directly into a brick wall thank you in advance]]></document><document><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time flirting w the line between ‘patient’ and ‘slow’.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanb1888 He got out of the shows, this is reason he make this fake accusations in 2013. https://t.co/OiBRMoUfIX]]></document><document><![CDATA[E.M. Bounds- “We have emphasized sermon preparation until we have lost sight of the important thing to be prepared—… https://t.co/UMe2sHALlz]]></document><document><![CDATA[And it’s funny, the Leafs should be the most confident team ever because Andersen is probably a top 3 goalie. What… https://t.co/eM429uCRzV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PierceLilholt They follow the same rules and standards as all large corporations under heavy scrutiny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coach Rosenthal providing an update on the preseason schedule for @AustinMaroonFB at our first booster club meeting… https://t.co/9oNFltOgw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz #RussianRoulette - Complicit #Trump Republicans do nothing while scared #democrats slow play… https://t.co/NZUTETc8mP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope @AndrewHolnessJM take note. I’ve been telling him on his timeline for some time now that this was coming. Hi… https://t.co/JancORbYGB]]></document></documents></author>