<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[PC babies I see you guys reaching 40 years back. Here reach some more!   George “slave owner” Washington   Thomas “… https://t.co/dwxOxrJoh0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell me how I got so lucky with Sammi???? It leaves me speechless just thinking how amazing she treats me a… https://t.co/109dcdZrCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melihubb @ScottJShearer thought this #MicrosoftFlow gear was appropriate for @PowerApps911 App-in-a-day 😜😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tu identidad hace la diferencia. No es lo que te pones.   • • • 🌅 #goodmorning #good_morning #toptags #morning… https://t.co/1wG4hN1jiX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot wait until summer vacation. Just 3 months, 2 weeks and 1 day left until #MyrtleBeach I'm not counting or anything though. 🏖️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning. McPaper with bad news for Trump loving truth fleeing climate deniers: https://t.co/hlblv75mrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do-over bc #illegalcensorship. I looked up that word grift :" a group of methods for obtaining money falsely throug… https://t.co/7SBQGWAkOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesaphd @HDITony @rex_hartley @stephanie101312 @MillieFinch13  look at this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This thing right here says it all. It sums up a high school career full of hard work, dedication and love of his sc… https://t.co/wSW6sVbC2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[*sickest i’ve ever been in my life on the way to rome. lindsey dopes me up on a ton of medicine before our first fl… https://t.co/X5kG17dnO2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I wanna go to law school and become a lawyer, but I’m also a dumbass so I don’t think it’s in the cards]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isaphila @jeffpastva @TheeFerringer @L2DesignLLC @schmangee I lived in a Trinity in Philly for four years, this ho… https://t.co/5Yo0GM0GLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinLathia @ManishKAghi @sdurkinbarnes @CCLRI @TylerAlban1 @CraigHorbinski Being a scientist doesn’t mean one ca… https://t.co/a9tjxhOAaI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javierdecanini @addiemoreno @ghdezf21 @Vickyasp @Piedrulces "No es competencia para ver quien esta mas jodido" "En… https://t.co/skX2L0rknP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marcos makes me the absolute happiest. Like I didn’t know being this happy was possible]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The only person you are destined to become is who you decide to be.” Ralph Waldo Emerson #LiveMyBestLife]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtree39 Yup one of my students instantly tried to become my bff/talk about kdramas when she learned I was korean… https://t.co/Fev5cKckuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[en que semestre ya dejas de preocuparte por no reprobar y no tener que repetir el semestre?? mi panciencia está acabando]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a visit to the Battleship Texas here in Houston. What a treat. Got to run around the ship exploring everything,… https://t.co/AgPdfcDm84]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you flying anytime soon with your kids? Here are a few tips to keep you (and your kids) sane:… https://t.co/ltUsoNTqSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you have a #band and #ball at home? Send me a message and I'll send you my latest playlist at @maitrainer ! •  •… https://t.co/r61tVhovz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me sum up my day: ducks tank, my fav on the challenge goes home, I got conditioner in my eye, my puppy is a DEM… https://t.co/eAHS8bfguM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UROCKlive1 @MollyJongFast How much did the Wharton diploma cost daddy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntv_sukkiri @joshgroban 30 million. That's absolutely awesome. Congratulations Josh!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder If she is really sorry, she should give back every dime she ever made and all the money/privileges she… https://t.co/mVIZ8f2YBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaylaRimpson Hey!! Seriously, looks great. Good for you.can I park my car in your garage??]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only thing keeping me up while studying is listening to legado 7 y fuerza regida]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaininLawson @powhite99 don’t do it unless you wanna eat someone else’s pizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes things change for the better &amp; it just takes some time to realize it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Just waiting to find out what the price was for @LindseyGrahamSC's soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnieFeighery Hooray! See you Wednesday. We have team members there both days. Looking forward to seeing you here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[3am and i literally just sat up and said “ la casa blanco “ and layed back down. someone sos]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nwetsch @JulieYAli @ryanjespersen @Emilyfo04914299 @shawn73yuk @gjglenn What makes you believe that I’ve eaten hal… https://t.co/H9bFnjyf9c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another thing- I think people are disingenuous.  I've actually been sexually assaulted multiple times but because i… https://t.co/NuHsSe0xpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0eD5U42X2C 🆓 I'm doing this at 9am Today - Join Me –&gt; https://t.co/4jjd12VLrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston Unfortunately... you’re the LEAST of our problems, and your definitely not an asset to ANYTHING. Get o… https://t.co/pxYPCfLmcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle @DonaldJTrumpJr It's a shame that the president of the United States is using social media programs t… https://t.co/6yzlE0Ivtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! What will CNN do???? They may have to replace their part time employee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngieOverkill @IndivisibleNet @MMLunlimited The worst part is they know more about the USA than the citizens do]]></document><document><![CDATA[from around $19 million to $291 million to get a loan from Deutsche Bank for a billion dollars to buy the Buffalo B… https://t.co/pAgAWk4xZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raincompany_ @CloudThai U  can say I love my wife so you dont get in trouble   as long u dont touch  her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@420bitchin Grain free cat food! It boosts metabolism and productivity and because it's higher in protein it's more… https://t.co/beopuxl49p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome group! @NealHarris6 Thank you again! See you in a few years for Store Manager training. ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karlbykarlsmith @Noahpinion @dylanmatt @EnriqueDiazAlva but equally vulnerable to disease or a long siege 🖖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doritnyc @jaketapper Weird how he so casually talks about falling “in love” w/KJU while being conflicted over his… https://t.co/iwweS1vx8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Caught Crazy~by🌟TecN9ne🔥https://t.co/5p2WtPP6DX❤🖤🎧🎶🎵🔥🔥#TechN9nespledidamente]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doc cleared me for shoveling just in time for our latest snowfall!! https://t.co/GxQkIgcyfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyKitching Yes! People pleasing is a very unhealthy manifestation of codependency.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRadloff I did not know that she had MS . A very dear friend of mine has and is forging  on. I wish the same for Miss Blair]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this terrorist Soros? That sounds like a threat to our President and sounds like Soros is behind all that is… https://t.co/HclSA6E1gP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s great when people take the time out of their day to show you how important you are to them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Consider this... Andre Drummond has made more threes than Ben Simmons has attempted]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad.....'90210' star Luke Perry dies, his publicist says https://t.co/K7TI2Izbf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisJZullo @realDonaldTrump Intelligent ppl don’t want to flip it. And they can save $5 too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino Is this from that million dollar plus expense account they all get????]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of @CadenHagler. It wasn’t the outcome we had hoped for, but we are still super proud!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EllisBht 2 Shoes= 30÷3=10  2 men = 20 - 10 = 10 2 ties= 13 - 5 = 8  Final answer = 5 + 5 × 2= 15]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulaGrabow @Minerva8918 Yeah really! How shameful! Gosh, just the thought of her pis*es me off!! Hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson July 4th would be a splendid time for a march in the streets]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbara_lopez21 @macabeso desde NYC 🍎 #juliantina https://t.co/2sg1iNwFmL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heal2bfree @ElaineHRivera1 @BrettVanderH2O @waynecooksys @JoyceGarcia215 @OptimumAmerica @Graceat555 @LernerJohn… https://t.co/Bfd8f6EE7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing is worse than sitting through a lecture with a high fever and sore throat and all you want to do is go home and sleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[Code Blue in effect until Friday, March 1 at 8am via @NYCDHS. #helpthehomeless]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudacityOfHoops @JoeySalads @zig314 @JonathanM0ral35 @AOC Could you be a bit more specific?]]></document><document><![CDATA[icefield.slick.shiny.almost irredscent white.shimmers in early morning light. it's coat of ice the remnants of yest… https://t.co/YOxQ2Bpx3A]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one time I DONT buy early bird check in, I get a B group boarding position despite checking in RIGHT at the 24-… https://t.co/GY5CWshjJP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things are moving! I might have a first spot for us to start #freeyourfearnonprofit https://t.co/gNK0VBFCKW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweeettweetie Sick of all these F@ckers telling us what Trump said when we heard with our own ears what he damn well said!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come by and see our homes in El Campo, Tx. Beautiful neighborhood nestled in a country setting. 979-543-2169. @ Cou… https://t.co/aEIn4KvoHK]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is everyone not in love with me IT DOESNT MAKE SENSE, IT DOESNT ADD UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @dawnzy23 Thank God these loons don’t get the final say🤦‍♀️🤯🤦‍♀️🤯🤦‍♀️🤯🤦‍♀️Liberal IDIOTS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[WIN the Cooking Keto Prize Pack full of cookbooks, ingredients, and meal plans! #giveaway #win https://t.co/mRHknWaB8a]]></document><document><![CDATA[This color is an oldie but a goodie. Raise your glass is the name of it. @dowens86 loves pink all the time. It’s HE… https://t.co/T3XIcmM7En]]></document><document><![CDATA[when she listens to el recodo......  @hellokyara https://t.co/plvanrGNiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eizamusica enjoying the set of alitamovie at #troublemakerstudios during @sxsw #sxsw ✨ @ Austin, Texas https://t.co/T3qSiF87uH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why oh why hasn’t wealthy Republicans started the same type of entity?  I just don’t get it.  Hire private investig… https://t.co/rwTi0LOevG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HAPPENINGNOW: President Trump is speaking following his meeting with North Korean Leader Kim Jong Un.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  How can the Democrats,lefts and sociologists say the border nightmare isn’t a national emergency.… https://t.co/6MpE8dNYps]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first thing I want when this baby is born is Monterey cheese dip! It’s been way too long lova! #9months #dryspell #gimmealldadip]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ooooo, I’m going through one of the most difficult phases in my life, but I’m making good decisions through it (alt… https://t.co/SDWHNFJsKz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fly high and touch the sky.🧚💫 #bloglife #makeupartist #blogspot #beautyblog #blogger #foodblogger #beautyguru… https://t.co/S59wt0SRsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh is the neighbor that State Farm wishes it could be. https://t.co/cyGrHSlrPn]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m so happy for him but i also can’t stop thinking about that one tweet a while ago that said he always looks like… https://t.co/nWhXaKzt3G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyaFay32 @kirstenlynee Look at that Beautiful. Little Girl❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Ribault now Kenny heads to the free throw line leading Ribault. The score is now 54-41@ https://t.co/BJw7Xn5Rtc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @SenSanders Bernie Sanders is NOT a Democrat.  He's the Democrats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents never bothered me so much then they should have when I was in misery now that I’m a little happy they go… https://t.co/wiG0RrpLf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So so happy to finally meet @HannahArtwork! I feel so lucky to be her tour guide today at Disneyland! 💕 • •… https://t.co/tLXZ0lYDEg]]></document><document><![CDATA[would u rather have long black hair or would you just have long hair that’s like brown , or blonde or copper (any color)]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up the day after a @KaceyMusgraves concert still in your fake eyelashes and covered in glitter… https://t.co/AbFb16qurK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Live your life like it’s GOLDEN! ✨👑🖤 #artist #live #perform #queen #lanalove #sing #love #getem @ Sofitel Los Angel… https://t.co/aYZGJ3b97O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley This is not a Repub or Dem thing but an American thing  Whose side are you on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter Ok. Too far Donald. She was one of your first supporters. Very early. She just wants a wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IrisWil82188689 No apology needed. I just responded on what believe is the definition of family. Nothing was wrong… https://t.co/PwRODMi1Qr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had an interesting conversation with @chmldc’s @GMonarchs this week about the varying degrees of bathroom freedom a… https://t.co/DYBZ4olOn3]]></document><document><![CDATA[i told this girl that i had a crush on a boy during recess, she double dog dared me to go kiss him, i did it really… https://t.co/yugeaYbk01]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @Andrea3rdGrade to post the covers of 7 books I ❤️. No explanation, no review, just… https://t.co/lfNxcmB4pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbaradye921 I would go to the principal or the school board if the school is of republican persuasion. I have no idea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for your support boo 😭❤️ here’s to my new career path in mental health 🦄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice @TheTreyRose @Avicii @aloeblacc Loved him and his story! #TheVoice]]></document></documents></author>