<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti This once is not a media circus these victims NEED to be heard a do your best please]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty excited about this show.  One of the most legendary beer joints in Austin.  It happened because of a bunch o… https://t.co/5p6lQEWOtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett is an embarrassment to the black community, as well as a detriment to the gay community. The next t… https://t.co/iJSFRan5ij]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maryland still has the NCAA tournament. Maryland can’t keep up with Megan Gustafson, falls to Iowa in Big Ten title… https://t.co/9St7hXHdto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spittinchiclets @RearAdBsBlog @ryanwhitney6 @BizNasty2point0 “Beauty” ??? I think you guys may have a listener in… https://t.co/g8CO67QoEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[2023 Shane Perry has been lighting it up all season. 6'3" and growing. One of the best shooters in his class. Finis… https://t.co/4xtVKRY1DH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavePriceTV @SU2C @letswinpc @CodePurpleNow I'm surviving with it for 22 months. Good luck to you and your brother… https://t.co/9je5ek6fu9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't forget the coaching changes. I firmly believe that piss poor coaching decisions resulted in that 6-10 record,… https://t.co/dcLaNU7Hju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champagneben He's really small and frail and freaking weird. He invited us to spaghetti dinner at the "lodge".  Fml]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work sooo much, I don’t know how to relax! #worklifebalance is out of sync. https://t.co/lYlYosY8qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like to bet any prideful son a bitch that doesn’t think “The departed” by Martin Scorsese will make want to… https://t.co/SXtA3TniMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[David Platt - God Hates &amp; Loves Sinners https://t.co/DdPRokiZRQ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can y’all mfs stop being fake horny for RT’s ?✋ some of us out here actually want to lose our bootyhole virginity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Migos @QuavoStuntin @OffsetYRN @1YoungTakeoff C U L T U R E II https://t.co/sVRJeUIm9o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen We already know that he's not mentally stable enough to lead the Country at anything !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So like, I’d shoot my shot @thecocojanelle, but I’m not quite ready for that honor just yet https://t.co/ho0Do6vr6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4UWell 💔That’s so hard to try to comprehend. That someone that was all of everything could look through you like you weren’t even there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FINALLY started shooting manually. 😂✊🏿 and that shit hits DIFF-ER-RENT.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final in Game 1  Burke 62 Avon 32  #GPCClashAtTheMount  Andes Central-Dakota Christian vs. Centerville up next]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen @graffitiwriter1 @realDonaldTrump Yea people smart enough to know you are a paid puppet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Emily34999161 @SupFletcher @sdclimateaction @sierraclubsd @SanDiego350 @sdaudubon @EHCSanDiego @sandiegozoo… https://t.co/tYrak283Hw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSNorthwest @Enes_Kanter @RonWyden @JamieHudsonNBCS He’s just a savy politician getting himself some pub. He’s not altruistic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dberrygannett @SenatorCollins So what will @SenatorCollins do ???  NOTHING I SUSPECT]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Standing on the defensive indicates insufficient strength; attacking a superabundance of strength.” Sun Tzu… https://t.co/uqIBDxgcBK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @RealMattyMcBoy The week is over and everyone liked my work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[... I'm also looking forward to vote! #firsttimevoter #USVoter @ACVOTE #registertovoteda #GeneralElections2020 #vote2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because everything is better with crumbles. —  #avotoast @YoteApp #SocialLab #iDontWorkHereButiWorkHere #tasty… https://t.co/vHiu42AWL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dafakerihanna Nah this ain’t it she looks like his mom though 😂 he sure moves on fast 👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dmgteach Unfortunately baseball isn’t an individual sport, and not all the good players are rewarded because you c… https://t.co/O9kRUG0nMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@roldanj1264 @VicenteFoxQue QUE SE LARGUE EL HIJO DE PUTA, NADIE LO VA A EXTRANAR Y LE HARIA UN BIEN AL PAIS.  LARG… https://t.co/LsFEt0ThiW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlitSplitter Yes I have.  The Norteno is not a morning smoke for me.  Full bodied and great for later in the day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cole_jacobs99 @JackSpencerr_ @nicholascefali @goknickstape https://t.co/AVkbgmJ2uy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nvk @MastodonProject Everyone should be in the business of deciding that Nazism is unacceptable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an unbelievable and heartbreaking disservice Jussie Smollett has done to minorities and actual victims of hate… https://t.co/VALETkGH4L]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @TheTayaValkyrie boobs are too strong for the Boobplex. @BarWrestling @SoloDarling @wolfinjapan https://t.co/DKdde0Chve]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNCP had 2 singles to start 3rd inning but Strickland got a double play grounder to Simpson. Carawba still up 1-0 bottom 3.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Democrats are so far left, they fell off the planet!!! There's always adoptions. So sad!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VSiNLive re-runs waiting on some @MitchMossRadio and @paulyhoward at 6am #AustinTX time 🤘🏽🏀🏒🏈⚾️ 💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMayfield6 I hope your minions don’t bite on this one. Would be historically sad. But also not surprising.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously: has anyone ever met a woman named Maddie that WASN’T attractive? #seriousquestion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mayawiley you were the best part of @RealTimers last night.  Great insight as always.     Big fan of your work on… https://t.co/L8RATTausG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marceloclaure Always great to come home Rylee #LoveYourPetDay https://t.co/SACcFoQHVy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saucy_jp93 @charliekirk11 @TPUSA I’m with you get the first punch on film theme whip his snowflake ass]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ 5Th Floor Or Near Earth Orbit Apartmess 509 https://t.co/eh8Z8fYAGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[MY MOM JUST SENT ME THE SHAWN MENDES CALVIN KLEIN PICTURES LIKE I DIDNT ALREADY SEE THEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StillComup Never fucked a brown or darkskin nigga in my life. All my exes Drake's color or lighter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamelHerring Damn.. Great guy, always showed me support in the amateur tournaments.. R.I.P. Coach 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las 10 chuladas del “Napito” https://t.co/xurmrPut50 vía @El_Universal_Mx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CourtneyBot_XX The coup in Venezuela happened whenthe Opposition won 2/3 of the seats in the National Assembly, an… https://t.co/ocy2O8yj59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OMAHATIGERS @TheLesNozzle @OmahaTigers2026 @ubanebraska Looking good fellas! Keep improving🙌🏽👋🏽 🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonHepworth3 @letterboxd It says it is not available in America!!!😳😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Read the OCC’s third annual Ontario Economic Report aimed at shaping and informing future public policy in the prov… https://t.co/ljvmrPVoKC]]></document><document><![CDATA[ya i can literally text the most psycho bullshit to ppl i don't even know and they still talk to me like are people… https://t.co/TaxOV6kfYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #RangerJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just hope both teams play their hardest and have fun.   #GoBlue https://t.co/q3LJfh8Yas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited after a long weekend that my flight would get home around 11:30am and I could head home and nap. Also me wh… https://t.co/JovsaarpFV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a corny douche. Just don’t say anything bud. You’re not helping anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got back in town and threw some quick ink in this #sketch #illustration #inks https://t.co/HhjO49yaTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timb116 @TVietor08 Advocating is cheap  They all have a history... Bernie has a history too. That's why (ex Clinto… https://t.co/594GLEEtaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t have friends that leave homemade Focaccia in your mailbox, do you even have friends? Thanx beckmr73 !!… https://t.co/JbbvXJJlmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlassButterfly9 @MingGao26 Space Force is for the gay aliens!!!! Duh! https://t.co/xF02WDAPzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite photo of my dog! Definitely gonna be my next canvas I have made by  @ArtsyCanvas who always does amazin… https://t.co/iR9MbXxYiw]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to have a dialogue. Something is wrong with Golden State .it ain’t that they’re bored shit, they don’t play… https://t.co/pKft2OPXXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeonBroad @EliotShorrParks Arguably one of greatest scenes in Office History]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sunrisemvmt @Revkin I agree. All fossil fuel money should go to Republicans to make sure they have the resources t… https://t.co/hBKA0ZxblG]]></document><document><![CDATA[6th Zac brown band concert together 🤪❤️ @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/f8knhEcCbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@James54375264 Not no dam article. In Colombia that’s a nice meal 😋 on Taco Tuesday that’s 5 tacos 🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup I remember this from a couple of years ago! Glad the pilot was able to recover!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leave it to Republicans to sue to protect white privileged youth’s right to be rude and racist in public, go MAGA r… https://t.co/0hunEbniwF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get a Switch instead of buying yet ANOTHER silly limited edition PS4, you idiots]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connections to the Capital Region and @NENYPGA @NYSGA1923 @SienaCollege @Siena_Golf @WNYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I was just woefully myopic to assume that mean-spiritedness was somehow just the province of the Right.   T… https://t.co/bhVNX3MSw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor Righty. I ran into this store with him in my arms and shouted, "He just stopped breathing, please help me, doc… https://t.co/Ky2S2AFyvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[GAMEDAY! Avera Select 8th grade purple competing in Tea today with 4 tough games. Let's go Select!]]></document><document><![CDATA[COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA... WORST PRESIDENT EVER... #IMPEACHTHEMOTHERFUCKER]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/kDWVlqbrLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyports Has to be Cehlarik push Nodstrom to 4th, Accari’s had a rough couple games maybe couple on 9th floor wi… https://t.co/QFWSLpFo4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialLivePD great stuff starting with the opening car chase and leading up@to this.   10-1 the guy confesses to driving it]]></document><document><![CDATA[If DeSean is going to get released anyway, might be worth it for the #Eagles to look into a trade for a late round… https://t.co/cpgWrpPLS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[MOJO FOR LIFE AND THATS WORD TO YA MOTHA  Mojo - That's My School https://t.co/xhmGr6y5Sr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Session 2 Peeps @kaukaunasd Wellness Summit 2019- an inspiring message.... the key to success is inside each of us.… https://t.co/Gw67uDyPen]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld What is more apt and effective...  KLICKBAIT Kamala ---  Kamala HATE HOAX Harris or could it be Corey… https://t.co/qpFTiMlCKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sin is a matter of the heart before it is ever an issue of our behavior. This means that your and my biggest proble… https://t.co/ZEocjHF64Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest blog: Some Publix Super Markets Are Selling Strawberry Festival Tickets At A Discounted Price https://t.co/MlhfPbH4Ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gang!! #slowplow #snowplow #snowremoval #winter #snow #gang #10mph @ Minnesota https://t.co/QltsZgGZI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HornetsGIFs He’s gonna end up being good and then going somewhere else isn’t he?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Snapchat can y’all please bring back this filter lmaoo https://t.co/AgeSd4Wmr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Steel_Donkey @GoldyHA @AOC Yes. The Obama recession is likely right around the corner. Need more tax breaks for th… https://t.co/NNNAvkucP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Killing time on a plane today counted 106 airports (74 in US) I have flown in/out of. #uselessinfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefanieKnightx sounds and looks like a superhero heroine. Marvel, DC, Dark Horse or Image Comics. Maybe a team up… https://t.co/sQHPQs9T9P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrT Positive words from the Southside Slugger! See you in CREED III !!!! 🥊🥊🥊 https://t.co/y7gp57w4H3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can see it now: “the slice of humble pie say in the Devils’ stomachs for the month break until the postseason.  T… https://t.co/Ff7ZlZ4uzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Threat of bad weather has passed. Back in the gym - pregame meeting with officials.  Almost game time! #godawgs… https://t.co/XtigSIR66a]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW REMEMBER HALL COUNTY NEBRASKA LEGAL MARRIAGE TRUTH JUSTICE JURSDICTION AUTHORITY. AMERICAN PEOPLES. AMERICAN ST… https://t.co/0HZI0Sy0nT]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF make good choices out there peeps. #livluvdance #truth #friday @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/q8NVB46nDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks so much @Pwn20wnd yours the MAN!! Does anyone know why this error keeps happening when I try to insist a twe… https://t.co/vjL4qmwPR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[9 for the QTR!!!  SSG Laise SFC Olvera  Awesome work!!!! Lead the way!!!  #puttineminbootslikeitsahobby https://t.co/KNb5bRVHEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiHEAT leading end of Q3 @warriors @AutoMatt_ic #heat https://t.co/Uu2mwMNOUe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin @SenDuckworth @RepMikeQuigley @janschakowsky @IndivisibleChi This is insane. Crystal needs a Pardon,… https://t.co/rhD0wUwcE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much?  @JustinPickard4 f.n.gregors @ Arlington, Texas https://t.co/LFAujjMKOJ]]></document></documents></author>