<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@NolaMom08 @NolaDad08 this HAS to be the correct version?!? I remember the crosses and walls in the beginning! The… https://t.co/JY2yVl3yrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Important for all parade feet, marchers, chaperones, police, and parade goers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraVi91710578 Good morning Debra happy hump day hope all is well have a fabulous day enjoy 😉🤗👊👍😎🙋‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Saturdayvibes #embracethetillerys @ Virginia Beach, Virginia https://t.co/VWFdaDQ9Bw]]></document><document><![CDATA[#QueerEye is a perfect example of both visibility (in that it features gay men) but ALSO represention because it sh… https://t.co/AiYjMGx9D2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emmaleihoku @JeffreeStar @tacobell @kayanakamoku I want some! Are they still sold out?????]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump did your ex-bff get as much for writing this love letter as ex-MD Bronstein for dictated bill of h… https://t.co/BK4UK74sNv]]></document><document><![CDATA[When ur friends know your fam is wild &amp; friend dinners always turn into parties 😂 https://t.co/c6EUvS1AIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for joining us. @GbulletPeggy proves to us everyday that teaching and learning is not designed to be bori… https://t.co/6nZx6Ik8QD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP #DitchMitch #GoIndependent long enough to kick him out of the job! This is getting worse! @SenatorRomney… https://t.co/j11K9XCDMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#alittlelate but shout out to @DreamChaser_10 for my love/appreciation gift..he’s not a momma’s boy but he loves his mom to death😘.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is tweeting just about everyone's wonderful life or does anyone care about others new to this and just dont know… https://t.co/HVwKkRkuvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot I had already taken pre workout this morning and took more rn 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve tried several new things this long weekend with rowandubrul. I’ve had bluestonelane on my to try list for the… https://t.co/2qGBNVWtji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goodreads I’ve been reading @adam_tooze book Crashed, so I’d currently be in the middle of the financial crisis an… https://t.co/vwN4EsWpbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[At a book signing and reading this evening. "Not By Blood," the first novel in a trilogy by friend, Joyce Adjekum.❤… https://t.co/Tsn8SRdQep]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse I was there not too long ago.,,, the only ones thriving are the wealthy politicos. The… https://t.co/IRCzJ4IOHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Madison, WI? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/sOD0iInd9m #SupplyChain]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m “I’m copying in my colleague” and I’m ecstatic every time I write it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[just took my comforter out of the dryer so you know this sleep is about to HIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[perhaps @60Minutes should do another episode - this time featuring all the awesome work by @reshmasaujani… https://t.co/mKDhq55g0F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaneyaArvizu @ChristopherSean You're both completely amazing! I'll be in LA area end of March, would love to catch up. 💕💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear that too ! As he stated at last visit " #What Beautiful Ocean Fronts You have here !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I FUCKIN CANT STAND THAT GUYS THINK ITS OKAY YOU CAN SEXUALLY TOUCH ANOTHER GIRL!!!!! This guy is lucky Frankie wasn’t there!!!!!😡😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Duke crowd chanting “We want six.” Shea Rush, shooting layups, picks up the ball and with it in hand chants “We have seven.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#25thAmendmentNow  Dangerous Don trusts Putin on North Korea more than US intelligence: McCabe https://t.co/eVVnPdMUrp via @nypost]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lady_Vi_2U @joyreaper You are sooo right/ we are being taken over without a shot being fired]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HurricaneSoniaa @sherrilee7 @SenFeinstein Talking to @davidhogg111 I apologize for not making that clear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great afternoon discussing CRO-sponsor relationships in animal health @KStateOlathe Excellent group of speakers! Th… https://t.co/dlSJImQpnZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farmer's Market run. Yummmm! ❤❤❤❤ #Vegan #DairyFree #GlutenFree #Organic #CleanEating #DTox #VeganProteinPowder… https://t.co/KJanWKHEpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because this presidenting thing is HARD. But like with all bad news...off he runs to Mar-a-Lago. Gotta golf!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arizona women with a comfortable 60-36 lead over USC at end of 3rd quarter — local hooper from Centennial HS, Sam T… https://t.co/ON6U2pFp3I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Through the darkest times...you really find out who’s there in the end.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want Hoyas to win. I’m less concerned about what they wear @Hoyas247 @CasualHoya. Does that make a bad Hoya… https://t.co/9LOzDBLvEC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thing nothing else was going in in Ottawa today so we could chat about this arcane &amp; irrelevant point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Tuition and housing make up the largest part of the cost of college. To me, the largest hidden costs in college… https://t.co/Y7jUtL0IP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeRushaJ @Matt_Brickman It’s gorgeous! And totally ready for a springtime cocktail party...should spring accept yo… https://t.co/rWmlxTcWBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roblox  as found the wife dogu panties got unconsious for uploading think is a red armband on 3 days mellie aquare… https://t.co/kuZ7L2Fhmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely end of the day! #20minutesoutside #springthaw #darewehope #freshairtherapy #clearthemind #blessed @ Wellers… https://t.co/rUwlZqDVXX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elliot Kelly crossed 13.1M. Time 02:03:12, pace 09:08 min/mile, est. finish 11:20 am https://t.co/YiX5wWmLAz #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[bro Olivia Benson is my fav and all but she needs to let DAT SHIT GO in some episodes......anyways #whereselliot #agentamarocangetit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sams_Antics @juliagalef You’re a sick individual! For a parent to think such is bad enough but to post those feeli… https://t.co/CElF7S9T1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Censorship @HWDSB @SStephanian @YohiMotite @HWDSBKids @AM900CHML @WPoziomka @JeffGillies2 @mannyhwdsb @qnp… https://t.co/0oy9jp4I4S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m taking 15 credit hours of classes and now I have to finish 150 credit hours for my foreign teaching certificati… https://t.co/Sy5w5NEB22]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 8100 Cormyour Way #BoyntonBeach #FL  #realestate https://t.co/rDRKMejNbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRCC No, all our tax revenues should directly benefit the taxpayers in the form of infrastructure, medical care an… https://t.co/w2xuDG8WRA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dustin88P @kendoll2 @SloppyYellow @jimmywaggs3 @IamAracingfan I would love for @ClintBowyer to win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santikapowski I came back later to read and it was gone, “unavailable.”  Your name was still in the “reply” so I c… https://t.co/AckK748mQC]]></document><document><![CDATA[So excited to finally share these!!  connoreqmclane ‘s bridal session has me wanting to do more!!  @getolympus… https://t.co/CBD60PEZfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamPazzano Good detective work, keeps communities safe, along wit the professional correctional services, or thera… https://t.co/jHKoQJo0iN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cut my Hot Pockets in half and put them in the microwave for 2 minutes. They come out perfect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[all your shit fugazi, let me find out @ TERMINAL 5 https://t.co/c0UV29Q6oG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Excelsior @lopezobrador_ Lo dice el que desde 1970 es político y vividor del pueblo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissKarlita Villaret and Moursund. It used to be chill but as the southside has expanded outside 410 traffic had g… https://t.co/vLxUGPtwjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hlb54 @SenSherrodBrown Seriously.   Senator, can we get some refinance help? Reduction in interest? Something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KFAN1003 Mr. Z with the best take I’ve heard on KFAN in quite a while. Academy Awards are garbage!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Rivera go back and look for Al Capone's vault... You must is missed something... Washed up POS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad this happened to these women.On the other hand this exposes Trump as a hypocrite AKA monster.@BlogChurchWork… https://t.co/CE6hbElZAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[V Day Vibez @wharfmiami ❤️ w/ my valentine @mieses_betsy 😘 #thewharfmiami #vday #love #goodtimes #memories #loveher… https://t.co/FwojQKchEZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhoThat_One_Guy Pretty serious situation involving a family member which isn’t health related and doesn’t affect my employment status.]]></document><document><![CDATA[toda la clase de discusión de neumo mi cerebrito se la pasa pidiendo auxilioooOOoOoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[BASEBALL!! BASEBALLBASEBALLBASEBALLBASEBALLBASEBALLBASEBALLBASEBALL!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better. Jerseys. Where everyone looks like a box. https://t.co/pxuUpnwTLm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt STANLEY saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea  Stanley is a small dog frightened… https://t.co/Nu7xVWMY8n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickGarzoni @Portosj81 @ltapoll @realDonaldTrump Actually every case is men. Must be your cup of tea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset assistant to my chief photographer. @ Mt. Tabor, Portland, Oregon https://t.co/TRYUC3DSEI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When something bad happens and you think it couldn’t get any worse but it does... https://t.co/FDSHnbKawa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX Congratulations! I enjoyed every moment. In this stressful time,this show was a comic relief, and… https://t.co/qzukAWuJgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristen_shilton  what were they chanting when our boys took the ice?  Couldn’t make it out..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love VANS &amp; I love working for the company. But I cannot wait to leave in a few months &amp; start my new job with better people]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noamsasylum @ProjectCiampa @KingRicochet we need a pic!!!!!! 🥰 at least a better one this time 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally found what’s at the end of the rainbow! 😻❤️🐰#mylesthebunny #kawaiibunny #rabbitsofinstagram #rabbits… https://t.co/Fq7AhtGapN]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT TOOK MANY BLOODY KNUCKLES, BUT IT FINALLY, I OPENED MY BEER IN MY CAR!! https://t.co/w1VW7jFfV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight Flower: An Anthology of Contemporary Christian Poems - Shirley A Mandel https://t.co/NcYdwMA6qa is an amaz… https://t.co/E6i2fIS9Y9]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of myself for keeping up with my credit, ya girl just got a huge credit increase 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ninapineda7 @LyndaBaquero4NY @News12NJ @starledger @dailyrecord #consumeradvocacy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtractionEngr @CNN @nischelleturner @smerconish I have conservative traits. Everything has a scale it’s not this… https://t.co/sfTxHtZhrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D0GSAREFAMILY @Shirleen9162 It makes him very unique. I always say a blind person does a better job being a true f… https://t.co/N0gMLTYhNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gillian8182 I agree Gillian it stopped my life dead in its tracks.People would tell me it didn’t have to it was ju… https://t.co/cyR88WD8dd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time the world spins too fast, You are always there to steady me. And I believe that love— truly, I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow look what came up on my playlist. Almost as if this whole backlash against Rep. Omar is absolutely bonkers. https://t.co/SztjLKyMbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheGoodGodAbove For REAL, though. #GodSaidNoTrump #TrumpCrimeFamily #ImpeachTheMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[You cannot be all for all the people, right?  Success is bringing the best you can to the most possible. Are you a… https://t.co/aN25KWdE1c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikewoodsfox5 Sure hope so; everything here has a good coat of ice on it. Definitely need some warm temps up here… https://t.co/I113U1QnwV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stand with Families. Fight the Gag Rule. Take action here: https://t.co/OhpRta8EcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA['First kiss' conversation between teacher, students leaves parents stunned https://t.co/cdHvDCtljB @SteveGWSB hears… https://t.co/5dOI6jP6wI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤞🏻 for a little ☀️ .. .. #arizona #az #travel @ Mesa, Arizona https://t.co/wIU8a59EmJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jazmin_Ortega when you return from your trek, we have to go here and stuff our faces 😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamKantrow Predicted storm has started, the deck is coated and it is slippery! (Seymour)]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay, so that story is called “A Letter from Hell” and it’s a video on YouTube...honestly really powerful so go che… https://t.co/n6XeJu2rlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunWithJason hitting all the right notes in his keynote at the Chamber luncheon. Thanks for the multiple shout-out… https://t.co/SsoX2xXl16]]></document><document><![CDATA[WTF! @dstluke @patriciaglane @lizaanne42 @anthoknees @benjancewicz How will that help?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where skills and business knowledge is integrated utilizing hands on real world application. Upon completion of sai… https://t.co/Nux91ShMlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[just a smirk for you. I will have to show this to jess, i pick on her all the time because... https://t.co/zzGWz5iPh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristenxLeanne just watched your tattoo video. This was the last one I got on my left shoulder. I’m itching to get… https://t.co/Mb9EolkY0t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before this year I was the only person I knew who had their tax refund taken for their college debt and this year I… https://t.co/KXj1kCwlif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamiaHamps 🏆🏆🏆 you won today.   Also anything Queen Madhuri, TBH. https://t.co/LTkbtEia5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulioCcesarr @drewg69 @Millium2332 @hopi1 @RealSaavedra because they don't care https://t.co/8sSdJ6rmps]]></document><document><![CDATA[@halliemess Disagree.... would you rather go to a school in a town like Bellingham or Pullman? Have you been to Pul… https://t.co/h0j6g3qOEO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_c_h_a_n_n_y_ You are beautiful!  Be healthy, but enjoy life and vacation!❤️]]></document></documents></author>