<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump @MSNBC 47 months that show you how you need to understand life on earth]]></document><document><![CDATA[Represented the buyers for this cute house on the Milton line. @ Quincy, Massachusetts https://t.co/DZozf6AV3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TWallack You clearly haven’t seen 1776 the musical (that little historical nugget is prominently featured)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whiskey and Wireless podcast has LEGO building and about a third of all attendees hanging around drinking and liste… https://t.co/zP2nfsiI8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[9. All of this is just for a SECRET clearance. It’s lengthy and somewhat painful, but if you’re honest and forthcom… https://t.co/ltywqS2RyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueSoulution Wow, not a very Christian statement coming from a man who calls himself a Christian minister.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wilnerhotline Let’s talk about how osu gets 3 fta and UCLA gets 28. You can’t tell me they were more aggressive. A… https://t.co/U7giaIfAPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Revives ‘EL CHAPO’ Bill to Pay for Border Wall https://t.co/a9VtAeK3mv]]></document><document><![CDATA[McDonald's called out order 369 and I yelled out "Damn she fine" and nobody laughed or danced, I hate where we're at in America right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wcmarkwalls You know it. I mean, “what can happen to an old fashioned”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CHICAGO 02-16-2019 #FultonTheatre supporting @heatherparcells as Velma 36-inches away during "Class"… https://t.co/lRsaqvrtvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crazy4OReilly90 I mean if Ottawa can decide which pick they give up to Colorado, I'm certain Anaheim can pick one… https://t.co/CGG6hG19j3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BowdrenJeff @davidbix Oh wait, I know. Wrong Lee. #bruce #hyapatia #jim #stan]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is not an individual issue. All universities hate Jews and want them dead. They only honor dead Jews and ignore… https://t.co/Z0M6T1wNzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thesportsjunk @T4X_Man @Scaaaaaaarlet Why do you think we're mad lol we're not the ones apeshit because a poster i… https://t.co/pg5p2CXrfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BevellsReturn Kirk Cousins doesn’t qualify, he hasn’t done shit. That’s right, it doesn’t happen, especially not s… https://t.co/HNBuxHHmmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[When he asks if I’m sleepy and I tell him no I want to keep talking to him. Then I pass out on him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KBAndersen @djrothkopf That’s just an argument for doing away with employer-based healthcare, not single-payer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieti I'll take my weiners anyway I can get 'em. https://t.co/cqnFlAHBnF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been on a ramen kick this winter. Wonderful to be home after a great weekend in NYC.   Tonight’s ramen was a roaste… https://t.co/ohoFHTa0wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrystiPryde in the off chance you haven't seen it yet Cardi dropped a new song with Bruno Mars https://t.co/MF0qslfgtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vincenzolandino @AlfaRomeoUSA @Schmittastic @alfa_romeo That’s a beautiful blue!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robertwickens We’re so freeking proud of you! Much love for @robertwickens]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning traffic, looks like a normal day.  Notice no chains on any of the cars. I could only imagine what Portland… https://t.co/QOM4XIQwMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember when Kylie and Kendal “wrote” a book? Where are the critics? The dissertations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[making this funny. My dog's thoughts every night when I'm kicking and pushing and pulling off the middle of... https://t.co/1XG0oiO1QJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading this and knowing it won't affect anything, is unbelievably depressing. https://t.co/Ho8YrTNwhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manny_benton If height and weight are not important everyone involved in this sport seems to waste an awful lot of time measuring both.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtjitsuMaster On second thought, I don't want to have this argument online. Turns out I'm still mad from the last election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notwokieleaks @AOC The world's largest corporation demanded $3 billion in corporate welfare. The people stood up a… https://t.co/2wWANjTK42]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa @charliekirk11 Colorado is going down the drain thanks to Californians fleeing their state and moving there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LumpyLouish Wow, this is unbelievable.  This old woman, who will most likely die soon, is arguing with these young… https://t.co/CYlpypJ2lX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman It always saddened me that a fellow Jew caused the execution of another. And as we have recently l… https://t.co/y5Le4NgmNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy housewarming to my film set wifey #housewarming #shotroulette #party #actors #dayoff #weekend #imadehummus @… https://t.co/oMlG0L4n9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[LIVE: Charlie Munger Speaks at Daily Journal Annual Meeting -- Feb. 14, ... https://t.co/a8QKmyFVy9 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[As if you needed another example of why @NancyBarto is wrong and @dougducey is right....https://t.co/50yMh4w7rG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmsamuelsmd I'll stop wearing a helmet when sand, gravel, oil, storm drains, potholes, manhole covers, constructio… https://t.co/YOt539beya]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the ones that have tattoos y’all ever stare at your arms and just start reminiscing when your arms were a virgin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@H_Stafford What?! Thank you so much 😊 that means a lot. Hope you’re doing well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Why don’t you just pay frumpf for his fake construction crew]]></document><document><![CDATA[yup my mom and @ashtonevans are definitely in the audience for opening (and my dad, who’s prolly drinking a beer) https://t.co/MSsACoBBlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude it's gonna suck when this guy submarines like 9% of the vote from Bernard and the Dems again lose. #BERNIE2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been wanting SKC to try and buy Enner Valencia for about 2 years.  They might score 80 with the current team and Valencia at the #9.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevconnorsespn Sorry for your loss... but can you lose something you didn’t have? 🤔 Sorry for the loss of your nea… https://t.co/wNyEYW5Fbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pubclub @OrganicRoadMap @aftertheflash @travelwithirine @JulesHalvy @TravelBugsWorld @LaceDiaries @mellymoorelife… https://t.co/qTiFViBjs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have work tomorrow for my other job so I can officially say I’ve had two jobs at once 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Libera_Rex @haig @ThouArtThat @MimeticValue @BillyRedHorse people are naturally going to be very selective about w… https://t.co/s8yUmsOPdO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dark77715 @sylwiaf2 Dziękuję Dark :-) jesteście wielcy :-) https://t.co/JONrR6lt2f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DinaPugliese Both looking very stylish! No “Northern Exposure” parkas here!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gmapes16 @scherftdog No he won his district but he wasn’t the highest ranked kid there]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are separate nations for a reason. We should all embrace our heritage. Be proud of our diversity. The New World Order makes no sense!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been tearing my house apart looking for an old Polaroid picture of young Haleybuddy with King Kong Bundy. Legend… https://t.co/VJ40sOXvrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep...this is how you #live a #life being comfortable with yourself and #loving #yourself!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🆘🆘🆘🆘 Dems Caught RED HANDED Slipping ‘Poison Pill’ Into Deal That Could Prevent Building The Wall https://t.co/8MlWa1z2Xk via @ILMForg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShannonSharpe Peyton Manning = GOAT  Don’t @ me https://t.co/EaSbcPzR7s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Example ....No Matter How Successful ....Perceived Intelligence...A Mans Brain 🧠 Is Somehow In His Balls 🏈… https://t.co/3yyDIvh5p9]]></document><document><![CDATA[They're not waiting on Harper, they're all in, but if they were to pass... go get a job for Bill DeWitt. He seems t… https://t.co/RSVu4Nrwjd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib @AOC @IlhanMN You two will end the Democratic Party LMFAO YOU TWO ARE IDIOTS AND NEED TO GO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump This is Your disapproval rating you idiot! https://t.co/Gd5ZF0SkGK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Styx666Official The author is referring to future Pres Sanders declaring national emergencies to push his unconstitutional leftist agendas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Only in your racist Hippocrate small mind of yours! 🇺🇸🇮🇱☯☮✝🚂😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlockCBlog @marco808s It's on soundcloud. I love it!  https://t.co/nzfOBxEMhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKupperman I don't think it's overstating that this country is absolutely fucking insane and the majority of the p… https://t.co/P9YoDbzyXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colleges are now dominated by women, creating an ‘education gap’ afflicting men https://t.co/bfRXI8fqjk via… https://t.co/Ny0XhchGKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready for a day of fun and adventure yaaa it’s Saturday !!! 3/9/2019 @ Perry, Utah https://t.co/wpVzGwGZch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your president and his crooked family are all going to prison. Kushner too. 😎 Your party is going bust. If donald t… https://t.co/idTTEgqUrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @realDonaldTrump Trump is correct "If we have no border we have no country". Let's start having a c… https://t.co/ASkmhfCHy0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there's anything this country can get together on, it's making sure PETA gets ratioed every. single. tweet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EthosUncovered @larryelder @RalphNortham @DNC @stephensacks No What history  says: Every major civil rights law of… https://t.co/Tw1oP0SzJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[D.C. attorney general subpoenas Trump’s inaugural committee: NEW YORK — President Donald Trump’s inaugural committe… https://t.co/ORB7tqU3Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest! https://t.co/2koH2IJG1v how a man should look.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Auburn women def. Ala, 53-52. The Tigers advance to a quarterfinal game vs TAMU tomorrow night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s ok to be a little bit delusional with realistic ideas ✅ #WednesdayWisdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CatalanCreativity!!! My only concern is that overloading Hidalgos with factual evidence might constitute « cruelty… https://t.co/x0KtPlljmH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsMeSveta88 Because American politics have always worked that way if you can make them smart they will know bette… https://t.co/fxOfjVgQcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDeclareClaire Isn't there a ferengi rule of acquisition that says that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanWright0 @LeeDixon2 Masterminds never forget, especially when you scored the first #CPFC goal 🥅 I ever saw #CPFC… https://t.co/TMxKcTdtcL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plain and simple. Ain’t no one close to touching MJ. 🐐🏀⭐️ 🏆🏆🏆🏆🏆🏆 #thegoat #goat #jumpman23… https://t.co/31AP5lfJXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/2g4wpzde2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ms_VJohnson @MrsGarcia_Jacks Yea he replaced injuried Jerrod this week...He played good. He was excited too lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AWilliamss__ But check out that #24 ... don’t fall asleep cause we don’t nap over here 🔵😈⚾️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHauserG8r @elonmusk Good 4 u! I'm 67 and i still flash back to a boy w/Mercury flights whenever i watch SpaceX la… https://t.co/NkpFmFxGsX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are jeans even a thing anymore for women?? Went to buy some and only found jeggings or whatever they’re called. I want real jeans]]></document><document><![CDATA[16 points.. #justsaying #footballislife @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/qNwEOaDzj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I almost threw up. It's absolutely the most disgusting thing I've ever seen on TV. I'm done with buying them, hopef… https://t.co/4xEJqDVZoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber @Uber_Support imagine that. Instant pay is down during the busiest week in ATX. You’re fucking your drivers over, again, per usual.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone. Thanks for all of your help with or fundraiser efforts! We will continue to sell ribs, and p… https://t.co/pO4uTRAvfj]]></document><document><![CDATA[7. The “French Kissing Bandit”.    That, of course, was Bro in a nutshell, and after that our locker room talk was… https://t.co/h5MS1mA03q]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: I predict the top 3 wide receiver performers for each event at the NFL Combine, as well as provide analysis… https://t.co/qx9RadQeOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UniWatch @PhilHecken It’s Texas Independence Day. And here’s a lot of beautiful logos that define this state. https://t.co/44gm35eKkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ride to thissss this morning. 🌞😏  https://t.co/L4GTOCHYWX https://t.co/Yqa5CKMIuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[two hour+ speeches to the party faithful: another hallmark of the caudillo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weatherninja @RepFrenchHill @TomCottonAR @AsaHutchinson One or the other, right. I prefer Standard time, myself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was going through my photo album and came across this one. I was all alone that day - which was kinda sad - but I… https://t.co/4c9FTLT4na]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Penetrator6000 @NoFascistLies @RachelLucca1 @CherieSkiba @Olivertwisted62 @MrsWRetired #CorporateCashPimps https://t.co/BhCRYNYERU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speak Sht into Existence, Stop Saying, “Can’t wait til I”, “when I’m rich” , “when we blow up”, Na I’m done with al… https://t.co/sajkYDaGmc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcarrick Hey Rob! Must be fun investing on Planet Zeldon!  Here in Canada we have.....taxes.  Your investor with t… https://t.co/CVaSpj6fLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[why are ppl so on edge today ? i have been honked at at every red light today after not moving .2 seconds after it turned green]]></document><document><![CDATA[@XavierGameday we better play great D, rebound, get to the stripe, and TAKE CARE OF THE BALL!]]></document><document><![CDATA[...in Everett, and that similar pilot projects were implemented in other cities, suggests this project was a succes… https://t.co/0WqOwIDnKH]]></document></documents></author>