<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Every65Seconds someone in the United States develops Alzheimer's. I am sharing the facts and raising awareness for… https://t.co/TKE7reM1BZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RCSD @OfficialLivePD Right at close of the show! Have a good night and safe travels!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmiForLove @AnimalLeague @ContestSource @bestfriends @Roscoe1679 #GlobalGoodEmi]]></document><document><![CDATA[What gets measured gets managed. Assessment week flexappealwf Now I'm ready to tackle a productive #realtor day!… https://t.co/WFaggr5MrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brooks’ favorite display at The College Basketball Experience is the coaching tree display - created by former Arka… https://t.co/vcG1cE3PSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why my heart was beating fast af as I waited for that entire shelf to fall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chaya_sorah @8thdaymusic @elimarcusmusic Great Video! Thanks! Nice To have the Brothers Together!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wonderchook Ah that makes sense. I did mine in Canada so the cost wasn't a big deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen man... long as you get it honest, and applying yourself grinding and getting to that check to provide for yo… https://t.co/P6KiI9VnfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welp. Better budget extra in April for this. @UrbanDecay , just go ahead and take alllll my money.… https://t.co/YAai09OUWS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My stress level has been crazy high for the past few months and finally it’s coming to end, hopefully  🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[If jobs with titles like "Physician- Orthopedic Surgeon- Ardmore Oklahoma" sound appealing to you, follow us to hea… https://t.co/OmseEdTeDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is literally no time to lose!! Tell Congress to finally pass #UniversalBackgroundChecks on firearms!… https://t.co/R4cfKeVkfC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesKlee I also actively played in bands at age 19 and was part of Chicago’s neo no wave scene in the late 90’s a… https://t.co/Zvu6fQfXtb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tomcitriniti @ausYenLoWang @BJMossman1 @DanRather When has anyone said they wanted open borders?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump No one said that. Just another rich, white, old guy getting off easy.   He'll still die, broke and… https://t.co/J2IFmOFfMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arpaio’s conviction should be wiped from the record, or whether the pardon merely protects Arpaio from further puni… https://t.co/jgOAbsDAn7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisStrub @JWatson_Wx @markwschaefer @ShaunAyala @tylerjmccall @ChrisDucker @TheSalesLion @owenvideo… https://t.co/7JD3ZrtvfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JadeAMiles I’m watching it. So far, pretty good, but it’s eating into my #LuciferOnNetflix workout viewing time. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennysingsalot 🎤and the 🌈🍎💯@Watson_Wildcats have #talent AND are #gifted 🥉Go Wildcats!!  @kishaculpepper… https://t.co/tGlBYzmu58]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sbz_Blt_Ngayon Lol ang babanal kasi ng fans ng namention mo no? Kung di naman kasi hanash ng hanash ibang fans nil… https://t.co/8olytfQYSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This project could use a boost to help my students as well as UNICEF with Power Bands! @LHBLovesEdu @StanLevenson… https://t.co/kkIQrwiGcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iCoachLindsay @WRCrowley111 @smccarthy3rd I know it’s one of your favorites😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Defend starving polar bears! Stand with me to save the Arctic Refuge!!  #care2 https://t.co/DUUD1f2E9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked The Write Stuff! It was a bit predictable ngl, but I really enjoyed seeing Rita and Lucy bond over somethin… https://t.co/flnoXv9cWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cheifsh8radrs @TomHall I don't regret being a Tom Boy. Was a lot more fun than playing with dolls.😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kudos to #davidmdraiman from @Disturbed. While performing tonight at #MSG in #NYC, he walked off stage, hugged a gu… https://t.co/i9jxq9m4q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Build the Wall!  Don't give in....stay strong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Demands from Trump  like "stop hurting and criminalizing gay people"?  You are right, he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crossing the border😍😍✌️✌️🇲🇽🇲🇽 catlynn_96 _jacky234 @ Progreso International Bridge https://t.co/pJcRbf35tU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here jasonktattoo working with his first official client knuckledottattoo Thanks Angie for being our first client.… https://t.co/kXm76C9FVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#uppers Isn't Manafort also facing state trials, stuff he couldn't be pardoned for? (also, isn't counting on Trump… https://t.co/OHSVxMUVNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve lost faith in my country. I’m heartbroken because I thought even those like @RoyBlunt @USRepLong whose politic… https://t.co/Dr7MOdeZyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@susan_artiga @Vovchick22 @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton @AOC @IvankaTrump a 2 year old,  all girls,  my daughter just had… https://t.co/GqzMX0Gmrp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio Mininno #125 match Drexel VS Binghamton University  Sunday, February 10, 2019 @antonio_mininno https://t.co/xfzZEemca7]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Wednesday’s we wear #DandI gear #beyou #Tmobile #DiversityandInclusion #twinning @livinwithdenial https://t.co/JKcIWvuRsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsRobThomas   Your gorgeous,the way I'm better when I listen and watch you totally memorizing performer https://t.co/9VGIatFaAN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw it and thought it was okay. I was a little bummed, expecting better I guess but that’s just me😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NTVsTimReith did not win $10,000, but he still gets the prize of being my coanchor (which is probably better 😆)… https://t.co/DtxYghugqy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Those people that ignored this woman,  are so cruel and worthless. It breaks my heart. That could be your mother th… https://t.co/9CrLEmZQmP]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SUN TODAY. My gif interpretation of @Fox26Mike’s forecast: https://t.co/Nz05pdBlI3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alivitali I like his partner also...wouldn’t want to have been her tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Virginia's 6th Congressional District https://t.co/jz69ir0oZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardKbach @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends 33 followers, bot, blocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[IM GOING TO PHILLY TODAYYYYY  ...for a mandatory meeting.  👎🏻🙄  But nevertheless, #GoFlyers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well deserved- sets the bar every day with an amazing attitude, work ethic, and mental toughness!! @forvevertrin yo… https://t.co/tTkygQEEGE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealcornett @VortexVixen45 @SenFeinstein Her pockets are fat with cash so she doesn't care]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adorable Japanese Playing Cards especially for Dog Lovers - I Want!  ~~ Houston Foodlovers Book... #funniness… https://t.co/ibySY1h3Op]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_Luka @TheMooshies @NorahNell @BeastieBoyKats @LilyLuWhoT @Buddythereddog @PurrbotKitty @SIDDYDOG417… https://t.co/rU7lqBa6Lu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GamerTakes Note to self: if making a game, make sure there are zero white characters just for these assholes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IDontReallyKara I feel actually offended by how accurate this is https://t.co/0EmmrXsoaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cheering on Layner at State Wrestling... Let’s go!!! 🤼‍♂️ https://t.co/BirIMGa0j5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else get infuriated watching #AbductedInPlainSight or was it just me???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_thepumpkinman @RepAdamSchiff Hahaha, I wonder if he can get grub hub to deliver McDonald's?]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Things will get better, bud’ @CP0031 is always total class. On and off the ice RT Canadiens' Carey Price helps men… https://t.co/7IvlxSJlaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So they’re playing Punchis music at the event Gabbi is dragging me to tonight 💆🏽‍♀️ if y’all wanna come there’s fre… https://t.co/EQwsHmAAGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know what?  There's a place in London where people can speak in public about anything, any issue.  It's a tradition in that place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking away my worries and weight! Still at it and going strong! Imagine if you will 5 years in the future if you c… https://t.co/Ym80hExlbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaRivera2207 @RoarLoudTravel @always5star @LoriMoreno @DemiCassiani @pietrosd @SteveKubota @suziday123… https://t.co/SH48dGk02p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gentleman of Twitter, settle a debate please! Is whiskey dick a real thing/legitimate excuse?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmblandocorona @holamexico 😂😂😂 que cree chavista el menso, por andar con una que tiene viente y algo 🥴🥴🙄🙄🙄 @gabrielsotoMEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying the sun at Las Vegas Motor Speedway #nascar2019  #lvmspeedway #nellistraightaway @ Las Vegas Motor Speedway https://t.co/svZE5XQ8vE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to Sugarland this weekend @blackbookali, any recommendations?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGmlittleORGAN I’m engaged and still celebrate galentines day. Love showing love to my friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@meghanvollmer @basedmh69 He’s literally using gifs Meghan... gifs..... old gifs....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol He was my hubby too! And did you know Matt Mercier played as well as Crom from Fire Emblem Awakening! ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I listened to baby shark a 100 times already this week and it's tuesday. The kids just come up to me and ma… https://t.co/gZx1zISkCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone tried/own the Nectar or Casper beds? What are your thoughts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎼SALINASSSSsss and monterey friends: 🎤!tomorrow!🎹 #salinas #livemusic #thursday #salinaslivemusic #aleciahaselton… https://t.co/sHvpTpzw64]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel lucky every day — because #SheInspiresMe @arisirenita @emilymccleave @KarlaEa @jenks #NationalWomensDay 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pontifex We need to follow a path of Wisdon, Virtue and Freedom. Freedom for the Soul not the ego. We need help to discern ego from soul.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joannastanford Ignorance is comparing a kid with a problem to gun laws. It’s not the guns fault he stole it and sh… https://t.co/spGblKIknH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhitCoko17 Right now I only take anxiety meds when needed. This time last year ago i tried for a while and i felt… https://t.co/ULllFE0BNq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncanzanobft Uncle Phil can’t be happy with Oregon MBB program these days!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafetyPinDaily @ReginaldALawso1 How long did Imelda Marcos play dumb? Greatest robbery of a government Guinness bo… https://t.co/d7NATIGTAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo excited to announce that I'll be one of the panelists speaking at the upcoming @ygtgofficial Women's Circle!… https://t.co/tHGI9zgTdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When kids these days think they got something, they aren't as focused on it anymore. - Ron Washington. So true.… https://t.co/20HX4Iei2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had my first Four Loko's last night... I passed out with chicken nuggets on my lap so I'd say it was a good night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bubbagump324 Ms. Graham is covering his ass and sucking up #traitortrump 's  ass.  #60Minutes #traitortrump #EnoughIsEnough]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra @SebGorka This man would have you standing in a bread line. Why do people not see this. Free medical is not free. Ask seniors.]]></document><document><![CDATA[TGIF 🎶🤘🔥 Join me TONIGHT at @CorralesBrewery from 6-9pm!  #getBent @ Corrales Bistro Brewery https://t.co/Q6xM1J3GGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[What will they say about you? https://t.co/AcDOUVlXbi https://t.co/UyRroDMt9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayaKudaibergen @WorldsBestCBS @dimash_official Please watch video here https://t.co/EAvJB1CXpD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still feeling short of breath after seeing photos of the new @mnwild player, #kevinfiala...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just open up to those who respect you fully and without having to "blink an eye" when you ask them to be there for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[my fam just need to make the executive decision to move to Dallas. i’m sick of the games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShelbyRena97 Probably because you don't get much down time in those cities so the memory of them is fleeting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coliform bacteria testing in #biotech @HCCDistrict this week. @sbisd_science https://t.co/AOj9DeUpnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HikindDov @Farberyanki @IlhanMN Most people have never read the Koran if they did they would know like we do… Isla… https://t.co/NANf5Lzomw]]></document><document><![CDATA[when smash mouth sang, “the years start coming and they don’t stop coming” i really felt that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chulllaaa @AppleSupport @verizon Why have they not given you a new one? Are you speaking with someone higher up?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah we are missing him surely, but Abhinandan is an active Indian Military employee. In the end he will say and do… https://t.co/daPPcH0kls]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of media relations rockstar @iamkasmer for landing this beautiful and vitally important front page story!]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 years of life and still have yet to be “mirror pic of my butt” confident.  🤷‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little girl loves her horses!  #MyMollieKate #hlsr2019 #grambabies @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/RNZR1IsNRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YasmineEvjen I feel like you in the office is actually pretty entertaining]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedcruz   Well?  Now you’ve got nothing to say?  We’re still waiting and we ARE NOT GOING AWAY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Isn't it wonderful!  The best part will be when you are found guilty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudicialWatch @RealJamesWoods yeah the power they really wanted is terrorism and no its dishonest dishonorable and disgraceful]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Saturday 9am Zumba®Fitness NorthSpringsPark Rec Center , 10-12pm Rockin Shamrock Zumbathon (meals on reals) 3pm A.… https://t.co/z4HcCIP4Fq]]></document></documents></author>