<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Not even an exaggeration. I know the UPS truck ain't even fast, but them fuckers out the damn community after the d… https://t.co/zV8X0tsabV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wake up to your son crawling up next to you so you cuddle him and he falls back asleep... ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got love for everyone trying to make something happen, no matter where you’re at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigBlueUnited Didn’t think could ever trade that contract. Bennett is better player today and would be 1/2 the cos… https://t.co/vLsdUmCHm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@withrowzone I’d give them an at large over some teams I’ve seen on the bubble..I.e Florida Indiana NC State..]]></document><document><![CDATA[These 8 United States Neighborhoods Are Hipster Havens - TripAdvisor  ⁦@WeicheltRES  ⁩#Community #LiveWorkPlay… https://t.co/2q0AmzYM2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Dartman #1 is available on digital at https://t.co/1QepIUYpiN https://t.co/zbG75jeiAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's Why The Wealthiest City In America Is Screwed | Zero Hedge https://t.co/xgvjx6hmkD Really, are Americans all… https://t.co/iER3sHu7a0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck what everyone else is saying, come to Buffalo, NY where the Fucking chicken wing was invented. On top of that… https://t.co/3ybvxTM9pA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damien Harris on #RollTide teammate and #Giants #NFLDraft target RT Jonah Williams: ‘If I was a GM, he would be my first pick.’ #NFLCombine]]></document><document><![CDATA[do y’all just recycle the same 4 pics of her and keep using the same captions ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Own an esports centre in 90 days!!! Where do I sign? #esports shenanigans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: Team Member - https://t.co/agHdISLPEy #Simon #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @kjfm34 and @Connor1323 and the 'Dogs on a District championship!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tylerperry @SadeABC It need to be a funeral for Madea. Leave this homo  s*** to Eddie Murphy😂 let's get back to yo… https://t.co/Ggi5NRtDDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @JohnKasich were a girl, he'd be @amyklobuchar #ForkAndPizza #CombAndSalad]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Valentine!! @wendypauls I am the luckiest man on the planet!! #valentines #foreverlove @ Baden, Ontario https://t.co/twm2bdsvw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[2014 - Woman rebels when her husband stops trying.  2015 - Woman invents a mop. 2016 - Woman learns to communicate… https://t.co/BvbEMX33Iy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nnovick @genemurphy @ACAAngelCapital @tcasandiego @AK_LaunchLeader Do you know @genemurphy? If not, you should know @genemurphy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sZWmu2XqxT for https://t.co/JgW6vPhoNP unconference about #dareucare as I mentioned in my @hl7 #fhir p… https://t.co/v5uSUancxc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisLoesch Add @IlhanMN to the list. Very urban district. Can't think of many rural Minnesotans who spew anti-sem… https://t.co/ei6k20dRVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨RESCUE UPDATE🚨 Daniel and his dad Tom are t-minus 3 hours away from picking up the two 3-week old sister piglets i… https://t.co/ihVZp6XL9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I've said it before stop beating the bead horse. Get off your fat ass do something about healthcar… https://t.co/p4GAr2LWjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @TheRealeDeal it’s 17 degrees @inletny with light snow falling]]></document><document><![CDATA[WHAT IN THE ACTUAL FUCK AM I WATCHING RIGHT NOW. LIKE??!!!! #AbductedInPlainSight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ice covered beach on the shores of Lake Michigan.   #winter #beach #chicago #lakemichigan #bluesky @ Chicago, Illin… https://t.co/EhXzWBR3M2]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you leave an animal in a car during the cold/hot weather and the car isn’t running or window cracked. You’re an… https://t.co/AajyHoT7sH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mommamia1217 Indictments if any before Mueller's report will tell us a lot but won't reunite families  separated d… https://t.co/MoMBMxhlKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricTrump He's going to cry himself to sleep every night.  Shawshank Redemption.  #MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiliBowlNomNom It also shows you spend more time insulting me than doing your research. I actually am a business… https://t.co/Id4Ce6BVIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every morning I wake up and go to twitter to see if @Bharper3407 has signed with the @Phillies yet. Nope 😞 #MaybeTomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last day, penultimate show for Pets Rule. (@ Pets Stadium - Pets Rule - @seaworld in San Diego, CA) https://t.co/cktDz5IAno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hamms_lite I dropped a soldiers sprite, it exploded in the street and I looked him in face and said “Casualty of war you know how it is”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mr. Donald Trump is a American🇺🇸The best President we’ve had in years. True statement, and Like I said, I’d follow… https://t.co/S6dWom6GO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DadoftheDecade Not taking sides here, but it’s good to remember that Chicago police are as corrupt as the trump re… https://t.co/4fobC7Z8yH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MisterPrez32 @SBNation I came here to post this and was not disappointed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammtacular Don’t talk about me like that. I don’t need my business thrown around all willie nilly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReignOfApril @TiffanyDCross That is funny.  Maybe I shouldn't find it funny, but I do. Dont screw around with wild animals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jjauthor @BernieSanders Bernie knows that his life is about over and could not care Less about the long term.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #PsychopathologyOnParade - “Delusional projection: Delusions about external reality, usually of a persecutory nature.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[DAMN first the Tristan Thompson/Jordyn Woods news... now Jussie Smollett LIED!? What a week!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suburbanitis What the heck, did they use any nails.  Hope they match the shingles well when the repair.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Germany and the EU in general is moving its focus east. US hegemony is fading fast. Our proximity and history makes… https://t.co/Pfz3wlICmA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls hoops final from Evanston: @mwwarriors 55, @ETHSports 50.#PioneerSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMurph207 only thing il send rest of the night, just figured you had to see this violation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Little heads up central SD. Local news fascinated by weekend storm, but no mention of Tuesday/Wednesday with its 5-… https://t.co/ElZjbiThSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirmigueljpg She did something to SOMEBODY and they was like you beta “Watch out lil BIH” and now she on GUARD 💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[After those technical fouls, the shooter only made half of the free throws. Ball never lies?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chempa @pochodiaz @LORENT_SALEH @MariaFdaCabal @PoliciaColombia https://t.co/zEkyibTFjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Onerous by @alarmistbrewing at @alarmistbrewing — https://t.co/Pystbixxet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mancan99 Thanks Gerald there's also a connection thru Clinton foundation and watered down medicine distributed in… https://t.co/K1zUPNmMMo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Súper a agradecido con Dios y emocionado de ser parte de este concierto delreinoproductions presenta @marcosyaroide… https://t.co/ErRkQIT2Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ObserverReport @Brooklynstop @thefuture1885 @Aussie_Jo @VanityFair @VanityFair is accurate: there was porn, softco… https://t.co/ZNUjE7iZpW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stuff I’m cutting today is dryyyyyyyyyyyyyyy... https://t.co/wFdySiXJrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love celebrating birthdays with my team mates! 🎂❤️ ••• Hope you had the best birthday ever @filthierich 😚 •••… https://t.co/XEWbYJDVf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bola_Sol Very true. The biggest changes are made through little changes in habits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrimandiTweets_ To be fair Alisson and Ederson are pretty much beasts lol. But I’m happy we got Leno. Not saying h… https://t.co/epcr6cT48M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t Sleep 💤 😐😐😐 @ Tower Grove South, St. Louis https://t.co/DEjCZVLkWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[LeBron James demanded the Los Angeles Lakers trade him to the Golden State Warriors in order to reach his ninth str… https://t.co/NBEMnGMYet]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poconoraceway @KyleBusch @NASCAR_Trucks @amsupdates Maybe he’ll get a Cup ride, now. #cherrypicker]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1 #MAGA… https://t.co/j5vk8G6GPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@British_Airways @HeathrowAirport @flightradar24 PLEASE post lot's of pictures...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kelly Rowland was a multi platinum solo act before Beyonce. Y'all need to do y'all research. Kelly just isn't as pr… https://t.co/EwqmQnFAn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved the preview of the Barbershop Quartet from The Music Man! Can't wait! (The Music Man musical will run at GHS… https://t.co/CjO8Eo39Ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@snoopdemidogg Well, most guides ask for use of butane or liquid nitrogen which can explode. It may take extra time… https://t.co/noloyAgALE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dandakich I was charged by a rabid raccoon when I was a kid and my Dad picked up a tree limb and killed it before it but me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RockChalkBlog I don’t believe we will be that strong. Doke coming back ? Recruits ? Program on probation from NCAA… https://t.co/X455cqlGVp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prachyl_randy @JonMelton21 @Jason_HD_8976 @AmberD___ @Nia_AndTHD @MiguelFuentesHD 👊🏾💯💪🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having everyone share everything and work together sounds nice and utopian; the problem is, this isn’t human nature… https://t.co/QuFvwAHMlt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3HL1045 Heck I’d Let Mike Leach look at my pelvic tear. He would probably have a solution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rubiconski @reddogsusie @leighjalland @Indigo_Pho13 @ruthmen @WinglessBird_ @SandraK93322487 @EMluvsPibbles… https://t.co/3cVeDsN0oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just want to be with someone and to be so exited to sing @TonyToniTone1 anniversary out loud ~B~]]></document><document><![CDATA[Traffic is crawling in #DurhamCounty on I-40 EB between Hwy 55 - Exit 278 and I-540 - Exit 283, wreck in the road... https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sgrate_ Black Dad:“My bank account depressed!” You got a therapist for that 👀👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paaay_paaay @warhawkbowling Great looking group @warhawkbowling. Proud of the way you continue to compete at such a high level!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our #World Is Going In A #Troubling Wrong Direction People. Is it the #Media's fault? 7 YR. Old learns how to hang… https://t.co/jRcn8m8D1M]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fat ass still leaning out... Please join us at the party, lower 4 abs.🤞🏼 https://t.co/5hqaqnxohL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkBessen @ScottWalker @theproselytizer also those cookies look like shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jake Roberts and Sydney Harvey @ Colby Files Photography https://t.co/hqa2ns9l5f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwansonAnders @NACTO @kteschke @schlthss @tooledesign @USDOTFHWA @Dutchreviewing Absolutely. But to get there, we… https://t.co/s5cKWS8lvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markephillips2 @TheNCHC @UNDmhockey @OmahaHKY For highlights you may have to go to https://t.co/fL0ikD02DC or @hphky may have some.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fellas this means she’s 14. Stay out of the DM’s with your nasty selves. Don’t be creeps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry just and random rant.🤷🏻‍♂️ as I said no one gives a shit anyways.😝🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein MAGA Hat's don't go back tracking now since Cohen flipped on Trump.  He was peaches and cream before… https://t.co/rHxHUT5ATv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Energy Drinks “Increase Stroke Risk by 500%” Due to Irregular Heartbeats https://t.co/k1yEzLesGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WinfieldWrestl2 @steele_morin This is impressive coach congrats on a great season!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#dallasstars are just hard to watch. They can’t score at all, and the D and goalies look like they’re on pins and n… https://t.co/t3eJNxvuNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Leon_Krueger7 @manyecastil Ni aquí en Monterrey nadie los toma en serio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVanValkenburg They won’t go for six for sure, but I’m not so sure they’d even sit for four.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is eating one of me.amato ‘s salads eatatrita . Get thee to Red Hook. #eatatrita #redhook #icecoffee… https://t.co/9QM0DvVAHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilMickelson may I kindly ask if you have tried working on a more balanced finish position to promote more consis… https://t.co/Fyf1nIaZnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mini golfing with the beau ❤️💛💚 #giligansisland #puttputt #myrtlebeah @ Myrtle Beach, South Carolina https://t.co/eJC8xsPCAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtneylea_x So sexy baby, I would fuck you hard in that hot shower baby! https://t.co/DCblS2GLvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @RampartNews @KamalaHarris She Fumbled and could not recover - she is not quick on her feet - I will not Vote for her .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Just like POTUS, the Orange Imbecile, you are lying sack of crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cubs get on the board in the fifth on RBI double by Mark Zagunis off Davies. #Brewers lead is trimmed to 2-1.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get ready for another round of TV and digital ads in the race for Chicago mayor. https://t.co/6gFGabyFq5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Just Gu away, your nothing but a partisan hack. We all know you have no love for this co… https://t.co/wp4UmrvFs4]]></document><document><![CDATA[LAFAYETTE,IN (LAF) ASOS reports gust of 50 knots (57.5 mph) from W @ 0944Z -- KLAF 240954Z AUTO 25027G45KT 10SM SCT… https://t.co/bKxfTFFbnB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was challenged by @MrsTGonz to post pictures of 7 of my favorite books, no reviews needed, for the… https://t.co/bq2RqwEUza]]></document></documents></author>