<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I have to create an Air Force heritage presentation to do on Monday in my Blues. Y’all I’m 6.5 months pregnant I ha… https://t.co/6qENKr1hHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full look at my outfit from sheinofficial! It’s one of my favorite places to shop since it’s so affordable and unli… https://t.co/PSvfLB4iE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_bummy7 @tylerherrickk I can see ur fat rolls? And u ain’t even post nothin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmund_Fraud @GoBeepUK @EdDarrell @SarahsCunning @WendyOrent @MsTrixter @GrumFromNorwich @iXeno @MacUmbridge… https://t.co/vuerHXz6ne]]></document><document><![CDATA[B went to stay with my cousin for the night and here I am home watching @theofficenbc on a Saturday night! #typicalsaturday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseGranger_ We’re strugglin on power plays against VAN! https://t.co/d7mTZTGiZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[12 year old me is screaming on the inside........ jonasbrothers @ El Rey https://t.co/SYdqt8NYcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afspnational and @PsychCongress are bringing #suicideprevention training to #mentalhealth clinicians around the co… https://t.co/FlQICH2SPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bet none of the #2020 candidates will release their tax returns because of Trump and Bernie]]></document><document><![CDATA[COMPASSION FATIGUE: First, we lose compassion for ourselves. Then, for our loved ones. Then, for our colleagues. Fi… https://t.co/5XTPIEKgnD]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is this even legal @charliekmox ? Second time in a week I’ve seen vehicles not even bother w/temp tags at all.… https://t.co/jZS0PbJGvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “most vulnerable humans” we have to protect are the MANY being born without prenatal care, financial support an… https://t.co/mf8IbUirPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[RE: data rights vs. reach, would love @karaswisher + @profgalloway analysis:  ➡️ #significantlocations = Apple’s mi… https://t.co/YUi1WldyL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PastorCussing Amen 🙏🏽 follow back please I am going to let people know your now on Twitter keep telling your spit… https://t.co/TBvsKTxi8G]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my son asks Alexa to pick a number between 1 and 10 octillion again, I’m gonna blow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amy_Siskind @audreyfringe21 I’m betting she wants all the facts so she can properly nail his coffin shut with his… https://t.co/nFAViokyYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McColganfiction THANK YOU! My husband cannot understand why I am not a fan of him doing that. https://t.co/LOtxt0Xv2X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone asked if I was a model yesterday and I almost laughed to death 😂 boooyy if you don’t get you goofy ahhh I d… https://t.co/fwFNMjZRtP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I wake up to snow covered roads, I still get that giddy feeling we won't have school today!   Oh, right.… https://t.co/qATgsaAXZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[the #jonasbrothers are back &amp; i needed everyone at work today to know this https://t.co/SbbhuHXkCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markschlereth Creepy staring gym dude taking surreptitious pictures is my number 1 irritant, especially while hogging the equipment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_Appelquist @erataskforceaz @girlsreallyrule @PiperPerabo @FemMajority @MajoritySpeaks Thanks for sharing,… https://t.co/LHLlXLKEYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the pleasure of running PR for a revolutionary event last night brandstaragency - Thank You First Responder,… https://t.co/8A9W8FT5LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[If this was my man I would beat his ass. SMH my gender reveal to this day is still the best day of my life. I remem… https://t.co/0wqouoFfNk]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's crazy how many places I've been but yesterday was my first time in Austin. Reminded me a lot of Denver I loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[So like I gave in and ate some chicken today... I feel so sick 🤮🤢 NEVER EATING MEAT AGAIN!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSZaidEsq @RadioFreeTom @FoxNews There are no “journalists” at FOX.  And there is definitely no news. #PropagandaTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[How cute is my father-in-law on the cover of the @DSCenturyNews with his 1931 Ford Model A!? I’m planning on riding… https://t.co/Mo9r8PuzfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anchorbound @nancylevine @femininecollect FYI.  Cancer sucks but we who kick it deserve peace of mind and free wil… https://t.co/KSN6pzinlN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honoring our Senior girls today! @keniecepurvis22 @aliyahcollier12 Danni Edwards! Going to miss these girls!  💜🧡 Go… https://t.co/bZ9bhCXmDX]]></document><document><![CDATA[omg 😩😩 “you” is so good already! He really just killed her fucking boyfriend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We still love you this is not your fault  , people needed to be paid .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan Jim get the republicans in push back battle now ! Democrats evil hateful players they will do anything to gain power !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Click the link in our bio to see currently open #SocialSciences jobs like "MASSAGE THERAPIST" at Covenant HealthCare in #Saginaw, MI.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t understand you try to distance yourself from themselves so you won’t end up hating them but idc so why should you]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever just really miss being close to someone ? Because same ☹️ I know back then you’d love to here about this...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Dean &amp; DeLuca in New York, NY https://t.co/N9L2EE3Fp8 https://t.co/7Sh9bmxwX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWSheaffer If I had your metabolism I would have ice cream for several meals a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@isopixel El odio está en tú corazón!  Cómo desear un terremoto ?  Cambia tú !]]></document><document><![CDATA[PE 7: How many kiddos can make it through the moving hula hoop? @TheJaysZone @jaixen_mike @meganadkinsPE… https://t.co/2E6uX14SbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#GOT7  #갓세븐  #TwitterBestFandom #SoompiAwards @GOT7Official  ✨ctto✨ https://t.co/qsN59tr1Pn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson @MSU_Basketball Go Green!!! I still have my copy of your first Sports Illustrated cover, you're in a tux 👍🏻🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somehow, unrequited love is even more sad in the Pup world. #dogsoftwitter #ValentineDay #yawn https://t.co/ucFPaZbm6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nancy_Marchese Not just ABA but SLP and OT. Not every Autistic person needs their behaviours changes. But our kids… https://t.co/Yl58niRE21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mafost @ChristineBemis2 @HOWareyousmart @DrP_Principal @SherriElliott82 @NowakRo @Bill_Huber_ @_on11 @RACzyz… https://t.co/qK9ma1KfP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sisters blackmailing me with ugly old pics of me cause I won’t tell her who I’ve been talking to recently. And t… https://t.co/kwtMM7AiRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does 20+ million daffodils look like? This is only a fraction. Daffodil Colorfest at Gibbs Gardens this weeken… https://t.co/cyg6dxoZXs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You shall eat the flesh of your sons, and you shall eat the flesh of your daughters. https://t.co/BM2mptURaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This man literally pushed me and another female out of the way to get on the G train, turns around, lets his mouth… https://t.co/chrBD11Zki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustG62 @Surviving2day @Ms__Positivity @bernadenedavis @PrettyBlue73 @GladysAnnJohns2 @NeasyIzMe Amen!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Long Island.  An early go for this PM flier.  #stewardesslife #comeflywithme #needcoffee #seekjoyyall… https://t.co/YIXoG1Xt7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GGyouthcentre Hi, I am Jackie, the founder of Origami Canada, in future both we can cooperate with each other, my… https://t.co/UIZ6hanBHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CyiRizzle_ No I did not 😩 We need to get it together lol ! Cause like wtf , I’m sick of it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[As women, we all are under so much pressure to be perfect. Social media has the “Pinterest Perfect” life and there… https://t.co/EgLULUvRY4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kathrineaw @miiranduuuh I’m glad that’ll finally watched it, she’s so precious when she starts saying maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaleJr These are GREAT quotes @DaleJr I LOVE reading them. I love your family's racing history.  It's amazing!❤]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please send feedback.. new topics at the TOP of Classwork. No website puts new information at the bottom.… https://t.co/DRoiJyeqJM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bella_pmk @paulacblades001 @JustinTrudeau @canpoli @realDonaldTrump @YouTube I just hope she doesn’t the Clinton t… https://t.co/QeXlQAWXXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m never worried about who I can fuck on next, or who face I can sit in . I be solid solo dolo !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyVirtualVaca @DivaVinophile @united @GailBenzler @jflorez @ChristopherB070 @SashaEats @LoriMoreno @always5star… https://t.co/hThW9YZN0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelseaBallerini @opry Kelsea I honestly think this is the best one yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were camped out each Friday. Conspiracy theorist can’t explain that. Just got lucky being there instead of giv… https://t.co/XU8Cg85Ilb]]></document><document><![CDATA[no entiendo porque algunos doctores se agarran contra ti tipo q onda ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilldeBlasio Not here. Perhaps New York and Cali will need to rethink their political choices, bucky!!😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonyaSone7 @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity Whose is they?  We have a Constitution that must be respected.  As a citi… https://t.co/DPV0eHII3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[i absolutely love when @mchildress_ comes &amp; hangs out with me at work💛💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anandramesh @MeagMarty @jkreim @jer0metran @Ginachka68 @kristybarger @cmcgovern1 @nadineseq @madslevs @Marge SNIPPETTTSSSS!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Concentration and so proud of their creations. #legoclub @HewittElem https://t.co/dJMzdowomi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyFakaBean @kathygriffin @JussieSmollett In other words, I must know Jussie definitely staged his attack before Zi say anything‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the key for the Cards in this one is to not let TJ Gibbs get in a groove. Notre Dame plays their best baske… https://t.co/nrHxGyffbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@La_Primavera_GE La Primavera, The grt news is that both SIMMONS &amp; GOTTI were PULLED TODAY from #nycacc by… https://t.co/BZ4IpXXJGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[*instructs* I dont know about anyone else, but I dont take my instructions from her...on any subject, much less wha… https://t.co/M3ffV5yFK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[♥️ this model for #datajournalism by @zhoyoyo ... how to connect two frameworks for data stories #nicar2019 ⚡️ talks https://t.co/Z0SMYyoSik]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'd like to see how many people would fall for that https://t.co/NKXhev5uKG]]></document><document><![CDATA[We've just decided to go riding once again tomorrow and I'm so pumped even though I already fucked me knee. Full send don't give a fuuuuck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we still telling people to kill themselves? That ain’t the wave, should’ve never been the wave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear watching the missed connections video from Cole swindell make my day everyday❤️ @coleswindell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes!! New @iamonlychild. I love everything Jordan creates, seriously so talented and a huge inspiration for my own… https://t.co/3UBNvlaTaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait okay Margaery never ate the cake now I think it was the cake again]]></document><document><![CDATA[That committee meeting is canceled!  The next meeting of Health and Family Services is on Monday at Noon and #HB3 i… https://t.co/qRwc0YNgjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Jussie Smollett. @NewseumED @bam1212 @loyolaUM_CISJ @MediaLiteracyEd #medialiteracy #socialjustice… https://t.co/rVk0xIpUTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/Jdl8Tkmbpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[☕️ ☕️ ☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/KvUl9YtPzo https://t.co/fn9bJN0C5t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LovelyVixen_ Wow, I should really read better 😂 the name will be perfect ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what we need; our representatives to get so fired up they just say “to hell with it” and let loose with wha… https://t.co/CRSYPAJHGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[VICTORY ALERT! Women’s tennis claims the second win of the season dominating Le Moyne 6-1 last night! We will be ba… https://t.co/z0tiRKE8Z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[zaxbys in lake wylie gave me unsweet tea today and i’ve never felt more disrespected in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shango5T @RevelsHiram @BrownWomanKing @flippedhatnupe No one is denying our african ancestral lineage. That’s a li… https://t.co/zvZ1dZ4uSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm So Excited to See You Full Suit 🤩🤩 🤩🤩 🤩🤩 🤩🤩 🤩🤩 🤩 https://t.co/lPBTTMrrzB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gretchenwhitmer @sean_prevost @SenGillibrand @ewarren @amyklobuchar @KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @BernieSanders… https://t.co/AR8bLuCWm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleeb @Anna_Louii @TiggerTherese @chloemmx @drlangtry_girl Target has short, curvy girl friendly jeans that fit perfectly! Good luck 💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hariashurst It’s homogenized out there. Every site and paper  covering the big names, pop, rap with little room le… https://t.co/FS5V0KD1gc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makes me feel a little safer today. I think a lot more that has gone on in this current administration is now being… https://t.co/s1qUTV7Wjs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rossputin @jackhealyNYT @CPRverlee @SenatorBrophy @630khow @ByJohnFrank @meganschrader @KyleClark @okmaher… https://t.co/iL0zcysV3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see my bestfriend after almost a year and a half apart and now we both have our little babies to add to ou… https://t.co/w6Fcbb45Uq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @lyft tell this driver thanks for making late me to work and holding up downtown traffic. Stopped in the street… https://t.co/aCGNuLDgbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lempstl @Kokomothegreat @realDonaldTrump YOU ARE SO WTONG! Please understand this is a fight between good and evil… https://t.co/SR1eQ5mJTr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't be sure, but the Oscars were so classy and glamorous I think @awkwafina wore underwear.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpudd @scoopercooper We need someone who isn’t political or associated with any organization. We need an individua… https://t.co/swkQnJvi12]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inge Mahn says that she needed to be emancipated from making figurative sculpture in the early ‘70s. So she started… https://t.co/2IEtswo5e4]]></document></documents></author>