<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@DefNotRyan I've seen no Ash today... Maybe because its raining and it all washed off. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawasook From my Tesla experience as of the last few years? This seems like it is about normal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[... Moscow Matchmaker, Putin... @RealJamesWoods @seanhannity @rupertmurdoch @realDonaldTrump @BetteMidler… https://t.co/G3CSr4mW2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1989deg @SeanSchemmel @vicmignogna You telling me coworkers have to work together and do promotional stuff? No way?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Location, location, location.  A #logos word from the prophet! @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/dHHZ8UGwe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like driving miss daisy all over again #Oscars19 #AcademyAwards2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was having thoughts of the Saturday night massacre.   Well there's your screaming headline quote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTtTos || 🇪🇸 The White RACE Spaniard BLONDES👑🇪🇸 Women Are The MOS… https://t.co/pjEfdP91WN]]></document><document><![CDATA[2700-2748 14th St 2700-2748 14th St, Santa Monica, CA 90405 https://t.co/tMEQu9nxgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikiebarb When I was at Time Inc, the M.E.'s contract included a shut-up clause I refused to sign as a journalist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Raiders new stadium is coming along just in time for 2020 season 👀 (taken while flying down I-15 in a Lyft, not… https://t.co/nssbDU9EwE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to all my ladies out there: single or taken. I hope you have the greatest day filled with joy… https://t.co/lGQrMfvDrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are ready! #BeatHouston #RollWave #Tulane @GreenWaveMBB https://t.co/brCKh8yh8J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Turns out diplomacy is more complicated than reality TV. https://t.co/84Cjnewlnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[update: Gallery Place Metro- Disruption reported to have been debris fire near the platform. FD has cleared the smoke, reopening shortly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing the Fed thinks the economy is cooling and may not raise interest this year.   And still looking at wel… https://t.co/po5yfZ6Q0K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @realDonaldTrump We are ready to work madam. Michael Jacome M.Ed  #MAGA #latinosfortrump… https://t.co/fiwSfZA423]]></document><document><![CDATA[Classic line that has been referenced many a times 👍 #Squats #Squat #BadKnees #BadKnee #KneePain #KneeProblems #Hip… https://t.co/MJcL6Zw2GT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Murray State v/s Eastern Kentucky 🏀🏀🏀 @EKUHoops https://t.co/PRBKlW0z8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevechimenti Story today has Holland claiming he is going to extend Blashill's deal.  He is very HAPPY with Blash… https://t.co/K2xzRXIP9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[But I'm just really glad that doing what #Lorena did is so uncommon that it warranted a TV show. https://t.co/4c7FXKs2RL]]></document><document><![CDATA[GBK - at the half @SouthWildcats 31, @TVAthleticDept 25 in girls D1 District semi-final basketball. @CDABSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's good because the stock market in 2018 sucked, sucked, sucked!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never thought I’d see the day when Disney would do away with their “Vault” formula, but I’m really glad it’s finall… https://t.co/tITkyANo1K]]></document><document><![CDATA[💨 Hold onto your hat! And watch out for flying garbage cans. Those wicked winds will continue to roar today and rem… https://t.co/cMtKSotDlO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Danville Walmart deer urine spray update 2:  police say boys were underage. Likely a high school prank.  @LEX18News https://t.co/mNEQ0Iy6oX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mayor_Steinberg @GoodDaySac @GoodDayMarianne Marianne Sacramento will miss you happy retirement❤️👍🏼🎉 https://t.co/8zsaLgu2Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Challenge the mind. #everydayathlete #trainingmode #trainingmodels #grinddaily #grindhard #grindmode #nevergivein… https://t.co/ruOyYWutif]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @nancy_hamm1 @Rbigzs @CuriousHobbyist @fortressfin @leftovergravy @rdrhwke @CandysOpinions @pcal4HIM… https://t.co/wdyII5RTRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ja Rule reminds me of the kid who gets teased for smelling who tries to combat it by walking around people going, "… https://t.co/LHQVoKsXer]]></document><document><![CDATA[These weapons will be in the hands of the leftist criminals if the left has it’s way!! Reasonable people understand… https://t.co/P0tqLvU6FF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: Steve how do I make it in America?  Steve Harvey: https://t.co/yuSLXpgxYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tousleshommes @myspierce @georgiemorvis Amazing!!! Also how good was that MF concert I’m still shook]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kanye better start going nuts on Twitter again soon, I need a new album]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pues mucho reencuentro de The Jonas Brothers pero cuando el reencuentro de Los Kumbia Kings? 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Featured Item: #Terex TA30 #articulateddumptruck #JeffMartinAuctioneers Early Spring Public #Auction, Mar 7-9, Broo… https://t.co/iA2hARJLg3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@queenknitter @DrewBMcIntyre But not *Baptist*--we tried that and it didn't work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sartorial statement; rural casual! From @nordstrom #Chinos #CashmereScarf @nordstrom_rack @toms shoes. Another S… https://t.co/fOn2Gzg0by]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GentleGiantLTD when will you reveal what the McQuarrie Exclusive will be for Star Wars Celebration Chicago?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #1 job of @CNN, @MSNBC, @MotherJones (sadly), https://t.co/Dib5m4ZSDT. is to erase people of color who support… https://t.co/BSfOBg7YQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another weekend in the sun complete. Back to reality. (@ Orlando Sanford International Airport in Sanford, FL) https://t.co/rzvJxZ0kmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/C8RhiHCwSR]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RD78J55h1p You can dial Verizon number and connect to experts at Verizon Customer Service Phone Number… https://t.co/nGR6fsGhTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kasio27 @gregolsen88 @BarackObama @dukebasketball @GoHeels @ZionW32 @Panthers @UNC_Basketball Why dont you learn t… https://t.co/eqYwtLCIgP]]></document><document><![CDATA[thanks for celebrating me 💓🍻 @TateWalllters @AshleyHutch12 @morgannrenee16 @ryleigh_harris https://t.co/LwdMFnrB7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @Juliw180 @morningmika “ incompetence” is too mild a word for this morally deaf person.  Was she always this… https://t.co/dHThGQigBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sianoresist Actually the old testament does not consider the start of life until birth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbelial @Mel_the_geek @Observer2541 @deelane @synredae @PATRICIAMEEHA17 @Elinor27652146 @Trixie883low @Hiveaclue… https://t.co/ciMmtjdcwh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The HARDEST part about the gym is just getting there, but once you’re through those doors (..) It’s easy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: what could possibly go wrong.  Aniexty: I’m glad you asked https://t.co/E7spgi3jJJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday we lost Ted Lindsay and King Kong Bundy. Ugh, hate days like that. Rest in Power Guys! #WWE #NHL #Hockey @DetroitRedWings]]></document><document><![CDATA[So let me see if I’ve got this straight: People murdered a family member and called for the criminalization of the… https://t.co/TK9FiMuCEy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustJeepGirl Sour Kraut with hot dogs. Oh and mixed vegetables out of a can. 🤮🤮🤮 Never 🖕ing again!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tjwatson0403 @andrewzimmern Your so blinded by hate. Can’t defend Hillary obama but go after trump when it all com… https://t.co/vIBgdXk4GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes it does haha #livluvdance #adulting #truth #funny #humorquotes @ San Antonio, Texas https://t.co/vx7QqcbEY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never wanted to grab a beer with @NickJacksonYB more than I do after seeing the way he acted at the BSB concer… https://t.co/Ldt6oPtC5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tithenai …aren’t conkers a kind of drink that Ford Prefect and Zaphod Beeblebrox demanded of a starship captain wh… https://t.co/dn1ieka6cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. This is incredibly difficult to decide D: but I’m going to have to stick with the world of Harry Potter ⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cardi B concert is so live she is a wonderful performer🤯  #rodeohouston #cardib @ NRG Stadium https://t.co/QCE3Lbp9Y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slept on my couch and received NO attention from my dog bailey until 6:30 when she decided to become a weighted bla… https://t.co/ugz3mX2zQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thearidior Don't want to. Mean Bitches are not loved long. My daughters know if they are like you they will not ge… https://t.co/7rKUyBJRvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just dread going into a @BankofAmerica to do any transaction. #slow #lines You would think in 2019 banks would ha… https://t.co/stmEtSvQfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TalkinACCSports You and many others lol. Syracuse baited them to throw some passes in that zone that lead to turno… https://t.co/aQWA0TiaEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jguaido @NituPerez @patriciajaniot @NTN24 @marcorubio @CarinesMoncada @MariaCorinaYA  Muy buena idea!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elnocturno @eloycam2012 yo hablo de todo lo que quiero, no se tu ¿que es lo que comprendes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnowWhite7IAM @nowhere192 I like to read too! And I like to write. Especially about the truth. https://t.co/9oW5cUEbXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravelKing711 @zagaholicpod @RemFifteen @BenStinar Ya I agree with you there. That’s were the whole topic popped u… https://t.co/ePf7Fitm02]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t tweeted since October! I kinda fall in and out of love with Twitter. 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWD #TheWalkingDead #NormanReedus #RickGrimes @welcometonissa @TheWalkingDead @WalkingDead_AMC https://t.co/V7PYkBEeMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te quedas en casa un fin de semana y ayudas un poco, quiero verlos hacer su aporte aunque sea 1 dolar. https://t.co/374oluN5Jr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raritansailor 1st we are not Europe. 2nd what Eisenhower did was infrastructure, not what you want to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews I’m over here, on the right, a proponent of common sense, “truth, justice and the American way...”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN What you've said is not anti-Semetic. For too long, it has been taboo to publically criticize Israel for f… https://t.co/1McfTiTFgF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@twitsmodernos @moskodelameche @DeniseDresserG @El_Universal_Mx Hablas como si 1.- La guarda Nacional existiera ya… https://t.co/0MvG7WpcNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#goodmorning #calabashnc #WECTwx @kellie_wx @jesslyn_wx @ericdavisWECT @medwick @TVsGabeRoss @PatrickEllisWx… https://t.co/k86Jd51SLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xpnmorningshow I don’t know what her plans are for 2019, but it would sure be sweet to see @liannelahavas at @xpnfest this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodShammgod40 Yeaaaaa but if we trade Carr to try to get Murry I’m be sick]]></document><document><![CDATA[We sure live in a fucked time to raise children. I never had any of this shit to worry about.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elvis Started The Drip 💧 &amp; Gave It To Me In HollyWood You Niggas 🧢 LOL 😂 @ Hollywood Walk of Fame https://t.co/CSxF7aME1D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skogkar Det är kanske så enkelt att kommunen har den information den behöver men inte får röja det eller att det f… https://t.co/x3tmqKsWNT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always time for catch in the pool and a swim all year round if you work hard you can play hard. #philly… https://t.co/4r7K2fMc8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[2/2 Vengeance is mine says the Lord (Deuteronomy 32:35-36). He also tells us to love our enemies (Matthew 5:44). I… https://t.co/uyHxNKimnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DFBHarvard @2scoopsCam We have another Reagan vs Mondale landslide ahead of us in 2020 no matter who the Dems sele… https://t.co/c15Gat9FFD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Choichan @GLEN85BLANCO @RichardsoRenee @carrishaw @RadonnaA @DignityPrincipl 😘😘😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VaL1Dz @jerryxfeng If you got 4 teammates, why can't you pass them the ball?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @senatorshoshana @StoolOutdoors @Official_Exodia https://t.co/KismFLP8AI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another from this press conference.   Tong tears into Trump advisor Stephen Miller, saying Miller has a, “sociopath… https://t.co/N5xISrk9DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @Finalsite for collaborating with us on this great project. Looking forward to Monday’s 🚀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can @RealBenCarson/@SecretaryCarson salvage what's left of his legacy? I confess feeling sorry for him at times. https://t.co/DKBRTsMRBD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xtrixcyclex @KamalaHarris Bernie’s a little bit of a deadbeat, let’s be honest.   The thing I notice about Harris… https://t.co/N0GcGUINsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[You gotta test drive it before you buy it bro 🤷🏽‍♂️ don’t know like the hustle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_howbizarre_ @TMMamaDrama My bad sorry just thought she was your friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 30 hours of Gary Cohn testimony to Mr. Mueller? It's GOLD, Jerry, GOLD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some mirth. Free and Simple Jokes ~ Write the question, read it with the class and have kids... https://t.co/lPRowaKJIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Momento en el cual nuestro Presidente encargado, @jguaido, entra al aeropuerto de #Maiquetia.   Ya va vía a la conc… https://t.co/XKRLG7nwpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agreed, Nuclear is dying but they are trying to milk the rate payers for a few decades longer, and stick the tax pa… https://t.co/u87KiI2NYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/QvP4i3cWPe]]></document><document><![CDATA[This just in!  My new General Lee coffee mug and Cars of Hazzard t-shirt has arrived!  Big shoutout to… https://t.co/M8UzCOWc7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods So far it basically comes down to 3 actors acting ! Put them in jail so they can see what real raci… https://t.co/7OLoZv9AGd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Executive Vice Chancellor @Education_Poole does an outstanding job introducing @goCLTCC to @cased4 at our Louisiana… https://t.co/MDo4i5xYov]]></document></documents></author>