<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@_ryan_delgado @JColeNC Issa good one but in the morning is forever my fave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @PamDamoff - what a fantastic choice! You will be wonderful.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shelisutz @EdKrassen Many people from many  backgrounds voted for President Trump... maybe Tuckers wife.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lu_Cossio Amooouuur me llegó hoy y estoy en muletas... nunca habia odiado tanto el ser mujer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Procrastination defers more dreams than anything else. Not only does it rob us of our time and talents, but it can… https://t.co/ZP8m5DQU5K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Timcast - The Smollett as victim story makes no sense, and leaves too many questions unanswered. The Smollett as h… https://t.co/Y5qAZouE7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encantó.. 😍 @TXT_members Puede ver videos en V LIVE. https://t.co/kef4gmFPKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[* Only two babies have been aborted for vaccine research.  * Vaccines used to contain mercury, but that doesn’t mat… https://t.co/Cr0wuSiVsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Hello...sounds familiar.  Remember❓  #TrumpTaxScam that you @marcorubio heralded and VOTED Yes👎🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Don’t hold much stock in John Brennen’s opinion....nor MSM for that matter]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big John just called UDA, USDA.  I said it is not the United States Department of Agriculture; it is Universal Danc… https://t.co/Upzz5xLnf3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealNoel2 @kimberlasskick Yasss that’s the shirt I want to rock, right there!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuzzFeed This is not normalizing anything this is making women look psychotic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beth talking about my little sisters feet- “yeah she he’s some sleighs” 🙃@BethanyMitcham]]></document><document><![CDATA[A capsule hotel I might stay on—— #capsulehotel #Japan #Culture #Travel]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 4 year old just created a game called “Sleep.” He says, “The person that sleeps the longest wins.” I don’t think… https://t.co/7V0xqGe9Pw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost Too little way too late sweetie. Retire to an island somewhere so you can never be heard from again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tweeting our hockey memories during Scotiabank #HockeyDay in Canada will support community hockey across the countr… https://t.co/XfLh6VyXbk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Larger primary market galleries tended to represent fewer female artists in 2018—those with $10 million plus in tur… https://t.co/KmoDgIIeLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why ! Elected government here in America gone crazy . Left want poor health care, garbage for food.. streets toilet… https://t.co/zGoPIQlB7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaseyAndersonPB This describes my neighborhood perfectly.  A really great post.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyDaniela_ Don't even get me started on the mental fortitude required to wash my sheets and make my bed.  So much dramatic agony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cutest bags this year for the #YSCSummit19 in #Austin!  #sisterhood #breastcancersucks #inittogether… https://t.co/xlp5rDMnRT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpuopolo @RyanAFournier yeah!!!!  that's not the red white and blue I love.]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 days, I'd give ANYTHING to spend it with you! Talk about the greatest gift EVER, baby that would be it! Fly me,… https://t.co/6BsDTNtVDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thattricktaylor @ChuckECheeses that’s the only thing on my mind for the past 24 hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flannel day!!! ✌🏾💁🏼‍♀️#CSCfam #centierbank #thatsmybank #flannelday @ Centier Bank https://t.co/CVihJKh8MG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear friends with me at the IHS in Manhattan, celebrating my new book with me! Kashi Rita and Jeff Bland are wit… https://t.co/TQ05qaDxEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I truly believe it.  Trump's Father was #KKK   Now, MAGA hats are the 2019 version. @realDonaldTrump… https://t.co/LP2QNpJT7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelSuddard Given we are marrying in elliot lake, the weather is even more unpredictable haahha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo no tengo la culpa de que cuando tu estabas chiquita durmieras en la alacena 😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolasD1977 @G_Padraic @thepapertigerx @thepapertigerx is so short you can’t even see her in the photo 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[La vida no se mide por las veces que respiras, sino por los momentos que te dejan sin aliento 🌄😍♥️ https://t.co/4cbGzoobX2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m always thinking about solutions I can offer to help women “flavor their lives.” How would making jewelry shoppi… https://t.co/sxGldSqUV3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and I quickly discovered, after adopting she at the #muscatinehumanesociety, that Casey was not fond of men.… https://t.co/jHj2vdpTfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TruckersVote @GOP Yeah.... you could kinda see this one coming. https://t.co/XMarKht2np]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mysticmelissa_ OMG I love that she has the beaver!!! I’ll probably get around to making that shirt at some point :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing the families in LEX for the Sweet Sixteen. Brings back such special memories when we went with @LHSHOOPS18 back in 2014.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeb_Hoge @scotticutlip Does it matter? It’s not the features of the device that are my issue.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wackyvorlon the wires carrying the signals to the amp are parallel-ish, but run on opposite sides of the CRT, and… https://t.co/gi5LPSWV39]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attention: April the giraffe is pregnant again and that’s the best news I’ve heard all day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get that delays happen but my entire process flying home this weekend has been a nightmare. Rude staff, 3 hour de… https://t.co/Im4bfIm4LG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think this has anything to do with the journalists but the organization that pays them and has editorial ri… https://t.co/wwN15xxF4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhay_11_ @GatorsSB You know what else sucks?? You know what NVM.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee @MartySmithESPN #MartyandMcGee A few hrs ago, my friends and I drove down to Mooresville for StocksforTo… https://t.co/JzVH9kJsAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[BBC News - Botswana mulls lifting elephant hunting ban https://t.co/YQSK8Ojxu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mradamwelcome Love it! Everyone has the ability to complete this task independently &amp; it doesn’t cost anything!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me and my youngest #womensday2019 @ Louisville, Kentucky https://t.co/d2JgvzMq4A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaneTheCatMom I was watching this video and my little kitty came in and stood there just listening...]]></document><document><![CDATA[IMPEACH RASHIDA TLAIB - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/tIIo6NEfkf via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole video is pure comedy. The way he flings the bag then the last like 5 seconds he just standing there plea… https://t.co/RCWOTKmafC]]></document><document><![CDATA[UC Berkeley has a huge problem with being bias. The college caused this problem by not letting students hear both s… https://t.co/wMkQmkjXoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Why I WORK so hard FRIDAY  For all of March Madness we're talking about WHY we've made decisions to live a HEA… https://t.co/0D8RVKaPVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[HI I JUST LEARNED THAT DR. SCOTT THE PALEONTOLOGIST FROM MY FAVORITE SHOW (DINOSAUR TRAIN) LIVES IN DENVER AND WORK… https://t.co/Kj0eBnMOdQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I’m gonna end up being a stone cold bitch before I even get to genuinely like someone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Every5thDay @stevenact4 the whole vladdy is fat and he strained it, is so silly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureniscooking @johncardillo That’s such BS! They were trying to start a coup because HILLARY LOST...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryBuckets2 @woodhe15 @BarstoolBDevils @UNCBarstool https://t.co/w4q7sNM8S6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRC @abarrica @nytimes This is so wrong. We need inclusive sex education. We need to support inclusion for ALL of… https://t.co/BVsgWkG2gr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielTorresAld If cops escorted her off the freeway I’m like 1000% positive it would’ve been on the news or peopl… https://t.co/oJamDr8dAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnkurMa15287277 Yes you are.  The fact you can not comprehend that again proves somethings about you &amp;  your view.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this is why kids have night mare.. COT DAM NIT OLAFFFF!!!!! https://t.co/LjKhQgdP9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKalenAllen I felt the same way and she just broke up with her man. Just sayin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i need friends who are down for midnight drives , lake days , cookouts , pool parties and road trips. 🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the “big stuff” down to fleas, every life force on this planet seemingly wants me get between me and starting… https://t.co/Vvt04vyVGS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish today was Sunday because my hungover ass has never wanted lemon rice soup from USA so fucking bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @twils22 post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or review… https://t.co/vZR54CFXl6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevCBJacksonSr Amen much more than that! He gave everything to us for us we should want to give him everything we… https://t.co/8vQwNPyOIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah you’re right up there with Kennedy and Abraham Lincoln you pussy grabbing hateful heart bigot… https://t.co/UBzoFAplWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Inner Richmond District in San Francisco, CA https://t.co/BgArLeUkxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sopbeen @politico Liberal anyone pushes for multiculturalism. But Israel is not that multicultural. Obviously its… https://t.co/hI2TxDNo7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snacks and all drinks,  on the house 6-8 pm . Nice !! #warwickhotelrittenhousesquare @ Warwick Hotel Rittenhouse Sq… https://t.co/R2FPXhfPTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @Saukel Interesting. I hope you are correct. @realDonaldTrump do you feel the walls of justice closing in on you???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kartos @ImFastnt @VoltronStore Either way voltron is over so I don’t give a shit anymore. Just hate the fandom. Ne… https://t.co/JpDESWzBFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel my Heart Chakra this morning. I haven't felt peaceful in a while like this and I can feel confident again. T… https://t.co/c0968BOyg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green New Deal would cost up to $93 trillion, or $600G per household, study says  https://t.co/BRACwNDOY5 HAHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maine teen charged after allegedly caught driving more than 100 MPH.  Troopers say he was going 109 in a 50.… https://t.co/WCwDT9JIhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darkwebhorsegrl hope it goes smoothly and if anything is wrong there are simple explanations! dont stress too much beforehand]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gary Sinise loves our Veterans. We are grateful for what you do. Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[guys staring me down in the mall got me feeling like https://t.co/wBRF2xWXcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have seen 8+ police cars and an emergency Hummer speeding down i290W 😬🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Merisssaaaa I don’t even know, man. I don’t know what there is to do around here. 😂 I definitely want to go to a dispensary thooooough]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do you need Valentine’s Day to treat someone special? You should do that everyday..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Should I go into thousands of dollars worth of debt to attend film school? Y or N?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArianaGrande I'd love to see you!! You're voice is like an 👼 but doubt I'll be able to afford tickets or get a ride......maybe next time 😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had to take the kid to the Pediatrician...Walked in to a living history museum 🤣#KarenRebels #visibilitymatters https://t.co/uz1xKutvlp]]></document><document><![CDATA[had another bad experience with the nail salon. someone please tell me where i should get my nails done in my area.… https://t.co/U4iS7uLCM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wide awake because it feels like my house will be blown down at any moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nosheepfollower @JohnOSullivan36 @Bitey_Bolger @ThorntonNiwot @JSapp_AR @tomwatson Who’s this fictional  “we” or “… https://t.co/OWreK0ixFJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[LA shows for shawn have me STRESSEDT I think i’m just gonna wing it with tix as the date gets closer 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much love to the sweetest country star out there. Dan + Shay are honestly the nicest artists to their fans, it r… https://t.co/IkbTdi0yCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyRedWave I agree. What idiot designed the oversized jacket? What woman wants to look bigger?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@livvjos both bc i’ve seen waaaaaay too many people do nothing after they use a machine and i’m not an asshole]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone join hands and let's get solar on all our neighbors roofs. Making California a leader in alt energy.… https://t.co/yhmNhx5K8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynnewbnc @EleanorMontague @Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump People get loud (like at a football game) but they are no… https://t.co/rOusQBd8X7]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only time you will be called cute is when your a baby no matter how ugly u are]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savannah Georgia here I come!!  It’s that time of the year...@AANP_NEWS #FAANP Winter Meeting!!  #NPsLead!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Great Hotel Options for Universal Studios Hollywood https://t.co/xvARwEz52t via @TravelAgeWest @thegarlandhotel]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Time is precious. Don’t waste it on someone who doesn’t realize that you are, too.”  Ok noted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AllEyesOnE And then one night we were laying in bed a few days before we found out the gender, and we knew we nee… https://t.co/fjImZdkhCX]]></document></documents></author>