<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@weismanjake @PatrickMooreRIP @mattingebretson Tonight’s ep: “Wrong. God is bad and vengeful and doesn’t exist. Now… https://t.co/pr3evrvjp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkRedbeliever @HurriKane_Jr_88 And at least this is in my town. I am not one of those poor saps who tired his ki… https://t.co/Ndx9to5MqK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hoganbrenda @AmyMek @realDonaldTrump I will, and I will keep holding those in power accountable and refuting ignorance like yours.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AB InBev’s Non-Alcohol Beer Byproducts Become Biofuel https://t.co/ysgoi9waUO via @AmericaCrftBeer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ptbocrone To this day, I’ll still eat either one or two slices of sandwich bread topped with a few zigzags of… https://t.co/GAgNuey8AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[My son is impervious to lightsabers! #lightsaberimunity #lightsaber #starwars @ Temecula, California https://t.co/JCDxxAbVtj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah, but it’s also pretty hypocritical for a man who yells at rich people for having money to then turn around and… https://t.co/kLWTnYYrJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember how we beat W in 2004 because we did not debate personal accounts? How the GOP picked up seats in 1998 bec… https://t.co/LmOKkbAfFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kupcakekami Decided to cut it without speaking to the mother (and apparently the child) trust me I read it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Creat1ve Neither, just stripping it down to the Explicit Content https://t.co/btizwC5CvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbusa617 @PhilMcCrackin44 yeah, I watch @GrahamLedger instead on @OANN of course Trish is much hotter too IMO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlminer Good morning Laurie! Have a beautiful day. https://t.co/nP3zR7uS5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreddieKraft Nothing wrong with being honest, that’s a good quality.  Don’t give up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlannaKennedy @lydsaussie 🤣  We Need  More Trivia!  Love that stuff. It's #May13! 😉🙂  (I should know.)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s Vegas Golden Knights shootout victory over the Florida Panthers was a great back and forth battle that tr… https://t.co/yBKfSIqkX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here comes the general! 🎶 @ Washington Monument National Monument https://t.co/Kh7d59YDvI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? SAP Development Manager - https://t.co/uTPFcsmz3E #IT #Wausau, WI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supposed to be off today but instead they decide to host a company wide meeting in the middle of downtown Tampa of all places 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic to see the GVHD crew all together to celebrate @fredhutch’s Dr Paul Martin for all he has done for the HC… https://t.co/CX5NnnDtPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Sorry ! 1.4 billion is more than a dollar ! Go back to school ! Trump wins Biggly ag… https://t.co/QAKGEkrNuf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Question: Do Courtier Heroes with Dark Acolyte command trait gain the Abhorrent Ghoul King’s spell as well? Do they… https://t.co/cSjKs0eO50]]></document><document><![CDATA[@terryreed48 @Tolerance_org @ClintSmithIII Thank you and I agree! Nothing pairs better than History and American Lit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well that was quick! Make it 4-1 Clockers on a laser by Jackson Hornung! 1:00 left in the 2nd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[IDK why I've never heard of @emmachamberlain until the other day, but I feel like we would get along.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KillerBebe Thanks for following my Finsta on Instagram. Didn’t expect that at all. Can you follow my main IG as we… https://t.co/CauS3DbwHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the IRS, instead of having audited of the T party members, would have audited the members of house and the senat… https://t.co/RXVv0tNwNX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Between the Blackhawks game earlier and this Sharks game now, I’m going to see 26 goals scored tonight😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heck of a Deal. Purchase today and take advantage of the fun that could be had. @OHLHockey @OHLBattalion    First g… https://t.co/HVCZTdwYd8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyskublics @DearEvanHansen @Mirvish Same here, touched on so many powerful themes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My secret on-campus bathroom has more foot traffic than usual this afternoon. Real shame, I was hoping for a more t… https://t.co/ps8JF89Tbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F3DickTrickle @NASCAR @Daniel_SuarezG @Mc_Driver @TonyStewart Also last time I checked we are talking about the “b… https://t.co/EgLsy1vNcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Children are the ones who are impressionable right now, and so she’s going to go out there and do the best she can… https://t.co/9vJVgbc37a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#koreanbbq #sizzle #foodie #asmr @ Furusato BBQ https://t.co/A8PkbKKEtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[America is not the greatest country because we prioritize money over knowledge. We live to the tune of post WWII mo… https://t.co/ju7VgWJ0YB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got back to North Carolina and I’m already tired of this cold weather]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAW was the first horror film I watched in theaters and I remember leaving that theater in a sort of stupor. Up unt… https://t.co/kA9prIIXsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you look at most of these you see the dbs be having they eyes in the backfield and that’s when they were beat. E… https://t.co/ofEUr2Msyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okeh. I saved all the people I followed into a list, then manually unfollowed hundreds of them who didn’t follow me… https://t.co/RNVVS8cl2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tatclouthier @ChairoMexicano Fui a buscar el libro (juntos hicimos historia) y agotado. Pero compre el de Neoporfi… https://t.co/j485JyYsJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thinking about stopping here. Don’t really wanna risk trying to get 1st. https://t.co/64aJThNVZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOneTAR My German is a little rusty or nonexistent, is this going to be more widely available?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFPespanol Si el gobierno de los EE.UU reconoce a @jguaido como Presidente, porqué Maduro tiene todavía un Embajad… https://t.co/z018gmjATS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacqEHoward What are your thoughts on Section 13-Vaccine Insert: Prevnar 13 has not been evaluated for the potenti… https://t.co/xmNUXMiqec]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSarelson @juandelcerro @SustainableMags Bradley Cooper is on the Hugh Jackman program.  True artist. https://t.co/Vx94kci3JU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @coachaubry to post 7 covers of books I love--no explanations--no review--just the c… https://t.co/XPqNgTiLBl]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you dig the song, but don’t know any of the words... 😂 #tough https://t.co/vm6ar7ZG8q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell A national emergency: inability to fulfill the stupidest of campaign promises.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Denver, CO? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Technology Internship at Vantiv #IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlukasX77 No doubt it will be good for Charlotte businesses as a whole. It’s just not my cup of tea and I wanted y… https://t.co/yDgZJgEgtm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dude at his first Tball game. #tball #baseball #slugger #futureallstar @ Mustang Ballpark https://t.co/Z4aMcuo4U2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pokemonsnapme Y did your armpits wish me a happy Valentine’s Day before you..?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKBHD Looking great 👍  Thanks for the review of the process, very interesting. Glad you found such a good shop.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waterworld: what would happen if more than Moses had a warning. @shapeofwater : subplot of Waterworld.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grogers1010 @abridgesmith Yes!  If you want them to podcast you better make your own podcast. #DLGWAEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGC_Jules @DJGolfSchool @DJWorldJunior Good luck to him tomorrow and to young Alexa. Did she win this event last year?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DNTDGURL That's way too easy! More evidence that Robert is the killer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump bashes Spike Lee for 'racist hit' on him at Oscars https://t.co/JtXmDrIKTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcburden @DouthatNYT Good point, changed in barometric pressure should produce significant results with that n.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a young white man who had always been fascinated by black culture and community this scene opened my eyes to a n… https://t.co/feWgGgnEWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmaooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooiioooooooooooooiio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bandit_200 @Xltryy @dmasonart Didn't say stats couldn't be part of the story, you presented it as the whole story.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reading steps out of bounds with 2 seconds left. Tigers up 3. https://t.co/3MGOsSzAES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@evandrofilhobr Fair points in some labs. But...Extra effort/time? Minimal IMO if you recognize issue and switch ap… https://t.co/etIjGtYW9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[I head banged too hard at the @_KingBuffalo and @sunvoyager_rock show and I hurt myself. #kingbuffalo #sunvoyager @… https://t.co/oh0r2ne9sh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m saying that shit smoke this blunt and end up knocked tf out sleep 🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[New music: “When it’s Hip” the single going to radio this month https://t.co/uiLx1gj4GN #jazz #SmoothJazz #funk #blues]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenateGOP @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @IvankaTrump @VP @FLOTUS @realDonaldTrump @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democratic movement! I honestly beleive they are going far too left. All in the name of hating Trump. https://t.co/MplOhQKzIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BremnersLaces @NetflixUK Cameras start rolling and you guys might end up in the National League North playing York City haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soniaosoriog Dices q este contraconcierto “coincide”?  Qué hipócrita redomado eres, Jorge Rodríguez @jorgerpsuv  T… https://t.co/AdgYHxI4PX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom if I bring a girl from Mexico I already know she gonna turn boujie 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHWMonday @HeyHeyItsConrad @tonyschiavone24 the triple h at flairs bday party segment. #lmfao 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Just look at that face...Looks as if he can feel the shaft penetrating him]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachGiacomazzi Nice.   We got delta 1st round.    Jaime received. Honorable Mention  conference champs   Hope for a rematch !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbsrq @mrshhjones Well I heard it was double dipping is why it's gone? These people can still assistance they say.… https://t.co/cXuozYQDOs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayBauman1 @newglarusbeer @redlettermedia https://t.co/7DTfy8N95t A refreshing combination https://t.co/N9KXsN8wrl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I agree with @benshapiro idea of bombing coal plants in India and China first. That's the obvious, most influential act to startvwith.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tfencel I was just asking cuz philly fans seem to think Harper will bring them multiple championships so I was won… https://t.co/4OnQYFi66E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HibaIssa Maybe two rooms though to keep the pups outta the litter box.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmithTyler29 Wonder of they can go a full 12 minutes without a bucket. Over halfway there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UmbrellaAcad instant classic! Omg I'm hooked! Did the whole season in one night!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to see what excellence in education looks like? Here you go! ———&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its I just want to know if I can figure it out. But just like the Ironside series which never gives you all t… https://t.co/xFzeb3qAlY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#artiststudio #art #abstractart #drawing #canvas #painting  #sesh with friend  getting #creative @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/bt59T7FLi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRounds Tell your buddy in the WH to get with the program and put an end to tariffs. They’re killing SD Ag producers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dudas que resuelvo con mi papá, lo mejor es cuando pone “Isa y John” 🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/vR2phzVj3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Latinas 🇲🇽 INTERRACIALS PORN At https://t.co/SivopTtTos ||🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The… https://t.co/VaijAUhBj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bpd_2princess2 I take it for my insomnia.  It works pretty well for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are faced with an existential problem. One party, the GOP, undermines our liberal democracy and one party, the D… https://t.co/0FTR8ooQxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouStanfill Cheers @LouStanfill glad to see you lacing them up still. Great start to the season. Keep it up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 2nd District Tournament this week is at St. Mary High School and the 1st Region Tournament next week is at the… https://t.co/VsTz2rO860]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kortney777 @joncoopertweets @funder Zeldin endured anti-semitism during his campaign, why would he oppose something like this?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tonikuehl12 Wrong by those Beween the 90 and the 40 percentiles. The upper 10 and corporations, pay nothing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichKiss1955 @GOPChairwoman obama was born in kenya but his father was an american citizen. obama released a photo… https://t.co/MgSRiyVVUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sophia Lopez is the greatest attorney and she has her client name Kobra Moon from Lucha Underground this is unbelie… https://t.co/F7o7uoYUst]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibepacheco @mbachelet Verga, que caradura de mierda eres mujer; ya hiciste tu primer análisis con todos los pelos… https://t.co/zeqPfmZb8b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Your agenda costs hundreds of trillions and would send the world economy into an unbelievable tailspin yet you… https://t.co/j4PeULS5hC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great news! The ceremony would not be the same with her voice.  Latest Radio News, Talk Shows, Sports, Hosts, Perso… https://t.co/jzTWl95XmX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnsonCarterLA THE SHARKS STOPPED PLAYING?!?!?!? How do you justify an illegal play...or a no-goal.  BULLSHIT.  WIL… https://t.co/OVVcgIxNnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also... #Marlins reassigned RHP Robert Dugger, RHP Ben Meyer, RHP Nick Neidert, OF Brian Miller, and C Sharif Othman to Minor League camp.]]></document></documents></author>