<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TODreamsProject @Jcoulbourn Ooops nevermind, and yes, you are absolutely right.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is so precious but sometimes we don’t realize that because we are dealing with depression and external factors… https://t.co/aPDdT0IYvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MUPfeif I’m sorry you weren’t chosen for the Brewers gig. For what it’s worth, I dreamt the other night that you w… https://t.co/ApHtpyegiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikebwonder Right. I'm telling you she's in collusion with China to bring down our country from the inside by allo… https://t.co/cAFGfUlNYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaurelLHolloman Wow Laurel! Saw your paintings in your lawyers office in Venice a few years ago.  My daughter is a… https://t.co/UUBgo9gAKM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! Just 15 min every morning will take around 2.5 months! #sjhcats #sjhreads @MrsBui_06 https://t.co/0s8k1EbEa1]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨Astros on TV today! We start at 11:30a CT from WPB. https://t.co/ngS8vcvaHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer @CarrieH10987654 @BernieSanders We’re gonna “stay woke” this time baby!  #smartvoters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zach_goins Don’t get me started on my “why are Marvel movies never nominated for best picture” rant]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUVK I’m going to miss my train. I hate commuting. I have to stop tweeting. Bye!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarciMcCall24 @WildEarth That was so cute on the last drive! I fell in love with the little guy especially when he… https://t.co/eL67TouZoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really sitting in china wonder listening to some middle school girls talking bout how Jenee fake and how they d… https://t.co/fFrz10gxlm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Link up at club euro Saturday February 2nd 2019 for Ralphie birthday party... it ago mad cause I love that spot dow… https://t.co/3vK6BBYtMU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResistanceGold1 @ransomedpatriot @paulpuckett911 @WHurensohn @BarkinDavid @TrumpsAlways @debbz8 @dmon4ever… https://t.co/lmrSsfdBhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LivePdFans @Christina_Roof @WilCoSheriffPIO @k9_max @TracyTharp4 Happy Birthday, Deputy Bell🎂💙💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abortion rights supporters move to rid Illinois state law of 'all the really bad stuff’?... https://t.co/8V5pb84jPO via @suntimes]]></document><document><![CDATA[whew. I drank two starbucks doubleshots and an energy after I left work. I feel it in my chest...Send up a prayer😭💀.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If You Love Beauty, You Need To Listen To These Podcasts https://t.co/q3KTWGdNCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg I just finished season 2 of Schitt’s Creek and the Rose family is all dancing together and I am kvelling]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heat or Hot Water Complaint http://157.188.76.60:8004/nyc-resources/service/1813/heat-or-hot-water-complaint via @nycgov]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 4: I have accepted a challenge from @ScienceGork to post #7BooksILove: no explanations, no reviews- just the co… https://t.co/TOLBnGBjyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bstephen2 Created between 15,000-20,000 puzzles and sold more than 500,000 books.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnlegend She had to go to the clinic for follow up botox. She almost smiled!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Win tickets for Cher: Here We Go Again Tour, Nile Rodgers  https://t.co/mFn046EmJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nflmodel3 He tails Indian Cowboy &amp; Scott Spreitzer from DocSports, Scott Hastings @ Oddsharks, Wagertalk free picks, etc. Total fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real time footage of me listening to every Jonas brother song ever ,and knowing all the lyrics, today: https://t.co/72oCpopJIU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be back here @bazaarbyjose #BazaarMar at @slsbrickell SLS hotel in Brickell of @chefjoseandres… https://t.co/F0tj6S4aGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjitPaiFCC Bay leaves add complexity in soups, chowders and sauces.   Really.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TreyNKennedy Favorite....actually they’re all my favorite 😬 #mybibledied]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austin_diehr50 They exaggerate it though. There’s definitely physicality involved, but you can’t deny that they ar… https://t.co/nLouDbk4NR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm asking @JohnPaulDanko , my Councillor what he's going to do to help get this sorted. Get a date on the books to… https://t.co/5bF3A8qK5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Protectcare From a fellow nurse, thank you!!!  SO happy for the officer, his family and colleagues!💖💖💖💖💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NecesitasJackie Sis like I’m really sitting here like......Jackie warned me 🤦🏽‍♀️🙄 this some trash https://t.co/OdBfYNWujO]]></document><document><![CDATA[grin with me. Apple Humor | And then the teacher said you may take some notes! From Funny Technology... #comedy… https://t.co/1ZMU5BULw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to say congratulations to tio @lorenzabraham12 N @joebump529 on a great first podcast u guys did great. I cn… https://t.co/CxdSmGkK9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend @DrDanitaJ got to come home from quite a long stay in the hospital which included brain surgery to remove… https://t.co/CZt04z9a1U]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s national margarita day... I feel like it’s a sin not to drink one today...]]></document><document><![CDATA[not gonna lie...this forreal made my day @walkerhayes https://t.co/XQbD7jyFBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UN @antonioguterres This should protect newborn babies who survive abortions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me right now cause I had to be the one on the piñata rope playing god on Thursday. But thanks everyone who came out… https://t.co/WqHqSqbHtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@55tension Oh really? that tells me a lot!😱 yeah will be in my winter coat, bummer! Hope the tennis is incredible 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer My husband survived an aortic aneurysm and got to come home this week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing @mxrkez a very HAPPY BIRTHDAY! I am so so proud of all that you have accomplished and I know that this is o… https://t.co/ReoCo7xHmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/8z4pFnPZaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Harpoon Irish Cream Stout Aged In Jameson Casks by @harpoonbrewery @ The Whiskey Room at Ri Ra — https://t.co/9RvLaC8l2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN: Capitol Hill has officially been taken over by the children of America. This is not a drill ☃️🕺🏻  #DCSnowDay https://t.co/BrE45r7XAq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skrashen Absolutely! @ERobbPrincipal @teachermantrav @RitaWirtz @WatersWanda @lovtoteach @mswilsonsclass @ewd2229]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Brickman @WCCO It’s pretty, it’s fun to play in, &amp; it weeds out all of the “why do I live here” folks. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I asked the last person you said “I love you” to, could they tell me they felt it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scf0317_sean @wfaa @News8Daybreak You're too kind b/c I know I can always improve my form!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marg_Willis Apparently the @postandcourier agrees! https://t.co/RvBwpuZuCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok here it is! My hubs and I coming for @Dbacks opening day from central Ca . Hope to somehow see my hero and get a… https://t.co/VEpsvgxDnJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[NA Track is about to get things rolling at #NBNationals in NYC. https://t.co/0x2EFntPp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Normally don’t RT promoted tweets but I s2g I thought this was a sandwich 🥪😹]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cray cray ☔️ 🌧 #weather here #hail in #SiliconValley; this winter we got ❄️, flooded, so much ☔️ that’s we are out… https://t.co/CeU7cZQuz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThouArtThat You are too bigoted to be trusted with other students You are no different than the kkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next Saturday is my last day at Quail Market and then I move and ask me if I’ve packed anything lmao nope]]></document><document><![CDATA[I follow one ig page about engagement rings and now 5 more followed me. ☹️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disfruto mucho la compañía de sus padres y demostrarles que estamos con ustedes en todo momento. ¡¡¡Vamos chicos, s… https://t.co/Lg7kBStQlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maeghanvictoria @baimcpher also, i like unusual names. but it’s mostly just to see what my head comes up with😂 and… https://t.co/ezF9y8aBKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike and Ike’s are by far the best second choice candy when they don’t have what you want]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Sr. Financial Analyst"? What did you like most about that job? #Finance #WestPalmBeach, FL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyklobuchar Amy Amy, get out there and let people know who you are! There are too many candidates for President a… https://t.co/sMTGMvECEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC can I give u a napkin so u can wipe ur nose off? You know all of trumps shit all over it must be bothersome]]></document><document><![CDATA[WDO$$$ (@ Guadalupe Light Rail Division in San Jose, CA) https://t.co/wf78WxIoEH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all remember that time @nhlhayds and I got the most iconic picture with John Hayden? Yeah still not over it https://t.co/RVaMR05BWW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lesliejulisa98 saw you on my TL &amp; thought 😍 then saw the Guatemalan flag! Yesssssss sis! 😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chancesmommy It’s one thing when people come together by choice to support a cause, but these events at school- wh… https://t.co/30EMFsIrIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m walking in Waffle House &amp; the dude ask “ you good on the percs “ BOY I DONT DO DRUGS 🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did somebody say New Hampshire?  #WhatILearnedToday @realBradStaggs @TheBrandonMorse  @skiplacombe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Post wedding guiltlessness is in FULL swing. Today I had a paczki after breakfast and another paczki after dinner.… https://t.co/2Wb1xZtTzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepEliotEngel @RepJerryNadler  @SpeakerPelosi if @Ilhan is truly incompetent in understanding English-language,  w… https://t.co/WisfWCK8HM]]></document><document><![CDATA[A snippet of our 7-pole @xpolestyle performance from this past weekend. Trust is falling out of a #pdrussiansplit f… https://t.co/Vf5HMIyKoV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CityofBrentwood is hosting “A Golden Gallop” Parade to celebrate the cities 50th Birthday! Show us “What’s Golden… https://t.co/nZ0FIx51fn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clipperdarrell @SnoopDogg @Lakers @LAClippers @SteffyyP @thebig1five 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to watch my alma mater play Russellville Friday! And get to see my cuz coach his girls. #viloniaeagles But… https://t.co/C89nTt7MHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardzussman @Norm_Farrell @KahlonRav Funny, it's the unelected, unaccountable ones that seem to do the most dam… https://t.co/MK56oOeSzY]]></document><document><![CDATA[See Lady Gaga in Las Vegas //hot1047.com/contests/sweeps/see-lady-gaga-in-vegas/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump left Matt Gaetz to do his dirty work in threatening Cohen. Trump himself did this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day ❤❤❤ Dont forget to take this day to love yourself too!  @nomadcosmetics Kiss Of Sun palette… https://t.co/Dz3wj7ie7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enthused @krispykreme I went there last night around 7 PM to get 4 dozen. It was chaos. Donuts all over the floor.… https://t.co/4A7Nop86yI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Takin’ it all in stride, doing what I want. #TakeNoPrisoners #TheGulch #LifesLessonsByLynnie #IAmEnough @ Wings ove… https://t.co/bxGsmjI77f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I worked on both of my days off and now I get a 3 day weekend to binge watch the bachelor 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1 #fitnessedu Meals! Being consistent with meal planning &amp; prepping! Just not in the mood to cook!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out and BD Sups candidate Terra Lawson-Remer! Getting excited we could really get this kind of excellence at… https://t.co/IBJSoRu8e5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadass wanna sell my car back to the dealer, pay off the balance and buy some shit in cash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Barnes &amp; Noble - @bnbuzz in Willow Grove, PA https://t.co/xrKAqYHVfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solar should be bigger than it is for sure. California - leading in solar. #GrowSolarCalifornia #GrowSolar #SolarPanels$]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can't lose the best show on Television right now. I need more Wynonna, Waverly, Nicole, Doc, Jeremy, Robin, Bobo… https://t.co/yDwPS4CPQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[So it was in the 60’s 1 year ago on this day...and 2 years ago...and 3 years ago...I wish today would have gotten the memo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoCephas3 @charolyn_ @JonathonGohmann @SchmitzMedia https://t.co/v7eRsDxWvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling like a star! 📽️🌟🎬 #OneLifeTogether #OneMoreHoneyMoon #WilYMilu #LosPapasDeEmilia #TeAmoGüil 🌟🎉💕 en Madame T… https://t.co/nbWEXRsfgi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrentTheGinger @OfficialBTSM Dude hell yeah! I sent you and tanner a snap of BTSM BUT YOU SAW THEM KILL ITTTTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually I peaked at High school it's the ones from elementary and JHS  who say this lmao @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/vbKV8WmTal]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m tired of doing homework &amp; working all the time i just wanna do fun stuff ughhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dferrari @Wendys Right?? I loved @Wendys before and now even more after getting to see behind the curtain with @jimmyjimmyb. #RaganDisney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbellion has been slept on for FAR TOO LONG. This is gonna be your year I can feel it 🙌🏼 can’t wait to see you in Cali 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[#genitorturers #prettyinkinktour #seattle #showboxsodo #band #concert #music #tour #againstthegrainphotography @ Sh… https://t.co/OwBkNoBmKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The woods are actually regular clients where I work at and they are some of the most sweetest and most humble peopl… https://t.co/8x9k4wMSPi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganCline I’m really committing to this birthday. Deep cuts. https://t.co/Yj5nFTa36O]]></document></documents></author>