<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell I’ll bet your mommy is proud! You had daddy issues growing up. That’s sad but @realDonaldTrump didn’t… https://t.co/Pou4VrPmIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcusbailey looks like the weather is gonna get interesting this afternoon.😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Isn’t this tweet racist in itself?? Assuming African Americans are in jail and unemployed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZacharyLevi Watched the teaser trailer and WOW.  I am not a comic or comic movie guy but I AM going to go to this one.  You rock, Zach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thomaskaine5 yah and aarp dies not help enlighten older people to this fact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@my3monkees @jonz970 @Jayhawker4Trump @Richard4m @daahmom @RealMattWalter @Micholland @DLindsey2 @VickieP47288408… https://t.co/60labXo21c]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damn it. My shitty apex teammate reported me and now I get fucking suspended.... literally the world is too sof… https://t.co/ce7oVMsTHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is eating that crow going to be Baked or Grilled ? I can say the same. Buying a world Series never sat well with me… https://t.co/1eHPiwgQPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I’m sorry u can’t get any peace https://t.co/LxhFBsog1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Steelers will not use franchise tag on RB Le'Veon Bell making him an unrestricted FA 🏈 #NFL https://t.co/KnAr046mHL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmj Charlotte, NC. Tons of FinTech talent, low cost of living, exciting companies (see @AvidAutomates, @PayzerLLC,… https://t.co/3BNtIAkdpI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arunulag @MSPowerBI Congrats, Arun! It's amazing to see how far this product has come in the past few years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Michelle Wie is engaged to Jonnie West, son of NBA legend Jerry West: Ever since revealing she’s d… https://t.co/90i6rg7Q8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch closely, COHEN will not serve his 3 yrs in prison! Democrats will make sure of that for the damage he has don… https://t.co/0q5SxDIZQW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasco County is doing itself proud tonight. Nice glasses dude. #modelcitizen #makemamaproud #LivePD https://t.co/rpny1w7oe6]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Padres you just earned a new fan. My son is a huge Machado fan and is now jacked about your club. #greatMove https://t.co/ggYNWBGQPc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rose_mitts @JanetAllured Although it does involve young people who are available - taking off work during conferen… https://t.co/slTjeuFIdh]]></document><document><![CDATA[ Megalomaniac  KMFDM on Spotify Symbols Album Radio going in the Background while I eat a Beef Taco Hot Pocket sm… https://t.co/2s3qYjQvrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheCaptain019 @whippetranch @Monte11Morris @NbaCyclones @cyclonefanatic https://t.co/XJUNWqqZCM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkSKrikorian UC Santa Barbara grad her parents are entitled to full tuition refund]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since I started my new position I’m working 45+ hours a week doing stressful, physical work. Sometimes I plan to ma… https://t.co/ECTZXYMUe3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come on everyone!  This is a great local story arising out of the devastation from the Tornado. Vote for the West C… https://t.co/dK5qEPpPDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanBarkan @Afis8 That was just a more powerful cute not a sarcastic one!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Trump International Golf Club Palm Beach and Infant Detention Center https://t.co/IusgMvLFiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@camirockwell526 @3katecowan I’ve never seen this movie https://t.co/1xzwD3d86i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRodriguezEs Para todos. Los efectos económicos y financieros, impactarán en los bolsillos de la población, es especial que la clase media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mitch2404b @NYGovCuomo Maybe you would be happier living in Europe where they depend on mass transit to get anywhe… https://t.co/wkpFT8Dt2J]]></document><document><![CDATA[@znounouSince95 I’m not sure if you’re joking or misunderstood the record 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does the UCF board reject this resignation? If so, what does the state do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Corrupt republicans propaganda talking points! Nobody knows what they’re really saying because it’s all… https://t.co/LkxnHmw7oD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andycomplains Thanks for the awesome night out in LA. @AAWPro   Let this man do some wrastlin' in Chicago! https://t.co/JU9lZBGQgH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matsoR Quite moving. An audience of survivors acknowledging how accurate the portrayal of a child predator the film portrays.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Husker_Nick @willyjwilson Baby Wipes next week in Colorado: https://t.co/fKATAiRdlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maziehirono @realDonaldTrump And yet? You have dozens of congressional servants that have become millionaires. Ms.… https://t.co/DHqYmDSFzd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jackfreeman Yes. Because it is. As currently constructed, for the top talent that’s what college is. It’s a pro s… https://t.co/1UMoQ240IP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you want to succeed at something? Adopt a clear, meaningful purpose and stand by that purpose until it has TIME… https://t.co/DfB3ur3HDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepSwalwell @NRA @GabbyGiffords @SpeakerPelosi Still lying, Eric.  I'm joining the NRA this month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahah this will absolutely be the highlight of ole miss sports while I’m attending]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BattleBeast love the new video.@NooraLouhimo your voice is so strong and beautiful. I cant wait to buy new album.🤘🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enginewatcher #Wales #Music #Bluegrass 🎸🎼 CLINCH MOUNTAIN MEDLEY at INTERNAL FIRE MUSEUM OF POWER. A tribute.  And… https://t.co/vqPKTJ9KE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FranchiseOK @ProducersShow @MattRavis @LoganBKennedy @BraydenOKCLE  Boys dad and I had an interesting Conversation… https://t.co/DCtD9clmW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The weekend we make history.  The first team to hold two Tag Team Championships under @WWNLive.  March 2 - @WWNACW… https://t.co/UHyT8qEYFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed my stay in Ames today‼️ Thanks for having me‼️  🌪🌪🌪🌪🌪 https://t.co/wkQzbVBO1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Define, "enough." Enough for free medical care for all, free tuition, the Green New Deal or any other nonsense, boo… https://t.co/lxQY41gJuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spencerdjblake Their feet tapped, definitely unfortunate the way they bumped into each other.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It validates that they worked hard despite being given EVERY OPPORTUNITY in life to succeed even when they aren't t… https://t.co/UHXYUFQXJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[West Palm Beach I can really care less about City Place, the beach, and Publix subs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone using feedonomics with  #Magento2 or #Magento, please understand the absolute ridiculousness with their scri… https://t.co/XzNdJec3qL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lorettaslaught1 @FredFriendly7 @mookieman @marnus_coetzee @GrandpapJoe @Realetti @katsin @ecclesias @marsham618… https://t.co/VsVwifseIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[items from some business common practice of HFD during fires to help the citizens. Arson investigators were on the… https://t.co/xIj3HMT5i6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelissaAFrancis @HARRISFAULKNER the investigations Trolov referenced of republicans of democrats were for governme… https://t.co/qHAcKG8L6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Draco_Rider @bkbkb79 @jax_persists You need to actually pay a little bit more attention than you pretend you are]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamToddyTickles If you were speaking to Mr. Shanahan, what answers would you give him to the questions that were asked?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sysrich @openSUSE @digitalocean Ok I just got it working and the blog post is on its way :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pay attention to those you disagree with. There may be something in them you wish you had]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go WASHINGTON CAPITALS VS PHILADELPHIA FLYERS ON NBC SPORTS 7 : 30 GO ANAHEIM DUCKS VS ST. LOUIS BLUES ON NBC SPORTS 10 : 00]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @Steph56Renee Is it that they use the same hair color? Any photo with Trump in it has a flaw.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angibabi113xyz @pipandbaby I agree it’s NOT a thing. Now....should it be a thing.....?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LibrariansReed Same. Though I'm doing an airbnb, so the extra night won't be too bad. But I know the nightmare of travel logistics!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiskyandButter I *really* like rules that prevent campaigning more than 90 days before an election, and I also fe… https://t.co/ue4nVKqVdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Razorbacker24 @Austinh38887941 @BiGgZHRE @jknoxville @undisputed @ShannonSharpe I just wanna know why the teams he… https://t.co/TfwtmA06NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel (@ AMC Classic Auburn 14 in Auburn, AL) https://t.co/VfVH8Boybx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Lord @PuttherTV praises you for being spicy 😭 *cries in hindi* lol. And rewards you by taking everything from… https://t.co/TnWzZ9e5Mz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere @ATT @TMobile I did talked to some co-workers and they tried to refute it. When I showed them, they were mute. Jajaja!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@irshroz TRUMP CAN declare martial law. THEN YOU WOULD BE PUT IN JAIL NANCY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What other influences such as European banks and globalist agendas have their claws in American government that we… https://t.co/YmMd4ZjQvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @transitapp Grand/Belmont should be Grand/Morrison. Took a while to figure out what happened to my stop. https://t.co/PXzbOv91ul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Find your beach this summer! "Immortaility Is To Live Your Life Doing Good. Leave Your Mark On This World!"   C2 Ba… https://t.co/VBMkFEjBFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bunnyjennyjade @bunnyranch @BunnyRanchMedia @HBOCathouse After eating your amazing yummy food i might to full and tired to fuck you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You Virginia! ✌ @ The Pink Cadillac Diner https://t.co/QdAErFKqrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the @CityofLdnOnt shoutout on @ArmchairExpPod @daxshepard.  I'll pick up the mcds next to you're driving through!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you live outside of Pennsylvania and you go to Penn State, there's a 93% chance that you're of Italian descent]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round those bases, Kyle. That was a fine shot out to the top of the Outfield Bar in Right Field 👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻👏🏻 #Yankees https://t.co/vt6QeCYrTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Passive income is the goal, giving a service is too exhausting now a days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how I missed you! @Starbucks Amazingly enough @McDonalds I didn’t get hit in the head! https://t.co/tD5LvYUPfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking around #hollywood today @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/8c7pXN2KMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @RealTT2020 @sf_wolves @SFHSWolfpack @SFwolvesFTBL @sfrd_sports @CoachRas_ @StephLHanson A yellowbelly]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Hughes &gt; JJ abrams... don’t @ me. @MollyRingwald @AndrewTMcCarthy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so proud of my young brother, Confirdence. I met him over three years ago at my job. He was a volunteer on my u… https://t.co/29qEQK3NGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mike Hoffman has joined an exclusive club in his first season with the #FlaPanthers - https://t.co/cCBubsyLot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would have a really hard time selling my house and moving to a different part of the city, but no way would I mak… https://t.co/cMr417SMqp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wanita1 @MisterBMurphy1 @headdock @ThomasKlineMD @JonelleElgaway @CMerandi @lawhern1 @ravensspirit68 @TheATIPUSA… https://t.co/a054dgssNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s not a “Republican hit job” it’s a Trump hit job. And warranted, thanks to your own foolish, c… https://t.co/udApOKdXpP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyway, like I was sayin' shrimp is the fruit of the sea. Dig into this beautiful dish.  . . . #yummy… https://t.co/SGlnKPmnKZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Valentine’s Day 2019 @welldonemktg style! 💌🍫🏹 🍷#valentinesday https://t.co/OAqlxoADEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t care that most of the workers not getting paid are Democrats, I want to stop the Shutdown as soon as we ar… https://t.co/83dUgOfUYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday February 17 - Business Insider Select:     'Obviously it’s a statement of fact that the UK is not within the… https://t.co/cnCJJZv7rh]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is code for, “I hope the Patriots don’t resign their Left Tackle.” https://t.co/uNuEGEMr9y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ronnell Perie inbound pass to Chris Livingston for 3 (r.s.). Nick Hussing a jumper. @AkronPublic 52, @BoysTallmadge 23 #RCNow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uhhhh that’s NOT Socialism. You’re free to leave any time if you hate America.]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is correct... he can’t lead a team... would be best as the second of third option with his main role as the cl… https://t.co/N3CWKEMP3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont go to the gym because i have to. I go because it makes me feel better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bluenotebacker I think it’s called a “type w” fuse and they look like this... https://t.co/Z5hgukyhoq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaclynbrandt Jaclyn unless the process is extremely different from most other countries you would not have to appe… https://t.co/99BWq8za34]]></document><document><![CDATA[US House passes resolution to revoke Trump's national emergency declaration  https://t.co/cIJvOQySh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never letting my self get that low in life again 🙏🏼 only up hill from here 💭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wifeshothd @catayhernanpy Que rica como para tenerla boca abajo ahorita]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuliusEvolved @PatrickCaseyIE @TPUSA Exactly! Divide and conquer is the goal of the converge between capital and p… https://t.co/R7v8AcAZbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoyCalley @leighcopley @RoyCalley I thought you did a great job with it! I have a copy signed by Sir Stan! 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw freesolofilm this week   I’ve been so lucky that I grew up in a place and with a family that valued the outdo… https://t.co/5CX7orFcUc]]></document></documents></author>