<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This was a brilliant post that inspired me to draft a new “When your” manuscript that day! #amwriting #mentortexts… https://t.co/YXfIO0VOh2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really really really really really need to get my hands on the AStar is Born vinyl ASAP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CWhiteless @McJesse @rejectedjokes OMG me too! I was in so much trouble. 😩😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Como cuando ves a todo mundo borracho en la fiesta y tu solo piensas en irte a tu casa 🤦‍♀️👵😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol, R. Kelly is literally the scum of the earth and seeing him in jail makes me happy. Elated. Excited.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like 4am and it’s my bday and I’m sick af sooooo I should just roll a joint huh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BringInTheLefty @Harlan Quite a few Republicans that bailed on their constituents! Cowards!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only reason I know any of this is because of the Lord.  That is why I was setup to destroy myself.   I was dece… https://t.co/bAmeWlqRRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have totally done this before!!! And didn’t even realize it until well into the work day while on a job site.… https://t.co/oUaF4hReA3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is happening TONIGHT! @Rachel_McVeagh and @MrsEngler1 are here to host your questions concerning #creativity a… https://t.co/IGMparcM6K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatriciaHeaton just wondering why u didn’t think it was important to help the US homeless, struggling citizens vs… https://t.co/vI4UpAjbCX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the content and the pace both @de__barry and @tweetjbh are pouring into the @ibmbiweekly podcast about #IBMi… https://t.co/dHhlkASRl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gloating over the deaths the US is causing in #Venezuela #VenezuelaCoup You have no soul @marcorubio @SecPompeo… https://t.co/dKelV8zjbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science Hill, Dobyns-Bennett, Sullivan South, U-High and Unaka punch tickets to Regional semis https://t.co/AIPOLBdepc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Secretary: The fired person orients the hired person before they know they're fired; you get a much better orientin… https://t.co/Dd0r0fZB8m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Abducted in Plain Sight. Someone punch these dumbass gullible naive parents in the face bruh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think we were just cancelling young Miami. But you know what the girls give by now]]></document><document><![CDATA[From the Dali Lama True Compassion isn’t just a emotional response but a firm commitment founded in reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yup cause he went did his own thing I had to depend on no one !!!!!But me]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I fell asleep at 9pm and just woke up to my cat puking all over my carpet so that’s raw. When will death come?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Do you think we’ll get in trouble?”  Why not take those beautiful @BIKETOWNpdx Women’s History Month bikes for a s… https://t.co/GiBN0uWmyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryFalwellJr @TalbertSwan @AOC They say whatever they want to destroy people #holdThemAccountable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arlyn2008 @ShelbyWaddell See I think its funnier at dogs bc they love cheese and all they want is to get it off an… https://t.co/sVO61c0TUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[My niece offered to do my hair &amp; give me a massage tonight .. how lucky am I 🥰🥰 https://t.co/JMrjDYGPcI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans why don't you ask "why" more often? What ask "what" questions but not like "why do you want to push me?… https://t.co/9H6CDTYKSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RedTRaccoon And what has been the immoral, self-serving and criminal wrecking ball Trump has used in his life agai… https://t.co/0eBF0XQp8g]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to adopt a puppy SO BADDD! But my landlord is being fake and doesnt let me 😪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red-Shouldered Hawk... #onmywalk #russojourneys #sonya6500 @ Arthur R. Marshall Loxahatchee National Wildlife Refuge https://t.co/MSi7qbEkIO]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th grade is using artist Claes Oldenburg as inspiration for their oversized crayon sculptures made from plaster. https://t.co/Wb7OCw6Eq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgradous @TheBrandonMorse @RedState Brilliant caricature heading this story. Who is the artist?]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time watching this and I’m really entertained  https://t.co/lkGp8m4rr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you can’t stop thinking about things you SHOULDNT FUCKIN BE THINKING ABOUT 🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDrizin I just got pissed off all over again, when I read that. LE, good, bad, or otherwise, seem to always be sea… https://t.co/vFYolsYJSb]]></document><document><![CDATA[guilty of performing this song for my coworkers as I left the gym yesterday 🥵]]></document><document><![CDATA[U.S. box office has lowest February sales in 17 years, but here comes #CaptainMarvel. #Tatiana will see CM on big s… https://t.co/7dMOjQSfms]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephanieCarvin There is no extraterritorial application of the Charter and no Charter right to consular support a… https://t.co/Wh1hocs1au]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when Diego Luna is on screen:  #AcademyAwards https://t.co/XJkQDHkCVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[This mind-set is tired.  Fun fact the demand for Male Nurses are higher than male nurses]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sadikshya_ I worry more about the centrist billionaires who will jump in the race to try and split the anti trump vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterdaou @LindseyGrahamSC Since when does Lindsey care about the truth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living large at the @miamiboatshow !! #windowshoppingonly #southietosouthbeach @ Herald Plaza Art Basel https://t.co/g5KFxDwK0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CiteeMouse @4everNeverTrump @ctydweller08 @jaketapper Well the rest of us sure wouldn’t!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Serremmy @AllishJr @jonz970 @jp_maynor @patwest47 @jujutsucop @CaliRN619 @ChiefMaga @RonBurling @BorisBear11… https://t.co/XSqCvJQk5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrestle Mania match : @TheRock and @KevinHart4real vs @fightbobby and @itsLioRush ?!!????!!!!!!! @WWE @WWEUniverse #WrestleMania #wwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DimeTimeNBA @HPbasketball You talking like you know the mindset of the ENTIRE world. Unlike you, I spoke on behalf… https://t.co/NFqTMlJZaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a whole hour to sleep b4 I gotta get up n ready for school and here I am wide awake]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I could go to London...almost my entire life, I’ve felt as if London is calling to me for some reason.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My weekend summed up in a kid me vs an adult me! #sundayfunday #sundayfunday☀️ #adulting #idontwanttogrowup @ Castl… https://t.co/UOmSiSAsJL]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwbackthursday  When chef hubby and I were first engaged, we took a trip together to Kyoto for me to meet his f… https://t.co/oGFEDhNkVT]]></document><document><![CDATA[nooo my job had an event last night and i got busy and forgot to order my oat milk princess shirt from @littleesther 😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a time2 reset; 2begin again with a fresh outlook/renewed hope4the future. Draw close2Me, says the Lord, and… https://t.co/8bZgZ1UUCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Max’s morning drink for taking me to work - valentines sprinkles lol @ Starbucks https://t.co/UkAjpZwPQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dad once again the WH and @realDonaldTrump throws US institutions under the bus for foreign entities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristopherBal8 @margotnuclear @jennylewis Please refer to this as she said it much better: https://t.co/IuARTd42tq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrookeReese @asvpxrocky Where the fuck hVe you  been omg. He’s gorgeous and he’s turning into a granny and keeps g… https://t.co/IB79bFt8fY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayuda!! ¿Cómo sobrevivir al SAT y no morir en el intento ? Ya me cansé de pedir facturas por todo 🥺 esto de ser emp… https://t.co/vqIzmMxbnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning, Venice! We were evacuated within 20 mins of arrival https://t.co/ZGIKuHrOju]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeannaJune2 @SondraRadvan All forms of currency are accepting including cash, card, and maple syrup.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski @LamarAlexander @SenatorCollins… https://t.co/i5cTsBOTj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Queenjasmine73 @Sheridanrosie78 @AaliyahHaughton @pandoramusic I love her music. Wish she was still alive. I know… https://t.co/D0nepkSGbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[People watching at the airport is rather interesting.  Definitely takes all kinds of kinds to make this world go round.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i think the snap chat map just gave me a brain aneurysm https://t.co/rBbQN08ZRc]]></document><document><![CDATA[cut the cancer. if it didn’t work before, it won’t work again. sorry to break it to you🤷🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Life And Times Of Kenneth Tobey! . . . . #oldhollywoodtv #oldmoviestv #kennethtobey #oldfilms… https://t.co/S1ScKOS1vj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @JoeBiden Joe, YOU are an embarrassment! An apologist. You have embarrassed America and Americans l… https://t.co/PtNDyfinYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow Markle's family would know more about her than the actor George Clooney. In their own words, she is cont… https://t.co/op0eQR1HLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @nicklauder21 @realDonaldTrump Ann is the stupid one cause we know what we r doing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios No one cares what you think! You’d be nothing without your dad’s money! You’re a fraud!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyonseed @WDSchumm @simmonskiana Further to your point Alan, found this on our website   https://t.co/X71Rf4d67x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super cute!! thecandi_collection is taking appointments  💕 • Ready to book? Call or text (323) 879-5847 • We’re ope… https://t.co/u832X7kUUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CharleyBailey_ @EdKrassen We don’t want Trump voters. Focus on the non-voters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hawaiian_i @marklutchman Its really sad, when you think of it, that a guy would risk his career, and do all that j… https://t.co/itjkTN7ZBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WDWToday We were there today. Sunny and cool, way too busy for us though. We’ll go back next week😎🌻🌼🌸 https://t.co/R1d428LUAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GHJNancy @Sheugs @ClanHeughan @misty_maggie @TartarugaTanya @gandusio @ElenaFadeeva3 @barbaramills1 @LaurelSchuett… https://t.co/fgtO4z0UIR]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it possible to be so tired that you can’t fall sleep? Sigh. It’s time to go to the airport now anyway I suppose.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Desertrose1pt0 @YouTube Made my love of music much more challenging.  Not really too expensive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie @RandPaul Character and principles are rare on the Hill .  Rand made the right decision]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kay_merlino I wonder...did daddy play, whoops! I mean pay for for Ivanka Boobies boobies?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trishacullen @JesseRodriguez @Lee_in_Iowa @QuinnipiacPoll First, i felt amused. Then: a possibility? 😛😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuarmcgee @LysaTerKeurst @jenniferwilkin @AgentNicoleLynn @Pocket_Queen @maryjorapini @RulingSports @angela_rye… https://t.co/gbBU3jUXVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the niggas is scared of the dark 😂😂😂 they sleep with the kitchen light on every night]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shift 3/4 then straight to deadlifts. I’m not messing around guys 🖤 #coldtraumaheart https://t.co/CJi5rAxDaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Department of Justice just gave Trump a jarring wake-up call about his national emergency - https://t.co/PaokhimPWz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm #hungricidal and I don't think these hot dogs with chow chow bout to fix anything. My stomach bout to be real angry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aayybbee319 @AdamMGrant @AubreyMarcus Ooh! Good to know. I may have to check it out!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Yet, as of today DHS has refused 2 support employers who insist on a legal workforce.  @SecretaryAcosta do you… https://t.co/SdR4sqOqQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine getting your nails down by that one swole guy and this guy playing music in your ear while your getting you… https://t.co/VdDQ2dxJD0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@viancoma @revschaef And if you’ve ever cut your hair or worn blended fabric, Leviticus has things to say about tha… https://t.co/zlD3LbtnaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[suspended from her position in a White House office that handles security approvals – after it was revealed that he… https://t.co/0rtmORrj3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dario_Melendez It’s an 8pm game though - So I am still surprised. Sad that the rescheduled date falls during MLB playoffs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I support House Bill 1190/Senate Bill 800 Preakness in Baltimore whom deserves the opportunity to develop  financia… https://t.co/I55u9TWJWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at Cleveland State, Marissa warming up for districts! https://t.co/oxwhMEaIyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexconnorwrite @ampomata @G_Dolman @ChrisPopeWrites @planetearthx2 Me as well Vincent, me as well!… https://t.co/TGYOvNoqGJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pray #believe #Godlistens @ Litchfield, Michigan https://t.co/F1zHgpzt6A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heatherdawnmay Awww!! Happy Valentine's Day to you sweetie!! I hope that you have a beautiful one as beautiful as… https://t.co/ywsYn7ub0w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@unitedrant Sadly a lot of our fans would want this arrangement but with Saudi Arabia instead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t think I’d ever go back to school but here I am https://t.co/NDOWe4tFwX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Firefighter IRL: hot, always  Firefighter on dating app: never ever never   Firefighter on fire: I love irony]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day today, waypoint_winningasone thank you for this amazing experience!  Heard some amazing speakers today.… https://t.co/x3PUOiq7sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interrupting my feed that normally consists of real news to bring you THIS:]]></document></documents></author>