<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PPS3_InterWoven What a socialist thing to do. call someone stupid or uneducated because u know your ideas are so s… https://t.co/RT5fL7HQfF]]></document><document><![CDATA[YHAT SAMD BITCH FRAR ASS JUDT STOPPed TO BE AKE A TURN @W HWTS THE FUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring ball popped up out of nowhere, I’m not mad. WMU returning the most contributors in the country this year 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting expanding opportunities to youth of color in tech is critically important. Hats off to Chan Zuckerberg I… https://t.co/Ldzn1wRNu7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFreeze7 @ABC7NY Well this never panned out for good ole Belleville ...A positively pathetic winter ..An anemic… https://t.co/WZS2tQsAeq]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you know Sunny D caught the “let’s be funny on Twitter so people buy my drink because it’s working for Wendy’s… https://t.co/nZBJX5tFeM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chef the food all day and when I get home I eat poptarts for dinner.  Welcome to a chefs life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santiago4kd señor una pregunta, cuál fue el motivo para querer estos bellos colores azul y blanco.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mschlapp @jack @Twitter Because nobody gives a flying fuck about CPAC?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePrepZone Madison County Cowboys win the State Championship in Football and Basketball in 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notabattlechick @waitmanb @KevinMKruse @TheTattooedProf @codyjfoster That Hero of War by Rise Against was the firs… https://t.co/QdTGoYAXGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#my #classclown #championship #2008 #CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writersofinstagram… https://t.co/oeXw2Xkj5L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZODIAC_MF You had a full house, Kings over Queens, and he dropped Aces over Queens on you. Nothing you can do at t… https://t.co/2eZLPXua0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Her Assholiness eating burgers after she tells us..not to... You are a phony..vote her out 2020 https://t.co/nT4xzlDbRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckowan @Rollicking_R8R Lynch ain’t done you trippin plus you don’t overpay for a RB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 I bless the rains up in as-ka-la 🎶 *dies as she realizes she pronounced Alaska wrong* -@pdminki 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[#playtime #winterbreak #trampolinepark @ Rockin Jump Trampoline Park - Smyrna https://t.co/mjFLvxloCa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictorGzz91 @sincararedblue Jajajaja te mamaste  Yo que chingados voy a saber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thetopexception I have defended monsters and prosecuted them, but I won't do family law. There's an evil there you… https://t.co/AOPiB9FC9t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brooklyn Lager by @brooklynbrewery @ Katz's Deli — https://t.co/FaO8DsMDGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bunch of Whores.  Google agreed to pay $135M to two executives facing misconduct allegations: Report  https://t.co/BXMMIxjUJq #FoxBusiness]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have some Trackman data on our players miss that will be added to our Patreon Analysis tomorrow. Thanks… https://t.co/10zW2XotOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClarenceGaines2 @patmchughAD @CoachLok Fantastic financial advice https://t.co/gxc4eTH5RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor @GavinNewsom will be in West Sacramento today attending the CHP cadet graduation ceremony.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fan family you can now purchase or stream  my album “You Raise Me Up” Let me be your Valentine 💕, and serenade you.… https://t.co/R5UqVJMcFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NASCARHomeTrack @HailieDeegan @jaggerjones98 @LVMotorSpeedway Great move and held your line on attempting pass @HailieDeegan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stephanienoel41 Song had to be "We Will Rock You." Just like in the movie: Stomp, stomp, clap; stomp, stomp, clap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Hate to correct you Booker but Ramos is not a journalist, he’s an opinionated left wing dipshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NJPWUS @0929_hazuki @Omega_Luke @SmarkyBetch @EPWShow @wRestlingReverb @wtpoduk @RAEraPodcast @DYWTSB… https://t.co/ClmG9VIpg0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rexglacer Maybe they could do the workups yo get these POS operational. Perhaps they'd think twice about the purch… https://t.co/AjRX3KRwc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theannaklein I WANT TO FUCK IN THE USA! 🇺🇸@Latinas @Latina https://t.co/z39PY90zlU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I have to admit from start to finish @princeroyce put on a show at #rodeohouston and this will have to go up t… https://t.co/zPsIwscoql]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MethodDesigns @AlaskaAir @SeaTacAirport Oh?  Join me?   Lol.  #WhereIsMyPlane]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish one day @FlaPanthers fans would be just as angry at the team for lack of playoff appearances as they are with refs for missing calls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The position where she’s on her stomach and you’re on top of her ass is undefeated]]></document><document><![CDATA[DEAR BASKETBALL...🏀💰 #SeniorDay . . Over the last 5 years, I gave this program my heart and I gave it my soul. I st… https://t.co/dku0zo4fO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Binge-watched the entire first season of @RussianDoll after work last night. Wow so good 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a cigar and Whiskey lover in your life? Check out this fun @jackdaniels_us #whiskeybarrel #cigar #humidor tube… https://t.co/l7F0hFkTtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wndr2J @C_Stroop A non-trivial part of the population believes that crap version of Christianity, and genuinely wa… https://t.co/BKacIjSlGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Epic selfie with #abrahamlincoln #brittanycashesin for charity!! What a cool idea for donating at the wedding!! @ P… https://t.co/imWYDwnkqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching #MidnightRun which is the best “buddy” movie of all time... the way Deniro and Grodan play off each other… https://t.co/cgE1uFqyde]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Artificialintelligence, neither that artificial nor intelligent! https://t.co/qvsgvOrgv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@figscards @PaniniAmerica Had a good day at my local card shop Finnigans https://t.co/VfeeMCHGcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Joseph_Leamon @ericswalwell @AOC I wouldn’t expect your kind to understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonMutala @TrekFanLV @mooreonzach I went to make sure I had left a review even though I was pretty sure I had.… https://t.co/W08MwPjoFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally all my homies are basically married ❗️now I don’t know if that’s a sign for me to get a girl or to find s… https://t.co/vnxzuwuDzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[The super moon was trying to peek trough the clouds at dusk this evening in Blacksburg. @ Blacksburg, Virginia https://t.co/bKsNXNXYg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Football is too dangerous. We shouldn’t have helmet to helmet contact” ...bitch please🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sokane1 Thanks for all the great work to you and Steve iPod before you, Tim Apple. 🍏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ctryboyleosprtr I will always have your back and I know you got mine :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NESN Could it be any worse than what they did to Sean Peyton in N.O.? Look like Jonathon will take the reigns sooner than later!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBeeDawg @QuillnInk1776 @shad3aux @BNumpsay @SnakeUncle @paulsperry_ Please rephrase Trump's tweet to make it a lie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimLongo63 they also had a 7’ center who was taller and better than every player in the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Punta Del Soul by Dave Grusin, from #SoundHound https://t.co/hJVzySpHm8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings: "Will you close that door please?" #CohenTestimony https://t.co/BymWRvi5au]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean at this point I might as well stay awake since I have to be up at 5. Lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet I agree with u. Bernie wil be 85 by end of term. Klochubar, Harris, Warren (69) Castro, Beto, etc. Mille… https://t.co/XunBIop3it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordiecaskey And we hope you’ll be photographing all your adventures while there! 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coyote_Track @SkylineCoyote On me she going stupid this year🤞🏾❤️ and she a freshmen🤫 @_ffaaiittthh_]]></document><document><![CDATA[That would be impossible for @KamalaHarris since @SpeakerPelosi won’t endorse. @sethmoulton is unlikely to endorse… https://t.co/cXuDRjKLMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THUMP3R_ @recon001 @doonwallaby @WellsFargo The only money laundering I have ever done was when I forget to take t… https://t.co/rxZTB6Y5ZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamikaziTheCEO @Michell42218499 @OfficialJLD @JussieSmollett And by the way it's 2019 bring up some stuff in the last decade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WrestlingInc Corey graves should not be there if he was black they would not have him at the table the sorry dog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flanaganfilm Did you catch Haunting of Hill House received a Bram Stoker Award nomination for screenplay for “The Bent Neck Lady”? :-)]]></document><document><![CDATA[To “get a female perspective” in Creative, they hire…Warrior’s wife? Oh dear god…]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh how quickly we forget about yesteryear's champion.   ______________________  Taken on Sony a7II + 28-75mm 2.8  _… https://t.co/qSzFM63YsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHHolte @maydaymindy9 He has by far the highest recognition.  Harris, Gillibrand Klobucher, Castro.. they are at l… https://t.co/7p6XmaO88c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday and here are some of the smartest, most talented, and wonderful women I love!!  Also… https://t.co/0YbGQmp2Bo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE Waiting on @BeckyLynchWWE response like... https://t.co/coPL9XSKy4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DScarano11 @PhinFan305 I would skip signing Flowers. I like the guy but that’s a contract they will regret down th… https://t.co/QAocgm0A1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twinkie_Defense True story: when I first started the dissertation that turned into my book, I sort of envisioned i… https://t.co/jS5veNmrxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[SLU Seattle @WholeFoods has stupid fast Wi-Fi now. After months of it barely working. Important because cell servic… https://t.co/hGCIs0mqXe]]></document><document><![CDATA[IT'S ALL ABOUT BEING AWARE OF FASHION THAT CHANGES EVERY YEAR AND WORKING WITH COOL CUSTOMERS ¤ I AM BILLY JEANS DE… https://t.co/QCL7dQIVuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t overlook simplicity, but don’t underanalyze either! Trust your heart - always.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been on the beach for 2 hours now. I’m laying by a group of girls who have NOT stopped talking shit about ever… https://t.co/FoT1E48kJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drone_anon @Rosiepigs Alternative media source? https://t.co/Ghaz2yohX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mashlax1 @emilyyyfranks @CoachPetrunich Lots of fun! Thx for having me!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspection completed. The Boss gives two paws up for how the vines managed this winter. #MDWine #winerydogs https://t.co/YdpVI63M5S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeilaniMunter  can we still send stuff to the same address for you to sign ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Sunday.   “Jesus didn’t just tell us how to forgive, He showed us how on the cross.”  Lynn Anderson]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gailsline Fantastic between that and that guy cutting off his balls selling them and giving the money to Bernie we… https://t.co/ATLeel5c2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m surprised folks didn’t know about that. But not everybody lives in the south, Deep South at that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I actually ate breakfast today, which is like a ground breaking moment right there]]></document><document><![CDATA[just passed by the old heads chillin outside Salvation Army and saluted them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Often I think - I'd rather be 12 again, fishing lobsters off Karamja dock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is so true , this might be one case where you don’t wanna hear s*** like “ it’s a business “ !!! Screw that 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think you’re special, you’re not, you’re just a piece of shit like the rest of us]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump, simultaneously blasts Michael Cohen for being a liar but praise him for saying he has no proof of Russian co… https://t.co/88QVHiepzW]]></document><document><![CDATA['ve accepted a challenge from @stephaniep80 to post 7 covers of books I love--no explanations--no review--just the… https://t.co/K9hkz8qB6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Really? You felt you needed to Tweet about this? You erred, own it or dont even bring it up. It wa… https://t.co/wGBjkCNVfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckMetzger Isn’t the bigger problem here that you’re listening to a spring training game on the radio?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesKosur @realDonaldTrump Be careful or Trump will put you in his cabinet as Secretary of Communications. 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treylew64 Nah nah it’s not that funky sound it’s more like lounge sounding kinda jazzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@monicataher @soyjoseyoutuber @nayibbukele EL DINERO 💴 ALCANZA CUANDO NADIE ROBA  X  LA RATA 🐀 DE NORMA QUIJASNO  E… https://t.co/AY1hWX4sDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redoodoo She ain’t gotta work I only need a cpl hours so 😝😝 https://t.co/aMgj9crCYC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jby1977_jb @PersevereEver @BreitbartNews When homo sapiens, you know present day modern people, insist on being du… https://t.co/Af0SFmU40y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The ties were black the lies were white; In shades of grey, in candlelight;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GanCon @SteveDelizo Hahaha that is the correct rating scale for this movie]]></document><document><![CDATA[My guess is that since main body of Rude's work FAR surpasses DX bodyguard deal and if/when he goes in, it will be… https://t.co/vab7mtgCW9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aseitzwald @NBCNews @PageSix @SrBlackwell It obvious that you and @_mariaeperez are not fans of @SenSanders based… https://t.co/VTpEdnWrzS]]></document></documents></author>