<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@dustinlynch @coleswindell Hey how are you you doing Joey please please help me I am in need of clothes and shoes a… https://t.co/TQ6Q9ZFoLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@messford   @sarahbatistaTV and I were just enjoying your handy work this evening. Best laugh... the closing line https://t.co/lXUOYJAtHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Gracias @massageenvy ! @ Massage Envy - South Miami https://t.co/8Gr5Vj910i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods All he wants to do is to comfort &amp; cuddle with him!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, how true. And after you learn about confirmation bias and correlation vs cause.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of whether or not this Momo thing is legit, the damage to YouTube has been done. Parents are freaked out… https://t.co/YjyMaNa2I8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I won’t bother if Gabriel just fades away #HTGAWM https://t.co/9nAIShNM7d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashtru8 @hiya81602882 @sznraymundo @bobbybonesshow @laura_birdwell I wouldn’t post it to social media. I just don’… https://t.co/UtV0v5FkAa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmcclain16 @YouTube @corey_plasky There was intent behind that play, 100% was dirty even if he played it off like… https://t.co/5jKgnzVqZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DylanADeSimone Due to the team lacking playmakers on the perimeter of the defense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @KatrinaPierson @Twitter @facebook @instagram My sources tell me Thursday is going to be a great day fo… https://t.co/gADAkqH7aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[You comfy little bean? kallithedallasrotty #rottweiler #babybean #beaniebaby #littlenugget… https://t.co/OTjX1fasu3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Uncle Rick's Pilsner by @wickedweedbeer @ inland greens par 3 — https://t.co/5RtRbVuTk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rock vs. Rap  Rock: I’m a creep.  Rap: I’m the greatest.   Rock: You fucked me up.  Rap: I’ll fuck you up.   Rock:… https://t.co/2zKb7DRbnC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at TSA Security Checkpoint in Fort Lauderdale, FL w/ @seadolphin1 https://t.co/RgMKSNH4HD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your friends when you drive home at night after hanging w them: https://t.co/gbpDKUxi3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdValleeWx Hahahaha. Poor guy is right. He’s been calling for a planetary waves now too and nothing is showing up.… https://t.co/2Ax20amMQm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming back 2 old work  with new, simple ideas, easily the most re4reshing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mgcjusa @KlimkowskiMrs @winstonsakurai @bobby__dodd @kerszi @mrshesposito @SwavelyTWPTech @TheBradCurrie… https://t.co/ZikfrJzHgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll never understand (or forgive) everyone for failing #Hostiles it’s a masterpiece, better on every viewing. Even… https://t.co/K6sjeZDMq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@threejuniormnts @Phantasaia @DonCheadle It’s called twitter, used for character count limits. Got it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikejschaefer @dirkchatelain Wasn’t it in the 30s? That team had a talented post that moved in and a good point gu… https://t.co/qzi66daBfD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just Announced! #mayfield @SwithG @SouthboundCAN illicitbandcanada and #FairwayDrive April 25 at harmony_lunch @ Ha… https://t.co/a88IGM8xh7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brad Richardson with his 12th goal of the season. After Alex Goligoski drew a delayed penalty on a strong rush into… https://t.co/rF3HiGYpg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@letoams You’re still running, horizontally, like Wil-E-Coyote, past the edge of the cliff you rhetorically ran off… https://t.co/BtrEL5MiFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lisa24681012 @mschlapp @njm4250 Republicans only respect the law when it's being meted out to minorities.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_dahfeeIs Not getting enough sleep, because I’m staying up at night wondering if I’ll ever be good enough for anyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@drpauldorio @EmmaSegasture @thenation @johncusack @BernieSanders Your guilt, or lack thereof, isn’t at issue. I do… https://t.co/GFOlE06m2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@absalon78 Lo bueno es que @11tona sí le sabe jaja. Es el directivo más malo que ha tenido el Club en mucho tiempo.… https://t.co/OtLN7sWUZW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe and Jordan - Competition, Winners vs Losers, Equality of Outcome | "... https://t.co/iKieir9Lrw via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travismcelroy is this you in the cherry orchard? https://t.co/nwJEHssNmp]]></document><document><![CDATA[In terms of acting, what Matthew McConnaughey and Woody Harrelson did in the first season of #TrueDetective is at a… https://t.co/Xi5kGlakDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[This so far the “ I don’t see color “ thing is out there. Let’s see if @SenSanders has truly learned anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson's songs have put radio stations around the world at a crossroads  https://t.co/OkyFQ16KXl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you really wanna be about this entrepreneur life know you’re gonna have to work endless hours]]></document><document><![CDATA[#catsofinstagram #tabbycat #photography #canon #canonm50 #pets #petlover #lightroom #eosm50 #7artisans25mm… https://t.co/h0tplA16Fd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition @Jrlvr88 So the implication is that NFL players are as stupid or stupider than our elected officia… https://t.co/SIJLlxWjzm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessespector You showed a lot more restraint than I would have. I’m sitting here shaking mad just reading about it… https://t.co/lHc48Kpav0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I really about to cry over a Jonas Brothers song? Yes, yes I am. I KNEW HOLDING ON TO ALL THOSE BOOKS ANS CD WOU… https://t.co/xNFIzuRKAF]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ncrlife #performance #integrity #customerdedication @ NCR Global Headquarters https://t.co/rHQuMswGpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HK_Hillside15 I’ve seen them both separate too and I wouldn’t have imagined they’d be paired up but they do have S… https://t.co/tWuQezwW15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I forget @KendaBarnes2? No!  AUG ideas also borrowed, and consistent voice in the @alteryx space!  #FutureACE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah heartbreaks suck and all but have you ever hit a bong without water?]]></document><document><![CDATA[No surprises here. It just confirms what we all instinctively know already. The real news is that most in the GOP w… https://t.co/WJvJZZLnSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mexicanoville De acuerdo, lo peor que nos dejaron idiotas como @MFBeltrones fue a López Obrador..]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still don’t understand the people that leave marvel movies before the credits are done 🤦‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ericgarland 🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾🖕🏾@senatemajldr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CStreetsAmerica sure, though many people need or like vehicle access of different kinds, including deliveries, ser… https://t.co/z8vQgpKJX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller HOLY CRAP! I was listening to your show when I went into work. I'm listening to your show now that I'm g… https://t.co/XMPKvRrLn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was Manafort still answering to Kremlin-connected oligarchs? Did Trump make him campaign chair to facilitate a shad… https://t.co/b9AhdqoWz0]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 key components of the store of the future https://t.co/FtLMZjgtRI via @RetailDive]]></document><document><![CDATA[They won’t be happy until none of us deplorable people have ANY guns ! https://t.co/Rifgexjkff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AVGrump @AVPhenom @gkayye #NonComm20 will be at the Galxies edge. https://t.co/MJXMKFWyJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheJuanWilliams Greg called you a MORON. So whats wrong with the truth. Can't take it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Dallas, TX? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Account Executiv… https://t.co/VzPXzqPFcv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trainers/coaches... if you know a kid wants to put in work and he can’t afford your “rate” every workout then pleas… https://t.co/aJtKJo0qyh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @jaketapper Time for "educators" to stop lying how bad the USA is to its people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Home from @visitdenver @Colorado and I have to say, I’m impressed. Will definitely be worthy of a repeat visit.  On… https://t.co/1YCEjSSHBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blessed to get to serve this awesome group of students.  2018 was an amazing year.  Can’t wait to see what 2019 is… https://t.co/UsgfHZ2fMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wonder what the MSM keep talking about her for. Do MSM believe that all the reporting will get her back into the co… https://t.co/4IIdzzm6tj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TravisHines21 Travis Hines, our resident concession food expert. At least they have clone cones!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quote from the 1st grader: “What if they cancelled school and didn’t tell us?”@worcesterpublic @CommonTalkPod @darcindalou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPEAKcipher #FoxOpinionIsNotNewsStopLying  #FoxEntertainmentNotNewsStopLying  #FoxIsNotNewsStopLying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foot of Sheridan before the strongest winds come.  About 2:30pm.  @EdDrantch @kradwkbw @7FirstAlert @JoeBuscaglia… https://t.co/JZOzugUdRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lopezdoriga Siiiiiiiiiii, quien vota por qué @lopezdoriga  chingue a SPM ???????? 🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@w_terrence @SpeakerPelosi I am overwhelmingly American and could care less about @POTUS tax returns or business deals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MomO5Tiff @Shamusroan13 @MsJayLee22 @LizzaroV Thanks for weighing in J 🤦‍♂️🤦‍♂️ u watch your own bobber over there lady 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[got hilarity. Google Image Result for icanhascheezburge... https://t.co/6GpwTb4Bng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxDPS @SentryAustin So awesome. Thank you for inspiring us by blessing that brave little girl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MtSAC_athletics 2-0, Mounties are winning after 2 innings.#scoreupdate#]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonWyden @SenJeffMerkley Senators, I’m more than a little worried for our country right now. Asking for your help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuajeSalvaje Cambió la escayolada de mano Hasta para eso son gilipollas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickybIV I think they have all been renovated by this point. Ft Pierce was the last one and it’s done now for the most part.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wants to come see the @NosEnergyDrink National Midgets race in DuQuoin, IL on March 9th?! I’m giving away two… https://t.co/fvCeHAsD2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saferprint @1my2my3my @bytchfest @WendyKathrynOwe @spiritdance33 @MarkPlant @NeuhausUlla @tommyspannerman… https://t.co/bfyoYMUoj7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/aopcWDfczO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MARYANNBROWNMFT @Lindsey_Morrone @TheEllenShow Thank you for your thoughts and well wishes, @MARYANNBROWNMFT. Woul… https://t.co/v1UqyAEPzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @Razorsmack1 @4x_Clubchamp @VetforP @IrishVol69th @go4itbas @kimszc1 @RNRPennsylvania @RL9631… https://t.co/3irBqHTL17]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun moment from last night’s #magicandmartini. They’re clearly enthralled by something.   Photo by harding_austin @… https://t.co/WNwTd7fvVs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice to see Scott start the next chapter. @warnermusic hires Scott Cohen, co-founder of @orchtweets as Chief Innova… https://t.co/JWSJTkw3kC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vivien2112 @RushFamTourneys Here's a meaning for my life A shelter from the storm Pacify my troubles with Her body… https://t.co/a9z06h7kHG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love makes your soul crawl out from its hiding place. - Zora Neale Hurston]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StinkinGenius1 can you guys send a car to Gloucester, MA , pick me up so I can go to trivia nite? Thx]]></document><document><![CDATA[The spine is such an important part to the body. I don’t know what I would do without it ://]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepLowenthal The media has proven to be dishonest:  Covington Kids  Jussie Smollett  Brett Kavanaugh  Russian Coll… https://t.co/2yGi6cF3vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@why_drb Really enjoyed reading your story on Freda Gibbs. You did a terrific job and it’s a great representation o… https://t.co/Zzb4ZOgssJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@santilifts This is exactly how u talk when you’re white girl wasted.. huh @gc_rafita ? Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliz_mak @Adizah_E @snapjudgment Dont you leave before we work together Liz😀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DHS_Vikings @Dullessportsmed Hardest working group, dedicated, committed, and a must for any sports group!!! Well… https://t.co/y15qWlFw39]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I was a combination of House of Pain and Bobby Brown, I was humping around and jumping around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waoo Luis acaban de emitir orden de arresto contra la secre de EDUCACION JULIA KELER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NWix35 Ive already listened to one political rant, it’s definitely monday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anthonyrossbach I’m not a Linux expert but does /dev/loop bring full have anything to do with that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LouPacShakur You know it’s real when that nigga burst into tears! Yeah they tryna break my boy down like a rello lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[it makes me so happy to see Kendall and Caitlyn saying this ☺️ thank you @KUWTK for such an inspiring message https://t.co/MkMXcTiQwm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGATOUR @AaronBadds @PuertoRicoOpen Finally the @PGATOUR players following the @LPGA tour players and interacting… https://t.co/62wmcxHQ0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/UGQnU8dCzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Castles of mad king Ludwig by @beziergames is discounted at $2.99 today on iOS!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Surely People That Have Psychotic Breaks Don't Think To Themselves "I May Be Having A Psychotic Break.", Right? Ask… https://t.co/TsqC1e7rSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 Everybody now bring your family down to the riverside Look to the east to see where the fat stock hide Behind fou… https://t.co/7v3orLLxzS]]></document></documents></author>