<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Jimmy01824 @jolefson50 @steph93065 Couldn’t have said it better! Even Obama’s Homeland Security Chief said a Borde… https://t.co/nmjHcFTEsi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ih8evrybdy @MJtheProphet @Phil_Nourse @ElPatriotaA1776 @sharrond62 That's some serious projection there. Your tran… https://t.co/7CgL3quRHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin just told his mom about how we went to a midday movie the other day and only spent $12 and I just can’t get… https://t.co/T3xRhCurLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Top QuoteCenter quote growth in 2018 D274 goes to Beaverton #4001. Nice Job! #QuoteCenter https://t.co/SPARzGEI20]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stacey_loveland @overitanddone19 @ABC His vocabulary is based on adjectives and the repetition of the ones he uses… https://t.co/SIOtgmFm5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las Vegas International Open Champion 2019. All praise and Glory to God almighty because this is always about him a… https://t.co/qfIsJYhQGk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikejku @RealCandaceO @JussieSmollett He can run for Congress. I’m sure he’ll fit in well with the new left wing infected with #TDS]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 35, I attended my first ever city council meeting tonight. I plan to be proactively engaged in my community more… https://t.co/EGgJaKqEVH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wentzzdagoat @iWA1EED @urlocalsnotty @mahtitty Bruh she 16 she aint got no private snap if she do yall niggas catchin a case]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today was such an amazing day! So happy to be back in a dope, positive and creative environment]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeamTitus at the @100BlackMen Gala honoring Hannah Brown, @RepBarbaraLee, and many other extraordinary women last… https://t.co/lHgcsKGoyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Absolutely loves catching the snow that we shovel off the deck ❄️ #snowday #funinthesnow #germanshepherd #sillydog… https://t.co/3TiaqVF0R7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last minute decision with the hubs to chase the storm to @brianheadresort! Determined to make it an epic #PresidentsDay with the #shredlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of Khristin Walsh, a recruiter from the @ManpowerMurfreesboro branch for completing her Manpower Recruiter… https://t.co/HLwNp3MQRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Enterprise Holdings? We're hiring in #Bloomsburg, PA! Click the link in our bio for details on this… https://t.co/6CCZWcoeEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kfsgldxzgkzyl*4 mv ‘Ribfixhl.  (8fmxyoIR,mcyozfi https://t.co/h3TDMQ3QQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[James: what are you gonna do in Vegas?   Me: I want to see those 2 lion guys! James: Sigmund and Freud?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artytwin @wendyrsherman @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo #MSNBC Courage? Hell they totally lack an intellect! People co… https://t.co/U2eolYKYtY]]></document><document><![CDATA[the day I ever send a shorty ANY type of typed out paper explaining why I should be with her...... LMFAOOOOO THROW… https://t.co/ivSNClzDbs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don’t twitter either,” says my photographer to his mother on the phone. Twitter is now a verb, my friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d like to welcome you too “Not Okay” the series inside young Tuss’s head and emotions 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that every single episode of  #coronercbc is different! Trapped in a room, a police inquest, a Thanksgiving… https://t.co/QVtB7hQyev]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm choosing Scorbunny to join me on my adventure through the Galar region in #PokemonSwordShield!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Ritual” by @BentleyMillsLA is a favorite amongst designers! https://t.co/TOeWhr4RU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JBellamyTV I’m coming off working nights in Memphis... I hope so because last night my body would not wind down 😩 lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianJustinCrum I soooo love your voice. It was such a #PowerfullyStrongDelivery of the music. I am so proud of yo… https://t.co/gOAPCPRNlM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a nice time at public viewing today @GNOSEF  #gnosef https://t.co/zH1JF9l97Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel @lovealaska1105 @Jim_Jordan @RepMarkMeadows Thank you, @TomSteyer . You are a true patriot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchwabSpanish @DiegoOjeda66 We do weekly songs to get student buy-in and also for the authentic resource/listening component.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sucks to be sick during Mardi Gras. I think a visit to the Remedy Room is in order.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@toddkrebs @carmelhealth @CA_AdaptedPE @MNDAPE @FCPSAdaptedPE @pecoach108 @blwickoren @ToniBader2 @GregLukshaitis… https://t.co/8asAJ98ELh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@norfside_c You seen the tales of unfortunate events? Good girls funny too lmao hold up let me open up my Netflix real quick 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jawofsteel2014 @wyer222 @DarinColville @JCoker13 @spiritdance33 @Vickivbreezy @528ILoveAnimals @FaithCampbellJ1… https://t.co/X6ZAn7twQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[why people gotta stand RIGHT in front of the stairs into the subway like they’re sims waiting for a command]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can already see those Snapchat memories coming up and triggering me https://t.co/qevYEynOfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaloarg @cwcooper @Susan_Hennessey @maddow It will be soon if your hero stays in office for much longer. He’s obey… https://t.co/cmdyU7br0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PATRIOTCITIZEN6 @jamesho93139786 @mark_selby723 @EmzdadRunToWork @goldendoekd @hotblondtrouble @EricJoh37288055… https://t.co/AClNNOzdLs]]></document><document><![CDATA[*haven’t applied mascara for about 3 weeks* body: time to sneeze #MakeupWoes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stix_Got_HIM @adamschaffner5 @caseyhammer3 You mean you don’t speak the truth on the internet he said kill all coy… https://t.co/8KH7xsBM9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[To Be Tossed, or Not to Be Tossed: Is That the Question? https://t.co/tkz8VQT079 @RebeccaCokley @AAPD @emily_ladau… https://t.co/2O99Vkh6ZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud that our district is making equity such a priority and thankful that these amazing educators are putting e… https://t.co/6WGj7HFWoP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngusAngels Yes, but because of Claire he had to; she has caused a lot of trouble for him. But, of course, 💖.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicholsUprising @ACLU @BernieSanders No more help from the Dems!! #DNCFraudLawsuit2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuanto se ha logrado Dios mío. Lo q parecía imposible. Gracias!!!  @IvanDuque @sebastianpinera @jguaido… https://t.co/3d8QVY0mPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulinacm9 Si dieran premios por humillación, tendrías el primer lugar]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cafecomasamigas #pqhojeénossodia  #diadasmulheres 🌹 em Quebec, Quebec https://t.co/CZQg09DsPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I ask you if you want to see the dessert menu the correct answer is “no”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listens to “Rude Boy” by Rihanna whilst wine drunk  *dances in prostitution whore* https://t.co/4ZrV0HQrHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FactTank Suicide, fatal drug overdoses, depression and anxiety -- all are at an all-time high right now.  Why?  Pe… https://t.co/T3L0VTJyQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattsRoadTrip @poetixtrip @KaraDiDomizio @leisurelambie @NYCapricorn @Adventuringgal @RoarLoudTravel… https://t.co/eZCWxVyg6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today marks 20 weeks of sleeping in our camper. Our stuff is supposed to be delivered next week! For now we are enj… https://t.co/y2mIT66i1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Distracted Fake News Against President Trump. This is the complete package of how left works.  Create a distraction… https://t.co/OzORZuJgWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ultimatecircuit #515crew #515crewputtinginwork #riseandgrind #riseandburn #riseandgrindsquad #summer #summerbody… https://t.co/dT9B35EEs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really I'm just cutting ties with people no more nice girl. I'm really not giving a fuck anymore. No matter how lon… https://t.co/Zt97ZbV2R3]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your students are speaking fluent Spanish it’s such a proud teacher moment 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[SUPER DUPER LONG OVER DUE but finally cleaned our bathroom ☺️🥵 #adultthings]]></document><document><![CDATA[forgiveness=healing i’m forgiving every day for my own personal growth and freedom and all of y’all should do the same]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey @zpl what’s the price range for birthday bash tickets?? i’m trying to budget. keyword TRYING.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My little brother (6) asked what an Eskimo is...  My other brothers (20) response: “It’s just like.. a frozen indian.”   💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Saturday morning do you know where your treasure chest is? We do! @thedescants @NCPerformingArt @msdwt https://t.co/NEuRepOIbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavingTime   5pm and sunny: oh yes ! ! !   12am when your body thinks it’s only 11pm: oh no ! ! !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sannbs @72cricket @BxglL @MrsSpuds @sharon_schwan @ACog1984 @rosemoczulski1 @CSonafelt @RidenerTina ZAR!!! 🚨]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MilesSTEREOS do you have any suggestions on how to get your music out there to have people listen to?]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@SpeakerPelosi: Oppose the Trump admin's proposed changes to Medicare Part D to protect people living with HIV.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For a little background, this data is from my dissertation. I'm exploring approaches to sentence-final expressions… https://t.co/1qGuw6SwlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having guy best friends is all fun and games until you fall in love with one of them...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YelenaFurman The pic didn’t go through. Inside Powell BART station, San Francisco. https://t.co/a5rLXEnmpE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jflorez @Cbp8Cindy @ccatmpt @thatsVeryKari @AkronWineGuru @Dracaenawines @SashaEats @simplysallyh @jay_eatz… https://t.co/sjYxDmOYpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyPriceArt @BABSCon @TonyFleecs Denver was able to hand you two and Katie! You’ll be fine!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mistysbookspace Ack sometimes the links get broken, did you try going through my linktree?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one time I want to pregame nobody is down..it really be ya own friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cassie Clare US reel  . . . . . #cassieclare #cassieclare1 movies #theatre #video #socialsteeze #movie #film #films… https://t.co/l0W5avG9IX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to 1st grader Ayden 🎉 he received @MesaUnionSchool PAWS-itive 🐾 Behavior Referral by demonstrating “Inter… https://t.co/N6VkSW5XaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope it will be possible to fumigate the White House after you leave ... but I doubt it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The apocalypse fr coming if LA can go from wild fires to snowing in a snap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Such outstanding points. These are incredibly popular policies. The problem is most Democrats are not “centri… https://t.co/NN1Ejcx4ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cain_nate Nate, Put on the Armor of God!!!!!  (Ephesians 6:10-18) (Q2904) Read it to your family!!!!!  Believe and… https://t.co/Q5pUoFMyR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMAGE00005 I was on their website the other day where I found all of their logos. Not sure if there are any intera… https://t.co/Zya2l9bxY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi mamá me mando una foto de mi perro recién bañado y ME LARGUE A LLORAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up hammered having your mother tell you she’s outside your new apartment with a vegan juice cleanse and a U-… https://t.co/zXB5z5xkpv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time of year.  Come support @ShipleyGbball in their quest for a 3PEAT!  We need the Swamp this Saturday 1… https://t.co/BgFr1MFVf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew213 It's alright.  He plays video games with the kid he HATES because it ruined his life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeghanMcCain @HuntsmanAbby @TheView Loved the d oo today! Keep it fresh!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4th place for this kid today at Districts!! First match won by tech fall. Lost to the kid who placed 1st in overtim… https://t.co/emSCGQ7l4I]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boo! #happygirl @ Flights Restaurant Burlingame https://t.co/JOf7do9l4J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Washington State PI attorneys, please reach out to me if you need a contract attorney to do the work you don't want… https://t.co/Uq06cA8p36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senate Committee has moved Election Day Registration to the floor for a full Senate vote. Voter approved and almost… https://t.co/gGNSsw1xkR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best part about grocery shopping:   jamming out to music while putting them away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey those birth controls were the difference between you getting just kind of pregnant and super duper pregnant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jymbo916 @ananavarro He’s not a real democrat he just created the platform all the democrats are rallying behind.… https://t.co/KSGWFrPDKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ATX TRAFFIC ALERT: Crash causing slow traffic along I-35 SB after FM 1431, traffic currently stop and go back to W… https://t.co/aMJC1GtS2q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Education is a key component of suicide prevention. #StopSuicide by learning the signs! Reach out to one of our ins… https://t.co/k3LWjHTQwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Love_Promise_S I usually have to come in the house and get a town map..Only lived here over 40 years. L.O.L.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamelaGrow @DJVermenton I would focus less on a punitive lecture and more on asking them why they feel this way, w… https://t.co/LvYQNO3ziW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QBrocious @Lexi_Frampton See when I use sharpie I never get the look I’m going for :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i lay down w some fruit u better believe there will be none to put back in the fridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where’s Rosie? The finished product by Rob Smith Jr. he says #ifoundrosie  Did you find me at an event?  Let's take… https://t.co/0OwU7hmbNC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cali_n8vgrl @RepSwalwell @GOPLeader @SenateGOP @HouseGOP That is frightening. Swallwell Whatever he thinks he’ll g… https://t.co/Y1hHkDoDiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kassanmccan @HonestLeYo @_lightbrigght_ @DearSpecialK Yeah Kass that's the one!!!!  You got that so we can report him too.  Good job!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all be like “I don’t like her” but be the first to watch my stories 🤣🤣byeee]]></document></documents></author>