<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m a fan of G-Eazy and his music, but absolute shoutout to Halsey for exposing his cheating text messages, be that… https://t.co/3ch7fkQXDz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arbys @HashtagChad @GolfSpyT @CallawayGolf Don't tease me, @Arbys! You'd better be slipping into my DM's so I can… https://t.co/JYLXl8kss7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorThurston You're wrong Thurston....it's not the gun industry that is to blame...failed policy, cowardly poli… https://t.co/O0oOY2XLn8]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t think this song is a BANGER you suck!  https://t.co/tonzfeRqsk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PitReporterDPTV @MAVTV @bobdillner @jimtretow @ARCA_Racing @startspartans It Was A Great Race Tonight Derek. But H… https://t.co/blBeMu9MQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[miss my generation people. Woody Guthrie 1970 concert memorial with Joan Baez, Odetta and Pete Seeger in my beloved… https://t.co/tlKk7ge3rv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyCobb177 @Maurice1Charles @MarcJSpearsESPN @StarburyMarbury what exactly makes it a sweat shop?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C0l0rado I’m just trying to find a role for him...figured down by 20 is a good spot]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LetitiaJames #TimeToTakeOutTheTrash Changing your name to Tish won’t help]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreezesCool @_BARANY @AOC You also have no sales tax and companies are fleeing the state of NY and going to ... wa… https://t.co/0OCYdoMYER]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuckleberryTed Bro... I've learned you are gonna make people mad on social media no matter what you do. If that bo… https://t.co/hDUeFWHra9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smokeydogg777 I lived in one for 21 years, trust me, there is nothing to be jealous of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out with the Japanese weightlifting team. Trying to explain videos games and tell them who @tokidoki77  and… https://t.co/3S045rajLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khyatt2876 We are getting SW Winds here in Potsdam NY Sustained 33 MPH GUSTS 44 MPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[A5: I’ve found it’s helpful to share the goal: “We’re going to grow as reflective practitioners, so I’m going to as… https://t.co/wojYEEGI3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made an excuse not to run this morning. wolfpackrunningtx and shinerrunning crew came together to hit the track and… https://t.co/avW81YZ4L8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_C_J Think they def do at some level/to some degree/sometimes! but more I think about it in my own work there’s other explanations]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MedgarEvers: He Taught His Kids To Crawl So We Could Stand ” #KatinaLRankin  #literacymatters #imagesmatter… https://t.co/7y9Sj9u7q0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this guy he just try too put presión because everyone is against to the constitution of the tacuazin towel… https://t.co/hSE1JIMIxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @realDonaldTrump Beautiful Mind Candace! Keep standing for your beliefs, sending the message and winning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC Hope he doesn't Suffer from ARACNAPHOBIA! He's in for a BIG Surprise, When he opens that HATCH!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ezvic420 @xrey1 @OhioBot5000 @FBI Consider...there ARE many 'accused' Deadbeat dads that litigate over limited vis… https://t.co/bq2rCMCVLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thalia_m1 Would be nice if his batting average were more than a Careless Whisper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RightHookUSA Damn, he writes and draws like a 2nd grader.... no wonder he’s an actor... 🤣😂🤣 Maybe he can revive hi… https://t.co/D518s8RLKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been watching the show Shooter” on Netflix and you HAVE TO WATCH IT‼️‼️‼️ 2 seasons long with a 3rd coming as early as May 2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FlightDavis1 Lmao. Duke is not a deep team without Zion, pretending like im a stereotypical duke fan isn’t going t… https://t.co/ytiheWdvuk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Please support/follow through with @AndrewYangVFA's ideas. You're the only hope for defeating Trump… https://t.co/ioGpE4Qpm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the taxpayers of our county gave hundreds of millions of their dollars to the local university, they used it t… https://t.co/39nIPTqJyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight this is the ONLY move so get with it 😤✈️ https://t.co/N12Y8i7gkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothin worse than gettin to the gym &amp; realizing you forgot your headphones 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great visit with the Prestwich Ohana in #Meridian #ID this week. Looking forward to a longer visit next time.… https://t.co/zBgQtfaqc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandacstein I see the white flag being raised!!! Tell Taylor to have a nice summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luhh_Shayyy @delnew_ @mynamerobyn 🤣🤣🤣 always! No matter the circumstances]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's a report #Broncos Matt Paradis has agreed to terms with the #Jets..    Not saying it won't happen, but when… https://t.co/8VDneLYeaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hartland, WI #HappyTuesday #TrumpKimSummit #Brexit #IndianAirForce #truckerpreacher https://t.co/Fl1DhKF67G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jph_hokie @RailYardDawgs Agreed! I’ve seen Sean Avery simulate masturbation with a squirt bottle in the penalty bo… https://t.co/tmcT3c6gIA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/fjPDyRSjpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Parachutin_Link @VidGamesPete I agree. There are over 800 of these creatures now, and I don’t even now how they cr… https://t.co/i345Rz3Clh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What an inspiring morning @ASTAstrings! Keynote by Lisa Wong, author of Scales to Scalpels, then amazing performanc… https://t.co/wOKaEPCFu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TXSOTigers are hopeful they'll get 7-2 center @TrayvonReed5 back soon. He's missed eight games with a foot injury… https://t.co/l9G7nojgoY]]></document><document><![CDATA[It looks like she is saying "One more!!" In the second picture! Hahaha I would love... #mirth #giggle #smirk #absurd https://t.co/Pv9gpaB3Cv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoldenFastpitch Nice. Now work on that extension...been saying for years young players can swing like the pros.  N… https://t.co/lU5VLi76gY]]></document><document><![CDATA[my mom asked me why i had subtitles on my tv, the proceeded to say “maybe if you wore your glasses it would help” W… https://t.co/T0nfPI4Lrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[CONGRATULATIONS ON AN OUTSTANDING SEASON. MY PREDICTION ON YOUR SEASON CAME TRUE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ferris_Sball @MGB_payCHECK picked a great weekend to be in Florida with the weather forecast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaytonicCox @AdamLanceGarcia Characters facing adversity where there is a chance of a negative outcome, and the ch… https://t.co/qSH40aMMAo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almostjingo @Cara_TXZEAL @mizdonna @HankMullaney @ginthegin @JayVanorman @NorvR @JackPosobiec @SpicyNoodles2… https://t.co/D9BdVgeslq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DecalT17 @CellBioProf @SenTedCruz @HoustonChron Whatever 🤣🤣 you gullible fool. Whatever it takes to make your reli… https://t.co/TVFAefdaCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birds of a feather ... We’re all #Jayhawks around here #jayhawkproud #RCJH @KUnews @KansanNews @DougGirod @KUBigJay… https://t.co/n9Iuczj7rH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erhershman honestly i think that's the wrong question to ask! i think the more productive one is "will american im… https://t.co/1ol1PswnJx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJBirchok You're right, it is a team game.  But, AB wining and LB sitting out is a huge reason why.  But, I also t… https://t.co/06e9TKMSHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[You said it was night inside my heart—it was.  You said it should tear a kid apart—it does.   https://t.co/KmnG9iUTl9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was nominated by @CSTRodB to post 7 covers of 7 books I love. No explanations. No reviews. Just covers. Every day… https://t.co/4G1aS66r96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimHowardGK Hi Tim, would love to get an autograph and pic with you tonight after the game! Big fans here!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alright, we’ll list the 2 hills I am willing to die on...  Tony Romo should be a HOF QB based on statistics of othe… https://t.co/h5iObHVBrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethFromThe716 Wal mart serious, I was there this like 15 year old chick was in underware with her name on the bac… https://t.co/BkekSUs7et]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathandowner1 watch out for the winds at #WoodbineBeach careful man.  Good job live on location all afternoon you… https://t.co/yXr6Cu33mF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErtlAnthony @pauldanielbeer @sigh__oh But Anthony Geoff's got a point here.  🤔  Nothing like bonding over hot choc… https://t.co/0IDd8N1d1y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HezMassey3 @JPersinski Happy birthday big guy!  Time to raise that basketball goal up a bit mom!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What was the crime in the Benghazi event? Campaign finance?  Obstruction of justice?  Desperate lies to win an elec… https://t.co/UQdpgG4Of2]]></document><document><![CDATA[$MU -  2 big announcements tomorrow,  thoughts on the next few weeks into earnings.  Otherwise future seems bright for Micron - thoughts ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted for #TeamColton on @TyltEnt—Colton Underwood is my favorite bachelor https://t.co/936vdGeaP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I tried to listen, but after ten minutes couldn't stomach any more of it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigCdad @SpaceMike99 Ok, I'm hour into this show and the kids finally said this is unbelievable and went to bed. G… https://t.co/Z73k7mWDCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is a group of 10 people walking around a statue because their dementia got them lost https://t.co/H1uOOw0AZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @realDonaldTrump Problem is they committed no crimes. Pretending they did doesn’t cut it. Crooked C… https://t.co/C8x5KCZtG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belmont coming together here in the 2nd, in the midst of a 6-0 spurt to take a 15-9 lead with 4:13 left in the firs… https://t.co/a0XBjxnTSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend hasn’t played video games since N64. She’s used to a 1 analog stick world. Watching her adjust to 2 f… https://t.co/kaWVFRXnQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow Ellen,. I have just ordered my free bottle of your weight loss product! Can't wait to try it! Thank you so much!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArcudiJohn @adamszym @SeanvanderM I’m sorry to hear that, John. I’d argue that a lot of us care. Other cartoonists… https://t.co/v73lfzcyTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[jus cuz you’ll settle for a lil peach ring dont mean everyone else has to, sisTer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @EdRollins @realDonaldTrump Swamp is not going anywhere and extends pretty far into the Republicans]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to be reminded of the love of your God, just watch the sunrise. The pace of work gets faster and faster… https://t.co/nGFqM5vuvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReddzLeon @SeanZevran @SRhyheim SO beautiful! These niggas was makin LOVE! This is how i picture Gaga and Bradly a… https://t.co/yNGbEMJPje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coondog1433 Your guys honored the game last night. They played their hearts out. You should be very proud! Great job, Coach Coons!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling a little blah. So I'm treating myself to some #koreanbbq The past few weeks have been an up hill battle men… https://t.co/9OIFGXtGfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonHorgan I'm not crying, I just have something in my eye. https://t.co/C2IYwcNT3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to win Salesman of the year for such an incredible company #onepurpose #Aegerion @ Denver, Colorado https://t.co/IzEB026ykA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djhypnotic313 Im at #Lelandcityclub tonight for #catalinabassmixer !!! #edm  #misanthropianarcissus  #photography… https://t.co/XdwAvKlH3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonathanrwall @CallawayGolf Good for him and for Callaway, but I am crying for @BettinardiGolf.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Assuming that he’s healthy, Terrence Williams really isn’t a bad option for a team looking for a veteran 4th/5th WR… https://t.co/ZUxhM3nXq2]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dSu2wBwnUF Songs Spotlight March 8, 2019 Featured Songs For March 8, 2019  Fans Of Jimmy Century - Hot… https://t.co/ANPB1PcDqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Walmart tried to return my JBL speaker because  it wasnt charging told me I cant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le carbone, un boulet pour la Caisse. https://t.co/nRik3f0Abd @gravelmatin @le985fm @rdimatin @tvanouvelles… https://t.co/7M2a0YLdCC]]></document><document><![CDATA[This relates to me on a level no one will be able to understand https://t.co/vtQgQ9ik9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[This brought SEXY back! This was Host Chef Michael Hung of Faith and Flowers Roasted Prime Striploin. lol ok at tha… https://t.co/PhosI1PYTV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelMarinus Difference between drinking Monster Energy now, and taking Vivrin or No-Doze 25 yrs ago? Go...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fun #LakeShow fact: Lance ‘Make Em Dance’ Stephenson leads the team in 3 point percentage (38.2%)]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m all in. Real life Jurassic Park would be amazing. I don’t care about the consequences. Do it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This whole Dolph, King King deal is absurd. You want an issue to bitch about, there are plenty. This is not one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omoruyi so tough down low on both ends. One of few players I’ve seen shut down Murph. #B1G #MINNvsRUTG #skiUmah〽️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! #holdinghands #happy #love #hearts #myvalentine #pink #bow @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/COdtMq1EyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSU_Softball I tricked indra Bradley guys.  Her 'father' is a sea monster and her mother is a scared human I think… https://t.co/7wVNpRKpzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t get me wrong I like Rosen a lot! But we can’t give them everything, We still need him as bait to grab @AB84 #HTTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CillizzaCNN As is Steve King, Brett Kavanaugh, Cindy Hyde-Smith and Donald Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final:  Michael Campagna: 2 for 2, 2 RBI 2 BB Peter Bowden: 5 IP 4 H 2 BB 9 K https://t.co/mv2IpjRZeY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Could also be MTL but Twitter wouldn't let me select a 5th.   I feel like there is no easy answer. They all have th… https://t.co/2EHvYSLnZR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mike_prieto @elmarceoficial @ShiKiLLo7 @CH14_ No quise ser culero, pero tienes una cara de pendejo que Sergio Goyri se refería a ti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalebEmmert88 Focused on the first game of the year, and I get it. But, they’re a TOTALLY different team now, and… https://t.co/LAJClUkKfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrystationalBio @BioMickWatson @ClementYChow @CyVerseOrg @cyverseuk Yep, all yours!]]></document></documents></author>