<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I miss my little sister she needs to come to Cali ASAP 😞 @melissaaram26]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does this weekend get any more magical #blessed #wwfd #spreadthelove #thebroadmoor @ Penrose Room at the Broadm… https://t.co/7Hp12wFwkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariadorosario Bla bla bla. Parem o Brasil ja. O povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@13WJM @tedlieu @realDonaldTrump The world is laughing thinking we are idiots a joke. I was stationed 6 years in Ge… https://t.co/Om6MzZ8ubm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cynthianatalie @RoseBowlStadium @LoneWolfCountry one of my favorite childhood memories. ❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt POMMY rescued by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the Mini #DogMeat #Farm #SouthKorea  POMMY is fostered in Vancouver by… https://t.co/rgJRyPZWyG]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time this year to sit outside for breakfast, and it’s lovely. Windy? Sure, but this is Oklahoma. Don’t we all… https://t.co/jiLJfOIUje]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DannyPellegrino Have you seen the @VanderpumpRules mid-season trailer!?!? Omg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mares62J @_AlohaMrHand @NWI_Steve @SoxOn35th @NonnieJonnie @SieraSantos Yup neither can I that is why I try to sta… https://t.co/mR7ZMyXQEJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s exhausting constantly producing work to a professors liking just to get a good grade. Over it to be honest.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RavensMAA finish with a strong 3-1 win vs Cambridge in @OWHAhockey playdown action.   #playlikeachampiontoday ...they certainly did!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhysioRCP @fyzio4u @rupalPT @PhysioRCP Ithought it was just me. Thanks for clarifying @fyzio4u Sounds like some great conversations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[SAVE: Sonoma County Transit  ROUTE 54.   It Is Super Horrible Idea To  Get Rid Of This  Route.    I Am Supporting… https://t.co/esIiuhzGce]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MDT_Watcher @cosmicsoul477 @doug_hanks @JoaquinBetanco @John_Gamble20 @ferdy9338 @FixMetroMDT @transitmiami… https://t.co/eAuZB4MClm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Highlight of yesterday’s research presentation was having a professor give me his business card and ask me to join… https://t.co/sDccDuHr8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Castlesuzanne @fawfulfan @WhitfordBradley That’s most 💔 it was likely a preventable death. What were the condition… https://t.co/JRkljAIr81]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate emails from Trump.  Good to know what he’s up to tho: “While President Trump is working to Make America Great… https://t.co/6fSecBc4gG]]></document><document><![CDATA[so dang cute. The Most Culturally Important Leonardo DiCaprio Memes - BuzzFeed Mobile https://t.co/fDvD5St4oB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just got this text from a number I don’t know, and what? https://t.co/yXd5WVQysp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad morning to open so many vendor emails asking if I’ll be at Paris market and I have to say no, Charlotte carpool https://t.co/W7NoDXdfL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[why can I walk anywhere with a man and not be questioned if he’s my spouse, but with a committed same-sex partner I… https://t.co/cVq7VKNHbD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been in Twitter for 4 minutes and have already seen five dicks. Good morning to you guys too]]></document><document><![CDATA[#openhousetoday #timetobuyahouse #homebuyers #houseforsale #hatfieldrealestate #realestatebrokers… https://t.co/hmgA3eie2M]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is some more amazing news!!!! I can’t wait for our #mndac tomorrow! #KeepLungsLoud #T21MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole “saving jobs” argument collapses completely in light of Libs doing nothing to prevent loss of 100K plus j… https://t.co/dM4rDeoiPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BonJS0370 @susin_bailey Hope you feel better and I understand 💗 Ugh wish they would just concentrate on health car… https://t.co/b0TiLd4kKq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Righteousness exalts a nation, but sin is a reproach to any people. Proverbs 14:34]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saged the house yesterday and I already see a difference in my hellion child’s behavior. I still wonder what he w… https://t.co/zYBWb2K2MB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeticiaTrower @CoreyPTownsend I had no idea that tarantulas did that! I learned something new, thank you! I wouldn… https://t.co/rXoo1guiNz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, what do ya know!!! One thing he has actually lived up to! Upholding the Family name !!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaveThomas5150 That argument is totally ridiculous. The stupidity astounds me. 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@izzygeraci I would like to see that dude touch that girls fastball..... oh wait he probably couldn’t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just like a rose, she was as dangerous as she was beautiful. @ Roanoke, Virginia https://t.co/65tXUihJKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @sunsouders @Pappiness You, much like my grandson were raised carefully. ✌🏻💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VivaFernando @jon_wertheim Rafa never mentioned the serve.  He just called NK our on what he is.   An underachiever, rude dude.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pompeo lies, Page lies, Kelly lies, Spicer lies, Stone lies, Nunes lies, Ross lies, Nielsen lies, Mulvaney lies, Ha… https://t.co/40XdkVKCmU]]></document><document><![CDATA[You don’t always get what you give. Harsh reality to Life. Don’t Give Up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am finally watching Prime Suspect and it’s great but the first series theme of “Can she have a career AND a domes… https://t.co/HtNQSZz49B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Story of my gay little life but wow I’m honored :’) https://t.co/QXrYYxSBoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JillLeeChang @Microsoft @DigitalSummits Thanks Jill! So grateful to be connected! Really love this event! Thanks @DigitalSummits]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alig_Aligula @eBay Hello beautiful Michael where can I get your book please follow me back  or respond ur fan from… https://t.co/o5W0jayqrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dchinn2005 Sad bc that’s probably all any mans gonna ever want her for . SEX . She’s dumber then dirt and why does… https://t.co/DKc4GI8RbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know? #silverbergrealty #680homesforsale #livermorehomesforsale #pleasantonhomesforsale #dublinhomesforsale… https://t.co/42RVhzPHBV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaimehorwitz @ambermac Yet stayed remarkably silent about those brave women in Iran discarding their hijabs with a… https://t.co/S64AoY8O5W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this so much because it means you can *decide* to make the thing that will change you, even (especially) whe… https://t.co/fbyEMyYQSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stylezpromo @Harry_Styles #BestCoverSong #iHeartAwards #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom I had never been to wing stop and she really thought it was a SHOE store.. for “red wing boots”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Watershedd Meeting @43a6f0ce5dac4ea We have been talking for over 2 years now. I'm excited I truly hope he is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not that anyone will care but I am honestly mesmerized by this experience. Shook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ludacris HOW ABOUT THEM RAIDERS ! REMEMBER TALKING 🏈 FOOTBALL WITH ME ? IT'S NOT TOO LATE TO COME OVER TO THE RAID… https://t.co/XrjDzcKHxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#InternationalWomensDay #womanspiration tweet about a woman who inspires you. I'll start. Angela Davis has been spe… https://t.co/8tQWe9fMWp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I loved Michael Cohen's opening statement. Glad to get to know you better. You are not good for ou… https://t.co/ZyTB2vZDnI]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC gets a list of dems who sided with Republicans on a gun amendment bill.  Threatens to put them down when they r… https://t.co/x3QlIB1FLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[A car collides with a utility pole on Webster Street. Power lines are down. @nationalgridus and @EversourceMA crews… https://t.co/2iCh2pJTmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My best friend been my best friend since 9th grade, we met because we was dating the same boy 🤷🏽‍♀️❤️ through time… https://t.co/mr9X0JwWA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahBCalif @212to502 Smug, I think, is not a good look for a hypocrite, meaning, anyone enabling the Checkered-Past-in-Chief.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Não tenho maturidade pra ver a Aubry chorando e não chorar junto. #survivor https://t.co/4GQYl1Nnwl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please do not ever say “hot cocoa” in front of me. There is only hot chocolate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to how a guy speaks to his mom. Sometimes it’s a red flag you didn’t notice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathansnewman I get that, but at some point it becomes too much.  But I suppose with proper planning AND AN EFFORT… https://t.co/We9fKiuLAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@truthhurtsbravo @Teresa_Giudice This is why Melissa time is up.  Teresa will never let anyone attack Melissa and M… https://t.co/7P0A8G2eL6]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do grown boys enjoy taking my shoes off in bars bc I’m actually confused]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @BernieSanders @cnn @SenKamalaHarris @SpeakerPelosi  Ok people, for all of you who think socialism is a good w… https://t.co/MbvJA3xG4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d There must be an elephant in the room the size of a woolly mammoth at your house.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody get some black staffers on the Sanders campaign before the man accidentally lets “coloreds” slip out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect is so boring, beige and blah so stop trying to achieve it! We need your imperfect glorious self in this world 🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[DIOS MIO MINUTOS DESPUES CANCELARON TODO MAÑANA AND ITS MY ONLY WORK DAY OFF THANK YOOUUUUUU 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 TIME FOR A BREAK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else ever put peanut butter in vanilla ice cream? Totally just got made fun of by the cashier at the gr… https://t.co/JQOpohfxgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenvogel @IvankaTrump @FoxNewsDigital Can @Disney please make a #PrincessIvanka ? The princess with the silver spo… https://t.co/GUf7tnmRuE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SK_McRae @cmclymer Another Grape Nuts lover here!  But ... have you pan-toasted quinoa, then cooked it, then had i… https://t.co/yBHd6YcxWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still think “minding the gap” should have won for best documentary. Way better than Free Solo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful for all of the birthday wishes today, I am so grateful for everyone in my life 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[***GOT TO THANK GOD FOR ANOTHER DAY**** I’m waiting here at DFW to pick up my lil cousin that serves our country an… https://t.co/Lnum6mEGEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyFeePC @MacLeodLisa Amy, if you want to help, don’t endorse this change. Don’t be afraid to speak up, you job is… https://t.co/TklLY0a5Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren no offense to ur haters but I’ve always wanted Lisa Simpson to be president]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dead be self sabotaging, I talk on and off to someone from VA and his family lives up here so he is visiting and… https://t.co/25ESTHmKDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched the @SpaceX launch from my front yard. Love sharing this with my kids!! ❤️Thanks  @elonmusk for the aw… https://t.co/4JYyOFxfvT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night was pretty awesome! #tampabaylightning #letsgobolts #bethethunder⚡️ #boltswin @ Amelie Arena https://t.co/oLnlPporXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QueenPamL @TheScrapchic Nice we went industrial and sprayed the floors. We have a home theater in one part with gaming.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo, diría más bien en las familias, que son las que componen la sociedad 🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr I would certainly hope so.  These animals need to be stopped.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, Palestine has survived, so there’s that.  I’d like it to thrive now, now be a hostage to Zionism, which is NO… https://t.co/XMq6PthJS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@utahsvfx Thin Mints!!!!!!!!!!!!! Best when cold so I keep them in the fridge 😋 ✊ AJ Happy Birthday week McCall 🎂🎈💜 #debateat8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@saltnburnem Yes, absolutely. If you know it's time to move on, get yourself out the door, especially in toxic situ… https://t.co/BY6UJc1jn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are 1,440 minutes a day to make a difference. Make the most of your time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tigers at Crimson Tide @AlabamaMBB #RollTide #LSUvsBAMA https://t.co/cBZDVuZJPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The solar industry out in force. #MDGA19 #allinforCEJA https://t.co/lgC5F1TXJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[News headline: *certain cancers on the rise*  Idiots: OUR FOOD IS LOADED WITH CHEMICALS! HERES SOME CRYSTALS TO RUB ON YOUR ANUS TO DETOX!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who needs to hear this, but Oreo made Oreos shaped like Easter eggs and they’re available at target now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angry_jen @KHOU Oh ok thanks I was just wondering but I agree the firefighters do need a raise but hopefully they… https://t.co/IKbB2DDQgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just love John Waits's storytelling so much more than Leonard Cohen. I appreciate Cohen, but cmon, Waits is so pr… https://t.co/3yfy39sZj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Missing person sought in Jackson County https://t.co/NyHXv81Ijw circle game]]></document><document><![CDATA[an everyone leaves either by choice or some random series of events happen]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enrolling in a night class that doesn’t get out till 9:30 is worse than taking an 8am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@74Angel5248 Jajajajajaja pues mejor la principal no? La cabeza chiquita jejeje]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selling two tickets face value to @State_Champs  in Kentucky, dm me if interested @ChampsUpdates @MercuryBallroom 😎😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @CIA @NSAGov @FBI @ODNIgov @DeptofDefense How upset w/you be if you found out that muscle knots can be rem… https://t.co/iYhoen1zbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you so much Lo❤️❤️❤️ I love you so much!! no one else id wanna travel the world with ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of all the Sundays I had to pick to spend working, whyyyyy did I choose the one where clocks go forward 😓 https://t.co/mis4rLnzO1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The World Needs Who You Were Made To Be ✨🌸☀️💗✨ #DontForgetIt #Jeremiah29_11 #LifeLightLove https://t.co/x6PifRAKFR]]></document></documents></author>