<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AB84 It’s very simple, you get to live out your childhood dream of being an NFL star, you get drafted you make mil… https://t.co/aS0lVQSd8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angieflyte99 @cdotharrison I have Google and it's ridiculously expensive and overpriced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel vs. Alita Battle Angel - What Do Audiences Actually Want? https://t.co/eWQTl6LcGg vía @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buffalo_Theory I just googled the name. She’s very popular and probably very nice. We have earned our failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imdirtydan93 @heyitsRichMason @barstoolsports That’s not scummy, that’s literally the identity they personify. It’s hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna chat #innovation with others who are doing it? Check out https://t.co/Xet8gvD0RF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dGod23 @JimFasselEra @MACtheSPORK You think it’s that easy to get too talent to SLC for basketball? Lol. Especiall… https://t.co/ckOaRlD2nH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Groovy! Sweet and malty... But hoppiness throughout... - Drinking an American Beauty by @dogfishbeer @ Casa Segarra… https://t.co/RNZPBEfUBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gerrydulac So I’m going out on a limb here to say the Steelers will pull the agreement on AB because he pulled the… https://t.co/nPMirO7Doa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer dije que odiaba el sushi, hoy les digo que amo las ensaladas, esa me la preparé yo mismo en un sitio por estos… https://t.co/94i7kuM6Sf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bekijo1 @GMB Could see her getting back in the uk an the committing an attack after they LET her back in. Clearly… https://t.co/3wvqzvMplf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlazersBySagar Roses are red Kanter is wack Sagar, please take Allen Crabbe’s contract back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Slow traffic in #Raleigh on I-440 WB between Six Forks Rd - Exit 8 and Glenwood Ave - Exit 7, accident at Glenwood Ave - Exit 7 #traffic]]></document><document><![CDATA[My like boss is super attractive and he told me " I should always work with the public"  😁😂😅 thank you sir.  bends… https://t.co/2xCQ0oOg9v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitoldRPL Szykuja rozbior Ukrainy.Jaka czesc Ukrainy, Rosja moze wydzierzawic Israelowi na uzytkowanie Israel bis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democratic party's Hate of Trump is Greater than there Love of Country and Trumps everything else  including tr… https://t.co/nxDnfutJ8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, there’s three games at Pinnacle Bank Arena tonight? #nebpreps https://t.co/1tKXOyu9TF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganA_mma I would love to see you Kicking someone in the face Again Champ be Well Keep Kicking Moving and Stickin… https://t.co/EMKUMmyoVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NicolleDWallace I cannot take “Humpty Trumpty”. Please don’t let that happen again. Much sanity at stake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pinky Jaime #portrait #me #pink #selfportrait #jaimecamposfoto 🎂 solopostresmty en Jaime Campos Estudio https://t.co/gjfohT0FLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumb_librarian Wanna hear something funny? My name on fb is edwlnd so I can’t be found lmao IDK friend of friends?… https://t.co/4dm5WimXEQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[no more than wearing tzitzit and head covering thus heeding  halachah makes Jews violate the constitution. It’s tox… https://t.co/gCHOAbUDTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the privilege to argue before the US Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit on behalf of a consumer who paid… https://t.co/xakSCDwlkS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even with a week’s delay, #Nigeria is still experiencing #voting problems in #Africa’s largest democratic… https://t.co/Bfa6IYiG65]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s amazing that @MizzouWBB has made it this far to the semifinals, and I’m looking forward to what the NCAA WBB T… https://t.co/tIlauWvnef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeWithDiablo Shit u need too 💀 this tall ass center nigga. Y’all cute tho👌🏽 https://t.co/0YtW5gPEIF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Columbus Circle #ColumbusCircle #skyscrapernationalpark #newyorkcity @ Columbus Circle https://t.co/qdrY56ciVz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Heart and Science by @NinkasiBrewing @ Tire Shop For Rent — https://t.co/9fMfT6yNeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValaAfshar Hi Vala, I appreciate your advice. It seems like I have liked the identical tweets multiple times, thou… https://t.co/8oI62MfXTL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColinCowherd Stop it. You’re using facts and crushing his “narrative.”  Youre just another example of the “they” t… https://t.co/yt9zD3QO8t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Humanity would work very well if we treated society like ants do except that wont happen because people aren’t ants… https://t.co/gaeBjw7ri1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Florida sixth-grader charged with misdemeanor after refusing to recite Pledge of Allegiance https://t.co/mSiWelDHOd]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ve never felt this love. i’ve got a kind friend. an amazing boyfriend &amp; i’m even loving myself more and more]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chills7134 ok lol. he clearly has problems. its INTRAMURAL basketball. he took it too far🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The biggest crisis America has is the corrupt, immoral, incompetent foreign operative occupying the White House.  M… https://t.co/nLWJ4UHgKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobpockrass Oh ok I appreciate the reply.  I just am optimistic since they are wanting to come here that it would… https://t.co/Dyg3GL94oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[after u die and ur in the loading screen for heaven waiting for it to load, “cold” by rich brian is playing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Regardless of what Fiala is or will be, it is foolish not to ask for something else even if you talked to another G… https://t.co/5ZgiMz6XOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m happy. 29 year old (millennial) our whole generation was babied and now the effects are showing....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAnd16120029 Can’t wait to see you in the Brown and Gold. Ride For The Brand 🤠🏈🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyhrains You beat me here! And my flight leaves at 7:30. https://t.co/dnHdiRMpOo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roll Call Just In:     Two organizations calling for Rep. Ilhan Omar resign from the Foreign Affairs Committee have… https://t.co/U8Qai2pUda]]></document><document><![CDATA[South Mountain Magnet Arts Center for Visual Arts Exhibit https://t.co/olEJ10Cx2n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottKaplan @MikeBellATL @putemupcdukes @DukesandBell929 @AtlantaUnitedES @MLS @espn @ManUtd @Arsenal @NBCSports… https://t.co/6XkAaVeDz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cvpayne @realDonaldTrump Job numbers tanked, but he still thinks he is winning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @MollyJongFast @TomiLahren Entertaining read, but let's all pray that there's a cure for Trumpism, not an heir to it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thinkprogress Not all the times. Some of the times. Trump has been a dangerous bully forever]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bro @DCookeJr is on a tear right now! Last 11 games is leading the @nbagleague in total Rebounds with 153 (2nd i… https://t.co/w4gNp4Sh6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IIIDeaton Exactly. And you also don't win over Muslims, Jews, Catholics etc by bashing their beliefs. You do it by… https://t.co/n2UqWzuCDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MercedesGlobal @GlobalNational Congratulations Mercedes. You’ll do great 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prediction: as soon as #padres sign Machado, the White Sox will trade Alonso and DFA Jay.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I could get through winter without getting stupid congested that would be nice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the good life @ Glassboro, New Jersey https://t.co/TFHdFN7g59]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @POTUS can cry and whine all he wants about #SNL! #AlexBaldwin  plays a great @realDonaldTrump! @SpeakerPelosi… https://t.co/3FSXbXzepW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Wolfiesmom Not sure I agree with that teacher comment.  I know a handful who retired in their early 50’s and now s… https://t.co/rZu1PYRJjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoddessDommelia Because some just try getting sympathy and thing it will help]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just woke up from a sleep paralysis and that shit was CHAFAA Ni miedon dan, nada más son una bola de maricones]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinCBS12 @SavanahResnik @CBS12 Gonna throw it out there...  Altamonte Springs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Del. Toscano! I’ll never forget that random Sunday morning phone call I received from you in ‘17 encourag… https://t.co/Uqalz6cfVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MauroManotas19 y Juan David Cabezas titulares hoy con @HoustonDynamo en la apertura de @TheChampions. El equipo lo… https://t.co/WjZZzpYNMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it though? You have scored 82 runs in 3 games against a bad team at home because you don’t want to play quality… https://t.co/tCPO9miG4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que nada pinta mas lindo para que @TrueKofi  gane hoy. Se lo dieron a @WWEBrayWyatt y a @IAmJericho alguna vez… https://t.co/AJseEv4AYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz Omar and the Democrats would be a good name for a garage band]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Man shot in Bayview while driving early Monday - San Francisco Examiner https://t.co/8MtCnLR2sh @HainesForSF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theneedledrop I think this is the first time I started listening to a newer artist before you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Louisiane-Louisiana, jour-day 5. Nouvelle-Orléans-New Orleans. Grand ciel bleu sur le Quartier Français...… https://t.co/ECkY64Yddp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgordonshare Never tried on a cougar. One time I was stalked while trail running at night I didn’t have any with m… https://t.co/1ik6wZ7gpd]]></document><document><![CDATA[La nostra palestra e sempre la migliore. #WhatAreYouWaitingFor? #SeaIsland @ Sea Island, Georgia https://t.co/faisfrPGJl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATMLA @revampedlyfe She's a stunner... I only wish I could book her tho...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tiaras &amp; Ties @ MLK...#Hares #DaddyDaughter @ King Early Childhood Ctr https://t.co/6VJaARQ0PM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Patrick Ewing.   I know he's not the greatest defender at this point of his career, but Mac McClung is a born score… https://t.co/iQk8dKdCU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[fat kid jogging past the crosswalk before we turn  kyle : jesus that kid HATES P.E.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When people say sorry they aren’t truly sorry, they are sorry they got caught... #realtalk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico You can tell, citizens are moving out and illegal aliens are moving in  Thriving]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t even really know Scottie like that, but y’all letting this porcelain pigeon YesJulz utter any Black woman’s… https://t.co/U2cElfBqcp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited for my 1st #FinancialPlanning workshop of the new year on Thursday.  Thank you to the @TheHuntleyHotel for… https://t.co/2dDDRskXJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@USATODAY Trump wall will never Separate America from the Problems of the World. What will? New Arm Race do to dest… https://t.co/MrPR7pfnMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrouchetDavid @fox7austin @NASCAR @FOXSports Certainly not, although I’m a Talladega guy - -Love #SuperSpeedways]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A majority of the people living in @VibrantRRHA are children. You have to ask what opportunities they will have to… https://t.co/JOA6NXTRrW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn, this is me on the mark!!!   I didn't want the damn bunny rabbit's!!! But let me go feed them with all my love… https://t.co/fjWOHgNuBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VOColleen @KariWahlgren @TheFederalNoHo @ThatsSoCravens @Julie_Nathanson @GirlMacFarlane BTW, U should join… https://t.co/eZ0TIJoJzC]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of our first outdoor meet this week! Let's get it echhs.wildcats.on.ig #WildcatThrows @ Wofford College https://t.co/yypeFwZQu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @realDonaldTrump Remember when Mexico would pay for the wall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched this tonight. Never seen anything like it. @AlexHonnold is a rare RARE breed of athlete. Incredible]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picked up these fleece-lined Northside Bromio boots on clearance at Sierra Trading Post and they have served me wel… https://t.co/nArNFBAvdF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamilahPrince @KatrinaPierson @TommyHicksGOP @GOP Thank you for your leadership and opportunity to be part of this amazing experience!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kenturrac @NiklasAstrand I think the worst part about dlc for the community is just lack of information. Ever sinc… https://t.co/YOQXr7ues2]]></document><document><![CDATA[My body can not handle all the festivities of going out. I’d 100% rather be snuggled up with my honey than go out to bars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[laura told me that she would be my sponsor and the fact that she was being so serious makes me realize i will never… https://t.co/mWnJ0RgLhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doobsnax @voluntaryreboot Probably just expressing my thoughts poorly. Obviously I've benefitted. But it amplifies… https://t.co/CvHbZsnCvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skrillex I really hope you can find a way to destroy the gorge with some prodigy tracks this summer!!! #Prodigy… https://t.co/KIfc3cMn36]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to see these elite athletes in action Friday night vs @Austin_E_Rugby ???   Get your tickets at… https://t.co/4CBZkL1lTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can all agree that witness tampering is a serious crime, yes? Whether any particular case qualifies is a separat… https://t.co/iKpxLpUZR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@What_the_ALANIZ It’s called a statement. I didn’t know your opinion. I don’t care about your opinion. I just used… https://t.co/plIw8C1ZlS]]></document><document><![CDATA['Asbestos fibers' discovered in Claire's makeup products, FDA says  https://t.co/95i7mFjjlZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@histoftech That's just Corningware.  People bought them at department stores and other places you'd get those sort… https://t.co/9poPv1vqQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Water reflection Los Angeles Japanese Tea Gardens. #fineartphotography #reflection #clouds #grass #goodvibes… https://t.co/QejMVGOtK9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of my son. I may be 3,000 miles away and not part of tonight, but I’m always in awe at what he can acco… https://t.co/Tg91TKX9nk]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Dickerson and Cher I hate this country now it's unbelievable it really is like a bunch slave drives to be smashed to Oblivion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarasikS You don’t wonder why they didn’t do them? Metcalf could’ve easily sat them out, or could improve on them… https://t.co/Dvd6fo1xmB]]></document></documents></author>