<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@niallerdiaries I am a late Directioner bloomer. I became of Niall's music when I first heard, Slow Hands. I saw Ni… https://t.co/7FiVGt96hb]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It began with a Discovery of Witches” time responded, in a primeval echo that set alight blue and amber threads th… https://t.co/FbUk6nyLgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[And scene.  Another day of Public Service in the books.  Love this city. Love this job. @CityofSouthBend https://t.co/BepKqGvPEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mekhibrown26 @chartdata @Drake @LilTunechi @PostMalone @trvisXX @kendricklamar @JColeNC @ArianaGrande All opinions… https://t.co/AhOiPYPwWk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntiTrumpReport Big deal. We don't a probe to figure out what he's doing. We need to STOP him from doing more damage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to put in a request to work in my Tampa office from January-March and be in the PA office from April-… https://t.co/yHJo7SUlTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESchultz_EM @ProMammaDoc @LakelandEMRes @EMsportsdoc @SheilaPhilpott1 @schraderdo @jfinch906 I sadly was not prese… https://t.co/3TpSsloSHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know a girl taking an uber in ATL and almost getting snatched. He turned off his uber light and directions, she s… https://t.co/EKZfdVt6J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 Beautiful Now (Zonderling Remix) (feat. Jon Bellion) by @Zedd on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/1xq6ifALDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shari512 @WildcatsBethune @MayRanch I told her and Shirley it’s the first stop of their farewell tour!! Well deserved!! 📚 ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ran for the free beer. 🍺 First Sunshine Skyway 10K ✅ #sunshineskyway #raceday #10K https://t.co/ofIDPG2Q5e]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll be damned if the weekend goes by and I don’t finish sewing my shirt]]></document><document><![CDATA[so glad i got to see you it’s been too long &lt;3 https://t.co/TuiIfkDGoh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lololol I meant 9:15 Barza not@Barcelona that 2nd division #Barza is first I believer lol 😝]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Alma~♡ @O_mi_alma Follows you Beautiful word, Tay~Smoosh @FloriKarma, Cheetah Deva @jaghuara, Nischala_po… https://t.co/8GpH7HpRNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Although I am a Black Jew by faith and my beliefs; I actually know very little about the state of affairs in Israel… https://t.co/O84tk1VRE4]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my kids were grounded from technology... come home to find out @RingwaldToby gave them a presidential pardon.… https://t.co/gqUH8q56eG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another home run by Chrf Jay at the Wildside Bistro in Oakdale. Scrumptious, delicious, heavenly meal. Happy Valent… https://t.co/qWtNuMmffI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jetergirl410 @Mantharalaya I could definitely get behind Drew and Liz sleeping together, but I don’t think they wo… https://t.co/WUm9q7UfXa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeyBeardMon @OriginalFunko Picturing @PostMalone as the doodle bear just makes me like him more...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing our friend @JoshCassidy84 a great race tomorrow at the #TokyoMarathon2019 !  #goJoshgo🇨🇦 https://t.co/aQ6yrLRJMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Band director says he “brings flare” to @KUnews ... Um ma’am,  he doesn’t “bring” flare,  HE IS FLARE.    https://t.co/iRb0I2lX7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all know what day it is.  🙌🐈😍🎉🙌  #campuscatmonday #campuscats #campuscatcoalition #volunteer… https://t.co/8qn3etFkAZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@p0cketfullasuns @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse Shame Shame Shame!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know there are prizes inside every OREO cookie? Check out The Stuf Inside for your chance to win!… https://t.co/068BgNwjjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SuzZurn @aews @DBroton Hi Suzanne! Weirdly, buying another cable was on my to-do list today. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reppin’ wylieelite at the Coke museum! 😄 #wylieelite #cheersport2019 @ World of Coca-Cola https://t.co/lrRppCy19U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_emileexo The worst is I know so many people that don’t even know what the song is 🥴🥴🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewN22182076 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Yep, you're so busy claiming fake news  you don't realize you're the fake]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiamiSup @MDCPS @cgcs @AASAHQ Congratulations my friend @MiamiSup You represent @MDCPS and our entire community well!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blkumathurman When I was young and single I looked like shit because I was out all night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib And... you sound desperate. Why should the man be scared? He did not collude. NO COLLUSION. America d… https://t.co/S3ZtFJU9z3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlanderCostum I love their snark! Looking forward to their Oscar reviews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great day @District31R MSs @is75 #IS24, #IS61, @MAELS63 TOURing @PRHSactivities - a day in the life of @PRHSRaiders… https://t.co/NybVQiOatZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HRC @RepDebHaaland Hard not to cry. These people are heroes and trump is trying to take away their dignity because he has none.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie American culture has always been disrespectful of elders. But just as we’ve evolved w other ways of thinking… https://t.co/HY4FLYVPMT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkCCrowley Whatever the platform, it all depends on who you are connecting with and how you are interacting. (as you know)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Está es la mejor cheve que me he tomado en la vida. https://t.co/lGvfOJczir]]></document><document><![CDATA[@friendlychuckle I feel like I’ve seen so many youngins starts podcasts tho!! And when we were in college we all did blogs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last month I took a very last minute trip to San Francisco to visit my boyfriend.   We only had 48 hours to spend t… https://t.co/joY7z4bFza]]></document><document><![CDATA[House Oversight Committee issues ultimatum to White House over security clearance information  https://t.co/NpWKyrdp4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know he’s one of their only players performing at the level they should be at the moment, but I feel like they’re… https://t.co/3BPRspbKHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[: "When you reach the end of your rope you will find the hem of His garment." https://t.co/exp0sFN0ZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SL1733 @sxdoc @AOC Pretty is as pretty does, my mother always said. She looks OK, but she is misinformed, loud and ignorant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@devere09 @freenaynow When I first saw this, knowing the next day he was going to meet Trump I thought it was suspi… https://t.co/qkt4PqBEWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartingThoughtz And she thinks she can govern! Her behavior only shines the light she is unqualified to run for dog catcher!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @DrEdwinBracho @jguaido This has NO way back and when the whole world puts their Eyes in a dictator its… https://t.co/HUeEjseQOz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you florettelovesyou for hosting my #oilslickhair class for pony.studios #ponyeducation thank you @KinkyKiana… https://t.co/8roh1LSJbI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never been so happy to know "I'm stuck with you" ❤ https://t.co/b3xvhV36nW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackiDeLaGarza @adelitasway I most likely will. 😊 I’ve seen them before, and they do out on an amazing Show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling destructive so I ordered a $44 shirt from Urban Outfitters and post mated myself some Chipotle even though… https://t.co/KC6qbAx4Dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started the day with a workout and some 2000s Hip Hop... lets have a good day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanRather @SpeakerPelosi The senate wont convict. Pick battles we can win.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump You live in a fantasy world where you are a good person #TrumpCrimeFamilyMustGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't mind doing High School tournaments. They're our future for golf but when our regulars want to go out behind… https://t.co/GsGKKvkK7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[A1: Mona Towner- Instructional Coach - working w/the best crew in ed tech #coachingtheafterhours https://t.co/9N1nUnvIY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytdavidbrooks @tribelaw Today’s editorial should be required reading for those who are confused/depressed/ nauseated😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianCJax I don’t get that at all. I appreciate confirmation and extend the courtesy back. What she did, immature… https://t.co/yVjLOHZZEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Rockford, MI? This could be a great fit. Click the link in our bio to apply: Clerk - Rockfo… https://t.co/pxXLZ18UZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baalter Yes, they are. Where were they when we could have stopped her? But please, this dangerous Hamas-tied Jew h… https://t.co/jZfXMkxTuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like if you know you’re a procrastinator don’t involve yourself  1. Everyone will still figure it out (if it’s not… https://t.co/tTUDnjj43J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somebody needs to sign this boy already! He’s better than most artists on radio now. 😳#dexterroberts #TheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome time last night at our Annual YAM Gospel Explosion! #YAM #YAMMentors #gospelexplosion #twjcogic… https://t.co/iwoM3nEBCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Leprechauns are coming! 🍀 The Leprechauns are coming! 🍀 Get your St. Pattie's Day green 🍀 on with our fresh hom… https://t.co/0Uy8KwpXYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianeengnes Thank you. He was loved by so many, that provided some comfort seeing all the love from everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackhowell55 @RyanAFournier The FBI has to get involved because he sent that hoax hate letter to his studio to get… https://t.co/0wlZuy0MOe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never stop learning, because life never stops teaching..... https://t.co/5ovCjqLR8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/rH9AWn4jU0  This is my niece. Give her a listen &amp;, if you like it, pass it around. (And maybe subscribe).]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baezalakew @AbuYoshi I got upset at her attempt at a justification. It doesn’t matter the context, it doesn’t belo… https://t.co/eorC2UI3do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wewatchu2 @Qafzeh @LiveScience Look at it more carefully, the Aleutians were probably a mountain range along the southern edge Beringia. 😺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is he wearing a headband?! No wonder why I’m freaking confused 🤷🏼‍♀️#My600lblife]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy stole a sick little boy medication from ther front door let’s get him and get back the medication]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where my grammarians at? Does “open-mouthed” describe The Elders, how they stared, or her? If her, do we need the c… https://t.co/vJ2f5xWAQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happens when the car keys 🔑 get shut in the trunk 🚘 at an open house 🏡 at Ardmore? You get almost 3,000 steps… https://t.co/ktuWEz2zmI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veto...States need to decide. I don't want ANY Federal Employees flying commercial jets that have "Pot" in their sy… https://t.co/FfQk452AvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out all of our alternative pathways to certification too! Applications for math, science, Spanish and French… https://t.co/SrwuVrONpm]]></document><document><![CDATA[LATEST: Officer involved shooting investigation outside of Hacienda Healthcare Facility south of #Phoenix. One susp… https://t.co/J1sdrVHckD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Paul196510 @MuslimIQ You’re a close minded jackass who probably hasn’t even read the Bible cover to cover. You cla… https://t.co/ojKKW4fkOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[There aren't enough expletives. @earthjustice report finds that detention centers for CHILDREN will be built on tox… https://t.co/atwLUHXIj6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lisarinna Hi Lisa :) I love you and love the show. You hold your own lady. Sending love😘💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bgpowelll @PeteMedhurst Ice cream is on me if you make the trek to Happy Valley!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 🤣😂 talking about da nang dick being a fraud  #TruthHurts https://t.co/mzjEPeUsU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cammysutra6 @ChrisStrub @Baierman @NickJRishwain @natxwang @ChelseaPeitz @MadalynSklar @KrisGillentine @JoAnnKrall… https://t.co/JxlBvQQ9jo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 11:30am and I’m in my second class trembling uncontrollably. Not that I have a lot going on or anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People in Florida had to have protests to get Trayvon Martin’s killer arrested. Yet they arrest a 11 year old for n… https://t.co/vB9s8j9Exr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@og_dbl_lo_g @GreggMarius1 @tlccourville @PollyPapaya @CIAnderson3 @BlkSantaX @MrsblksantaX @OG_WeDemBoyz… https://t.co/kfmOjfL7Bf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Earper Queen! 💕  Why WE fight! We are FAMILY We are here and We stay! #FightForWynonna #WynonnaEarp @SYFY… https://t.co/zXJ810blmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart was stuck in denial. There were too many miles between us. @MsNikkiFlores]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justanassholee My god that’s horrible. Was his passport about to expire in less than 4 months?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitRECordJoe An Affair To Remember. The waterworks break out when Cary Grant realizes that Deborah Kerr [*****]. N… https://t.co/D4xR64QEX7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ida_skibenes It’s fascinating, germs aren’t real because you can’t see them... but God is because...?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeviMarshell @MaskedSingerFOX Really no!! I want Rabbit to@win it all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jefferwaddle @joegeldard_ @gofundme Would anyone be able to please look into my story and help if you are able 💜💜💜 https://t.co/zsaFESSXRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABFalecbaldwin @kenvogel @CPAC @HillaryClinton @CNN How can you even listen to him. Oh yeah it helps you hone your… https://t.co/je9y71SS6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[My amazing #PhysicalTherapist, @EnvisionSportPT, takes care of my back and my sweet tooth! ❤️  Happy Valentine's Da… https://t.co/ylSXx8kp82]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claddytaemin Lmaoooooo I feel bad but I actually hated bts' music for the longest time bc id only ever heard bst a… https://t.co/2GIbGODRIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorOSoule 🙌🏽 I’m so glad someone finally tweeted this! I’ve been seeing some discouraging tweets and it’s just… https://t.co/qDeC2Msku2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff @cooperchip1 what is next?? Don't say Meuller.He needs to go.. now., with Pense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janemarielynch Yes!!! One of the funniest monologues &amp; funniest SNL in a while🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[昨日、忙しすぎて、この写真を貼りなかった。 もう３月ですね。 一ヶ月後、もうレスルマニアウィークが始まって、3日間連続でROH✖️新日本プロレスイベントに行きます❣️ それからバレットクラブのブロックパーティーにこのパンフレットを… https://t.co/5q7M14ufXb]]></document></documents></author>