<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[My week: SAT -&gt; DFW -&gt; BWI -&gt; PHL -&gt; SAT -&gt; HOU -&gt; SAT. And it’s Spring Break in Texas... 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @realDonaldTrump Then why are the republicans voting against a strong border??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheObamanista @SowaTheArrogant @Kennymack1971 Compared to what bruthas wore in the 70s i tip my hat to him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being a Health Science Major at Lincoln😭 I’m dead serious to https://t.co/ngAXFMEdbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[District 12 City Title Games for Saturday:  5A: @WoodBoysBball vs. @MasteryCharter North at @ARHS - Vikings last wo… https://t.co/r7KzjvPWH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tagged by the very awesome krissyluvsbobby_rny2016 for an #sds  ————————————- Chilling w my parents nursing my… https://t.co/x7dJbL8URF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing dedication to our youth..we really appreciate it it! @Bellaswings06 Pay attention to the end of the video!!… https://t.co/FbqYgJpcWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not bad for a quick supper.  Tuna salad on lettuce and tomato topped with black olives. Peaches on the side. @ Vict… https://t.co/ibzveYmU7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfoundation @MarioLemieuxFdn @ATTSportsNetPIT If I can send these back and get them replaced let me know! All t… https://t.co/WvcKzRNHjN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nas and Diddy rockin the 9 Mile Music Festival _________________________ #Nas #NasirJones #Diddy #PuffDaddy #PDiddy… https://t.co/ELJjCv6G3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff I know there are about 37% that will be shocked, the rest of us not so much! We warned you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No more driving with the emergency brakes ON‼️ #excuses #fear #BREAKTHROUGH #TRUST #BELIEVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week was a big one on @CBSThisMorning - but that’s nothing new for this team who does such a great job with or… https://t.co/gdRgOjdJDx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying a @NASA_TESS update from our own @PadiBoyd at this afternoon’s Astro colloquium at @NASAGoddard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its They made Twitter to talk to each other like walkie talkies, it’s alright if I talk like this isn’t it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackson once said there are no Cubists in Vienna but there is one in Canoe Lake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[As weird (and wonderful) as I remembered. 🐔 + 🎃 = ☠️ https://t.co/BXL5rM8oMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elbonitoguapo I couldn’t be the only one seeing those lies and deception]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ohhwade So lean and handsome! Wade, I would love to meet you in Los Angeles!]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Februburied:’ Up to 25 feet of snow has fallen in mountains on the West Coast this February… https://t.co/kBl2q72zFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The DNC said Wednesday it does not plan to partner with Fox News for debates during the 2020 election cycle.… https://t.co/HCpmvvLTrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Uy no, ¿pero este @PresidenciaCAB qué putas quiere? Saca lo único rescatable del equipo (@joseflabio) para meter a… https://t.co/YHkQSdYGNA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moreover, you have to really like the site placement in that case: Jacksonville!  #LSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Josh leading worship @ First Baptist Church Lake Alfred https://t.co/hahKMnOwp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JONGOD_ I even stress that plus I feel like if you don’t get in a accident you should get your money back]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning I was walking on Miami Beach, this evening I’m in freezing Las Vegas #TakeMeBack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @SamsungUS please dont ditch the 9mm jack from everyone in #musicbiz in #note10]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your barber tells you "Today's my last day, I'm moving states" My heart has been fucking shattered. #todaywassupposedtobeagoodday #why]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing and hearing you whenever you are on the tube.  You are great.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elisasboy72 So great to see you on the big screen in #GoalieMovie Woo Hoo! 👍🏻👍🏻👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Vicky4Trump @td21241 @donlemon I wouldn’t be surprised if @donlemon  helped #JussieSmolettHoax  plan #FakeHateCrime]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knows? Is this the start of something wonderful and new? Or one more dream that I cannot make true?  #cityofstars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevavera No necesitas saber cuanto cuesta el kilo de azucar y si el programa economico de CAP2 era el adecuado has… https://t.co/k25W7rkaDB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawneeSwick @Para_Mystery yeah but hats just a common theory that is applied to any type of mass strangeness or m… https://t.co/YtWTZam4kx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods They really do not care or like the idea of American Exceptionalism. Obama taunted The well the Dem… https://t.co/AzIOxAMAzE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will prob take the rest of the week for me to finish this but pretty happy with tonight’s work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Voteforthefrig @drabbott66 @hughhewitt Again, it’s the person. Never said drugs were safe lol. And you’re comparin… https://t.co/dhUsFEPOkz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't Deny Compensation to 9/11 First Responders #neverforget - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/zNBmaMHpPt via @Change]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t care where u go podz..where ever it is..it will become my new favorite school and I’ll be watching every Sa… https://t.co/rj1PVK4TrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dissa my editing face. I editing. @ Scarborough, Maine https://t.co/amM4AjTndC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexmontejano52 @Mel_the_geek @iron_lombardi @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton I've said that a bunch. Trump has re… https://t.co/wOnQQkC8a8]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/scwHUde8Uq Yeah right if you believe this story you're going to be dumb enough to believe I am a correspondent for CBS News]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrdyPackard I wounder if ThinkProgress became a parody website, but just forgot to tell everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews A supporter of Nixon's order to MURDER ELECTED CHILEAN SOCIALIST PRESIDENT ALLENDE and then support the Co… https://t.co/tM8GxCfva7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdorchen @sgtcattywampus @WalterOhlinger @AOC Ate you trying to tell me your emojis are your retweet,? Are u fucki… https://t.co/s2tDtUT5sl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkarlovi Composer may not be outdated if your version restrictions are such like ^1.7. You could miss 2.0 that int… https://t.co/AWnvdSTSfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MFS314 @kwilli1046 your saying I am not allowed to have and opinion because he is dead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP will try to make an issue out of the fact that she’s saying it.   She’s saying it because it’s 100% true.   Can… https://t.co/fjhaEUA1Dc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla Always impressed at the innovations you guys are adding to make the overall Tesla experience better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sunrise @ Cadillac Hotel &amp; Beach Club, Autograph Collection https://t.co/f4VxnHmde4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottbelsky I would be able to drag and drop assets from a local or theme library. Simple logic includes hero basi… https://t.co/66KXpNkfQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceciinhasanttos @EliLeonarda @irvinejulie @SaraRsrs @ElioeneLeonarda @Zenibeta @amfroes @josybreda @Carla56725378… https://t.co/6eL7o5GgFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did a dope rig on a car last night ! #griplife #setlife🎥 #lovemyjob #keygrip #funtime #rain #bts @ Rubidoux, Califo… https://t.co/F34zzkeODx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJSADelrith Anything published by EA, Activision, or Ubi for that matter, since the launch of DLC hasn't been fini… https://t.co/m9RbWefzhy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reuters AMAZONS idea of PUBLIC... At least LIC in : LONG ISLAND CITY LIC ONE  LOCK IN CENTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HedwigAFreeElf @RealityGazette @by_finch @rexpault @wdunlap @realDonaldTrump That’s me a Trump supporter.  I appre… https://t.co/s2iBlgPAqk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So far tonight been a wild night. Almost to wild but show out to boyfriends hating me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ @CaitlinPacific Would you take the word of one witness in a trial and not check around?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pinwheels #are #delicious @ Orange, California https://t.co/pDyJnmKYrI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cohen met with Schiff staff for over 10 hours before House Oversight Committee hearing, sources say Shady Shiff is… https://t.co/X2O7udBLUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left the plane at 14,000 feet. Awesome day glad to have done it w David!! Skydive Carolina the best!!! Would do it… https://t.co/xx5x2CZFKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to #LiveTweeting the #KACMatWSU social media presentation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heARTISTatWORK @dintersmith @TeachersOnFire @unleighshed @MSSBullyingBlog @SJSaragusa @JasonSalhaney @JustinNolan_… https://t.co/3a7YwbMaRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[You probably get tired or repeating yourself. It's okay. Keep going. The role of a good leader is to get people fro… https://t.co/o5yysDMNKm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_KingDHSHST has a lot of funny class related memes that make me 😂 in principles of health science @FBISD_CTE… https://t.co/BIjmbuRGWP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over under on how many times @SCSUHUSKIES_MH chases a goalie tonight!!:{) #GOHUSKIESWOOOOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Arresting families. Your mother must be so proud if you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCohen Thank you Congressman, I know this has been a huge problem here in Shelby County.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealFoxD I chose to watch Suicide Squad instead. Can't sleep after watching losses so self preservation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@castorenamusic @FabianMcNally @KenCarman Was prob 50 cent who edited it 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@modernfarmer @Agridome @Pasztor79 Yes... definitely not safe yet and not likely for a while or ever.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started reading the CL in the 60s. up til last yr when it went up to $5 a copy or something like that.I was looking… https://t.co/ULRreNsVtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tushyraw @EmmyDemure @violetsaucy @AlyssaReeceXo @KarlaKush420 @EmmyDemure, do you know what the thing is that I’m talking about? 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@montaguethecat @oilngas007 So what, exactly, would you charge them with?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepThomasMassie @RandPaul Most of them did not deal with our porous border, hey?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC That's Republicans and snobs 4 you.I was thinking all workers of menial jobs should strike for a week.. Let th… https://t.co/6TMIzSStRx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SoNotThePoint_ @CantWaitToNap So, Condescending Remarks Fly Right Over Your Head, Huh ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got some insane trades last night!! One step closer to being ready for #TempestCup! #pokemongo #trades #legacyhunt… https://t.co/zg9BCM7UKP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is completely accurate. #LeavingNeverland #AfterNeverland #MichaelJacksonLikedLittleBoys #MichaelJackson]]></document><document><![CDATA[Savannah at-risk conference discusses rise in 'wounded students' https://t.co/n5f1xXzPoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[honered to work and create #music #indiefilm #scifimusic #percussion #compser #reggae #drums #Jazz #housemusic… https://t.co/Iixr6AOGjC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: why is this plain loaf of bread $2 more than this other bread?? It’s plain bread.  Me, now: I’m never buying ch… https://t.co/n5HVJ5gdvL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three friends. Three years. Same result.  Forever climbing. https://t.co/orbRRLUs7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dignity, Self Respect and Grace is what you wanna hold on to at the end of the day...]]></document><document><![CDATA[View of the ConUS Precipitation Forecast today 03/09-10 #NWS NEXRAD Radar Reflectivity composite and time synchrono… https://t.co/WvxDSOPs8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yusuku13 @salty_nerd @pablohidalgo @RogerLarson1970 Cringey. No way. You know what is cringey. This..... https://t.co/xsTXdk6WEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did the sun go? With Janine #cardiorehab #runCARA #caratrained #ShamrockShuffle #ENDALZ (@ Cricket Hill in Ch… https://t.co/d9oqZEjolZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@safe_its Not sure maybe religious reasons? Maybe they blame Jews for killing him since he was Jewish I guess. Witc… https://t.co/Rqy3dYFT0s]]></document><document><![CDATA[The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me. - Ayn Rand  #truth #daretobedifferent… https://t.co/wgVMwyHFrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[For the first time in the 2019 season finally we get some ASAP Rocky in pregame and it comes at the region tournament. Morehead is jiggy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DerekCressman @LindseyGrahamSC isn’t only betraying the senate more importantly he’s betraying our country!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump maybe the money for that wall should be used to fund some of these useful inventions! Starting… https://t.co/4I29mDOK8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Rite Aid in Woodland Hills, CA w/ @theltmgroup https://t.co/x9hMR57NwU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The composition of “Make Yours A Happy Home” is fucking brilliant. The strings, brass, percussion. Whew.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Delta Baggage Claim in Salt Lake City, UT https://t.co/teSJGSB7WS https://t.co/ZjVbwVObrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dfank_BU My boss a few years ago threw “D.C., VA, Motor City to the Lou', what it do? Finna blow like Waco...” int… https://t.co/tpB6iXSVx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimmyVanBramer @NYCDisabilities @maawallace @brentoleary @NYCMayor @macartney @FabianBuchheim @MakeQueensSafer… https://t.co/0wApcCtakQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Key issue in what's problematic in our divisions! @rshawnm @aafp @MtAFPhysicians #MultiStateForum19 https://t.co/iHItb2dEG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickcapra If only I was a bit younger and better build. At least its all good in the manbits.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎧 93 'til Infinity by @SOMHIERO on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/RlILsTFRZV #HappyFriday]]></document></documents></author>