<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HondoResists @Ldogls @RealAntHen @EveScottGarner @Jessie092859463 @oldmanliver @Uhuruhsiempre @illegitamatepr1… https://t.co/6pMmEUXgli]]></document><document><![CDATA[ESPN announcer adds: ‘How can a Division I program function like that?’]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really what is behind the new green deal? Communists know that the most effective way to control a country is pover… https://t.co/A0NS15r4Ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NerdAtCoolTable Yes, and if I told you who he really is it would blow your mind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marcia91760332 When I was younger of course I’m still able to Give Girls pleasure before myself I have always done… https://t.co/4Tn5rLZz9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@dog_rates will you help find this lovely lady a #valentine? She is a good girl. #Valentines #ValentinesDay… https://t.co/kKc8W5FRTn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelAngelBris Yo si Los pago de niño lo mire jugar un nunca pude tener una ahora si los pagaría]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't like blocking people. The Mute button is a powerful tool though 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is this rumor and innuendo true? WWE bringing back huge name to work in 'top' creative role - Monsters and Critics… https://t.co/nFn5G1G0ZH]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 years ago, met Finn and Bayley. @ iPlay America https://t.co/cTArEPmQso]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @realDonaldTrump there is election fraud, and it's Republican!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@e40 &amp; @blegit72 - "Snap Yo Fingers" ((🤞))🔊 #nkcmo #e40 #40water #blegit #thesavage #oldschool #bayareahiphop… https://t.co/7gIj2BQHhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I mean what did we do after her? We saw @HeymanHustle eat soap! Wow entertaining NOT]]></document><document><![CDATA[am I wearing the same outfit I was wearing the same outfit I wore exactly a week ago? Yes. https://t.co/c4IPz8xRil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grew up on shattered dreams and broken promises. It’s only fair for you not to expect the same from me, though I’m… https://t.co/q4eyjZ8VyY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the EvCo All-League girls basketball team. Locals on 1st team: Madi Haakenson (WFW), Paige Winter (ROC), Ann… https://t.co/cnnapEiVfm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collusion: DEA bans plant medicines, then Big Pharma patents them for profits https://t.co/SwxQvkUbjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[As far as the east is from the west, so far has he removed our transgressions from us. — Psalm 103:12 https://t.co/L0qA3RYdR1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched Abducted In Plain Sight the other night. What. The. Fuck. Sad thing is that the kids still defend what their parents did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I’m going to get the clothes out of the dryer.  3 year old: OK. If you find money in there, bring it up to my p… https://t.co/AkzHJgGNZx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@celticproud22 @RealSaavedra Remember loser trump has a 52 percent approval rate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged by @SalvadorBlanco3 to post covers of my favorite books over the next 7 days, no explanations… https://t.co/iVsMJkwiwC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes bari weiss is precisely why I canceled my subscription. Your @nytopinion section is insufferable and dange… https://t.co/4GAa7vkyTB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rjjago I believe Dr Samuel Johnson—who was not so learned he wasn’t a great opponent of witches—had the dignity to… https://t.co/udThWuMS5Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorJRogers That’s easy. #WoodyHarrelson and #MatthewMcConaughey  #TrueDetectiveSeasonOne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michelleDbelle happy Saturday to you beautiful lady enjoy your weekend from John in Manhattan NY 💜 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mates y torta fritas en un día de lluvia puede haber algo mejor? Gracias latitybarrios por malcriarme y mimarme en… https://t.co/QUn8Pyr92g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@parkermillsap, @wayneandgraham and @blackberrysmoke come to town on this week's live menu. View all of my top pick… https://t.co/WRNwOvTKw5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenGolliver @SpectrumSN @KingJames hey LeBron if you would put as much effort in your defense as you do as throwin… https://t.co/whVfdzfJAu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PiolinCementero @daniManterola Construido con martillos de $1,500 pesos, y palas de $3,000. Cosa de ponerse una pi… https://t.co/iq9eMzalnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it fair to say that Nancy Reagan was the First Lady who was most like the Church of Scientology? https://t.co/iWQVJxjFO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shalennials  (from last September) Youngsters doing deals....#OOTT #natgas https://t.co/kNjqGvKPXq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaraLeaTrump @IvankaTrump Paid family leave is not a conservative principle, nor is it a constitutional right.  Th… https://t.co/AEQv7yVWaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍😍    😍      😍   😍😍😍 😍      😍    😍   😍      😍 😍      😍    😍😍         😍 😍      😍    😍   😍      😍 😍😍😍    😍      😍… https://t.co/1Fkdbb8Ock]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios Well she’s out of the race already. She doesn’t know?  Where have you been?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Please tell me what ivanka has achieved for the USA! PLEASE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ladydshops @janetshoemake @roosterpisces @Marizellell @CharlieD2749 @DoodlesTrks @azredhen @yrwol7 @WmScottBlair… https://t.co/99hTu3OI8f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllbrightNFL @BleedBadgerRed I would if the Packers got him and Vikings signed Clay Matthews. @SconnieSports may a… https://t.co/RRFeAWEpry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@305FoLife @AnthonyBufka @305FoLife, you're an ass to criticize a guy who lost a child, maybe you should sit this o… https://t.co/jBG7UX5QMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[W our righteous focus on nuclear disarmament talks at #NorthKoreaSummit-also in Asia #Pakistan just shot down two… https://t.co/0CiYv4l2ou]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdanton Does one have to have 10+ years experience on SQL 2014??  #iheardthisonebefore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels thanks Cohen for his 'courageous' testimony — and asks him to retract his attacks on her https://t.co/JQYWa54qWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NikkiHaley @CondoleezzaRice @JohnBrennan @NBAAllStar @NBA Sadly u showed very bad judgment u can't talk with liars… https://t.co/NGwGdxzhYt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yesitsdelicate @swiftstrilogy @sarcasmswiftie *sigh* another failed attempt at a comeback. You guys really need to… https://t.co/9xU71C2Jb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just think how much better you will be as a wrestler and a person. Keep up the good work and great attitude TQ.… https://t.co/eqH2yLbPYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need the place to stay for the last and firs time in my life ,  get my own place tomorrow but the place I stayed tonight blewed up]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheIvanDarko @MidnightRider__ @MySportsUpdate Marketing for his work with mentally challenged? Or marketing for hi… https://t.co/Wj42AWnCdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG, @qantas QF74 (VH-OEH) - a 16 year old 747-438 - sitting on the tarmac at SFO has had failure after failure. No… https://t.co/nCuyOLhesI]]></document><document><![CDATA[The power of three...  https://t.co/GdezgJqicS #greggplummer #ambient #peace #earthmantra @ San Francisco, Californ… https://t.co/gPC6fFcXHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDStateOfMind @RedDirt_Roots @JasonIsbell I would choose Larry Cordle and Jerry Salley]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadreMiaVzla2 @NanaPikki @estebanfg @thatdayTH @jguaido ¿Que se hizo? Eduqueme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren Perhaps if you had not cheated your way through college, you would have learned the difference between science and statistics.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephNSanberg @laurabcapps My dad was a pastor and he received a housing allowance as a significant portion of hi… https://t.co/93NZ7Hhrpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr GET THIS TO JR. ASAP!!    PUSH!! PUSH THIS!!!  SOO? DEMOCRATS SCREAM? VOTER SUPPRESSION???   ANSWER… https://t.co/Kke19gLEoW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MastercardCA #SomethingPriceless #SpringBreakEscape #Staycation  I'm thinking the seats between the benches at a L… https://t.co/DIr1uULHKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imteddybless I bought a girlfriend a knife before.  She did try to murder me with it, so...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DineandDish I discontinued my news feed, some days the news stories were just too depressing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tommyxtopher @SenFeinstein Firat she was still rude and dismissive at best of these young constituents. Second, th… https://t.co/KOWZ9FpVZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got that love for the boy George... @ Seaside, California https://t.co/UF9hetqsr1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Canadian dollar is strong when energy prices are rising thus It could be short lived since Justin Trudeau the P… https://t.co/xAWbNOkkXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t deny that this dog has charm. It’s what makes folk art, folk art... #AntiquesRoadshow https://t.co/Vutb16MPhb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andredaughty @4salmom Looks like a good read. Was it?! Thanks for sharing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If it is indeed Boyle, that’s a great signing. With the amount of two TE sets we’ll see from Greg Roman, Boyles blo… https://t.co/rEadjZZmZB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SitBakN_WatchME Our state has a lower population. Too which got a lot to do with it. But we had a TV show about hs… https://t.co/7ua19kN43v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realMattCosta Her huge expenses were racked up long before becoming speaker. Don't even think of defending that ass hole.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooo nice an invitation to join the parents prom committee. That’s a big NOPE from me. #killme]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally had so much motivation pulled in all nighter researching stuff. If you're not committed go to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did y’all know that Napster is STILL a thing?! Like, damn, is Limewire still hanging in there? Where’s my iPod nano at?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TxsleuthUSA @UnimpressedTX @HSchouten @deaconcruise @BBackerman1 @brendap1949 @MarilynCapps @FactCheckU… https://t.co/JYpADQa93T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManeatGrass @berracahband @obrienmaggie17 @BestEverYou @helen19242686 @SanaMello @RobinsonWoodrow @edengirl58… https://t.co/UIxZWG9nFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LAValiant let’s gooooooo!!! Not the best looking in the ranks this season but it’s still early!! #WingsOut]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paytonbock I’m not sure what happened. I think your super gorgeous. I thought we were friends. I guess not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristamarieyu @mollyjmccook @StophSanders Jen, your a joy to have on #LastManStanding ❤️😊🌈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobandtom @ThatJoshArnold Wont eat for three days?? You pussy!!! People down there and up here eat like that daily!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicaclic @AlianzaCivicaNi Hombré, ¿no hay nadie que le dé su vergazo en la jeta a ese hp?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luluHru @ImabitcSumtimes @8b7bd77a54b54c2 @Larrybarnett777 @PamChapLVPCJOY @MichellleUSA @littletrumpers… https://t.co/uorYVVn1cl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because, you know, let’s make it even harder for folks who need to travel to #GTMO to get there...]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the snow is so good, sometimes this happens. #steamboatskiarea #steamboatsprings #skisteamboat #gondolasquare… https://t.co/whhY8JybG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nous devons faire plus afin de mieux préparer nos jeunes pour la nouvelle économie - voilà (une raison de plus) pou… https://t.co/kYR3ebOhHs]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! The White RACE Russian Women Are The MOST Beautiful In The UNIVERSE!!🇷🇺🌐⚽🌎🇷🇺👑👸🌵🌹💍😋🍒💝😍😘 https://t.co/ZSoigsqUxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a great Valentines Day home. Thank to #outbacksteakhouse  for a great dinner. ❤️❤️ https://t.co/vhijZeTytI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSkipBayless AD and Kyrie won’t work either. Someone’s gotta be Batman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BluntlyPadres I like that we have someone on the team named Ian. Other than that? If he hits more bases clearing d… https://t.co/ttAEldpn0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatorfun1 @Tim_Price_1971 I don't care about BLACK FACE OR KLAN GARB, I AM VERY CONCERNED ABOUT THE KILLING A CHIL… https://t.co/xlH3K5P35h]]></document><document><![CDATA[World's largest bee, once feared extinct, rediscovered in Indonesia https://t.co/quAObNbyMt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IproudCanadian @Floorphiler @DonaldJTrumpJr Ok, I’m bored now let’s call it a day, get up to speed with some actual facts and get back]]></document><document><![CDATA[why am i going to waste my time just waiting for you? If you’re not showing me you WANT ME, then move outta my way.… https://t.co/MsZCmKZ2be]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Party, Who Dis? Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez to star as a superhero in her own comic book. https://t.co/n8iffAOEoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Señor Tequila's in Ashburn, VA https://t.co/qDyYbHn7he https://t.co/nUcVSKNVsa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTWTWellness @bulletproof I used the chocolate protein powder mixed with coffee this morning to make hot mocha.  Not too shabby!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So yo. DMV. Whats the skinny on this snow. We gettin snow snow. Or is this typical Maryland overreact smh. I need to kno.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ctfu cus the dentist just gave me a prescription for Valium cus I was abt to cry😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VincentCrypt46 @777KAB1 @TheDrGinger @_LauraJWilliams @Michigan0323 @rhondamint @smoss319 @JustMy_NameHere… https://t.co/l1KAeAbgW4]]></document><document><![CDATA[The closing bell is a bell that rings to signify the end of a trading session at a stock exchange. I spend most of… https://t.co/LUWHEtnMoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Every hour, 800 people are dying, many after years of suffering... from diseases directly caused by breathing poll… https://t.co/MGxjxl5z2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally anything that could go wrong does go wrong, i.e my tire blew out on the highway as I was going to pick something up for work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBaseGoDJAY @ItsMeNsTincT Your right I’ll hit up faze to play with them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Half of AI startups, aren't. Information on them mostly comes from Third Party aggregators. End state - have a work… https://t.co/jdIFkrso7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget working in medicine and saying things like "I got my first brain tumor today" means something en… https://t.co/jrjtQxKfi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JasonKirkSBN Stephen Curry, Colbert and Hawking. I’ll take on Hawking because he’s recently deceased.]]></document></documents></author>