<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@AliNasri90 اقای علیزاده دیروز گفت تحریم حزب الله هم تقصیر اقای ظریف هست. از حالا به بعد. این اشخاص تمام مشکلات در… https://t.co/YsUBk8iObW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m proud to be here at this year’s Great Place to Work For All Summit - representing @PwCUS with these amazing col… https://t.co/1VWaeiOuz1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear fellow SLPs: OSLA is always advocating on our behalf. Become a member if your aren’t already. This association… https://t.co/MNKlm3420W]]></document><document><![CDATA[The LN PFO will be hosting a Fat Tuesday breakfast for the staff on Tuesday, March 5. Please use the link provided… https://t.co/JLbBsIk60V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okaaaayyyy I discovered overtone deep purple and now I’m too chicken to try it on my hair cuz my hair is reddish br… https://t.co/KVlvFiHPQj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, beautiful...! I’ve know you from when you were a little 17 year old girl from Nizhny Novgorod, Russ… https://t.co/c1DnfaEhog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joejonas Can you please get mine together for me? I'm dying over here!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can and can’t wait experience this type of love for a human being that came from me 😩❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[my daughter deserves the world and that’s what she’s getting and is gonna get for the rest of her life 🤷🏼‍♀️ idc who tf it bothers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who goes all the way to Rome and literally doesn’t want to go do or see anything?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElkeHansen7 @Karrasamelia5 @andrewdecker593 @WarriorAllways @Lynette84649831 @Diane09876 @flowerchild2017… https://t.co/HGKjcpijaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight at Joe E. Newsome High School. 6:30 pm. Distracted driving prevention! It could save a life. https://t.co/Fm9DecvvwS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey everyone I am thinking of babysitting or cleaning so if anyone needs someone like that hit me up now at 9514679… https://t.co/fpP8NpbuYY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSugarLily @TWITMO_INMATE @1RealLori @Bmw2163Heart @tillmantweets @busylizzie48 @ukwildcatfan191 @HarrellRyan1… https://t.co/bAxk9vUBeJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow- what a way to start the week, being fed spiritually.  Coosa Eagles Soar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyKeck @charliekirk11 @GOP IMO it’s never been about Democrats and Republicans - it’s between the globalists… https://t.co/2A709CGF15]]></document><document><![CDATA[Most of the girls in my friend group are funnier than the guys hands down]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the swag @libsyn - love ya’ll as humans and as an organization #podcaster @podfestexpo https://t.co/J2JWzU34S8]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy 21st birthday to the most amazing human being to ever walk this earth. love you the most sweet bb.… https://t.co/VYErV8KfFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um pouco mais de #newyorkfashionweek  #sonow  Evento na cobertura do melhor hotel de #NY ! Vestindo leblancdresses… https://t.co/ube0Jt1inP]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know you have a good relationship with your best friend’s mom when she threatens your boyfriend 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier today I felt a little discouraged that I hadn’t made more progress on my current work project but I’m doing… https://t.co/ADMMXRivVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[no money or materialistic things will never be enough for me to stay in a unhealthy, or unhappy relationship]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dava123 @nelsonbocaranda @dava123 @nelsonbocaranda I am not a collector of published media; otherwise, I could sho… https://t.co/bJlBf95ZaN]]></document><document><![CDATA[#OneDayAtATime is the Best show on @netflix Caution: watching it is addictive! 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[taking a bubble bath and eating chocolates out of a heart shaped box while my grandma sends me lip filler coupons v… https://t.co/ESVCNVXB0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theodramatist This is not an appropriate question during the Duke game]]></document><document><![CDATA[why do ppl gotta shame creatives for having a day job instead of pursuing a creative career.. inc. saying things li… https://t.co/hdcxbnbofL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Corcox02 @JussieSmollett @AOC It was called a moat.  Barriers for protection have and always will be used.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrHallsMusic @ronclarkacademy @mrronclark_ @kimbearden What neat classrooms they have &amp; where is Ron Clark Academy?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My King Cake baby survived two loads of laundry to join me at the Islanders game tonight. #Crazy https://t.co/yuKkFGmCHf]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No matter how good things are going for you, never forget how important it is to stay humble.”  I love this articl… https://t.co/sV54x0SeVF]]></document><document><![CDATA[a lot of niggas claim chicago but on god wouldn’t last a day in the street 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[can someone just knock me out with a fucking frying pan so i can sleep already]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The fact that we’re all still here means no ones ever REALLY had an everything bagel.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BHTVeric @NHLBlackhawks Love this; look at all the Chicago Blackhawks on that list]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_TrumpIN Will anything ever be done to fix voter fraud?? I feel so helpless. It’s not being addressed  that DOJ report said nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesForbes17 @Scott_H_Rome @ElieNYC @AOC No surprise here.  She chose her staff, gave them direction on the prep… https://t.co/ijBb7ieWx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @DonaldJTrumpJr She should have refused to be used like that. If you really aren’t racist, you won’t be c… https://t.co/75gvt1F412]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rubithecat   Goodmorning Rubi, I know is early but I wanted to ask you a question. I have noticed that Twitter is… https://t.co/vI4HKOG5L1]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I said “Pepper, pepper, pepper, salt!” Would you know what I’m talking about?? @phatcabb didn’t and I was shocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lmecham I got two for you! First, check out @TSP_Writing. Second, I’m teaching an online course on experimental po… https://t.co/6coqHtuWHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n0ne0ther @clairlemon People with conscience who see that the globalized, corporate capitalism of today is 1) prod… https://t.co/dRjJLAwilP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wisconsin: putting your own cheese on things that already have cheese on them]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Mamaskatch A Cree Coming of Age by Darrel J. McLeod   “...various meanings, ranging from, 'How strange' to 'It's a… https://t.co/NtzCvpIVuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaGeDown1121 @TheKarmiDance @b8QTRcDJw2hMd4O @lionfirefocus @carlozaktion59 @Makedni @kmitsotakis @NATO GREEK alon… https://t.co/hxfMO6WrjH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nprscottsimon At #SBM2019 (@BehavioralMed), many of us focus on optimizing use of #digital in health care. We disc… https://t.co/khKKTQAFX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TexasFancyBoots @psencikk Absolutely agree! I’m so over this bipolar weather! I start out freezing and dying of he… https://t.co/q7Jd1lnvjw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Wells Fargo team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/aOnU3h8QG8 #IT #Charlotte, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot There goes Dumb and Dumber! Choose Which one Is The Dumbest!!🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[Didn’t think I would need night lights... but this anxiety is fucking with my head..]]></document><document><![CDATA[It really amazes me how little people know about the court system and what things mean. Just because someone pleads… https://t.co/Sri9lNsIaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took the last rose Matt gave me off my dash board like 3 weeks ago, it stayed on the ground for days n days in th… https://t.co/ckr0ykKB11]]></document><document><![CDATA[Small town vibes. Love my city #ilovemcdonough #pastamax https://t.co/MxjzAYr6hU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lion! 🌹💕 #StevenUniverse #stevenuniverselion #lion #pencilart #Pencildrawing #art #ArtistOnTwitter #artistsontwitter https://t.co/MWDtqDLA9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[We watch it every day,we all know it’s true Putin is destroying America from within, specifically from within the W… https://t.co/02hJXFzm0E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bobloch Yes I think a lot of it is baked into the setting, though. With large lecture classes, limited pedagogical… https://t.co/NuDQAlWELn]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS ABSOLUTELY SICK 10 Michigan State vs 7 Michigan | Cinematic Highlight | Men's Basketball https://t.co/PQ1NfhSAow via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[We clean up nice and ready for our next new challenge #attemployee @CerritosPride @N_Vega_Guadian @IamJosephL… https://t.co/x5Sqk0msAW]]></document><document><![CDATA[You keep telling yourself that. Trump has golfed more in one year than President Obama did in 8. What national cris… https://t.co/1SO9BZpDP7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hannaross16 @hayyyyyyyyyyyyp Wooowww no need to get hostile. Just a misunderstanding I think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrisResists Does Pence not realize that he works for the world’s most hated dunce?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amy_braggs You can shout, jump, whatever. You deserve it. Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes we get to ballet early because Ella likes to watch the grown up class. #ellagram #babybird #ballet… https://t.co/ULjObVwhh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Custodial Services Worker - Reliant Medical Group (Fallon)-EVS - Ready Med P… https://t.co/Dn49Rxj3j4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy National Margarita Day (and no plastic straw day) everyone! I went out with a couple of great friends to get… https://t.co/6yco4dXCxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out the feedback we got from our annual @nnlmner Regional Advisory Council Meeting. (Thread)]]></document><document><![CDATA[First #PP2019 pick up from @TandiaTweets Ancaster and Upper Wentworth locations! Full car + beautiful donations = h… https://t.co/tHfVBUNTDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am all for learning from each other: and learning for each other. Learning is a gate way to a Consciousness of in… https://t.co/2Vo3OGGpZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cold and wet didn’t stop us from enjoying a stroll through the streets and alleys of downtownbrenham. @ Brenham Dow… https://t.co/5dSc7ITRmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[R2R Day Post #11... former @leadworthy students gave up their day off from school to help @BeckendorffJH get ready… https://t.co/YteHrcsfxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hanpansy I’m so proud of you for being smart with your Girl Scout cookie choices]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jim Morrison said that the purpose of art was not to observe, but to co-create. I love going to a show that truly m… https://t.co/eE4ntBaORf]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is the same question I keep asking myself. When Are They Going To Be Held Accountable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I genuinely care for people but once it’s time to reciprocate, there’s nobody to be found. It’s always about someon… https://t.co/mjTQtkV5Zg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi yes I don’t know what just happend to the people in the dorm below me but like...dying does not mean you get to… https://t.co/aj1avO0w0o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to be collaborating on this meaningful project!  #Repost seven13films with get_repost ・・・ 📣NEWS! 🗓 Yesterday… https://t.co/c3mx6XBC1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hate to admit it but my fav show #TheWalkingDead has turned into an #estrogenfest @RealJamesWoods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillCThomas Used to visit Aunt Jenny's grave in high school. She'd be a fun topic as well. https://t.co/sQlFqj58qw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well if it doesn't kill you ,it will make you immune to Measles! Funny that none of the Cancer Researchers haven't… https://t.co/yytzuq0LfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I only had one beer with dinner, ONE, and I officially think that means I’m growing up???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @YonkersCC for two great shows!! I’ll be back!  #comedy #funnygirl #leatherleggings #whitebeforelaborday… https://t.co/dTNGHK9ZJR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yashar My eyes are sweating I related to this so much. My nutrition teacher told me my brain thinks faster than it… https://t.co/nQ7CFqomxe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Skatunenetwork @Moon_Lit_Ska I’m 954 at heart &gt;:(( I just had to get 561 recently cause my parents are communists]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dlbernson I will always remember @merck CEO Ken Frazier’s kindness and compassion. He was/is the real deal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JABeltranFelix @CDE_PRI_Durango @AlyGamboa @CNC_Durango @EnriqueBenitezO @RocioRebolloM @hernandezderas… https://t.co/fnn7oCBB5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @ericbolling She can't even control her husband! How is she going to do anything about the opioid crisis??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToaFraser A trailer and time for naps will be written into all of my contracts from now on 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@conor64 But in all seriousness, don't you have to be fundamentally kind of delusional to run for president... period?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmBoomerStrong @barb71 @FMedic921 @bluefamilyprays @ElkeHansen7 @KathyDutton16 @laker477 @SimonSaysMoo @elow2K… https://t.co/7wmVJtYQ4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prosecutors testifying in support of criminal justice reform..... its a new day #moleg https://t.co/k77yS5c6WZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[UPDATE: The road is now open. Oil-dri absorbent is down on the road @KDKA]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very cartwheel 🤸‍♀️ worthy sale! #sold #riverfront #riverfrontproperty #listedandsold #louiselists #louisesells… https://t.co/1qgoj9Rtol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t take anyone’s statement that they are “striving for greatness” at face value. Some people really mean that th… https://t.co/eLaG8uVqpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BGbloggers @TheUncorkedLib I know. I’ve been feeling this way too. It’s still tough especially if it’s a long time… https://t.co/91u1jAF8WS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not only is kindness always possible- but it is something we can all improve upon -#growthmindset  https://t.co/k6AIxtQ9du]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fantastic five-course gourmet dinner thesaltedpig with my Valentine of 18 years. ♥️ ♥️ ♥️ ♥️ #foodie #foodstagram… https://t.co/8PyPCkZNfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[- 3:49 1Q - Tech wins the face-off man up and kicks it to McEvoy for the fast break finish  6-0 Tech]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything more non-user friendly or disorganized than the iTunes podcast app? I HATE it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday’s Field Trip to @mwdh2o was once again an amazing experience! Students learned about water and the importanc… https://t.co/OZTSG6rM6f]]></document></documents></author>