<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@patdennis But they did have those few beautiful weeks with the nitro cold brew]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where is this year going? We have now entered Lent. . . I always try to create Christian Art along with my whimsica… https://t.co/lovaNVuAiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’ve never seen this show”  “It’s a Netflix original.”   “I don’t watch Netflix.”  “Ok well that’s how you’ve neve… https://t.co/SPN6Wg4hsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaterinaKestem1 @SkyBoivin @EssentialBron @Birdy_Willeke @imcorinnemec @SPN_Stargate777 @Classichassis… https://t.co/DkBuLzxFQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@denisesaturn  Sending my She-ro love, respect, gratitude.    XOXO https://t.co/BgQRNje5CS]]></document><document><![CDATA[What if there’s a Getaway Car MV and it’s @taylorswift13 whole journey with @BigMachine and it’s a farewell MV!!! F… https://t.co/YNEcEaIAWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Capitalism won independence, WW1, WW2 and built this country. “We will never be a socialist country!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had the honor to train all the TRPD at SUPERIOR FITNESS. It was an amazing experience and so much fun! Every offi… https://t.co/YoTA5XuRiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stunkles the magician! Tag your favorite magician in the comments below.  🎩  . . . . . . . . . . #ventriloquist… https://t.co/xVDHz97mB7]]></document><document><![CDATA[How this kid gonna go to the toilet I help him up and he wanna say “okay go away pls” 😒😒😒😒 ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I’m not funny because I’m a woman but don’t be rude, at least give me a pity laugh.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How #TheBachelor search for Colton should have ended: https://t.co/ty3jcCKaWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had my hair dyed black for so many years I want something new any suggestions on a new hair color?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatRU4USA @horseloveriowa @tictoc My integrity???  😂😂😂 wth do you know about me?  Nothing!  Why do you people alw… https://t.co/1vSlprpQtT]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beautiful #roomwithaview at #hotelxtoronto #hotelxtorontobylibraryhotelcollection #royallepage… https://t.co/ZS7pb3QGI6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @SpeakerPelosi it's a good thing that these people are a fake emergency! Build the wall now @POTUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JLo Being bombarded by the “big news!” So ... was it the clock @TheEllenShow gave you that did it?!? 🤣 💎  💍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let me on B-2 to fly over mountains 🏔. Sure I might not find them but I might get them out of their holes 🕳. Then w… https://t.co/szg9vQngvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@KennyYuko: if @GovMikeDeWine plan does not include public transportation, I want to know why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't just blame Big Pharma the DEA has more responsibility for closing pain mgt and terrorizing docs - no concern… https://t.co/uenuW1tm0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yay! Shout out to @NetZeroLee 2nd graders who joined us in this challenge too! We would love some pictures of what… https://t.co/DtJ7TNBe9h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to #RyanCoogler and his wife Get the scoop https://t.co/NaMkI8PNWG https://t.co/RAvtrp3z7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe that tomorrow makes a year since I first met jordan. Ahhh, so in love with him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The true embarrassment is Joe Biden the Groper Racist  blathering his bonehead nonsense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Derek: that’s a dope ass thetarade shirt. Me: do you want it? I got it for your brother but he doesn’t want to wear… https://t.co/Y9CKJ7YDdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just over heard my mom say downstairs by herself “you’re being a little bitch right now @ Alexa, I’m about to throw you out the window”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making coffee ☕️☕️#Coffeetime (@ Da Penguin Kitchen in Marana, AZ) https://t.co/cuAhc2b59t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gosh damn why tf did i let that nigga nut in me? Now i gotta deal with a bitter mf for the rest of my life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can't you think of more important things to discuss? This has gotten very old. This issue must mak… https://t.co/Wvjp5WvSBy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Schultz came across ed as a detached phony. I don't understand how PPL like him become CEOS of successful countries… https://t.co/VQrw3nCRv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't this interview be alikened to a contest to see who can tell the biggest lie? Is Liawatha really an Indian… https://t.co/uVC1iAkmrE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@s_malcolmson @NicholasSimons @ClippersHockey @jjhorgan @1069thewolf Ha ha ha! better get up early! #NaughtyMLAs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe this to be the absolute truth. God has a plan. #GodIsInControl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndreaGil55555 @tonyposnanski @CoryBooker Yes, by the looks of their girth, some veggies would be good for them😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiking in The Valley of Fire. @ Valley of Fire State Park https://t.co/7rPba05XHu]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s an all-Women audience tonight. Whoot! They’ve got great ideas, too~]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is one spot on the map that makes the sound appear high when it’s really low. It’s the pavilion with a respaw… https://t.co/jiDPZjTAOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thrilled to be in DC for the introduction of the #StateofBabies yearbook with my partners at @ZEROTOTHREE this morning.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We saw an interview with you today! Enjoyed it, and your mission! Never let your age diminish your calling! I had r… https://t.co/Oj09DHukVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bruh I remember when I was little looking at the lil bubbles and digging these lil sand crabs out but hell na fuck… https://t.co/GKaF1TwaTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adulting is when you remember to cancel your free trial subscription before you are charged. #lifegoals]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inezfrid @nytimes @D_Chamberlain @DiscoverMartin On my way. First leg of the journey: https://t.co/u9LbGSfs9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[My parents bought a juicer and stocked up on fruits. Next time I come home watch they become vegan 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[My seat for the next two hours. #ufc235 @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/vPGNFMzllK]]></document><document><![CDATA[reid from criminal minds “this quote is in a lot of self love books, i read 22 today”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally feels like I’m going to be pregnant forever. I swear if I’m not at LEAST 4cm dilated on Monday... I’m los… https://t.co/4spbNZ6rfd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gonna get even more light blonde in my hair next week. 🤩 I don’t think I’ll ever be a brunette again, I just like t… https://t.co/egEs12IKuv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try not to be that person (and I’m several months late on this) but #AStarIsBornMovie was one of the most overrated movies I’ve ever seen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[. #gabrielahearst finale @gabrielahearst #nyfw. @ Spring Studios https://t.co/gbzLl4lKZS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially going to Yellowstone in May and I cannot wait to finally travel out west🤩🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobianeM @WalnutCreekES @WCPSSTeam @WCPSS @WCPSS_TitleI @WakeESM @krackley1 @veekai1 @T1Director It was absolutely… https://t.co/OyM0bU4IHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Marvelousiggy No cats. But yea on the notebooks you can't write in cuz they're too nice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SDFan2378 @padres_faithful It’s not unpopular and those who think Reyes should start over Hunter have me scratchin… https://t.co/qGcdOZW5bT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quiero despertar con ganas de darte lo mejor de mí, quiero despertar junto a ti. Quiero amarme.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many insights for anyone in higher ed. An honor to moderate this panel with Louis Soarez from @ACEducation Kate… https://t.co/SP81IPrQYS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristinkuffner The last part of this tweet made me laugh really hard even though it shouldntve]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Women’s Day to all you amazing women. @ Spring Valley, Nevada https://t.co/nkYvK9Kwyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm  scared, I just saw a lady with a jaguar,  EMT was on the scene ......]]></document><document><![CDATA[the team members said.  The pressure is more pronounced at events like the World Government Summit where new ideas… https://t.co/jEkxh50cAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JThrust @magpepper @donna_zimmerman @MuslimIQ @neelysgracey @FBI @FBIHouston @houstonpolice Oops wrong Neely. My a… https://t.co/cvjJTD2vlD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need help @aaroncarter How do I request you to please come to Grand Rapids Michigan?  Any information from anyone… https://t.co/LmJxbaKJRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Muriel395Muriel @mindysexton0109 @Hotincal38 Take a look at the population in her district.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamAracingfan @SloppyYellowPod @bobpockrass @jeff_gluck @LVMotorSpeedway @TimBrock_DtD @jimmywaggs3 I hope he is a nascar fan 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming Soon! Odessa Pool 🏊🏽‍♀️ 🏡!  4 🛏 3 🛀 3 🚘 garage  Exterior and interior recently painted , gourmet kitchen, ne… https://t.co/xZiDU0F7f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomanP11 @voxdotcom @mattyglesias The new people wouldn’t live in the housing 0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BearHawk73 @captainmarvel @brielarson shes so awesome! another great movie thats currently out with a badass femal… https://t.co/M9hjIyzEJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Video 7/Day 7: I have a cold 😞 #creative #confessionsofanactress #cold #snapchat #love #feelbetter #mood #instagood… https://t.co/yXYXQwA8nT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been using @turbotax for years and glad they have #TaxHero! #Sweepstakes]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dance Team placed 1st at State for the 10th consecutive year, receiving 1st in both Pom and Kick. https://t.co/IBJG31Nup8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krolander 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤣🤣🤣 where in tf do they come up with this shit lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great show by “Uncle” @ImCharlieWilson who asked people to tag him on social media. The former Gap Band lead singer… https://t.co/4PWMokC9w1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the first hour of #hotpod summit, the key industry conference on podcasts, and already clear that a lot of fol… https://t.co/BlPfTNFBf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pinkpeonyjoy @mfow020 @tedcruz And I resent your generalization that the mom doesn’t want the baby. There are many… https://t.co/YHr4burWZK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@M_pritchh @cuntyspice_ @BrookeeCC I don’t wanna think about my grandma having sex period]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinelogan there’s a quote from one of the broadway versions in which she states she’s “a gemini with a double cap… https://t.co/ukJFgtjRqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@horowitz39 @whpresscorps Even if the Democrats did do this, IT WAS THE GREED OF COLLEGES THAT RAISED THE PRICES. T… https://t.co/iHFA3aXZX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antontheweenie I'm the birthday girl!!!  Thanks, Carsten! https://t.co/fPzvn16Vu8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LewisBlum What I’m saying is George Smith Towing, your uncle’s company, is a horribly corrupt institution that che… https://t.co/A7IkB2nFVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[when I listen to tigers jaw I feel like I look like this still: https://t.co/qxjYS7IV2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good time to vote! #DontMindMeImJustWatchingArrowAndShippingOlicity 🚢💘🎯👓 #Arrow #Olicity]]></document><document><![CDATA[They said this trooper has been hit 4 times and he has only been with ISP for 2 years. SLOW DOWN PEOPLE!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cocowilk18 @ayerya_01 still mad y’all never slapped since into me honestly 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richardmoore73 @velonews In my experience, The only thing harder than asking for help is Receiving it. Rest In Perfect Peace, Kelly 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OTHdiary @teespring @savannahgochoel @sydtinch good thing we already have these]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wegohealth 2/I had hope the Duchess of Cambridge would have made it a focal point if Mental Health as a new Mother… https://t.co/hApICisby2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad I don’t work tomorrow and my son is out for spring brake lol This going to be a good week I can tell 😏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlliterAndy @parkerrsimmons Reminds me of senior thesis time lol  Interesting things happen during late night work delirium 😆👌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryPolitics @kinseyholley And she’s starting as one of many editors. She’s not going to be in charge of CNN’s political coverage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THEY WERE PROBABLY THE ONES BREAKING INTO MY APARTMENT WITH A KEY, AS WELL AS PROBABLY THE BLONDE AND TALL MAN WHO… https://t.co/iBJ44zvXkK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Présentement en train d'attendre pour entrer sur le plateau du #DailyShow avec @Trevornoah . J'ai hâte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sotoreyesj Te juro que después vas a extrañar eso, ya que tengas trabajo y estés lleno de responsabilidades, DISFRUTALOOOO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Griz @NASSfestival Omg you get to reunite with Too Many T’s! Catch Loyle Carner for me please]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do you teach someone who has never seen that there is such a thing as Color? @OneFallenAngelM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes trying to get a candid of Sean without him knowing is like trying to photograph wildlife. Just as you pre… https://t.co/mX71iVB3Rd]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @kelly_kmbrennan @krislynnkelly @Molly_Boddy @MayorJoyceCraig @meredithnyoung @GlennonDoyle @Veg_MD @alange710… https://t.co/t9j4hBhyhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing my students share their love of books at their Book Prom. @KirkElementary #kirkroar https://t.co/KA4NboIebP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am blown away with how incredibly strong all the female characters are. The writing and the acting is just amazin… https://t.co/lwQnro9QPj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alwaysDandie If you want, take a walk as far as you feel comfortable and take photos of picturesque views of the snow. That's what I did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Despues de tantos Fake videos de youtube lo encontre  https://t.co/YXGqKR2Jrn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielSchulman @KCGibbons I’m SO ready to go back to a time where headlines like this are actually shocking.  #crazyisthenewnormal]]></document></documents></author>