<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@HPEschools And you know the sleet, ice pellets and freezing rain combo happening right now.  #snowday #Canada #ONStorm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, another birthday in the book and I couldn’t be more grateful to have spent it with this group of people. Also… https://t.co/vrMkmvp8Pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Blame It On The Boogie by @Jacksons on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/XL2Z58IRZ0 https://t.co/X92GG88Ygy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the asshole in chief. But you won’t read this because you can’t!!! Sad!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Lord, All I want it to witness Lupton Magic with @kaelynbuskey 💜💜💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/S6o2iIhUUb @KidsHopeJAX is ready to help address the impact of trauma on our youth by offering trainin… https://t.co/WfLAWHPEWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Azaleas in full bloom around here.....one of my favorite things this time of year https://t.co/tliPd7wLLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buddhist68 @NaphiSoc @MaQualeSantone @JuddLegum @IlhanMN Thank you! And bring tgis to the floor is wrong because o… https://t.co/P6CK4n2bvq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really interesting paper suggesting the long term child penalty for women is the result of the uneven burden of car… https://t.co/iBYOnZlntt]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Encourage #Girls to Lift Each Other Up, Instead of Tearing Each Other Down | A Mighty Girl #GOTR goals 💕… https://t.co/DfpItlQAYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Better to be independent thinkers than @GOP Trump loving automatons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@geminicutie01 @KyleRichards @KyleRichards did not bring it up first. And pet adoptions should be handled w privacy… https://t.co/hiLIUIrLf9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Love living 5 minutes from this place ♡ https://t.co/b34D8ajW5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pxwhittle Here in Georgia, they've recently charged Jenna Garland with deliberately delaying responses to FOIA req… https://t.co/r95LdaBW9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_lightbrigght_ DM me the recipe 😭 I swear I’ve been trying to make some because the edibles I be buying be garbage 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MingGao26 @NoAppleIndian @GeorgePapa19 For real this time? If so... let her be so mad she spills ALL the tea!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian @jordynwoods Lmao ok Khloe if that helps you sleep at night 😩 https://t.co/ypDixUfbkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here’s @NewsdayOpinion ‘s take on the Amazon deal. Editorial: Nothing to celebrate https://t.co/W3hDAAidww]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking off Love Of Reading Week with a visit from a parent who happens to be our fabulous IC reading about goals v… https://t.co/AMu8vnM2Pe]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ICE can no longer use information sharing to arrest and #deportation of parents and sponsors, at least through Sep… https://t.co/lLKiMCStPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[shrek is honestly the most humble thing ever. i love him. fiona is lucky]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed a @womensmarch petition declaring a #NationalEmergency to Defend Democracy. Sign here: https://t.co/qsReCGp6Qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had one of those weird drawing days where almost everything I drew in my sketchbook didn’t “feel” right. Ugh 👎🤔🤢]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, Roger Stone? After a gag order, you posted a threat to the federal judge hearing your case? You posted a… https://t.co/zqWGwDMDW8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a new friend at work today 🖤 . . . #toothless #toothlessthedragon #howtotrainyourdragon #howtotrainyourdragon3… https://t.co/vM4ojvmodL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbrown Saturday August 4th, 2018 @ @TMobileArena Las Vegas, NV w/ opening acts @Jacquees @richthekid @6LACK… https://t.co/njgwTH8q2N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissAusten @tcm Yeah, never was a fan of UP due to those first mins. Almost worst than Bambi...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mostly horrifying because I was on the chair lift with some friends and Josh Groban had randomly decided to take us to dinner that night.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat won’t stop meowing and it’s 5 am and I have no idea what she wants.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out BULLY BLESSED - T SHIRTS &amp; SNAPBACK SET from Hog Mob Merchandise! https://t.co/XwqsE4G7hA #bully]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Max_n_Ruby @fcsok92 @OHFCSO @OfficialLivePD @LivePdFans @danabrams @LHVanhorn Oh Ruby!  Get em Ruby!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh ya those are the questions, conspiring with foreign powers?and we paid for security for this enemy of Our Country]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best Adaptation: Alice, for never exaggerating the details of her breakup earlier today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sweetnonnie He was never impeached! And he was never prosecuted or served prison.]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they are off for the day, nice the bus picks them right up at our door. Moms are going to have a “mom day”. Bea… https://t.co/e4V4XiVTx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbcsnl went too far with their meat “skit”.  Not funny.  @thelittleidiot]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have been encouraging my students to submit to the @DyerIvesPoetry competition, but I had to practice what I prea… https://t.co/SW7EUw3kAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[How y’all going on spring break yet graduated from college ?? https://t.co/M9k3LcATHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you're born with skills it shows! I didn't see this coming. I am shocked he made the basket backwards. #Talent… https://t.co/ldD6q7J3jK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @RepAdamSchiff @realDonaldTrump Think of the long strong wall and infrastructure repair or replaceme… https://t.co/SzPoANc4oC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChipotleTweets @WineyMelissa Same thing happened to me yesterday https://t.co/0T53uBaXPx]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Irish #irishblessing #home #family #luisachocolatiere https://t.co/PAhvykaVgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it should be America first. A choice was made and this is the consequence @IWF @IWV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KevOnStage Hey tweet a Blessed evening to you and that looks disgusting and terrible]]></document><document><![CDATA[it's 2019 and baby shark just played at a bar and suddenly everyone forgot how to act https://t.co/2IMQgV7F7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk know why, but it was at this very moment as Ta'teanna stood here admiring this mural, all it stood for and the… https://t.co/RTpwlyxItI]]></document><document><![CDATA[This how I hype myself and by myself 🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️🤦🏽‍♀️😂😂😂💫😂🤪🤪🤪🤣🤣🤣 https://t.co/MeFOKnCdvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZubaidaAKBR Hi @ZubaidaAKBR, the Afghan government has said that women will make up 30% of the next loya jirga or… https://t.co/pzBSLfcRQD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Of course I start getting sick the day I have a night off from work 🙃🤦🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mountain lion attack: Colorado runner describes suffocating animal with his foot - CNN https://t.co/OHNGmZ2rw7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait for my bf to give me a million kisses and hugs and orgasms later 💓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gobierno de Venezuela suspende jornada laboral y clases por apagón masivo https://t.co/RliNsouCOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jkirchner12 @BrandiGlanville @lisarinna Thank You!!! Someone I agree w. LVP causes most of the Drama.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was hauling ass from CC and I think I hit someone's dog in between sinton and skidmore. I feel bad, I was going 85 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @DurangoPolice for being very sweet and calming today when I got in my accident... it made the situatio… https://t.co/6m4FgOJmSz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I still taste you on my lips, yeah I do Last night we made love 'til the Sun came”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel like I could maybe write a memoir entitled “So you’ve decided to cut it close again.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[At first, I felt sorry for the old cardinal to go to jail because I love old people but then I thought about abuser… https://t.co/zNyRBzxjUL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #SundayBunday to my Favorite Hoe With a Heart On, the super sexy @TheWesleyWoods 💜💜 https://t.co/gUtLD3yq59]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nala got a lil Valentine’s Day bubble bath so she’s all pretty &amp; smells nice for daddy 😂❤️🛁🎀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barnini America is tired of the crap! People that know they are busted(of dirty 2-faced swamp makers) that dare U.… https://t.co/3o3VnfyoMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jayden: CAN I HEAR IT FOR LIFT?  Jayden: oh wait its not LIFT its L.I.F.T. Here at with con we like to shorten things]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kingkrv12 @FaisonGarrett @FaisonGarrett you really are so very talented. Super proud of both of you boys!]]></document><document><![CDATA[-"If you have any problems, please let us know. Have a great trip Miss. Taah." -"Thanks you too. Or uh... Umm. Have… https://t.co/tv0Xv6ofHv]]></document><document><![CDATA[New from @ABC News' “The Investigation” podcast: Michael Cohen’s lawyer Lanny Davis says his client is a “transform… https://t.co/cP2pijKDn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Costaball Exactamente, el Presidente demostró ser muy sensible ante los ciudadanos que se expresan en las redes en… https://t.co/tFbpYsyqDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@planetepics @realDonaldTrump Let Freedom Ring Dear God Let Freedom Ring 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some shots from the orchid show at #missouribotanicalgarden #orchidshow  #art #photographer #photographerlife… https://t.co/upha5NnnKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@JohnCornyn I urge you to reject David Bernhardt as Interior Secretary. If appointed, he will DESTROY the Endanger… https://t.co/WdHTOn060U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mollie_Bednarek I am gonna crash hard tonight zzzz mother duties never end]]></document><document><![CDATA[@morningmika loved David Schuster back on the network. @Morning_Joe @MSNBC @DavidShuster]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its so weird coming back home and not being able to go to my house anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[can’t wait to cut my hair short again so I can like it for a week and then be mad at myself for the next year until it grows back!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[EXACTLY!!!  If @POTUS @realDonaldTrump lies to his WIVES, of course he’ll lie to US!  It ain’t rocket science!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way Back Wednesday: 4 years ago I was on The Hill to meet with Lawmakers and advocate for the real estate industry.… https://t.co/6RnDQmZXXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuinceMountain I grew up in Oshkosh, learned to drive on 41. I was dumb enough to risk back roads sometimes, but e… https://t.co/svk6MQaJ0x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Amen. But ymbut ya know the right say that’s socialism. It makes no sense at all. It’s like they ar… https://t.co/FlYXU4p1w4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyroneStreete2 @MistyKitty3 @BonnesenKim @kring5897 @Stop_Trump20 Didn't his former employee on The Apprentice say… https://t.co/JPDHT7PkkP]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Our anxiety does not come from thinking about the future, but from wanting to control it.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshuaostroff I’m of course waaaay too young for this 😉....but oh man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paula: have u ever taken greyhound??   Me: I have taken flyaway   Paula: https://t.co/asYPnI0aFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @Jantxnc Not Jerry or shifty shiff They haven't gotten over Hillary loosing yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance America if Mueller is gone we are lost this can not happen  I want too know every word in all reports Mueller has touched]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP THE CHALLENGE: Celebrity moms like @KimKardashian are begging @YouTube to stop the “Momo Challenge” that encou… https://t.co/4GW3g6ShcF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has @SpeakerPelosi stayed sober ? I thought maybe but then the stutters started as did the the mumbles]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to make a short film for @solangeknowles self taught Houston woman (black) film maker. One day y’all. One day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amywilson @danaMpatton @leslielone22 @terrencemcd @carla_astudi @kevinaskevin @gioia1234567 They have a veggie burger now? 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @CyrilRamaphosa @tito_mboweni @GovernmentZA for committing R157M for free sanitary products for school girls… https://t.co/B7imz501qd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me encanta mandarle fotos mias haciendo cualquier tontada a mi mejor amigo💙]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Bullsnation #BullsRoadtrip to Detroit  #CHIvsDET https://t.co/VtuUrsxILY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darth_Maelstrom @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump I need to turn off spellcheck and re- read before posting.  Traito… https://t.co/gvlrHkHCSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YankeeYardbird @Tia6sc Thinking, they had lots of skeletons in their closets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Charli_ChaCha @boxycharm Congratulations! Your probably the only one! 🎇🎆🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@josephstern I gotta think it’s a lack of established  historical consensus thing?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love is calling! ♥️ Happy Valentine’s Day! @ Tampa Museum of Art https://t.co/7epuL3BtxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoarseWisperer The storms on Sunday stranded us in Disney, so we got an unexpected extra vacation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are we gonna talk about Salma Hayek’s new owl tho https://t.co/jGHShTi8m7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McKenzieMosley if I get abs one day I’m gonna thank my anger and anxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ron_eisenberg @KENS5 @VinnieKENS5 @GinaEisenberg Thanks @ron_eisenberg !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s gym victory...increased weight on my decline sit ups. They were hard to do, but I did it!! #fitnessjourney… https://t.co/v1Ksj0juMl]]></document></documents></author>