<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I'm at 24 Hour Fitness Super Sports in Walnut, CA https://t.co/ZVaZZhYoij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewScheer We are in the midst of #climatechaos, Scientists, doctors and kids understand this, for some reason y… https://t.co/D2iRPt6bvk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RicardoMonrealA @lopezobrador_ @senadomexicano urge terminar con aduanas mordida de vicente fox  gil diaz--agreden… https://t.co/jjUhQF7Ob3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at it again. Sunday group session with @MattWigleyLS in #theLAB 🎯 @SMCHS_Football https://t.co/pDNpGFb0AW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaqi_B_2001 Omg this looks AMAZING. It's like when I play with my dolls (yes I still do that lol)  Love ya Barbie girl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[brother, beer, memories and unresolved mystery. the stuff of life  #greatful]]></document><document><![CDATA[A flower on my afternoon walk through Carlsbad @ Carlsbad, California https://t.co/h2ZfqqMe0h]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DaylightSavingsTime cast very long shadows. North Summit Snow Fields -Rips @bigskyresort https://t.co/vyZj23MlPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enterprise has a *very* different meaning @devnexus and that's part of what makes it the most awesomest tech conference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life’s too short to hate your job and what you do everyday. When you look back at your life over the years, you’ve… https://t.co/G5ocEBD51L]]></document><document><![CDATA[108 women have run NASCAR races since 1949. She is only the second winner.  Not a bad way to start a career. https://t.co/1L4H6skE7n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bryanallenmd @BernieSanders Bernje is energetic and has a vision that is embraced by younger populace.  There is t… https://t.co/8CcYoLvRyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KantsImperative How much does DeAngelo Russell get? Obviously depends on Nets not landing 2 FAs themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who will stand this close to me after workouts is definitely in it for the long haul. This is the best Valen… https://t.co/nlI3DgmJR9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rained all day yesterday and today...blue skies. #loveflorida #dontmissthesnow @ Sarasota, Florida https://t.co/eCahkP60U0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just got a vid in my sms that...you know what... https://t.co/REDF3xwgRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s interesting we have heard very very little about anything specific in Robeson County over 2.5 days]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACadogan_NZ @chadcookpt Differentiate bewteen clusters &amp; CPRs....or how do u explain that to students???  Help. Thx!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZachViana @escapepan4two @JRobinzson @Adam_A_F @renfamous I have no idea who that is. So I don’t have the authority.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubLuckyStarr Had several dejavu moments reading the last part.  Reminded me of my younger days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Christ Church Dallas (Episcopal) - @christchurchdal in Dallas, TX https://t.co/HJKrsUl4W0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buen día mis amigos madrugadores, que sea una excelente semana, a darle con ánimo, mañana fresca con el ir de la lu… https://t.co/Db3I4jI8eN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A huge thank you to our entire @StJohnsU family ... we always need you with us! 🔴⛈]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im glad harden lost the streak.. smh 0-10 3s. Thank god we were playing the hawks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol So pitiful. This is such a sad tweet. So many great things happening in this country (employment up, w… https://t.co/5lIncoJIxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to rautodetail for the great wash on the car today looks amazing after bad weather! #cleancar #bathtime… https://t.co/CbN9WBDMkM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah and friends relaxing before their performance on Saturday at Texas A&amp;M Corpus Christi. https://t.co/HisbzWIEZI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deutsch15 I’m not buying $400 Phish tickets. If I wanted that, I’d just get some of these platinums.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You teach people how to treat you by what you allow, what you stop, and what you reinforce.  —  Tony Gaskins  victo… https://t.co/s6cOagEr7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[KD and Kyrie chop it up postgame   #CUsRise #DubNation   . . #nba #thisiswhyweplay #warriors #mikeanddrewsports… https://t.co/sKGkxS7H4w]]></document><document><![CDATA[22 months went into making our first ever game an unbelievable experience. We scored EIGHT goals by four people. Ou… https://t.co/IfOKMk04O7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7SCOTS @UlyssesTrust @hrfca @7SCOTS_CO @The_SCOTS @ArmySportsLTRY @ArmySportASCB @Fighting51st sce Ten]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizzoSober @trubiskytits @NationalLeagueH @DingDongsAllDay Since spring training means so much to you Cubs fans https://t.co/1PgmTnVtLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both, but I still prefer my « chosen weapon » to « slay the monster of Ignorance », the book 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great podcast: @ginsburgtapes. Uses audio of SCt arguments by Ruth Bader Ginsburg from her ACLU days, annot… https://t.co/wtB9Hm2BpU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think this is a concern in all federations when it comes to development of the women's football referees. England… https://t.co/pEVb5dEE3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@real_defender @lindanye6615 Because he didn’t give a shit about what the Swamp or the liberal ass kissing MSM thou… https://t.co/B3ejnk1fXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judging from the dialogue in his movies there is a distinct possibility that m.night shyamalan has never actually h… https://t.co/NOYGzlVLoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRsBBQ JR. You probably knew my dad Darrell Wright.   My brothers Mike and Daryl Wright are class of 72 My cousin… https://t.co/TiXvDZC4s9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ONC_HealthIT head Dr. Rucker tells @hipaasummit audience that TEFCA rule currently in clearance. #MGMAAdvocacy wil… https://t.co/oMzlTeuXrC]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AlexTrebek Prayers are needed. I have seen how quickly this cancer can take a person. Very sad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Disappointed that none of my local reps felt the need to publicly condemn @NYGovCuomo and his disparaging remarks o… https://t.co/23rry8DSCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Race this is the card that has been used by Democrats for over 60 years. And now that th… https://t.co/gu89kIEsFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 hot ladies purposely stopped by me and then became elusive at @CityGrillEast. But they don't know it's different… https://t.co/6CKJ6Nqo1d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m unfollowing anyone who is not being positive on here. Letting yall know right now😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @SouthwestAir cancelled my flight late at night. Was this due to poorly maintained aircraft? Or are the unions p… https://t.co/NQ8XYQXsyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabiesFree @BBWave2018 @hach_g @grantstern @eliehonig @PreetBharara You are right age shouldn't matter and I hate… https://t.co/iHeq9elJsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks bad at #STL’s @shakeshack but the good news is @mightyjofoto reports no injuries, the red stuff is transmissi… https://t.co/7mvxDksQns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HowardSchultz is another old white billionaire. Sound familiar? We don't need or want another one.   😠😠😠😠😠😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you have a real bond with someone, it's not easy to just stop thinking about them. You seem to deal with a lot… https://t.co/25uhfDS7AZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RefugeeNik @thehill @TheHillOpinion Now show me a photo of her dead. Stop the stupid and damaging conspiracies. Ma… https://t.co/xCQYQNVzAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[My exterior : beard, long hair, tattoos, all black clothing, snake skin boots.  My interior: https://t.co/ynG12VSY3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Treilly1298Tara @CNN I’m from there it’s the truth every time they stroked they threatened GM. This is also the sa… https://t.co/Rlpfyu7lnz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndoverWarriors @Andover_HS @andoverhsap @EagleTribSports @GlobeSchools @BostonHeraldHS @MassHSHockey One heck of… https://t.co/pOcXXS64sx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good for him and to hell with anyone involved with imprisoning this man or tracking him down. Let him live in peace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFive It seems Hoda Muthana US citizenship will turn on these facts, or lack there off: A person born in the Uni… https://t.co/2xqOc2ctUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skau61 @RedactedTonight Someone is fooling you TC I didn't say anything like that...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeWest52499669 @arvia2u @MatchaGreenTe16 @Ilhan Hello friend he backbit up with documents man.  Obviously he tell… https://t.co/O3oEY24xkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Placere coniungere velle me ipso a Felix dies natalis meae matertera Hunnicutt Verna, quae celebratur eius 90th nat… https://t.co/g8TvFeGXZk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a great afternoon with Big Brothers Big Sisters of Central Ohio at their event, Bowl for Kids’ Sake! Thanks to… https://t.co/EWgbhz7hu4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga Perform "Shallow" at the 2019 Oscars! https://t.co/CsTF2vJCzC via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[We all know #Trump is implicated when #Epstein pleaded the 5th and #tRump is likely one of the big names not being… https://t.co/b4amguOHGx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting over an hour for my @jimmyjohns order so much for “freaky fast”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch "Anthony Brown &amp; group therAPy - I Got That  (Remix Audio) ft. 1K Phew" on YouTube - https://t.co/uqjzMSmPTN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tragédie à Halifax : on révise nos plans d'évacuation https://t.co/0QrDXn2DCV https://t.co/sRtoTwom0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RegalCourtier7 I let my woman wear what she wants; she is beautiful and brilliant (but humble about it). Also, my… https://t.co/USoEclbqEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOScrutinizer @DieterFrikadell @rln_nelson @henry5rex @ladyspat1 @puntanenyahoo @cdjstrydom @MedBennett… https://t.co/yvEWvlJcIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrShayPhD @htjfto3 The experience depends on teachers &amp; which textbooks used!]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #getswole saga continues! . . . . . . #getswoleisthegoal #focus #grind #work #kmooremusic… https://t.co/dPjk8STRNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always great running into familiar faces at the starting line and finish line. @clontz @readysetgreat rich_eevolvin… https://t.co/keTQ0qoYZc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CDunning929 Imagine NASCAR's response if a fan drove a car on the track during a race.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AhmedBaba_ @bhsnitzer @FoxNews @GOP Idiot racisd white people should be in concentration camps. One so they stop s… https://t.co/JEeIwqeuz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow I feel 100% different this week than I did last week. Life’s weird.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomZohar @tawilliams11 legitimately from my website https://t.co/4RhAO9FuNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayGuentzel So envious....I will miss your voice with Chad, Adam, et al.  Use sun screen!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WonderPix It was also the uncertainty of the job itself too. I wasn’t ready to leap into a job where I knew that I… https://t.co/gvVS1zueru]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cathyob1 @Fahrenthold @realDonaldTrump That does not seem to be important for Senate confirmation]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rough Valentines Day? Imagine getting your final divorce statement of your spouse of 20 years who you went through… https://t.co/gMTXTFRFjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I take a two month hiatus from writing and come back with two in one day?! Yeah, that happened. #OpeningDay is righ… https://t.co/WGrbqw2s47]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever since I've gotten home all I want to do is sleeeep during the day!! I don't think jetlag is suppose to last this long]]></document><document><![CDATA[No i ain’t no hoe no more you gotta buy me food https://t.co/fQyD08Z2Qm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to my friend for winning the Oscar, you deserve it 1000% ❤️ you @ReginaKing @sportsoneclt clubonecl… https://t.co/aytYLehiPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Raiders have *three* first round picks this year and you couldn't get them to give up any of them??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone explain to me why @senatemajldr has disabled the opportunity to comment on his IG posts??? It isn’t oka… https://t.co/UV1u6TP1l3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing my new glasses from @liingoeyewear // Their glasses are made from premium materials and they come with free… https://t.co/chd2UPZ34c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaBrookeNY @SoonerCT22 Really proud to see he’s using words as big as OCEANSIDE these days ...hard work pays off!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachJeffLeach It’s a PIVOTAL moment in the swing https://t.co/XEBcwUHR7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dom_Petsch maaaaaan, I wanted them Tri City Fire season tickets....  thanks for being A1 since day 1 homie. Apprec… https://t.co/CKXtSxkdQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kokomothegreat @chezbeckie Do these two know that Trump and everyone in his audience hate black people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[V-Day date with Ash 😊 (@ 801 Chop House in Des Moines, IA) https://t.co/NjrqepKVeL]]></document><document><![CDATA[What in the world😡😡😡 I pray that all of this isn’t true. To go so far as causing yourself to be hospitalized all fo… https://t.co/v9GMa2IkQt]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is farcical. #mirth #lol #grin #amusing https://t.co/LwyaTgUUQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making pour decisions at wine o’clock🤪🍷 #winetasting https://t.co/qZD2pCqPZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BBSSmeeting #SIB🙏❤❤🙏.... Wednesday Morning 3/6/19.... @ Temple Judea https://t.co/1T99XgDHLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Texas Independence Day!   #Texas #RememberTheAlamo #BattleOfSanJacinto https://t.co/JhFaVCF7TU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to The Police Song by Dan Devon #np on #SoundCloud https://t.co/nol36YSwVe]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s probably not great that for the past hour as I get ready for my 14 mile run I keep reminding myself “you signe… https://t.co/yKbOmPy0BY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gavi it's the vaccinated who spread the diseases. I've done enough research on vaccines to know the dangers of the… https://t.co/UCIrVjhaNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevesi Give me three, or even one result. I’d rather do that than launch my phone, find the app, and figure out w… https://t.co/XdP0z6ftds]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKevinBrady @WaysandMeansGOP @HouseGOP @SenateMajLdr  @SpeakerPelosi At a time when this country desparately nee… https://t.co/6bkdnN7cUb]]></document></documents></author>