<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I stand by my luck, but the weight of healing is heavy, even for the lucky ones. https://t.co/houoTcZl6C Great essay by @otraletra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TedFlintKansas I have a real honest question:  If a man did the same things she did tonight, would we call him bitchy or just a beast?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dustyn told me forever ago to get a tattoo on my butt and I’ve wanted one ever since.. sooo we’ll see what I end up doing next paycheck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TearsaSmith thanks for your help this morning finding info about closed roads. We were able to get to church safel… https://t.co/mbV4vE4UCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, unt rec center, nothing gets me pumped up for a workout quite like Hey There Delilah does]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NiclaGL @marlenaNmurray1 The look that Stef gives Lena is one of a kind pure love! The kind of love everyone looks for]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit my Etsy shop at https://t.co/2ucWlxwYLq or follow me on https://t.co/Mmh8Qrq4Me #necktie #queerfashion… https://t.co/44b3FCGq1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just entered to #Win @GeorgeStrait tickets. You should too! https://t.co/AwUxu5DmAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alethiahbasurto @salmariscal2 @epigmenioibarra @Revolucion3_0 Ahí van,  no lo dudes, ni te pongas al cambio cuando… https://t.co/Nbaz7hNt2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BIGGeorgeAZ @thespinzone @SBergerBOSTON @BearDownSteven @ZonaZealots @CohenCurse1580 @BoogiePhoenix @azfamdoc… https://t.co/JeWHqqMARc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know if I wanna shave my head, dye it, drive off a cliff, or a combination of all 3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Oscar Sunday. Love to see the fashion and of course who will win the coveted award! Some Oscar trivia- The Os… https://t.co/RiXHToMXf4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACMawards SHAME ON Y'ALL!  MUST BE PRETTY DAMN JEALOUS OF @ShaniaTwain 👀ING AS Y'ALL CONTINUOUSLY ACT LIKE SHE DON… https://t.co/82Dgqen4qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kevin Hart Cussing Pictures, Photos, and Images for Facebook, Tumblr, Pinterest, and Twitter https://t.co/9QihJ8mFtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DBTayor Shane MacGowan does the song the best of all.  I first heard it when watching a Docmumentary of Tim Hether… https://t.co/2ZjfDwAAce]]></document><document><![CDATA[You Nailed it Mr. Sajak..great tweet..we can thank Obama &amp; Hillary for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@missinflint @BlackInkCrew U cannot even write full sentences. Go back to school bc idk what ur trying to say lol.… https://t.co/Mvr7umi1v4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wsbtv @NicoleCarrWSB I hope that he is ok. Thank God, the damages can be fixed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prime example of playing for the name on the back of your jersey rather than the front #Machado]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only thing that is "ill" about this is how it makes me feel that they did not act more forcefu… https://t.co/E6plsqYIGg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePostman68 @CabarrusBrewCo You sure about that? Mine just gets all sweaty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got all that plastic surgery &amp; he still gone Cheat on you with a lil booty sis..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone preform some sort of magic on me that’s lets me fall into a deep peaceful sleep for a year please and thank… https://t.co/l8pMGkVQ9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[That is not what happened, anfmd he was immediately confronted on it and forcefully answered follow up questions sa… https://t.co/Kc2DL8VWoD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to share this with you @jongarysteele  As I was looking at pix from my son’s wedding. I was struck by the cei… https://t.co/K0h3efmGaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[The reason Mueller does not investigate Hillary on the Uranium because he was in on it, he is being paid by the Cli… https://t.co/RsKaJtPRhU]]></document><document><![CDATA[like yesterday I listened to my resident talk to me about her life for 20 minutes and then she said “thanks for tak… https://t.co/gDS5UY2Hqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher I’m  not finished Oppsie... in twitting or life. Further more: we chicks life longer... and love more or more… https://t.co/832kyHiKbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I don’t know how I stayed with someone like that for 4 years.... seriously crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 ‘Look at this stuff Isn't it neat? Wouldn't you think my collection's complete?’ 🎶🧜🏻‍♀️  Actually, it’s not YET c… https://t.co/pFcNcUaBoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like we’re having some weather. Don’t we always? #wind #rain #morewind #morerain @ Swiftwater Brewing https://t.co/C710RZ239V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaQuinnsMom Being able to hug people is nice. Being able to actually commit and on Reconciliation issues in Canada impresses me more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanroche @nathanpboston @drvox See Mothers Out Front website Resources on Health, Mental Health and Climate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RelentlezzDre Prayers for your family and friends thank @Kimberl38218406]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrototypeMEM LOL it’s a show???? it’s edited!!!! i’m sure they cut a lot of the extras out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump As PT Barnum said, “There’s a sucker born every minute.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImTheRealLux I have set my bow in the cloud, and it shall be a sign of the covenant between me and the earth.        Genesis 9:13]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar me when I still can’t get your amazing brushes... https://t.co/5jATNZpLmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lunchdatewithmom #finished the #hcdeRecruitmentFair #hcde #chattanooga #tennessee #lookingforateachingjob… https://t.co/TCy7rUxVgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some shit just don’t concern me therefore it doesn’t require my attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dkMOMUS I’ve been reading this all over the place. I always feel much more comfortable flying in a big plane. I’ll… https://t.co/cixdprbrbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenolin1 Seriously! Name one that isn't dirty, under indictment or about to be. One?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mana Extracts 😍 . . . . . Come get your dab on! 💨 . . . Fire OG Live Resin Sauce THC 48.31% | CBD 5.33% Terpenes 27… https://t.co/bYk4tmt9lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@readingtheend why not? I'm dependable, okay, but this is like Gorsuch wishing that guy froze in his truck. Probabl… https://t.co/PD1EgC5EpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FlashbackFriday #80s #nyc Love the Doc #studio54  #Netflix https://t.co/2Zy7ou5sTl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LetterkennyProb Guess I know what I’ll be watching this Valentime’s day. 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreperryedu Blackness and housing devaluation is about 23% or average $48k or $156 billion aggregate in the USA. https://t.co/zAbzJ8h5Ob]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AstorAaron @wuttangie @ToriTeal1 @GetBenThompson @maggieNYT You're wasting your time. Angie is in denial about bot… https://t.co/DHAT28VbSv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhilippeReines @CNN if they could have her not involved in the campaign coverage at all that would do the trick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlamLifeGuru Happy Belated Birthday Miss Tati! You're simply the BEST! Love you sister! (I just turned 63 in Jan.)… https://t.co/nsEuCDlb9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big S/O to former volunteer assistant coach Kayla Schanback (@KSchanback22) on getting an assistant coaching job!… https://t.co/RYTbL2NQDY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I speak facts while others just run their mouth. We are NOT built the same. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red violets are blue, starting a ❤️ happy day with Kara and the CG crew!  #wutwut #bettertogether @ Sola… https://t.co/mrWaEAhNo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought these two little plants at aldiusa about three months ago for $3 each... the fact that they’re not only stil… https://t.co/JOEwXs43Z5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried to take pictures of #averleigharia being a badass on the basketball court and all I ended up with was… https://t.co/n418PXb3M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[🗣Listen to these queens world!  Proud of you two and what you’re birthing at @sxsw ❤️❤️. cc: @vacumberbatch… https://t.co/90LoVWReyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally copped Frank’s cover of GQ and lmk why he talked more about his skincare routine than his mUSIC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN I think she explained that she wants to be known for what she stands for and believes in, not her label.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews That is so damn wrong I can’t tell you  put  Kaepernicks  name back up]]></document><document><![CDATA[#waybackwednesday #washboardabswednesday #absworkout #ripped #fitnessmotivation #fitness #leanmuscle @ New York, Ne… https://t.co/VbLy8vhoWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mexicancupcake just wanted to tell you that love! you my sunshine https://t.co/kvyBGhclPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alike_no @jkokkoris8 Share please. emcmillan@carolinarapids.org thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a day for exploring and being tourist and ending the day with everyone ‘camping out’ with a good book and trea… https://t.co/cmULHdtFPC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has the entire world gone mad?! ’Suicide isn't fashion': Burberry apologizes for hoodie with noose around the neck… https://t.co/TCyzuiEmzp]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first block ACAers made museum exhibits for their Gilded Age projects! https://t.co/hIiWIyu76F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshishShrawan @AussiesInTheUSA @AussiesInMD @qldcricket @VicStateCricket I retweet a ton from @usacricket. You should pay closer attention.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Lyft way better than Uber because lyft is cheaper and they randomly bless loyal customers with 10% off for 10 rides in a row.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It subsidizes their conservation efforts, insurance coverage, marketing, export sales, research, and other activiti… https://t.co/5qC5ZIYwnp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ellis was always out of line during this entire case! He values whiteness at all costs and will say anything to pro… https://t.co/zDWIcyNOxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took pictures of my hair yesterday and I liked the way they turned out, so I decided to share them. I'm thinking… https://t.co/kXMwbxoqWG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do the people on TV know that when the say “s-hole” countries because they can’t say shit-hole countries on TV it a… https://t.co/X4TI2wgU65]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SchittsCreekPop @annefrances @danjlevy @DustinWMilligan @Realeugenelevy @PopTV I’m obsessed with ur show! Watching… https://t.co/4Ta8CquQ77]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sweepstakes ends Feb. 15, 2019 11:59 PT. Extra entries are https://t.co/nJerhXHbjt PURCHASE OR WIRELESS DEVICE… https://t.co/AgpVGnhnSL]]></document><document><![CDATA[En 2011 marché contra la militarización y la guerra vs el narcotrafico de Calderón. Recuerdo a muchas personas que… https://t.co/QcapB4akID]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Long Island City, NY in Long Island City, NY https://t.co/kbE0NM7IXD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told my mom I’m going to be alone forever and her response was “oh stop, you’re not going to be alone forever! Yo… https://t.co/hscE6cOEzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HemmenwayPhysEd @HemmenwayStreak Our tigers literally rock! https://t.co/F8szR3N43K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenMalfour HAHAHHAHAHAHA BET KO TALAGA PARA KASING BLACK HAHAHAHAHHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud of @RepStefanik: There Are Just 13 Republican Women in Congress: ‘We Are at a Crisis Level’ https://t.co/UoNHCKTBuu via @glamourmag]]></document><document><![CDATA[That great little innocent child Miley has grown up a to become  a disgrace to America! Her nasty Vulgar Language i… https://t.co/pyT3n55XFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoy hace 19 año que nos casamos al civil. Happy Anniversay Chula mimi_chiquiti @ Westlake Village, California https://t.co/TIsUQTZg9z]]></document><document><![CDATA[At this comedy club and one of the opening acts is hella funny.. I go to follow him on Instagram and it says follow… https://t.co/POWakpRVaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hypocrisy of Jordan to question Cohen’s tax dodging when Trump has kept his tax avoidance private.]]></document><document><![CDATA[everything good by the weekend @ Statesboro, Georgia https://t.co/ovxwNvlGss]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your supposedly BFF cant hang out with you because the bitch needs to do dinner?? Like okay its 3 in the after… https://t.co/OMcMOQalBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @PlanetFitness in Madison, WI w/ @mattkensethis1 https://t.co/slsWDLzR8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobersonCarolee AWWWW..." U R THE BEST MY CHICAGOAN FAN FRIEND, THANKS 4 SHARING UR FABULOUS EVENING WITH ME, I AP… https://t.co/KioPwvzzr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Early Birthday To my Aquarius Brother Mook💙💙. You thought I would forget about you hun🤔🤣. I did something out… https://t.co/0GCaaBuZn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndrewYangVFA @SenSanders @SenWarren @SenBooker @SenKamalaHarris @RepAOC  🇺🇸 will never be a socialist nation!  https://t.co/nSmDSXbIA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[But the one thing I believe he’s telling the truth about is Rosenstein was involved]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really just wanna go on a long drive up in the mountains with someone, talking about life, goals and ambitions. Sha… https://t.co/ej1fWe3kgR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahjeanfry @TW2CayC @Dianafowles @KnowSmallParts @Cheryl_L_Hyde @MeganHubbell @TathamSmith @confessions_cup… https://t.co/JJ2FvMIvZT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Super proud of the effort and execution today...regardless of the final score, the wins are going to come...keep gr… https://t.co/nEGYrTwvMr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to my amazing boyfriend who works 40+ hours a week, goes to school full time, and still makes so much time… https://t.co/Tb1ljUyGeW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elmiracat14 How in the world does he keep getting away with this 💩? https://t.co/awjnM9Gi13]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we’re just days away from the #CaptainMarvel release, this week’s podcast episode is perfect timing.… https://t.co/KpOBMWSOMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @PickeringPHE Blayne Helou (51kg 5th Place), Dechlan Papadopoulos (54kg Gold), Mateo Anisi (3rd… https://t.co/PP53TdVfcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[A friend didn’t recognize me as I was walking down the hall and I’m 99% sure it’s because I’m having a good hair day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luney66 @esoriram1 @WBAY @fox11news @WISN12News @ZellnerLaw I am in the US and it didn’t trend.  😩 Need to recruit… https://t.co/FYliQluI9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[saying kylie jenner is not a self made billionaire does not make her any less of a billionaire https://t.co/QZYM6cLace]]></document></documents></author>