<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@cybreco Thank you for supporting my constitutional right to bear...... just barely...... with any of this shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day of using Filepass from @brianh00d and already it’s going to change the way I deal with revisions from clien… https://t.co/fh9HhSu4UB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Este Sr hace los autos más impresionantes del mundo, el maestro Horacio Pagani 🚙💨 https://t.co/vxCeIgu0l0]]></document><document><![CDATA[All fun and games until he ends up dead.   Also, there's a shower patch cereal???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm af I had to close today just got home and i open tomorrow working that 8-4 shift. On the bright side is that I'… https://t.co/M8jUobY5eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Exmotions @slmxny @zachdenobrega Hit me whit im sorry but im sorry no #ANoNo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Them: I don’t be making noises and moaning during sex Me: https://t.co/OIwq4w9a8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[How you know a place is fancy. #LeadershipSummit #HowWeRollInSubro @ Vito's Chop House https://t.co/BRrf0gunDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It will probably be yet another reason to put on top of the pile of countless other reasons.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#supermoon #amateurphotography  #ballislife 🏀🌚🌝 https://t.co/5pZrOCsEzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harsh but it couldn’t be more true. In the real world - no one cares about your struggles or mishaps. Stay focused… https://t.co/2UlmU51OvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes #HamptonsFinest #RuthCarter #BlackPanther @TheAcademy #Oscar #Oscar2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsLisaLouWho Remember, one day at a time. Find something to celebrate or find your happy thought for that day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s sad to see people with such talent leave this world so soon. May he Rest In Peace 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's always when you're at rock bottom that noone is around. Not like anyone gets it or gives a fuck anyways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excelente lunes para trabajar con toda la actitud por el bien de los jóvenes bachilleres....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya gotta understand I’ve been done wrong way too many times to have this much patience.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgot about my man @GregJennings ! Did your thing on @FS1 filling in for the big dawgs . Looking forward to seeing… https://t.co/92wvd1A7BU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FretzCrystal But, I think you're right! The migraine meds or those for vertigo tend to help along with rest and st… https://t.co/qgReLnKY8z]]></document><document><![CDATA[At least the two concerts I was attending for part of this work were good.   Plus the work distracted me from being… https://t.co/yo7YWvC5t8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColtKnost @ForeGolfersNet @USGA You do realize the Tour had a seat at the table, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbransco @ValMackinnon @DonMartinCTV If only voters had other options...*sigh*]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Sweet Jesus come and destroy all these heathens and save us]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joaquinlife Agree on both counts. Again why Bernie should register as a Democrat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SelirioJennie i mainly loved grilled and fried fish, Cod, Orange Roughy, Tilapia (no head or scales) scallops, Oys… https://t.co/lxfjhmp7R2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Juan is a real POS, too dumb to understand what is going on. Truely the racist]]></document><document><![CDATA[classic me falling asleep at like 9 pm and waking up around midnight. if there is a day this doesnt happen presume i am not myself]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayFunday #NorthPittsburgh #Wildcats 🐯on the ice @YostIceArena #PresidentsDay Tournament 2-16-19 #AnnArbor… https://t.co/6mAvJz5CoS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKAnes Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist We are all Cryin' Brian.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougboneparth @RampCapitalLLC The "none of the above" party.  We'll sweep into power! https://t.co/GR7l1zXtFW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ca_afterschool 1st @NatGeo fellow to work exclusively with afterschool. Excellent news and progress for our field.… https://t.co/2lqyqrPi6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHundley44 @2chainz @Tyler_TLove @RawisAlejandro My man @2chainz been snapping since playaz  circle]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trurnp is signing bibles. He literally has a god complex. And his followers who are getting that done?!?! What the… https://t.co/3eIwEthOLP]]></document><document><![CDATA[It always makes my day when @NASCAR and @NASCARONFOX broadcast the prayer before the race. #praisethelord #SundayBest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you imagine being so stupid that you actually believe this is true?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breakfast meeting of Tri Valley Executives. (@ Vic's All Star Kitchen in Pleasanton, CA) https://t.co/fYKTfztbDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#sexdwarf #softcell @MarcAlmond #oldschool #classic @ Globe Theatre https://t.co/3iq5ntw5qE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sdeebocane Good morning Dee and Happy Thursday and happy Valentine’s Day 💖💖☕️☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @MarvelStudios title at the beginning of #CaptainMarvel was the purest thing I've seen in a long time #ThankYouStan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cpdzone7 Jussie Smollett didn't drag your reputation through the dirt! That interview on TV saying he dragged your… https://t.co/Y3uQEa4iVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillKristol Guess people forget what bible says bout loving people especially your enemy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaishii Hi. I was just wondering if you thought if this was a good look for me? 😊 https://t.co/wR427Rq4JR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @Qanon4life @AOC In Hawaii the natives call us Haoles.  Mazie Hirono obviously is Racist and does no… https://t.co/qz150rQVOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vegemitecyborg I found you a place to live brother 🍁 https://t.co/c1xnvnS4wQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t worry Nationals fans. Harper will most likely strike out against Scherzer when he faces him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jesustarre @jguaido Es cierto lo que has expuesto, son tan criminales que de verdad son capases de matar gente sin… https://t.co/7sF9noVtGp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I yelled Lebron you suppose to be the goat!!!! Take little Trae to the rim!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been challenged to post pics of my 7 favorite books. I was challenged by @CoachGinn Each day I will challenge… https://t.co/dEZGMnZbvN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, Franklin Brisket. 2 hour queue. Thankyouverymuch. @ Franklin Barbecue https://t.co/HWZNX9dh83]]></document><document><![CDATA[LMFAO and Lil Jon: SHOTS SHOTS SHOTS SHOTS SHOTS  Middle school me that had just signed a pledge to never do drugs or alcohol: 🤙🏼🤪🤙🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nigella_i5e @jungman0073 Obviously Ms Abbot is unhappy so she should go back to the country her forefathers came f… https://t.co/c7OBmyhKBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bittersweet moment as my last time (most likely) I the gmc_athletics Eagle Dome was for a college fair in an effort… https://t.co/QxC0ZrR5G0]]></document><document><![CDATA[My interview yesterday with @cedarient Thankyou for giving me this platform. Everything is in motion #las Vegas @ N… https://t.co/wUu3f9db2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ElliottGagnon @misterorange Why ban or unban anything in modern when they have an entire new set coming out to shake up the format?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lawrence Boys &amp; Girls Club in Lawrence, MA https://t.co/OKTmJ4zC1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricCross04 What you think his numbers will be this year? 75-15-75-20-290-350?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo uso bragas por fuera de mis jeans pegados en #nuevayork #sexy @TheShops_ColCir @UniContigo @TwitterEspana… https://t.co/bhCgqRt4yu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexmerced @AOC Send her your high school picture while at it alex lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyVidler @MavenAdviser @mjoehlerich @John_Tyreman @NeilsonInfo @HingeMarketing @KellyJWaffle Tony vidler you got it Howard ///]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Artemio Gracias por aclarar, pensé que la Hyper y la Turbo eran la misma y solo cambió de nombre por región entre America y Japón :0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not sure how I feel about this... the #BreakingBad finale was (to me) perfect... but the fact Vince Gilligan is inv… https://t.co/HdUpOmXuvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioMARCA @PipiEstrada1 @pepegh7 @njuancof1 @RobertoGomezOC @raulvarelar https://t.co/Lk2UvFMHNw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@350_dave @_MyiaB You Right lol La’Pooh got over 1million plays on SoundCloud.. So if we do the numbers game La’Pooh got it]]></document><document><![CDATA[People either act like they 2 good or think they better than you either was everyone can see thru that mask u scary ass insecure joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnarkyL Trump just defended Jordan’s anti-Semitism. Will anyone in the GOP speak up? Or does the GOP only denounce… https://t.co/tuHV2qhFjT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nel, no estoy capacitado para ser inspector, ahí pa'l otro año busco otro rol secundario 🤷🏻‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayneJayne311 @311 @Metallica It’s not going to happen.  Not keen on an ass kicking today.  😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeFFrazier @T_S_P_O_O_K_Y @RobertMosesIII @TheRickWilson @RadioFreeTom @DNC Probably a coloring book]]></document><document><![CDATA[When dancers have a snow day ❄️ @ Ottawa, Ontario https://t.co/koFGStAwMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thespinzone @GSklash @sak_shoes Gil blocking me like a grade school bully. That’s what’s going on 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deadspin Fixed: Evil men sentenced to prison for giving UNPAID college basketball players some money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun is...#toddleractivities #slime #daddydaughtertime @ Beltsville, Maryland https://t.co/X7yiXV3qTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal Why is #MLB so worried about the "casual fan" complaining about games being too long? The game is fi… https://t.co/F94QUc6qLd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesANagle @StonyBrookMLAX @SBAthletics Coach, tell Jake we’re happy to help. And psyched about the W! @StonyBrookKids @StonyBrookMed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@playing4keeps69 @JackPosobiec The only difference between ¡JEB! And Feinstein are the letters of political party.… https://t.co/QmVlnAUcEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Britt said that she would fill out ballots she collected that weren’t fully completed. She said she recalled all of… https://t.co/OYT4SOW63Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life has its ups and downs as long as you stay positive and strong you will survive. Just deal with it suicide is not the answer]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I please have a sugar daddy that only pays me thru PayPal NO OTHER FORM OF PAYMENT KAY THANKS 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perryman_taylor @masonramsey I’m rumpling everyone responsible if so. I got a list]]></document><document><![CDATA[It nothing like wet pussy on my dick, and a tight ass on my Tongue. Located in East Orlando.  #ucf #waterfordlakes… https://t.co/6ay4rA7kbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LucyAppa @shewillnotfail @momcahoon @shannon_box @RogerFisk @PressSec @realDonaldTrump They should be told that ma… https://t.co/6dG0GBTyzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobbySkinnerNFL No it's not Allen's accuracy during the season was just as bad and used his legs just as much if n… https://t.co/H9ab5Jzlai]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DAMSConsulting Yes, but $XXII already submitted their package for MRTP for VLN cigarettes and I’m fine with them b… https://t.co/k3xxGAaFhh]]></document><document><![CDATA[making film/production homies is the best, nobody else i relate more to]]></document><document><![CDATA[A full day of  sessions planned in Philadelphia. Looking forward to learning about the latest ideas, issues and tre… https://t.co/tPlFYwBn6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Monctonscout @xenodog @TonyMarinaro @PaulHReporter1 Exactly 94 happened once.. yes was awesome I was there but no… https://t.co/MIfhh6RKOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MemedCa @WashingtonPoint If Turkish democracy can still function.  If not, Erdoğan can make them eat bullets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you leave this country for #ISIS you are not allowed back in this country. You are a Radical Islamist and this g… https://t.co/Zi3q5TQ4XT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buy a #NewHome in #California  If your #Negligent #Builder #Lennar screws you, trust me #Government cares none!… https://t.co/CPTYZNBaPq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heytherejeffro I don’t want to meet anyone who doesn’t think Tom Hanks sparks joy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FightForNYCHA @SDNYnews @NYCMayor @BilldeBlasio @NYCHA @HUDgov Someone please explain if this is due to more aid or what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SATNAM52 @realDonaldTrump Well, the country I live in is being attacked by a President 24/7 trying to turn citizen… https://t.co/Pj4tMtZju4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juliey4 Hence my reply.  Heh Twitter is way easier than all of them it’s just words]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has there ever been something more patronizing? https://t.co/4IHIPNO6Zu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattMencarini @courierjournal Congratulations Matt!  Well deserved.   The @courierjournal is damn lucky to get you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Us Democrats have spent far to much time simply speaking.  At the minimum, this is finally something that makes use… https://t.co/9MzobFJskZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@__linnglingg @lexiyee_ she smelled like cotton candy and it felt great... had glitter on my face for the rest of t… https://t.co/m5I1n4WJin]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever wake up look at the clock mad asf like nah why Father Time fucking with me this early in the morning 🤦🏾‍♂️ like it’s not 5am]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would’ve caught a seizure and played dead from that hit after I seen her get In a Jaguar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent undergrad in the Friendzone. Started dating @A2RecDirect in grad school. Married at The League.  Twenty-two y… https://t.co/Zvc2CB0fz8]]></document></documents></author>