<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Our flight attendant ...   “Welcome to LA, enjoy your Saturday night. Be safe ... don’t drink and drive... Don’t tx… https://t.co/g5oJis3e6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[CSU faces UNLV tonight for the last home game of the season.  Go Rams! https://t.co/xKAWNQ7jt0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Embrace_The_DJZ Maybe with the food ‘cart’ on the back for late night drunkies 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I mean those of quality. I’m the girl that saw you speak for cougar town in New York. I’ve seen scrubs and emba… https://t.co/Xx8RrLLjoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌹👁🌹🍇👑😎BLESSED DAY EVERYONE FOLLOW THE CHOO CHOO🚂💨 @TAMMYYO86840808 @_KLIY_ @_Mr_Clutch_3 @daysidity @Yitabug… https://t.co/UwbBkuukht]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate Jacksonville. You always see stray cats &amp; dogs all over the place. It makes me SO sad. 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what’s gonna happen when Justice Jerry opens erratic fire into a crowd to “protect from the bad guys” or the pol… https://t.co/oXfdTZgZDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[My greatest struggle is finding time for me, to relax and recharge. Between rotating shift work and being 600 miles… https://t.co/WYJGVmdOP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so tired of people pretending to be my friend then doing nothing but complain about me behind my back. If you don't like me, leave.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TallTalTeaches Bold School and Big Magic (not specifically for teachers, but still amazing and applicable. I recom… https://t.co/WHkittAYaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofballgeorge @PhatMommy3 @PhillipDenton @Phillyfann @Philmast60 @PinkElefunkus @PoboySr @PoliticalCaptn… https://t.co/5OMG3QPnfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexs_journey @Writer_DG @LincsMiniPolice @T_ACCShaunWest @wwf_uk Congratulations. ❤️👍🏻❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[listen. i KNOW room temperature water is better for me than cold water. but UUUUUUUUUUGGGGGGGGGHHHHHHHHHHHH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Didn’t I hear that @realDonaldTrump say that @DonaldJTrumpJr was the dumbest of his kids?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJandRHfan I DONT NEED THEAR FN SWAG TO SCREAM FOR MY DRIVER ITS ALL GOOD 🤗😎💪☝️🏁💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[“@TripAdvisor said while the company was unsure if the reviews complaining of rape would have an impact on a busine… https://t.co/UzOMHSRb8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me at 7: drinking from the hose (water from garden hose in backyard)  Me at 27: drinking from the hoes (breast milk… https://t.co/u3oX0460cX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anyra___ @Tareesha You always have to have an English professor, however the usage is correct in my post because i… https://t.co/3SojvWq30Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dogturd3 It seems like you may have an in with catturd2..Why did catturd2 block me? Loved his tweets!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarahQuinn Still struggling with K 😂 all I can think of is Kite and like, I don't fly Kites so that isn't going to work haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flava_av @whateversace I honestly wanna make this my background now LOL this is awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eleventyrock @Alduanem Just order one, looking forward to your #concert in #Columbia #SouthCarolina @NewBrookland… https://t.co/1LhfMtecgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[i feel like i’m the only person who isn’t trying to be like all active and shit with james cause i lowkey want a ch… https://t.co/MPGqpT1KDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IBchemmilam @mschemwoulfee Awesome idea thanks, I have 2 SL students and they are having some trouble coming up with ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious. I’ve taught preschool for 15 years. Thanks for keepin’ it real. #teacherproblems]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader @RepMarkMeadows @RepMarkMeadows evidently has a history of racist actions... https://t.co/Ol8AXwhxB2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RushRush74 @bethtank @WatchLilyTweet Not like that actually.. Lol. But those laying chickens for the eggs in the g… https://t.co/rvu5QlpvbK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMNr With all the issues facing this country right now why is Israel your focus? There are atrocities in Yemen… https://t.co/RRJUKdha6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC You are a grown woman, you should have know better than to try and cover up or dodge the investigation. Make… https://t.co/0gqxD4D4fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[calvin_harris_feat_florence_welch_sweet_nothing.mp3 is still the backbone of our society]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EstherThePig @CBSFilms @MikkiDaughtry @TobiasIaconis Oh my Gosh !!This is so exciting.:-):-O:-D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zeroonewatts You mean “bhocolate bhip bookies”?? https://t.co/ygBvTXRJNf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had such a fun time bambeautybar with this pretty lady raising money for #FSFAC and super exited to show everyone h… https://t.co/UhCYsou6fI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge Scrapbook update for Dean! Don't forget to send me your thank you messages, fan art, edits, and any and all pi… https://t.co/Z16RC5Avqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accept your challenge @RayGredder...  to post the covers of 7 books I love; no explanation, no review; just cover… https://t.co/GQ7b3aWNx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Baer incident (being investigated by league) is a reminder that domestic violence, in its many forms, is a perv… https://t.co/QNlBwCsv3s]]></document><document><![CDATA[why does every town in the new pokemon game have like 4 houses in each town they don't even have like grocery store… https://t.co/yLZp6w1PEY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@physeqs That being said in the therapeutic horse industry people get off the horse in all types of different ways… https://t.co/nMxlqYt1l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best place I love to do homework is in a coffee shop.  I like the thought that people think I'm actually doing work… https://t.co/QH9lwKRRbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@formoftherapy If it happens you spoke it into existence and I’ll be coming for you https://t.co/9RMqX101o2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apparently there is NO LIVESTREAM of Awards~I was going to GO LIVE for Awards~It was possible earlier so standby in… https://t.co/YB8oa6QTKp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RipKarlLagerfeld the fashion world wouldn’t have been nearly the same without you and your imagination ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made it 🙌🙌 now to turn on some old episodes of @GreysABC on my laptop and go to sleep.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissSPants @FirstNetGov @MrAndersonSS Amazing win. Firstnet game changer!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then once we got to our destination he was like “ what’s wrong now” like you told me to be silent wym🤔🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 1 of GYTO getyourteachon is in the books. I never grow tired of listening to so many amazing educators! Sure I… https://t.co/baXtRCXI1w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special counsel prosecutors say they have communications of Stone with WikiLeaks - CNNPolitics https://t.co/vs05XD2GLN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesCraigmyle @SOMissouri I donated, not as much as I would have liked too. Anything for Lor‼️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s nice to have a few small projects to work on in the evening while watching tv. I’ve decided to add some hand s… https://t.co/ROMjfp0AK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRealPatarHD @scopely @YahtzeeBuddies Well in this guy’s case, it’s because I wouldn’t let him sexually harass me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Autistic individuals are also bound by the right to human dignity, to autonomy, and to the need to experience comp… https://t.co/kPFX5zKPs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodRobinsonRVA lol that’s bc you’ll have to classroom manage them too! 😂😂 you’ll do great!]]></document><document><![CDATA[E eu que n fui pra escola hj pq nem ia ter aula direito daí minha host mãe mandou uma nota q eu tava doente KKKKKKK amo uma mulher]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OCMomBlog @monicazyoung @Belairmommie @healthy_mouse @HorsingAroundLA https://t.co/zIEn55xdTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did you know that there is a monthly #Veteran networking and information session at the @NationalVMM? https://t.co/HddyhPXZcs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing to see the #TradeGuys podcast live now - with Scott Miller, Marjorie @mchorlins  Bill Reinsch and Barbara W… https://t.co/IbfWhDJYQx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lynne Patton needs to focus on her day job, instead of being of being a 21st Century Slave on the Auction block.  W… https://t.co/1nEmQHdTf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHSMarauder Every time I watch them my jaw drops!! An amazing group of ladies!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anytime my mom sends something in caps I simply send these too her. https://t.co/MuPySAst8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day at Spring Training in Mesa with the #Cubs - talked to several players in the Clubhouse, we’ll also hear fr… https://t.co/zPF6PGR3RN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troll #Trump wants to increase air pollution. Do his 'supporters' care?  "...most pickup trucks owners seem to like… https://t.co/bDBnSsCD7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[El que siempre ha estado enamorado de ti , te vio llorar ,lastimada y apesar que no parabas de hablarle del que te… https://t.co/nY7qr09QW2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supernovaslight @bigredwavenow @Cordicon @StormIsUponUs @qanon76 I'm reading "The Great Awakening" on Scribd. Chec… https://t.co/ohCGnF4Zy9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelsea_bucchan @SheBlessed @CoyaMiche Chelsea and this damn Groupon!! 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m Baaaaaack!! To-do list is a mile long but that’s OK! Happy Friday friends!!  . . #desmoines #catchdsm… https://t.co/412d0Hd5J0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidJHarrisJr She is an elderly woman.  These are not uncommon symptoms of old age.  She's still very attractive… https://t.co/uQtcc19kHE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does listening to @LanaDelRey make anyone else for soulful af or just me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[can you imagine if dj d wreck was the dj at your wedding and all of the sudden you hear “DJ D WRECK CUT THE BEAT” a… https://t.co/bZBCNXugsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deport Maria Gabriela Chavez, and send her back to Venezuela. https://t.co/5KdM4fKE5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Text from my hubz:  “When and why did you teach your daughter to poop in the bathtub?” 😬🤣 glad I’m out watching hoops!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Con mucho orgullo celebramos 90 años del PRI, un partido que ha sido actor determinante en la construcción del Méxi… https://t.co/dkiZflSI04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@findingfletcher “I'm afraid to turn the lights on I don't want to face this rebound Is it weird if I come over? I… https://t.co/0oaurURjii]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Chuck E. Cheese's - @chuckemty in San Pedro Garza García, Nuevo León https://t.co/lB9oMp1hJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fun fact: My sister has a hoodie from every.single. Ex of mine, I just give them to her 🤧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jnthnvsqz I didn’t realize I was shaking till Mike was like “can you sit sill” “why are you shaking” 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was fine hasta que el uber me vino a buscar y su carro huele a demonio, ahora tengo ganas desesperadas de vomitar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the #OSCARS for saving #BlackHistoryMonth https://t.co/HHYsPPLRnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zgfisch and @overbay22 ‘s Miami wedding was a dream! The ceremony was at sunset so the bistro lights and lanterns… https://t.co/p05hYTaPCU]]></document><document><![CDATA[In case you missed the cityline episode today! I tried my best to shorten it into 5 one min videos! I demo the look… https://t.co/oaZ1JqjXiE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foils upon foils upon foils!  What a fun day with this anime lover! It had been quite a while since she was able to… https://t.co/WEO9KqL5Az]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evening walk scenery. #greenville #gvl #gsp #sc #carolinas #fallspark @ Falls Park on the Reedy River https://t.co/VmufML44JY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I scored a hat trick in the #NHLHatTrickChallenge daily game. So did 32% of @NHL fans who played. https://t.co/OI3YWQZReD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jupitorbacksUSA @SBDSoultrain @provdcrumblover @AIIy4LGBTQ @PwrCane1 @SwampFox214 @ACMeyor @LeonWhi63670221… https://t.co/KIufL2koUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly at this point, I don’t even read anything about the post, but if I see a dog on Instagram I will like the post]]></document><document><![CDATA[There may be no more @ShadowhuntersTV but new episode released on @Netflix_CA and I’m SO HAPPY 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Move your phones away from the table I have some crazy tea to spill” -@aye_pena_]]></document><document><![CDATA[As long as I start my 4 page paper due tomorrow morning by 3 am I should be fine]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hits a little harder when the people who brought so many people joy couldn’t find enough for themselves. Thanks… https://t.co/JGPySpyJRW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgeHarrison Actually yesterday was his real birthday according to family records 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[sure, shamrock shakes in march are great, but have you ever convinced your local @McDonalds to add mint extract to an oreo mcflurry before?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Anddrikk @SpecSports360 @FHSAA @AustinRLyon @TorelloSports @MikeCairns5 @twittyjones Always great sharing the boot… https://t.co/0sT5M6swri]]></document><document><![CDATA[@philipaklein Oh, the self-righteousness! You wonder why GOP has a hard time winning, and it’s this. Mitt Romney sh… https://t.co/y7RSVHvLEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanCrenshawTX Even with one eye you can see the not-so-thinly-veiled threat implied by this specific headline/pict… https://t.co/U0P5gNgrkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SamiaAliSalama @funder @StephenKing Thanks Reagan, his legacy keeps biting us in the arse.  Rupert  more damage than chump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jojoptyoga OMG!! Davey Jones!!! The monkeys! My former husband picked “I’m a Believer”as the song we walked back d… https://t.co/TVZj7BxZrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[so awesome to see you accomplishing goals!! proud of you girl! @TidwellTuesdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eu odeio demais q machuquem a minha família meu Deus Eu tenho vontade de matar quando fazem mal pra alguém que eu amo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lights and Magic ✨with ladytron @ The Fonda Theatre https://t.co/qyB1jutTNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[suuuupppper late... but happy bday abby!!!! stay funny big dog love u💜#yuh #nuh @abbythomss 🎉😹 https://t.co/88r0grqhmN]]></document><document><![CDATA[i had a dream i got my tattoos removed because they weren’t trendy enough and what the fuck.]]></document></documents></author>