<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@RealWayneRoot Hope you’re right, Wayne! Give the Dems their stupid victory, and then while they’re taking a victor… https://t.co/I7JVoXKNlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theroastedbagel Shit like this killlllssss me !!!! HS show choir for so intense I swear sometimes i think back to… https://t.co/lCC0wM3QH6]]></document><document><![CDATA[How good is this!!? I love it!!  @NickFaldo006  https://t.co/RpyWvt8jGz]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of our girl julbeggs12 and cbdforlife tonight!  Schooling the crowd at the #cewthefutureofcannabis event!… https://t.co/iFP6x4I8dS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHJennifer @jwgop @MZHemingway Thank you, Jennifer...l so admire your decency and truth-telling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Take what? A fake President,  a liar,  adulterer,  cheater,  racist,  I could go on and on and on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NinoGuz right??? jesus. i’m not that religious but i do pray when i need to and fuck, that wasn’t even something i… https://t.co/nKej3qixuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Berube: "Perron's still the same. Schenn's making good progress."  As for making the trip: "I think Perron's still… https://t.co/yS0J3MFMXM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fien_charlie @KPeikert @MZHemingway My tweet is criticizing that culture not your t-shirt or you. But again, pleas… https://t.co/KspDi3truS]]></document><document><![CDATA[These measures are useful at capturing stress reactivity among young adults aged 18-24 - an age where many people a… https://t.co/IeYjkg7kHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello it’s 2:17 AM and i’m glad to announce that i finished 19 bio questions hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[(I’m having difficulty elegantly translating “shibirenai” into English. Non-shocking? Not Numb? It makes it sound a… https://t.co/a3fWHZbUew]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a new scholarship program for STEM-focused students at @swocc that is lining up nicely with the college’s n… https://t.co/FpPSVwuBbm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of the "Barn Door Incident": I may have broken my toe. And Miguel is very concerned since he's a big factor i… https://t.co/Am6f47buAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Annaanbg Such beautiful pictures dear Anna An, thank you for sharing them with us. Have a peaceful and blessed night dear friend 💫✨💫✨💐😘🤗🍃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ameliabrantley I wish you all the best and thank you for opening up to us. I am so sorry you have had such a hard… https://t.co/AjhhHyHEtG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zman_is_fam It seems like a lot of work probably, but it’s definitely way more creative and fun than anything else you get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So lets maybe celebrate the victories. I got out of bed finally. I managed to get dressed. Its sweatpants, but it i… https://t.co/UXmL6qirlP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How did Bruno get hot all of a sudden? Y’all need to go watch the Please Me video with him and @iamcardib!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is an incomplete documentary. It fails to include other victims, boys close to Jackson, and allows conviction… https://t.co/9wNUnWyYPa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreaming of those white sands! Such pretty watch towers on Miami Beach 💕😍 @ Miami Beach, Florida https://t.co/m1BcimOStO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I seriously ❤️ @AnyaVolz’s to the max &amp; this was seriously a blessed reunion.   Check out her new monthly #ThirstTrapComedy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PSDesertDolphin @ssoozer45 Lol I just figured out what this tweet was. It took me a minute 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I hear the name @JamesRoday I immediately think of @RosewoodFOX .... man, I miss that show!!!! @bionicanadian]]></document><document><![CDATA[This video is making my heart break and making me want to go adopt every dog in the shelter.😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tru7hS33kR @counterchekist Bernout paid his family almost a million a month to "help" him run.  It's about the mon… https://t.co/FOpyZpOYj5]]></document><document><![CDATA[God please let me get tickets to see BTS live 😭😩 they changed my life 💜 @BTS_twt #BTSSPEAKYOURSELFTOUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Husband Catalog (43 pics) - kitten; kitty; cats  My favorite is the one of... #funniness #giggle #grin #cute https://t.co/HVBzENS8l0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielMuitabayi @realDonaldTrump Always beware of one individual who claims to represent “The People.” Right off t… https://t.co/aaWBTyaJPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish that all my coworkers would get these tweets straight to their phones.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im throwing whiskey on a heart thats on fire Forgettin you aint no easy thing each night for me ends up the same Wi… https://t.co/FiSm9WVfB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Indeed. I agree, Stu. The frustration we feel is not with the  @ottawacity employees, but with the elected official… https://t.co/PX4PrweE6G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arrived in snowy NYC yesterday. Bad move having a meeting straight from the plane. Now fully prepared for 8am havin… https://t.co/nbySL3RU10]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had an art competition at school and I entered almost every category; painting, sculpting, drawing, photography,… https://t.co/jchFqmw867]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you María Eugenia Mejía @buenorigen, 🐯Donal_Berto ™ Lothbrok  🐗 @Jamfer_tm,SHIRISH JOSHI @SHIRISH65149661 ,li… https://t.co/CfLsK6Cb2A]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr  The height of hypocrisy. In case you are confused, you, Donald are a hypocrite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi Loves @MissMarisRacal @InigoDPascual! #MarNigo  #POPSSSS7 https://t.co/Xzo72NEqFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jellybean is on the Scene at the Goshen Chamber of Commerce breakfast to hear update from Assemblyman Colin Schmitt… https://t.co/2ZtmciKvz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[FITMOJI | sorry the colour of my #wod is hard to read will fix next time. first good sesh in way too long . .… https://t.co/p838zSW6gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Guy if you want this #UNSTOPPABLE T-shirt you only 24 more hours then it’s gone 20% of all proceeds go to #dav… https://t.co/skedxrAQcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖💖💖💖💖💖💖 💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖 💖💖                         💖💖 💖💖                           💖💖 💖💖                         💖💖 💖💖… https://t.co/G86I4nLFfp]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great time to kick off the winter blues with feasting on a NOLA buffet and dancing to Zink and the Oxides! $49 pp… https://t.co/pzHi8OZ3wa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Money23Green you deserve every part of this hit! You also are a world class flopper and not a nice guy at all. I w… https://t.co/lwaEJzLUyS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This hot mama’s new locks! #ombrehair #goldwell #behindthechair #modernsalon #ericashairstudio #hairstudiosix @ Hai… https://t.co/DSgvRcelVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week’s opportunities for Students: -Sr scholarship mtg during enrichment Tues. - Ironworkers here Wed 1020 am… https://t.co/7bImOKgJbQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brymarrr @ChewyChulo @BankofAmerica there is one! The fraud dept! Trust me I’ve looked into it hahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have another Nighthawk in the family! Yay, Grayson! 💙 #ungdahlonega #mamaisalumna https://t.co/ylSN5H0jZJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear Martin Scorsese: Will you please direct a biopic about Freddie Mercury &amp; also have Rami Malek play the lead? Thank you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KENS5 #AKidney4Zenzali  https://t.co/WFVmxf8A7f https://t.co/X7vq0N6jeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so pleased with #FFF. Job extremely well done @icp. Can’t say enough. I’m fuckin touched. 🥰🤡🔪 I love Freedom an… https://t.co/ZoD4jh4NPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blizzard Arena is even better than I’d expected. If you haven’t gone yet and you live in LA, get out there! https://t.co/5ztZTkPv9l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me, 2010: horoscopes are dumb, we need to let logic dictate our decisions and feelings   Me, 2019: Mercury is in re… https://t.co/tVrjeage4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patrici15767099 @kjoypohl Black List like in Hollywood’s next best thing?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SjCattledog @dogcelebration awesome, way to start my day. Seeing happy old throwbacks.. Have a good day. Bye the w… https://t.co/VZwFsyFV6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[#collected1fortoday #ishowedup #growingoldgracefully #thisknee #abetterme #beautifuldisaster @ Stow, Ohio https://t.co/rJsjY5X2ys]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is important that we strive to distinguish Bernie’s real limitations (from the perspective of left intersectiona… https://t.co/HFOv28oGnR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1kxavier Had to drop the baby Pic too because I was cute 💓 https://t.co/zwQ6ngx2NI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Abigail_Larson @sispurrier These are gorgeous— where do u find the finished product?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andyjamesdalton Spike Lee is a purest. While his actions spoke otherwise, he is truly a class act. He received an Oscar-finally! Well done!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Las Juliantinas brincando a conclusiones por la pinche voz de un robot de YouTube que nos dijo qué si va ver una ju… https://t.co/aAThrdjenD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back to Nashville and adulting. Missing Portuguese people and scaring @garysnowpatrol with my nervous energy.… https://t.co/ov0cXcGWbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @GarBear4Trump @SpriteJ11 @stlpcs @Patti_Sc60 @lizcabrera55 @Bigbillshater @callawaykeith… https://t.co/i2pxddgJMZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m “The Kitty Cat Dance Was A Huge Thing” years old. 😂😂😂  The Kitty Cat Dance. https://t.co/sCPwMocDWJ via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @SerenityFirth #CrookedHillary https://t.co/4T5FkVCX8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[„Take personal democracy to the next level!“  Wunderbares Schlusswort zum Talk über Journalismus.  Danke an… https://t.co/6u51KwAJfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Davidkuenstle @ThisIsROCK2019 I agree with some of these. It's very tough. I rank him up there with The Ramones as my favorite musicians!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesPPierce Apparently Dershowitz and Giuliani have been taking the same medication which has rendered them incoherent nincompoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[“It is amazing how much love and laughter they bring into our lives and even how much closer we become with each ot… https://t.co/IpAUOTsfBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 39 degrees with a 27 degree windchill.  Go home Mobile, you’re drunk.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Levendaki17 So what if it is? It’s health care at no cost. Call it anything you like. You don’t have to worry abou… https://t.co/JL4yFp0FOv]]></document><document><![CDATA['Extinct' Formosan clouded #leopard sp... | Taiwan News https://t.co/HR2qxOAe1N 🐆]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve always shit on Tiger Balm (too weak!) but these Tiger Balm patches tho 👀👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 Star National Panhandle 13u Champs playing in 14u in the Opening Day Blast Xl in Tallahassee,Fl. Good job boys!!… https://t.co/NOKtBPGhdo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to see @JonTLangston again and meet him for the first time in Milledgeville!!! https://t.co/n92fa8do90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoodDayAtlanta kids need homework to finish work that they can’t finish in class.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is very Sad.   Others can scream over a microphone announcing prayer, in the streets. And a Christian can't of… https://t.co/i8ZMZV7Rgu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Khill82758 @mrsdurkinmuses @shannonrwatts @kelliohara @corbinbleu We have tickets for April.  Can’t wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round #4 for JRW’s testimony by the Commitee.. I think it is done!  No more questioning necessary!  #cndpoli]]></document><document><![CDATA[After Brunch photo ops at #sxsw2019 😍👌🏻🥂We wandered past some cool pop ups on Rainey but hanging with these girls w… https://t.co/u3ptMLfEzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul I'll tell you Canadians and everybody else aren't numb, we just can't figure out why Americans aren't in th… https://t.co/vCWf59XtWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorrisonsClass @mrspfisters_k @MsTMorrison @eaglesofEES That is awesome!!!  We will have a celebration after the grading period!!! 🎉🎉🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[TEXAS IS A FUCKING LIE ME And BELLA ARE GETTING CHICK FIL A RN    😩😩😩😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lostinmusic1982 Did you find somebody then? Great song. I can't believe he's gone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance #MSNBC Unfortunately a portion of that 60% don’t care about politics much like that portion of the Ge… https://t.co/R8XiqJ2uJZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[ADVKEN Owl Tank available👍 #advken #vapelife #advken #owltank #vapeatomizer #advkenowl #hotselling #stopsmoking… https://t.co/7cKZuMcQlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday is NOT in March but my beautiful sister and Aunt and my wonderful brother have birthdays!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just get writing!  Everyone has a story to tell.  Great time at morganchamber lunch and learn with Tamara Klein And… https://t.co/kIMy2haYyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great for early ed CTE teachers to try with young students #mindfulness]]></document><document><![CDATA[So many lies by @gop.... Cohen is right, they are putting Cohen on trial instead of the purpose of this hearing]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at The Stepping Stones Group? We're hiring in Macon, GA! Click for details: https://t.co/4TDsrLFXJJ #SLP #SLPeeps]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this tea with Jordyn, Khloe, and Tristan reminds me of when my “best friend” hooked up with my man (at the time) 🤷🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steveo031 @ShaneDaleABC15 Look at ASU’s roster for next year and get back to me Steve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovBillLee Any task force that doesn’t include removing the prohibition from cannabis is a farce]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me estoy enterando que el mensaje a las 3 AM de: Dónde estás? Es pa ir  a coger. Pinche inocencia la mía me cae.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Google @yahoo @Microsoft @Apple @Att @TMobile @USCellular @AP @Reuterstech @technology @WSJtech @BBCTech @Amazon .… https://t.co/TKum4DYbsj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us fix our eyes on Jesus, the author and perfecter of our faith (Hebrews 12:2). Stay focused on Him, this wor… https://t.co/2i28yVcGo5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waterflowerpml @SeaWorld The animals they keep after rescuing are deemed unreleasable by the NOAA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wonder if I should knit him little ear hats. https://t.co/qnR1cwamRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveHammActor @gigirules7 @awlasky @Backpackjohn1 @KMFras @mfarca @CattMcCreary @sweetishj @PoloOrtiz9 @BodManip… https://t.co/7qFiXmyDLh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I see myself playing a guitar on the ceiling upside in a vision idk seems kool tho]]></document></documents></author>