<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[CPFC to shelter homeless 'for years' after promising start to project https://t.co/Pa0syZK3nh This is how it’s done, Amazon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[One dead after stunt planes collide in mid-air near Yelahanka, India  https://t.co/BAlDLiKwT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to really get my head around how to write good RxJava code. It's an independent variable from the other Arch… https://t.co/t0qufnaYKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Yeah, they don’t really know you, and can’t vote for you, so there’s that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Torrance, CA? View our latest opening: https://t.co/kEwyvEehpa #Retail]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice dinner this evening at Texas Roadhouse in Murrels Inlet. https://t.co/CobVAAgDJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Honestly, sir, you just don’t put in the effort into your schemes you used to”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonathanWillis Kosky is not a tender of the future admit that a mistake was made and get a killer goalie or else w… https://t.co/8Yj9DxtcDG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story behind Odna Zhizn (A Life) is worth reading. A poignant work. The live recording with the @nyphil is fantastic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuillermoBGR @capi_april Tenian un DC-9-15, verdad? Junto a Quassar , y en Mty habia SAM con un DC9-32 y VARSA con… https://t.co/RhNiROiDzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a crazy idea that gravity will become weird feeling to the individuals living in the international space station]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let this sink in: 6,796 Americans killed in the $2.4 Trillion post-9/11 wars due to cockpit doors unlocking w/out 2… https://t.co/N3miqH4YLy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great afternoon with a great theatre artist. And pearcebunting is pretty good too. @ Arcadia University https://t.co/yKFeuPruh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fascinated by hotel carpets - I think I could be a ballroom carpet designer!!! (@ Luxor - Egyptian Ballroom in… https://t.co/2fImJ3aOt8]]></document><document><![CDATA[some things simply cannot be addressed and thoroughly worked through the first time or first couple of times.   rec… https://t.co/59vbNi45dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joliboucher Using Multimedia in the Classroom, taught at Fitchburg St. U., last summer.  One week, 8 A.M.-4 P.M.… https://t.co/pqQPA2zXyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattjenson Dude, I ABSOLUTELY love this song! You should listen to it live from South Africa. That's a great rendi… https://t.co/o1ejUNx1BG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByCodyHills I have been in more than a few meetings withGabe, he is as aloof (being nice) as they make’em. Also do… https://t.co/fy6BCN2qtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RevCiancio @Foodiechats @foodwinechickie @TravelingMurphy @j_cohl @HeavyMetalTeddy @WhiskiedWander @MyPrettyBrown… https://t.co/4tZA0MWkQL]]></document><document><![CDATA[The heart of the problem is usually a problem with the heart. When your heart is right w God. It will be right with others too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need some comedy. Fun Halloween game for the family.  Hide-and-seek with a Halloween twist. #laughter #lol #smile… https://t.co/OYlgolILJ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else wants @JuiceWorlddd to drop #deathraceforlove at 12:00AM ON FRIDAY ????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think you somehow got e-mails between POTUS and Senate Majority Leader]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are live with @PlaySpellbreak I have a lot to learn Let’s DoThis 💫🧙‍♂️🧙‍♂️🧙‍♂️💫https://t.co/JRpgAlFVyE #Spellbreak #Wizard #Twitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shedsandfins @Fight4T @SeanUnfiltered LOLOL  I love this cliche. As if teachers are CIA operatives.  As if we all… https://t.co/ShniaZDZYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IN_duckhunter @LindseyGrahamSC @JoeBiden @realDonaldTrump @VP It was something that happened for a few seconds and… https://t.co/hRfzvn48nx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@troyhall3 And sometimes it’s best to let the team create their own success.  #leadingfrombehind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AthleticsWshs @PrincipalAbney Bring your signed permission slips to me tomorrow! Room 1113! We are leaving at 3, y… https://t.co/0h2nUmsqPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamieGlazov @Alyssa_Milano She will never admit to any wrong doing. She is part of the loony left that sees things one way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@incarceratedbob Tells it like it is. Always did. That’s why he gets the respect he does]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early for my trip to NYC.  Should give me enough time to catch up on work.  Hoping for smooth trip (@ Peachy Air… https://t.co/K6qM95keon]]></document><document><![CDATA[Before the finale I’m going live at 7 pm,talking about all the things I seen y’all saying in my comments this seaso… https://t.co/Vo4EcMmRHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmfao the complications I come with are a matter of WHEN the wedding will be. Nothing more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All done upstairs except for some nail holes in the mouldings. Put the nail punch next to the bed last night, it's… https://t.co/dDjKy2M8fW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@V_actually @gaye_gallops @TheLast. didn't find nothing on Trump but destroyed a lot of guys lives and made one cried like a little bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me reach 100 followers — I’m halfway of the way there!  T H A N K S 4 THE S U P P O R T😁 https://t.co/47XrOmovKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe some people hate James Harden, the guy can just score. One of the best scorers in the NBA rn🔥💯🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kayeri The issues she's had do not effect her wellbeing. She is now living with two of the best horse vets in Kent… https://t.co/HMc7YAucuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@comicsandjack @iamsteranko @TheRealStanLee @ComicCrusaders @ComicCastPod @ComicBookRumors https://t.co/I58Cd9vzve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolWSD Fuck this shit. We had the money in a year where only a few teams were making a play at a transcendent… https://t.co/YFxIakJPxg]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@michaelCohen We the people understand that the Republicans are afraid of your truth, and will go to any length to… https://t.co/YGKyHDILRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Akamaimel Dallas is going all in for him. Miami doesn’t have a chance in hell. Flowers fits the scheme anyways]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is a man paging an endless list of passengers who is completely unable to pronounce French or Chinese names.… https://t.co/DA5ZRQlqVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AltChristians @Franklin_Graham @realDonaldTrump @VP Unfortunately, it doesn’t offend conservative Christians who s… https://t.co/foznNsXCdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chaz3232 @RyanAFournier The new trade deal that's putting tariffs on items so now that farmers have to get a buyout that one?]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know, when you spill coffee on paper it soaks in so fast. But when you try to mop up coffee with paper it doesn’t work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump President cry baby doesn’t like getting made fun of get the hell over it go back to golfing drurin… https://t.co/JTYTOnnyLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/6ihzGM8bY7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow can’t believe David is 68! Holy crap @ Levittown, Pennsylvania https://t.co/JWWRCe5MpT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the view of # Pittsburgh here a top #MtWashington just spoke to public works director who says extra crews… https://t.co/xK5thMA6i5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#F1 @Speedcaster Gallery: 2019 Alfa Romeo C38 keeps its colors  https://t.co/cm98izS4uC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adam_gutheil @TomEggemeier @CynicalPSurly I blame 2nd half start on Grant. TV guys even said you could see in thei… https://t.co/10R1FZbQcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great job of clearing Donner’s Summit by the valiant plow drivers! #CAwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmaLaineAuthor For a YA spy novel set in the early 80’s, I’m using Light and Dark Elves to provide a parallel to t… https://t.co/XQQPwcLFp3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javiwankenobi Pero están preparando tour: #SmashingPumpkins &amp; #NoelGallager después de eso.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always good to see the fam come out and have a good time at our #IslandBlockConcertSeries inside @HOBAnaheim. Make… https://t.co/93Rlxh8X7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governor Kim Reynolds [@KimReynoldsIA] appointed six Iowans to Iowa Commission of Veterans Affairs ICVA. Congrats t… https://t.co/MQ5sKeLg1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  a Reminder.. @SenSanders 's Plan to have 'Public State schools' tuition Free... this means No NCAA scholarshi… https://t.co/P6XxLPhJ4v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToddBPhilly Doing the same thing with Game of Thrones. I have no motivation today]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey! If your wondering about your car and want to make a checklist, click on this link and understand why your air… https://t.co/kTfgj0ySaC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Isn't your arrival in Viet Nam 50 years too late? As I recall you were suppose to go via the draft… https://t.co/F4gXfdEaXB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good shooting!  Wisdom: it’s better to be tried by 12 than carried by 6!  When shooting back NEVER aim to wound!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This cat is trippppping if she thinks she’s going to sleep in my room while she’s caterwauling heck no bby]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WriterMera They are demonizing pain patients. Primarily they demonize those who still have access to treatment eve… https://t.co/bF3TH2zZk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think cfiffie needs to snap some photos of my new toy 🤔 #ThePornstar #lonestartrucks #millerind #century5130… https://t.co/I7zc99Jj3M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaloneySuzanne He’s saying he wants the ministry to have its rightful place -that’s be the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Johnny fields like to hang around the little boys he moleste, hints little daddy Ronald lil brother, Michael, and r… https://t.co/Pd3BJG6s00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corruption, and fear of getting ratted out for their own transgressions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When serious minds are lacking information for the ears that heard, they attempt to overuse whatever they heard to… https://t.co/FQWjo1qVRm]]></document><document><![CDATA[No sorry, this is where I draw the line. I’m throwing this dog off a cliff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPLeader Yes. I'm sure they told them he would be discussing Trump! Big news you idiot!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ToniDewet You're so good at replying to everyone... :) Not my strong suite... :( Happy V-Day Toni...]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Chinese buffet got them for cheap.... otherwise y’all go in the boats and put in the work for y’all “cheap” cra… https://t.co/YRsZJJQiUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_CodyDavis @realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends And who left him in prison and didn't bother to negotiate his release?… https://t.co/oJYmvsmRcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexi_virginelli Those are battle scars be proud of them! You earned them !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyD Hi, Philip I have been meaning to ask you to cover a certain topic. It regard the trucking industry our ec… https://t.co/Jj2BzJsBUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[White walker.  Telluride, Colorado (12/31/18) #telluride #colorado #skislopes #frosty https://t.co/yNvBTuc8FK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell the @packers front office that off season it’s really off season. #FreeAgency @NFL]]></document><document><![CDATA[My co-worker is trying to kill me...  9M Scovilles.... I'm scared....  #worldhottestchocolatebar #chilihead… https://t.co/aBLsvOa4US]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made a new twitter for art purposes. Gonna delete this one. Follow me here @devonghoul if you care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ve all come across some real asshole coaches who feel the need to drive their guys into the dirt over and over.… https://t.co/HVGr0k9bXY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Holiday Inn for hosting brunch &amp; Thank you Daniel’s Desserts for the awesome hockey cookies.… https://t.co/qALxr2FUef]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_benjiblanco I was iffy about Apex but then I played one game and it is so good 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy Futhermore, as a Catholic (Christian) it is an article of belief, which is held by our Protestant c… https://t.co/nTmwE4GzdN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomansDay to all the amazing women out there fighting everyday to make this world a better place, you inspire me 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[#txlege #SpecialElection HD 145 update.   A big congrats in order for @Moralesfor145. A great race put up by… https://t.co/k6sDLo7woS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyLolaRyan That’s because the cats listen better than she does, and they set the bar very low.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris You are never going to president of the United States lady]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Oxbow Buckwild by @oxbowbeer @ Monk's Cafe — https://t.co/1b6z22ExGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@c3convertase Good on you for not taking that shit. Now concentrate on you becoming a doctor, the world be damned!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dana’s flowers from V Day are still looking good. #rosesarered @ Lake Saint Louis, Missouri https://t.co/RAcfv1Topt]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Spurs have recalled Lonnie Walker from the G League. He's scored 20-plus points in seven of his last 10 games with… https://t.co/weR132UVyH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost ig_nycity with get_repost ・・・ presents  I G  O F  T H E  D A Y  P H O T O | bennycchan  T H E M E | Night M… https://t.co/aUYBizno6h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daniellendoll What’s your personal opinion on scooters in Frederick? For or Against?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @Jeffrey52095461 @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/8qtxRnl1oK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @ICWestFB WR Tate Crane for receiving kudos from the @LemmingReport !! #MakeItHappen #CowboyUp… https://t.co/XCHaTN5CtF]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Miami Heat are now 2-7 in February  They have a +0.7 net rating in 256 minutes with Justise Winslow on the cour… https://t.co/Vo1sMLUMgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[17. Night Mode because I don’t need the sun in my eyes at all hours of the day]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love the compassion in this man's voice. Humans helping humans let's not forget about that part. There's a reason… https://t.co/hIc3UFrqWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Earlier. Really nice.. - Drinking an Alien Church Double Dry Hopped With Idaho Gem And Conditioned On Soursop Purée… https://t.co/ayCDc7g1cy]]></document></documents></author>