<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @colbertlateshow Then there’s trump!  The proponent of hate crimes to the extent that HE’S a hate crime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler @Surfermom77 @realDonaldTrump Tellup.  Let's not sit on our hands like Kilkery did. Kets work and win like Trump does.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So sad. I remember having a really in-depth conversation with him about fame at a house party in Hollywood Hills on… https://t.co/a8yxQ6BUxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASimplePatriot @SavtheRepublic *Ghost in the graveyard  *Riding double on a bike or riding on the handlebars *pick… https://t.co/zHLzRHMJ75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulObrienUSA @coolhandjux @DineshDSouza That doesn’t excuse the current WH occupants bad behavior! Blame everybody else!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need our left we need our right so we can agree to disagree and meet in middle to continue to advance our great… https://t.co/LL6LZhZbqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸This Offer Only For U.S.A👌 Get $1000 Visa Gift Card Now!👉 👉Money  Back Guarante👉 https://t.co/WXiDza1xrH  So You… https://t.co/qbOqxzVx8O]]></document><document><![CDATA[wow what the heck is wrong with Marty saying that crap.. delusional!  Does anyone think that pool push was real or… https://t.co/JNesV8ZLF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bills aim to improve career and technology education https://t.co/JqYQWgwLU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all have no respect at all teachers don’t ge toaod enough for childish ass motherfuckers like y’all]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Look if you ever think I don’t have Jesus, I got 3 Bibles right here” -@MadisonSauls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @artandfeminism @POWArts @MuseumModernArt and @Wikimedia for another incredible edit-a-thon!… https://t.co/B1wiUyphnl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning how to pick cotton. @LME_Lions @RoundRockISD https://t.co/gHjMApRrPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lukeylux Yeah certain places like dominoes wouldn’t deliver to my apartment cuz i was to close to Sf state but doo… https://t.co/l4nNoTeEqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND YOU DON’T REMEMBER EVERY TIME YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE MINE FOREVER FOR ETERNITY https://t.co/4RnI4QEKvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak Peek of our #NewSpringCollection of products: Color Your Pout with these new water based Colour tinted pens..… https://t.co/52otONlggt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Omg two days ago it said ten days of rain and possibly snow lol https://t.co/xHCNlmIyTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peyweeeezy Ask him if he knows the deets about the Jordyn, Khloe, &amp; Tristen situation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carlquintanilla so Bethune ends by intimating Pilot may not have taken manual control of a plane,'s system that willy nilly FAILS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FolderRed Jackson is nicer and more scenic  But more expensive and more crowded]]></document><document><![CDATA[#islanders fans are classless. The guys gave you 9 years of hard work and that’s the welcome. Shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are my kind of vegetables   @TheFreshMarket https://t.co/vQdW50ynlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[DT: I cannot work in the WH. I can’t have DC schedule.   I belong with the American People on the road. I have been… https://t.co/kruoP3qApL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every afternoon after session I get in my car, sanitize my hands and eat the same nut and cheese snack on the way t… https://t.co/6jHiDgZdjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEllenShow This is Hudson when he was a puppy. I’ll let you meet him when you book @AshleyMcBryde on your show.… https://t.co/GFl6vhQpvx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last week I told one of my coworkers she was so old that she sat next to Jesus in the third grade. Without skipping… https://t.co/BakXEjJxwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Immaturity, not my cup of tea in friends or in anyone really. Not sure how 20+ year olds can continuously be immature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andreakrey @Goatmug @thehorror71 @Kates254 @FalcaoPunch @darthbills @JoeySalads @AOC Watch those charities dry up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another outrageous, easy-to-prove lie by Trump. He is delusional to keep thinking he can just “say it and make it t… https://t.co/MjrKOkgTCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again feeling like there isn't a single person in my life who actually knows me lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother son team getting it done. #studio #photobybbmoonsammy #photography📸 #cleaning #teamwork @ Sussex County, New… https://t.co/Md4nu92Pk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannastrology So iF YOU NEED SOME MARIJUNA PLZ Replying to @ROSE52941131]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @tim_holtz fans! Look what I saw at my local shop! Maybe I can convince @mariojrossi to come for a visit. Would… https://t.co/JSFPfuWaJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This crazy old cat lady would like to see these beautiful creatures live long in peace]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so sad to have to post this, but I'm asking that if you have it in your heart, please help my cousin's family l… https://t.co/Lkv9s6lU4x]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TeamNoSugar time to get back focused and start feeling better about myself ☺️ #healthyMe https://t.co/osVfXpggr4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nategettys15 @jcowell15 I definitely look the best in this photo if we want to be honest I’m so pretty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone know this little Panther we will be honoring tomorrow? I’ll give you a hint- he’s rocked a few different hai… https://t.co/DgR9K7wM2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m terrified of snakes and this video took me so off guard I almost fell backwards down the stairs 😂😂😂😂😂🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KezzaSim @Devoted2Death @VersaillesFam @Mathilde_Felton It’s a Funko...you can google and locate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A negative space painting of a positive pup. ⚫⚪🐶 . . . Lately beautiful inspiration has been coming from many new p… https://t.co/Rtp9zwUFLq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princess_snide @Popdust Woah bitch calm the fuck down lmao no need to insult me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will my body go into shock if I quit drinking and smoking at the same time??? Stay tuned]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful tribute. Lisa Quiroz was a such a humble and beautiful person.  Always giving great advice and connecting… https://t.co/aX1gh82EOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @IvankaTrump I wish more was done for hard-working, single people with no children.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr. John Henrik Clarke and Dr. Amos Wilson - Taking Back our Minds https://t.co/jJWzEalmpx via @YouTube👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheryll1950 You can learn a lot by objectively reading the comments. There are some interesting points there. Of c… https://t.co/CjNooL4ypz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlfredLewislll @Cam_Mob56 I have a friend who used to be. He was raised in a strict church and was a true believer… https://t.co/gCrn7NCd37]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BLACKout . #BHM #BlackHistoryMonth #BlackHistoryMonth2019 #WhitneyMuseum #WhitneyBiennial  #WhitneyBiennial2019… https://t.co/4FfOAPnojj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prageru It was fantastic!!  Roseanne was a terrific guest and you never cut her off!!  Thank you!!  Can’t wait for… https://t.co/58pVPi5IVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nation_myers Didn't recognize most of the  contestants. Especially the winner. Fun idea, but too many obscure people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mememoreme @leahmcelrath I want to see all of them and their plans I am not dismissing anyone just yet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesss!!! Thanks @EM_RESUS  and New York Presbyterian Hospital for this GREAT resource  - a “Songs to do CPR by Play… https://t.co/PdXodVgxFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I LOVE coming every year to see these guys I’m proud to call friends. They rock their lives every time they go to w… https://t.co/tC7oAUOygw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisfarley71 @MLB I think it will be between Nats, Phillies, and Mets to win the division and posisbly one will b… https://t.co/MdeWUQ2dpu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrownWomanKing @MayaShotYou @keepitrare @wessideTy Cooooolllllll what zone are you from?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I had some major anxiety when I thought about moving out of my house. How can I want something so bad and be… https://t.co/kepukCihgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto Obama revoked her citizenship.  End of story.  I hear Yemen is pretty this time of year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She said drop a selfie and name your favorite anime show.... someone said Love and Hip Hop 🤦🏽‍♀️ https://t.co/YGxowMmVqn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Oh my people are STARVING TO DEATH.  And Pelosi says no???  Then babbles about walls being immoral?  Omg unbelievable!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @Zwoodbutcher Imagine having a limb being sawed off without any anesthesia at all. How can anyone be so c… https://t.co/0oxTZLkWxB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder if it has to do with sibling interaction -  if you grew up with a big family interaction you’ve had no practice doing things alone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@corey_gantt Cool 😎 he will be crying when we’re drinking listening to Chris Stapleton without him]]></document><document><![CDATA[I accidentally closed a pocket knife of my pinky today 😭😩 I refused to go get stitches and just kept changing the g… https://t.co/MCzECN8Qjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I tell you that I’m gonna “close my eyes for five more minutes”, DO NOT LET ME!!! Because five minutes turns int… https://t.co/r5W90JgDgt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taylor: 💟 Us: OMG GUYS SHE’S RELEASING NEW MUSIC TONIGHT!! Us at midnight: well we’re all boo boo the fools]]></document><document><![CDATA[She wore ‘a long cloak of the same brocade as her wedding gown, lined with a soft white fur and with a deep collar… https://t.co/KCGNj6AeL0]]></document><document><![CDATA[What happened to his gag order? It's as if tRump's cronies think laws are simply suggestions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Izzy’s critique “Last night was amazing !!!! .... everyone has such amazing voices that I was freaking out - Yanno… https://t.co/dZDDSdD1ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesLGarrett Try reaching out to A GS Rescue in Texas. Just a thought from an Aggie Wife/Mom, dog lover, and rescue lover.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleissmeister Let’s make it official, shall we? Do you want Khloe Kardashian to be the next Bachelorette?]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARIES | The Pisces New Moon emphasizes your 12th House of Endings, encouraging you to release unnecessary attachmen… https://t.co/hxSCuwMT4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reykjavik, Iceland following an exclusive Associated Press interview with Maduro, who said he was willing to meet P… https://t.co/1yIM0Bfjhg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy President's Day.  Talk about a job with major responsibility and stress!  Bless our President's past, present… https://t.co/x6X6z5HcRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badalllergies @maxbeckaaa Yes lmao I cut it wrong:( I can't even bully him right]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a rough end to our week, stuck between missing Tyler and getting back into our “regular” Tyler-less routi… https://t.co/8NC7uXAjaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaCastruccio @GloriousAllianc Happy Birthday. May you have many more years filled with health, love, lots of peppe… https://t.co/JPohiG1Zjk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OliverMcGee @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse @AOC @CoryBooker @BernieSanders @KamalaHarris Love those 😍 DEMONIC-RATs!  Tee hee hee]]></document><document><![CDATA[The upside of all of the rain we've been getting here in San Diego lately.... ahhhh, those beautiful wildflowers...… https://t.co/apnsHhkw71]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re bachelorette for the night.... Bad moms, wine, leftover sushi and puppy cuddles!  #yesplease #forthewin… https://t.co/jq8cC4mWY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kush_jones_ @cahaldj @neuropunkdj @RinseFM BOSS SHOW🧯🧯 https://t.co/fGn9LGHaxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Determinaciones cada día..... en Miami, Florida https://t.co/bGtw5OkTZ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I find myself NEEDING to be at the gym. So good for mental clarity and kinda just lets you forget about the world]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok just sayin Sarah as much as Micheal kept you in the dark about Megan. He did the same mother lovin thing to her!… https://t.co/MdYgXzeGbx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring has sprung! ☀️🌺 Time to get out and do some yard work! 👩🏼‍🌾 #spring2019 @ The Shepherd House https://t.co/o34RVaDSQ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday this girl I work with got on my ass because I had two tip buckets on my bar and apparently one of them wa… https://t.co/4Zj04yZpjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inchighpvteye Awe that was sweet. Meh he called me the “C” word!! 😳🤭 I’m like “uhh is this to me? Even if you can’… https://t.co/JWkwaEJqtO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Esas escusas que das cuando ya no querés hablar con alguien. Jajaja por favor ya tenemos 30! https://t.co/BKev17ApBP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Singing my heart out to duelo @ the kitchen &amp; all the guys wanna come @ me Lmfaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting home at 6 am after driving all night after a @russelled show is well worth it ♥️ love you thanks for another great night ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Go back to North Korea with that shit... this is The United States of America where we have a cons… https://t.co/F0Z0dnh2do]]></document><document><![CDATA[I try to know a bartender at every place I go, and it's the best decision I've ever made.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Cass Park! It’s time to rally behind our community! Let’s make it to the Top 4. #HockeyvilleUSA #Contest https://t.co/rJZkqLKZYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_viciwill The Bay Area is its own little world in a lot of ways, and there's great stuff to see and I love it, but… https://t.co/nZNO2HEQC7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarlaBechtel @nitagale @trevorlv31 @Wodins @RyanAFournier @CatOnA_TinRoof Um you mean the Republican owner of the… https://t.co/AeTjC7ijrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out this short interview from the Hollywood Premiere of @HitlerBigfoot @Aidan_Always @ATurnerNews @Bestvoices]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at My Dining Room ;) ;D in Independence, MO https://t.co/g0CF3jqlby]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m in desperate need of summer, as I would like my freckles and tan skin back. And before anyone starts with me, I… https://t.co/tq0a4Aw0H5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kobebryant @Granity How upset would you be if you found out that muscle knots can be removed immediately anywhere… https://t.co/rRhKVCJNIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello my pretty #asus #rog #heroxi #motherboard #gaming #pc @ASUS_ROG https://t.co/T15XOOgFs6]]></document></documents></author>