<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Becker_ @PhilaStreets @PhillyMayor Keep fighting the good fight Dave!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry Apathy of the American people have allowed our Country to be taken over. Allowing ourselves to be divide… https://t.co/hZHAjJl7a6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Not IMHO. Lots of bluster, but Cohen more than handed it all back by saying that the GOP members are… https://t.co/2339zDTsfw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erininnashville @saraclark Being blocked by Ramsey is a badge of honor. It’s even funnier when I get recruiters ca… https://t.co/DTZklBI2G7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yancey_todd @CNN @FareedZakaria Todd I never voted for #Obama not for either election but every time I see “he did… https://t.co/2sa0TzraWa]]></document><document><![CDATA[My assistant travelwithbruna just called saying she will not show to work today.... lazy #Schnauzer mode. Should I… https://t.co/oynTXASVlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrequelMemesBot I don't remeber episode 7 involving a trade dispute but go off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[the 10th World Festival of Youth and Students. In the mid-1970s, Jim Jones, who developed the cult Peoples Temple,… https://t.co/WC8PYGX4h2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great happy artists =happy students.Come have fun with us.  Great classes. Paint on canvas, watercolor, collage, cl… https://t.co/W2zW5BnLSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And if you’re still filling yours out: here’s the spreadsheet https://t.co/2lTvUnNOa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[How many more performances by American Idols alumni are there in these Oscars? #Oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to Ithaca College! Check out my scavenger hunt video. #icvj @AllisonFrisch07 https://t.co/hA2KydZDUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls Bball starts the evening with a 58-23 victory over @LightningLhs. Great job girls!!!! Let’s go Hawks!!!!… https://t.co/si12B35N6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theonlyneya No no, he poops outside just fine now and he doesnt bark when I leave for work. But he is also kinda c… https://t.co/kxIaHk4lfq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And let the peace of God rule in your hearts, to the which also ye are called in one body; and be ye…… https://t.co/AC0M4fDCma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ntdaily The @achahockey Nationals are coming to Dallas starting on 3/21. Great chance to help promote the sport!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time for #puttingpatientsfirst   Let’s pass #collectivenegotiation now .@CarlHeastie .@AndreaSCousins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brandy Gutierrez, aka Big On Chocolate, Not On Romance! #chavezhighschool #chavezlobos #classof2005 🃏🎲😘🎭🌀❄⚡ @ Houst… https://t.co/mf8DyinE98]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #OpioidEpidemic In 6 Charts Designed To Deceive You 🤬  @LasVegasSun @NevadaNewsNow @OpioidTaskForce @FDA_Track… https://t.co/3DUzjccqEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[A look at My Brother's Keeper at five (@edsurge @MJMadda): https://t.co/bFnAPrg95r #edchat #edu #Lead #Learn]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Three Californians contract measles on flight into SFO - San Francisco Chronicle: Three California… https://t.co/vtPTMC1uP1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sixteen Counties by @allagashbrewing @ Big Philly Beerfest — https://t.co/WyLfqjCixO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caden Fordham 2021 DB  Ponte Vedra High School  @Caden_Fordham  Offered- University of Colorado  @Coach_mtucker… https://t.co/BQ0qyklv2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we all had a friend like @TankSchottle wouldn’t life be a better place.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Juwan_Joseph3 I know like people making fake accounts of me. They don't even deserve to have social media.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thekidet retweet for vets! 11% of homeless are veterans. with ptsd and mental health issues. Venmo rob-donley-2. C… https://t.co/cPRGfy0j4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si Señor. #Mezcal (@ Bear Hollow Village in Park City (Utah), UT) https://t.co/0H8dZGP8Xv https://t.co/1Vn13r4fVx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walking into art museums these days reminds me of going to the bars in college, seeing all the old familiar faces.… https://t.co/NNS0Xe2EUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[See our latest #Monett, MO job and click to apply: Technical Support Representative (night shift) - https://t.co/CyYgNTvkGJ #CustomerService]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cern_lXXl @zypisfy @ellen5e @PolyRhuagh @DB_Grimwalker @mikenedie @Dylon59556561 @tklforgiven @Wolfpak561… https://t.co/QMazMuSdiF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly couldn’t have asked for a better 21st birthday...except for losing my ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people make ‘quick questions’ not so quick by mentioning the quickness of the question?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Zion shuts it down ppl w say Coach K cares about his best interest. If Zion played for Kentucky and decided the… https://t.co/oimjIBGSog]]></document><document><![CDATA[Came here to find ladies and ended up playing cornhole the whole time lol smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@strandquist @TMobile @JohnLegere @BuddeGail @daneandreasen A glimpse of the near future!]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are so proud to welcome Emily to the Wesley team as our new Marketing Assistant! Many thanks to our partners at… https://t.co/6uYkcJqc7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[This little light of mine... Reminds me of a set of photos I called "breakthrough" since the sun was breaking throu… https://t.co/XOUnFTh9B7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahKSilverman @lowetze1 Dems still blame him and his followers for what Russia and GOP vote tampering accomplish… https://t.co/YIuyfe1LDv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmIOnCrazyPills @JustinTrudeau I think that’s every day that ends in “y”...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grateful to be with this amazing human being. 🤓💕⚾️ #mylegacy #prouddaddy #springtraining2019 https://t.co/ALFn0ibVdg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kar_marr @TRYVNS @iamdesireb I understand what your saying. I just think this goes over everyone’s head though. No… https://t.co/FhgGuGJCNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pretty good pale ale great of citrus 🍊 flavor to it great with a Ruben hoppy aftertaste also not as good as the p… https://t.co/u1qyEbfwQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnTargetFishing @BlueCollarFishn and that beard.... swooon..... i just wanna run my hands thru it all day.... oh wait...]]></document><document><![CDATA[*taran taking her passport pic* (me always thinking how she is my sister bc she looks asian) *lady turns camera on… https://t.co/kISUdv6KUQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snowy day in The Chi but I'm bouta be OWWWWT!!! @ Oakbrook Center https://t.co/0OMV5VajxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paige__LWC @tractarians This is in Scotland 🏴󠁧󠁢󠁳󠁣󠁴󠁿 of all places! And evidence of absence is not absence of evide… https://t.co/Q3oEb3s15p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meanwhile I'm mostly on here to self-promote and complain about the potholes on 17th street. 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[When tRUmp comments about the Epstein scandal seeming like such a long time ago, he is actually reminiscing about t… https://t.co/FYj5EuiXMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people are incorrectly reading this tweet as criticism of @realDonaldTrump rather than as praise for Charles II.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ballou1010xl @StopholusPrime $800 equals 27 bottles of Jameson back home......just sayin......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NYCMayor @NYCMayorsOffice @realDonaldTrump #FakeMayor #exploiting #Ignorants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LMcLachlan60 @MonteMcNaughton You either accept the science, or you don't. I do. I believe surgeons are better at… https://t.co/LrgUMWsQeC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers Um, there's no copy editors any more, since all reading is free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#aristotle #quality #act #habits by #stoicgorilla #tvwriting #screenwriting #amediting #amwriting #amrewriting… https://t.co/qi86PNulxq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Limited Time Specials  1 hour for $20 2 hours for $35 3 hours for $50 4 hours for $65 5 hours for $80 6 hours for $… https://t.co/GaP3MLDh0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[some of y’all never got grounded when you missed curfew by one minute and it shows]]></document><document><![CDATA[This coming week is a stretch So much music to work on, so many classes to study for midterms and catch up on assig… https://t.co/vaneopIOtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bag Chasin💰. Welcome To Brick-Fil-A! We Fenna Go To Warr. #rapper #rappers #mixtape #mixtapes #needbeats #producers… https://t.co/oahg1RrKXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSteelCrew @ravenfannews @Gr4yson_ @GoatPhilip @AdamSchefter Bruh just give up and quit living in the past we ar… https://t.co/LZVQmPw4is]]></document><document><![CDATA[what a long ass time. i cant believe i’ve been complaining for 7 years wow. here’s to another 7. ☺️☺️… https://t.co/CMzR4u1kOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice progress from this young jr... kid has a great mindset and tremendous hand speed. Excited to get him ready for… https://t.co/S1GrMBQNGs]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/lQjoGZl8yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[...do not need tax help. QE saved the rich while people lost their jobs and homes. The tax credits tied to hiring w… https://t.co/Fmcz6hlNtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ljspoon   New Dirty Machine single “9:05” produced by Matty J (Travis Scott, T-Pain)  https://t.co/j0aZbvB0ii… https://t.co/ly0YBIhBCw]]></document><document><![CDATA[America has given us a lot, it is time for us to give something back to America. America gave us freedom, respect t… https://t.co/51m3HQSX2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Poor rebounding effort by the Rebels gives Missouri essentially a 5-point possession.  Rebels lead 19-15 8:52 1H.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado It’s almost as if having it in the winter isn’t that smart]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Here's a little 'She's a Lady' for ya, originally by the legendary @realsirtomjones)  "Isaac, what are you doing?"… https://t.co/dlGau9hCZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FuckinBrian1 @joerogan So far, this dude is my president for 2020. So far]]></document><document><![CDATA[USCS Winter Heat 360 Sprints | Southern Raceway 2.23.19 https://t.co/1s5FHE9GCo via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinWhite__40 Hope you had a great Birthday! We can’t wait to see you play at the next level!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RARRRRR @RealTT2020 Same thing with me. Join in 2009. Hardly used tell 2016.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaomiPescovitz @FOX9 @TimBlotzFOX9 Congratulations Naomi. Good Luck in your New Job. We’ll miss you in MN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Student Engagement @linfieldcollege as part of inauguration week! Our students are doing incredible things!… https://t.co/pfGPPJVT9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zackwhittaker This feels like it has parallels to the due process violations many colleges have had to address ove… https://t.co/kzbbhsSNfU]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Indivisible #Democrats #Progressives #Independents #TheResistance #Resist #BlueWave2020 #IndividualNumber1 #MAGA… https://t.co/2OwvtImTsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants.” ❤️ RIP @KarlLagerfeld]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JTJ24 That being said either all games but one have an asterisk or none do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever appeals to the law against his fellow man is either a fool or a coward. Whoever cannot take care of himself… https://t.co/UE0Yx19HTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My wife and I just made contributions to @SamiHamed for Tucson City Council. We are both very proud to support such… https://t.co/jVWJCD1kkC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zigmanfreud you have never been sincere in your life. any answer you get, you will twist to hate,]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RetiredSkeptic perfect use for old trash..ppl just don't think ya know..have great night bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[Race seasons gotta be getting close, it's 3:15am I'm laying in bed can't sleep and thinking about setups for a car… https://t.co/A2Zc9hp4KV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you shoot 40+ shots and less than 50% from the field, I don’t care how many points you score.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you expect from an ex-bartender with no political experience? She's like a bull in a China shop with no hor… https://t.co/qNU2z6NvB6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. Just got caught up on everything I missed. Thanks #YankeesTwitter!  Definitely still watching the replays of both games though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AfterRMC @DanielRiolo Merci aussi pour la touche d’Histoire sur la Juve. C qd même mieux de parler d’histoire que… https://t.co/MLKqqkv8qZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[FIU Softball has been nothing but impressive this season with taking today’s double header. They’re now 13-5 on the season. #FIUSoftball]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Teachers met at the #Florida Chatauqua and formed the @floridaea #otd 1886. @ DeFuniak Springs, Florida https://t.co/MEF0kgm1AC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EscoBlades Jaguar cry every time he listenes to Eminem now https://t.co/0rxFyPXxbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t understand that the 25th Amendment is part of the Constitution, you are not fit to serve in Congress.… https://t.co/prS5K72JGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Screen on my phone broke. And idk any of my passwords so I just have twitter on my old ass Kindle. Sweeeeet. See y’all on the other side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that the Jonas brothers are back, hopefully One Direction will pick up the slack]]></document><document><![CDATA[Iwish the freaking familyseparation with the children would stop so we can get on already to start working on UScit… https://t.co/3UdiWhCnIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI (with PHOTOS) - https://t.co/7EJcm63r7Y #LLsports #PaGirlsHoops @LCHS1022  @LancasterMenno]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scowen13 It won’t. But like those damned scooters, I imagine cities will be stuck with these robots soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[My daily therapy . Be and stay blessed. 👊👊👊 – ♫Nunu's Sunrise by Kori Linae Carothers, from #SoundHound https://t.co/UAuFGtQoi4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @stlpcs @DonIsMyGuy @bunnycat007 @PinoyDances @stoughton_sam @KennRWeeks @CallMyForest @tonguepiercer… https://t.co/bEohvj7gql]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Oscar2019 peaked with the singing of When A Cowboy Trades His Spurs For Wings performed by Gillian Welch and David… https://t.co/Qcwfns5jxh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico There not scared Smart people no you do not tell the TRUTH !!!!!]]></document></documents></author>