<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump did you lie about the security clearance on national TV? How can you sit there and lie so calmly like… https://t.co/k22Q0PQJzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@My_Tweet_Lord I have a brother and sister in law who are Methodists...they are watching their church be torn apart… https://t.co/cYCs2e6lnh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Food is really good on premises. #sojospaclub #sojo #spa #nj #newyork #nyc #lifestylesoftherichanddysfuntional… https://t.co/qKHGiUoaIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pitchfork Who can blame the man? #irony #oscars The @TheAcademy needs to step up and into the present moment. They… https://t.co/WgFXk0RBjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[SB | FINAL - KSU 6, UC 1 (G1), UC 6, KSU 5 (G2).  Golden Eagles rally for a split against the Thorobreds in Saturda… https://t.co/5FWKqEa2Xk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Saturday plans. 🍩  @Toppot ‘s version of @girlscouts #samoas cookies. 😋 https://t.co/5irR1X2Y0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @amphetamine47 for the awesome dumbo boots and Disney necklace. ❤️ you]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please follow @aisdpd . We need 1000 followers by LivePD tomorrow night’ we can do this together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my twitter is A MESS!!! Somebody tell these babies to go to sleep! 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsfaz16 That's what it was when I  got up. Probably was -30 or worse last night. Was supposed to be. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCRoyL @yaboii_Jimmy @JayRed1771 @GGeneral74 I’m trying to get some flip cup going]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deanbrody @Spotify @dallassmith @SpotifyCanada Love you Both together Would make my 2019 #Dean Brody]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow the money . . .   Trump’s declaration of #NationalEmergency to fund the construction of #BorderWall could op… https://t.co/8TOFiybI35]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look what a wonderful work colleague just brought for me! I’m going to guard this with my life! @JoeCarter_29… https://t.co/Jeddrqn9UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jbenoit37 We are downstairs in a private room this time. Ace will be packed with other events but parking should s… https://t.co/c7Wrl4cn0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump @RonaldWeiser @MIGOP @MIGOPChair Trump 2020🇺🇸❤️👍🏼🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have certain traits that rubbed on me from certain ppl who are no longer in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had half a drink tonight, hated it. That concludes my semi-annual attempt at alcohol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Yes , check out ALL past presidents with s long reasonable list.  Not one stood before the American… https://t.co/FpINEs2iZt]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is merry. #laughter #giggle #smirk #cute https://t.co/q8rYQOMRGy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VictoriaLoder_ Also I don’t think it has anything to do with who you’re following because before joining the… https://t.co/wvqaO2EpIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting how the bible says not to eat pork yet the church I went to liferally would roast a dead pig in front… https://t.co/eC7yU1ogTK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lufthansaNews @Airbus @Airport_FRA Happy Friday! Und ein schönes Wochenende🛫🛫🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aj2657 I’m doing great! Hope to see you soon so we can argue about that 2020 election ;) https://t.co/D87cJHa2yV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m out here listening to Robbers. This is equivalent to me blinking 3 times as a cry for help. Kiyhjjkkkij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pneumaz @IsaacsHauntedB @therealjoebob Some folks’ replies were leaning towards the “ho-w dare you?!!” side of thi… https://t.co/FRmJDLVfeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alpha has never cared for her daughter! She watched her choke on plastic then saved her then knocked the fire outta… https://t.co/ai4XOBwYIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom cut my hair and gave me a Dora hair cut in middle school because I kissed a boy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love to see our students in the Student Activity Center (SAC) which was funded by student fees. @AStateSpirit, Ulti… https://t.co/BFI76zqKck]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍😍Can’t wait😍😍                               • • • ++++++++++++++++++++++++++ 💋🤩😍 Entrepreneur😍🤩💋 +++++++++++++++++… https://t.co/qHFY1HJMnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you wanna check how tall your heels make you next to your bf 👠 https://t.co/oL4sOaT35I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gailpacheco @wvjoe911 He's probably an alpha male. Holsters are for liberals.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the other kittens are sleeping while Mary gets her bottle. (I'm supplement-feeding the kittens 4 times a day to… https://t.co/knA1IP5T8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanHayes @DebraMessing It was so funny! I was LOLing, literally. Comedy perfection! 💚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VamosYankees @OlFetusFace @NYRaiderette Yes that’ll be the next thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wrong on so many American values!!  She is wrong for any true American period!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This does not belong in Congress, this does not belong in our government or on our soil 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @aoscott @Wesley_Morris Cada vez que veo Roma, me encanta Yalitza Aparicio!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My big warm parka is in Dallas but my ski jacket is in Houston and I’d just like to thank my momma for reminding me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rollinwith_ Already following you on WP. You had me at “applaud yourself, you deserve it”. Following now on Twitter.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MurrayCityUT how do I get updates on power outages? After hours dispatch went to voicemail and I don't want to kee… https://t.co/vvoMk9Iw7p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer @BarackObama Maybe because you did most of your time hiding it.  That explains the minimal interaction… https://t.co/c1f0hblqbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[If your in a crisis and need an emergency flight do not use Manny @AmericanAir, his heart is a block of concrete!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mrtonytig @People4Bernie @ninaturner @SenSanders @laforbernie @KyleKulinski @jimmy_dore @SamSeder @HumanistReport… https://t.co/jhcs64mJvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had a BLAST learning about force and motion from our Take Flight presenters today! The kids begged them to come… https://t.co/KoGPT8wukr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnaMaria_pasch Thank you AnaMaria splendid international women’s day too 🌻☕️🥰☀️🍀🌎]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancy_hamm1 @Angela_Enders @Jenn198523 @Crunk5454 @45Quickdraw4 @grgbkr37 @heyitsCarolyn @Rbigzs @mymynags… https://t.co/WuDqtpXV45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooo like I wanna make one of those cute videos everyone’s posting.. 🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s going to be late today. I’ve never seen such bad traffic in Rochester.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bar customer: “what are your specials tonight?” Me: “$2 wells” Bar customer: “ok I’ll have a well”]]></document><document><![CDATA[#audiq7 transformation by #sunshineautospa *complete interior detailing *Exterior carbon fiber vinyl wrap removal a… https://t.co/BaNhJ4ppiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#interdisciplinary #STEM #STEaM #curriculum #STREAM curriculum @ Bethalto, Illinois https://t.co/iT5Vm8r4xc]]></document><document><![CDATA[26 points and 9 rebounds, 👑@moss10_moss you played one hell of a game tonight!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it weird that I just don’t like having phone/FaceTime catch-ups? I’ll obv have them but increasingly I’m finding… https://t.co/SZEe7ryIEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pharmacist_lisa @GuilcherLab This is amazing work! Would love to learn more! ❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What one thing could make a difference in your personal finances? https://t.co/QJa18xAsUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart ❤️... #toddlersofinstagram @ Oakland, California https://t.co/1evIlfHvnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Needed a beer to calm my nerves after taking a curious child to the Shameock Bicycles #NAHBS preview party… https://t.co/ZJBCVMbm4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[People with depression who can afford a pet should adopt a pet.  It will make a huge difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would rather die than be on bourbon street during Mardi Gras, damn how do yall do it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @IlhanMN @RashidaTlaib @lsarsour This is gonna be so glorious to watch.  Islam vs LGBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@T_FLgal @GinnyGinny_1 @garway95 @RevKeithBritt @AlissalovesUSA @OLDFLACO @ShirleySueThom3 @MAGAgirly… https://t.co/syQR6CBHPy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get $300 eyelashes put in and I sit and play with them and watch them come out. What’s wrong with me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carternigel7 Guess you’re willing  to die because that’s the only option for leaving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@90TJM @FatKidDeals Tori and I are contemplating ordering one from Amazon. I absolutely need one though 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@axios Friends, I am a former Soviet attorney, please read my No. 92 -- Ripping the Mask off KGB Activity in Our Mi… https://t.co/Ah36L2Lrji]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whyyyyy is this office always so slow? 😩 (@ Swedish Covenant Hospital Foster Medical Pavillion in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/J4SJVw0UTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdorrancfarnham @JillWineBanks @milliker2017 Very much so. I am so lucky to have had thee best growing up time in… https://t.co/DVMq7IvjAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really changing. Now a days, I’ll go to bed without my phone on the charger.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @billbray62 @SpeakerPelosi Omar wants to be close to the center of intelligence so she can warn middle… https://t.co/EaKUMOdOa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@busywriting @ZeroGaslighting @MeetThePress @Liz_Cheney @chucktodd I don't know but letting that stupid Cheney woma… https://t.co/RZFIuLZSzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who needs a #racetrack  Not Ed Beyer! #pahrump #howtowaketheneighbors  #nascar #silverbullet #beyertime @ Pahrump,… https://t.co/HbrGiCMsqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't deal with how serious we all are having deep chats about pancakes. I also can't think of anything better 🥞… https://t.co/B9kc6jJu7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found out my story, Stand-Up Guy, is a finalist in North @NTRWA Great Expectation contest in the Mainstream with Ro… https://t.co/PMJwVyFYPS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone who believe this bullshit is in serious trouble.  we should all be talking about white on the world crime… https://t.co/PdFzbFgfSB]]></document><document><![CDATA[goodnight then ugh go away no come back just to break me again enough to remind to never play a player playa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IL_CCA @IllinoisCropSci @ACESIllinois Thanks to Dr. Adam Davis for always being willing to offer up information fo… https://t.co/vCdLBV6lrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@muzee65 @TheDrJessica She Will recover and learn to see her worth. She Will have so much support after this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prayers are much needed! 🙏🏽😔 @ Hawthorne, California https://t.co/Ezo2iGuXKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@uberinginmelb If 3 little old ladies said you pleased them, you passed the test! Great job. 👍😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[El tamaño Perfecto de mi dignidad (bolsa roja) y mi nivel de alta autoestima (bolsa beige)]]></document><document><![CDATA[This jacket is great but the sound it makes when you move is so loud 😩😂 à Greater Montreal https://t.co/YGtZgkB1Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[My husband and I are arguing if we have a boy, if he’s going to play peewee football. I said no and he rolls his eyes. 😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love my two babies more than anything 💗 cutest little twins https://t.co/eDtnYCb3aW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MayorBriley How ‘bout paying your police more money AND hiring more police to protect the fine people of Nashville!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want to go wash my car, but it’s supposed to rain on Thursday in Northridge]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenKamalaHarris proud? that says a whole lot about you and how you support murdering babies, illegals, and how you… https://t.co/JWlD3e2TTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[This family lost everything. They have 6 little kids. They need help to rebuild their lives. That's why I donated.… https://t.co/1sBSUOxKxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[s/o to the girl who sits next to me in math and always gives me the notes if i miss a day, you da best]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SkyCameron I had to do that a few weeks ago. Hope you feel better afterwards!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianKarem @realDonaldTrump As God told Moses and the Israelites: “You shall not circulate a false report. Do not… https://t.co/6OXafiet5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@slownight_ @TatiaRosenthal @calebmealer @walterowensgrpa @PressSec I'm rothfbl!]]></document><document><![CDATA[They spent the budget on a couple non-Canadian headliners. We can spend OUR money on other gigs. Like… https://t.co/PlCe7hH77H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows U called out  black women for calling out racism! It was racists bring a women of color who works f… https://t.co/YUb0tFZRZi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some client selfies are just better than  others lol.  SOMEONE... try to top this please. I would love it if client… https://t.co/EwKcWBnd01]]></document><document><![CDATA[After a full day of binging critical role (so close to being caught up) i think I'll go to bed 2 hours later : fluf… https://t.co/vGJBArUjYE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HappyQuailPress I’m simply wanting to bring awareness to policymakers, administrators and even hospital foundation… https://t.co/RKewfaunGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RolledPerfect Honestly this is more of a Plato or Socrates thought babe ... I knew you were always smart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damsorrow @Muna_Mire I’m mad for all the cool abortion art that will not be made #Beauty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Barbsnoturchick things like this make me super happy, but 7 years to become legal is ridiculous so i will still st… https://t.co/DUmgEJUfQE]]></document></documents></author>