<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@PamBondi and @realDonaldTrump conspired to violate campaign and election laws - @SDNYnews @TheJusticeDept… https://t.co/fM2CUdvCbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Calf found in by Chuck E Cheese’s” in my town.  That’s about as Texas and you can get.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Documents reveal Attorney for UNL Athletics knew nature of accusations against Washington https://t.co/a2iTlXQinR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tpain - 1Up (Review) do you agree? @ Tallahassee, Florida https://t.co/5jjwJaIC0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dans te toujou lou aprè kanaval! Tout ap mennen kapital politik yo a chak evennman yo vinn jape , vinn pran woulib,… https://t.co/e3COmWavVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleybee818 That is strangely kind of hot.    Me:  * I  can't believe I said that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grandma_satan It’s good, they aren’t like drenched in it I’ve always thought they tasted good with their tritip sammies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job in #FortMyers, FL? https://t.co/HM4YaCf0uu #Healthcare]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielleELarson Yes. And Yolanda was flawless. Per usual. She’s gotta have perfect pitch.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#quakes74 #vamosSJ light up the loons (@ Avaya Stadium - @sjearthquakes for San Jose Earthquakes vs. Minnesota Unit… https://t.co/zofq8zVcVk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell down to earth From a hundred miles away and somehow I still make it work]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikaishii @TeaganMorrison ahh, so this is why Teagan needed to go suit shopping!    Good picks, its just missing… https://t.co/WlQgmbvVfk]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the wolf removes the sheep's clothing, then you know who is really underneath.  Sure happy that those in the… https://t.co/nYprP2uF04]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Bang energy drink I had this morning at 7am is still going strong...  😳😳😳😳🥴😩😴😳😴😳😴😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ousted has come through when needed, defense solid in the center with Marcelo/Kappelhof/Bastian/Dax containing Ibra… https://t.co/e1lPSpYJq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatharineGJRyan I also have very understanding supervisors (who strongly encouraged my time off) and a supportive… https://t.co/K0yKPylp5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jedshug @nytopinion @nytimes Trump organization is a perfect target for a RICO charge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonParr3 take one million out of the savings and USTreasury is still a head How much did the Obamas spend buzzing… https://t.co/Fq5jxkGnZF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel Bernie is right on many things, however the free stuff bothers me. I believe in affordable healthc… https://t.co/uaJ40xLMZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realmadriden El campeón de Europa le dijo adiós al mejor goleador en la historia de la Champions y no le buscó sus… https://t.co/u1wTWpKWFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[How do so few people know how to spell? #InternationWomensDay is trending above #InternationalWomensDay :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesSt_PNW @CocaCola Just drove to @townepump looking for this! Not only did they laugh at me for asking for oran… https://t.co/ueSxsFryoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Save your breath. Meghan has zero flexibility. Ready, shoot, aim. The rhetoric and lies coming out of CPAC RE: abor… https://t.co/0iFr38gTkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Brutilicious by Stewart's Brewing Company  @ Stewart's Brewing Company — https://t.co/vwFz3qsP6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Kenny Chesney said “the girl I was with the business degree probably wouldn't recognize me. I was gonna run th… https://t.co/FjgCyGtnmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing solo 10:30a-1:30p #NOLA (@ Live Oak Cafe in New Orleans, LA) https://t.co/FkbsHUWkxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@raulmares72 @JJ66616 You Guys Pumped for May 👍 https://t.co/DuQLcGMN5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our gracious @FLOTUS does a spectacular job of representing America!  Thank you for all that you for our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever hit the screw the rangers button can seriously eat a bag of dicks. Horrible officiating]]></document><document><![CDATA[Star Wars: Galaxy’s Edge  May 31, 2019 #Disneyland August 29, 2019 #WaltDisneyWorld https://t.co/rLBa5ZV48D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Why don’t journalists use this stuff when you’re interviewing these assholes? Play it live for them, ask fo… https://t.co/fdIrH4HBQ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Be willing to fail. Because without struggle, what is your success anyway”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bored can’t wait for warm weather so I can get more videos for my YouTube channel]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another year is upon us I’m absolutely excited for #NasCar @StewartHaasRcng best of luck this year. It’s Go Time. 4… https://t.co/Xsgn6vUdta]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jRomz Happy Late Birthday Julian I hope your day was and still miss you so much and hope to see you soon bro!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CarlnolteSF loved your article about #coffee in the @sfchronicle! Heading to SF in two weeks and look forward to… https://t.co/egD5YJ4Nqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hN8oetLQL0.  Working at the Lab #EmbracetheGrind https://t.co/xBkwU0AiGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NBAAllStar Saturday Night Picks....  Skills Challenge: De'Aaron Fox-Kings Three Point Contest: Seth Curry-Blazers… https://t.co/OdPvCYhRhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mozzberg I know you can’t replace this monster!  But there is no excuse for the performance of this team the past… https://t.co/NPBdWpDryC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PresidencialVen @NicolasMaduro ¿Y quien le pone precio a la electricidad? Empieza a cobrar lo que vale, pues! Mien… https://t.co/b8Il2yfVue]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @ADBirnbaum  did you know @ONC_HealthIT  leader @donrucker graduated from @KinnelonHS ? Another #northjersey alum… https://t.co/Yxk0iw9Kwz]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/ch2wDuo7Og]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway Quick pivot to: Trump should have lifted sanctions.  We need a deal at all costs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS @TheChildrensInn @NIH Donald take any kids from families today, Melania?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daveg924 @marisaleigh Stubhub - I don’t even know how to platinum. I’m already embarrassed enough that I have the StubHub app.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@58littleflower @mtracey Anyone who legitimizes illegal aliens is simply a virtue signaling fool lacking  both virt… https://t.co/opVjvPxckf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GolicAndWingo Game 7 of the 91 World Series to see the @Twins beat the @Braves, right @RyanMeowstrom?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC After yesterday’s hearing conservatives still don’t think.   They never have.   They just blindly pledge fealt… https://t.co/hgoWiQerTP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Total missed shots (FG and FT missed for both teams) = 71. Total rebounds for both teams (including the 5 deadballs… https://t.co/RHrAb1bBio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClubInfernoXXX @SirTomMoore @devinfrancoxxx @d_arclyte @AlexKillian1 I am so excited for this!! 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s gonna be ppl outside of Turning Point’s event protesting on Monday, 😂😂 bro why don’t y’all just come inside… https://t.co/vUHGBSOm7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Career tip for landing jobs like "Senior Oracle Security Analyst - Houston, TX" in #Houston, TX. Go on informationa… https://t.co/AhN1uUpoz3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sir Ronaldo was on THE BENCH with an injury for Portugal’s final against France .... that win had NOTHING to do wit… https://t.co/XHqqVUOS67]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andygrammer thank you for the dream come true with tonights Donut Run in Burbank!! Dream come true for mrsknopick… https://t.co/sMbbvQIZmO]]></document><document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks on Immigration Reform https://t.co/Cr2YQPXSID   Just Wondering if it was ok then for this ?… https://t.co/WftBNVLpNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazing! #hamiltonblake #ohanastrong #taketimetohavetime @ SHN Orpheum Theatre https://t.co/XkhSebgvrw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos dias mi gente tenemos doble  Clasico si nuestro America se pone las pilas seran de nosotros  #S13MPREÁGUILAS.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t wanna seem like an idiot or anything but what does cinammontography even mean]]></document><document><![CDATA[so lil b just blessed a curse Ja Rule put on the Timberwolves, this isn’t going to be good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeaceActionNY @MoveOn @NYWFP @WorkingFamilies @SIDemsPathway @NYPANetwork @NYDREAMers #StatenIsland… https://t.co/2bkOa0REVA]]></document><document><![CDATA[resemble anything that was told to voters a decade ago. This is wrong. Today’s report clearly shows the real system… https://t.co/jcw5m59vkX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Starting another countdown! 30 days till our normal high is 50°! https://t.co/Ha4EFCR9Jv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maddow I enjoy your show but this whole thing about the height of the President-really ? With all that went on today...really?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinUdany @bmf1314 @whitesox Justin Becky’s suspended so she’s not gonna be at mania so move on k geez dur charlote rulz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_alpacas Absolutely. It’s s great 👍 feeling 😁🙂 to get away . Wish I could live a vacation life everyday haha… https://t.co/r6QovDOdYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to new UFC Welterweight Champ@Marty from Nebraska job well done]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mckwilzie GIRL 😭😂 jokes, that’s more like my fat rolls poking through sayin HEY 🙋🏼‍♀️🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where Kevin Guy will simultaneously be excited that his team won, while livid his team also lost. ... I still don’t… https://t.co/ut1tDwxN2g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to the male Ivy Leaguers who only publish in Nature and actively discourage collaboration]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um, no. They’re seeking the truth and reserving all rights in doing so, that’s how litigation works. It’s not about… https://t.co/K73O48zhWM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, I don’t know why I’m clutching my pearls so tight during Episode 3 of @pen15show? I’m mean I’ve gone to e… https://t.co/GDekIJR2zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviWoolf But the current rash of buybacks is not likely to be sustainable, and when earnings growth slows or goes… https://t.co/bPuhUpl9fX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendatracy24 There’s a respectful way to disagree with you if they do. Respect for others is lost]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn shame Democrates didn't take the Senate  and resore our Democracy. The GOP continues to run interference for t… https://t.co/6n6P14ZkT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ConnorHawks12 @CBSSports @NFLonCBS one is purple and one is battleship grey]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tremendous performance by @MarloweMustangs in Shrek!  Tons of talent in @Dist158!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio I believe my guy @mike_e_kaye wrote the article you referenced on foles]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra basketball. McCabe could have been the hero at the buzzer but the 3 didn't go down. WVU could preserve the 6… https://t.co/byfjS55421]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that it has yet to be 70° since my first weekend in LA in JANUARY is so goddamn hateful like WARM UP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenasmith @Lakers @Suns @KingJames Crying because u didn’t get AD !!! Lose to Suns ??? Joke]]></document><document><![CDATA[The game is trash. So glad i sold it. I only took a 20 dollar loss on the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[After going nearly 14 minutes without a field goal, Freeport on a 7-0 run #3 Freeport   11 #1 Gray-NG 22… https://t.co/hL4BJEqWN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonreinekephd What did you think of TD S3 overall? I rank it a close second behind S1. Incredible acting. I love… https://t.co/tftvR2KSUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanShazier and @StuartScott are easily my biggest motivations. My signed Shazier jersey hangs above my bed remind… https://t.co/Hh3uPXJFpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Better to remain silent appear a fool or speak and remove all doubt !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rising 9th Grade Family Night at Greenwood High School! Great turnout despite the rain. #FutureEagles @ghs_eagles_… https://t.co/2mm13j3mz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[*mood: waiting for St. Patty’s Day* 😂 Happy Valentine’s Day from your favorite dancers ♥️💃🏽 @ Arthur Murray Dance S… https://t.co/a0k0tAEvRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um, I’m not TRYNA start a beef here, but.... #Chinese #ImperialPalace #Deathstroke vs #Bandai #Meisho #Deadpool.… https://t.co/j8YxnYQGIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HannahDPhotos @scuderiagta @ItaliAuto @IrishEndaC @bourdyot_ @LienhardRacing @Cladounnet @Snugbucket @HeidiEly… https://t.co/WabVI8AMFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Karl Lagerfeld. If you know anything about fashion, you know how iconic this man is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people always want to talk deeply to me when I’m drunk? I don’t want to look you in the eyes, I’m drunk, bitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karenphilip Yes! We were just saying the same thing about the Nike spot. Damn.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolWSD Your "future core", the one that you are supposedly saving money for, can't stay healthy. https://t.co/FdpATdYd5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @ColMorrisDavis I see @VP as the handmaiden of @realDonaldTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpavlovitz Waves of drone strikes *might* constitute moral scandal for some. Just saying. Don't deify the dude.… https://t.co/85Nu7RDIEX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_pedrotrouxa_ it’s so disgusting. the amount of hate we receive for being ourselves is alarming and scary]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes the best idea’s are borrowed ones! Thank you team 1247 and @VanessaJuelfs for this great idea now in plac… https://t.co/wt7kUIeaiQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[AND I can only imagine that’s sweet tea in his hands!?! Oh this guy really knows how to do a surprise!  Thank you f… https://t.co/AH66nsB5aV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Daniel Bryan turns heel and refers to himself in a promo as “the new Daniel Bryan,” because he’s mean now, he’s dif… https://t.co/SwS34Dxqb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshuaAtLarge @nsarwark @ThomasEWoods @charles_peralo A trial in court and arguing before a judge and jury is a fo… https://t.co/1FGQMFO8Us]]></document></documents></author>