<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m not surprised! Every child needs these books!! My students love them ❤️congratulations! @IamJoryJohn -… https://t.co/CbKR5M8u4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday everyone! Make it a good day 🌞 @ Maple Valley, Washington https://t.co/15SIdlmlw8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Napa is my happy place 🌸 @ Saint Helena, California https://t.co/5rlk24S8qV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MotherShuck  Ok, have at me.... Throwing myself under the bus before you do it. #cantedittwitter 🙄 https://t.co/H5qu0z9dc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DusanaMichaels @darianeal1881 @CJFoster2 @jodikantor @AOC Colonization has literally been happening since humans h… https://t.co/AitWVugDeU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ilynem @isimeme_9 Pls stop this blasphemy, he’s a great guy and he’s very smart. He may be a coward but guess what… https://t.co/tiNXkheDxz]]></document><document><![CDATA[whole waiting for freshman to finish being a rich white boy in the apple store, i drew this on one of the ipads. https://t.co/HtDdurLF01]]></document><document><![CDATA[Orlando... Let's do this. SOLD. Call Deb @ 407 342-7421. https://t.co/NYscJyRWEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taniacaarolina Jajaja ya lo había escrito y ni se pudo publicar, pero dije que sí, que no dije cuál lunes 🤭 y ya casi 🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Prior to this, we’ve had no domestic history with them. ... This relationship was off our radar,” @NassauCountyPD… https://t.co/RLnxENFTem]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stupidity at its finest!!  No class..  Pathetic behavior brings consequences..  hhhmmm appears to be a trend here..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our flight to @washingtondc last night was cancelled due to a mechanical error so we are back @cvgairport this morn… https://t.co/moRy2P3JzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦⁦⁦@ShamelessLipG⁩ . So sad to see ⁦@emmyrossum⁩ go. I swear on my life that Lip is the basic guy in his mind. In m… https://t.co/0Qm69J7GJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Friday night at #nightingale__la No cover Open from 10:30PM #davidelaffe #Nightingale_LA  #andresrigal… https://t.co/BonXGm2DRl]]></document><document><![CDATA[lmao my bf and I just got home tipsy af and had a full blown snow ball fight outside]]></document><document><![CDATA[@planetepics That one guy who entered the wrong side of the highway. https://t.co/GWXiRzsslF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“No temptation has overtaken you except what is common to mankind. And God is faithful; he will not let you be temp… https://t.co/vgsEtxx9fN]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the #FCCincy debut in MLS....   “The man with the injured hair was not pleased.” 😂   It’s soccer season… https://t.co/LVt90vNamr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let' do this! Get this day started and this am meeting done. https://t.co/VT4GIUjkUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Child, this book by @tressiemcphd has caused me to forget my book-handling manners! Prepare to read it with one han… https://t.co/6CHVINPGxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Win Your Favourite Gift Card By A Complete Simple Sign Up.  Click Here: https://t.co/yM9CxahqMt… https://t.co/MFwDcSxr8h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a pic of a guy I went to high school w and he looks like a whole ass 34 year old who works at foot locker and has like 5 kids wyd????]]></document><document><![CDATA[baby I can’t really miss you if I’m with you, and when I miss you it’ll change the way I kiss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I killed someone via eyelashes. Are we surprised that it is @corpsecaptain? No. No, we are not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is it that the youngest of the easy come up family is a self made billionaire?   Also, can they cut Ray J a che… https://t.co/yur1eO9647]]></document><document><![CDATA[The guy next to me really did not brush his teeth and is in my space trying to spit game, no sir.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing is, no matter how much I love his song, my mom brain has never once wondered if he is eating or sleeping… https://t.co/xkPklYTfRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@millersoto @IvanDuque 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 ya quisieran un poco estar en el lugar de ella!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[But first, we eat. I can’t think of a  better place than jackswifefreda @ Jack's wife Freda https://t.co/EoolKDkvor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mano.. parece que passou um caminhão em cima de mim... putaquepariu... nunca fiquei tão cansada na vida ... mas Gra… https://t.co/491ttjNmw9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Husband- “I was thinking- when you start your new job you should...” Me- “I know, I know. I should start washing my… https://t.co/lVcseDh3gZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a great community effort to help retain our youth in #NorfolkCounty #MinorHockey #Waterford #PortDover… https://t.co/Zu1ypliEaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Le livre n'est pas écrit qu'on en fait déjà la critique, Lisée a raison finalement !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Ivanka Trump, a gift from Jerusalem: earrings of Queen Helena from the City of David.Deputy Foreign Mi… https://t.co/O3pyI8wQK0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adopt OMI saved by .@NamiKim_DogsSK from the cruel #DogMeatTrade #SouthKorea Gender: Male To adopt OMI ➡️… https://t.co/snu1SsbqHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hauser_molly It just brought me to tears. They know that this bill would allow people to kill other citizens parti… https://t.co/Yf2XcuVAFZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLRivers214 Thank you!! I was waiting for someone to give me a report! It’s not sticking to roads though right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MatanzaPancho @nowthisnews I'm sure who ever Tuker is he loves you back.]]></document><document><![CDATA[a man with a MAGA hat sat at my bar today and told me “you look like you go to UNT, and based on what I’ve observed… https://t.co/9giusHjmqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the ocean really does make us happier #ocean #happiness  https://t.co/tiXgW0jkPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt YES I KNOW YOU ARE THE LOVE OF MY LIFE &amp; OWN MY HEART 😍😍😍😍😍😍❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️💋💋💋💋 https://t.co/98zoUvToAS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laureanomar Y en la misma onda Maduro dijo ayer “no le paren bolas”. Prefieren ignorarlo, así será el terror que t… https://t.co/q4TUwiCXyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This salad! Almost too beautiful to eat, but I did. Heirloom tomatoes, baby arugula, hand formed burrata (yum!), fr… https://t.co/oCszEK2X9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJack So we have a federal body that is promulgating an illegal act? Where is Justice Department? Out to lunch… https://t.co/ANAnBlbXO5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyLoriL I'm thinking in the end they'll let him stay behind with one of the older married kid's to finish school… https://t.co/FXsNvwRzvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating #women today and everyday! #InternationalWomensDay2019 #InternationalWomansDay #WomensDay… https://t.co/muZTf5PMji]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Connection Between Verbal Abuse and Anxiety Everyone Ignores https://t.co/9e50qaYrBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@delondra_w Yes, I totally agree. It’s a mental &amp; emotional practice. We’ve gotta have a lot of boundaries. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 35 foot polar bear sculpture when the lights are off. Very cool. I wish it had a component fir raising money no… https://t.co/wBonAN6BUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't think lawmakers can ever agree on anything? Apparently the ones in this committee did. They passed along a pl… https://t.co/Pu8AVTxThf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChicagoPenguin2 @MrsSpuds @BxglL @sharon_schwan @72cricket @CSonafelt @sannbs @RidenerTina @ACog1984 They need a win badly 💛💛💛🐧🐧]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TallGlassofStyL Yeah this a lil too far here. Nobody who ever had my back gettin left behind. That’s principle. That’s how u stay blessed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanking God for blessing me with 34 years of life! When people your age is dying it makes you appreciate life so m… https://t.co/AfX35oCnvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaneLabGSU Haha, the imagery of faculty squaring off for a good student is amusing :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youneedwaldo I legit stayed up till 2 last night making a list wish of shoes i want 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizziMyers   Awesome voice powerful and beautiful. 💐 loved it. Good luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[Front commun des maires Canadiens et États-Uniens pour agir rapidement contre les espèces envahissantes, particuliè… https://t.co/mTRNpdW56U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SecretaryAcosta @STLCCworkforce @RoyBlunt @Boeing @STLCC Love these programs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let the Magic of Disney Continue!  Miracles of life...Blessed and Thankful... @ Give Kids The World https://t.co/rANkrOmVcB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trisha25229622 @Ellie60294712 @JeffreeStar I think calabasas is a color! tbh might be the one I own all I know is it's bomb af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up bright and early and at the gym about to burn off some serious frustration with some #Cardio. When life gets you… https://t.co/TFvgeAkiWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I care about children and what these "parents" are doing to these children is abuse itself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pineywoozle @SF_Gary_ @sheetalaiyer @KFILE @JoeBiden Oh my gosh. That's serious. So sorry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@olivia_frawley Funny...I read your tweet and wondered where the real Olivia went. 🤔 Then I read on...🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi  #DoctorWho #TheUniverseLovesPeterCapaldi https://t.co/tTQybbStHd]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s rather ridiculous the way the media keeps printing Breaking News Stories about that which we already know. #newsreruns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Many have an image of me, few get the picture 📸 https://t.co/DbuuywUQI7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile At what point did that security guard realize he wasn’t moving?? 😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 Thessalonians 5:9-10  God has destined us for acquiring salvation through our Lord Jesus Christ. He died for us,… https://t.co/twZTrkd1rP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who the fuck are you to cancel plans after I shaved my whole fucking body you bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anybody seen my knife? #look #makeup @ Bikini Bottom https://t.co/4KbM4cxtfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tesla Whatever model you get its a MUST to pay for an upgrade to self drive! And 40K is still a lot but I got my a… https://t.co/1cGjzbQjyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@welcomet0nature "And let me tell you about Charlie, he things he is a big shot because he brought us a leg of one… https://t.co/DMmJ5BaIhF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else totally ready to skip town and finally ditch this cold??? 🥶❄️🌬I’m ready for a little Spring sunshine, a… https://t.co/j1NQGAjFrV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr Why can’t you get all republicans to stick together and vote for this emergency declaration to support the president]]></document><document><![CDATA[#PresidentsDay The "Kitchen Debate" between President Nixon and Nikita Khrushchev, became one of the most famous mo… https://t.co/SU43TBmuIg]]></document><document><![CDATA[since i don’t have a film, dinadaan ko lang sa alikabok filter mga litrato ko but litsi i luv ‘em 🎞 https://t.co/Sl7sCMbiED]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s hungry? Don’t miss this chance to see how the chili and chowder recipes from the Westfield PD Department and… https://t.co/9Nwjcvec7g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Por si perdieron la primera sesión de @kexp en CDMX con el @IMS_MIS 🇲🇽🎶 https://t.co/2omznI8QY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathySc84402748 Hi Kathy, Would you like to get expensive battery charger case for your iPhone 6 / 6s / 7s / 8swit… https://t.co/CFghdwazJ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always doing incredible things, @Litz72 and making women across the @CFL proud! #InternationalWomensDay @TeamSheIS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got two free shots of Henny and that is the turning point of my night]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bullet_blake The longest @TheBosse_  and I went was two weeks so you’re better than us! 😅 Keep it up! 🙌]]></document><document><![CDATA[undefined images on Imgur https://t.co/5oodtiKNyS via @imgur I AM Echo 😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kyle_Ohhhh @kursamusic @theslugwife Totes magotes counting down until hes here in chicago!!!!!! #slugwifeyforlifey]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forgot to do my math homework but it’s okay cause I’m watching A Star is Born]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring Valley NY Sun Feb 24th AM Forecast: TODAY Rain Hi 50 TONIGHT Partly Cloudy Lo 29]]></document><document><![CDATA[The better renew @NBCBlindspot That show is so effin good! #blindspot #richdotcom #patterson #janedoe #weller https://t.co/WyePR4WRrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys, my flight is finally about to take off. What a crazy 24 hours. https://t.co/jmVt7evdr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me  -“ we need something healthy ?” Jacob -“ I mean sometimes pizza has vegetables on it.”  DEAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because it’s Valentine’s Day 😘 thank you @Onmy_DancingTip #Dance #dancer #actress #model #atlanta #losangeles… https://t.co/exvCdJBF6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico No, He should speak out against the way he has been treated. The FBI went to his home in the middle of th… https://t.co/jRjCfInYtC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning snow ❄️ ❄️❄️off to gym .. brrrrrrr https://t.co/fefnxDVoGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW MIX 🚨! Link in bio!!!   Had a great time spinning the closing set for #hazyvegas last Saturday. Shout to… https://t.co/TlnIi0vEhv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I was delivering annual performance reviews yesterday at work and I had one of my employees thank me for how har… https://t.co/xkNkfZXbm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[All this drip on me                                            I need a mop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusyBangtans @WGNNews Sorry but nope. But if it makes you happy that's all that matters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChampionsKlein @KleinISD @HofiusKISD @KleinCollins @KleinHigh @KleinForest @Culture4Caring Way to go Anna!!! @BESTKleinHigh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you ready for your dream job?! You’re invited to a @TBABJ workshop @USF_ZSAMC Monday 7 p.m. in CIS 1021. 🤩 Meet… https://t.co/UuXcnywKMi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an amazing #otspsecretsister thanks so much Sarah. I am starting the book tonight. 😍📚]]></document></documents></author>