<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Woke up with the word caboodle on my mind. Googled caboodle. Discovered its usage in “The Trouble with Tribbles.” 6… https://t.co/w8KSZYuWtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dpshow @PaulPabst @brooklynfritzy @HiMyNameIsSeton @andrewperloff https://t.co/GYT7IjiXmo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thegoldenmuzzy MINE EYES HAVE SEEN THE GLORY!  There is no taste left to acquire after that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Express: Type 2 diabetes: Eating this fruit daily could stave off condition and lower blood sugar. https://t.co/TiGP3Umw6k  via @GoogleNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauraarmy Fuck you @BlueJays and fuck you Howdy Doody Ross Atkins.   Show your faces in TO in 5 or 10 years when y… https://t.co/HXIE0PxaJm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS  Good morning Mr President, may Almighty God continue to bless and guide you today, as well as your entire f… https://t.co/WTttFAmEZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dawn breaks over two of the little lakes in my community @ The Villages Golf &amp; Country Club https://t.co/iYYjonPOyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Both coaches have been issued warnings as each have been lobbing for calls. Century leads Dickinson late in the first half 28-12 #NDPreps]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov.Cuomo reportedly pleaded toJeff Bezos to bring Amazon HQ2 back to NewYork why why AOC your new ignorant leader… https://t.co/1sERLR5HXk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mel_faith1 Caught on camera RED HANDED!! I really want to see these punks like him jailed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Old Italian Ladies in Carroll Gardens go to the bank JUST to chat with the tellers. And I kinda love it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time with my friends last. So so proud of these guys.                                             We st… https://t.co/bfPSKfMcOS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zachwylie99 @ESPNNFL @AB84 That’s just how old crusty white dudes look]]></document><document><![CDATA[The North end of this tract is an abandoned industrial site local NIMBYs are fighting tooth and nail to keep vacant.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a blast at Rutgers today💯🤘🏾 @CoachKDobes @RivalsFriedman https://t.co/APGsRRkYBp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again! Second time this year we got snow. Not quite like last time but it still sticking. @ Sierra Vista… https://t.co/DfrWBDc11e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WallStRique @GNYR_82 100% agreed , no idea why Kenny Atkinson loves him]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please check out page, our blog, mugs for sale, and our projects. https://t.co/WivkJTYKtx @ArkaciaVentures #mugs… https://t.co/VVANYvSrzJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 Since u been back you have been you have been on a tear. It's nice to see the younger generation passio… https://t.co/ifxtVCeTbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders If we spend as much on the poor and the people that need help as we do on that stinking military our… https://t.co/a6mEcG8zTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bornabrit1 🛑BOTH OF THESES REPUBLICAN PUPPETS GRAHAM AND NUNES SHOULD BE INVESTIGATED.🛑PUTIN AND FAKENEWS TRUMP PR… https://t.co/1FDqqxxDxF]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:32.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[So BR starts a shoe page, with the same info 12 year olds can get, and they start getting sent gear? LMFAO.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like one thing we take for granted as humans is how easily we drink water/ things in general.  Imagine being… https://t.co/ERSzwsHmgD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EndFamilySeparation   Judge rules Trump administration responsible for 'potentially thousands' more separated chil… https://t.co/hYccCXuHHp]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you guys haven't heard @WS_Boogie new album Everything's for sale I recommend you to. I can't wait to hear and w… https://t.co/f8zjFm5U8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOilKnight Wow didn’t know he had that extra gear, had to do a double take and make sure it wasn’t No.3 Boqvist]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are just two of the 17 young members of Boys to Men Club Minneapolis, learning what a hard earned dollar trul… https://t.co/zckykMeCS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliprangley @charliprangley when u find it let us all know. That would be awesome to find out for where i am as well?! 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fill er up ... #IAmHere (at @QuikTrip in Greenville, SC) https://t.co/hBs6HQyAfy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Green M&amp;M and Cruz Ramirez wins the bonus round, Green M&amp;M and Cruz Ramirez grand total is $64,950. https://t.co/9JYIQyOOVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lesssssss gooooo #yotes!! Send all those dumb Maple Leaf fans home crying! @ArizonaCoyotes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelseyzettle Good one Kelsey. Hope she flips a girl head over heels on a rebound the way you could!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jj_mason Feeling out some ideas on Cut To The Feeling. Thoughts?  The ribbon on their left arm is Tiny Little Bows… https://t.co/5gcZiMVQYo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mcfaley22 I can dig the university but the whole state I can't agree with it's a beautiful place]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys They Say it takes 7yrs. for a Tree to Bare FRUIT! That would make me 72! Planting FLOWERS might be more Appropriate! lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UKParlEducation @UKParliament My thanks for the presentation of presentation. (Twitter, being an item I had very e… https://t.co/GLB3fO6gI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeOnThinIce @GreatLakesPeck And in that article @EngelForArizona speaks too:  “Every time we seem to be turning… https://t.co/l5600uo9cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud that you left that toxic ass team they don’t take of they players 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sent my dad a picture of my new tattoo and this is his response 😅 https://t.co/kgiPteJL25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dirkchatelain Or 15? I mean, based on program history, getting back to the top 25 in five years seems a stretch. S… https://t.co/aBi3WItBub]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MGeschwind @andizeisler I thought you meant ME for a half second, but that’s just because I’m upset about… https://t.co/7UtKaLWrGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, I’m watching someone eviscerate Betsy deVos’s war criminal brother Erik Prince for an hour on Friday night. Be… https://t.co/2HvgT0mk0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[A-Rod truly is the second-best player of all time. Even in retirement he just keeps winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ever had one of those sleepless nights wondering how you got where you are and what life has in store for you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Meadows is  a racist and always been. He gets away with Obama commits and then brings to the hearing a woman,… https://t.co/tX88mD1ZCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to my boy @j6landers and his girlfriend. Wish you'll the best🙏🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[The New England Math League competition for 7th and 8th graders is in motion here @WillistonNS! https://t.co/9o7gyDYvh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jordanlperkins The podcast service I use has an auto-transcriber, but it just produces a hilarious word salad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fordnation is a criminal and should be in jail. That is the only reason a family friend was appointed head of the… https://t.co/IXHHIqbqaF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will not let my failures define me. I will not let rejection break me. I will not let sadness overcome me. I will… https://t.co/f1YOE0i3RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saturday March 9 - Morning News:      Californians voted for year-round daylight saving. Could this be our last spr… https://t.co/z8P94xrpGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Niandra_ Did a few years of veganism and was very into a Trader Joe's veggie pizza with a caramelised onion base that lasted bbq-y :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markcstory I was at the Kansas game in 78 and the Houston game in 84.  Both were among the loudest crowds I witnes… https://t.co/oP4Xw68hMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SaintRPh Said he forgot what it was called because his head nurse was out.... 🤦🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UAmatt @daveyoung84 Ok agree to disagree. Bear Down. Let's hope we get out of this disaster soon cause I'm not sur… https://t.co/viWL1sMhh4]]></document><document><![CDATA[scored some heaters with @krfoege today 📸 appreciate the homie for letting me practice my craft 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey Tallahassee Pain @TPAIN . You better not ever never use auto tune again bro #TheMaskedSinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@K_Hughes52 @Harpua29 @st0ckm0nster Didn't stone castle publish a nice excel spreadsheet with the capital structure fully diluted ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taking it back to 2013 as ‘TSUNs of Guns’ blared over the speaker as Murphey Holloway was introduced.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ccsubaseball @dean_lockery @nick_garland20 @CCSUBlueDevils Great happy for both of you guys , enjoy the dream]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funnylookncig @Spartacussin @tomwatson I'll give you 2 examples: University of Illinois has a 62% acceptance rate… https://t.co/h8LYF6GYzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WritesJodi @DestinyRaeSmith It is teeming with interesting stuff though not on most tourist destinations.  Pocahon… https://t.co/fjFaGQH2vi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GNSensay @Ben11744515 @Big_Orrin 4/ Response relations like CI yield curve are powerful b/c cross-plotted factors… https://t.co/lpWD7owAgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of Sleepy iTunesu - you Grumps https://t.co/V779e65UlM b via @the. Bank s by Bhubaneswar Ishisb. Hybggngivjs i… https://t.co/vTLnaYwR2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my new logos created by @WweBradMartin96 . Great work as always. What do you all think. @KlaytonFioriti… https://t.co/SXVHyOT150]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TVMoody Hasn’t been about wins for LAK for awhile. Understand fan frustration but don’t have a problem with Luff b… https://t.co/3NjqFuH6rT]]></document><document><![CDATA[filling some gaps . . For appointments esnaolafer@hotmail.com   Link on bio 👆🏼 . . #FreehandTattoo… https://t.co/n3JPa9M24X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you! Lord for another day. I promise I won’t spend one day not chasing my dreams...🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday March 11 - The Washington Post Today's Headlines:     Trump’s reelection campaign has 2016 themes — and a bi… https://t.co/RMCX1hJXeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[28th of the season for Brendan Gallagher Awesome pass from… https://t.co/COOMchJIhW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@100MilesOfHate @legionfielddj It was sarcasm. You know, the thing that used to exist on here but no longer does. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Deshklok @benshapiro I follow lots of people.  I'm not even a fan of Ben Shapiro.  Probably disagree with him over… https://t.co/wVW3SsnfpR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAdverderada @FPC_Raiders @Petecertified Bravery respected. Petty acknowledged]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The7Line Other than a couple of home outings and a couple of away outings I have been an Army supporter from the o… https://t.co/053DM0tRRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Right Stuf Anime's out of print reminder, it was now or never to get this Aniplex titles😅 https://t.co/kt1QE18Cyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s a health gap in Canada – and women are falling through it /via @globeandmail https://t.co/ggYpLe8oUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jontaffer Ugh..... The bartender serves me this and then says "I'm not really good at this beer pouring thing."… https://t.co/d6gaQvdgTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[when my boo that’s not my boo that I want to be my boo is out here going out with our guys my heart just 😤🥺]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Uber driver is speeding down rainy, crowded streets while blasting Christian rock and occasionally belting out,… https://t.co/erpVKLH1Ow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiefinCarolina @barleyhop what can you tell me about this Jordan Wyatt kid? Seems to always be around the ball, n… https://t.co/gE7AWB2qi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahamcrosby Cheers! And as my friend and old colleague @warrenbarton2 says, “Come on the Toon!”  #NUFC]]></document><document><![CDATA[By the way, I just posted @MBeavenABJ's story on @GirlsBball_THS-Buchtel on https://t.co/MPRfp1cAry. Hopefully, I w… https://t.co/YoPL6OXK25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notrussianbot28 @realTylerZed Ya actually learning about breaking barriers was awful. Why does it bother you so mu… https://t.co/5p3FauZJba]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fucking conspiracy-minded do you need to be say ‘hey these people asked fair and pertinent questions about my c… https://t.co/ggRjVxY6rS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politvidchannel 👍EVERYONE IN AMERICA AND THE WORLD. AND THE REPUBLICAN PARTY.👍KNOWS FAKENEWS TRUMP IS PATHOLOGICAL… https://t.co/6JA3ZhHDUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I finally saw blackkklansman last night and holy shit. Amazing cast, editing, and direction. Spike Lee really deserves the Oscar for this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lebron loves n looks up to MJ, and MJ fans hate lebron lol it’s like how’s that work lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve had a growing fear of heights for a number of years. Today I looked that fear in the face, and told it to kiss… https://t.co/hquves6oWU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GroverNorquist It's prime real estate is the reason why it's expensive to live n CA not because the state has good… https://t.co/FW2PcZ9OVX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y si le pedimos a USA ayuda humanitaria para Chille .especialmente Hospitales publicos ,remedios y jubilados... Ver… https://t.co/aHABv3R5uO]]></document><document><![CDATA[One robin doesn’t make the spring. 🌸 flora_carter 🌸 en Grey Gardens https://t.co/58jzb5M79H]]></document><document><![CDATA[1001-1029 W 96th St 1001-1029 W 96th St, Los Angeles, CA 90044 https://t.co/ybAp16JAFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benshapiro please can you just “accidentally” be at one of her events? It wouldn’t be cat-calling then right? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why can a national emergency like the ones called before by previous Presidents be valid and a National emergency p… https://t.co/1sDOh2qfQY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Todd_Conaway Thank God UNF’s Sophos Web Protection protected me from your site. That was close. https://t.co/ZImdWSsnHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @DonaldJTrumpJr Yeah and Trump is still President. Shameful 🤦‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[KEEP GRINDIN BOYS! 🔥  @Naz_moore3 // @Anixon42 // @jacobrosales_5 https://t.co/DsVoR2Tasf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@winstonCovfefe @Marilyn122868 Yes Somalia has been such a shining star of a place to live why not emulate in the U… https://t.co/3Rua3rJgzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks!  Diagnosis is RSV. Guess the ins carrier would rather pay an ER bill when she can’t breath.  Hope all is go… https://t.co/yRlAuXt0t0]]></document></documents></author>