<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Lee_Foster @Reflog_18 If by golf trip you mean drink beer while watching others actually golf...then I’m in! I ref… https://t.co/szaXKfoZex]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for Adam Jones, and so so happy it’s the Diamondbacks. 🐍 Class act guy to a great clubhouse. #DbacksSpring]]></document><document><![CDATA[People who negatively talk about others are insecure with themselves. Don't allow the negativity bring you down...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Marvel movies made me realize that it’s not true love unless they make you ceo of the very successful company that… https://t.co/N99DVkUY1S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in hs: when the fuck am I gonna use Pythagorean theorem  Me in college tryna place a ladder off a vertical vesse… https://t.co/3ZgfF7uUES]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods 😂 what an awesome show to watch. That’s what you do, you go after people in your own party, making… https://t.co/qIQnw1KWHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alleypat @dfwWORDwriters @DFW_Writers @angryrobotbooks @JennieGoloboy I’m editing something new. 😊  Always gotta h… https://t.co/uS4dDQhEXw]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to Encourage Girls to Lift Each Other Up, Instead of Tearing Each Other Down | A Mighty Girl https://t.co/HRyZVKo6NP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @realgrace_kelly @KamalaHarris #NeverKamala #NoOnKamala2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today I saw @NicoTortorella In person! I didn’t meet him but we both were at the @Queerty awards! He is sooooooo dreamy 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/3 This is why we need more leaders line AOC and if you Corporate Dem followers don’t like that ... Well then the… https://t.co/FPZwNNEc0j]]></document><document><![CDATA[i only got into hot yoga cuz an ex said he didn’t think i could handle it so thank god for that]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9lsfz2ojzg  Everlasting Dreams music video and motion is up and ready to go!!! ♡♡♡ #MMD #RuneFactory2… https://t.co/TpnDmBIFOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I would never vote Bernie he’s a lier and says only what you want to hear He’s in this Only for his… https://t.co/WU7rULb4wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe that on a Friday night all I wanted to do was clean the bathroom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@J_Shantel_Ro I do!! But I'm old.... I was mad lo y in love with John Belushi when I was like 7...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdwardGLuce Congress, and it makes us all a bit gitchy. We’ve stripped the decorum down to base accountability and… https://t.co/YL5btz8YDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day to this mean muggin sushi guzzling mfer https://t.co/CUQWvMqkFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @realDonaldTrump You're pretty gross yourself https://t.co/23BvtIIVH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[i met a gypsy and she hipped me to some life game, to stimulate then activate the left and right brain.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I absolutely loved all the speakers, incredibly inspirational and motivational! Certainly one of the best things I'… https://t.co/CARQ3SBg8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hot sausages at 2 a.m. with my big sis, Vainglorious, aka @querismatic, aka Keeeey! ☺️ @ Papaya Dog https://t.co/qOnNSlCFCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nickielegal Mika is crazy,  biased,  and I don't trust her.  She helps divide the country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s Day 1 of Key School’s Bored &amp; Brilliant Challenge - Keep those devices Out Of Sight @ The Key School https://t.co/4yhZAHoS3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just walking down the street in #Straya @jharleyaus @dannykeens @PhilGoyen]]></document><document><![CDATA[While warming up  Mai grabbed her back and limped for a min. She keeps stretching her back. Hope she’s okay. #AC2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeneralHospital @RealEdenMccoy @itsgarrentho @LiptonWilliam @SydneyMikayla They are all so darn cute!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[A testimonial. #actorslife #auditionlife #characterwoman #itsfunnybecauseitstrue #giglife @castingbyally… https://t.co/kdAzqUnfoO]]></document><document><![CDATA[02/24/2019: We had another successful fashion show. @ Marriott LAX - Grand Ballroom https://t.co/mbUN8AcM0B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 3 with the awesome 6th grade students at #ThompsonSixthGradeCenter in #Alabaster, AL. Thanks to @Alabasterk12 A… https://t.co/hvzljz45bt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kori insisted on buying my a coffee and I said “okay fine just get something cheap” and they got me an iced latte w… https://t.co/8ng65m4Shp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loryncourville_ @_loryn @HailiMoore Your so welcome!  TY for being a great friend n big sister to H.  Yes for sure… https://t.co/6MoZBXRWof]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I don’t remember but I can tell you I do and be very “LA”.  🙄. But yes tell your friends!! You know how hard i… https://t.co/ZeB1HMAKIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes indeed .  More coming .  This should never ever happen to another innocent kid again. Fur should fly alright .]]></document><document><![CDATA[J’e suis tellement fatiguée , je peux même pas faire les roukaskass dans la fête de ma petite]]></document><document><![CDATA[mario on the phone with ary*  mario- “oooo i need to go, my phone is about to die”  ary- “you say that every time”  😂😂😂💀💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @sweetgreatmom @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett What about all the democrats who got on the bandwagon and… https://t.co/DptXt9r7H8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot ✅ Administrative neglect, ✅ Reductions in tenured faculty, ✅ Reliance on adjunct labor, ✅ Class cancellati… https://t.co/EQP85Q6voZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skotblater @MrPeripetia @pettingchickens @aparnapkin I used to take Ativan. Shrinks gave me restoril, Xanax, kloni… https://t.co/J8Nzw3ZaL9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh wait Lisa.. Don't go Lisa.. Please.. Sit here a bit longer and let us ice you out and make you feel uncomfortabl… https://t.co/DmzsN1lDFx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winters almost over. But I can still feel the chill in my soul. 🤫⛄️❄️🥶#northfacecap #northfacebeanie… https://t.co/xNyX33CLaX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted the 7 Day Book Cover Challenge from @MsDowdsclass ! I’ll post covers of 7 books I love: no explanatio… https://t.co/3jTnfcRte7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ain’t first, you’re last! @KyleBusch @LVMotorSpeedway @NASCAR #18N18 #NASCAR #ShakeAndBake #RowdyNation… https://t.co/8sZWrK2hhd]]></document><document><![CDATA[*talking with my dad on the phone*  Dad: Okay kid, have a great week! After we hang up, go to your freezer and trea… https://t.co/5mZoqngPae]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s such a dilemma to find out my two greatest passions will be on national television at the same time tonight ug… https://t.co/1n0xEecbog]]></document><document><![CDATA[blackcurrants and elderberries need to find their way into the mainstream american diet]]></document><document><![CDATA[You notice that the SCOTUS does not have twitter sites. No contact through FB. We have to Snail Mail. We should sen… https://t.co/qXDPw27T4B]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Alexa, Play Island Song by @zacbrownband” 🌴🚢😍 @CruiseNorwegian #CruiseNorwegian #FeelFree #NorwegianEscape… https://t.co/EUxDr0lpPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved these science outreach  ads they ran in the TTC by @DrRayJay and his team! https://t.co/TItKtkZ89y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NoteToSelf Taste and see that the Lord is good; blessed is the [one] who takes refuge in him. Psalm 34:8… https://t.co/wO3XdKkiFI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Make sure you follow @NCAALAX on @instagram because on Thursday, Feb. 28, @regann_quinn will be doing an Instagram… https://t.co/woaTNZpJjY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TuckerCarlson Need to schedule phone appointment with The President Donald J Trump White House ne… https://t.co/OKLQekG1sZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sailor_mo0n Lmfao!!!! Me right now after eating a crepe with strawberries and whip cream!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FaceTheTruthTV I went back to work after 5 months. I then used a sitter for the first two years, then a daycare ce… https://t.co/R5rDKA7SAR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t gotten good boba in a while and I just got some from this new place and I drank it so fast I threw up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Here's To Feeling Good All the Time by @BissellBrosBrew at @thepublickhouse — https://t.co/29DVycOm5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn't it be nice to have someone tell you, literally and face-to-face, what to do to break the $100k ceiling in… https://t.co/kL09VwtfKx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voters Oppose Democrats’ Stance on Abortion via @freebeacon https://t.co/cfxRQBlcgq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tried to disrespect me and I’m not going to let anyone treat me like that so I robbed them and left because I respect myself!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@supermaren @NewMusPrincess @OliviaKieffer No, and I'm not sure if I should be terrified or intrigued]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Claritin commercial doesn’t make me want Claritin, it makes me want a dog 😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[@janaplauen hi again what are you doing? Just say it the best as you can I will understand it 🤗💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[5X's Draft Dodger Coward #Trump  Crook is heading 2 Vietnam where he refused to fight in the war 50 yrs ago Many heroes died in the war]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've accepted a challenge from @LPietrosimone to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations-just the covers. Ea… https://t.co/uy1yDEJJLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[How is election interference NOT worse than seeking asylum? Democracy is becoming a joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gratitude is essential, it engages your brain in a virtuous cycle ... ✨ @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/pFJ432ZK7j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whatmaddness @sdrockcab the whole album is and ive had it on repeat since it’s release. try somebody else by them… https://t.co/kCp0iuWvWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Austin worked a 24 hr shift so he’s asleep but Sophie keeps trying to wake him up to play 🤦🏼‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mrs. Gingles #models #annotation and #EvidenceCharts with her students so that they understand the expectations for… https://t.co/sufXQ77jbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessWaltonYR Happy Birthday🎂. May your year be as beautiful as you are. Wishing you all the happiness, health and… https://t.co/eMPIfbGv2W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally watched Bohemian Rhapsody and I’m 😭😭😭 What an AWESOME movie! #BohemianRhapsody @ItsRamiMalek MUST WIN EVERYTHING!]]></document><document><![CDATA[March 03, 2019 Snow we got this morning. @ Altamont, Illinois https://t.co/J3cW27Ggo4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joeybagovdonuts Last time was a water main break. Tonight apparently someone hit a line while doing work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited for @CBSBigBrother tonight! Who’s gonna win? #bigbrother #CelebrityBigBrother2 #CelebrityBigBrother]]></document><document><![CDATA[loving this @backstreetboys chile performance!! omg i feel like im there! soooo excited to see them in september!!!… https://t.co/OQwj2R3rt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ConspiracyTheories @shanedawson did Chuck E Cheese sponsor you to get everyone to go buy their pizzas 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicks hoodie smells like fish tacos but he won’t wash it bc the bruins and patriots keep winning while he wears it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@britishairways #getYourActTogether  poor service  #silver member means nothing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ava @GayleKing Normal people don’t have to classify if someone is “ legal “..... of he’s fine I wonder if he’s legal... yea no]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inspiring Olympic Champion Lucile Wheeler at 83. Beautiful. Video via @mtlgazette https://t.co/nn08yFKbIM #WomeninSports]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @AOC She knows too much🤣🤣🤣🤣for her own good,  all of it learned at BU, embarrassing.  But she is goo… https://t.co/7NVh4IyM6P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KJThrace @tylerkippp @jespo1024 @voguewriter @Nnedi @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Child trafficking does not come thru p… https://t.co/4ztDjhjrMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[DID YOU HEAR? I have partnered up with some of my favorite bloggers to gift one of our followers a $1,000.00 gift c… https://t.co/ufe6eM6xOr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland The landmark decision represents a broad agreement on the Supreme Court that law enforcement’s legaliz… https://t.co/Bgg7iXAv5x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMSTODAY registration is open now from 3-6!!! Stop by on the ballroom level and beat the lines we will have later… https://t.co/ndU3Fp41m4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justin0wings @denvercoder I ran up a 1K bill on Prodigy one amazing summer when they billed by the hour. My dad di… https://t.co/9MYWtHlEea]]></document><document><![CDATA[Constitutional experts are also demanding an official inquiry. “We need a full accounting by Trump’s justice depart… https://t.co/q3lNEfTXzR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoyed spending my afternoon with Chef Ryan as he cooked a home-made meal for River City Mission in Paducah.  Love… https://t.co/WKLhwb5fAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iTrustPRO @JeanneBartram @NekoMeganSenpai Thanks for the mention~ Have a nice day~]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therealJuliaAnn @CindyStarfall @lexigirlxxx88 Thank you babe💓💋 for your patience and talent and attention to detail and funny jokes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesBlunt Happy birthday James. I think you're actually older than I claim to be. I usually end up telling them m… https://t.co/TvHnsmROBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Michell19040941 @BTS_twt Always gorgeous no matter what he is doing. I’m just- https://t.co/wdbl6kT0Gm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nocretinsplease @hjkhelsinki 1st pic is Timo &amp; I in Helsinki last November. 2nd is us in LA in late 80's. Lol https://t.co/0TkEjbfc0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[A juvenile faces a second degree murder charge after police found a woman dead in a home in Madison, NH Friday even… https://t.co/9mLBFbbi0k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I feel super hungry and then when I see food I don’t feel hungry anymore????]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used to think I was movin too quickly with how willing I am to have a life with my bf until my cousin told me her… https://t.co/UsdM0GjjAU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Violet_theNewfy @crowned_warrior @ThoughtsOfRally Done for the day, and calendared. You are lovely.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@proxactears @Trident_Druid Have you seen Cash App? Try it using my code and we’ll each get $5. PVXDKBL  https://t.co/iQiEASHqvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you, David! So glad to have you there to celebrate a terrific year! We couldn’t do it without you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/JlVees0FRq]]></document></documents></author>