<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[The Pal Family from Modesto drove off in a new 2019 Tundra they picked up with Aaron’s help.  #modestotoyota #toyota https://t.co/vbfUbPwOnN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corrales, Borics, Caldwell, McKee, Sanchez, Bandejas, Archuleta &amp; Curran. Winner gets Pitbull]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lakers are embarrassing. LeBron is a baby when things don’t go his way. This season is a disaster.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaVosk i’ll give you the sun by @jandynelson is a GREAT read. if you liked jane eyre (or even if you didn’t),… https://t.co/bZ8wtmJovk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Skipper's Stout by @eriebrewingco @ Hodgepodgelodge — https://t.co/C1Z9rbjFPp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrRogers99 It’s  1.)Roxanne  2.)Roxanne  3.)Roxanne  4.)Roxanne  5.)Roxanne   Honorable mention: Roxanne]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeatherFox64 Allow me to recommend the folks at @dreamsutravel, we’ve used them for years now and they’re pretty damn awesome]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be stanning for the Houston Cougars as my team that I will put in the final four blindly and without question. SMH lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unicorns, rainbows, and stars! The perfect little summer dress. Sizes available for order: 3, 4, 5, 6 Contact… https://t.co/ngnpyvQOe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #RangerJavelin is my @anthemgame exosuit of choice. Make your selection to unleash your power and watch your suit in action.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter Thread:  Things you learned on twitter but not in school!  👨🏼‍🏫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Olimpiasfitness @AmyFreeze7 Your cats' good lives are the envy of many humans! 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CrystalRose don’t be sad. Work hard again it’ll be fine in the future. You have God’s voice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PornstarPastor Sadly, yes. They would fully support a theocracy as long as it was them. Why “The Handmaid’s Tale”… https://t.co/mshwBiM7Dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorrisCtyHockey Thank you!  So far Morris-Sussex is 2-2, heading to the state finals!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRIMINALS @ WORK‼️🐷🤛 Trump Crime Syndicate👀 @SecElaineChao @senatemajldr @realDonaldTrump #realDonaldJethroTrump… https://t.co/3HyWdYO37d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder Really what happened to lock her up? Or Mexico is gonna pay for the wall?]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I run for public office it’ll be on a platform of getting every DMV office up to four stars or higher on Google reviews.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driving in a crazy hailstorm while along I-680, entering Fremont, CA!  I don’t think I’ve ever seen such a downpour… https://t.co/bDj83he8kj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 TOMORROW, FINALLY, THE ONCE #BESTRAVEINVEGAS RETURNS; XIV IS BACK, but this returns on a Tuesday instead of Sun… https://t.co/5uk38DrrEh]]></document><document><![CDATA[We can build the wall AND have El Chapo pay for it... @tedcruz's #ELCHAPOAct is how. Stand with Ted Cruz and add yo… https://t.co/qbS4aJLPk0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone in Cali wanna go to Florida and everyone in Florida wanna go to Cali 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BIGEASThoops powerful win by @MarquetteMBB [NCAAB] BUTLER @ MARQ, Final: 69 - 79 https://t.co/5enCA9iEeC https://t.co/fomAXyS1sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SundayDove @SenateGOP Ooooh, their fuming. What are they going to do, just kiss one of his ass cheeks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[More hats for some of the 4140 night crew drivers!!!! Thanks for all you do the backbone of the company!!!!… https://t.co/pO5JpAxvs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Writing is so painful I don't know why I do it, also I might have broken my pointer finger so that could be it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Kendall: few clouds, 74°F 41% humidity, wind 13mph, pressure 1025mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffmorgen Goes for wine too. You know who reuses glasses without rinsing? Who serves some reds cold? Who drinks w… https://t.co/eGpuzENje7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Kenny Williams gets cooking, it cld be a long night for #Duke #UNC #GoHeels]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Worthy trying his hardest not to slander Lebron on this postgame show 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is wrong on so many levels. I’ve never heard a podcast that sticks with me for more than a day or two. Whereas… https://t.co/F9VX5rPalu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thebunkershouse @ananavarro @ChrisCuomo Hey, probably married another cousin and they're on the Honeymoon.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another 1st Listen to me sing "Stand By Me - acoustic" on #Smule: https://t.co/DTmH3vWZ8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge one-timer from Tyson Barrie and #Suuuuub makes the stop.  #VegasBorn 0  #GoAvsGo 1   #VGKvsCOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a dream the Feds was on my ass about this particular gun for some odd reason.... Woke up outta my sleep like damn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showed up 15 minutes early for a pre-9am doctor's appointment--take that, MTA. 😎]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Song Spotlight February 21, 2019  Featured Songs For February 21, 2019 Abba - SOS  https://t.co/Sl46AAkgXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrErinkate @SenGillibrand What's greener than a cow foraging and fertilizing at the same time ? Who will mow the grass ??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scullyfan I haven't seen that one yet, I want to see something on Jackie Wilson.]]></document><document><![CDATA[morning everyone, hope you have an excellent day https://t.co/pZWQrNcJvR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garnekmedia Walka ortiz vs hammer taki troche żart z wagi ciężkiej ( taki wiecej niż troche]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie__Cooley Yep he’s is 10th now. I saw the ticker at 7th before they corrected it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another way of looking at this: What’s fair to ask of the activist?   Original issue for @Kaepernick7 was police br… https://t.co/tCYEq3cFAE]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Ulm looked exhausted at the end of the 2nd period.  Mahtomedi can cruise into the 3rd period.  #TheTourney19]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @JBardoulas stressing taking social offline. This is so important. Most don't realize it's not just about a scree… https://t.co/0FSRhq7acb]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TennesseeGirlsHighSchoolBasketball #TSSAA #District13A 1st  Semifinal: @ucgoldentornado(gray) vs.… https://t.co/eEFYcGNY1u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittt_mcguire Imma bet he’s on the trading block sometime this season........ BET 🗣🗣🗣🗣]]></document><document><![CDATA[v.1.0 - the blessing of Biblical concepts is not to do things perfectly and everything will align. The blessing is… https://t.co/XMfLOCjcVo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoCardShow @DixieOutletMall https://t.co/CPfe40AISI can be for sale for the right price - contact me for the… https://t.co/3eXc8cVeRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great week @RSAConference #RSAC2019 this week, first big news item was @NSAGov release of #ghidra #nationalsecurity… https://t.co/N6cqktarqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fernandeznorona El gobierno está a favor de la termoeléctrica. Matan al opositor. Me recuerda el caso de helicópte… https://t.co/5NyL8aV4Cz]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/9WsQxcm3pZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Albers throws a strong third inning for #Brewers, with a walk and two strikeouts.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@libernate269 @CarriageCavalry @nyclass We r lining up our horses uphill @ 7th Ave to counter the inhumane downhill… https://t.co/O0sNgR7oiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reminds me of getting a detention in high school from the principal for watching the B1G Tournament. Did I mention… https://t.co/SXHOU04E6H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CurryLashanta @TMZ He’s a racist for planning an attack to make white trump supporters as the attackers... you don… https://t.co/8We7XqdZzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you NOT like Mitch Lightfoot? He’s a boss. Great game tonight. #KUBBALL #ROCKCHALK @Mitchlightfoot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jillibean557 Liberals will ALWAYS claim it's TWO BAD guys with GUNS !  It seems only Illegal guys with guns are permissible ...😟]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quarter pounder 🍔 (at @McDonalds in San Jose, CA) https://t.co/S3YNHpMS0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[El #21F no se olvida, no se negocia ni se entierra, así como hace 3 años vamos a seguir defendiendo Valores y Princ… https://t.co/BGUCcCuEte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espn @ESPNNBA @KingJames No matter what team you support how can you hate this guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lake Effect 🌊❄️ // 📷: @nickhartlerode #2in1day @ South Haven, Michigan https://t.co/pu2B7TTHTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[i rlly hope taylor is coming back tonight. pop musics return will officially be cemented then!!! #ts7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forward, not backward -- upward, not forward -- and always twirling, twirling, TWIRLING TOWARDS FREEDOM. Happy BIRT… https://t.co/FgAoDKjbW1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winter in Wisconsin ° #diamondlkphotography #winterscene #dairyland #country #snowy #openfield #travelwisconsin… https://t.co/oNA3VsYgKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@judeorazulike @YarKafanchan @Demoore90210 @akaebube @EuginhoCortez @andyRoidO @AbdulMahmud01 @realKefason… https://t.co/0FGGCE3AcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because republicans dont care about the nation , they are concerned with lining their pockets only !! Trump is a na… https://t.co/WqS4X25UQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheProductDS @beyondwrestling Uncharted Territory is going to be interesting. @beyondwrestling https://t.co/oktO9LGtZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stronger Together #WednesdayWisdom Art by Mauricio Abril #hope #choices #action #supersinghs🙏🏽🕉🇺🇸 @ Guardian Life I… https://t.co/Lvy5npQ1RZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moral of the story here: never believe in any politician—you will only be let down.   https://t.co/OgbC1FW1HE]]></document><document><![CDATA[But age is a qualification for all political offices.  It’s why AOC is legally banned from running for president. Y… https://t.co/S1QMNE2BHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those who lived for Gus, Dennis, Jack, to X, Dale, Tom and Det, then GP and Kemp. I feel the same way.… https://t.co/E8jLLrMuyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clevareno @DrunkPolkaroo @Ben_T_Johnson @BeerGirlCA Okay, was just on @dominioncitybc  website - they have a Tripl… https://t.co/d71vThQfyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calldaburd Are you able to send me any info your team discovered regarding the pump? PM me please.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justinbieber @scooterbraun @taylorswift13 YOU fuckers followed me, stole from me...   #Pussy  Hey SCOOTER maybe yo… https://t.co/bDQTRVjgLr]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you wanna see Kim K pretend to know the lyrics and wave her pointer finger around for 40 seconds, here’s your vi… https://t.co/vzCsBsFCzh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/eRJ3AoGmuN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Central calls its 4th timeout. Sock leads 55-51, 1:13 left. Central ball at half-court.  Regardless of what happens… https://t.co/tmqI4EQzNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pls enjoy this pic of Mariah in my pullover 😂😂💀 https://t.co/wyuHBNbNQ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Full day of wrestling. Boys got the hardware needed to advance all to regionals! #prouddad #strokesandaneurysms https://t.co/noCDNC7Kn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some people really put an act on in front if everyone when they are totally different on a personally level.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would not waste any time monitoring the possibility of Antonio Brown to the Eagles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[They will definitely reap what they have sown, this just won't be silent..]]></document><document><![CDATA[My spring break is going to be kicked off in the most epic way possible!!! At @ABQTopes Park watching @NewMexicoUTD… https://t.co/oTMLoyjTS9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont know who needs to hear this but..    Your baby deserves a part of your tax return...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin is a part of history, and he's making big changes in his field! I'm so proud of all that he's doing.  https://t.co/xal5L0eW41]]></document><document><![CDATA[Science Salon #54 Dr. Michele Gelfand—Rule Makers, Rule Breakers: How Tight and Loose Cultures Wire Our World. We a… https://t.co/oStF6HeBIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephenfhayes killer news about you and @JonahNRO and the new venture. If you need a whisky swilling disabled lega… https://t.co/YIMwAV19yA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Steven Means provides the Falcons with depth and much needed toughness in the run game. Unlike Derrick Shelby.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeaVerou @svgeesus A blessing, congrats! An #opensource project or proprietary? 😇💜🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ewing sarcoma is a malignant bone tumor characterized by primitive round cells without obvious differentiation. The… https://t.co/5P9ISF8KBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Bertram put the game away for Barren County late with this big and-one basket. Barren County comes out on… https://t.co/PI4L00LlUT]]></document><document><![CDATA[laughter coming your way. Make your kid laugh with these Thanksgiving Lunch Box Notes using Thanksgiving Jokes for… https://t.co/A3QpsT8qez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffEd_HCSO @HCSOTexas Are yall still searching for the suspect? Or did yall catch him?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You have no idea what the stock market may have done. You are delusional]]></document><document><![CDATA[#manhattan #architecture #urbangeometry #newyorkcity #shotoniphone #iphoneonly #iphonography #mobilephotography… https://t.co/xB8xuSaVll]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FridayMotivation😉Learn in your own time with Spanish Dialogs translated side-by-side with innumerable exercises an… https://t.co/xznCqLZ0yr]]></document><document><![CDATA[THE @BillSimmons weighing in on the state of youth soccer in the US and going hard!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatMcCroryNC No seriously, did you just say “political operatives” in reference to #NC09?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCharchian I think Kirk will work out.  Bad season with the coaching issues, shore up off. Line. Case and teddy… https://t.co/C90AQX7FXf]]></document></documents></author>