<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@hazem_awad @Austen All speculation.. would have made it more difficult for me as a software company owner to hire… https://t.co/bh4jnX8VOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WingfieldNFL Take cornerback in the second round. There will be lots of good ones available. I likely go DL in the first.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I'm so proud to see the response in a manner of intelligence and class. I'm proud to be a Pakistani and proud… https://t.co/7MzKqtQEpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been touring for over a decade.. and this last run with @ColtBout45 may have been the most fun I’ve ever had o… https://t.co/1JvJ7ZICmf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinK3623 Easily could be Gonzaga.   But even if it is Duke back at #1. So what. There are no National Championsh… https://t.co/lZJoryl0aI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFienPrint But a damn fine speller of names and applier of correct accents]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood Dude is being ironic. I mean... some kind of performance art to screw with us.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1999, Troop 2609 #girlscoutseason @FlightNurseBee https://t.co/SmBd8DPWbc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Sr. Web Analyst" at Fossil Group, then look for people you might know… https://t.co/428Nm2XKlr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ELIERMUNOZ1999 Yeah they are! They’re fun af though once I got it down. Tried nose grinding it though and it’s jus… https://t.co/ic7ubyQy9O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AztecaDeportes Al más grande de la galaxia Hugo Sánchez marques 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Update: sadly neither happened but I did 225 at 133 body weight so that’s pretty cool I guess]]></document><document><![CDATA[😂🤣 I thought the Koran demanded the death of homosexuals.  He’s Islamic?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjmjackson J'ai.une vie tres rempslie. Mais. Lis le journal et j'écoute les nouvelles à la radio]]></document><document><![CDATA[this fucking job has the WORST hostesses in the world i’m so glad to leave sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsdoctorem So good! Every episode of that featuring Bob Mortimer is crazy. Have you seen "Taskmaster", that's so… https://t.co/WG8rDHjhtu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmiller1973 My bad, they only have millions of dollars. Makes such a difference, she totally worked her way up from nothing. 🧐]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t help you fix yourself but at least I can say I tried, I’m sorry but I gotta move on with my own life 🎧]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day, probably not anytime soon, but one day @TheBachelorTV will have a country music artist that more than two… https://t.co/FB02HIhnwy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Are you don't even know what the h*** you're talking about The president is a croolet president he lies too much]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelsijsteele @USLChampionship @KelsiJSteele saw it coming, folks... https://t.co/McePxKeVzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@segalink Because he has been busy being vindictive, unnecessarily nepotistic and wicked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dressing up in costumes. Playing silly games. Hiding out in tree tops, shouting out rude names.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@F_DiStefan0 @jermp09 Do yous really not get any laugh out of that at all? A piece of cheese tossed in a babys face… https://t.co/L5m6h6w5lo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just setting my alarm up before bed causes me ptsd cause I can hear that Apple radar ringtone in my head already https://t.co/U1yzaukWYw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_bobbyds Is there a cheap but healthy way to sustain yourself as a founder? Would love to read this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Public invited to sample recipes from food writer at Concord Market https://t.co/48zX7waUdw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The music always slap a lil harder when they really a shooter https://t.co/nMV4m10gSt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larrynemecek @startrekcbs @StarTrek @StarTrekRoom @karterhol ....then the visitor(s) from the future have knowledg… https://t.co/xFxELjbtFs]]></document><document><![CDATA[#1111 make a wish!! Wish granted= @dairyqueen #love #icecream #dairyqueen #saturday #treat @ Dairy Queen https://t.co/EBMaQKe0Yh]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s the term used for when you can’t survive the day without alcohol?  Being a parent, that’s what.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My upstairs neighbors dog has been barking for the past hour &amp; it’s super fucking annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rothstein tweeted this 16 hrs ago.   Wade is all but terminated from his job now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@afriendofmine2 @annefrances @SchittsCreek @Realeugenelevy @danjlevy @CBC @PopTV L.O.L. I like the “eww” at the end 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone’s zodiac runway commentary: I’m serving it up, living for the fantasy, feeling fun,   @VanessaVanjie ‘s zo… https://t.co/huZlTKFLpS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katanna @TheAcademy I feel like none of them belong in the pantheon. Quality films, but history will judge this to be a weak year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So nostalgic for the NBA on NBC Theme. The Greatest Sports intro ever. #RoundballRock]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think Bentley wanted me to stay home and play today!! @ Wildwood, Missouri https://t.co/tbYqGQP3df]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just drove past a kid with a hoodie on and sweats with jump soles on his feet cool to see kids are still down with the old school training]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome to the first day of Lent. I would like to invite you to Ash Wednesday service tonight at 7pm.  It is a beau… https://t.co/MzNRvee72M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annual Breakfast of returning citizens. @ Oakland, California https://t.co/bk1VWu3P2j]]></document><document><![CDATA[A shake up at @CBSNews? I enjoy @NorahODonnell in the mornings so she would be missed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody ever think about the fact that if a restaurant wants their cheesecake to look fancy they add a single raspb… https://t.co/9FgkKN5HyK]]></document><document><![CDATA[SftR 052: Paying off $490,000 of Debt and Buying a Camper in Cash with A Sunny Side Up Life https://t.co/FDnhaZjH2v via @campingworld]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can Lie to me Lorelei, if you Choose to! But, why would you Lie to yourself? You'll Never believe anything you… https://t.co/9NqyUle4Eg]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of the most inspiring social entries I know, Amber Runyan, send to have endless energy. @11thcandleco works to… https://t.co/URbDkUmSqw]]></document><document><![CDATA[16/25  #touringmusictech #basstech #guitartech #stageleft #stageleftcrew  #stageleftview #thistourlife #zoé… https://t.co/ByYROzZpqP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JunoMalik And condemning them I'm sure will solve all my problems. Irrelevant.  As stated. I brother would love yo… https://t.co/IuoPIa6rUY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AjMunsch10 @sofiajamora Promise I’m not fake like those LA people you cuttin off🤷🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump Good Morning! Thanks to @theresa_may @EmmanuelMacron and @AngelaMerkelCDU for hel… https://t.co/Bue1bsEEco]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OutlawedMind @JonDoeLives @KeithDB80 @courvoiserking @Birdseye1 @JaackSchitt @imrie_lisa @AnthonyVBrice1… https://t.co/84o3lBdrMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SudburyHomebrew @BrooklynBrewery @DrunkPolkaroo @david_buist @linda_lballis @raeraegck @xBeannote @Paul__G__… https://t.co/V7w7rtqr1v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LaraCroft #Giantess #gentlegiantess #giantwoman #giantwomen #BeautifulGiantess #animegiantess #mangagiantess… https://t.co/v4XHvtobSn]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna go out to dinner with my people but they ugly asses trying club n shit 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Newark Liberty International Airport in Newark, NJ https://t.co/iDb122n8Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[current weather in Raleigh: mist, 44°F 93% humidity, wind 7mph, pressure 1021mb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damwop2 Was just picking out clothes to give away ... to make room for more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[S San Gabriel Blvd &amp; E Valley Blvd San Gabriel, CA 91776 https://t.co/kTxMkQADN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhatiCanChange @_stumbler Right imagine being on the receiving end of that 📦 an trying to open it. Will be MF’ing this guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman @WhiteHouse @realDonaldTrump Why is this guy constantly talking about manafort? Lovers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Proof of Concept” #mixedmedia #digital with #acrylic #artistsoninstagram #thesilosatsawyeryards… https://t.co/GoW1bokcEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next up in the #whatisrural challenge? For the next 10 days, I have been asked to post a picture a day of what… https://t.co/iEmzkn09pW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve come to learn that the single greatest behavior issue in the lower elementary grades is...the PENCIL SHARPENER!  #usecrayons]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every good &amp; perfect ☕️comes from the 👨🏻above. #GoodMorningWorld #SundayMorning #coffee https://t.co/tSlfhkNYxX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just click on this link. No worries... #EmailMarketing  Is this legit @AskFrontier? https://t.co/uLU1LRRzOW]]></document><document><![CDATA[While the crowds were massive and engaged for #VenezuelaAidLive, Maduro’s concert was small and, hmmm, bored! To my… https://t.co/FZgI1y4LRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zendaya could simply put up a picture of her toenail and that shit would be fire]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catmandoustin @apdoran You can have a nasty cough and not have pneumonia or lung cancer too. Just trying to stay positive here. 😀👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoying @GregIles’s new CEMETERY ROAD. In a time of taut thrillers in tiny domestic worlds, it’s nice to sink into… https://t.co/iMe5QslFXd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nervous to apply for a job like "Case Manager/Community Liaison-Supportive Housing" at National Church Residences?… https://t.co/LmTERDjgKH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenyada17 They'll beat the deal they gave Ben Simmons. That's all it takes. A kid his size shouldn't wear PG's any… https://t.co/WzqOkL6lMv]]></document><document><![CDATA[viktor &amp; rolf haute couture printemps-été 2019 https://t.co/PM27glYXLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PBSherren @precordialthump What did the sphygmomanometer you say in this case?]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be shady but @captbeardrogers is the most fashionable trans man I’ve met and it’s not even close]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #KAGFORALL2020🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼🙏🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jharrisonAVL Certainly makes one wonder where it all went...I have no doubt there’s a Wanda Green tie in somewhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Democrats are as much looking for truth, and justice as nazi storm troopers were focused on Human rights!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back at the Ford Center for the OVC Championship. I'm expected a larger crowd than last night because there are fan… https://t.co/xR49xDxftR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itvnews Well leaving raw food on the counter top sure as shit could cause cross contamination...  loll]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VWalkerWells Did you, too, unwittingly look like a member of the hitler youth?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clintbetts Such a beautiful, revelatory piece of writing, brother. Thank you so very much for sharing 🙏 #thebeehive]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxBoot The people who defend her or high five her for owning Abrams — which she doesn’t — have seemingly no clue… https://t.co/bvDNzYZ9oH]]></document><document><![CDATA[BOYCOT THE PREZ. DJ TRUMP HATING OSCARS. DON'T  PROMOTE  ANYTHING THAT ARE AGAINST TRUMP. WE HAVE THE POWER TO CHOOSE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chargers win the District Title with a 48-23 win over Bay City Western! Go Dow! https://t.co/9SjPm2muY6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@galacticaactual @Dave_Green_NRA @Deplorable_Man @DeplorableJena @mbales250 @raducom @SealeyGerald @John_R_Berna… https://t.co/ApPmLLCOFK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj Is the iPad’s built in camera good enough for this purpose?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay @PrimeVideo Not Cinderella's Type was fantastic. The perfect modern day Cinderella movie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CREWcrew It's disgusting how the #trumpcrimefamily undermines America's sense of right and wrong, moral authority,… https://t.co/r0B78QXCAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunday March 3 - Your Morning Five:     House Democrats will subpoena Mueller if report is not made public, Schiff… https://t.co/3Eo4hSWoND]]></document><document><![CDATA[And once again I refuse to take the #forkintheroad https://t.co/amsch0D4lY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreeStar @LouisVuitton You are every fucking thing ! Pure perfection]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSJ Yes I definitely agree with you guys there #QArmy https://t.co/ba2QFO0KBt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mialynneb No DM button on your page from my page. Did you turn it off?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I beat the @toejamandearl tutorial. Still can’t exactly figure out how to play the hyperfunk mini games though. :-/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @AmandaLang in the Green Room @CTVNews @BNNBloomberg. Will be up at 1:40pm w/ @RichardCrouse @bdthomson an… https://t.co/rEQgpXeyYQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Way to go Avery .... you just may have lost the game for your team .....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yoshiki89 Sure. I think I still have extras of Finn, Kylo, and the stormtrooper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrairiePhlox @RodSalm People too often desire to unnecessarily govern others.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaylaRimpson and rub the outside of her pussy with your hand ,then she knows its real]]></document><document><![CDATA[@8baboom @OssiTaskinen @thebrandindex @HedgeyeIndstrls @JohnR03186885 @elonmusk @Tesla Sure it's easy, I gotta remo… https://t.co/9hsrMmWxnY]]></document></documents></author>