<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Some work days are wonderful @ Signal Mountain, Tennessee https://t.co/FUQisqs9Ph]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djbeatnick They have this thing called Day breakers where it’s sorta the concept you mentioned but I’d love to hear your vision.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deaconcruise @yanksteel @marthaj44 @MrsPerrin @nocovfefehere @FactCheckU @D_R_Gringa @Regan0002112 @UnimpressedTX… https://t.co/UPjgos7CAH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who decided to drop by during my radio co~host Retro Sunday Night on KHEW 88.5 FM we got all decked out for th… https://t.co/O6UAcFaTT6]]></document><document><![CDATA[“if men find out we can shapeshift they’re going to tell THE CHURCH”  .... am I a catfish? asking for myself https://t.co/p4ITCdtku0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow As a person from eastern Kentucky, I am very familiar with a similar exception.  I'll work on expungi… https://t.co/8Q6aG4qyNc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lucyyy0426 So incredibly proud of him! Do any other diver do anything like it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nmenon777 @Lrihendry @realDonaldTrump Exactly! No background, a bare history of posts. Soooooo plausible that an i… https://t.co/MiCT0LIMLi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbrraannddeenn @angeIictears @juliarusler Woooow, I really didn’t take advantage of the TN floods lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chelseahandler Mine too waiting for a chest X-ray. Happy f... birthday to me. Lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@studionoises @joshellistucker @meganromer @BroderickGreer @BrandanJR What’s intolerant about that statement based… https://t.co/fSj2V3noTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ilhan there are more ancient dicuments in the history of this world, then you have brain cells, that stateJewish p… https://t.co/GJ5goJSnKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that a bunny hanging from the building? @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/oMpEopTz7i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such a tasty, refined and fun dinner at #UNI With @tony_messina1 at the helm, @kenoringer ‘s resto is just tops!  A… https://t.co/Y98iyzoueO]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot more people are going to watch Roma after tonight and that is a very good thing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I WISH "WOODS THE WARRIOR" WOULD COME AND RUN FOR OFFICE IN NEW YORK! AND DO MORE GREAT MOVIES!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m literally crying tho + I’m jelly r u kidding me this was my dream lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish more than anything, that you were here. Happy Birthday, papaw ♥️ https://t.co/sOZs48XlPI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh, it’s all fine, the @DallasStars brought back #LesserOleksiak Problem solved! You saw how well he used that big,… https://t.co/dD0PiT9sRV]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s no correlation. She went to a club to have fun. It’s an establishment that’s for everyone]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Aldean is celebrating his birthday at his own bar and I’m here so it’s like was invited 🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[DESAULNIER: .. Did the president have any involvement...In directing you to do this? COHEN: Yes. DESAULNIER: What w… https://t.co/Atb0OmYvKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbusa617 @KennedyHDnation It is probably sitting in a fund to help them run against Trump in 2020 and I'll bet the… https://t.co/lnAcB1FAsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GianinoLoera @opciudadana La limpia la necesita él y alejar todos los demonios malditos que lleva adentro 😱]]></document><document><![CDATA[55 of 365: #skylights  #lamppost #settingsun #clouds #color #contrast #sun #trees #365smiles2019 @ Capitola, Califo… https://t.co/YB0de8aM8i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naijagym Big spoons? Little spoons? Does the oil have to be warm? This is vague and poorly written. #teampizza]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awaiting the Stepan news #OurPack @ArizonaCoyotes https://t.co/zvcdo2s5qW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maibortpetit @federicoalves Todos esos equipos eran alemanes imaginate ahora ni el embajador esta para ayudar y la… https://t.co/o7oLlDIlT7]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 days ago emily warmed my car up for me when I was sleeping and I’m still thinking about it, I am so lucky🥰she is my lord n savior]]></document><document><![CDATA[My relationship has nothing to do with anyone. At the end of the day.. I’m married, I have a son with him, and what… https://t.co/IcfRGaFQ7V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaLuizito @deganitos @rosecooleredboy @MariaEd07812623 @GuilhermeBoulos Então vc se enquadra nos dois pq está defe… https://t.co/1n6I4vtVQh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnnybananas @ChallengeMTV AMEN AMEN AMEN Johnny Bananas preach it!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dr Beth Erickson of @MCWRadOnc discussed how our programs including pancreas, #MRlinac &amp; image-guided… https://t.co/cV392eDdbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@FHSAA Class 7A girls basketball regional final: #FortLauderdale #Dillard at #Miami #Norland  Winner goes to the s… https://t.co/ALmcKYHezO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Selfie Sunday! Haven’t done that in awhile! To be fair the photo before this one was taken a different day! Ha! @ N… https://t.co/lX5JZgeUWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a horrible toothache and can’t get into the dentist until tomorrow 🙁😩😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadisonU 😂 post recession! I’ve been meaning to get those gagets that help you squeeze out all the toothpaste. I a… https://t.co/TNjMzYcpGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandacarpenter @brianstelter If your so concerned about crime look no further then the fake dossier]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just finished another project for my drawing 2 class! art #artmajor #drawingclass #artstudent #fiona #artwork… https://t.co/tdl0QsCDBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think these will sell just as quickly as the others 🌼🌱@SamuelHines80 @megansmac https://t.co/zbHvOaS7Pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pretended @nickjonas was actually singing this song to me and to this day I still so this #myfirstlove]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally gonna attend these work out classes at the Y tonight 😋😏🏋🏼‍♀️🧘🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[How well do you know your women in history? Put your knowledge to the test with the Guess That #WCW social media ch… https://t.co/Kh946Ho09H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz Aren’t you a congressman?  Do you really think what you just told Cohen is proper tweeting by a congress… https://t.co/vZnbZ8R3w5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dad served me a pupusa with a FORK AND KNIFE. You eat pupusas with your hands...I swear he set me up just so I could wash dishes]]></document><document><![CDATA[His photo was above my bed in middle school. He was truly my crush and today....he crushed me. Heartbroken.… https://t.co/bfIFA9nhnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oktiamarie @DrewBrownWrites King Herod to John the Baptist when he called him out for divorcing his wife and unlaw… https://t.co/L1UrpNW6eo]]></document><document><![CDATA[my heart never hurt so bad. i always felt i was worth nothing but hearing youre not worth it by the person you love sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I needed to hear this last night and today.... so thought I'd share it with you. "You're gonna be alright, It's gon… https://t.co/HccE3EJMv5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I found this groovy zippered neoprene cable management stuff on Amazon, too. — #cablemanagement @ UNT College of Vi… https://t.co/SydsNY9Vsu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't submit then quit. Apply for jobs like "Financial Acctng Cons" at Wells Fargo, then look for people you might… https://t.co/c7Vl2KYQsx]]></document><document><![CDATA[i don’t think my body ever gets used to two practices a day 7 days a week :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sarahhwarder @wogantayla i’m so serious let’s get tickets together :’)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Probably not without a fight, or rather a ‘Tantrum!’, as he has shown he’s capable of!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoicephusP @johnson_nkiru @girlsreallyrule Are you really that stupid?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Summer Walkers- Girls Need Love ain’t really need a remix 😒 not feeling it AT ALL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best renovation- Small goes to Memphis Music Initiative! #MBJBuildingMemphis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Blackrocks 51K IPA on tap now. https://t.co/JYsbisn5E8 @blackrocksbrew #BeerMenus]]></document><document><![CDATA[He has said so on many occasions. @gop @GOPChairwoman @SenateGOP @SenatorRomney @BenSasse @lisamurkowski… https://t.co/kiocca2Jvz]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the people on my 7 am flight who decided to have a loud conversation for the whole entire flight:  #InCharlotte… https://t.co/jwSqbWxA9w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work in #Charlotte, NC? View our latest opening: https://t.co/R21ybjLdC7 #Banking]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so glad it's game day! On my way to the Stone! If one thing can turn this day around, it's hockey!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coleyworld @SenFeinstein A doctored video, I fell for it, as soon as I found out I deleted it. I posted that every… https://t.co/nx5zeI8KHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeauOverman @ashtorix I witnessed this 😂 your face was just so done with life 😂 lmao happy birthday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Travis and the rest of our squad do such a great job, and it’s really nice to see this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_Universal_Mx @lopezobrador_ Es terco el cab... y nadie lo hace entender]]></document><document><![CDATA[A date with spaceykacey for Valentine’s Day 💕#goldenhour #giddyup @ The Theatre at Ace Hotel DTLA https://t.co/gYW726R0fP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo que un dia fue no sera, ya no vuelvas a buscarme. No tengo nada que darte🖤]]></document><document><![CDATA[The family experience at the Coliseum just got 💯x better! #RootedinOakland]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amaandaguerrero @bryyynnn You both suck 😂 why am i just now seeing this lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone has asked me what I’m doing today, shit drinking mimosas and taking a bubble bath so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[Charlotte NC Sun Mar 10th AM Forecast: TODAY Chance Of Showers Hi 70 TONIGHT Mostly Cloudy Lo 49]]></document><document><![CDATA[not to be dramatic but i really am over here crying bc of that fucking meme sarah made aldjskks i love feeling ,,, noticed aldjskks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SharonneHayes @DrJMieres @lesleejshaw @MinnowWalsh @Drroxmehran @iamritu @TIMESUPHC @ArielaLMarshall… https://t.co/f4y3GRuOOE]]></document><document><![CDATA[i get more love and support from strangers than my closest friends looool]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris @CoryBooker @SenWarren @SpeakerPelosi  STOP USING RACE AS A WEAPON.  RACE TELLS YOU NOTHING ABOUT A H… https://t.co/aSOunG6OBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Niggas always offering shit then when you take them up on their offers they wanna cry and say “your using me” 😒 nig… https://t.co/T0JPjZx1rJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leader of the Pack midway @72 feet @CoachPark2 @hannahno_banana #lhsscienceforall https://t.co/4HwI4zsM22]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VFranQuiLin @citizencydonia I haven’t checked it last time the tickets sold up really really quickly not sure if t… https://t.co/4p2w3vLVjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris Sick, now i know whY Trump said. Make america GREAT again. Find a cure for TDS..]]></document><document><![CDATA[executives under his personal control.   The company posted the letter on its website. There was no immediate comme… https://t.co/rkQ65UC28b]]></document><document><![CDATA[CNN doesn't deserve to interview anyone.  Acosta and others cannot report news, they just make it up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never in my fucking life yo. People were waiting for over an hour for their food, drinks , etc. as an experienced s… https://t.co/U0hZ7CYAMl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great way to spend #InternationalWomensDay w powerhouses in #AffordableHousing from across the country. Vicki Been-… https://t.co/izGLes5tjr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kairyssdal "I proceeded to curse at him a multiple times and then haul him back into the barn before he had a chan… https://t.co/6qKcarlbSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna stop telling my family my days off bc they’re always trying to ask for favors &amp; I can never enjoy my day off smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[VERSE: Nevertheless I am continually with thee: thou hast holden me by my right hand.Thou shalt guide me with thy c… https://t.co/utXrJKT72W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepKulik thanks for showing @CabotOG  @starkgeorge the Crown Jewel of @CarnegieLib The unique civil war history an… https://t.co/JH5GNtukXi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feel free to share! #csssj #cactuscollectors #succulentcollectors @CactiSucculents https://t.co/hv7lVYwe3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Master’s thesis proposal: am I finishing my education or is my education finishing me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m never going to forget that I Facebook messaged my chemical romance to come to my 13th birthday party at the cit… https://t.co/FHauWSVkM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @CharlesMcCool @Sostraveluk @RickGriffin @SonjaSwissLife @travelwithirine @TouringTastebud… https://t.co/PxnVjO9tS0]]></document><document><![CDATA[she brought a little piece of home and a lotta happiness💞 @ 5 Mile Dam https://t.co/3BWVOkTr7t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want a new tattoo! I know what I want but don’t know where I want to put it. 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m saying all of this to say; asking me to perform for $200 is asking me to perform pro bono. I only perform pro bono for @HerStoryChicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got guap not tax money like a glock you'll get popped if you act funny]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really want a new car but am I adult enough for a car payment ?? 😰😰😰😰]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I LOVE most about SkinnyFATS is that it’s the best of both worlds! You can eat healthy or you can indulge! It’… https://t.co/Qf6DPwcQRP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen The entire GOP is covering for a sleazy psycho. This will not end well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnDebMartin @wildswan @AOC @RashidaTlaib @LynnePattonTotally correct. If you all stop calling RACISM  and treat each other the way you r]]></document></documents></author>