<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I saw the highlights from the #oscars and this is what captured my attention 🤩❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[After all undeniably strong pa rin ang kanilang chemistry @DirekChrisM #ADNForDaddysGurlWithALDEN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker For the rest of her natural life. Think if she got 1 yr for each child, that's thousands of years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n_silverstein @Jim_Jordan LOL nice try yourself believing liars is par for the course for liberals but please save… https://t.co/RfSw52Ly6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @GOP , republicans have a very short memory.  Benghazi, countless investigations of Clintons.  Cou… https://t.co/7DsiAH49OZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rachel we've seen all the light sentences for everyone involved. Stop selling ppl false hope in a fraudulent, biase… https://t.co/Xd4UWK4oqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nolan1vernon @BellflowerVern4 @MHSCoachWilcox @Coach_MattGray @CoachTriv Thank you Nolan and all of you for making… https://t.co/THCh4DGi5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gwenstefani @blakeshelton Happy Valentine's Day! Can't wait to see you in Vegas next month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AidenHatfield OMG!!  Some people. I had a creep trying to follow me on IG. You know it’s not good when they messag… https://t.co/1psamtArNV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The fencing is being repaired/replaced right now.  #Foreverlying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KrochetxKorner #ThingsIveSharedWithMyDaughter   No matter where you are or how you identify, there is a sacred cir… https://t.co/qPCuhblKzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UkulelePreacher @eJoelWatts @KeithMcilwain @ClayKnick Chris WCA always said they can't live with local option (ie:… https://t.co/mdiHiu6utq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I made a lot of deals with god so my dog  would return.  He seems like he is annoyed with my life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FFortrue @survrad @PaulMer70053201 @WattooWattoo74 @RevKeithBritt @Gay_Man_Dan @Kitty01121 @FlyingEagle555… https://t.co/r6MJ0aHXOQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kinglj013 @leahmcelrath My Nanny (paternal grandmother) had one of these corn sticks pans. Sticks were a treat, si… https://t.co/LbNHnGcjIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Se entera que le esta poniendo los cuernos, o sea, explicame esa verga tan ilógica. Bueno, la cosa (digámosle asi)… https://t.co/0UMtii2ihC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/JGQE2UHrqj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HWDSB How is it that you haven't at the very least cancelled school busses! Possibly because you're sitting in you… https://t.co/a3T8iDXoBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeSilverman7 @Susanperchede @LinklerMatt @BernieSanders Bingo. Although I always got the impression deodorant was… https://t.co/ja6Rq7Z6kG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I the only one that on a rainy day, and driving, pulls the seat all the way up and to the front and also has win… https://t.co/DtsBio1Yc7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBenanti WHAT A DOUCHEBAG! Your reply is perfection. You’re a mom first.  PS-I hope your sweet girl is feeling better. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@learnics1 I actually added some since you updated your teacher dashboard.  Looking forward to seeing the new stude… https://t.co/Ssb6cQFeb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes. I still remember the advice the best mentor ever @Mary_C_Wright shared with me when I started my post-doc at C… https://t.co/2Z5BRG8JfX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never Estimate The Power Of Your Examples • You Are Enough • Change Takes Time Sometimes • We Can All Do Good By Do… https://t.co/w4Z3VV7S4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it halfway!! On to the rest of the week!! #humpDAY (@ Town of Deerfield in NY) https://t.co/gs5DJ3uBve https://t.co/03YKqjm5QQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfBlacktruth Donald Trump tweet that the 52% or so he got was good news!  Sho you right!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joshscampbell @brianstelter @mdornic You are respected Josh!Stone is repulsive! Any idiots who believe him weren’t… https://t.co/GcTwc9J1UQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't care that I do her every year. Emma Swan is probably one of my favorite heroines of all time.  She's dealt… https://t.co/qUuWHYmsXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@42Ceecee I guess I just told myself it was okay not to... everything would be FINE haha. I don’t want to be a slav… https://t.co/7K8oK2Baft]]></document><document><![CDATA[About 4 left @hragv @coreyhelford @matthewgardocki #artistunknown https://t.co/PIDJFhnxzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@backt0nature This is amazing. None of mine have ever done this that I know of. So cute.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t want to spend the rest of my life with no one else but you🌅💛💍 https://t.co/mJYTtZiPsS]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/o6KUZVfq9H  I’m very thankful to all of your birthday wishes! I am very blessed with all the love in the world. Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my favorite dragon! Wait til you see what we made today 🐉🦈 @mytalk1071 📸 @HannahBrugman #gameofthrones https://t.co/X56ly2tBZp]]></document><document><![CDATA[And this walk is personal, between you and God. Thank you, God for your abiding love and mercy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new favorite reading spot 📖 #WhereInTheWorldIsSummy #Miami @ SeaFair Mega Yacht https://t.co/i7FAMuSuKc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl I’m otp with my friend telling her to hurry up and pick my room and bihhh I see a whole nigga name under one o… https://t.co/jVTej6Rhgx]]></document><document><![CDATA[See, now that’s your model portfolio shot, one of them, to keep in your headshots for publicity!  You’re really bea… https://t.co/MfwScuBBfv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sincerely_steff When I opened the door to let him sleep in my room he meowed and hugged my leg again. Pinche weirdo gatito!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My boyfriend has decided to make homemade pickles so I have decided to find a new boyfriend. Applications open now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitheresteph_ yes!!! me too. it happens slot in the morning for me. they’re almost like fever dreams bc they don’t… https://t.co/wof4AIO1bI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Sportyvern @BxglL @ChicagoPenguin2 @MrsSpuds @72cricket @sannbs @CSonafelt @sharon_schwan @RidenerTina @ACog1984 Boy he sure is!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I’m on bar and we make eye contact for a good 3-5 seconds and I’m smiling the entire time and you just glaring a… https://t.co/95cCqo3Ma5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alot of mf's be in the right place at the right time an still wont take advantage of the opportunity that comes they way.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’ve done kind things to me and I wont forget that, but I always won’t forget about that shit I just found out lol!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeiferA I haven't seen the sun moon dubs but I'll agree with that just on what I have seen. Brock is good tho.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want FREE Botox?! Join the party! Details coming soon!! Space is limited so reserve your spot today! #atyourservice… https://t.co/9WU4pLBtCO]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was a Structural Engineer and so was one of our Structural Engineers. Having those to two people talk, who are… https://t.co/3uk3Ugf7Yt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kimi wa my~ BEAUTIFUL HANGOVER M/V https://t.co/RKvFjwQxIl yeah~ it’s me GD...😆😘❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I KNOW I ASKED SHOULD I DO FEED INS OR FAUX LOCS CROCHET BUT UMMM YEAH THIS WAS THE OUTCOME 😝 ... WHEN YOU SLAY YOU… https://t.co/AENWatwXpN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoying the views at Silvies Valley Ranch, a luxury ranch with stunning accommodations, gourmet food, a… https://t.co/7pRKuVbJeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get asked all the time, “Why did you move from Toronto to Cobourg... and why Cobourg?!”  Honestly, I love Toronto… https://t.co/1uGBRWXI9C]]></document><document><![CDATA[Health reasons? How about liability of admitted fraud purposely committed by his campaign? The state and opponent's… https://t.co/mFYB0n5nRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@k_e_nnedy I’m assuming it must have been under control. They didn’t block off the area to traffic or anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tenerlo de frente y estarlo viendo a los ojos fijamente con una sonrisa enorme mientras me cantaba uff juro por Dio… https://t.co/dBTwEGfcmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump Hey, @PressSec - I call bullshit on your claim! https://t.co/XY90pU6daM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikkic97 @khloekardashian Truth...he wanted a smash n grab. Khloé went overboard with the grab]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteinbrinkLaura @lmsbreeden @thezenteacher @bkulak11 @TheTechRabbi @LisaJohnson @Jeff_Zoul @casas_jimmy @tishrich… https://t.co/M9lUiEto9V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here's the spicy AF cookies! They're so good! Tastes like a regular chocolate cookie at first, then OH HEY SPICY KI… https://t.co/1kJhPlmcxt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actually also TBT to when all my former coworkers excluded me from their holiday party because apparently I’m “too… https://t.co/7WOBLYJafI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coming back to my stomping grounds was made even more pleasant by having brunch at @tandem_cc. The crepes and coffe… https://t.co/4jEwZVOtjl]]></document><document><![CDATA[My love for @taylorswift13 grows more and more everyday ❤️ I’m so proud of the woman you have become. Thank you for… https://t.co/Rn0jiDTH4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlenderSherbet I'm so fucking pissed off today. Thank you for the post that was just right to bring a smile.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When their favorite coach of all time starts talking about their freshman year starting Varsity and tears start rol… https://t.co/xgtcP1J5XU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t be a normal night if I didn’t forget to get gas and then HAD TO GET GAS DELIVERED TO ME CAUSE MY JEEP STOPPED DRIVING LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveSiwek @fromthe108 I need to take it to get a code now its been bitching about the anti skid needing service t… https://t.co/HhbugXY2qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol yes you crazy bonehead blathering fool aoc. Put out your stupid list. At least there are a few sane Dims left? Maybe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bbygrimes It’s good that you know that. Now you just have to avoid them. There’s no cure unfortunately. Mine is cr… https://t.co/IEThRf1X2p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laura24fan Good Morning Laura ☕️☕️☕️ Totally Awesome ❤️🏁❤️🏁🎶 https://t.co/itK91eFOdq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nutri_chomps I'm confused...the tweet says this weekend, but it also says @TXMotorSpeedway. Fontana is this weeken… https://t.co/ItFhKuVERL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looked at 4 nice ass houses this morning...I can't wait to fucking move!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freddysanchez84 Im watching it too with D. I’m nauseous. It’s sooo wrong. 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJeffMerkley Maybe we should help at the source and stop relying on bandaids....]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man gave these to me after a performance last weekend, saying he “found” them on the street. We’ve been gone for… https://t.co/kUurOnUSYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Icegirl69 I understand why people are upset about Crenshaw, the guy is a POS and while I, PERSONALLY, don't think… https://t.co/cCx3WZdOX8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erikajayne I hope you’re recovering well beautiful lady! I just had a total knee replacement down at the end of August last year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyMelisande @Anna_Mazz @medickinson @whaeavee @hollyjmathieson @annamleese @cklibabeth83 @WhoresofYore… https://t.co/8rflPbl1hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[An hour in to watching Abducted in Plain Sight: This cannot be based on a true story. These people are literally th… https://t.co/56ttFrrO9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ACE2019PHILLY Pres. Munoz/Univ.ofHouston/Dwtn on ensuring success of men of color - “students aren’t fragile;pathw… https://t.co/DsFTvhlvmq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trix8591 @SylviaPlayhouse Those details are available when you come in! ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danna_johnson11 It’s always good to hear from you! I love and miss you and I’m proud of YOU. Thankful for our life… https://t.co/6AZxRW2poy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@WCCO #mymorning making the most of all this snow! https://t.co/fDva9ac8K7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beat Chef Hubby in Connect Four at the @dtmarketgr Tropical Chill Winterfest. Then we went inside for some amazing… https://t.co/Ym0TTyEdAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 My #1 advice for anyone attending the Six Invitational this weekend: if you get a chance to say hi to/take a pic… https://t.co/X9xeNg4cbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this ribbon concept! Thank you @acgme 🎀 #ACGME19 https://t.co/hndueHwNZQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imaginarymargo @EdonaGKrasniqi @_starpostgroup_ She feels guilty about Noah cuz when she thought he was cheating s… https://t.co/DwXmIKI65M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jsandusky95 Sasquatch got nothing on your sass 😏😋 twas a wonderful day! https://t.co/S8URWISFFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Silence is the sign of Truth... Patience is the sign of Behavior....Respect is the sign of Character...” -Harshu… https://t.co/Gp60WurYYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rolandoarturo1 @KarlaCalle Otro más que menosprecia insultando y agrediendo @rolandoarturo1 , eres igual a Noelia]]></document><document><![CDATA[AP  #masculineusproject #areyoudocumented  #thisisamerica #harlem #noflagnecessary #human #community #courage… https://t.co/r58A5VjYKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it’s really fucked up how the plane we got on to bring us back to Michigan actually brought us back to Michigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Damn! I wonder how much my three levels spinal fusion cost! Probably as much as a house!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryLDixon @NHLBlackhawks @LinBrehmer Love it!! ❤️ The @NHLBlackhawks know how to take care of their fans!   Is th… https://t.co/bPNqQcYI1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrincessJ114 Happy Friday Princess Hope you have a fabulous day 💄💫❤💅👠👼🕊🦄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bevtitle1 @odellawilson @alllibertynews @justinamash @POTUS @realDonaldTrump They have 3.7 billion to spend until… https://t.co/4SBKxmCoR8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yooooooo depression is real and I dont think there will ever be a time in my life that I dont suffer from it. Some… https://t.co/idWykmfX5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timhakr @rumbleroller @Marce_AZ @marathonmarj @paulcli @DavidCarrozza @runman317 @c20h10n2 @Alpine_Skye… https://t.co/govjUmPwnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love that people dream about the Oregon coast like this but when I go there, we just getting lit in a sand hole.… https://t.co/gaIUkVzfsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janina i was molested by Jeremy Gilbreathe. He worked on Pearl Harbor starring @BenAffleck he played a sailor feat… https://t.co/MSZ0xWuCgd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si je n'avais pas eu confiance dans le système administratif québécois, je naurais jamais confié mon fils à ma mère… https://t.co/5jmiJL2skE]]></document></documents></author>