<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[6 more hilarious portraits of Channing Tatum and Jonah Hill: https://t.co/jpm5nrdt4u... https://t.co/Eyc0ncQAbC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brewerytravels @SommBeer @BeerLoversofWI @tilbeerdouspart @ephoustonbill @excitedtofeast @TapTakeOverPod… https://t.co/duQfkVsn7A]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging at a Bruins haunt before a game tonight and of course the nostalgia programming has me thinking @thehipdotcom and Fireworks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonArcherCap @jbarro It's because of white supremacy and rabid evangelism and irrational fears that anarchy will e… https://t.co/aRcoMoSLsp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Terrell Suggs to part ways with Baltimore after 16 years  https://t.co/BFB8QX8w5X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of you never collected every star in Mario 64 and found Yoshi at the top of the castle and it shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Son is about to implement him some #Kubernetes Network Policy with #Calico #Tigera https://t.co/Bi11ezy5vl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to present at #Empower19! ▶️Emerging Leaders Ignite! Snapshots of...All Learners (1627) March 16, 4:15-5:15… https://t.co/GZO84t5rUU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima need you to get back to annoying working out mikey....you’re getting comfortable]]></document><document><![CDATA[*gets multiple unexpected bills right after one another, immediately starts eating ashes and boiling a single potat… https://t.co/vVJNQePEGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at The Bench outside the Maria Miles Visitors Center in Salisbury, MA https://t.co/LoapBgUXpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[History will not be kind to you @PressSec, or your lump of rotten cheese of a boss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all are all asking me why I tweeted this and the answer is cuz it was 5 am and I was exhausted]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WestendWhale No one -Kayge Calypso &amp; DUNN Remix https://t.co/g2cc3RerTZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brodiesmith21 @QuiviraCabos Those cliff-side holes are unreal.  Wait til you try the sliders in one of the comfort stations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @PHSchwager. Excited to see where your journey takes you. #LeadershipMatters]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SContemplator @LCbasecamp @leftarmisme @HempTemptress @Hardluck_Josie @LoreCurious @sluts_guts @PositivePyrami1… https://t.co/su05Zr3MYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:38.8°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[extremely upset, and I don’t get to know if it’s just on why her screw date is done conversing w/ her / didn’t seem… https://t.co/qny4yjWWOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[1- The @netflix issue is yours. Your rep said so - many times. It’s yours to fix and if can’t deliver then offer yo… https://t.co/LshnyM0Bks]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lochhead Your turn to come on MY show! I’m coming to the studio ⚡️⚡️⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dollar1075 I have a Note 9 now and I love it. My battery on my S8 was amazing until it wasn't.  Now I have this an… https://t.co/2n7dO6B2r9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Every President half the country loves you other half hates you. That’s what Trump is experiencing… https://t.co/T82WB2KfpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleachyBleachy @dbongino So I guess you must have some evidence that 2 years hasn't produced?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MizzouPatriot @GabeDeArmond Those injuries aren’t KA’s fault. What you can blame KA for is the lack of talent/dept… https://t.co/T4swWMrVNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, Kenny said otherwise. Good too see the organization on the same page.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paradise Nightclub celebrating Josie and Terri's Birthday  #happybirthday #paradisenightclub @ Paradise Nightclub https://t.co/SzMtnhiJne]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dear friend Leland Sklar #lelandsklar #rock #rockandroll @ Pasadena, California https://t.co/GsSTjuGfMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johndensford @JOSHMBB19 I think the food is good in relation to other chain places but it's definitely sub-standar… https://t.co/yNzjPG38O8]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 🎁 👍 Awesome! I just got a freebie! Try it! Let's see what you can get, cellphones, cash prize or notebooks? The s… https://t.co/cztoBaO36x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hillary Cliton says she's not going anywhere. . Thats good. Saves the taxpayer lots. Of money. .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Players view walking from 17th to 18th @TPCSawgrass @THEPLAYERSChamp https://t.co/sGij4ZUa6w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Patricia_Traina We have made the decision, if they don't draft a QB, trade Odell and roll with Eli, we are putting… https://t.co/AI0YedSbmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago you were wonderful. What a great city. Next stop Washington DC.   #Travel #Adventure #America #Chicago… https://t.co/XrifU7hcvn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visited and prayed with 4 representatives about HB 1182 and the value of life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Does that mean your going to giveaway 2 of your 3 homes to poor people? I would love an upgrade but… https://t.co/QLZi76ABUG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnthoApologist @BOStoPDX @nhannahjones No, they were questions. Because I couldn’t understand how such a broad sta… https://t.co/Bpp5lC8zcT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unfortunately UL Girls bowling came in 4th at sectionals and were unable to advance to district One individual did… https://t.co/COpVQ5piLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how excited LA gets when we have a little winter weather. #cawx #CAstorm https://t.co/lmY0IBGHIY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate the term "speak it into existence" NOTHING happens to those who wish for things to happen. You have to set g… https://t.co/VkhnS3gv9n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chicago Police: Jussie Smollet is under arrest and in custody.  Detectives will have news conference at 9am.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGirlInPhilly Me at a Navy Football game this year in dem grays lol https://t.co/ABY2DRX9XG]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Oscars are nothing more than a bunch of Gold Fish entertaining themselves in their little bubble world. No need… https://t.co/9z8ljRFNWl]]></document><document><![CDATA[100000000% true. When I started my business I makes 6000 the first year. Well below minimum wage.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yea sorry Teddi but your shit ain’t still making sense. Seems like you’re overrreacting #RHOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[We got work and sometimes two job plus school......yeah you better not worry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To keep DFW’s economic engine revving, American Airlines has to make a call on a new terminal… https://t.co/U0AcmoihSK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@streamyardapp Love #TheYard and how much you support your users! https://t.co/1KR25IamnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[We need to guide and support younger generations because they will be leading the world we are leading today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally starting to feel better so I thought I would do a quick sketch @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/XtkWYuOEU6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awesome check out who made the trending ads on Yahoo today! 🎶🙌🎶 #musicismylife #singersongwriter #countryboy… https://t.co/EZCngVBF9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very proud of our school district tasing over 2K for the Madison Food Center. Always looking to give back! 💪🏻💙⚡️… https://t.co/d3rCim4W1k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ManvsAle @neonraptorbrew @JohanBBT @mtravis63 @badhopper @linda_lballis @beerhunter74 @kosind @Claus1974 @wrayzors… https://t.co/8NFFyVc8DK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaihenH @jguaido @CNNEE Lo que es un auto proclamado en la calle y ahora ya pasó al olvido como un tristemente célebre]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice job @LesterHoltNBC #NoCollusion "Instead of reporting on their massive breaking news story that drove a flood… https://t.co/6HashISizT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoa... This was a sight. Flasher - Material (Official Video) https://t.co/JQCkxd0pzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sportsreporters I can't argue with that fact that shooting is a silly metric]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish What about Jared Kushner? He wears a weird hat thingy and observes strict dietary laws. Is he against the Constitution?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a rivalry that dates back to 1960, @SacStBaseball hosts @UCDavisBaseball under the lights... And other regional… https://t.co/RZcnAcAfvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[$2.08 (@ Costco Gasoline in Royal Palm Beach, FL) https://t.co/WhjfaYiEPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabreezy8 @ruthhamblin Visit Capilano Regional Natural Bridge Park just north of Vancouver city.… https://t.co/3Hxx5n51dh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSchwarzenegger Grant come home the kids miss you. And the rams went to the super bowl this year, you would have loved it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crackheads are a completely different breed, they know somethin we don’t. DUDE HIT THE ONE TWO STEP in front of the… https://t.co/lXhusM2x72]]></document><document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel was better than I thought it would be but the end credit scenes were wasted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fox News: Trump's remarks on Otto Warmbier case reflect 'chronic problem' in president's rhetoric: Charles Lane.… https://t.co/PDPnw9kZcO]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘Where we spend our money is the biggest tool we have to change our world..’ #PowerfulWords #Sustainability… https://t.co/vIICwyFSeb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Casting GIANT Underground Wasp Nest with Molten Aluminum https://t.co/btrDaHGDER via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjaymeow is jaymee gonna black out again tonight? asking for a friend]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Feel-Good Love 🧠✨❤️ #dopamine #designbyjorgenieves @ Orlando, Florida https://t.co/u4Gato421D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CollegeFriender @rachaelpacella Depends. Which dress? And which accounting department? 🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Satan wants you to kill, steal, and destroy each other over those idols/projected images]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carmen38004447 @Ruben37889962 @BJ_Stew @FrankLangben @Franklin_Graham Actually, God orders an abortion in Numbers.… https://t.co/19NgJpxWzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dharasanudo U shouldn't. Sometime they could give u shit when trying to come back tho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Swimming World and ISHOF Just Upgraded Their Website: Check Out This Story... https://t.co/wK5GAvGS2N… https://t.co/IjSl6z2mgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m half asleep this morning going To the bathroom and I open the door and I tear off my toe nail. Talk about pain man]]></document><document><![CDATA[@I_Am_MFR “Let the past die...kill it if you must” https://t.co/W1gFIUiqqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therunchat @historianed_ A6:  overuse something else... err, cross train #runchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was reminded this AM: When I have questions I should go to God for answers. John 3:1-21]]></document><document><![CDATA[@liamgallagher Eh...keep the set list basic:  1. Live Forever 2. Don’t Go Away 3. She’s Electric 4. Champagne Super… https://t.co/53bTLs8WH5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaryErickson1 today while I was looking at jackets, “I know you like a good asymmetrical neckline.” By god she’s r… https://t.co/bjnFfrbtaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cameron_kasky I get it. Just take it a few bites at a time. Then it won’t be so overwhelming.  Felt the same way a… https://t.co/jbaKLmhcUg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe the homies in love with paisa/ Latina girls smh. You can have the tacos I’ll take the ham sandwiches 🤣👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[The greatest gift of life is friendship, and I have received it. Hubert H. Humphrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA  @FBI Stone belongs in jail just for his stupidity, not to mention threatening a federal judge. America… https://t.co/rqexyMPJRC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wowe_sophia @wow_junglegrrrl I don’t know, tricks become predictable and then they lose effectiveness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOnea75146898 @RealJamesWoods What’s that got to do with what he’s done for the country, don’t forget Obama was… https://t.co/ZjfnhszcYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ive never been or will ever be ready for when the beat drops in Plain Jane. I'm always just like HOOOOOOLY FUUUUCCC… https://t.co/1y7S8t8Iz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@docjewells @USFVinikMBA @Harrolle_MGH We can do more together🙏🏾 #SPB6807 Implement #ShineTheory to uplift and brin… https://t.co/c4pMV1YKu2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Simardtweets1 @DeezHabz He’s the reason Price got injured in the playoffs against New York a few years back. Was 1… https://t.co/PO6MhoWUGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @TomSteyer I mistrust the people of the Ohio 4th Congressional District coach. They elected you. This d… https://t.co/R5vmrqEK52]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antoine Anderson presents “Model Monday” peace Lounge 2632 Georgia Ave NW Washington, DC Tonight 10pm-2am  Host By:… https://t.co/bYN75Z8HIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rcjanderson The Journal needs @paddybrendan back so STM can get the respect they deserve in the paper. Trying to f… https://t.co/bQR0VTVSmW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayTeeD We were in the middle of car searching when the announcement happened :(.    Still have the pass on my win… https://t.co/eglOG8sAqe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dave_Winbod @gazbod They’ll probably claim it’s on police advice. #HornyToads]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also the chord progression??? and the harmony in the chorus??? Wow 20/10 worth Roger hiding in the cupboard for]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LapstoneHammer ugh I know y’all have some hats stashed away in that beautiful store but it’s a 3 hours drive!! 14… https://t.co/Igj2nOmx1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[A pictorial of our families recent history starting in 1802.    Fortunate to work for ⁦⁦@CortevaCA⁩ and… https://t.co/hHs9gosh4T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson Matt Gaetz is a licensed attorney in Florida. His Bar Number is 48962. He violated 18 U.S.C. § 1512.… https://t.co/XjfWtrg6r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weallscrewed @Pats_Fan_603 @CNN Ive found that folks on the right generally dont like doing that. Not sure of its… https://t.co/xXJVFwvqAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@farmingtonfhs with a couple breakaway layups, now leading .@VSCHS_Storm 60-53 with 58 secs left in 4Q .@JamesDYodice #NMAA]]></document></documents></author>