<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@loudblkgrl Seriously. CHEERS TO YOU! Mom-ing is f*cking hard. High-five to all the teen moms who come out ahead! T… https://t.co/Abz8fs6sbT]]></document><document><![CDATA[How We See: Color and Materiality laumeierstl with Anne Lindberg annelindbergstudio, Jedediah Caesar thecurseisback… https://t.co/PRBKZLrfhu]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I want something bad enough I sacrifice everything. I really wanted to go out this weekend and enjoy myself bu… https://t.co/OHnmDSnG4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@loopylarner @MissPassey @kyleipryor @Hollyoaks BB Never was my favorite! He tried to destroy #Stug and now James i… https://t.co/UFZWHxLaft]]></document><document><![CDATA[florence and the machines cover of stand by me. thats it. thats the tweet]]></document><document><![CDATA[ahahaha and here I thought I was going to get some stuff done before seeing captain marvel again this afternoon https://t.co/1KfJmytyi9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I found were moments. Moments of advice. Moments of support. Moments of love. They’ve all pushed me on my way.… https://t.co/fpBxwxCWbh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrJenGunter @meganranney This is the only solution. You already know the truth.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rickwilliamsjr @carymagazine @HTrentEvans1 @julieresua23 @jganoe @cindy_yaeger @DDMSBuzz @AlstonRidgeMS… https://t.co/gsKvUwP0kX]]></document><document><![CDATA[My finance professor really Buggin yo he’s saying that if you rat on someone cheating during an exam they get a zer… https://t.co/sYsfhqjZHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 37 FIELDCREST DR #Columbus #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/E2frUgncDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger Yep —- but what can you say?  These last 2 1/2 years the Republicans have supported and promoted THE… https://t.co/jVFaDbO9UN]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY BIRTHDAY ITZEL!!! I hope you have an amazing day !! I can’t wait to meet you! Love you💓💘💖 @itzeldlgomez]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UWVascsurg Hey we may not have high quality cigars like at Dr. @malas_mahmoud’s meetings, but IR isn’t that bad...… https://t.co/IA0D8DYW4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please support my community  @CrossFit gym #KanehsatakeCrossfit 💜Tragedy struck 24 hours ago when a fire burned dow… https://t.co/35Kxk6y2jx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmmaWatson K A L E I D O S C O P E: offering free analog creative sanctuaries dedicated to the refusion of a fragm… https://t.co/AytyJ5eJzw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing an all-white shirt (a rare occurrence for me) and I just ate lunch without spilling all over it.   New Achievement Unlocked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Extra happy happy hour in Morro Bay #CentralCoasting #SLOyourroll @ Morro Bay State Park https://t.co/8klBQSLbCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drive by photo on waterfront, where the Gardiner  expressway has been taken down the huge concrete supports remain… https://t.co/gbJeR0QBCb]]></document><document><![CDATA[That attacker needs a JOB. I know,  go apply to one of the jobs the President he opposes has created for the black… https://t.co/z9RkcyTHRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ValerieDenton8 Good morning Val. Hope it’s warmed up a bit out by you❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/fP8ifrwsb7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ahhh yesss the perfect time of night to watch TAZ videos to be inspired but for some reason to start sobbing becaus… https://t.co/v0FktcfjzI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AparnaDahanukar @JohnOSullivan36 @SpeakerPelosi I agree. But time is not on our side.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un avant - après comme on les aiment !  #nailsgram #onglesquebec #quebeccity  #quebecregion #quebec #nails #qc… https://t.co/zO8nj6w5Oy]]></document><document><![CDATA[don’t get me wrong, i still struggle, sometimes even more than i did then, but now i have these friends, memories,… https://t.co/zpA1au6Uz6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoarLoudTravel @TouringTastebud @monstervoyage @always5star @Adventuringgal @sl2016_sl @RoadtripC @HHLifestyleTrav… https://t.co/XkcLSElmoa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best text I could’ve received 24-hours post bday;) https://t.co/rb9cm1dNpO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reddogsusie I RT and shared Please help COLTON get ADOPTED/RESCUE/FOSTER/PLEDGE/DONATE/To his cause he needs us mo… https://t.co/MrI2HhdAfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyMcKew You rarely see him with Barron. When you do, Barron is walking behind him. I never see them interact]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asi mero yo. La primera semana del 2019  Y el resto del 2019  🐷🐖🐽  A lo q da😊😉😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I have to give is love and loyalty and Im constantly still getting fucked over]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StefanTigges @CMGlastonbury @ASHNRSociety @rhwiggins @MedPierre @CDP_Rad @cmtomblinson @gmoonis @phudge54… https://t.co/I5dQ5t7sMP]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much good stuff in here for anyone interested in the future of local  news. “RETORT FOR AMERICA” by Chris Faraone https://t.co/ChrrRhpQ5D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nprevito7 I thought we were crawfish brothas ok https://t.co/pFQy0jlSxp]]></document><document><![CDATA[50 Cent https://t.co/uy30baFAML via @YouTube   @kristen_mason5  LMFAOOOOO 😂❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 show play day! Brunch and drinks @ESTnyc for @YoungbloodNYC and a free play reading @LarkTheatre. Mirror selfie s… https://t.co/sAOLM8kTUu]]></document><document><![CDATA[You are looking at them through the lens of being reporters/journalist.  They are simply royal gossipers creating a… https://t.co/SYFBbTDRFw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dixie_Principal Gives me chills and tears at the same time. Kids do get it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i am so fucking over @Bharper3407. either shit or get off the pot already! #BryceHarper #OverIt #MLB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flea market fun with these amazing ladies ❤️  #lovethesegirls @ Mission Viejo, California https://t.co/YMu7OHXvYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heh. Just saw @rcatanese on ESPN, following Josef into the stadium. #ATLUTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jajajaj castro101046 parece que te estamos haciendo cuchicu 😂🤣😂🤣😂 @ Laura's Zumba Lovers Studio https://t.co/JBodL0v99r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like so many cities, Portland’s black population falling behind on homeownership  “the homeownership rate for Portl… https://t.co/KS3hK5Yjrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This is the way we make the love grow...smile by smile, day by day” - Snatam Kaur]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BTS_twt #jungkook Hey sweetie, I was trying to wait to tell you goodnight until you tweeted Yoongi's birthday twee… https://t.co/VU7ij3luhS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatRamsland What happens if Mueller finds Trump fingerprints in Russia conspiracy? https://t.co/RvTkVmAYCC via @Yahoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@metssec413 @KevinnSnow @TL8throum @ArianFoster His 33 and your 33 are 2 completely different things buddy 😭😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oonkeeta26 I have a question: is that one-way asymmetrical or two-way asymmetrical? #cm215bu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh god. I remember this. I'd be in the dark half asleep, and the talking would start coming from the closet.  So ma… https://t.co/iHJgaIsV23]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarshaPatriot @ctanner3 @LibertysThunder @pokergod12345 @waters77 @TankIncU @ThomasElliot6 @Kitcars88557088… https://t.co/nVnUFyYCGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[The act should be reintroduced!!! All those that oppose should be noted!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also pray for me to get out of this odd funk, I was happy and I kinda feel sad???? What is this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@larkingin I have this one!! The eggshell unzips and he fits inside. It's so cute 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kelly_clarkson So sorry you’re still feeling crappy.  But even with a head cold, you still sounded amazing Saturda… https://t.co/LBRw8Z7mAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[42 days to opening day! Go Brewers! 👍🏻😁👏🏻🎉🙌🏻⚾️  "The game of life can be too short, so play with everything you've… https://t.co/fvIgAac2BH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infopresidencia #PND contra los menos favorecidos. Imagino las risas malvadas, del Enano Malvado, @MinHacienda y E… https://t.co/p5RULwRAo2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robrousseau Sorry but I already took all of Jerry's cows and they are in my back yard]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im just over here tryna be responsible and still live life. Mind ya business.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @DPSNewsNow teachers’ strike is over. We talk about it w/ @GovofCO at 8:12am @KOANewsRadio @ContactLenz_KOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[chronic migraines : what actually works to cure them? this is an issue i’ve been having for years and after countle… https://t.co/GWrBVq4B6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jondhoward I don’t see Trout coming here. I think he stays in LA or goes to Philly. I’d love him in Atlanta though.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Harry is still going strong even after it's been almost 2 years since his first album and solo career was launched.… https://t.co/ZLPGoy6DZd]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WHk9LMS0Sa #truth #GoVegan it's all about your perception. ❤🐂🐕🐖🐺🐏🐵🐄🐣🐪🐐🐼🐰]]></document><document><![CDATA[september just can not get here fast enough i am so excited about going to the concert and seeing the backstreet bo… https://t.co/6LQIiXKx30]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidaxelrod @realDonaldTrump This is really beneath dignity. Shame on you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@go4itbas @okWessler5 @formerbondgirl @TryAgain1955 @Happyfeet5150 @janasea21 @Jay05757467 @JayChpJones… https://t.co/N0oYZD9wJe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atrupar WTF is Van Jones doing at CPAC and why is he spouting this factually incorrect garbage?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxPowe02028661 @the_patrushka @nappypappy420 @irvmuller @itsJeffTiedrich @DianaPMesser @realDonaldTrump Maybe he’… https://t.co/nYoGsJPIng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrDane1982 He took money from NRA to become legit and win a Senate seat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Likewise Chris! Thank you for showing us all such great hospitality tonight  @DallasFed !]]></document><document><![CDATA[high off acid , fly like aladdin on the red carpet dressed in high fashion]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahaileyy think bitch u dumb I’ll call u out but ain’t about shit just like 3 years ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Liberty Ball! So happy to be supporting such a great cause! @6abc https://t.co/MymvxMBVXS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn wouldn’t wanna be in downtown #SanDiego right now... lol ❄️ https://t.co/JQ3X7bx2u1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetterEating_ Great news! Hopefully people will know about it. We’ve been feeding our dog home-made vegan food and… https://t.co/ev0XExoJRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CampbellVideos Saddest image I have ever seen!!! They seem more miserable than any #IllegalAlien #ungratfulamerican https://t.co/Iqkkgs2k0I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeBiden @CynthiaNixon I thought you were merely pointing out the international reaction to trump. I got ya!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ln495 Girl me too. I’m surprised I still have black hair. I do need a hair cut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lamar Football players offseason workout is live at #GloryFitness w/ @BIGBUB409 all work no play... @LamarTexansFB… https://t.co/hJOx8CI6tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Next time someone doubts me when I tell them I have a long torso I'm going to show them things Google search bc I c… https://t.co/Rw6Cg4LvVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bcreativ2003 😂 totally. Like quit, blowing up my notifications for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdawsey1 Why are you still calling it a press briefing?  It's just another chance for this administration to lie.… https://t.co/0pIa2yO5Kb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MCHammer I’d say that the story is as old as time and technology was never a barrier because “strangers” were alwa… https://t.co/Wj3stcdpGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandyhadleyx @GavinGr90576041 @piersmorgan His kids aren't even his biological kids. The mom claimed that he never… https://t.co/AVkd9M84hm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shadows #mickysweho #gatorosso https://t.co/HRyQ8FB1tF https://t.co/pYuTBaI00F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RickiLikeLake Wait a broccoli fro sounds super cute especially if the front hits like a bang! I like the updo with a bang look]]></document><document><![CDATA[This music is from the movie Up, right?  I played this in orchestra help]]></document><document><![CDATA[So will My word be which goes forth from My mouth; It will not return to Me empty, Without accom…… https://t.co/k19D6yOItu]]></document><document><![CDATA[highlight of my work day is this grown ass man singing to story of my life by 1D. it was beautiful]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PascoSheriff Yogi! Not now Shep! What do you mean not Now? I can’t explain but something just blew past me! A Leaf… https://t.co/4DECbsGE4p]]></document><document><![CDATA[First day of mercury retrograde and my car already broke down can’t wait for the rest of the month :((]]></document><document><![CDATA[Musetta Seamless Long Sleeve Top w Breathable Moisture-Wicking Fabric by: @fabletics.  . . . Salar Statement Powerh… https://t.co/FYIEiz2FSG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@88_heather_88_5 True but hasn’t it been out too long???? That part doesn’t make sense to me??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @OversightDems Congressman better put seat belts ,because MC going to rock that house..hope he buries Donny.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So disappointing that #FindingYourRoots giving the horrendous and hasbeen #PaulRyan, also the #shiteatingRubio on his excellent show.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hannah has the hardest breakup because there’s no closure. Like how do you move on from “I might be making a mistake”? #TheBachelorFinale]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosHiguera28 Wait for real though we're the same height and he's only got like 8lbs on me, I stand a chance. Ti… https://t.co/GRiz5W5xH2]]></document><document><![CDATA[☀️Good Morning Beautiful Ppl #goodvibes #goodmorning #goodmorninginsta #goodmorningbeautiful… https://t.co/Wbp6eUFr6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WakingLifeDream @RepMattGaetz https://t.co/yTn7pMAeRg https://t.co/BEUM5fy8SE]]></document></documents></author>