<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Jai from customer support is the man!  After going through two other reps with zero results, he got me back in!… https://t.co/xtp18npHVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love playing 2 gigs in one day, except I have to wake up at a decent hour like a normal human.]]></document><document><![CDATA[saving earth day https://t.co/K3W01ud3o8 I PUSHED SNOW ALL NIGHT. . . OH AND ALSO I WAS DRIVING AND A DEER WAS CROS… https://t.co/y5SyErfdXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Revelation 3:1 I am coming soon. Hold fast what you have, so that no one may seize your crown]]></document><document><![CDATA[Over the next few days I’ll be gearing up to start recording all of the tracks on my EP. I always start with record… https://t.co/4ofjhgF3qQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zak_Bagans My first experience w/a clown was at the circus when I was around 4. This freaky looking clown came cha… https://t.co/ovrJtr6Ehi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MittRomney Romney you are a backstabbing POS, how much cartel money did they pay you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At long last, the finale of Disney Afternoon After Dark fireworks! #agoofymovie #goofymovie #gooftroop… https://t.co/2DXnWdMHrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[More gambling is never an answer!  #NotOurValues Committee takes look at sports wagering bill @SenatorJimmy… https://t.co/cfyHpGTErC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's so hard to make it work. Just look at the rest of the developed world. Hasn't worked there. Just ask Blue Cros… https://t.co/wmZ2UgBBLf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Twitter @Design which one of you thought it was a good idea to put a pull to refresh at the BOTTOM of a long scrol… https://t.co/yOZU5Guyfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nicky Lopez (2017 @WilmBlueRocks) picked up a pair of hits to start his spring in the Royals 9-1 win in their Cactus League opener.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilfordFungus @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Dude??? His steaks failed like all other ideas he had!!! https://t.co/vIwpELB1IN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barstoolsports @UncleChaps could you have been any later to this story? “Breaking news” congrats on refreshing Twitter once a month]]></document><document><![CDATA[How come I can sing along with “Summer Girls” by LFO to this day but have to think hard to remember why I opened the fridge?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fresconation He’s gonna fuck it up by trying to overcompensate and not play the open passes.. and clear opportunities]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robkinger91 You're more than welcome.  Had to have our Beagle put to sleep in 2017 because of cancer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hrtablaze What the people say in this tweet thread about the military proves my point that they would like a non m… https://t.co/nyh92cnbf7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I distance myself from those who find a problem for every solution. Life is too short for those loud on noise and s… https://t.co/cO8Al5h6GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetsbyCoachP @realdeal_seals 6’6 160lbs +1 (361) 389-9864 2018 Defensive MVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@martadavies426 I was wondering what that was...thanks but really weird]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating great apps for you https://t.co/pulMfwRGhH https://t.co/Cnrn235I6g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nseguin721 @GirlNamedBoston @zsc4297 IMPROMPTU #FFOT!!!!!! https://t.co/tPJGhNcHDi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@magbulldogs Here is what shows up in the calendar for this week. Will it be updated or was this a generic automate… https://t.co/hzw14GaAA0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Newsweek: White House Is ‘Hiding’ Something About Donald Trump’s Physical Exam, Says Dick Cheney’s Cardiologist.… https://t.co/CDPwDXBQoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Grand Central Market - @grandcentralmkt in Los Angeles, CA https://t.co/pMqxoDOTox]]></document><document><![CDATA[@963bigfm the plural of moose is moose because when you are that big you only need one name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck bro, I need to stop taking naps cause now I’m gonna be up till God knows how long]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump Trump is a Putin puppet and so is McConnell]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HarleyKeiner @MelissainJax I am of a live-and-let-live mindset on these types of things. However, I think there’s… https://t.co/ydng8m6smx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Minco Schools will be in session on Monday.  If your child has no way to school in the morning,  call your child's… https://t.co/eFso2TuEGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Lofton Henderson Memorial Bridge in Lorain, OH https://t.co/yidJIq43X2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheReal_Martin_ Yes sir. Dude even leaves wit his hand over his groin during the time he took my pistol and never… https://t.co/XwqixJbC0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougfun @CNN Dunno about you but i'd rather be a scientist than a snitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anthony Cirelli is one of the first #Bolts on the ice for today’s morning skate. Was the lone Lightning player not… https://t.co/UonrHxxAS8]]></document><document><![CDATA[For any of my followers who are in New York, please go and vote for @NomikiKonst this Tuesday. She's a fire breathi… https://t.co/umgsUaif9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[From last night with these two Lovebirds @kingkidlove and jahise.lebouef  I’ve known Kid for 10 years and still loo… https://t.co/PR3SNHO2Wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was mad very mad last night but I won't let that mess with my day off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Dal Colle was the best player on the ice for the #Isles tonight. That’s saying something based on the entire team’s effort.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Ponte Vedra Beach, Florida https://t.co/CsVhMQCwPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KGertsen @IowaHoops @connor_m30 Not on the show, but in our pre-show discussion. 50/50 chance it could come up on Beyond 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Blonde by Cerveza Urbana @ Las Margaritas — https://t.co/UFmVMqjJ6j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mich_anon @MrJeromeTrammel @TomiLahren @iamcardib So is yours MR. BOT 🤷🏼‍♀️ MichAnon  Report. Block. 🚫 https://t.co/V0fh78kEPZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you think you are going to bond with me or impress me by talking bad about someone you know I have an issue with… https://t.co/Oatkiehy0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vibewithade Prydz took the cake that weekend though.. first time seeing him and omg lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dailybible_app Titus 3:4 - 7 But when the kindness and love of God our Savior appeared, https://t.co/HFfxvemWbM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t work any harder than tons of amazing pros living the @CoSIDAnews life. Blessed to be part of this dedicated f… https://t.co/0A1Avsy3Ru]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost time to announce the championship matches. #pac12wrestle. https://t.co/AXF6nZVERP]]></document><document><![CDATA[14 years of waiting came down to 24 hours, 5 minutes and 54 seconds #KingdomHeartsIII]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner So by your measure Hillary, Bill and Obama need to serve prison time.  Because they all did the same thing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FT @TayTayLLP Ben Bernanke made me fat. His cash for trash swelled my portfolio and I ate a lot of hamberders. https://t.co/YR1T0o1G9Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great weekend with tyler_klutts getting the work done and the deer fed so come October we can have big racked bucks… https://t.co/Xy8oIe46zk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mslizaj @ewarren The US government demands other countries to act responsibly toward their citizens; however, this… https://t.co/aHPvuArt4N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MW55 lets play some golf Saturday. Maybe you can sign one of my diecast cars while we’re at it!😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to all the Train Organizer’s for Adding me i Sincerely appreciate all of you ! IFB so if i have missed adding you please message me !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judy_Cockerton @twizmwhytepiece @Wrix2 @CarolynNewsom @RoyPullin1 @lori_knutson @80MusicGroup @RooferXX… https://t.co/Wi2knDIVVg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Un país así en este momento es capas de cualquier cosa incluso de ir a quemar Miraflores  con todos adentro.......]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters This is what the face of Trump derangement syndrome looks like 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FollowSellers @JavonteeHerndon Exactly. That’s why outside of work and grad school, I started trappin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FixTheMBTAnow @MBTA The blown engine wasn’t an issue worthy of notifying the public about. It was troubleshot. 🤣🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Buck_iBlakely22 The funny thing is you don’t think I’m about some IPA’s lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichEisenShow @richeisen Frosted Flakes - eaten at full speed, before they break down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every time I get sad about my ex I try and remind myself that if he loved me as much as he said he did... he would… https://t.co/BEmlarGyHa]]></document><document><![CDATA[The definition of  coup d'tat. No grounds existed then or now to remove Trump from office on medical or psychologic… https://t.co/YxBUuPFMpt]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring in #EdgecliffVillage, TX! Click the link in our bio to apply to this job and more: Tax Staff - Corpora… https://t.co/XNhkqJw9Ts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom's moving to Nevada for a few months so my apartment is my vacation spot for the weekends until she get back. Mi… https://t.co/C4NQVpNXiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prob the best workout song to ever exist. This shit makes me wanna run trough a wall https://t.co/C6aH1T2jKs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardHarmon23 @sabsterrrrr @ArizonaCoyotes Facts https://t.co/l4ckqgOLRv]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: A memoir unlike any you've read: A young woman's inspiring struggle with her invisible killer: Mal… https://t.co/ELYOnN7MgU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stay on the path...the great victories are on the other side of the greatest struggle. #stayonthepath @ Yakima, Was… https://t.co/9s4N1gF7DP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PKMNTiana Aren't those the ones that are like $50 each right now for whatever reason?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interesting website for comparing all sides of an issue. Great for research and multiple perspectives.… https://t.co/B7qlWJF1js]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hinchas del Barcelona, agredidos en el Bernabéu vía @OnefootballEN. Leer aquí:  https://t.co/K7LZZBuIGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamcarolla  In the history of movies, how many time has this line been said. "Your making a big mistake"]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add a 129 bpm kick and some snares and high hats and your have a 1999 club track. #oldschoolubkid… https://t.co/91u5gLtLrT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@betsports365 @AdamSchefter Aka you’ve got nothing left. Which is surprising, you actually seem like a really intelligent guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck to @ToledoWBB @CoachCullop in their first round MAC Tournament game tonight at Savage arena.  Looking… https://t.co/xHryluxVNM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaupliusTrevor @resing I didn’t look at Jekyll much. But the basics are the same.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bizEducator @PowerLrn @DrBillHunter @MisterRana @aimeelou34 @DrLauraPinto @UOITMEd @OISEUofT @vickiemorgado1 Thank… https://t.co/NtN57EnumX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Los Viñedos Torreon https://t.co/bRCPVT0d5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justininoo @TwitAbuser @BBWslayer666 @ange1dusts tough scenes. i’ve been to arby’s once and i will never do that t… https://t.co/fS0J4timZo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or if you want to Join IBM’s Public Service Salesforce Practice - hit me up!  (Sorry Emily but good press is good p… https://t.co/Q0MGYpgkZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been saying "okay, one more match...." for like an hour. Am I one of those online people now?!?!?! #Tetris99]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Integrity and economic vitality hang in the balance.” Georgia leaders demand Congress fund Hurricane Michael relie… https://t.co/S5nuBvsIxC]]></document><document><![CDATA[It would be more proactive for officers to walk up and down Turk, Eddy, Willow, Ellis, O’Farrell, between Van Ness… https://t.co/zAOK9AJDMS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jacob_Collins27 @Megd714 @alison_janell Conservatives love to feel superior. They get off to starvation wages. The… https://t.co/xH3jx92L2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some politician got paid off here guaranteed. one of his friends made out like a fat cat. shady deal for sure]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZackDavisson @TristanSevers @SPD4649 The answer is always issue #1 with the Chromium cover.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet @dyankane2 @HillaryClinton @StormResist @mcspocky @TheSWPrincess @DanaScottLO @drbashir2018… https://t.co/UW39qsp7v5]]></document><document><![CDATA[It doesn’t change the fact that portions of the discussion showed @SenFeinstein to be acting in an insensitive, dis… https://t.co/hl6gSG3cv7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Their WANTS revolve around Economic Survival, Gun Rights, Religious freedom, elimination of Abortion.… https://t.co/RjuUmQ9iDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Socialist Friends Profits are better than WAGES  Wages lets you pay your Bills Profits can make you  Wealthy Ame… https://t.co/4C4jBYcb0V]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not a Sanders fan but this sandbagging of him by former Clinton staffers is frankly ludicrous and counterproduc… https://t.co/nj9NSPvDDH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#saltilllo #nutriologo en Nutriologo Saltillo: Arturo Meza https://t.co/ya2gQL43Hk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never get over how fucking weird Rashida Jones and Ezra Koenig having a baby is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_KarateChris Spurs won 5 in 17 years...  Warriors gonna have 4 in 5  They're doing it better]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HyperXESALV Tetris is really fun but as a battle royale. Hmmm???🤔🤔🤔 This should be interesting]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kehlani’s new album is a nice move from SweetSexySavage. thank you for blessing my morning 😘🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikelsuave @shxronp @IbrahimJafr @ChiefMangosuthu @BlacksArchive @matigary To be fair, pretty much anything that d… https://t.co/JjLnJLmVKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amazingly, Mattel's new 3.75" Dr. Ian Malcolm has removable glasses! #JurassicPark #JeffGoldblum https://t.co/9fG49FeGUj]]></document></documents></author>