<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[This is the state where that great Democratic Senator Joe Manchin resides. Joe Manchin who never read a Republican… https://t.co/9icfA4LW9F]]></document><document><![CDATA[these things go on in other countries more there than here where they have a strong sense of community @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tried the bacon cheese fries from @McDonalds today. They are not the business. Maybe take a cue from @tacobell on h… https://t.co/V95R1Tqw7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤔 wonder what’s under the red sheet? #Bigmouth maybe? @DeltaDentalCO #dentalhealth https://t.co/t59Zg0dHF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GCHDutta @fghdil @SoniavBahl @AnupmaMichael @IamSunitha777 @HarbirSinghSuri @SsanjayTaannk @greatairi… https://t.co/4ea44YwjPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mundian to Bach Ke came on at the bar and the desis lost their damn minds @mank06 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the ability to make good decisions and I just fucking choose not to???????????]]></document><document><![CDATA[The chances of you being born is 1 in 400 trillion, you’ve already won and this is your victory lap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asked Neal to take me to Marshall’s before the snow gets bad and he said okay but you are NOT getting another candle.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo Why do you never talk about things other then POTUS? So much news out there but @CNN And you and your c… https://t.co/MdVJZSj3Ma]]></document><document><![CDATA[Having a little fun w our staff picture @WilsonAISD #WEdreambig https://t.co/tCp9Fv7Ces]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confirmed on scene: the bus had Brook Hill students on board. @kytxcbs19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenJackyRosen Thank you Senator for taking the time to meet with us and learn more about what all our organization… https://t.co/7fyKWwLTjn]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are working hard in our privates. Well done Gracie ✅🌷 #ballet#barbaravallesclass #barbaravalles#privates#trainin… https://t.co/Yrsp3GuKxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods It’s like handing your checkbooks over to someone in an insane asylum]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @colbertlateshow when I remembered “that one time I met Colin Quinn” #Chicago 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChenZhen @AlisonDunn13 @jiveDurkey Think of his tacky gold plated ugly apartment in NY.]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone else remember when the chambrigals were in venice taking pics in our tuxes and dresses and a bunch of touris… https://t.co/wlIoIpNgk9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jvineyard2011 @itsJeffTiedrich @realDonaldTrump Classy?....dresses nice, great makeup, class is not something hid,… https://t.co/GxwGFwwjbl]]></document><document><![CDATA[From shoppersdrugmartofficial a Power Bank - 2hr to charge - portable usb for phone etc. @ Mississauga, Ontario https://t.co/WMcG7B4dyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AskChefDennis @SouthwestAir @SouthernerSays @mora_jaymie @MiaVossOnTheGo @suziday123 @RoadtripC @halekoahotel… https://t.co/4Ys0ez5JTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lkirdani1 @SandiaWisdom God you must think I’m a goof!! Of course you are sweet friend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SabresFunStats @Jack_WanderS @MsAFromBK @lno09281978 @SabreKevin1639 @DragonMom98 @TerryBdattd @TheNotriousBob… https://t.co/qmqtBPVWsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #SkyClub is located at 📍700 1st Street in #Hoboken, New Jersey. The building consists of two 17 story residenti… https://t.co/ohTrkaCXN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cover of this new MARVEL TALES is gorgeous. Match it with the @Loungefly_ purse and wallet. You've hit a home r… https://t.co/WQH6GRBHnU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m ready to tailgate, be with friends,drink lots of beer and cheer on the freaking union again tomorrow 🐍⚽️💙 #DOOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO happy for all of my friends who break up with shitty boys who made them sad and are now with boys who treat them… https://t.co/Z7ApSn95fX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcbu2018 Since elementary school. My friends and I split up the planets and wrote our first stories about the worl… https://t.co/epVJcZjlWr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gbUSMC @frankgasaway @NikkiHaley @JohnBrennan Brennan was never a DoJ head and he is now a private citizen who has… https://t.co/Xgrdm7DrzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best dressed my a**.... They were downright hideous! #Oscarfail https://t.co/UxKKs5a8mw]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you want to see more of AOC WATCH HER ON ALEXANDRIA OCASIO CORTEZ POT SMOKING SEX TAPE @WWW. Pornhub. Com. View… https://t.co/5EYIMASE9d]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acrylic Nails with color gel and designs. Book your appointment with booksy or call at 201 4281550. @ Genesis Hair… https://t.co/gefBrMRZyp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sorry for the glare.. And yes that is a Wii and a snes classic you see. https://t.co/4CQCJZDB6c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah.. I wasn’t able to fall asleep the whole fucking night until now. And I have work at 8am. So I need to get off… https://t.co/WChzTcYQT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dutch is studying for his next career @ Norfolk, Virginia https://t.co/Oiwky6HyeF]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s from NY. He’s treating it like NYHC. You know Freddie Madball, Rick ta Life, Tim Apple....]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand why people park RIGHT NEXT TO YOU when there’s a million other parking spaces]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HouseHunter216 @KimKardashian I know a lot of people will say she is in more “privileged” situation but she’s defi… https://t.co/zLOl60t5lq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Awww right back at you @cinehead! It’s been too long since I’ve seen you! I won’t be in Anaheim so maybe we can cat… https://t.co/Qkp1QDkGyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelH872 @punkspeced Yes, it's called letting go of the magic wand (even if you didn't want it soley in your han… https://t.co/UrwdLHwTZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t see them having white children act out a time when white needed us to reach them how to bathe cook and clean]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning!! Happy Saturday!!  Overslept on this chilly Saturday. But got up just in time for the Community Calen… https://t.co/fXF4neXd3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hearing @petersagal say “Fuck it” on Lovett or Leave it has fulfilled this little npr-is-the-only-thing-Mom-let-us-listen-to girl’s dreams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Luke Bryan - Drink A Beer (Official Music Video) https://t.co/hVmFVp75oy via @YouTube.    Every time I hear this I… https://t.co/Fg4hT6NNJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[the wind in Bethesda was exactly the same as it was in this One Bite Everybody Knows the Rules segment from this mo… https://t.co/RBs2GjNrRn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy crap @CodySimpson you are exceeding my expectations Anastasia on broadway. I see a bright acting career in your future 🤩✨🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interview, First-year, Junior-year, Senior-year! Thank you @ElonEdFellows for making my 4 yrs at @elonuniversity ev… https://t.co/Qf6ijUoj9i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will get super in my feelings about something and then God will remind me He got this!  #DontEvenTrip 😁 #crybaby… https://t.co/cQbt0Oz7KC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring the 9 Areas of Learning within Phonics, Spelling, and Word Study with @PETigers, @MaplewoodElem,… https://t.co/dtxzY8WvTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[my life is a shit show right now so please ignore all depressed sad bitching tweets for the next 24 hours. i should be good then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trump2S2G2T @mmpadellan @realDonaldTrump @JussieSmollett Really? Ok let’s start w 5000 in PR by sheer neglect bc h… https://t.co/xcT40n5lRK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to be celebrating #IWD2019 at @mcdonalscorp at MHQ today! #balanceforbetter #mcdemployee (@ McDonald’s HQ -… https://t.co/a2vuJxbiuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@High_and_Inside @janelle_2310 That’s literally the only reason I agreed to do it tonight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @talkavino @masi3v @Stefschwalb @JvBUncorked @foodwineclick @martindredmond @winetraveleats… https://t.co/8gcrW058Md]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marinavibu609g @akomama_tm @LindaLeeKing @PatGrant7777 @fahadma45457790 @yukio_nemoto @EliLeonarda… https://t.co/IXHI91OoaA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LorettaLMart VOTING IS OPEN AGAIN!!! VOTE FOR @RandyHouser LETS DO THIS!!! YOU CAN VOTE ON FACEBOOK TOO!!! 🎤🎶🥃🔥 LI… https://t.co/f6tmaNRlc9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenny_mcgown @amyemiller1473 @WynneLaToya @MonShall2 @TrevorWoolley77 @hollytmason @kb_kcoyotes @cadproctor… https://t.co/ME6An6xhSi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ladies! Let’s do this!!! @Ehmee @SiobhanLeachman help me spread the word?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Write your reps! Support the Bipartisan Background Checks Act of 2019 (H.R.8) https://t.co/l45QoVrRev @IndivSeguin… https://t.co/JIL1IZ3uxi]]></document><document><![CDATA[From #yourfavoritedriver #ValentinesDay  #itsmysunday https://t.co/4PlU23hpq0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YourTaylorFarms I gotta ask? Do those wooden spoons come along too!?🙃🙃 I'm ready to eat my veggies #NationalAgWeek  #GoToGreens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mamawrenn @realDonaldTrump Are you jealous you don’t pay play golf. That’s his relaxation. What’s yours?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t understand what is wrong with people?! Even after experiencing all of this, the poor child is still unvacci… https://t.co/vwlHY8jd31]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cheyanne_Skye normally I said 'you’re canceled' but I’m not opposed to switching it up a bit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoItToJulia5 @ABRadFems @TeelaWild @MorganeOgerBC @preta_6 @FeministCurrent Is what personal? Observing someone’s… https://t.co/exdMMuBlV0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't think you can move a mountain. They're stuck in the ground. #kidsdom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LisaRago1 @MarioLopezExtra I think ISIS sucked her brain out! She’s still dressing like them yet wants to come back? Oh, okay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Homeschool Days (Colonial Williamsburg) https://t.co/m6OrV1DhWr via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[They’re in a library, on the floor, cuddling and he’s reading to her. What is this!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#relayforlife #sponsored #chosen #healthcare #surprise #youcandoit  #sohappy @ New Albany, Indiana https://t.co/84wVcECF3f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emtothea You do the same!  Thanks so much for bringing this shitshow into our lives!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MensReaPod @HauntedRide @PWLTpodcast @truecrimeisland @DCSuperSons @PenanceRPG @MythicalPodcast https://t.co/iDcK6Ia7Wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveScalise @NRA @IngrahamAngle @FoxNews Ridiculous. #HR8 might have kept guns out of the hands of the mentally u… https://t.co/E3qTleGvf8]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how you know it was a good #TRX class! LOL! Join us every Friday 6am on the edge!! trxtraining bayclubs xtr… https://t.co/80dxloeWrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇨🇴en donde la hierva crece y x ella la gente perece en donde ser pillo paga: quiénes se robaron la salud y comida d… https://t.co/eLbrMZd20R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two things to celebrate!  It's the weekend and it's #NationalMargaritaDay. Not only does #JenniferAniston have perf… https://t.co/WeZkyGw9es]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMeanChick @scottkfoley @WhiskeyCav Look what I found today! #timessquare https://t.co/NJqpbHDHQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvanDuque Sr presidente olvídese del circo diplomático aquí lo único que ellos entienden es la fuerza y usted tien… https://t.co/Fjdfa6dQTm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Where is Mitch #mitchmustgo #TrumpCrimeFamily #TrumpRussiaCoverUp]]></document><document><![CDATA[6 months ago. The day before climbing Mt. Kilimanjaro #justagirlfromjaneandfinch #yourfavoritedriver… https://t.co/Q1DK2VNdO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖Con Sue Photography and Design💋  💝Like our photos...Follow our IG 💖  ❤️This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/spRG41Z2Vd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shakestweetz I believe as bad as these things are he has done much worse. He's downplaying Russian crimes. But the… https://t.co/ng42lBknIw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy DALENTINES DAY I’m sorry lol I had to do it. Happy birthday you beautiful queen!! 🥰@_dallasesguerra]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cnnbrk Didn't we establish he wasn't Atlanta based? Like thats the whole point! I hope things work out though]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmanuelEfunbote @marklevinshow Too bad there is no evidence, suck that up for a while.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @ThisIsRobThomas perfect timing as I celebrate my 60th trip around the sun]]></document><document><![CDATA[Give the President 5.7 billion so that he can safeguard America and her citizens...its obvious the the political de… https://t.co/RAP3jgRE5b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidHaydnJones @SophieNPieters Ok but I really wanna see Knight Davey now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look who came to visit for the week!  #daisy @ Arizona https://t.co/QbdK3jLs7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t eaten in over 24 hrs. But I just made myself the most bomb pizza everrrrrrr. 🤤🤤🤤 Ready to eat it 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend, Syd: my eye sockets feel really heavy Me, a creep: maybe you should take your eyes out of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting for a truck.... And people watching.... #comfychair #mysisterisbetterthanyours #discountuniverse @ Danville… https://t.co/ufeMV6uoO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Using @EpicKidsBooks to compare different versions of The Three Little Pigs. It's all about POV and Perspective!… https://t.co/FfRTCenBap]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarrySabato @NBCNews It's all so monstrous. This picture...breaks my heart and I can't imagine being his parents s… https://t.co/m1295Ksl8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[Comp weekends are my favorite because my eyelashes are longer than my will to live]]></document><document><![CDATA[#flashbackfriday  Massive gratitude for this guy to share this lifetime with him.  We all need that rock of support… https://t.co/egc4Bod19p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikeinthevalley @richardzussman @GlobalBC @KahlonRav Ravi himself is in favour of ride sharing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ZerlinaMaxwell Her job is wearing her June Cleaver pearls and spewing Trumps Fake Facts. She needs to be looking for a new job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tvseriespolls_ The healthy relationship that should be cannon!!! They protecc &amp; attacc!!! ❤️👍👏 https://t.co/HUn7VhYtJB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hitmanhedge .A 'good adult relationship' means different things to different people. There are many different kind… https://t.co/E6QCsiY9gu]]></document></documents></author>