<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@gregwhitworth I still remember a Chrome dev telling me 5ish years ago that handling scrolling off the UI thread was “impossible”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FrankTieri has been one of my best friends for nearly a quarter of a century. I’ve admired first hand his talent,… https://t.co/Fph41zGoKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[With a new job set up in mid March, I can for the first time in months take a break.  No more phone calls from recr… https://t.co/jNEePA8OJh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond Oh, good grief! Does no one pay attetion to science fiction novels anymore? They predict a lot of this stuff.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@42Gnome @L_a_w_a_n_n_a @hardhouz13 @Steelerschic85 @CunningSq16 @pam_brundige @bfosterls7 @jhgurf @jawofsteel2014… https://t.co/8ikIcmcM1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soo the @buffalobills are in on Antonio Brown!? Close to a deal. say whut?? I mean, cmon. This is BIG #billsmafia… https://t.co/dE7wiVfAWo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJonAbramson @fk_eduardo @FutbolProfessor @reesetheone1 @EricUhm @tomwatson Brazilian Lula fuckstain knows all ab… https://t.co/n0MfHP9uLu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angcould @pervy_lady @we_r_Psymese @Bowman03Troy @JaiNoelle01 @MariaGivesHugs @Kirkinky @MtRahas @DeviantMl… https://t.co/udMVz3ml3j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Phone case is needed... I’m scared to even pull my phone out outside of the house 😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richeisen @RichEisenShow @chrisbrockman @MichaelDelTufo @kirkmorrison https://t.co/ssa35y33kY]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is like when someone dies and they're always "such a great person. Kind to and loved by everyone". No, they pr… https://t.co/ZpFgLbzWQQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ajw545 @Tfarmandranch Oh maybe an ole Melroe harrow to break up the extra residue. Real safe, Clark! 🚑😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The true meaning of life is to plant trees, under whose shade you do not expect to sit....” Wish I could’ve been o… https://t.co/8yvb5gX8Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JutsuCosplay 2 buildings away? Tightrope walk 2x https://t.co/UR3U3baha0]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s been a busy weekend for @robertwickens @gpstpete but every time I’ve seen him he has a smile on his face. https://t.co/qaqo0Hs6uS]]></document><document><![CDATA[You only feel lost because you haven't decided what you really want. You're scared to make the wrong decision, but… https://t.co/Bat13t6eGV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 Imagine using the word "coup" correctly. 👍  #45 needs to be removed ASAP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanfordBSB @E_Rex23 K is an inside ⚾️ baseball term for strikeout - Here are nine examples   https://t.co/YPDr8L5BNh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsSturm @NotJackKemp my 4 elementary kids appreciated the Momo report. They were a little worried @bracketdan]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn I spend 2 hours playing Fortnite with Destanie and we never got a win....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to see @JimmieJohnson running top-5...last time he finished top-5 when he finished 5th in the Coca-Cola 600 l… https://t.co/R2cmbfBs4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laraeparker Oooh are you on season 1? There is a super insane scene with them later in the season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TimBarker @TobiHaslett They are all connected by having no idea how to pair jeans and sneakers, they're all rolling like Jerry Seinfelds]]></document><document><![CDATA[This job might be a great fit for you: RN Case Manager-Telehealth - https://t.co/hmo222N7WX #Nurse #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therichturpin The Skins decision depends on Alex Smith.  If they think he will play in 2020 they should pick QB in… https://t.co/IpD8ID6Nnw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jr. Jays excellence at its finest - congratulations brother - i’ll see you up in jumbotrons soon 💪🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SmockingScott Steve Irwin encouraged irresponsible behavior toward wild animals. At whatever tavern animals gather… https://t.co/s19l3zctAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[#IntervencionMilitarInternacionalYa | @NicolasMaduro FIRMASTE TU SENTENCIA DE MUERTE! ¡Asesino MALDITO!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#DiaMundialDeLaEficienciaEnergetica  #GeneracionDistribuida La elección del #UsuarioGenerador para tu energía eléct… https://t.co/tDWviQr1se]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pedroferriz3 Al menos AMLO es el presídete De los Mexicanos...... y tu quien eres nadie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BWH85 Baseball projections and expected stats. That's what really matters Lance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga: He tore my clothes right off, he Me: ATE MY HEART AND THEN HE ATE MY BRAINSSSSSSS https://t.co/L1npBpmXpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jneeley78 I took a class on the history of the CIA. Our prof explained that most conspiracy theories are based on… https://t.co/CsRIcDcc9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDanB95 @washingtonpost @Israel @GOP Why would Israel want Saudi to have nukes? https://t.co/DreM5nHqbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost there!  Hoping for a strong finish for this small painting of a funfactoryusa Wicked Wings vibe for… https://t.co/XHRJpAzzvY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyUva44 @NHLBruins We’ll beat Toronto and lose to Tampa in the 2nd round again. Seems like more of a push to sel… https://t.co/Pf28v8jm1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have waited my entire life to see Anthony Johnson knock Jones out.  Please Santa, all i want for XMas is Jones vs… https://t.co/5r3hWUgA1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Repp. Gohmert needs to take it one more step. Suspended all existing court dates on immigrants.  Spend all the immi… https://t.co/JSddGsaLin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewkimmel And having sex with a child under the age of 18 is rape? When? Only when it suits people???? Wow how… https://t.co/LExgtXBYLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a wonderful weekend in DC. Met with a lot of faculty and admins and discussed future areas of collaboration aft… https://t.co/HwFyl65i7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Short take on the Graves Situation:  Messed up for the family.  Graves standards are a bit low (Have you seen Carme… https://t.co/fss7Gji520]]></document><document><![CDATA[according to the homeless man at the QT down the road who doesn’t have a phone but asked for my number anyways, i a… https://t.co/MWOYm8okL2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The caption 😭😭😭 real shit fho! I would of thought I was going to heaven.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught the Lights v Rapids preseason game on a cool Vegas winter day! https://t.co/rMg8YSUHRM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@szn_lakers @champagnennuts Wrong! Their issues were not on that side of the ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honour of family day, I will kiss my dad on the lips.  But first, I must find my dad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He is being totally played Kim only wants Individual 1 to beleive he might de-Nuk but only really needs sancti… https://t.co/tSqaODFlHj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jfk_annie @RWPUSA The video of the boys sexually harassing the girl a few minutes before should be fun cross examination evidence too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ACLU How is it healthcare. Just repeating it doesn't make it so. So if the unborn baby is female does she have a r… https://t.co/DmtcuIOYV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yourboytobias @obj @buffalobills Yeah but thats not how you build franchises, you gotta draft well man thats the n… https://t.co/gj7ky91cZV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ronmadison303 Because it was cold in the hallway? Maybe they had karaoke keyed up and someone had a rocking versio… https://t.co/pFLcMpXDqh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theresvtrvn @Troy_Do @tletamz this is where i take my leave https://t.co/r86wGI85SK]]></document><document><![CDATA[UK clarifies a couple of those notes from last night’s win over Tennessee...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cdngolftraveler @NorthBerwick_GC Love course reviews. Despise course rankings.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Don’t Know Who ELSE Needs To Hear 👂🏾 This, 🗣 Keep Going....In Spite Of...Fall 7 Times Get Back Up 8....In Spite O… https://t.co/YLZVEI3ohI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miley: "I like to think common sense prevailed in many respects." "There are about 10 to 15 Republicans who can go… https://t.co/WGKzma385f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottOlling @AveKathleen @matt_weiser Maybe twice that wide, but I doubt that presents much of an engineering obst… https://t.co/1aqYmxJ4uU]]></document><document><![CDATA[2017 488 Spider 🕷 #ferrari #488 #Spider #kevsevauto #cow @ Chevrolet of Wooster https://t.co/oV7du4spp6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinskyleigh Jesus is about to push Trump into the sea. He can be sneaky that way. It may happen next week. . .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve Worked SO HARD to become Champion 🙌🏽 Placed 5th last year as a freshman and came back this year On Top 🥇 HUNGR… https://t.co/sSIdL1ws2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MyDaughtersArmy Greg, are you pretending to be stupid or is it real?  Trump knows the truth about the Otto tragic… https://t.co/684AQThtYR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frank_seravalli @JustinTrudeau TSN tainted now cause of that loser joining them @TSNBobMcKenzie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik @RubyRiottWWE @YaOnlyLivvOnce @sarahloganwwe Sweet ruby root has some wonderful lips.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 days!!! ♠️💙💜🖤😆😇🥳🤩 @AustinMcbroom @CatherinePaiz @hogan_tamieka @MiekaNJay061718]]></document><document><![CDATA[#AnnDemeulemeester #PFW #Fall2019 #FavoriteLooks anndemeulemeester_official @ Phoenix, Arizona https://t.co/CuTho8bptC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SedatedJane @MigBaird @NBCNews @KenDilanianNBC Wow. You should try to keep your crazy a little more hidden...]]></document><document><![CDATA[What does it mean to have courage? How can we be more courageous in our daily life?  If we take stock in ourselves… https://t.co/S1Kfr1sV1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MRosenberg21 @Josh_Macri @Buster_ESPN @dschoenfield @esotericeric0 Was just kidding. Lol. There are million choice… https://t.co/RuoS03jVCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[If someone call my daughter a bitch she don’t even gotta do allat her big brother gon crush him. I respect this gir… https://t.co/OtrO8kwbFU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BhavishaPatel @tslauson @RobinDich @ecwangg @BrandiKruse @EllenTailor @AlexLewisTV @dickinsonliv @JohnHopperstad… https://t.co/FaWBSW7579]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keileykaiser I'm curious about that as well. I just upload my review for it if you want to check it out 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I was playing a game against someone I like, I wouldn’t let you win, because I hate losing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So true. Ralph Nader was the hat year’s Jill Stein. Imagine where we’d be without these “radicals” who hand us the… https://t.co/ifaqYIDKhD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@laurafwild @Cjw6187 Tell the legend I said hello and hope alls well with the family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TSNBobMcKenzie Could this mean...🅿️anarin???? 👀 https://t.co/OfaJoUYGch]]></document><document><![CDATA[ASAP❗️💙 @disney pixar @FATRAT30 ©®️™️ @ Oakland, California https://t.co/50MCQBtkJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Sunday special: Delsea coach Tom Freeman sets example in face of cancer fight https://t.co/A7GTVxdNxg via @phillydotcom]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Emergency? No wall (which is NOT under construction) will save America from the real threat of thi… https://t.co/PdoZEXnSh6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best wrong number ever, and as they say, when Liechtenstein calls, you better answer. It was a guy shouting in what… https://t.co/TXtdoIxzin]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the cashier start yelling about your card being declined https://t.co/NRsXmdFsCR]]></document><document><![CDATA[how many fucking times is that right overhand gonna catch cody??? so one dimensional]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elitomac oh hw we like the motocross style tracks. Smokin run at Daytona.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealTimBooth Ha! James @ottawabluesfest !! Close to Montreal! I sense a little little tour of festivals of somethi… https://t.co/nEuTsJYGTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pensfannc5 @44_rem_mag Here too!   GOT CABIN FEVER!  Three weeks til spring!  Shoot sum ground hogs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhotoHazard A lot of academies offer scholarships now (like CHL). That’s the way things are moving]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Time to call in The A-Team I love it when a good plan comes together keep up the good work President Trump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Varneyco Americans For Prosperity is being short sighted on trade and tariffs. The President is playing the long game on trade.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching videos of people get there back adjusted on Facebook hoping through osmosis this back pain will go away.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sorry Traitor Don but you are a disgrace! McCabe worked for our country with honor until a POS TRA… https://t.co/rVpS3NX46t]]></document><document><![CDATA[#shameless⁠ ⁠ Do y’all remember what happened last time Lip Gallagher thought he got a girl pregnant https://t.co/p2GAvNLhpj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Or do it like hockey. Fan penalty box by the concession stands...two minute minor, 5 minute major, game misconduct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GerryCallahan I just shoveled the driveway this morning... I tell my “better half” to park at the end of the drive… https://t.co/KDm7JpRX9b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PGalbraithUSTA @RajeevRam when are you publishing the list of number of players playing and registered since you a… https://t.co/ju4K5lXZpl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carry me @EliteBeardedTV  - - #dubs #duo #fortnite #kills https://t.co/9GirV6Ob2D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HappyDeathDay2U was pretty good. They tried to fit too much in I think, which made the story a little hard to foll… https://t.co/7BKY4kHSjG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bov_chris @MostBiglyMaga @TheTruth1011 @captain_crapper @Twestytwesty @TeaPartyOne1 @QbertCobain @MAGAJesusJTrump… https://t.co/sw3mjIrKET]]></document><document><![CDATA[The starting 5!  @madds_12  @SummerStoewer  @kathy_pinnock  @Abby24Coates  @MarquittaEasley   #StrongerTogether https://t.co/7IxfairB0a]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all my friends with other agency’s...please be careful responding today..remember your life also matters💛]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heilharvesting Ducked up this hay deal is what happened. Heard there is a new one going in south of Sunray.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radhamesjimenez Así es compañero @radhamesjimenez desde el @PrimerVa @SEconLeonel2020 @PLDenlinea ya estamos prepa… https://t.co/q2czRoBXfu]]></document></documents></author>