<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@MeatSauce1 would you rock this @Twins 1987 corduroy ballcap?!?! https://t.co/JfVmp5D1o3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elizaskinner I did not know that Richmond even had a zoo until years after I had moved away. It’s way out in Chest… https://t.co/0ckIqbehZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CIA now it's time the CIA works on having people integrity like tha wakandan's because just having neat shit with… https://t.co/J5p8EQalGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @AOC were a cartoon character her catchphrase would be, "The power of emptyskull!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[For crying out loud. Stop supporting homosexuality as if it is something that is good and should be promoted! Homos… https://t.co/HXDAXeCtUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao. That is legit the dumbest thing I've ever seen the Bengals do. Think about that statement... and you'll under… https://t.co/elyn1XeDPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contact private label #clothing #manufacturers to start your clothing business as there are more advantages in part… https://t.co/1gw70u905m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews I think you would be surprised about how little people care about him. What surprises me is why lemo… https://t.co/svhRvr9JIM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beckyquick #cnbc   Good job trying to hold Meeks accountable, since follow up #samzell 😁😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oneshiningpod @clubtrillion @tatefrazier Just joined the OSP crowd this year so dunno if this was discussed, but d… https://t.co/uHY8lsZ5r4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/yxysdAWVDp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamdarby Didn't that American 'chick' say that the only Emergency  was "A PRESIDENT who is an Idiot"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaepernick7🏈 raiders @FATRAT30 ©®️™️ @ Oakland, California https://t.co/oTqurH25qR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jon_greenberg And the @GenoEspn books, Cubs Nation. You two should write a script. Is Denzel available to play Dusty?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just feel like the ball is jumping off of my bat. I'm feeling really good: @Burgatron13 talks to… https://t.co/rn6XG8qDQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shoutout to those people in Wisconsin that wished us safe travels back to Louisiana! We couldn't have made it without you guys🧀🥳]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol why are y’all making a big deal out of tamera drinking her sister breast milk? It’s supposed to be really good… https://t.co/ohVmJa2xwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then they’ll say calmly, “We can do this easy way or the hard my bitch Michael Cohen. Make’s no difference to me!”… https://t.co/MWP1dlBIiL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oregon turned magical over night. Taking bobsled team applications. https://t.co/Y73dME44cm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roberto. #timeoutnewyork #nycactor #nyccastingcall #nyccasting #actor #actorslife #actormexicano #fashionista @ Wor… https://t.co/w3OMDKrrki]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canceled Open House!  2306 Touhy unit 201 do to weather!!!❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️❄️  #Openhouse #FirstTimeHomeBuyer… https://t.co/gLU30OgJ4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kirpa getting all defensive to Cassie about what she told Colton. Yet she was telling him about Cassie and Caelynn… https://t.co/7sjeYwHLvU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VassyKapelos Canadians deserve to know the truth. https://t.co/tb44uvUZm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AriMelber Apparently, Judge #TSEllis does not consider "White Collar" crimes, "real crimes" and #Manafort, like… https://t.co/LE7u4nTVqL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of the best people in the business! Make sure you check is our this weekend! #theheights #bxwest]]></document><document><![CDATA[Suspending the Health Insurance Tax (HIT) for 2020 is the most direct way for #Congress to provide financial relief… https://t.co/naUVLGuDPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a script I get to read for class. Very action oriented. Very cool stuff. https://t.co/9bOfwZyQye]]></document><document><![CDATA[Contento por conocer al #actor #cubanoamericano @robertoescobarX esta noche en la Galería Art Emporium de la… https://t.co/MHvXapZgWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill @realDonaldTrump and the #GOP are walking national security risks, national emergencies, and national disg… https://t.co/spOLKsoQbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[how thee fuck do girls casually take their nose rings in &amp; out whenever they want?? mine closes up &amp; heals in 20 mins]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BradleyBaseball @NCAACWS @d1baseball @MVCsports @BaseballAmerica @aaronfitt @KP_Omaha @ShaneDennis34]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigDaddyGraham the amount harper makes affects the whole team because what is everybody else gonna make if he is n… https://t.co/URAtBtLRS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben1Pappas I built a landscape company to over 100 employees and was never a landscaper.bought an IT company and w… https://t.co/66Aa4GffiT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Edurodriguezg Buenos días Eduardo! Mi familia en Maracaibo me informa que la situación va de crítica a desesperant… https://t.co/0EGqVtGAkY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Metro_PR La resilencia no es hacer relaciones públicas. Es levantarse día a día y lichar por el bienestar de los s… https://t.co/XFZzlPzVaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[More LIVE @Cubs #SpringTraining coverage from Arizona. We go 1-on-1 with the boss Theo Epstein. See this rare inter… https://t.co/8Nwj4DAZFP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grant writing is fun. You become the most vulnerable person to beg for $$$ just to prove you can write a paper,, an… https://t.co/6T1sNcx45r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats to @RheumResearch ! Our specialty and patients are so lucky to have you]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll just say this in denfence of Carey Price: Dryden had 3 Hall of Fame defencemen in front of him, Roy had 2 HOF… https://t.co/kOtCjxWzIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StuartBrown58 Nice fact sheet on your incredible credentials on page 22 of the  Tankard Times !  ---&gt;… https://t.co/8WXxl78VpG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you get done working all day, it's time to live like a Captain. #diageorep #captainmorgan… https://t.co/Wimpz1qhQn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rhythmgoddesss @TheAuracl3 Yeah. I refuse to pay that much attention to them, but, yeah.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews KILL YOUR NEWBORN BABY! (Vote Democrat in 2020!) https://t.co/fndgYeXgBU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewsHour @KrisKobach1787 Why was he even on? What’s his expertise to discuss border security? Did he build walls a… https://t.co/eI5BnpxbOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarlosAdelValle @InvictosSomos @CH14_ Espectacular!! Notable! De lo mejor del mundo mundial..!! LA HORA DE CHICHARITO  JAJAJAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UNLVRebelGrl They are the best team in the MWC but that’s because the conference isn’t good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New Episode Alert 🚨 Episode 135 is LIVE (Direct Link in the Bio) #podsincolor #podernfamily #podcast #podsbyqpoc… https://t.co/D6wPYJWWLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is just bad low tier journalism i would expect from this “news” outlet. Misleading people is NOT a story. It’s… https://t.co/opKdpgQupE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xGabrielPhoenix Aww you're very welcome 😊 😘 and oh got the book marker yesterday https://t.co/DzU3nuLotD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandymH @realDonaldTrump @GovIvey It’s ALWAYS about him. Classic narcissism. He’s a pathetic and embarrassing blight.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I still look and feel young. I kinda figured I wouldn't by now. I don't know where I was going with this. Life is surreal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure one of the scenes I put on tape today was one of the best performances I’ve ever given]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron8News @VCU_Hoops @8NEWS Yaaaaaas bring it on home to Brooklyn!! 🙌🏽🐏 🐏 #GoRams]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Billy Club Pale Ale by @badhabitbeer @ Bad Habit Brewing Company — https://t.co/fS4Hp8VylQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really tired of waking up before sunrise. But I’m stubborn so I’d appreciate it if the sun would change its sle… https://t.co/kYMWF4IOzS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We started with dark leaf for our What Else exclusive, and after a short waiting period we’re happy to bring you th… https://t.co/W8S0nvIFgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The WHY is the purpose, cause or belief the drives every one of us . https://t.co/IGyFYPTt6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BilboWompins @strawburrysoup I'm visiting u on day 741 and blessing you with gifts and hopefully bringing some homies with me to celebrate]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Red light treatment. It was awesome. Gonna do more research on it. #redlighttherapy @ Planet Fitness https://t.co/R9eqnq0Ewl]]></document><document><![CDATA[내일 월요일 출근이고 나 빨리 자야되는데 마시던 맥주가 반 정도 남아 꾸역꾸역 애플뮤직 틀었는데 완전 클래식한 린 음악들 (내가 어렸을 때 오백만번 듣던) 나오면서 너무 감성터지네 xxx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeepSmashed @xladventures @Only1_Adore How can I be apart of one 🙋🏽‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBarbosaMX @MorenaEnPuebla @JavierLopezDiaz @JCarlos_Valerio @FerCanalesF @AristeguiOnline @carlosmartinh… https://t.co/nPX3A0G4l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@existentialfish Hey @JudgeJeanine I agree they hate the Constitution. https://t.co/hsszzmkFf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyonseed @jerodmcdaniel Binary thinking stops progress on this. One extreme wants to halt all economic activity, t… https://t.co/6HjhtvOJpq]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@KendallJenner⁩ ✨❤️💎😉💗💍😘🙏🏻😂☀️😇🙌🏻😍💕✊🏻🤣😎👦👋🏻👎🏻👑🔥😆😊👌🏻🔑🚶☺️⚽️💙 https://t.co/BoTV2ccZPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking through old photo folders and found this shot taken during the filming of my #ShortFilm, Parallel.… https://t.co/cATt0kYF62]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alex_Davis_ 13 years 330 million HOLY GOD we should have done more push ups when we played at CO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised here. @AGBecerra has promised other families he’d look into egregious police use of force cases, only… https://t.co/boGxZqpVvW]]></document><document><![CDATA[As a runner I have admired this winter of 2018/19 for its slow and steady opening, followed by an incredible sustai… https://t.co/RaeGx4U4Dy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beansterrrr @toritrice04 Sorry who are you? And who was talking trash in the original tweet? Are you illiterate?😕]]></document><document><![CDATA[Strach says the records may have intermingled forms tracking ABM request forms and voter registration forms that we… https://t.co/pRWtYWDNuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Couscous for breakfast with spam and eggs. 😅 something different and even got @instantramain to try it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump That makes no sense.  What do you do when you don’t like someone?  Send them flowers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @gatewaypundit Lock Cortez up for Life without parole. She's been Laundering Money for years so it's abou… https://t.co/q5xKeVpUil]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BlueFox #MensFur #SnowStyle #SnowFashion #NYFW #NewYorkFashionWeek #Fashionista #Fashionable  #MensFashion… https://t.co/CBdEN0cv9A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LittleMissAngr1 Afterwards, do you feel guilty about putting them away?😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arkwxwatchers @sgrimmett6 @jacobdickeywx So much has to come together for perfection. Still — a successful chase t… https://t.co/3U1u1XduVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This Kentuckian does not support #HB136 and I hope it doesn’t make it out of committee, but if it does make it to t… https://t.co/EJ8sWCxNy7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dave Hamer completed the RnR Washington DC Half Marathon! Time 02:06:37 (UNOFFICIAL) https://t.co/rNuyEm4uBz #RNRDC]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s not enough of a selling point to justify the years of delay for a game that should literally have launched w… https://t.co/Yx1Hzf85zP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love seeing passenger rail advocates rallying for funding. USA is maybe too big for a nationwide rail expansion.… https://t.co/tgbNHaSZYj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SocietalCanary @brandonmccall8 @KocherNoah @TradeGainz @SwampRob @nowthisnews Who do you think the bad guys are  g… https://t.co/AnHZjvhdbA]]></document><document><![CDATA[People forget just how insane the Pierce Brosnan Bond was. Dude rode through an oil pipeline and disarmed a nuclear… https://t.co/TIHfVaLfTS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MonsterGirlMonday shoutout to my favorite monster girl @AshWilke 💚👩🏼👱🏻‍♀️🖤 https://t.co/wS3T4zH7HN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acts as if he’s on meth cuz I’ve seen meth heads! Best to get him some help quick. #crazytrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[The world lost a hockey legend today.. Rest in piece to the great Ted Lindsay, my thoughts and prayers go out to him and his family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC What Climate Change? You said “ the world is coming to an end in 12 years!” So I stocked up on flatulent cows… https://t.co/02Vyr8NS8W]]></document><document><![CDATA[“that some kinda eastern thing?” “far from it” https://t.co/EU8WKxN1ub via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoshGrahamRadio  Desmond is the typical Tar Hole! “I felt real good about our chances before the Duke v Carolina g… https://t.co/kYeNFNeHbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does a gas station go from 1.99 for gas to 2.39 in 8 hours.... guess I shoulda stopped on the way to work instead of on the way home]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t see that people were freaking out about her become the worlds “first self made billionaire” today LMFAO. T… https://t.co/sV3R7hiFsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@awsten i hope u have a good night and drink some water and tell urself that ur the king of pop]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wes_mur @cheetoCLU @joanpzls @RobGuy3 @scoobydooclt @RoaringRiotZ @roaringriot @JessMReynolds16 everyone knows the… https://t.co/9PPKWxhayY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dreyer_smit @OhImLaughin If there is a way, Elon Musk will try to do it...😁 https://t.co/JjSJn56bWy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TMZ In more interesting news: All these people actually felt this article was worth retweeting. https://t.co/z8eTeOHafQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueToRecruits I get annoyed by those whom only support the basketball team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching @travelchannel to remember what the ground looks like without snow. Also all the wanderlust.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeremyM0314 @takecomand @hqCOMANDER @suzukimoto2 Awesome. Congratulations.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JGreen_PRsports u too sir, see bills and jags fans can truly get along. Thats good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Electrotek2 @LindaMusgrove9 @jackhay86865097 @VikingWilli @Inge_Mausi @side_show007 @CraigChermside @t2gunner… https://t.co/KWa61d3baS]]></document></documents></author>