<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I support local boutiques more than anyone but I’m getting real tired of seeing these boutiques copy each other. SE… https://t.co/eYYG360Oqr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love cereal so much. Which is why I can't buy it.  I don't know how to not eat the whole damn box.  Raisin Bran m… https://t.co/tgfiJ1ApO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The OK @MomsDemand Chapter supports our Muslim friends at the Capitol today. We took part in a panel about intersec… https://t.co/aHkIprI27p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let us be Thankful that God is allowing us to move Froward in our lives keep Believing and Praying for All Will B Well Jesus Name Amen]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear I can’t relate to certain things like anymore or even EVER for that matter. I’m not even on no cocky or rud… https://t.co/Cc47TSnjAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaarreaza TIC TAC TIC TAC TE SUENA EN LA PATA DE LA OREJA 👂 JAJAJAJAJAJAJAJAJA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThruTheBridle He will have no resistance from Jacobson, Jay or Mike...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PogoWasRight Well under an hour. I’m pretty efficient :). And if dogs or cats get privacy rights, I will be hiring :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jnj49 It shows both sides, in my opinion. One person can literally steal millions or billions and serve less time… https://t.co/z6opHwEKxM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Acaba de publicar una foto en Miami International Airport - MIA https://t.co/QmcYCkORsg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neilmeron @lifetimetv @meganhilty @CallieKhouri Thanks for shooting in Nashville. Hope to get some days working on… https://t.co/AZam5QSBsz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to see how lit the studio got during this whole album 😫🔥 https://t.co/YN26l4jqRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS IS RIDICULOUS. Please @NYT talk about more important stuff. We are counting on you.  https://t.co/rukYui4SFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go forth and make it happen.  #courage #faith #trust #hope #lifestyle #leader #mantra #mindset #mom #author… https://t.co/L7eCmJq6UW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi MEET THE ANGEL FAMILIES AND STOP HIDING BEHIND "YOUR" WALL, YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO BE A SPEAKER FOR ALL… https://t.co/Hz7BDYYUEa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JuStanley_ Hah there’s something funny about a guy named Mane losing his mane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Holy shit, R Kelly was charged with 10 counts of aggravated criminal sexual abuse. R Kelly like... https://t.co/r6XJzOXWFa]]></document><document><![CDATA[FDI Fiber Burn lab day 1. @ The Woodlands HS, Conroe ISD https://t.co/X2OvCiStsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[😳 Report: Robert Kraft is not the biggest name involved in prostitution case – ProFootballTalk https://t.co/h46xW56RKw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjs5555 @stefsstuff @daveweigel Go look at his actual record. What bills has he passed?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday love at work. My co-workers are better than yours!! @ Scottsdale, Arizona https://t.co/6PctWxFMCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[GDD tip: Get into the board game industry and you will suddenly care a lot about the way mail works. #gamedesigndaily]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrisbharrison @BachelorABC Is this giant leap the fence? Because the people have been waiting and they have a right to know!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great first meet just a lil cold! #lorenatrack #strengthinthe99 https://t.co/ybzIUtPyeA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RescuingDogsVE @HAABERSKY @ClaudiaMRola @ThreeDogsNappin @MARIAACLIFTON @pocs80 @AlmeidaAlzira @chortletown… https://t.co/rZrhEhjBtI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just washed these sheets, but I’m eating dessert in bed. Way to go meeee.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The air is so cold I almost choked 3 times by accidentally inhaling :-///]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, I think they mean they are coming to take a bullet,  not the gun. Or at least, that's what I'm reading into thu… https://t.co/uQUtvSNvNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CRPSDocumentary has anyone researched CRPS and heredity?   I now have 2 children who are diagnosed with CRPS.   Th… https://t.co/030BRp8NWv]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is seen thru all her actions. which sucks. bc like u dont even gotta front. we know you broken, heal yourself.… https://t.co/Ki2ceZwXga]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jane_Depa @sugarmillpride @sdedragons Your amazing! I miss seeing you everyday at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Huge .. YUGE...... crowd! 📖✒️#BookSigning next he ll be signing Martha Stewart Cookbooks 📖at Barnes and Noble..… https://t.co/urFCjin5yx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IbnHawqal @WuChang16 @IlhanMN Nope.  But her “fashion statement” s reams loudly.  To deny that, is just silly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimBoiLee @realDonaldTrump @GOP @Comey Sorry for your blindness. I used to be Dem til the socialistic movement with Obama.  Good luck.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Winding up day 3 for the 83rd annual #jlprummage. We kick it all off with our Pre-Sale Party Friday with live band,… https://t.co/7L5cOujFTd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @GailBenzler @kevinunexpected @CaththeWineLady @SteenbergWines @winewankers @DemiCassiani… https://t.co/yMyjaQXFN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SarahGould_SA @jphn94487 @DudekLinda @andrerucker51 @judeaa @keanothedog @NOW1SOLAR @Itridpm @JayValenz67… https://t.co/g50bJB71Ny]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Urban Growler Brewing Company https://t.co/mpJ8wnDCCI]]></document><document><![CDATA[There are times when I trust things and there are times where I just can’t do that and I just don’t believe in peop… https://t.co/8WwJJeH8wL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KoKoShyelle @MaSeshield @xtraTreesRus @_BeyondAverage_ @AuntyAdj It’s almost like I can recognise the issues in so… https://t.co/WsVXKfmBeV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@triana922 @JackPit65654062 I would like to see some proof of that....  Doesn't help much when the cost of Illegal… https://t.co/LqsNUUCG58]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaked Documents Reveal Government Database of Activists, Journalists Linked to Migrant Ca… via @Countable https://t.co/9or3JHpuEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually don’t take requests but when guys talk about the NBA my vagina dries up on the spot https://t.co/Z4OzDphg97]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jali_Cat @DaRealGrizzle @MattWhitaker46 @DOJ_EOIR @StateDept @TheJusticeDept @senatemajldr @GOPLeader @JerryNadler jealous swamp creatures]]></document><document><![CDATA[@masnNationals this would of been a great game to telecast. Potential opening day lineup vs division foe with a lot… https://t.co/TDyP5BzaXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ask yourself if what you are doing today is getting you closer to where you want to be. #Notjustacareerbutmypassion… https://t.co/kiQkCFVzHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Identifythebox @Aimhere2000 @RepAdamSchiff It's so great that farmers need bailouts! So far 7.5 billion in welfare… https://t.co/oDGkVUnwcu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We couldn't string together 3 wins to save our lives, now we're on an 8 game streak and have gotten our rookie goal… https://t.co/vum7iuuOsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The3rdFrame @liamgallagher Haha , Liam’s not being nice with you huh. You gotta praise him if you want his love 😉😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's all close our eyes and hear the ocean calling ☺️💙 #DreamingOfTheCoast #LivingInLinen #WhitneyLinen… https://t.co/FMYwOKxJwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChristGardener @bricey16 @gabrielmalor You’re only allowed to say that if you live in NJ. I say it every day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was laying on the couch and got up to go to the bathroom. Apparently I had put my blanket on Quinn. She wanted to… https://t.co/KYqO1z2Qpx]]></document><document><![CDATA[me talking to myself when i tweet something that exceeds more than 10 likes]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandPaul You know this is needed!Go down at the Sourhern Border,like real Senators that cares,and then try to tell… https://t.co/bivrOo5MsI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maegahan Everyone expects the “Disney experience” every time they shop. I didn’t see Cinderella’s castle last time I was in a TJMaxx.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimlewis99 @robertasmithnyt But I would guess more art lovers go to museums, which connote education, than to gall… https://t.co/lGTA6JMlmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Used to praise @UberEats delivery times but it’s not worth it if they refuse to refund a $23 order that never arriv… https://t.co/g1FwozzUQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Once again, NYT come up some nonsense “bothsideserism.”  Mitch McConnell is to blame for 95% of the harm done in Co… https://t.co/fGCI1yq8t6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly I just want one of my friends to come live with me and Hayden and I’ll hire them as our Nanny rather than… https://t.co/8Zv2krnhWb]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's the first day of my spring break, so naturally, I've just been shopping and bought a train set for my nephew for Christmas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m blocked someone please tell me what this says I’ll love u forever 😥  https://t.co/r4d5RrpbUB…]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaskedSingerFOX I've been saying Donny Osmond. My husband just said Wayne Brady #PeacockMask]]></document><document><![CDATA[That end credit scene tho #CapitanMarvel. Let the count down to #Endgame begin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AGirlHasNoPOTUS @NatashaBertrand Stand up for your actions Mr. Stone!  Let's not turn into a whining bitch now!  S… https://t.co/QsSF0pOBLF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atAEON @DeplorableMe55 @stu00stu @GregShugar @seanhannity @realDonaldTrump @POTUS You're no veteran, BOT. McCain w… https://t.co/Ext3nDLmgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Wow!!! isn’t it true that a biological male has a larger muscle mass than women and that the hormone levels are different?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rashiduzzaman82 Awww. I love seeing happy couples! Helps rein in my jaded cynicism. Congratulations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods They don’t want Trump and America to succeed 🇺🇸 We will again in 2020👊 #MAGA #Trump2020]]></document><document><![CDATA[KR: I don’t change my mind. Enjoy your day. The American People know me. I never change my mind.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SusanBr63598322 @steph93065 @realDonaldTrump @ICEgov That was 3 years ago.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyThriller69 @TheScoop_US @BlazeTV @therealroseanne https://t.co/bhQQY2uYmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Number 19....💙💙💙💙💙 just love it.  Saw it and had to have it forever.  Def Never disappointed.  On to the next one .… https://t.co/nUKPOnpD77]]></document><document><![CDATA[After struggling to keep up with loan payments, West Ridge Mall’s future is uncertain, leaving shoppers worried Top… https://t.co/LuqMRqS7YL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks @MariManoogian for this amazing opportunity! @CaitlinFinerty is more excited than ever to major in political… https://t.co/gYatTVJzFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @JackConnie @Jesus_Luvs_Us @debratankersle1 @Jimmysimmonds1 @MelindaYoe @Iluvinspireu @roads2… https://t.co/8krMk90QA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A fellow teacher thought I was fresh out of undergrad (aka 8 years younger than my age) in case you want to know ho… https://t.co/3rsceiotaY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone pls remind my brain that it is in fact NOT spring break yet and that I still have a chem lab, chem homework… https://t.co/LgZd7lRkx3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RawStory I knew this in my heart back in Jan, 2017 !  Too many people blabbered right after swearing ceremony !… https://t.co/CvTBfSQpho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Je participe à une étude en cours pour avoir les données fiables au Québec. Vous pourrez valider vos impressions ou… https://t.co/E7ToQT1Whk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Lucero39 de nada adorada siempre contigo para celebrarte y agradecerte los 365 dias del año!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP He took us from 14 to 21 Trillion in 2 years giving tax breaks to the rich and screwing the middle and lower c… https://t.co/BaXDFtGaXy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sheena Easton - For Your Eyes Only [Bond theme song 1981, Widescreen] https://t.co/HSBbNw7pa2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I assure you, young lady, that I am a 52 year old retired nurse,from Kansas, living in the Ozarks of SW Missouri en… https://t.co/LqIaWQ9riI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last night with my Tia watching Mamma Mia! It was so much fun. #MammaMiaTUTS #Abba #TutsHouston @ Hobby Center for… https://t.co/XwnmrGctdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AviLoveXXX From personal hands-on experience, you are more than gorgeous. You are breathtakingly stunning inside and out.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning about federal funding updates at the National Governors Association  @PALaborIndustry  @NatlGovsAssoc https://t.co/8IJoRhj4X9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This actually looks like Walden Pond... wonder if it is? #morningmeditation #henrydavidthoreau #WaldenPond… https://t.co/Ifh1il3YLv]]></document><document><![CDATA[GET BETTER - Scotty Sire X The Weekend Riot (Live Acoustic) https://t.co/FLSQEY0GR2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love these!  Right now Starbucks has the pink sleeves for breast cancer support, must collect... #humor #laugh… https://t.co/Vs7g1SBoma]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lt_gray Thank you for your service.  Which LEO from #LivePD would you do a ride along with? #Dadgummit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kepler_johann @hospicio_brasil @belle_ckbbio A Bolsinhadefezes e Bolsodefezes]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good thinking, Firsties! I’m guessing the character must have had some changes over time? 👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABC4EXPLORE Nice pic Andy I saved the and I'm going to put it on my wall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I grew up in a small town... I know backwoods corruption when I see it #murdermountain sheriff 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSanders how abt NOT running again? Why don’t we give space to all of the new POC and female voices to be heard?… https://t.co/GThqONBwJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I did not order this.. where is the return to sender slip? 😒❄️ #ontstorm https://t.co/Lu0XDZEYcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would give the world to see mar’s tap dance routine to white &amp; nerdy by weird al yankovic]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cillizza is the king of bad takes.   Jim Jordan was awful. If he felt the need to add a Republican for "balance", t… https://t.co/Xz4WXYvZLp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_granata @justinsplanet42 @Bizzlex8 @MichelleCaissi1 @296_cool @loveujustinjb5 @BhanuRajput33 @kulsgrace… https://t.co/dkFzenCqoA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@campueroh and I are gonna get a cat and you all will be it’s aunties. That is all]]></document></documents></author>