<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@CR_HIATT @jolynn_gibson @ricotorrea @IndyByChoice @rip157 @mizzhays @Lax_Mom01 @johnrobertsFox @WhiteHouse Why cov… https://t.co/txKsUooIsD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@m0nirath Bro I tried taking my little brother and his friends and they wanted to go see The Prodigy. Im like yall gotta be kidding me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carsoncoachswl You’re da man, Coach Steve. I’ll be in China Grove in a bit if you want to surprise me with lunch too!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASAPDORIS @VLashell_ @_dejabajaaa @__BankHead If that’s the bottom line then yes. Just don’t understand why it’s a… https://t.co/62GETYVkPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chortletown Pretty Pup. Why would anybody turn this Pup in to a kill shelter is beyond me !!@]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔴LIVE🔴  Running behind due to setting up a awesome new overlay!    Come tell me what you think!… https://t.co/P7qGSAb6D3]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has to be sabotaging the Steelers at this point...If he were this stupid we would know before now...Right?… https://t.co/JDZJGxcoMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyiFalls You seriously didn’t have fury losing that fight, stop it. He hit higher % than wilder, landed more punch… https://t.co/VXnSw8bpmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sacarle madr al Monstruo d Qqta,aunke signifike dshaogo dl malestar q llvamos x dntro,no va a hacr q El rflxione so… https://t.co/UKqGZ1brnL]]></document><document><![CDATA[A2: We use it for rental revenue. We just worked out what it looks like with our events office on campus. For us it… https://t.co/rhoDrdoUbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[We actually do like those people we see in the field.... Even though @TJParkerABC13 is no @wrigleyABC13… https://t.co/enQHWgavGi]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was in the pubs and clubs in London I learned that they go HARD to this song. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never saw this, i styled it  .. as you can see she was HORRIBLEEEEE this day.However the shots were fabulous. Pho… https://t.co/z3n32Vq9zQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judahperu1984 Complete domination for 25 mins. Twood got absolutely mauled and owned in every aspect of that fight. It was bad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y'all shoulda seen the face of the very attractive girl standing next to me as I audibly said "Treat yo self" befor… https://t.co/ZyWhQcYfXg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PuckettLogan Well sometimes you hit a turn and say “I think I’m going to fast” and then send it into the ditch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Diddy encapsulated my entire life in one small video clip. #Boss https://t.co/VrNbq7f9qK]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed the @BlueAngels looking for a parking spot on campus this morning. All I saw was a @JetBlue Angel landing @LASairport]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the group of amazing Black Belts who took time to inspire us at the end of our Youth and Adult Karate… https://t.co/a6z9W5vFNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you then plot those growth rates vs initial seeding proportion and fit a line, the intercepts will give you the… https://t.co/X5exGfxGyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats Ward girls. HSP WON their first state championship. Kemia has 3 state rings 2 with McEachern and 1 with Ho… https://t.co/ZVipdnOHk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merlinspants07 Umm, I just left work an hour ago, in the most capitalist country on earth.  Tell me more about that socialism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The best way to describe my five years in college was coming to terms with my preoccupied/anxious attachment then w… https://t.co/SW2M3aVDGI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GottulaTodd @GBRosenthal @nsaaevents @nsaahome @PrepExtra @NEPrepZone Always enjoyed talking to your dad when he w… https://t.co/QEOxp4Hq2s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freestyle  My skin is clear as hell. That shit look Hollywood as fuck wit no make up on. I thought I looked fucked… https://t.co/2U4gaLHcGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ballerr_Rayy you speaking down on a nigga you once idolized nigga you a damn joke.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter @TitaniaMcGrath You disappointed so much by criticizing President Trump that you simply are not a relia… https://t.co/3SxQnEIQS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregLaTour @TSMDetroit @rehashertheband doesn’t have anything booked, but good idea 😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilKuziVert__ A is Collins and B is Markkanen.  I would still rather have Lauri because Collins benefits a lot from playing with Trae Young]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanMcElwee This may be the only way to undo the damage the Trumpzis have done to the Judiciary, if all of the Ora… https://t.co/mLfcfhLuRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenChuckYeager @larlar1971 Happy Birthday Sir, did you ever live in Mt Shasta in the late 70s or early 80s I would… https://t.co/n4Y6W2S3GF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lemme be clear.  Zion or no Zion, this morning I’m rolling into work like... https://t.co/Tw4adO9dDb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rainman_SR16 @Hamzetupapi @BR_NBA This kind of stuff is why kyrie left Lebron]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mateagold @OConnellPostbiz @Fahrenthold In 2019, for the Trumps, EVERY day is Yom Kippur.  h/t @StephenAtHome]]></document><document><![CDATA[If there are crimes related to Russia trump committed, mueller will uncover them.  I bet he hates trumps guts. https://t.co/cPac48N6cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yeah a about that.... @ Paoli's Pizzeria and Piano Bar https://t.co/kFX8HQ0uCo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@claredoogan Trying to confirm if Americans have the same association with the word 'mongo' and it's been fifty fifty so far]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daigle_sylvain @murphycooper 🤝  Je comprends à 100% ton opinion, et j'y réfléchis depuis que je suis au cegep (com… https://t.co/zEXh7rZNgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lynndaeastland When I saw them in 2000 on an off date from Ozzfest, Josh Hommer said "This song is about fucking"… https://t.co/X2wM68TPQw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JRBoh @Morning_Joe What happened to a strong military and a war on drugs? Oh yeah, they weren’t a fake enough crisis!]]></document><document><![CDATA[IZQUIERDA CONTRAATACA  Dilma Roussef opina que ayuda humanitaria que varios países quieren llevar a Venezuela es la… https://t.co/7tW7glesPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattmusic14 And then there's the whole filming his friend masturbate in front of minors thing. That may provide some insight as well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hqsports Gymnastics: The vault being set at too low of a height at the 2000 Sydney Olympics for two full rotations… https://t.co/5WWmRKTflP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLRumorsDaily My point being there are in place to do that with acquired picks taking a blow from the potential o… https://t.co/i3wPlRaKrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand Will you fight against the drugs coming across our southern border, by building a wall? Alot of peop… https://t.co/DVWxkMqk96]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk @PFTPMPosse What restaurant are you most looking forward to eating at this week in Indianapolis?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me too. @RepCummings @AOC @RashidaTlaib @SpeakerPelosi @RepJerryNadler @RepAdamSchiff]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sillyredn3k @StewartHaasRcng @Nook4SHR @ColeCuster @ChaseBriscoe5 I got to get a listen on that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the boys freshmen basketball team on winning the freshmen tournament championship tonight at LC!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never flown early on a Sunday before ... never will again. This place is an absolute mad house. Longest securi… https://t.co/euEcpoAiFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Futbolero_ @shakira Lugar donde el Madrid ganará una futura Champions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happening now at @sxsw, our own @table81 is chatting with @DCfishwife, @envisibleco, and Tommy Gordon about how blo… https://t.co/nma2iHyFQI]]></document><document><![CDATA[El café de Costa Rica brilla en el mundo, nuestro sello es un elemento de alto valor agregado 🇨🇷 Mantuve un encuent… https://t.co/eEfQimDeFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH MY GOD I REALLY THOUGHT PEOPLE WERE *exaggerating* ABOUT HOW WILD ABDUCTED IN PLAIN SIGHT IS. I was wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proud to work with companies that value student experience and inclusion. Join Varsity Brands, @herffjones and the… https://t.co/QE167QcUFN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smh ..they robbed you ..stole bread ..and fucking ya BM ..did all that happen3d at one time ..why would u still be… https://t.co/JxA4LYH4HF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melotonin5 Agree to disagree! Fortunately those old stories we both love are still out there to reread.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robleathern have you tried pickle juice for recovery? i've heard some interesting things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianwacker1 Gentlemen’s game, call penalties on yourself, etc.  super easy fix fix this problem, the in group sco… https://t.co/B5sHHsqkmu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quaint little town... #Jacumba ▪️ 🏚 ▪️ #abandoned #california #imbroimages #nikon #abc7eyewitness… https://t.co/3n6uCC5NmK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@perccnowitzki @Mavs_FFL @luka7doncic @MarkkanenLauri @swish41 I’m an engineering senior at ISU rn 🧐 I’ve loved the… https://t.co/BK08ElHGRa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red  Violets are blue Valentines ain’t quite over  There is still time for you                             to be my boo]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cropping feature for choosing your new profile picture for Twitter is hella retarded and lame. You think my big… https://t.co/TYNKXN6dEV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsianOptionGirl @CEtoruom @realDonaldTrump But wait love, the great thing about logic is that I don’t stress about… https://t.co/LgoAHQNcqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@okmaher @lyndseyfifield Seems like a perfect time for us to call you in...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lady Gaels Basketball are Tournament Bound!  Monday February 25th (12) Clinton @ (5) Leicester 630pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some guy they pulled out of the stands just beat Steph Curry in the three point shootout.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KhurtissPerry @CoachJonesRB @TFootballGeek @Madhousefit @ChadSimmons_ @DatDude70 @_Mack7 @JohnGarcia_Jr… https://t.co/scfUzwR691]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikesmoniz It’s an old contract. I’m surprised they didn’t renegotiate it sooner]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sethseaborne I been said he was gettin her back lol it was a matter of when]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plank, Dodden, Sambo - off to Jersey, Atlanta, Boston - see you soon MOC #singersongwhat https://t.co/jKbotMFbHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the Mueller Report Might Disappoint Almost Everybody https://t.co/4XmboAREQN #Nadler #AMJoy less]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: EXCLUSIVE: Listen up, #WWEUniverse. @WWEDanielBryan really wants you to learn how to focus...#WWEFastlane… https://t.co/zyhe5sjkoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[106: Marco Sanchez, W, dec Coy Olsen 2-1. Takedown in the final 15 seconds clinches it.  Willmar 3, Bemidji 0.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great stuff is happening in #Brockton and that is a direct result of the outstanding leadership &amp; vision of… https://t.co/q6uibWrY5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SanDiego: I just entered to win an #Aulani vacation from #Star941FM and you can, too ---&gt; https://t.co/OKjXLU43ZE]]></document><document><![CDATA[🏀 SUBSTATE FINAL GAMEDAY! 🏀.  📍Muscatine HS, ⌚️7pm, doors open at 5:45pm. 🎟 $8, no passes accepted. Game 🆚 Davenpor… https://t.co/QYDecASSOy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bambino7142000 @BillsQBwatch @buffalobills @JoshAllenQB @AB84 https://t.co/wLfLv31Ng3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyPaul1984 Amen!  10 year contracts were dumb then and owners learned their lessons.  Players live by anaylytics… https://t.co/JifE6DQTTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@7DaystoDie I hope they focus on game play. Alpha 17 became even more grindy and so hard to start. Our gaming group… https://t.co/kII7LRFg4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrotherNature Time out am I the only one who noticed how this man isn’t having a hard time speaking while he runni… https://t.co/uDHvlFvD18]]></document><document><![CDATA[ATTN LA COMICS..This is how I feel when I see some of you acting like you and Brody were friends. Shameless, why do… https://t.co/PH45TVHY0X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrianPKos I’ll actually be at Class AA wrestling: section championships tonight and WPIAL championships tomorrow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @Lakers are not goona make IT to the playoffs. You guys heard it here first! 💥🔥👊 #NBA #NBAAllStar #NBATwitter]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #TeamAli on @tyltsports. Ali would outbox Tyson easily! https://t.co/epNa8WCJ2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Llevame de vuelta a casa  @jennydweber #NewEngland #6Rings  @GilletteStadium https://t.co/EyjdMbbxKS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the most important comedian of our generation is George W. Bush.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't wait until it warms up so on my nights off I can go night fishing instead on playing Xbox until 8 in the morning]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #GotThanked with T-Mobile Tuesdays! I just scored a $4 movie ⁦@IMAX⁩ ticket to @AlitaMovie from ⁦@atomtickets⁩! E… https://t.co/JQTeJlVgBA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nicncor22 I hope the Celtics can get it together. Seems like Hayward is starting to get in stride. But I think the team hates kyrie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk Then he’s not a good coach. Patriots players said they changed nothing from the season. You always… https://t.co/dOsBXqk3mp]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're at $37,132 already for the Relay For Life, still accepting donations throughout the event!  Feel free to shar… https://t.co/R9ydrfKIgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kalendil how are you seventy? I know you're young. but sometimes you're seventy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwb5777 @JimKilbane @realDonaldTrump No one said he was Patton, dipshit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So much for the plot line of my renaissance sci-fi murder mystery. ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Re:false statement:fossil fuels R good for the world:"...Plants waste many resources at high temps,so… https://t.co/xh4ulOW1Al]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bowman: “a couple things were on the borderline of happening but at the end of the day we weren’t going to make a t… https://t.co/falvF1mKae]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CaptainConnell @AustinHinds1 I was just trying to ride the elevator bro]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoraneChisholm @cnieuwhof I took time to read this RevDrLorane, I’m glad I did. Nice share and I’ll be sharing wit… https://t.co/tEXKBrEXIp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MorganOrtagus Those are some seriously cool shoes you’re wearing tonight!! 😎]]></document></documents></author>