<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[If you just sit there in silence while I pour my feelings to you, best believe I’m breaking something of yours. You… https://t.co/HQkkspRSzr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Took out all my wisdom teeth at once and I look like this https://t.co/KNPkd5VWfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like im sweating its busy af at work . 2pm hurryy uppp its my fridayyyy 🙌🏽🙌🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marianaa_alfaro @THR Agreed. I would take the "Friends" characters off. Period]]></document><document><![CDATA[Attachment is the great fabricator of illusions; reality can be attained only by someone who is detached. ~ Simone Weil]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleyagans @tarawestover @JCHSTennisCoach @johnscreekmedia @JohnsCreekHS Read it for book club. It’s a powerful s… https://t.co/OIaatKA2IT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Branched out *slightly* at Dough Zone yesterday and got a spicy beef pancake roll along with our regular order and… https://t.co/ukya1jd3tJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If only media weren't so concerned with Hillary's emails they may have caught this, eh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eugenegu @realDonaldTrump Really. Cause your governor said he is canceling and made that public announcement YESTE… https://t.co/cQ8WldIT6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morgxn2001 Attacked * by the way they bully and do more hate crimes that I have seen and private attacks happen by… https://t.co/ffzTf8bYBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ayer @LeonBenLarregui me felicitó por mi cumple y le dije que si un día necesita un violinista para una canción que… https://t.co/sEsc8SuHts]]></document><document><![CDATA[Governing by pundit opinions. FFS. #AmericanExceptionalism #MAGA “advisers placed the calls in the hopes Trump's me… https://t.co/L4yhPQSH90]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AB84 my son has been your biggest fan and still has your Steeler fat head in his room. All the best to you with the Raiders.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Social media is always going to have something new-we have to decide how much time and effort our organization need… https://t.co/FrhAdVl7sQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me in 2013: This is the worst year of my life!  Me in 2019: This is the best year of my life!   #JonasBrothers https://t.co/hvjRRUR2af]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not gonna lie, I'm intrigued by the #cbdheals movement... checkout some puffy taco eye cream 🌮 from @QuimRock! https://t.co/RjkxZEOJgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Myla_Bee @iamcameronb @kkendalllieghh It’s the exact kind of vibe I expect from someone named kendalllllllieghhhhh… https://t.co/NHsDH5J74N]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nctcsf #SanFrancisco @ New Conservatory Theatre Center https://t.co/Il71qfzicS]]></document><document><![CDATA[My one goal today is to find a heart shaped pizza. In my 21 years of life (22 on Wednesday 😉), I have not encounter… https://t.co/0kWfOLwqBh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wwoz_neworleans Saturday morning, working, listening to the beautiful voice of one taken too soon. #TrumpetBlack… https://t.co/edJZn0SqUf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kamala, I know ur having a bad week but WT Front Door is up with this tale from your crypt? Your involvement in thi… https://t.co/m50dWqkyCz]]></document><document><![CDATA[My managers got me this coloring book after I told them my bf cheated on me and I’m SCREAMING LMAO https://t.co/wRtpThGsGe]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌟🌟🌟🌟🌟 Have you experienced a Twilight Tan?! Come see what you're missing! #welcometothedarkside  #spraytantukwila… https://t.co/eFjcrQY2dN]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Robyn Effect @robynkonichiwa #NYCsubway #postconcertbliss https://t.co/GhHD1ZtOvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobSalesforce @SalesforceAmy @dougdunfee @billpowell__c No tool can fix all of that. You need good process and pro… https://t.co/LYUSxOwU7Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Late night thoughts... If social media doesn’t exist, will our life be more productive and happy? #whatif]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling after a good workout at the gym &gt;&gt;&gt; anything else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryanjreilly @PreetBharara But the standard for a majority of legal documents is Bluebook, and not APA.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The PlayStation Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below… https://t.co/CdFmyQiYyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you work in our biz, you never know who you’ll meet!...or what. In this case? Goats! 🐐  #bossbabe #realtor… https://t.co/l9r8yTlckb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chemjobber They can be a long time coming if the search committee is waiting to see if it wants to return to the p… https://t.co/FcWtnK3eO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really, this Michael Cohen loser is what you are leading with?  Isn’t there anything else that might be news worthy… https://t.co/yg8mQbhgzA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea people hated fritos, they’re literally my favorite. What is wrong with y’all?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working nights is fine until you have to sit in a dark room with a fan on for 12hrs. 😴😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[#fitchickfriday @allisonethier #fitnesscompetition #arnoldfitnessexpo2019 @ Columbus Convention Center https://t.co/QoG1pdZecO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your girl just ran 10 miles without stopping! 🏃🏼‍♀️ https://t.co/tq8949xTHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realtorlife #dreamhomefinders #realestateagent @ Waxahachie, Texas https://t.co/KABqz4XoPL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FartyCheddarCat Where did your mama find that toy? My kitties might like it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk why everyone acts like my life is a complete shit show,I pay all my bills on time that’s having your life together😊😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[HAPPY FRICKEN BIRTHDAY TO MY BESTIE have the best day ever nugget u deserve it 💓@maddynugent_ https://t.co/Jw6jKNj9EC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Book Twitter is amazing, and here are a few of my favorite follows on that front - @j_zimms @likaluca @luxlotus]]></document><document><![CDATA[this actually made me miss California for the first time wow so nostalgic]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AnnCoulter Weren't you in love with "wacky nut job" Coulter just a few months ago? Ann coulter fi… https://t.co/igkhTbh3Is]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katee1624 Happy birthday baby girl. i can NOT wait to sss u tonight love uuuuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Proclaimed to have been 'the best horse who ever bit the briddle.' Grover Buddy Delph]]></document><document><![CDATA[Be in your own power...whatever that may be...be in it.  @lil_k20 you make us all so proud of you wearing that purp… https://t.co/Njh55sqXRo]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m not trying to look bad in front of people that I may be working for one day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mass_ave @rachelgetsindy Dang! These look awesome! I second the thought that we need a dim sum place. Like, immedi… https://t.co/pRu96r3wik]]></document><document><![CDATA[I usually pay the plow guy $100, but instead I cleared all the snow myself today, so in a way I EARNED $100? WHAT S… https://t.co/DcNRjemuKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goofballgeorge @MarshaPatriot @maryllewis53 @MaryLuWiliams @MasonHurst10 @MattBobandy @maureen14156319… https://t.co/sCgxUzFIoc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanagonzales I WILL LITERALLY BEAT THE FUCK OUTTA YOU KINFOLK 🖕🏼🖕🏼🖕🏼🖕🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you think my Uber driver will become irritated if I start chewing my ice? 🥶🤨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our HS women arriving in style! #HopeStreetWomensLuncheon2019 #FirmFoundation #20YearsOfHopeStreet https://t.co/FOneUUS6vo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up every morning and wish I was in cars land. WHAT IN CARS NATION?!? https://t.co/WVUsTXKftA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Paramount Theatre of the Arts https://t.co/0GjWj8PdPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi yeah mr. Spotify? Can we please get the original wii song on Spotify .          -a bitch who just wanna listen to it]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my Scholastic Writing winners. We had 40 students win and 125 enter. Go Warriors!!!… https://t.co/iuBskDJMBJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bflay I could seriously spend all day-everyday watching #BeatBobbyFlay 🍽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KiziriiW And I’m not accusing you of saying that. I just saw many yesterday claiming that media in the US reportin… https://t.co/kgY6idVMOZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSasquatch702 Depends on the crime tho. You don't wanna go to state. Federal prison is the nice one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neuromusic Millennials are killing it and now they wanna climb up the mountains]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that the Repubs aren’t even asking Cohen questions and just trying to discredit him is so telling. Even Co… https://t.co/iAPM1m4Onl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paracentesis Day...I’m going to predict 5.3 liters extracted from my abdomen. That would be 11.6lbs. I’m currently… https://t.co/Ht0HjYbvme]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maydaymindy9 I usually LOVE glasses on guys. I like him w/o..  Great interview.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cprwarner @thericandback @adukakis Erica, why pile it on the poor piano though?! 😛]]></document><document><![CDATA[Siempre lloro cuando  mi bebé se va a conciertos de su banda favorita, Ojalá el se emocione tanto cuando me  vaya a ver a  mi Julion👨🏽‍🎤]]></document><document><![CDATA[So less than a month from #baby due date means walking, sitting, standing, breathing, sleeping, eating, not eating,… https://t.co/NahdYky8ns]]></document><document><![CDATA[Recently I enrolled in an extremely intense blogging course. It's taken up every bit of extra time that I have and… https://t.co/VUbp2vLiym]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannenicole04 Hahaha I know who he is now. He had to make us new topperstix because the original order was stuck… https://t.co/2ywCr9wd7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't live under a rock and have seen @starisbornmovie and have sang "Shallow" a billion times, but imagine my sh… https://t.co/uA55sWuHGH]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you think im going to listen to the Jonas Brothers now even more than i did when i was 9 then you’d be 100% correct]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin @MosesDidItBest Thank you for shining the light on a crime I didn’t quite understand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[confidence is the intangible force of faith &gt;&gt;&gt; otherwise temporary and short-lived]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to end abortion by executive order flies in the face of years of litigation that got Roe vs Wade passed https://t.co/6vQeKAmqkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sandy_REACHLab @KUALZ @KUMedCenter @nicolekeithphd @morrisjillk @dublyn14 @JaimePeralesPu @Jaimielynn9… https://t.co/XAWJlXArHZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want free access to our tobacco-prevention videogame smokeSCREEN? Visit our website, https://t.co/ueCHHlQn4V, and s… https://t.co/StJiiEAHSI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrettyRickyBSF is coming to Nashville in March. Union City, ASSEMBLE. @mollyjnapier]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Indy_Austin P.S. Iowa City is like the Bloomington of Iowa. Lots of similarities between the cities and campuses.… https://t.co/J6jHe2qwUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is in the U.K. -protest against LGBTQ curriculum being pushed by the legislature in schools. I just let them k… https://t.co/705izukrYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BulletPeople @jaspar @BridgetPhetasy I’m aware of all of the indictments and people going to prison. It’s not a ho… https://t.co/9c1Qae3ebr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday three different New Yorkers told me I had to visit the famous ‘how’s pizza’ I did and it’s safe to say it… https://t.co/f9ObANMnpK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't say it wasn't you how else could they have your DNA  https://t.co/w23LpMOAuC]]></document><document><![CDATA[never been so happy with the number on the scale before 😏 #HappyGrowingSzn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is actually really sad.. this man needs some loving care and help. She just posted this for likes. Please take… https://t.co/77owaUzPIu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people feel good about themselves wanting to go across the ocean to go help people while at the same time wa… https://t.co/kUJfIt3OTG]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the office changes the radio station in order to “learn you.” 🤭😲 #newgirlintown #awkwardmoment]]></document><document><![CDATA[@biigbesto Lol I tried, I was one of those people who played their music out loud today]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm working on an article about enemies and I'm done justifying an undocumented person's right to stay in this coun… https://t.co/q0KD1rlrqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak @SpeakerPelosi @IlhanMN @Ilhan Total BS Senate needs to grow a Spine.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katielmorrison Get a towel soak it up throw it in the wash and add dirty clothes. Problem solved]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day I get closer &amp; closer to just saying fuck it &amp; joining the military lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaraGay @jbouie 😂😂😂 We are a Republic, whose Founding Fathers were smart enough to realize that there would come a… https://t.co/uSHBXFJcui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stolen from Nick's snapchat because his entire story was basically all of us dancing at one point or another. https://t.co/PKANhQrR7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuckeyeCuti @moonrayvin @tnormandeau22 @24loves75 @jessaugie @LobsterBFFs1 @JEEPGRL732 @Katie_Elaine012… https://t.co/qVx8mqlpHg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Safe to say this is the last generation of men enjoying 'begum ke haath ki paki rotian', for Pakistani woman wont b… https://t.co/5PIBR90g8U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobynUrback W is not a thinker rather a self centred ,narcissistic controller of the council . He feels he is in c… https://t.co/0tmw5XYlOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clearwaterfire I have a yellow wildlands fire shirt (size medium). Used for a single season but in great condition… https://t.co/55D2gOOcN2]]></document><document><![CDATA[They were watching RAW when Roman announced he had leukemia and they grabbed the bull by the horns and told him Mad… https://t.co/8tBnqh8MVa]]></document><document><![CDATA[PSA TO NIGGAS STAY OUT MY DMS I DONT WANT YALL. I LIKE WOMEN. I LIKE PUSSY. EYE AM TIRED OF SAYING THIS SHIT FUCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrDenaGrayson @RepCummings @OversightDems @Trump I hope it's televised.]]></document></documents></author>