<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Epic Performance by the one and only scarsonbroadway In the #Wiltern! Thank You mintysacks 🤘… https://t.co/nfxio30HPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinnyM7 @SeedsofJake I would argue this past weekend is more than enough proof]]></document><document><![CDATA[#throwback. Prob 17 years old at a #highschool #jazzband concert in the gymnasium at Prairie Central High School in… https://t.co/uDwVTKnj9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was 6-7 through #childrenofthesnow and one boy was found on the other side of the woods behind my house in Livonia.… https://t.co/HQqB7FcHT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jamesworth21 Wow dude ! Out of anyone u the one talking about shaving ur butt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Investing in myself is really tough bc I always wanna invest in someone else. I’m learning how to and it’s great, b… https://t.co/iT1NnFtAIj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulietteBrass @chelsea98164450 @KelseyBrass @DanikaBrass @BobbixoB @AutumnxBrass @Carlie49067108 @Mssbellabella… https://t.co/n14bZf2bEl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghohpe Check out https://t.co/1nYtBoFXHi, it’s fast to get started and integrate with CI]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/dIkTX0mDHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[OPEN FOR SOME TRANSPHOBIC SHIT FROM A CHEF IN THE BAY AREA. YIKES MICHELLE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching 'Forever Amber' on TCM.  Was filmed at Greystone Mansion in BH but there's an outdoor English garden scene… https://t.co/Vm7XJOT0Ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[The seasonal @SweeTARTSCandy "Chicks, Ducks, and Bunnies" mix is the most superior candy on the market today. Thank… https://t.co/73tppMhwa9]]></document><document><![CDATA[People always forget everyone earns money differently. My expenditure will always be different from yours,so will b… https://t.co/nyLXn2NH7m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lo juro, llegaré a santiago y voy directo del aeropuerto hediondo a avión a comer en lumberjack]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Allwynkelly I FINALLY FOUND THE PHOTOBOMB PIC. April 2016. You’re correct, gray beard not relevant here 😂. Also co… https://t.co/09lUjOcfHm]]></document><document><![CDATA[My blood test came back and they found an unusually high concentration of DMX cells.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Too much ice and winter (@ Brampton GO Station in Brampton, ON) https://t.co/6y2KcpeEGB https://t.co/YykuncimkV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsAvaArmstrong @trojanenvy Nice true statement- https://t.co/cLCwK4vkBL]]></document><document><![CDATA[‘20 ATH De’Andre Wilborn ✅ 3.6 GPA ✅ Northwestern Medical Scholar ✅ Illini Division All City Team ✅ Honorable Menti… https://t.co/BdO5teKxEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just enjoy the remaining games the Flyers have left, all this hope for the playoffs is childplay]]></document><document><![CDATA[...I come out victorious in the depths of despair, lonesomeness, and struggle.  Even when friends hammer me and acc… https://t.co/S77Tkwkgdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🔥When I first started, I always stared at Arnold in the magazines and it inspired me more than anything…⁣ ⁣ Most p… https://t.co/3xqGC2PYSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weis_randy We all know now that Hillery was wrong and still won't admit it. This seems like just another attempt b… https://t.co/vYMS0viUIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[46-40 @HurstAthletics up on Seton Hill (on the hill) with 8:22 to play.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quién te controla? Tú naciste pa' morir sola. Vienes y vas, y no hay marinero pa' esa ola 🌊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RootsMon63 @LaurenScala4NY @gatonyc1 @bflay @newyorklivetv Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Ar… https://t.co/uQCnkj50rg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really Wanted to get into an @TheNFBC #FantasyBaseball league pretty badly this year for the first time, but with m… https://t.co/zyZJcCIXjh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gushing_Grannys @Donald_Wood @BigMikeY3587 @BGNY3 @RingRustRadio Both are going to miss the playoffs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nathanreid You’re too smart for this administration Nathan. Only the dumbest may apply.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first MLS Sports bar abroad. The @HoustonDynamo crossing borders. 🇲🇽 https://t.co/AzIy8pEnxJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have to pay our building $100 for a security guard when we are moving.   $100!!!!  For that price, they better be helping.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Upper Arlington's Golden Bear could get this new six-story replacement: https://t.co/SeCTy2WRW4 https://t.co/w4rccw6Tu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewbehar Also playing out at state level (working with project here in MA that prevents the 104 semi-independen… https://t.co/soFEdlnPQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris So just to be clear, this was NOT “an attempted modern day lynching”?  Asking for a friend.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NRO @KatTimpf All holidays are silly, but they serve a nice. cultural purpose..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ate so much seafood on this trip. No such thing is too much haha #cajun]]></document><document><![CDATA[You may be tempted to make jokes about the Robert Kraft soliciting charges today. Please remember that it allegedly… https://t.co/xvS9VAFK8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[That moment your bank ( @Chase ) makes you their valentine! 😍😍😍 https://t.co/2SwRPNWKNp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best believe I got even Tonight 😈  #LovinIncomeTaxSzn  Rhodes :1  Ditzy duckers :1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulmac708 The fugitive hands down him and tommy lee jones killed it together]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went for curry with my sweet amycornew .  Chettinad and Lababdar respectively!  Mighty spicy but oh so delicious, j… https://t.co/TTxKnK8GFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dragon’s Milk by @NewHollandBrew @ The Ski's Dugout — https://t.co/qHaevkzmgB]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite Photoshoots from 2 years ago! @allswagga   Beauty Photoshoot Bookings   💥Link N Bio 2 Book💥… https://t.co/YkGpzGVgCB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner Only the most stupid in his base......and about 75% of the media, can’t see this snake crawling up their arm.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you love a black man. Pray for him. These are dangerous times for us......]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess is like Prog Metal, idk, I can't believe Spotify has 3 songs from that game before it's even released.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepCummings @HouseDemocrats Thank you for your closing comments. That’s the kind of leadership you were sent to Wa… https://t.co/KNEfhkNL8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaraSewellTV @GregFieldsWX You never know when the come back will begin!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ewarren A real fundamental change would be to stop having babies out of wedlock and have the man disappear. Educat… https://t.co/35u15Gt09D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Offset- Father of 4: 8/10 Gunna- Drip or drown 2: 6.5/10 Lil Pump- Harverd Dropout: 5/10]]></document><document><![CDATA[NYC! Back home in the Big Apple! @ Times Square, New York City https://t.co/QEq6EBEdGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been setting up and rearranging my home studio like 10+ times. After days of writers block. I moved the last p… https://t.co/9qfUSE6kdy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvCoRadio Joey Porter and Mike Tomlin had the cops called at a high school football game check it out]]></document><document><![CDATA[buoyancy ... Water technology is buoyancy, rotation and energy ... without rival the basis of tomorrow's computer .… https://t.co/P5YkgKfgOB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul He needs to be removed now. The experiment of having a mentally ill reality TV star as President has concluded. It’s a failure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beard Trim  #changingthewayyouviewenergycompanies , #grindneverstops , #RM https://t.co/bUPFWqdZvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you attend a black church service, ONE gospel song will go through 7 modulations 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheTomBurkeShow A white man vouching that a white friend isn’t racist can never fly ( oxymoron?)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaleoPhil @PersuasionRisng @TheWooperNation I'm not a fan of using labels to dismiss people. Read Taleb on local f… https://t.co/avEMRySOgV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vintage Sterling Silver Art Deco Dog Wolf Brooch Pin Heart Love Howling Barking https://t.co/XbSnulcaoL via @eBay]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aegies Easily what Bayonetta did best was the dodge and parry mechanics (same as MGR:R too). Tilting the stick int… https://t.co/UvyjoqzuJF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TNTLEE34 😡🧞‍♀️😡teachers in California are striking now but they deserve what they get voting democrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is the frustrating part of Nassir Little... he'll have games like this and then you'll forget he's even on the… https://t.co/YYInHWemod]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiveStormsMedia @ABCWorldNews @CNNNewsource @TWCBreaking @NBCNightlyNews @FoxNews @Ginger_Zee @DanManWX… https://t.co/OxM030xMCA]]></document><document><![CDATA[How nick Perkins isn’t a starter is beyond me. Cuse would be a top 10 team with Perkins. I’m not kidding or exxager… https://t.co/NUup2DFA07]]></document><document><![CDATA[À toi seul que je demanderais « bonté, grâce, miséricorde et motivation »pour cette nouvelle journée. Je ne suis pa… https://t.co/M8LZCBbPYb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brie Larson is my favorite actress named after a soft cheese, followed closely by Camembert Zatapatique, the famous… https://t.co/xWSPgP2sTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carterwpage @MarkWarner @RepAdamSchiff @tribelaw @Harvard_Law @AlanDersh Republicans need to take their moral comp… https://t.co/mPaSWAKHZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone loved or hated Breakfast Club...   #deadlydetention #Netflix #Horror]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN you guys are a little behind. I haven’t heard you blame @realDonaldTrump for the Alabama tragedy. Not blaming… https://t.co/0scJgbFAFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NilWil72 Sold Gnabry for basically nothing....the list goes on and on for players that we let walk for free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[when Drake said, “some nights i wish i could go back in life, not to change shit, just to feel a couple things twice,” i felt that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It hurts. Prolly Mosley as well cause I can’t see the Ravens giving him 16 mil a year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 of #Stonewall National Education Conference. So much great learning, sharing, and radical love! ❤️🧡💛💚💙💜… https://t.co/PeXYmoJdpy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flowchainsensei Yup! All too often I see projects described as "bpm" projects or "sap" projects. Project named for… https://t.co/podP23NcjK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@codyblue_ Definitely keep my site current. One place to see all of who I am as a creator. Great looking site Cody! 👊🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity THIS NOTE is legA-L tender HEAVEN LegA-L Public And priVATE  For A-LL DEBTS heAv-EN LEg-A-L  question mark]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TDIH March 8, 1910 – Raymonde de Laroche, became first woman to earn a pilot's license. #InternationalWomensDay… https://t.co/iFyJv0XsWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hickory Valley Road in Heiskell currently one, but please be careful. Photo courtesy of Ginnie Stalvey. https://t.co/4IuAAJtC5G]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Phillies OF @dylancozens' .636 batting avg is currently tops in #MLB #SpringTraining. His 2.097 OPS also leads all of baseball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told crocodilegunnd that Nick Foles wouldn't get Franchise Tagged! We discuss it tonight on Quick Slants, 6-6:30!… https://t.co/7dVX24xkwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_the_believer @Samer_Kawash @brianjshay @fjdevereux @RobForsyth3 @shawnglinski @TomMonahan10 @GreaterLakesMkt Welc… https://t.co/WCMet8SCtH]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 more K's yesterday in a shorted game so the magic number is ⬇ to 81 for @LoganBryan19. Keep grinding it out my ma… https://t.co/xMtCVm5Ibw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiroTouch Future chiropractors need to get out there and shadow #mychirojourney]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoldenL That might have required more coordination than I am capable of.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bionicanadian @loveGoldenHeart @NoorioZehra @GoodScrolls @SemaCiel0101 @BabyGo2014 @jill_magnussen @TanRob22… https://t.co/J2hMOKc01w]]></document><document><![CDATA[“These people that are trying to separate us” -Jussie Smollet  Who exactly is actually doing this separating?]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #ufc opioid campaign is based on the collaboration with The Trump Administration edict.  Don’t think it’s going… https://t.co/8YMdH68PX4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Beverly Hills, California https://t.co/RicH17GMaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me when I introduce someone to @KaceyMusgraves and they come back to tell me how much they love her. https://t.co/j7yGDW9x7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had a great time at #TheRalphReportLIVE tonight! Great to see @RalphGarman, @eddiepence, @KariGarman, and… https://t.co/Cz5KRDrtU5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think it is pretty clear how Iran received it's Money to build it's Military. Barry Obama is to Blame. Keep a clo… https://t.co/mHE2VsuoDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Wildcats take down the top ranked Vols 86-69 in their first top 5 matchup   #BBN #weareuk #rupparena #SEC… https://t.co/GqeiGagryc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tina_schonbrodt The queen So much talent hard hard worker https://t.co/58eIcTIqZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Standards of humanity care and dignity are exceeded by these young men.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillHemmer Is Eddie Johnson, the police chief or is he running for election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mohoroski6 manny signs for $300M, i think the least i can do is buy last years BP hat (not mesh like this year’s)… https://t.co/J0sNswzolx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Soooo if I actually take this 3rd job on the weekends it’ll be for bucket list purposes only. But I’m really excited about it lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little @cielocycles with some @NoTubes and a touch of gold... think I matched #thebandit #transam… https://t.co/H4e6naaWmd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoastalOtter @VillalobosE @Carlosjostom @Iwori07 @ConsultaPara @PartidoMorenaMx @PRI_Nacional @AccionNacional… https://t.co/qPbSPooRXc]]></document></documents></author>