<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@adasomg @realDonaldTrump I’m very sorry to be the one to tell you this, but, there is no wall. Your cult leader, t… https://t.co/iJWsk00RJp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wku @caboni Hey @UofLPresNeeli I think you need to start your own cooking show. @uofl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HollyConrad My offer remains open should you  ever want to talk more about it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A couple weeks ago, I was honored to be 1 of 10 winners of the @Dodgers #DearJackie contest. James our tour guide m… https://t.co/IQGBCBKim4]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOW THIS GIVES MEALL THE FEELS!!   One of the reasons I create public art and #murals is because its creates a dial… https://t.co/2whr39Wl6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tasiajeffries I glanced at the pick and thought Noah was building another arc. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC @RashidaTlaib You’re violating the same rules she violated. Hopefully the House censures you both...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is pretty much all about eating... and when you’ll eat next 🤔 #eating]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FTFonFS1 @GottliebShow @getnickwright coming back from vacation to defend Lebron https://t.co/v50q2nX5T5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Backmarker Believe it’s the musings of a @gm designer.   Will need to do more research, but that’s most of the (as… https://t.co/tnaejvaw73]]></document><document><![CDATA[@derrick_ots Always to sides. Everybody with a story to tell may not be telling the truth.#Justice]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WakeMBB @jcollins20_ @CoachDManning I would be late if I didn't want to for Danny Manning. Bad sign. Players rebelling.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tinomabwe @ZANUPF_Official @Wamagaisa @ProfJNMoyo @DrVChimhutu @cdesetfree They are giving us something sounds lik… https://t.co/MFcmZRXBed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Madonna How did this resurface.... Is Madonna feeling like she need some more attention]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t let love play you like a fiddle. #valentinesday #HappyValentines #comedy #bathroomselfie https://t.co/JklvSN484w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Making the most of the snow in #Minnesota. #Saturday #Mood #GetOutside #Outdoors #Snow #Sledding #Family https://t.co/0DwaiZ5u4o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get your friends moving with @helbizofficial #Helbiz #HelbizGO https://t.co/DZgjxUfVFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImJonAbramson @LisaMarieBoothe Sorry, no. Use facts, not liberal talking points. The reason the MSM keeps getting… https://t.co/I48fpNwNUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doubledumbass @bionicbigfoot Fun fact. The folks in the video are not the real Vengaboys. They were basically avat… https://t.co/STTF5M44NY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Genderplasmic 🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️🤷🏾‍♂️ my childhood was gr8 n i don’t wanna invalidate those who DO experience ptsd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @CoachMerk_SHP to post 7 covers of books I love: no explanations, no reviews-just th… https://t.co/avISjkQi4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcfunny @VeritasEver That was rather cryptic. But the industry supports what you do in one way or another. If you… https://t.co/DnZuHOeyMm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamInTaunton @BOSsportsaddict Again he got handled by Jeremy Lin and Danny Green in a high profile late season gam… https://t.co/ZG0d4CUl4k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGuterman Babe Ruth promising a little boy in the hospital that he would hit 3 home runs for him and later sleep with his mother.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy day at #EMSToday. Lots of great conversations. Taking in the #JEMSGames at the moment. Good luck to all teams. https://t.co/PLO3XlzIgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dipndots32 @barstoolsports Man...every time someone makes a crazy throw people are itching to deepthroat Mahomes...its insane really]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @DonaldJTrumpJr You remind me of my idiot sister?  Let me guess you hated Hillary and Pres. Obama?  Do… https://t.co/fp4NuC18Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C_Blake05 Yeah I meant in terms of getting closer to locking up the two seed but good point on Houston. Ideal migh… https://t.co/QGFCpNzLXu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@32BHawkins @DanWolken @USATODAY If he went over seas and got seriously injured, he would be worth less than if his… https://t.co/Gk15LXGqzx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swishchee @renegade_roo @OKDoogl @CheetahObscura @KotanuCheetah @FireHazardCat PEOPLE.   We’re losing track of wha… https://t.co/1exeMcf3J9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFermtdFruit @OpusOneWinery @JMiquelWine @winewankers @KellyMitchell @DemiCassiani @onceuponawine_ @NapaVintners… https://t.co/5yUdMYeTjj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlexandriaKells Omfg I’m obsessed with u gonna post it once our video is live 🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorgeramosnews de univision retenido en #miraflores #venezuela #venezuelalibre @ Univision https://t.co/0wUnsOXgAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats @ItsRamiMalek much deserved @callychisholm97 #Oscars2019 #oscars let @QueenWillRock open each year and ski… https://t.co/uSdT8iu68R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeenMom Joe calling Kail a hypocrite just want work because you have to believe in GOD before you can be a hypocri… https://t.co/2rCAYAAgKv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulJournet Mais aussi ceci parce que Ron a toujours le bon mot ;) https://t.co/UNc6IcT2PF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DiamondandSilk @RepAOC Yes they have no place in government and if they don’t like it here leave!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coolest. College. Class. Ever!  Mike Leach to teach seminar titled 'Insurgent Warfare and Football Strategies' at W… https://t.co/a39dRGHn4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[About to watch @Mirvish Production of @DearEvanHansen at Royal Alexander Theatre in #Toronro with my date… https://t.co/KvRT2r7o4b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Al shrier was great friend to so many. He was temple. A throwback to other eras. He will be missed. There will neve… https://t.co/1uTC4Ersni]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Did you ever oncebtuink of not taxing their labor? Shut up commie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I will not lie.  Today has been the best day in 15 years for me.  Switching to economics was the bes… https://t.co/tpB89Hm7sc]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I apparently got a promotion at #work last October and I just found out today. That’s some #MondayMotivation for… https://t.co/6ViYjiJMDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I #StandWithTrudeau is one of the dumbest things I've ever seen in CDN politics .. the real hashtag should be… https://t.co/L10GhXGzwH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I cannot be alone in thinking that the only way to find a way to those 100 new @SIRIUSXM music channels is with a b… https://t.co/sxkgUD5fIt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaxGraham just introduced @_mohitarora to A Delicate Sound of Many. He stopped moving at 7:12 of track 1.  Don't worry. He is still alive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JUCOadvocate 🇨🇦 Ethan Passley aka E.T  ↕️5’10” GTA PREP Fletchers Meadow/Pas North  Brampton, Ontario 🇨🇦  https://t.co/8XbwNCZZG8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to this group on becoming State Champs! Was truly an honor to work with you all off season. Credit… https://t.co/pCClU8BZrK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChooSparky @Tesla Prepare to drive around with a silly grin stuck to your face.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraFluke @MoveOn @IndivisibleTeam @CREDOMobile @WinWithoutWar You should work u don’t deserve a holiday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gordon_hughes2 @markknoller @CivMilAir Well Trump had to rush home because after days of constipation he's finally… https://t.co/0Fq1IJgWLb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell Btw, did anyone else notice the Zombie in the background! ? 😲]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man hollll uppppp, this new gunnnnna.... my god. This is fire. https://t.co/UmIiVVK7Aw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilyNCali @realDonaldTrump @w_terrence @RealJamesWoods @TuckerCarlson And I bet his roommate would be just as nice… https://t.co/qJDkt95TMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two Morris goals and a season opening win immediately sets the tons (and takes some potential pressure away). Well done #Sounders! #ebfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer @dnc #DemocratDebateQuestions #DemocraticSocialism #DemocratsAreCorrupt… https://t.co/VSBeXdYAit]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s always about the money... the longer people live, the more they cost the government. Politicians like @AOC thi… https://t.co/1pone76lAT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PUMAGolf @RickieFowler Will additional colorways be coming out later this spring?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ulisesjaitt @Pilarsmith Policia de PBA, Walter Daniel Román, desafectado de la fuerza por tomar fotos de Natacha J… https://t.co/399CsSEHDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You keep bring up collusion but remember you have committed crimes that’s what they are going afte… https://t.co/ZvBbdRkR3a]]></document><document><![CDATA[my dad, desperate for me to drive, booked 2 rooms for a cruise in 2020 that i will only be allowed to go on if i get my license before then.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Susan_Hennessey Bill Haley seemed cool until the kids got a load of Elvis, Chuck Berry, Jerry Lee, Little Richard.… https://t.co/iPJ0IxWA9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Like OOH-AHH by TWICE on Apple Music. #kpop #dancepop https://t.co/55TqyJuU2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Pre-Order My Song In The ITunes App Y’all!! 🥰❤️ https://t.co/MrMPfgyyet]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dark Reckoning ••• Imperial Porter ••• Baltic-style ••• 8.0% ••• IBU: 30 ••• Intense flavors of toffee, dark fruit,… https://t.co/ZWr5H1U3GL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me bajo del camion como sin nada en manga corta a -1° me va a cargar el payaso cuando regrese a Monterrey]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is college: 1:58 AM and FINALLY laying down in bed but still not done school work. so alarm is set for 7AM do… https://t.co/ia1lsrSK2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spot - Your Inner Circle by Shenzhen That Technology Co., Ltd. https://t.co/lK8aYkDWGp @Mapbox https://t.co/QikikhqpEd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau @MarcGarneau @NavdeepSBains @KirstyDuncanMP @Astro_Jeremy @csa_asc 🖕Hope you enjoy being unemployed come October.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A lot of winners been through the halls of Valley Heights High School.  On an unrelated note, I went to VHHS also.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jen_keesmaat England is an example of public transit perfection. If Canadians could arrive on any corner in Canada… https://t.co/0EykHP0zQq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yep folks this just confirms the D in Democrat stands for DEATH.   They really are a DEPLORABLE GROUP OF POLITICIAN… https://t.co/zBxZbbMChs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyHerren I have watched BB since the start and I barely remember anyone. I do remember you because you remind tw… https://t.co/pUhsNrUEgh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JulieDiCaro @crawlyscubs @BleacherJeff @ChiTownSports @EntitledCubsFan Julie may have been born at night. But it w… https://t.co/1q83XXb71h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WMTFT2016 @JerryFalwellJr That's @GOP's hypocrisy. Digging their own grave! They're also theocrats like Sharia pol… https://t.co/Xdr1sx78ee]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going from being the garden variety pedo and perv right to sex trafficking. Maybe @AlanDersh needs a client...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JCaporoso Mac is a lot like my wife. Great at spending money but can’t pick anything right!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briandelancey @AP_Oddities @AP Found a really great place on Frenchman. Beautiful city; absolutely love New Orleans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Yum-Yum Donuts #42 in Beaumont, CA w/ @pstowncar @latowncar https://t.co/AEu0mSwSP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spending my Friday night doing required sexual harassment training for work. According to this u should ask before… https://t.co/f44YBdK3sj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me eating my last meal waiting for the snow to come in https://t.co/anSMKjk89E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABREG_1 @marwinGF9 So he’ll be back in 2 years. https://t.co/Y7a86qaez4]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are in @soflinfo summer games had lots of fun dudes! We are proud so much bro and I have it makes so well. Then… https://t.co/eR5fups6wU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol... Of course like when you become a fashion Icon you gone be im Just a kid from Chi town... Illinois]]></document><document><![CDATA[The meme where I’m turning around to look at Omar and AOC is angry at me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iam_rg4 I gotchu. I guess I’m a Michigan fan willing to own up to it. MSU was the better team in both meetings this year.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adding to my collection of dubious service animals in Seattle, I saw a service dog at Wintergrass... that was in a… https://t.co/ix1rABcpo0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaniC80 @kvngchoch @TheRealCordova @DrewSpurling1 @BrandonDawe_ @chriskc510 @JeffGohn77 @stephenasmith @steelers N… https://t.co/ca9SjaJhNJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @RepMikeTurner You hide behind the collusion farce!! You won’t be hiding behind this for much long… https://t.co/b7Qqv6uvvt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_stevensCT @michael__rg @antonionicks16 And I was the first so blow me motherfuckers that are skinnier then m… https://t.co/aYrbY3GUf5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cutest baby in the world! @ Rudy's "Country Store" and Bar-B-Q https://t.co/2muZGj7Ee8]]></document><document><![CDATA[“And now, just as you accepted Christ Jesus as your Lord, you must continue to follow him.” Colossians 2:6 NLT https://t.co/UkHZBSWz9S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders I am so excited @BernieSanders is in the race.  Pushing the Demorats waaayyyyy too the left.  It's g… https://t.co/FdfzwBaj99]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gabrielzamora gabs, just ran into a guy wearing your merch at a bar, tweeting this from 6ft under cause I died ✨]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fastest girlfriends ever.  #halfmarathon #runners #speedy #runchat #fastest https://t.co/gK7M6EBHwR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe one form of this would be to divorce the almanac from its annual cycle and to just change the scale and frequ… https://t.co/YcwF54PqVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThinkforOnce @RealMattCouch Actually they did. They are. And I haven’t seen a confederate flag at a Trump rally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarkOmenClub @Wizards_DnD Look at @jssc85 that's one sexy nerd! 🤓 And a hot cameo by @marroyo1325 🎲]]></document><document><![CDATA[@theferocity Remember when Black History Month made our skin feel richer? Ive been ashy everyday this month https://t.co/0hsKn0NEkf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tgradous @politicalelle @FDRLST It's also typical that the members of the Black Hypocrite Caucus have never once v… https://t.co/F4t9nheB9Z]]></document></documents></author>