<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Packed all my stuff to go to the gym after work...except my shoes 🤦🏻‍♀️ guess I’m not going today]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyaRBlue1 @DavidDiehl20 @RoverDov123 @petergraigs @kdubhitcountry @highwaypaynet @KFearri @ebkdog2507… https://t.co/Pzby4crC6Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Best of all a shared life can give!! Enjoy this day above all else]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IshovelU @malibuleslie @OrenIShiKiddo @Chrisstto12 Funny how that question (as you would say) s (people) tfu. Shuts people the fuck up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SalVulcano @nikestore @Nike @nikesportswear That’s just crazy $400 dollars for Pants! https://t.co/HF39OtZBrY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else can’t wait for @treefortfest? 💙  #treefort2019 #musicfestival  #ILoveTreefort #Boise https://t.co/Gmjw4dXq7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[We now have even more pre-rolls options! 1 gram/150mg of CBD each! Stop by today! 1921 North Pointe Drive Suite 110… https://t.co/dgXMpp1Ws3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smithton_m @gbroh10 @rep To show her disinterest in the importance of the affairs of the govt.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We guessed it right from the first episode!!!! @realjoeyfatone #themaskedsinger]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KaceyWhite59 saw you from far away today. Didn’t want to interrupt your conversations after the game, but wanted to say hey 👋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone is freaking out about galaxies and maybe there’s more people out there but I just wonder if there’s a plan… https://t.co/sJWq7idfaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love love love when my man sees a cute lil baby, gets all excited and says “babe look at the baby!!!”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Julia- Randy calls me baby or bb, Karie calls me sister or sissy bear, my mom and Abby call me Jules, my nieces and… https://t.co/zrs4kEKrmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants.  - Karl Lagerfeld… https://t.co/egg1y9oFZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello Twitter, a week from today, I will be sitting in The Tonight Show audience. 🌙  I’ve only been waiting a decade, nbd.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder We must realize the mindsets of Gaetz  Jordan  and meadows. If Hitler's soldiers didn't protect the boss an… https://t.co/b3i7yAjdvj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DantRagee One time I had to sit and listen to why it wasn’t ok for girls to wear pants to church. Oh and also why… https://t.co/qbrUxlP0oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnderwaterMommy @ruthbadergins Same 😭😭😭💕💕💕 she is tough as nails but it’s too great a load.]]></document><document><![CDATA[THIS!! 💙 “We rise by lifting others”  Let’s all LIFT someone up today!!  @ifireup @CottoneMegan @Syndee_Sue… https://t.co/g7YriMrohq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiest of Birthdays Coach D!!! 2019 is your year! We are all blessed by you and your life is a gift from God!!… https://t.co/ninHCpoivV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @GaetanosTavern on Main in Wallingford, CT https://t.co/QpleSqRhUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Just more psychological projection, deflection, distraction, doublespeak, and groupthink! 🤪🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NationalEmergencyDiary We had red beans and rice tonight. Not because we were out of provisions, but because we li… https://t.co/Sj2g3irDpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wanna go see Florida Georgia Line but $80 for one ticket is ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCChicagoMed Yes. Ethan finally acknowledges he still loves April.  #WillCouldHaveBeenThisCourageous… https://t.co/U2i8u9Jjh9]]></document><document><![CDATA[You guys I finally get to see @ellamai tomorrow night 😭❤️ I have been waiting for this since I got the tickets in October]]></document><document><![CDATA[En pocos sitios de EEUU se puede gritar “¡Viva Palestina libre!” o criticar la “deshumanización de los palestinos”… https://t.co/Ca4E6g96in]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOnlyDJQualls Yup. I struggle everyday to eat the minimum. But one good thing, I gained back 6 pounds since starting my fight! 😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[...bad bc I’m too competitive with other women but good bc I’d be there all the time...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Janelle’s in the situation she’s in because of her husband. It’s not anyone else’s fault. MTV didn’t make David say… https://t.co/e0lQH74JaJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFHShive @freeporthockey @davidgaspersic Thank you @TheFHShive for you unwavering support this season. You guys… https://t.co/7B6WTtbY2T]]></document><document><![CDATA[I swear @russdiemon you never disappoint my song cravings 😭❤️ I fucken love you! ❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cultivar la atención es un arte. La meditación y el ejercicio físico pueden ayudarte. #22feb #emprender… https://t.co/8rzbuYzpP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like I have to vent a little bit about the things I have been feeling. It’s crazy cause I never would have t… https://t.co/XsiDd7U5Fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IMFprattMYELOMA Wishing you much success with the walk and your fight over myeloma. From fellow #MyelomaWarrior]]></document><document><![CDATA[ACCESS for ELL 2.0 testing is here. Our @SaludaHigh #ELLS are beginning @WIDAConsortium speaking today. I've got co… https://t.co/Cp9n4xce2G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@big_business_ First it was soft titty Big Cass. Now it's a married with CTE Corey Graves... Somebody gotta help Ca… https://t.co/iUhk12qAeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I voted #StrikesMakeChange on @TheTylt. Teachers are trying to preserve the soul of public education–the time for c… https://t.co/LfhQ8M6t7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Add me guys!!   #snapchatfilters #snapchat #follow #snapchats #selfie #f #like #snapchatfilter #snapchatfun #cute… https://t.co/xWM3yLdFfN]]></document><document><![CDATA[(John testified concerning him. He cried out, saying, "This is the one I spoke about when I said, 'He who comes aft… https://t.co/c6fBA9452c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilywagenbren1 Maybe we should look at this differently. Why would you want to celebrate diversity in a classroom? #4000ch2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a Beautiful Saturday! @willylevy29 @WLWCalifornia @WLW_Florida @WLW_Slovakia @wlwrepdom @WLWPuertoRico… https://t.co/ad7AMs2974]]></document><document><![CDATA[No one’s scared of you girl stfu anger issues doesnt mean you have hands 🤪🤪🤪]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was always told “when ya done, you’ll be done”. Ayyy, that hit me and I was like “yoooooooooooooooo”]]></document><document><![CDATA[LGBTQ fans of @HBO series #GameofThrones have been left disappointed by a new competition which encourages viewers… https://t.co/9QrU2ueSPU]]></document><document><![CDATA[In all my 20 years of life I have never gotten cramps as bad as these motherfuckers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite @target is going through a renovation and it’s like I don’t even know who I’m married to anymore. #target]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rip to @LukePerryIII  , I actually watched the ild 90210. Loved him before #RiverdaleCW . Un the less my heart goes out to his family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WamboltAustyn Instantly heard you screaming canela when we were hunting😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Left picture was one year ago (on the 18th of March) . Right is today March 7th.  It fucking blows my mind that I d… https://t.co/LHwd5SH6dR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: I need to go grocery shopping before the weather gets bad.  Also me: https://t.co/D7pbCQYdkJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamkevingates a lot of *people say shit they don’t mean out of being hurt — not jus men]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever my bf goes out and I stay home, he invariably comes home to me, slightly wine drunk, singing along to nost… https://t.co/KI9Sjm2u5y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @KokeReport I am for free speech however one Congresswoman has taken it to the point of sedition. Unaccep… https://t.co/PkIy027P4j]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week I am most proud that my phone autocorrects “talk” to “y’all”. Very on my Southern introvert brand.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump They can't except the fact that you Won ! #sorelosers #MAGA2020 🇺🇸🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[This should be the subject line of every email from Emerson College School for Memes https://t.co/It7QBD2fkD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MySelfAndHeize @Jmjkboyfriends_ @BTS_twt Nothing is impossible, just be positive and focus your mind in that, and… https://t.co/xirD8fD4Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks interesting for those wondering how Twitter can help with #professionaldevelopment #edusp19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerryDNY Thanks Jerry! I am feeling much better than last week! Stay warm today 🌬]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW DETAILS: One man is dead this morning after attacking and stabbing his brother with a knife and ignoring office… https://t.co/TAxBg8egml]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GraigKreindler @PhilHecken @nlbmprez @yaquis_oficial @LMPbeisbol I sure do miss Buck.  He was such a great spokesman for baseball!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creo que coger a las 6 am no fue buena idea.   Ya voy estúpidamente tarde al trabajo.   Patrocinado también por el… https://t.co/n7PB3GLsIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting w/ our local #highschool teachers about our Young Civic Leaders Academy! Thank you @pylusd @ylhigh… https://t.co/JYcYWS0QVG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starstrickenSF I love the #Cosmos and plan on visiting someday!  Fantastic Capture Sarafina!  Many #Galactic Kudos… https://t.co/x9UrWshs3u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonahhcarlson The other 10 moderate white guys can also have several seats.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girl you know I'm ready for that Mariah Carey inspired makeup look!🦋💫 @stillGLAMORUS]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4p8sEXtVnv  Amazon Phone Number runs round the clock 1-855-431-5111   #amazonphonenumber]]></document><document><![CDATA[@STXsashi @cvpayne Give it a teeeny bit of brainpower if you have it; Why do you thinik so many black people suppor… https://t.co/TnhQetWYBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[About yesterday... Book signing in ATL...it was simply amazing.. I am apart of an awesome book “Your Child My Stude… https://t.co/yVtYPZ8yvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanPantz I want to see the .50 if no RS needed than this could organcially run to $4 to uplist to Nasdaq which is… https://t.co/GGXKCR6DU7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister You look wonderful together! 💕 Let’s heat it for love on Valentine’s Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KCrossling3 @OssiningSchools @OssiningSup @IDODI This is #OPride at its finest! We have dedicated kids, parents, and volunteers! 👏👏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking out at a full room bright and early in Chicago as @AILAExecDir, @immcouncil ED, @marketalindt and I kick of… https://t.co/bKSQHnu8N9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lauradistefan10 @netnarr @helterskelliter @alexsaum Yes! I will make sure you receive the link when we set up.👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JussieSmollett You must be scared. No one goes off like this unless they are worried they did something wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JovannySaavedra is so offended that I retweeted this. Lmao https://t.co/rJNYFKikei]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brothersosborne It's true!  I say it all the time! Like prisoners, why don't they get cancers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just took a one hour nap with my golden retriever 🥰 happy Galentine’s day to us!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BronyBurningAxe Or, if yer someone like me, an intellectual: Ship Appreciation Day❤️🧡💛💚💙💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chief B tracking some gusty winds and rain. Check out his forecast at 11 on when to expect it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Red the new color #love #followback #instagramers #envywear #tweegram #photooftheday #20likes #amazing #smile… https://t.co/Nb5BtWSJmZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump President Trump will always put President Trump first. Wake up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mickelle_8 But then there’s the fact that horchata and basura don’t even rhyme or sound right at all. But idk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IndivisibleNet Honey, don't you think it's just a bit too much/ Afterall, we're just hanging out at home.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr  FAKE DEMS - Casting Call to Play a Part in our US Government (House or Senate) AM… https://t.co/Brz1cxB19R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will never understand people who make their own lives hard. Like what’s the logic behind that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@starkindxstries @marianatmel Yeah I stop and turn around. Don't have any saved memes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/7ptIhlT8pU @hinclusion Great EdCamp opportunity! https://t.co/dQNTES55oP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@justintarte @hwschoolssuper Excellent comments here from teachers in the trenches for everyone to consider.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If my parents would sell us their house I think we would move back home. I’m obsessed w their house 🏡]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is so transparent, “I haven’t finalized my decision” translates to I’m voting part lines but don’t want the bac… https://t.co/VT2WTytQ7Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my classroom on @DonorsChoose! I'd love your help to bring my project to life:  https://t.co/uzzuStRlq6 D… https://t.co/vbCIBqJyQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life is normal to the people around me, However, to me,  my husbands death is still a great loss...felt extremely d… https://t.co/6UjUtk9W3J]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶🎵🎶#meimeiXchi . . . . . . . . . #streetstyle #currentlywearing #winterfashion #bloggerstyle #fashionblogger… https://t.co/Hvyf3U6hPf]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Air with Ryan wants to send your family on vacation with $10,000, thanks to the Capital One® Venture® card. Ente… https://t.co/dlmeUBchwL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, just out of curiosity @POTUS WHY THE FUCK IS @officialjaden bringing water to #flint? Why aren’t you? You know… https://t.co/xH72SoDXxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanHillMI @realDonaldTrump @FoxNews Propaganda? Does anyone really need to ask?  They reported the 2 biggest, stu… https://t.co/1RN8MwIImr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow SHINE is available on all music streaming platforms ⭐️ • You can still pre-save on Spotify! #linkinbio . .… https://t.co/1onERkBIGw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Me thinks the past president was responsible for the kids in cages first and foremos… https://t.co/6lrrEkVzAr]]></document></documents></author>