<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Marlon Wayans on Tupac saying on how they were boys and hung together but there were times he just didn't hang with… https://t.co/M107goxvt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Burnt toast and coffee time... (Borrowed from a friend) @ Mount Pleasant, South Carolina https://t.co/rSZK4MEUMK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch If they win this than the families of every person to die of a heart attack should sue McDonalds]]></document><document><![CDATA[mad confused why everyone had black shit on their foreheads till now lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenCurry30 @warriors @WarriorsTalk @LetsGoWarriors @DubNation_247 @DidTheWarriorsW we are Golden state warrior… https://t.co/DSU86e7UC4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner Experiment #1701 ... Crustless #Pizza. sullifarmandkitchen beed + lickcreekmeats pork sausage "crust". Mozza… https://t.co/t93t8KDjZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corey LaJoie once again brings out the early problems in the #DAYTONA500. It's a right front tire that went down an… https://t.co/8vkzEnYO5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@NDSUfootball QB Easton Stick, when I asked what he will bring to an NFL team: “I’ve been fortunate to learn the p… https://t.co/ZnvE6bNCKe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lol @JesseBWatters wants a job on campaign. Only lie this often when looking for employment. Get h… https://t.co/W4ilcoRQ2V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HardenRoger @Kybballking Missed being able to follow your tweets recently... appreciate your input as a former Cat… https://t.co/qqGlAuryGM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir And don’t forget the airplanes! Now all we need is a Mac and cheese bar in the admirals club https://t.co/6elpzWr6Na]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @realDonaldTrump @Jim_Jordan @FoxNews Ha Ha.... he is not Mr Mueller. Tick Tock !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pytash21 These men have gotten so soft and weak. I would return that shit a diss her ass. People need to stop 🛑 pl… https://t.co/16Z1wfEIy5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My brother @_CoachDT challenged me to post pics of my 7 favorite books, no reviews needed. Each day I'll challenge… https://t.co/GB5QqWqej2]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Beverly Wilshire Hotel in Beverly Hills, CA https://t.co/JNYJxFBRfB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays Peer-Reviewed Survey Finds Majority Of Scientists Skeptical Of Global Warming Crisis via @forbes https://t.co/oDIFgtoZxH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bet or hope she gets a favorable status and screw you ever even more and the theft of my americant vote]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimmy_coppa @NYGDaily Because he fucking sucks and he’s making 23 million..... they have no problem paying a dude… https://t.co/UWRllOcHdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don't hold me, If you don't mean it. 'Cause I'm tired of waistin' my time on things set on leavin'. 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardiffGarcia @TimDuy Very true, in fact LEI hasn't even gone into its decline stage yet. Also, we have a lot goin… https://t.co/5eAmjNPnlg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probably one of the craziest dinner parties we've had. Lots of amazing laughs and overall a great dinner at Lola's. https://t.co/i6fRnuSrVJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone investigate mueller &amp; his team for collusion &amp; abuse of power]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RJMersereau What are your top prospects for draft picks ?? #hahahockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iron_lombardi @Mel_the_geek @HillaryWarnedUs @HillaryClinton I don't see how dems can want open boarders if Obama… https://t.co/5PKytDRhAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re a juvenile, getting paid by @Nike to wear their gear while playing a sport is fine. Adults getting paid t… https://t.co/AE5Vn1oQcD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pound for pound, Steve Cropper, Al Jackson, Jr., and Donald "Duck" Dunn might've given me more pleasure than any ot… https://t.co/57pgUpmoOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto I’m more of a Yellow Submarine and 20,000 Leagues Under The Sea man myself. https://t.co/VVmaD2biDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ErinBlewett1 wrote my favorite article for our Feb. issue of Kensington Voice. Check it out here:  Fifty years aft… https://t.co/HRqHEpWALK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @IngrahamAngle Great job last nigh Dan on the @IngrahamAngle. The democrat on their proves that #TDS is real.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevinGOATBooker @AndrewLeezus @Suns Cant argue with him. Its literally in his @]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCOUT @NYCSpeakerCoJo @tfitzsimons My medicine is over 3 grand a month. Horrible.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lentil and brown rice soup—and The Cramps for supper. https://t.co/u96zEd2RQa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t wait, Call today for your preapproval!  #mortgagelender #mortgage #homebuyer #realestate  #firsttimehomebuyer… https://t.co/YCPACQ4zBY]]></document><document><![CDATA[hi @taylornation13 guess who took a big step and lives in LA now!! 🙋🏻‍♂️ (missing your mom is torture fyi)  Hope y’… https://t.co/RIeNogjWO4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler Bette, Love you 😍 but you are so negitive💤⏬Tell us what you do like➕In my opinion it’s time to change… https://t.co/TJIcsGWv3U]]></document><document><![CDATA[We teach girls to shrink themselves To make themselves smaller We say to girls "You can have ambition But not too m… https://t.co/xE7C3OrsRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WildByNature94 Well I’m going to give this one to you. In 1966 there was a draft and many young people of the time… https://t.co/SUeYPcfYrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's nice of you to tweet this, since you seem to have left too quickly to say so in person. Tweet… https://t.co/rFmpp9HDmv]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. Cal. Ocean Grown Crew One Impeach Trump &amp; prosecute, now! ☯️☮️💛💚💙! https://t.co/qG9gR27srH]]></document><document><![CDATA[All my friends in my rave “fam” are 21+ and I’m here being stupid pointless age of 20 not being able to go :/ I gue… https://t.co/5U1ORy5CvJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[For dreamers; aka #Knicks fans to, in advance, blame #Dolan in the event FAs don’t come...  Are skimming over 271 l… https://t.co/la1y6LXQqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[J'ai joué à la machine Britney Spears et c'était grave stylé 🔥😂 #lasvegas https://t.co/9X0AhLa46l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MVivant @fernandeznorona Jajaha. Ese @fernandeznorona se me hace que es uno de esos viejos con esquizofrenia, que… https://t.co/XhIkxMwfi8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TripleH are you ready I said are you ready for Bailey and Sasha to win the tag team champions and we won’t have it… https://t.co/KHUh3EBqJK]]></document><document><![CDATA[And we’re back.... @ Royal Caribbean International https://t.co/68OKj3oAdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[ז [Zaʹyin]   With the mention of the abundance of your goodness they will bubble over, And [because of] your righte… https://t.co/yDiwMugWgA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Devinrios23 @stanley_alvey @Devinrios23 honey, I meant that about @stanley_alvey lol I’m not talking about me 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LyndaLoveland @WRALKathryn @alamb @RupintaABC11 @BGibbsABC11 @tleew @JulieABC11 are just a few of wonderful ladie… https://t.co/JxG2W2qa0D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@L0velyMissJenn Yup, yesterday. A little sore today but otherwise not bad. 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ponysmasher I don’t want a new trailer, I just wanna go ahead and buy tickets :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MuseZack Actually the 30th AND 31st. Captain Marvel starts this in a week or so and will be quickly followed by ENDGAME]]></document><document><![CDATA[Been waiting on this fight, catching up on some boxing 🥊 #AHHYEAHH #degaleeubankjr #london #england #boxing @ Everg… https://t.co/Z0ge6LfU59]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ucf_problems @Fam2412 @UCF_Knightline @KIsrael07 @predatorsorl @UCF_Football @UCF_FB_Facts @UCFKnightsNatn Don't need it, still don't.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#snowday #hellskitchen #skyriseliving #keepingwarm #workingfromhome @ Sky https://t.co/w9oPWEbDSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuffyvDarkangel @ACirillo21 @GavinNewsom You don't even live in the U.S fuck off lmfao.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelENewton1 @benshapiro Question: “Why should you have more than I do?”  Answer: “Because I worked hard for it… https://t.co/DkHUaFHSEn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout out to my man @brenthatley from my beloved @sternshow for being part of what May finally bring Tucker Carlson… https://t.co/ovsW11czvf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@baereirei @troxler_jackson @Outlaws My guess is with burst damage, it all hits at the same time. So it would destr… https://t.co/6QjiJpZaZg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormiAguilera5 Muy buenas noches 😘🌙💤😴 Norma y que descanse saludos cordiales y hasta mañana,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amanda_mfd Words don’t work at times like this. So sorry to hear of your loss.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is a really good Accounting and Pre-Calculus professor? #ASUTwitter #ASU19 #ASU20 #ASU21]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd check in for this beer. A bit sweet. Light for a scotch ale, - Drinking a Scottish Terrier Ale by @leaningcask… https://t.co/tlg9MvWYRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you sit on a plane for over an hour waiting to take off...and get a notification your connection is boarding b… https://t.co/ehIOH1Nw1C]]></document><document><![CDATA[What eponym is used for the plump macrophages with chromatin that often condenses into slender wavy ribbons that ar… https://t.co/Dji84Qu3lC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @GhostOfTick @GreekVikingX @Lo_Gannicus @Hybrid1979 @r0xie_f0x @BertJ4411 @dgvreiman @CoachforPOTUS… https://t.co/UEoR4GbkjZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelionlogos Genesis 3:22 “And the LORD God said, Behold, the man is become as one of us, to know good and evil: a… https://t.co/W8aKwNnLUO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@suniaa @RealSaavedra @realDailyWire People did not like the government telling doctors what to do when it comes to… https://t.co/rZRi5Tl8Ls]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday Mika!!!!!  #brothersforlife @ Wknd Hang Suite https://t.co/eaaNtCqpOO]]></document><document><![CDATA[39 years ago today.  Feb. 22, 1980.  Where were you when the #Miracle took place? #miracleonice #lakeplacid… https://t.co/u2DmC6zg24]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SRuhle @rickwtyler I’m sure this has been noted but I wonder if Trump would have the sense and compassion to go to… https://t.co/7jJPK4MaGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Crew96 is undefeated in the preseason and now it's for the regular season]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerOsborne2 Considering it’s a 1 in 6 chance per box, 3 gives you a 50% chance. Fingers crossed for ya! 🤞🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaydenThaRippa They probably do have a better grasp on real life issues than AOC does though I’ll give you that .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got my new Jo Sonja’s paints in today from Chroma. Can’t wait to start laying these paints in some decoys. @ Greene… https://t.co/XxNZGV6Rzc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight is the night! Join me at @MidwayonHigh where I'll be performing live.  Special thanks to socialcircle614 fo… https://t.co/suVaQY2hVv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck to the Gorham Track athletes competing at the New England Championships today at the Reggie Lewis Center!! #gorams]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarah_K_Hopkins @BrianWHopkins Doesn’t LK play soccer ? https://t.co/by1cPogYn9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamfgoldberg Digital Derby????  Where did you find that????  You're my toy collecting hero!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @POTUS @AmbJohnBolton  Costume parade in Spain...reveals our deepest needs...we appreciate all actions… https://t.co/ahGoMnXfL8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS @donlemoncnnnews  Trump have proven and showed he can b… https://t.co/xT4BrjjVpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ANiceGuy96 @ghutchins97 Now GeorgePatrick......Why are you tweeting me? Nobody asked you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PrttyOddVariety I'm so greasy I'm starting to look like the white version of Pete Wentz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_Lee_Cal @DallasWoodhouse @NCGOP @GOP Common sense says it is nearly impossible to know if voter fraud by ind… https://t.co/FovrZ3VjPB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jasafella @ComoNTvoyAKerer 😳😳😳😳violando recién nacidos??😳😳😳😳😔😔😔😔😔😔😔que Dios lo perdone, yo no puedo😔😔😔😔😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[A few pictures of this absolutely beautiful theater, built in 1909, and I just had a wonderful tour with the… https://t.co/Xg5xPzkDeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LannyDavis @jaketapper @RepMattGaetz And I’m paying for this craziness]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WorldHistTess @TheDemocrats I live in a swamp and we ain't got no progress round here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday I nearly bought tickets to a Burner party that’s tonight. I went two years ago and had a tremendous time.… https://t.co/Zg48dMF25K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItsJustRaleigh @AGoldFan @TheRealJaiKumar I mean....nothing stops anyone from making a high-quality Black/red/whit… https://t.co/UEuiIiuZZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My favorite brunch partners @ Cracker Barrel Old Country Store https://t.co/stmg8LJKAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markchappelle I was so excited to see the red-toned, goth artwork I saw online prior to the album’s release. Then… https://t.co/6wSX8NlaFF]]></document><document><![CDATA[How to use Facebook Messenger bots ft. @jamesonwhiskey &amp; @lyft #SocialMedia #SMM https://t.co/0TUgQVMYoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI — Agostini: Changes ahead for season-ending wrestling meets. Home run or foul ball? - Front Row Sports https://t.co/afVRstkRD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Satosky24 @maximitodiaz @jorgebrahma2 @JromanJuanroman para mejorar los tiros libres lo primero es conseguir un ps… https://t.co/a02c4AtjNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well, you and me? We might have an issue if your dad decides not to give you to me. @ Estes National Park https://t.co/UiuEt9oriZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zero_deuce @gmfb @PSchrags That’s not his point tho. His first point it that this is Keim’s decision not KK’s. And… https://t.co/LTugZvieT3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just booked my return trip back to Chicago! Taking the amtrack across the country. Not looking forward to 35 hours… https://t.co/z6XXCIynVS]]></document><document><![CDATA[People will try to check up on you and speak dirt on ya name , y’all funny lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joncoopertweets @TheDemCoalition That does not Mean Shit to his Zombies! Not a damn thing!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I love Target, they have great stuff” - @ImAngelaBassett. Guys, the Queen of Wakanda is just like us.]]></document></documents></author>