<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[That's still very tempting. However, it would probably be way too much of a distraction. I won't even allow myself… https://t.co/SrJWQpndXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Need something to get you over #HumpDay come to your nearest @stlmattress and start sleeping better for the guarant… https://t.co/0o3tGrHv0Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m gonna put in to photograph a show. Who wants photographed? OR Who do you want me to photograph?]]></document><document><![CDATA[What idiot schedules an 8:30 AM dental appointment the day after the Daylight Saving Time Change? This idiot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@john9williams @JoeyIckes Agreed. But my point is this has the potential to go bad in terms of feels]]></document><document><![CDATA[So everyone who is acting like nobody knew about Warwick's financial woes, I have been sounding alarm for...15 year… https://t.co/6MNLunZWR3]]></document><document><![CDATA[The only national emergency is Trump’s rogue action to fund his unnecessary, unwanted border wall and Congress lack… https://t.co/URc8bOEOLR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLB No. Washington was much better, with far superior pitching, plus Harper and still didn’t win. Stop all the crazy hype crap.]]></document><document><![CDATA[An anthropologist explains the concept of 'language denialism'  https://t.co/JeLDUX1Poc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mzrsd @dmt4mt @Tom_Winter @GaryGrumbach Cool. So what do you know about the FARA Act, and why aren't the Podestas… https://t.co/QtmAsNU7EG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an awesome shot of Norman OK aka old stomping grounds. 😆 Great view of the stadium, which makes me ready for f… https://t.co/ooEFukLoVn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@notch @intheMatrixxx @Obtusewindow @POTUS Are We Having Fun Yet https://t.co/tnZUY7gO2U]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s 50/50 when rebuilding trust in a relationship and you on the better half of 10 rn FOH. Doesn’t even make any sence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost About the same percentage as New Yorkers.  Include Warren Wilhelm Jr. on list of #foolsfakesandfrauds and worse.]]></document><document><![CDATA[James Clyburn: Ilhan Omar's Life Experience More Powerful Than Children of Holocaust Survivors - The Political Insi… https://t.co/0c7haFy8P4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Speaking @SXSW about Autism and they are SURE not Autism Friendly!!😡😡😡😡😡 #SXSW #SXSW19]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Dangchick1 Glass prison cellar where anyone can walk up to point and laugh and watch as he is tarred and feathered… https://t.co/RJ6FXGTo7J]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve noticed a big turn in sentiment toward the Jussie situation. Is this only due to that article with two unnamed… https://t.co/0e37lmC1S2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chad Johnson was a character. Had spunk and attitude, but cant deny he  is a good dude. More proof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SirLanceWoods @FloydMayweather That’s a masterpiece. Making us wait to see your scarf game to build suspense. Beautiful!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrenHardaway I’ve never tried with egg. Brutal filters work though. Gotta do it several (like 5) times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤓🤓🤓studying . #followforfollowback #following💞 #follow4like #follow_me #followersinstagram #trending #facebook… https://t.co/Ha1aAQ2hA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[What size home can you afford? A look at how much house you can buy for $200,000 in each state.  #Oklahoma… https://t.co/rEMhClPxLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[The end of a season is rarely easy. The end of this one has been one of the hardest. It would be easy to focus on t… https://t.co/dyUdR9Kf0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrueAme12118111 Very Alarming: Boss of the Swamp says "Something ain't right" If you’re not concerned you should b… https://t.co/PWtLY52Ay2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landed in Cali. Next stop, Hawaii 🏝🌺 @ Los Angeles, California https://t.co/RjjYqjgWDs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOVTWINE The Great Negotiator, my ASS! He couldn't negotiate his way out of a soggy paper bag! Winning?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t scratch Teddy Blueger is the moral of the story. Pens take a 2-1 lead thanks to the rook.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chantoeknee Nah I still do lol but I also read most of the comics, haven’t kept up lately with reading the actual comic vs issue synopsis]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting work in with @bferguson50 before the @TheChrisRubio camp in Los Angeles this weekend. 😎#TheFactory… https://t.co/aNT0ZAqrGC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Follow me at Open House today as I show you why you should be a #WrightState Raider. https://t.co/RzR8A5HBrP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume Van Jones will turn on conservatives in a heartbeat. Thank him for these comments and show him the door.… https://t.co/FgHXFsFjoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaddyFiles @TomiLahren @realDonaldTrump When do we get to dispose of you? https://t.co/mtfDIq4zmE]]></document><document><![CDATA[An offering of a King Cake baby for "Bobby," from the cast of Night Vale #KimoTheatre #WelcometoNightVale… https://t.co/edBludgZyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartinSantosR @ColombianEng Proceso de paz de Santos, solo le faltó estar redeada de coca]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great start to the week! @pedialyte dropping a care package to help get through this last snap of chili weather.… https://t.co/KOcOMZd6Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you  @TAP_16 for your support at last night’s game. I really appreciate the encouraging text messages and wor… https://t.co/adEb6IRN2b]]></document><document><![CDATA[we were talking about shovels the other day in my history class and i was like “do you guys remember shovel girl?”… https://t.co/FO15Bm4f3v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CVO3_ Their defense is getting older. And like I said, there is no guarantee they get guys like Flowers or Trent B… https://t.co/tp3zVEPUYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sooobad6 @EddyFinnerty @g68_charlie @GiantsTBR @Patricia_Traina @Giants2019 They also didn't have Mahomes or Watso… https://t.co/px20Alqb1o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamSchiff So, how did you help beaten up little Mikey Cohen prepare for the congressional charade. This convicted… https://t.co/zjWFELDCx4]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@CPAC is flooded with millennials and Gen Z who understand the importance of common sense policy and values. The i… https://t.co/MeP6YOd2UR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cafecnn Por favor DEJEN DE REFERIRSE A maduro COMO PRESIDENTE. NO LO ES NO ESTA CLARO PARA CNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anissa_oxox Went from your first tweet “I’m back hoes” to sad real quick lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/63ooXGDNdW  This is the link to the state championship gear. Feel free to share with family and friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill This person should be fired by the paper..racism vs free speech has been a issue, clearly racism has no place... period]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Longjon859 @namsdrawkcabht @Benaskren Tony likely took the Pettis fight so he was on the same card as Khabib vs Ma… https://t.co/xVpErEPPJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to believe in myself like i did when i was kid. Do you believe in yourself? • • #YBNORMAL @ Tennessee https://t.co/qRF50BOgQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Know body will tell me nothing I been trying to solve the crime my self and I did it was a cop a rookie cop  the sa… https://t.co/59zzlq6BSH]]></document><document><![CDATA[So conflicted: does a former Baltimore boy (who makes an award winning crab cake) dare to try a @gelsonsmarkets cra… https://t.co/5VbuRdCGaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are some highlights of @Sheldon_HS win over @MC_basketball  https://t.co/dFoa1QPa0T @SacBee_JoeD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dallasnews @TimCowlishaw What a SAD end To a GREAT Ballpark. Still remember the Preview day then Opening Day!!! .5… https://t.co/Qq2IdZvImQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Permian battled Midland High to a 1-1 draw tonight. Here's the quick game story: https://t.co/4SlcO16XYX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Delicious! So sweet! Just enough coconut. - Drinking a Coconut Milk Stout by Untitled Art @ The Den  — https://t.co/1Dnri5SCUX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sexton getting a masters class on being ready to shoot. He’s passed up three open threes because of a slow gather w… https://t.co/4RCHXVt0DX]]></document><document><![CDATA[How does an investor assess a deal when they’re getting pushback from having their own representation? We’re going… https://t.co/ZJb7svs9hv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mai brane are healthily enuff sankyuu every more.   In case you needed confirmation I intentionally did that previo… https://t.co/oW9jix2uoe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregiousBe @realDonaldTrump You've no idea and your tweet shows  you have lost any abilities to be impartial. In o… https://t.co/IS6wcGAsk1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @JohnJHarwood More for LGBTQ than any President. Whether he realizes it or not]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hopefully I wake up to my door slamming open and preme saying "wake up fool"]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jessica84236449 Me parece que no habíamos coincidido, aquí he andado jaja felices madrugadas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos tiempos cuando no se buscaba quedar bien con x agenda correctita y el Señor de los Anillos se llevó las 11 n… https://t.co/jF5HXvAWOG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@art_stapleton He was poor the other years. And the trade offer was a rumor. Stop claiming it was a fact. Only DG k… https://t.co/x4xlAftd78]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parody is protected by the Constitution. More than anything,  it's comedy. Entertainment! Coolest thing about a fre… https://t.co/QK2SokTzIm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Yes, we need to protect our nation, and yes I agree with how he is doing it. For he has to be aggressi… https://t.co/K7K9PEaHVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITisSunshinexo @CreekCoffeeHous Have a beautiful Saturday Miss Sunshine ☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[The fact that @AOC has to spend her mornings correcting dudes who refuse to take down their misleading tweets about… https://t.co/e732g7d4Rf]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the president can dispense with the legistlative branch’s power of the purse, there is no Constitution.  The GOP… https://t.co/54Ym80Tgv2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Crankenpants Does that still apply when talking about areas like Fairmont and Redwood Falls? Trying to find an all encompassing name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES. @zwgarth dropping #BubbaHoTep on @FarriersBellows!   Also, listen to this new show... it’s real good y’all.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HelpingHearts1 @CBSSacramento @tomhoganlaw @sacbee_news @SacramentoKings @thegrupeco @SacPolice @SPDOutreach… https://t.co/0BQr2AV443]]></document><document><![CDATA[Out Now on all digital platforms! Shoutout to @kaanlifemusic @seeblev @demjointz for allowing me to be apart of the… https://t.co/BIOT9Cucde]]></document><document><![CDATA[Remember that Battle originally committed to Michigan. It’s scary to think about what these last 3 #Syracuse season… https://t.co/f6659HJoIk]]></document><document><![CDATA[the amount of random numbers and text messages I have in my phone from partying is insane, I didn’t know I was such a social butterfly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guess I’ve been ragging on Chris Bangle a bit too much; now, when I type “chr” into Google, his name pops up firs… https://t.co/Xmq3OXu8fU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelodieCerin - Ayiti guin bon moun é Ayitien guin bon kè.  SVP tandé message ça é patagé aak tout contact sou résa… https://t.co/tHzmiadnj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@carynrweiss Hmm. I'm surprised at early returns on your poll. This was so boring and not pulled together without a host. Even a bad host.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A unique approach to the implementation of dedicated bus lanes. Interesting that Everett, MA took an "unorthodox ap… https://t.co/HA4R0c7B3k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deeplyclassical As a young singer I did my apprenticeship with Sir Charles Mackerras and will always be so gratefu… https://t.co/NmeAxdCLlu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can anybody guess what show I was loading in today? #rigger #riggerlife #rigging #beamlife #groundrigger… https://t.co/EwLt1uaUgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[The host-less awards show that's worse every year limiting what's included might not have the intended results]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nancywphoto Don’t know what the answer is. Cormorants have all but taken over the Niagara River it seems. Moving inland too. Crazy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProFootballTalk Destroying any semblance of leverage the Steelers thought they had haha @zbannourah @T_K3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Wow Same things your husband never fixed and you never did to anything about as a senator wow. Mayb… https://t.co/c1d5CpDvc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Cinépolis for Can You Ever Forgive Me? in Monterrey, Nuevo León https://t.co/dFkaCwf7bC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a way to reject the president*’s #FakeNationalEmergency? Join @CosechaB on Monday, Presidents Day, to m… https://t.co/8CEa7AYG9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bern_identity @BernieSanders @janeosanders More! https://t.co/3rjL5izkjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IPv6Freely my wife would like to get our own chickens. The problem is we neef every neighbor to sign off on those chickens.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Ale by @Perrinbrewing @ Clique Lanes — https://t.co/bmjGUgj9JC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieroginsky @JaneMayerNYer @DNC You mean like the liberal main stream media being in the pocket of the democrats… https://t.co/QJHyE63xJ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lauren_mcclinton naturalsoulexperience # @ Analog at Hutton Hotel https://t.co/8VAUG6svUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waltshaub @realDonaldTrump And with Trump, the buck always stops somewhere else.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CheriJacobus #Qanon Why are so many big shots friends with Jeffrey Epstein? @thestormisuponus]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I don't wear deodorant and only take bubble baths.” https://t.co/DHWcMAT7lQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ligon_jamal in OL vs DL Drills @TheOpening #GetOpen https://t.co/TeyeBnmp11]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnLegere @TMobile T Mobile Is No.t BASED In The UNITED States Of AMERICA; My Phone COMPANY Is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DJarJarTrump @realDonaldTrump Jar-The-Retard. Go back and sit on the shelf.  You’re not needed.   MAGA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @FMR_DEM Russia hoax Delusional a serious mental illness psychotic disorder.Dems cant tell whats re… https://t.co/pIU0uNSUXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Choose Faith over Fear today and be GREAT! #TogetherWeWin #ItsBiggerThanBall #TrustTheProcess]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three of Scioto County’s best have a chance to reach the district finals with a win tonight.  @dw1509 will have upd… https://t.co/FtVHFoU5gJ]]></document></documents></author>