<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@GoldenSt8OfMind I dig it!I don’t even want a diamond as a primary stone,for My ring. A lot of the celebs are only… https://t.co/GmAx8jwOVj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TPachera @A2SchoolsSuper @DickinsoLee @A2schools @PLTWorg Love these educators! Inspiring the world ...one student at a time!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barbls23 @jssjanetss @maggieNYT @HillaryClinton @nytimes @realDonaldTrump I second this. Leave @HillaryClinton alo… https://t.co/rxuLorLWPA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si no les contesto los mensajes, que les hace pensar que les contaré el chisme? 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mmpadellan OMG, how n the world can MSM honestly report cops thought that STEPHON(on PRIVATE PROPERTY)n his GRANDM… https://t.co/nDxaGCmEcw]]></document><document><![CDATA[does anyone blast christian music in their car in the mornings and have like a mini worship service? just me??… https://t.co/kCE0Db7Gvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine’s Day! 💕 #goodtimeswithgoodcompany #touristinmyowncity #educateyourself @ The Broad https://t.co/HPitW08niK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why or why @AndiMackTV did you leave me with a hiatus when I need to know if #TJ will ever fix things with #Cyrus a… https://t.co/006sj6qoJu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and when I was prego with Ty, I was babysitting contractors, working on converting the old base chapel into the… https://t.co/crIeEVPkMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennyjaffe @dave_schilling I for fucking real think about “These Are the Things in My Jeep” like once a week.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgenJulie Yes and we've seen this in the reaction to this new policy too. Lots of people saying "schools aren't… https://t.co/ouuUAalZCd]]></document><document><![CDATA[First nice day in what feels like forever and I’m home throwing up. Neato.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RueNahcMohr @MLE_Online you should know about the Cugnot steamer because it's ridiculous:  https://t.co/IvxmSXowjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OffTrackTravel @IBBtravel @Hannahlogan21 @RoarLoudTravel @OliviaRutt @ABritSoutherner @DestAddict @kathrynanywhere… https://t.co/atNmp7C8KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are yoga teachers writing newspaper columns I don’t try to teach your yoga class]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wobinjayden thank you! obviously this is a few years old and rushed, so i totally get what you’re saying and hard agree!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUmarkwoods @ValpoU @NatlParkService Did some surveys in the dune ponds back in the day when I was at @NotreDame Love that place!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not surprised, it’s about time and he must resign immediately. Trudeau believes he is above the law and we need to… https://t.co/2WRUfORHbt]]></document><document><![CDATA[In tribute to #MaliaObama I’ll be sipping on this tonight as I watch @ReginaKing #GlennClose @realmahershala… https://t.co/9OfEawmYVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Golden Corral team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/tTDtRZ2tmR #Franchise #Restaurant]]></document><document><![CDATA[Visit Fisher Day guests for days!  Welcome to @fisherosu.   #VFD19 #gobucks @ Ohio State University https://t.co/lux8gZlkMJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff Cohen said you were.. humm but this statement is false also https://t.co/CrcI2kLEdS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bulletgifts @Snookums1379 From what I understand it saves time not needing signatures anymore. They just use track… https://t.co/1ANi3MWjYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Special Guest: Chucky the Schume! Is he going to wear his douchebag glasses? 🙃 @jimmy_dore @miserablelib… https://t.co/Mkd9uQJVFr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ksd_18 Very well said, my wife is a FA with a major US Airline and besides serving drinks etc, she would save pass… https://t.co/IXocKTQfGY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMaxineWaters Give it up Maxine you will not win this battle. You do not decide who our President is. I feel sor… https://t.co/cHB2EBiuss]]></document><document><![CDATA[.....There’s no Gamecock WBB Bus for the Auburn game but we’re literally about to have a mini van... https://t.co/wbDIaVlzpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Fit in 30 Studio Battle Creek, LLC in Battle Creek, MI https://t.co/xnDWQo6tSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton Great job police ! Enough hate toward conservatives! People open your mind to a mature conversation not… https://t.co/myuC5vOFkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[My way to convince my family to rescue another dog: I take a picture of it and tape it to the wall so they see it 2… https://t.co/JxPWj4Vkit]]></document><document><![CDATA[fun fact: The lipstick Koko K is in regulation for military uniform according to AR 670-1 😂🤙🏼🎉 https://t.co/fjUF4ytGug]]></document><document><![CDATA[*plays becareful with me* by cardi with a man in the car just so he knows I’m not playin games]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Roboticolgamer @TrinAndTonic And yet you don't see that as "political." I wonder why not.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When i had my hs graduation party, my dad invited his chiropractor just for the heck of it and the dude showed up a… https://t.co/UkyMHW6p9k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm that type of girl who loves to receive flowers for valentine's day  💐☺💗😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hastings Water Update: Last week, city staff recommended to the Council a slightly different approach to chlorinati… https://t.co/9NI3v8JLSl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boating is exhausting 🚤☀️Man I love those cheeks 😍💙 — #LiamJayKelly @ Lake Travis https://t.co/MfcWoxdvf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 4 is fast approaching! the dancing with the stars episode up first. #mariettaga #mariettasquare @ Earl Smith… https://t.co/o9K8c2pBQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Each day you should start your day with setting an intention for the day. This intention acts as a gu… https://t.co/1NTqhQjyt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My doggo Portia looks like a Portia sandwich 🥰🐶 #shihtzusofinstagram @ Toronto, Ontario https://t.co/a9CAaZw36w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Line Dancing Cabaret.. we had an amazing time....this is my Twinny Twin Twin @fayelivelove ❤❤💃🏾💃🏾 #LineDancing… https://t.co/d0E1e0plXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Lock_God @OfficeOfSkip @C_doc_911 @marcellacomedy I *wish* they would read a book. Then they’d know it’s not spelled “persay”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JHMSparky @HopKnotIPA @ephoustonbill @JohanBBT @JonMontag @DRE_Go_Fish @badhopper @beerguypdx @wolv54b1… https://t.co/b276dgtGa2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The “I Think We’re Alone Now” séquence alone should get the @UmbrellaAcad and @TheEmmys Nomination and win for best… https://t.co/YnHPgwCGTo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please vote! I thoughtfully vote for evian   VICE: This is evian in the #ShortyAwards. https://t.co/T9kLWVyND4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations @reikorenee and @NashvilleCaters for winning Judges Choice-Best Overall at the Taste of Williamson… https://t.co/KeKIBdXZTf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spreading your joy, park of your sick sexual conduct of abusing women? Your career is over pervert!!! This is what… https://t.co/vI6mkqStOb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kortney_Vieweg @Mark_Sheppard @cw_spn Great! More bandwidth for the rest of us!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learned tonight that silent discos can be pretty fun. #InVisionIRL https://t.co/UEMbXbTgiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TjBallS Dude I know , you have to come see him he’s already growing so fast !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billadler @realDonaldTrump President Trump is simply stating the TRUTH!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MollyV178 Rest and liquids. Wash hands Disinfect your devices so you don’t reinfect yourself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nate from Motherfolk offered to officiate Matt and I's wedding if we ever get married 😭😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’ALL. I love my roommate so much 🤣💙 #appalachia #mountainlife #relativelyeasy #WHATAMAN #conducting101 @ Reinhardt… https://t.co/vOKr2lvXRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[We'll be playing all of 'In Us We Trust' at our release show with @TheVampireYouth @GiveWayHC and @wearecarvist  Yo… https://t.co/MDUXPjgIan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SergyHeddy Yay I’m so happy 😁 go bolts go have a nice rest until Monday hopefully kick kings butt on Monday woot ⚡️⛈🌩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Parents: support your concerned child inspired by @GretaThunberg and her cohort to walk out of class today and JOIN… https://t.co/vqU7CnzO25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdesmondharris Along with her initial complete confusion that this was unacceptable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The one morning I don’t have to be up ridiculously early, and I’m up at 5. Ugh.   Brain, please shut up. https://t.co/Klx0plwzoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[The celebration kicks off in two weeks as Gov @dougducey hosts Amb @Martha_Barcena at the annual @AzMxCom Governor’… https://t.co/Safjq165eV]]></document><document><![CDATA[had a friend really put me in my place today, told me how my ego is what’s getting in the way of my happiness and g… https://t.co/8URLghW2M9]]></document><document><![CDATA[UNTIL WE STOP KILLING OUR CHILDREN WE HAVE NO HIGHER GROUND WHEN IT COMES TO HUMAN RIGHTS IN OTHER COUNTRIES.. INCL… https://t.co/rCevpFivYh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to some students work on their projects like mixing Bob Marley songsnor their own music. https://t.co/n1DeQeNfAX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 601 Paul St #SunPrairie #WI  #realestate https://t.co/DMjHzZ5xcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NomdeB Yes. @divaskychick saw that live. That neatly captured the GOP’s ugly deal with this grifter. They’ll all s… https://t.co/MIsmzXYqM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AAFFleet - Fumble Recovery for a TD....INT for a TD..gotta be an @TheAAF first?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 Worried about loosing your Florida law license?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics Anyone with a heart would not rip kids awat from their parents.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iMakeArtifacts @AOC @AltUS_ARC Hillary handled it by getting the corrupt FBI, AG, and Obama to cover for her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RunhappyKat It went through our house last week. The 16yr old who hides in his room typical teenager mode avoided… https://t.co/m8neXjue9R]]></document><document><![CDATA[´Trumpites hugely intimated by competent women. Six people in Trump campaign indicted, 34 under investigation _ no… https://t.co/A5UDqjifrr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDanB95 @RepSwalwell @SenatorBurr @MarkWarner That has been the major problem from the beginning. Republicans w… https://t.co/toBKfVBVMF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Message from the Northbridge High School library tonight: https://t.co/vVXXEsGfnv]]></document><document><![CDATA[These meds need to kick in already. I'm fucking miserable. My body is sore and I haven't done 1 productive thing this week]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think the thing that scares me the most about turning 18 is going to prison :/  Oh and adulting that too]]></document><document><![CDATA[This food is high in saturated fat.  And *you* are high in judgment, MyFitness"Pal". Sod off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[put on your red dress  &amp; slip on your high heels  &amp; some of that sweet perfume  it sure smells good on youuuuu 🗣 .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimguilfoyle He speaks for me. Trump is a fraud, liar, hater, bigot, moron, need I say more. He has brought great… https://t.co/WrqlGwCcKK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods I believe Justice Roberts should give American people an update]]></document><document><![CDATA[Estoy harta de soñar que tengo novio y despertarme y no tener.   Ya hasta sueño que @PauloLondra es mi novio]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lexmedlin Your daughter looks a lot like you.  How are you doing today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[In need of this ! I love for a good fanny piece 😩 specially #lv https://t.co/CakhLQOvxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thewingsnation Definitely a penalty.... Should be 4 min power play for Detroit..... Blood was drawn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone believe the #GOP will do ANYTHING other than line their pockets in the here and now? Clean initiatives… https://t.co/QbCibc3ozr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a cool experience for Ss! Would love to chat with her on Nepris with CVUSD Ss. Doctor + YouTube star meets TV… https://t.co/kbm2UzaZLY]]></document><document><![CDATA[My first Absinthe! #bbbnola2019 #NOLA #absinthe #greenfairy @ The Old Absinthe House https://t.co/rgPjmjO50D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @nancylee2016 Anyone remember when they tried to blame Trump for the Synagogue shooting? Funny the med… https://t.co/2jL6ZjGVj1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodmorning! Haaay my heart is so full I couldn’t ask for more. Have a blessed sunday y’all ♥️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quando algumas pessoa te avisam sobre alguem, e tu defendes esse alguém com mãos e garras as pessoas q falam mal. M… https://t.co/RzK6e9IUDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any other girls watch sad movies when they are already sad just to bask in it or is that just me ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Someone tell me they saving their dominant hand for the next team I breaking it 🤷🏿‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get out of her head. As much as I’ve liked Shauna, don’t you dare hurt Sykes#ThePassage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@turquim5 @brasil247 povinho naniquinho viralatinha tupiniquin resolveu morrer]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman @chrissyteigen She is a mom, model, cook, married to John Legend.  She is smart, funny and interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sneak peek 👀 - new @INSPIRE_2022 offices are almost done at the #rosebowl! Who’s ready to see what America’s Stadiu… https://t.co/m83rwAH7dU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec This is INSANE ! Will the Republicans stop this mess? Do something ! What a waste of time and money for nothing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This girl said the only playboi carti song she can name is magnolia. Never blocked somebody so quick lmfaoo]]></document><document><![CDATA[“pour me, pourrrrr me another drink” @saigeekingg https://t.co/3YBwCVOGEF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@senatemajldr U will be done, finished in 2020. Bye Mitch M., we will be so happy to see u gone finally. The great OBSTRUCTIONIST!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CraigMalRob @MichelleObama MICHELLE you are a racists and you grew up with privilege so stop your lying]]></document></documents></author>