<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I can't stress this topic enough, just because you laid down and had a baby don't mean you are a parent. Taking car… https://t.co/A40F1rnqqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Weird because @mulaney is at once my best friend from middle school AND my more-adult-than-me, pipe-smoking uncle 🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djsworld2012 @TheRightMelissa @realDonaldTrump You are still talking MAGA asshat?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear God, if today I lose my hope, please remind me that your plans are better than my dreams.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was gonna be productive and wake up at 5:30... guess who rolled outta bed late at 7:40?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am looking for a buyer on 378 Bella Rose Drive #Evans #GA  #realestate https://t.co/nDKuMjqqVl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You got that right Coach @TonyLBenford🙌🏽👍🏽  @LSUBasketball kicking off the first of many greats moments coming for… https://t.co/PSOYjcXK7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did this instead of buying more lip balm. Good dude. Cute dogs. Important plans and opinions. Feeling very optimist… https://t.co/RaYPR6XWN4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaeA_94 That’s what my hubby said some are asking for cash app. Seeing the pros and cons. We may keep square and add that too😁.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inquiring minds need to understand.  A one world government and socialism would negate or destroy our Constitution,… https://t.co/T1Hvyi1UsL]]></document><document><![CDATA[the only reason i would have kids is so my parents can be the cutest and kindest abuelitos (but that’s no where nea… https://t.co/QjFeCvJu63]]></document><document><![CDATA[There's something "unsaid" behind the Dem's wanting to abolish ICE!  They are the most crooked members of Congress… https://t.co/vzfcSsMxQ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiborMilian )))))))) #Cincinnati #Toledo #Walleye #Idah #Utah #Tulsa  #Wichita  #KansasCity #WheelingNailers… https://t.co/DHxq9VFuEr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ifthehoefits @therealhafeez @miIIerj Girl I thought of you! And @jordan_beals  Like I want you both at my wedding]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billymflynn I wish you all the best 💝 You are loved and will be missed ⚘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Such an inspirational #naisac session about #innovation and driving change in schools from @jbrettjacobsen. "School… https://t.co/55fnOEhLx2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight, join the #sangha at #bhaktiyogashala for #manta #medicine with #johannabeekmanmusic #dcstringer #tour… https://t.co/NhpgAJOLk7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MonicaRiosssss @elalbertomedina @jorgevilla25 @contreras_p1 @Chaposoto @VictorMendozaL @Darbelom @DoloresAragonRL… https://t.co/F2aR1OhIu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@easwanson2005 @choo_ek Knock it out of the park! https://t.co/ScL1Rj8urB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@agarzon Entre comunistas la miopía es de 6 Dioptrías para arriba. Eres incapaz de ver 1 solo de los abusos cometid… https://t.co/1917IImoyv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nite, nite.🍎🌃 . . . . . . . . . #tgif #fryay #weekend #newyork #nyc #nycblogger #citylights #travelgram #traveller… https://t.co/7Dn0WzE4pQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NyashaJunior @YNPierce Leave no room for interpretation. If this person deserves tenure, start your letter with: “… https://t.co/RpvAGRnHOA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel so loved and appreciated by my students, parents and FBC volunteers. Thank you for the sweet cards, gifts an… https://t.co/qwWk84HwKg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsRabbitResist If he's going thru it, so are you.  Positivity. https://t.co/4C13bF5C97]]></document><document><![CDATA[Through Community Rx, @CleanAirMoms is providing parents w/ tools to unite their communities to learn about the env… https://t.co/fLKL2slqfO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@diddliest @BoycottStuff I would also like your opinion on the information left out. Some of the employees say yes… https://t.co/54UO8xiqkL]]></document><document><![CDATA[East Coast: Tapped the Keg West Coast: Broke the Seal  #MarshallMoments]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Once again, how are comments like these unifying?  You are the most decisive president of my lifet… https://t.co/9fbKpYDa2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MeganPanatier @LAPublicLibrary I’ve always wanted to do this! We got a map of them and have visited about 20. Hoping to do them all!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi to the guy at Yerim earlier seated by the door haha happy hearts day gdnight 💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is trynna Uber me home rn? This night straight insulting me on so many levels I’m over it. How do u bitches do… https://t.co/Js7RpRKUdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jamie looked at me and said “you know you kinda can pull off the gangsta look” lmaoooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[F.... my mind should be a platinum record right now. Or it is......... in my mind. hahahahaha]]></document><document><![CDATA[My dog is so fucking smart y’all ! He teaches himself shit all the time that I start picking up on. Like this fool… https://t.co/VrJtwH8mXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Zendaya @BeverlyJohnson1 @Beverly_Peele @veronicawebb @iampatcleveland i need the skirt in the Veronica Webb picture immediately 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shelleyann1817 Nope! Got home last night! Loved it!! Cant wait to go back!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 2 month tolerance break ends tomorrow and I’m so proud of myself... I myself along w everyone else never thought I’d be able to do this]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopping by #Artopia at @thechurchdenver for all the colorful people https://t.co/SAwyX9lHg4]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I talk a little louder and speak up when you're wrong. Don't get mad it's a it's a brand new kind of me, it took… https://t.co/2fqD6qbkQ2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MiguelandHolly I'm totally with you on Jessie Smollett, Miguel. I feel totally betrayed and keep waiting for the s… https://t.co/EL6ed3GNvg]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was bad, I’m not saying in comparison to the old Kim Possible either. It was completely predictable, yet it was… https://t.co/cjzNS9N3pH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in a job in #Washington, MO? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/bhz4vAVaPl #HealthWelfare]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone comes in and eats at my place of employment today.. i hate you. Stay home pls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[RT if you too have lost count of how many times you’ve almost ate shit because of this ice/snow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Clearly we don’t know how to take nail pics. ~ ~ ~ ~ #pmtstemecula #paulmitchelltheschool #paulmitchelledu… https://t.co/Hhf2l2p7HS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the great conversation!  We looks forward to collaborating with you. @carlosaotal @hughesad12… https://t.co/LUxhVy5U26]]></document><document><![CDATA[for the Rohingya, when aid was blocked to refugee camps, and protests were held condemning anyone who helped them;… https://t.co/vA1Ah8cSwA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DivaVinophile @_drazzari @jflorez @GailBenzler @SashaEats @jimofayr @damewine @KellyMitchell @SLBriscoe @sl2016_sl… https://t.co/3cmUL0WUBe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paper Airplane Game! Take the simplicity of making a paper plane into the ultimate Paper Airplane Game and see who… https://t.co/dUP9vNpRul]]></document><document><![CDATA[Midnight manic episode cleaning company #milliondollaridea , imagine having a group of people with manic episodes c… https://t.co/CmGGVw8lAD]]></document><document><![CDATA[to all makeup wearers: @ColourPopCo is having free shipping going on rn  you’re welcome]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LSU gets on the board first after an Army error on a bunt by Broussard.   #LSU 2 - Army 0. Bottom of 1st.   @TTV_Sports]]></document><document><![CDATA[MEMPHIS LADIES! Be sure to check out Lady Sure Shots club at @shootpointblank   • Only $10, register online • Women… https://t.co/z2cF0KRJH7]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kiddos and one space invader #twins #twinning #bullypit @ South Omaha, Nebraska https://t.co/iTjmx00o3b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yesterday on Dave &amp; Johnny Live! Full episode on @YouTube @davesimonmma rants on #MichaelJackson #TravisScott… https://t.co/gteF6mCXrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you were supposed to have date night but he went out for a drink with the boys. Sure enough he walks through t… https://t.co/Qow91xACPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @kimguilfoyle @KamalaHarris This coordinated with her anti lynching bill. In fact it was handy sinc… https://t.co/8vEhYkHy3S]]></document><document><![CDATA[My bois for life. Thx for being good to us, 143 ✨💜 https://t.co/OHwqhjflze]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don’t think healthcare should be free to those who need help obtaining medical care when shit gets rough, I… https://t.co/IsmEnKLGNI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeniseDresserG @MovCiudadanoMX @Pat_MercadoC El problema aquí es que muchos periodistas critican el gobierno actua… https://t.co/fUdVZfmkzz]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how someone’s not that attractive anymore , especially after you see how their personality is. #Trash]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still remember the days when Girls couldn't wear pants to school! Somehow we just can't leave women free to make th… https://t.co/NAtATMDgFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@manczano @roaymarteyetona At talagang demonyo ako ah HAHAHAHHAAHHAHAHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish my whole family loved Taco Bell as much as I do so I can stop doing 2 separate food runs for dinner every night🤦🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[My thought is that teachers are benefiting the educational community by sharing their work. More Ss can benefit whe… https://t.co/IKK40uUddi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LtRayMack Please dont take it as towards you , but I've seen many whose authority to teach is derived simply by th… https://t.co/w0dy9WG009]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is better than my alarm. #Maggie #calicocat #cats_of_instagram #catstagram #nephewspet @ San Francisco, Califor… https://t.co/sRaTQpzPkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nassimzaid1985 To your woman yes 🤣 but as a first pick up line ..... https://t.co/3rbmlZxu2c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SykesCharlie @BulwarkOnline Good luck with that.  Romney is spineless.  He has his lips firmly planted on Trump’s rump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If you pursue your passions and believe that you are more than an athlete, you will succeed in life after sport” s… https://t.co/anNDDzhOII]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is my Saturday afternoon, while ronnie and hunter play video games. I love Jodi Picoult's book, Nineteen Minut… https://t.co/xwufKlUOpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rorycooper @TheRickWilson There is no mercy in American justice. Except for white-collar criminals like Manafort of course.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nature's music! #upperpeninsula #Upnorth #Puremichigan #OptOutside https://t.co/tGJJ6AKDQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out director’s Gillian Greene  comedy  “Fanboy “ with Fran Kranz #frankranz ,   Sam Raimi #samraimi ,… https://t.co/xdzGgnj5Y7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markcubsfan @ericswalwell @FoxNews Right.  MSM asks softball questions to democrats.  Don't think they could handl… https://t.co/qLhWAzPebV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sharing my new favorite natural fragrance brand! Get 20% off your first order at Skylar with my link.  I tried the… https://t.co/R1StLKk8JB]]></document><document><![CDATA[You're the Director so shouldn't YOU be doing something about it. I didn't think you needed orders from Trump to en… https://t.co/EiSjCJZSL3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have an event invite for every day this week and honestly I think my social anxiety (yup even I have that) is rea… https://t.co/RUk0nRS3zJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things I see…  *a foggy night in Houston.... . . . . #iphonography #photography #fog #foggy #houston #texas… https://t.co/DHrCrcf4Tb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol he said lack of patience lol yeah we don’t want another Maria on our hands lol but seriously thank you… https://t.co/RAFQEbFWE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[overheard at Oscar viewing party: “ok I need to stop watching ‘the kissing booth’ on netflix”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thecjpearson No it didn't.  It was a starter position as it should be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[You almost make my heart dance, and dancing is forbidden. (Puritan Valentines Day Cards - College... #humor… https://t.co/7P73m3j9vR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had the best time at #PupiDupi and #TeenieWeenie Birthday Party #loreenarbus 🎂🎉🧁 @ Upper West Side https://t.co/oMoDH1iSB5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gifts, dates, and romantic notes passed to one another are very sweet and romantic. However, there's nothing more r… https://t.co/YmqlTRX2FH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alam ko iniiwas niyo Kat yung balls. Okay lang pero gumawa din sana yung iba. Haha]]></document><document><![CDATA[ayooooooo shoutout one time to women I love y’all n how y’all smell and feel and look, stay killing it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cariboucoffee won’t let you pay for a cup filled with ice and a top, with your order of food. 😫😤🙄 😡 #annoyed shoul… https://t.co/r0gXYZZFnb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kicking things off at #CapitalOneHouse w/ @julieaelb62 @karlitaliliana and Mimi Fox Melton for Breaking Barriers: L… https://t.co/iJwpfgSBWe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RachelHeine WOW:  satisfied (hamilton)  climbing uphill (last 5 years)  all i ask of you (poto) what you want (leg… https://t.co/9o7a7W4C6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why all the curses? Selling of cow is a good business. Dont you eat Suya, Kiloshi,dambu nama,pepper soup etc? How p… https://t.co/wZJWSa2aIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vxx46 @90IP6 @YouTube @PittTweet @MTV I agree!  I have found quite a few new bands that I love producing music rem… https://t.co/DamWjemVQN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigInTheCountry 💔😿💔 (never mind your hair.. the girls at the gym still want to flirt)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mo_fierce Do what’s best for you! You deserve to be happy ❤️ if things haven’t changed, what are the chances they… https://t.co/hhDgxWWruG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swopes This video was soooo helpful, swopes. Thank you for always being so generous with tips ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is my old photo.. not i just need to try to duplicate this outfit 😂#appleEDUchat https://t.co/IbH0N49ChQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TraciMcCullou15 @matthewjdowd @KatiePhang Keep your filthy head off my silky threads... 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#T3Learns that as instructors we have impacted over 64k educators! Which in turn impacts students! Are we instillin… https://t.co/BrXrbBH6fL]]></document><document><![CDATA[i can’t sleep so i washes all of my dirty brushes and i feel so clean now even though my nose is about explode]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight! Join me at @BlattBeer Legacy for an #omahadines and @OmahaBeerWeek event! 6 p.m., beer, beer books for sal… https://t.co/CeE7MkIUzu]]></document></documents></author>