<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Light sabers in the courtyard @hackwithtrees #DisneyTech https://t.co/bhReAyrhvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know how they say every action must have an equal, and opposite reaction?  Pretty sure I'm the opposite reactio… https://t.co/PTN3FRcx4P]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just catching up on this but I’m super-psyched for the Jeopardy! all-star team tournament]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your turn -&gt; @karaswisher   ❌⬛️⬜️⬛️⬜️ ⬛️⬛️⬛️⬛️⬛️ ⬜️⬛️⬜️⬛️⬜️ ⬛️⬛️⬛️⬛️⬛️ ⬜️⬛️⬜️⬛️⬜️]]></document><document><![CDATA[HOLD THE DATE!  All your supporters will meet you on the 9th hole later tonight.  Wear something nice Happy… https://t.co/c0p4m4IXVq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Embattled Virginia Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax compares himself to lynching victims  https://t.co/ojc90C26jy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tomkeene Hey Tom, with Mark Stone going to @GoldenKnights , I suggest you find a reason to take @bsurveillance and… https://t.co/Tze7tB4a3F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just in time for Galentines Day I got a Valentines Day care package from mom. I’ve never been big on this holiday,… https://t.co/ppK5spiJRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HuffPost @HannahDrake628 this is the article I was talking about a few weeks ago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OttSpecEvents @ottawacity @KeithEgli @JimWatsonOttawa @Ottawa_Tourism @JarrodGoldsmith @dylanblackradio… https://t.co/hCXM5AzEhk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Warriors lead the Bulldogs 21-14 at the half! Lets Go Bulldogs! https://t.co/l8QyuNiflC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aj_NDrancher @RealJamesWoods They are if there stones, then at least you can see The Rolling Stones if you shake that there box free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i don’t snap/text someone back immediately then i forget so sorry if i seem clingy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to find creative ways to let your friends know that you're sitting on their car, patiently waiti… https://t.co/F6C94HJpyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Matt Murray's Stadium Series pads are mostly black trimmed in gold. #dkps #penguins]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just burnt my tongue and absolute belter on the aul morning coffee goupin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alfonslopeztena Very unlikely. He thinks (and relentlessly tells us) that he's the world's greatest deal maker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArielTohar אהבתי את מערכת היחסים בין וסרמן לנייג׳ל ופחות התעניינתי בסיפור שהוא סיפר לו. הפרק הדני עם הדגים כמעט גרם לי לוותר על הספר!]]></document><document><![CDATA[US Marines repping at RodeoHouston!  #USA #RodeoHouston #Horspitality #day2 #horsearena @ RODEOHOUSTON https://t.co/uXunqVHDcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe people can change and grow, but when asked to comment on these old posts she said she sticks by what was… https://t.co/oKcR43oCeK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It’s a manuscript and not a book asshole.  It was written when he was still kissing your orange ass.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceWolfChi “Gross”? What, she couldn’t bring herself to use Kevin Matthews’s “icky bad”? Reads like the bus scene in Sixteen Candles.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChadFlyers15 @WGI @CLTMotorSpdwy @DISupdates The Roval was amazing! Not the end seeing my boy @MartinTruex_Jr gett… https://t.co/YNmmaCiOtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RafaelR89260945 @econokafka @CartonCalderon Que Dios nos agarre confesados!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Max Domi, Andreas Johnsson (though I don't know what you did to piss off Domi) and Kasperi Kapanen for br… https://t.co/bjSy5WlPs2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank God Herro has showed up tonight... please finish this, get Gafford a 5th and let’s go into UT Saturday with a big opportunity]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kenpro11 Et c'est au nom de telles fumisteries, parce qu'il y en a d'autres, qu'il faudrait payer une taxe carbone !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting read to kick off Mardi Gras with a little help from cigarfactoryneworleans #thecigarnewb #barrelburners… https://t.co/hQyV93LYE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little flamethrower action from tonight’s @ https://t.co/69hwH9hjBy https://t.co/Fcyddthfbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoelandLia   I suggest tha you should check out https://t.co/2zxFOR0SUa whenever you plan to visit any tourist ori… https://t.co/7A0pksHQvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DoreenHunns @RealTT2020 Mueller interviewed Sarah Sanders. He will nail her for perjury.  Suck it up, buttercup!]]></document><document><![CDATA[.. Families of Santa Fe shooting suspect and those of victims are in the courtroom. Several survivors here too. Som… https://t.co/GUlzFM5zSU]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went back to the beginning and read "Baltimore Blues" by @LauraMLippman. Loved the gritty, realistic depcition of… https://t.co/ox72xRG6r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[February 15th is national wear your retainer to work day. we will NOT be silenced]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear twitter readers: One of the great drawbacks of being on Twitter is that I must receive insulting twitter from… https://t.co/FXdraokb8B]]></document><document><![CDATA[[riseagainstthehate] sings Can't Hear You Now by Mike Shinoda, what an incredible voice on The Voice! #music #kar... https://t.co/HEUT9DA8DB]]></document><document><![CDATA[So we missed the race and just saw the podium shot of #StradeBianche and I thought I knew what happened in the race… https://t.co/gtYcRC9oLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/tkaYIInP2y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commentary would have been much different in South Central LA had my grandma rolled in to find this mess going on..… https://t.co/5ePTZy66om]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ylreajd @kaymariebur In your early 20s you learn, fail, and succeed. You grow as a person and when your time comes… https://t.co/08d3TJEVdJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Inject this straight into my veinzzzzzzzzzzzz @Pollard5065 @McgoughDylan]]></document><document><![CDATA[If God had meant for us to think for ourselves, he wouldn't have made autocorrect.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bry_yup @TrevWall not that it matters, but I’m the first to say that mayo F’n sucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[We should all miss the days when water was so contaminated that we were reduced to drinking a gallon of rum a day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueUvino It was tough but I choked it down. Ya know...so nobody else accidentally tasted the awfulness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let's go to more live events! Sign up for SeatGeek and get $20 off your first purchase. https://t.co/oeZMnOm8ht]]></document><document><![CDATA[This game has a super frantic pace right now. A lot of running around without any sense of direction. @WHS_Hoopz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Electra_Bicycle hook me up with merch and esp decals for my matching helmet.  😎 #supermoto8i https://t.co/krNuPlNdE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobalPandya @DiscussingFilm First, for the love of God, learn how to spell and or write.   Second, Rotten Tomatoes… https://t.co/fiO9dvuHyJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Johnny_Bahama21 That may be true,  but I definitely don't spell the way you do either.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The build-up. #maxgraham #seattletrancefamily #seattletrancealliance @ The Underground https://t.co/TFcJev99rB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadFaithMovie @DaveNGoodman One of the best times I've ever had on set. I didn't want to leave. Thankful for film family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmmaxson @PrepVilla @JacobEngel15 Wednesday night prayer service was outstanding as well!!  The outpouring of supp… https://t.co/fQymn2NAUD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I pull this Tigger on,Samsung window concert,, pos,ture,45,, https://t.co/SH07BWM8f4]]></document><document><![CDATA[classic material 🚫DEAL ◾️◾️ OUT #BWVS #NODEAL #MADEINNYC #BWOODKNOWS #VINNIES #X  a cult following like a cult 😈 @… https://t.co/6Y2j8LMb35]]></document><document><![CDATA[@flapjacks62 @johnd200 @R_KellyFans @rkelly I think you have to look at charges, most if not all othe charges in fi… https://t.co/Iw16CT6SxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MWC_Aaron Slowly. Everyone seems to expect a “hockey stick” (exponential) growth when they enter into AG. Very, ve… https://t.co/oTwbXRKr05]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. @JIDsv  2. @S_C_  3. @2PAC 4. @FreshBarz via @ShaqSmith 5. @Therealkiss  6. @Drake  7. @thegame’s @pascurtis  8.… https://t.co/ZdHim4zcdM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sheena_shardae #highheelshoes #karl5026 #love #like #instagood #instagram #follow #art #happy #spandex… https://t.co/fbFbfhNst0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ESPNMcGee Here’s another one Ryan that’s just as big as meeting James Brown. Getting to shake Wahoo McDaniel’s han… https://t.co/LQmxMRaJms]]></document><document><![CDATA[I enjoyed speaking with members of the business community this morning in @pottstownboro about economic development… https://t.co/xpClAWuBCQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[(I know, I know, it would've been Aramaic, don't take this from me. :-P )]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keithmfenton @6b4bc93416fe402 Smart people usually don’t talk about how smart they are. But I’m glad you have mult… https://t.co/oThCieOQiG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HassanElzeeny so!?? the main ball handler doesn’t always mean he’s the number 1 option]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've been thinking about Alita A LOT in the past week. I wish her luck making enough movie money to get the chance… https://t.co/obDtjfFROc]]></document><document><![CDATA[719-799 S Curson Ave 719-799 S Curson Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90036 https://t.co/ipEHWKynMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pmokane Beyond the normal stuff, the Texan bar was a favorite, though the Pink Panther was also well known in my household...]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a winter we’ve had. Snow blower and myself got another workout this morning. Snow, ice, cold, low wind chills,… https://t.co/N04yfysV2K]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2kTwoStacks Like they can’t just walk up to the bar and place an order]]></document><document><![CDATA[My birthday week = winning.  Just stepped out of #MDW, saw a bus leaving to Economy Garage.  Thought “damn!”   And… https://t.co/4fDFcDLPii]]></document><document><![CDATA[@infoecho @StevenSalzberg1 @dnanexus @Google Assay design. Single 100bp amplicon/loci (50bp primer) in a genome wit… https://t.co/suenm5P7J3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PetePaguaga @StopandShop It needs disco lights, music and lasers. Make it a partybot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bestmec01 I had vanilla porter stout from leinenkugel before we moved last Saturdaywas really good]]></document><document><![CDATA[sarah got mad at me earlier because our favorite contestant on master chef was eliminated]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritualSooner Cool. Thanks again! I am a rookie so I appreciate the ideas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Arroyo Grande, California https://t.co/eeXWiBlw2e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MileyCylas @BrettHakey Please humor me with the average salary of a lawyer in your position sir?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Atlanta but I wish I knew about real estate as a 16 year old, I woulda fucked around and bought some propert… https://t.co/KatRHK3cdB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you kidding me James? He got taken out and paid to shut up by the DNC, and Hillary Clinton. I'm surprised you t… https://t.co/rMo5Ac3XzK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VinnysWorld @cspan @senatemajldr I think the better question is are Democrat Senators ready to vote for it. My gue… https://t.co/ucKBAqkQvb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catturd2 @SandraTXAS 🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋🙋✋✋✋✋✋✋✋✋✋✋✋👌👌👌👌👌👌👌👌👌👌👌👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍👍😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are getting close to launching a few and have a few experts around me. Also a local guy that can help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MartesdeMhoni #HoyconMhoni @magdaproducer ✨📺🔮🎬🎥 @programa_hoy @Canal_Estrellas @mhonividente 🧿 @ClubMhoniFans… https://t.co/XrUxFGdJof]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soestupidasofia @daisysegovia @2litermtndew @YoDayJuan @dsscott3 @yaboyTylan S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendon_kaufman game is so dope i feel like they pretty much just fixed everything wrong w other battle royale gam… https://t.co/hCjjLNtGDV]]></document><document><![CDATA[another reason why Ross from the friends was the worst. Jurassic Park could happen! fuck you Ross from friends.… https://t.co/laPbWbhWck]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlairHduQuesnay @RampCapitalLLC No use Blair:  https://t.co/swlaKxCsiY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SueBeeUSA I was looking for my favorite left one, but could only find the right, are they the same just newly repa… https://t.co/5VTNzeVFWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_ianks ...and a short memory, maybe? Tata had trouble in big games in year one, too!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HotlineJosh It's high in Mainland China where tens of millions of Jews live.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This week is Miss Steph’s last week at DFK. 😭😭😭 Please wish her well in her next endeavor in life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for helping me reach 100 followers! I literally couldn’t have done it without you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias It's okay for Obama to exert influence as long as it's aligned with my interests.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meeting Up Love  #LoveIsLove #InstaGay #Gay #GayGuy #GayBoy #GayMan #GayLove #GayCouple #GayWorld #GayLife… https://t.co/Vm3Azg6hp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its looking better for a race weekend in @amsupdates could be a wash out after 130 pm Today stay dry everybody. https://t.co/5yEDtpr11p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adammc123 Really sad! I’m really starting to think taxing all that one-use plastic is the way to go. Cut the base… https://t.co/FFQrXiY7Yo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My current daydream is to be at the university and someone to text me saying "hey, I got you Costa vida".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are very gracious spending other people’s money. What would you have done if there wasn’t a deep coffer of… https://t.co/3ibxu5jXNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RudyGiuliani @realDonaldTrump @Kroger is suing Generic Drug makers who have formed a Republican Drug Cartel. Drugs… https://t.co/BXpxLFg06q]]></document><document><![CDATA[No runs, no hits, no errors in the bottom of the seventh. As we head to the eighth, Florida still leads 5-2.]]></document></documents></author>