<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Brenda eating her damn oatmeal every morning is the bane of my existence.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillyTolley You guys are hilarious tonight !  I don’t know if it’s intentional tho! https://t.co/cp1fqwQqcK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching this game is like thinking you’re going to laid and then getting a handjob while she says, “sorry I’m just not ready”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ssantinii I thought Tarte was bad... this is a whole new level lmao Jesus Christ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IFeelLikeTwit You are precisely the reason I made sure to specify “in snow.” 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've never liked big bang lmao the members just always gave me...sketchy vibes]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m really gonna see my boys scott and todd perform again tomorrow with my bestest friends 🥺 i cant wait it’s going to be insane]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love seeing @LOLIbeauty near the top of this incredible list of #beauty brands! Go Tina Hedges! #natural… https://t.co/4hRNV3IAGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gross! Even photoshop gross! Pls use PS for art! https://t.co/9tn4zj8roj]]></document><document><![CDATA[all I wanna do right now is cry, but instead I’m pretending like nothing is bothering me. Healthy, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanGriffinWLWT That’s should be “hat” but I guess I’ll have to start actually doing my hair again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I respect Tayshia so much more after this convo with Colton wow @BachelorABC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on a new one today:) #boughnerart #paintsketch #sketchingwithpaint #burntsienna #onmyeasel #artist #artwork… https://t.co/PgWHFT6L67]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re great so we hope we see you next time you’re in Nashville!!! And if you’re still hanging around Tequila toni… https://t.co/ZyRKN8VsFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[WATCH: Unarmed Mexican immigration officers were attacked by members of the latest caravan after the government off… https://t.co/MSWML1b5uW]]></document><document><![CDATA[NRA casually suggests shooting Nancy Pelosi for supporting gun safety https://t.co/XM5EYfqEZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[if i could turn back time i’d go to a 1D up all night of tmh concert. that’s all i ask]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RWPUSA @realDonaldTrump Unbelievably mentally ill that he does not know this has been happening for decades!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/OnE4ixipHD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/5kVHBfi6Vx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officerdaddo It’s not spam, we like seeing him, he’s sooo precious y’all are blessed! 💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crissbarrera Yo solo ,soy perro en el horóscopo chino 😂😂.Besos Cris bella!!💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti It was clear he has lack of knowledge, struggles to make solid points, did not answer the question… https://t.co/BtyNE6749z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StrokerAceKid @KyleBusch @JoeGibbsRacing @mmschocolate @NASCAR Hmmmm chocolate]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WattersWorld @JesseBWatters @realDonaldTrump So, why do we have 13 Republicans voting against our President of the United States?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@POTUS I live in Panama City, Florida. Lots of your voters do. You need to come visit again please. 5 months after… https://t.co/gnMP645dDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[niggas love to get all spiritual and religious when you leave that ass alone lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/vzHxrDuE5B]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tenacious_O @ThatWokeAuntie @magi_jay @ShimonPro Actually it was a miscommunication that you’ve oversimplified usi… https://t.co/ISjJWFqgMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonact I would agree because the early 2000's I had a set up just like that in my classroom. In the 70's I had r… https://t.co/HkQJWk7q6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have the most creative colleagues! Starry Night, American Gothic, Mona Lisa and The Scream have never looked so c… https://t.co/kRAM3mtNb1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bjcreigh It is showing our kids how to be disrespectful and throw food instead of being thankful for it and eating it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MadMaxMusquin Tous les ans c’est la même histoire... j’ai fait la même depuis New York avant un avion. Laisse moi… https://t.co/bS4qldkAtV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GFrondizi Porque nunca se actualizaron los programas que se dieron antes ni ahora, por eso. El gobierno es muy ineficaz , muy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working until 1800hrs. (@ BlueCross BlueShield of WNY - @bcbswny in Buffalo, NY) https://t.co/lyGrJaoeS2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DogginTrump @NBCNews I have not minute respect for anyone who tries to say marriage isn’t for everybody. Love is l… https://t.co/UWS2HKmWlE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #transformationtuesday !!! Both recent pics! I think I am much prettier as a lady! Thoughts!? #drag… https://t.co/iJKvH8ovRS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some angry Tio Hectors. Low Rez because I can’t find the originals on CamScanner. Will probably repost later.   Peo… https://t.co/NzAkRihxJ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another fabulous performance for the @SparkmanPerc #ALLMeansALLMCSS @MadCoSchools @SHSSenators https://t.co/CSlTpsIdGr]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sB7CggCY80  CLICK - DONATE - SHARE 💙💙💙  Ready 2 Roll Day Post #28: We are SO “READY” for our 13th annu… https://t.co/QvUbF2oTc4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyome who bought Pilots tickets for Columbus CHECK YOUR EMAIL. I woke up to this. I got this for BOTH NIGHTS of my… https://t.co/efwt7RBBng]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BankScrewedUs @BankofAmerica The locked my debit card without them even notifying me]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy #InternationalWomensDay to all my girlies!!! beyond thankful for the many strong &amp; beautiful women in my life 🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[People don’t fall outta love, you realize you were never in love to begin with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AFH|SIR one week under contract!  #simplybest #springmarket #sothebysbrand #sellwithme #marketingproperties… https://t.co/RAYfp2xhJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fire ceremony to the gods for all the blessings flowing through me and to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The story highlights the shortcomings of the ADA’s legal protections. “Reasonable accommodations” are out the windo… https://t.co/IOoiXegBAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teachinb @pinkbikes1 @erhill88 THIS! This is how we need to begin our work with teams, districts, cohorts! Then al… https://t.co/W7AxNA4Pk6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want to work at Mercy Health? We're hiring in #StLouis, MO! Click for details: https://t.co/jk6qUB5kce #Physician]]></document><document><![CDATA[I Know Who I am has been sold. But she will be available as 10 limited edition 8x 10 prints. The top two are still… https://t.co/jNonNdeOsW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe we need to bring better corporate jobs @townofws  We need to keep feet on the streets to sustain daytime… https://t.co/SXDSJpza7y]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JADKASS45 IF, YOU HAD ANY #COMMONSENSE #YOUWILL #PULL OUT OF THE #ELECTION2020 "KNEW WHAT IN THE HELL AWAITS YOU!!… https://t.co/kg8xC5cUGW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ResidenceInn I replied back and it seems the shuttle driver continues to work for your company. @Marriott that is a shame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People still think she fucking and not getting paid to give these men exposure?? Who is this man??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimGuruLyndsay Situations like these are tricky and sometimes mistakes are made. I think the fact that you all hav… https://t.co/OHE7Ydarrx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JakeMorris186 Happy Belated Birthday! I hope you had a great day with your beautiful family!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JessicaFennen When we had ours (sadly, crypto got them 😔😔😔) they were the joy of our lives. Would love to own one… https://t.co/sVRNm6NeLK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Economic Justice is exacting repair amongst a group of people suffering under the atrocities for 400… https://t.co/Y0yFF49Xod]]></document><document><![CDATA[At 4:10pm yesterday, I became an aunt for the first time to this beautiful little one. Welcome to the fam, Charlott… https://t.co/C4Q1UzVHjM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best of luck this weekend Daddy as you play golf in South Carolina! We love and miss you!🏌️‍♂️ https://t.co/QpJxPNDZ6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was watching The Bachelor...now, my Valentine candy has disappeared!! Lord, the stress!! @BachelorABC @colton… https://t.co/wVxeOS6N5O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alliecape That’s hilarious! Hey if this Education thing doesn’t work out! Even people who don’t appreciate the val… https://t.co/uR7MrisHJT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also worth noting that I had a midwife with me in the delivery room, ended up having a c-section and my son needed… https://t.co/fyHRDWBWie]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pepeandarnold Sorry. They are extremely cute and very entertaining girls.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yung mga BN mas alam pa ang endorsement ni Meng. Paano naging Exdeal ang MAC? Di nyo tlaga ma accept na pang intern… https://t.co/hqb4MoV4N1]]></document><document><![CDATA[ashton irwin is my happiness and i wish he knew how much i love and appreciate him :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goin hard this morning!… You Can Do It by Ice Cube https://t.co/tqBCRqkzuw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IssitaMarie I wonder if there is a way we can DIY some next time you're in town!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjkjjk1977 @FresnoStateMBB Maybe he wanted the seniors to have a great send-off]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roomba tried to eat my pearl project! 100” of pearls traveling around the living room ! 🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️🤦🏻‍♀️… https://t.co/nTnDG3ycX9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DragonMom98 @MsAFromBK @lno09281978 @SandiMarie79 @SabreKevin1639 @SabresFunStats @audsabres @jimmyreu81… https://t.co/VkWXyngeI9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look, I’m not one to complain but I paid around 7.50 with tax for this half salad from @panerabread. There is barel… https://t.co/74Eeh7qFy1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Busy night at Gravity yoga. 2 Thursday eve trapeze yoga classes, then quick set up for Bibi McGill. You can see her… https://t.co/oeMXslw47S]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you,@ABrindisiNY, for voting yes on #HR8, a bill to require background checks on all gun sales! I'm thankful… https://t.co/SI7c8S7LQl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t sleep. Still on a high from another phenomenal #Pac12WBB⁠ ⁠ tournament. To our student-athletes, coaches, sup… https://t.co/Wp9jFBOjzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just spent 2 fucking hours waiting at urgent care to be told to gargle with hot water and salt and to take Advil]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw a Lucha Libre show in Mexico. The luchador ripped off his mask to reveal another mask under. Roxxxy Andrews’ influence everywhere]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HenneyLarry @SpeakerPelosi @realDonaldTrump @senatemajldr @SenateGOP The only fear monger is the one who lives in… https://t.co/gDwjihV3cE]]></document><document><![CDATA[feels good buying my mom an apple watch and some airpods knowing damn well she won’t know how to use them   but she’s happy :)))]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyone know what all the copters over Silver Lake/Los Feliz are about? #silverlake #losfeliz #griffithpark]]></document><document><![CDATA[💡Con Sue Photography and Design💡  🚚 Like our photos...Follow our IG 🚛  This photo taken by: Connie Wheeler… https://t.co/C56zQ0Olfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s thumbs up . Recovery in siesta is the key 🔥❤️☀️ https://t.co/CirXjhxDyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LeadinLeviathan I don’t understand exactly what you mean ?? Def interested 💫 plz explain]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of these days I’ll really have to drop a debut solo album on the TL https://t.co/QLjqQGAPgO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So when I found out I was pregnant I was with @mxssx_ @erika_cortez8  and after we were like nah we need to go to p… https://t.co/v2SS9MCfh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matt_Kroschel @SummitDailyNews @SummitSheriffCO @DillonPDCO @Krystal93Radio @AAAColorado Great - blast and well de… https://t.co/BGCsJPgdHy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now that we understand that Jesse Smollett maybe unwell, we should rally around him and make sure he gets well and… https://t.co/WQttV8L0c8]]></document><document><![CDATA[The cat is sleeping peacefully in the sunshine today. He is calm and happy this fine warm day. Some days that cat h… https://t.co/yZqLUo0zWO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I unlocked $35 Rush tickets for #ChoirBoyBroadway at @MTC_NYC on @TodayTix! Unlock here: https://t.co/Uhez88Mb0g #TodayTixRush]]></document><document><![CDATA[@x_marieeeeee 😫 I ain’t expect no cup ping tho you fucked me up with that one]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Amazon Gift Card Giveaway is LIVE 😱 Now YOU have a Daily Chance of Getting it 100% FREE in the Link Below   Cli… https://t.co/xjb3YJz4JD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein I don’t know who president trump is but I know I will never vote for trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TWUG to you Donnie. I can’t wait to get a real hug tho. One day my time will come. I’ve waited 30 years what a lit… https://t.co/cFmXN7gRD4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#oakland #rental                     2 Bedroom  1 1/4  bathroom $2800 Rent.                  $2800 Deposit.… https://t.co/B7rE1I8nvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s non stop high flying action at @MarvelOnTour @StateFarmArena #MarvelUniverseLive #MarvelBlackPanther  Catch th… https://t.co/To4ti17SEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[yu killed yo own son mom/yo wife ohhh iyanla PLEASE SAVE THIS FAMILY LIFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aaaangieloza @wmnisadevil_ @mishizzle94 @valeao_ What color was the thread?! It has to be red or else it won’t work!!!!! Lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everything has been working out in my favor what did I do to deserve this?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught taking a selfie with @andybankertv on the big monitor. Happy Friday from your @KPLR11 7p team! Don't forget,… https://t.co/R9NvrVMNue]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LifeNewsHQ Jesus came to give life and save lives. Children are a gift not to be murdered. He also came so we can… https://t.co/nSJjb27w2A]]></document></documents></author>