<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are not my president. You are a Russia owned tool. https://t.co/pZamSCa4qS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailySabah I'm hopeful that Texas prevents this invasion of our economy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Masataka Yoshida (grand slam) encabezó la ofensiva de Japón al producir 5 carreras, y México cayó 6-0 para dividir… https://t.co/DlkAAW19hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Asharp52 As they should. I’m not opposed to kids in after school care getting free dinner either]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jayasrinivasan @cardcataloggirl @spritewrites You know there’s a short spin-off novel called Slade House?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey IC is anyone hearing a whole lot of crows going crazy outside or have I finally lost my sanity?]]></document><document><![CDATA[City to spend $300M on new boilers for NYCHA buildings: https://t.co/yqGtIiw33T]]></document><document><![CDATA[N4TRQ-5 Near CHKD Health Center at Oakbrooke, Chesapeake, VA https://t.co/PBPtuqZ8lv #APRS 13b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SKORNorth Alright Eddie, enough of the fastballs. Start throwing the breaking ball.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Statements by @Corey_Feldman reflected suspicion for the alleged victims' stories in the critical Michael Jackson d… https://t.co/3mzjaYZbZ8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unicorn and T Rex celebration workout @ LA Fitness - IRVINE - CROSSROADS https://t.co/BVGkmXKtlG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edarm1221 @JimGaffigan @FoxwoodsCT He’s Fkn hilarious. I’ve seen him live 4x in CT, one of my absolute favorites !! https://t.co/GfGO0cmf7x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@C3Cmarkst @RLSTERN9 @GatorDave_SEC Yep many times.  And sometimes we lost him eventually.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you cheat on me or if you get raped same goes for me including Baby forms. Stay away from that guy. I've been si… https://t.co/ZPR3MYmb9s]]></document><document><![CDATA[solved the mystery.  It was Col. Mustard, in the library, with a candlestick. 🕵🏻‍♂️ #nailedit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stonecold2050 @FiatChrysler_NA @michiganalumni @ColgateCareers @CP_News @MI_ESGR @EspanolaSBDC @Michigan_Irish… https://t.co/Lu6xUFymR7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FScopers @ItsANewDayYes @metsandnesfan @Target @FullyPoseable @HOVAAA @MJGIV79 @BillMiekina @RepackAttack @Mattel… https://t.co/sw3uHVMMwZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JPHILLBSU @JPTum @dxendres @MickTidrow @dbrant03 @CharliesChirps This one is called chili beef soup.. you are not making just chili.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz @GovRonDeSantis I hope you get voted out you racist right wing Idiot! And I hope you go to Jail for s… https://t.co/pjYZI3ANTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[when i find myself in times of trouble john @mulaney comes to me https://t.co/kTW5NQd9YQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenAndWoods But nobody's really worried about Zion financially, are they? Isn't the idea of paying NCAA athletes f… https://t.co/0sL50QPANK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night of pumahoops and @mrkreamwynwood. 🏀👟🍦 - Miami Beach - 12.5.2018 @puma @shopnicekicks #PumaBasketball… https://t.co/GKFb7lfDiB]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Pool F - @MississaugaBall def. @NTBasketBall 67-56 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Yay, just what we need from a shameless political shill—more fake Christian pandering! What will this g… https://t.co/grK7V9e6wy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerFernando Finding out that Rolex Branded Politician you loved and adored is nothing but a fake imitation of… https://t.co/aJdFUzBye8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASFried If you ever want to have that debate, we can have it.  I’m currently reading @KevinGutzman’s biography on… https://t.co/qVWJI3iwNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ceciliakang @anniekarni @PatriciaMazzei Doubt they came over the border with duct tape on their mouths.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better game if Zion play definitely but I cant say they would’ve won cuz we came out playing defense from the jump… https://t.co/s8cpAfbp1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wind 2.0 mph WNW. Barometer 30.262 in, Rising quickly. Temperature 16.8 °F. Rain today 0.00in. Humidity 70%]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CHawk_Talk Wouldn't a low round kicker pick cost less and not be worse than suggested free agent?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alicere @lisasaurstomp It shook up in Healdsburg too - I was v smol but I remember feeling it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Get off my freaking bumper!!” I yell as I’m right on the person in front of me’s bumper]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianklaas only the people who cant work or make more living off the taxpayers are left. Lots of jobs out there still, no qualified people.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my #listing in #Hallandale #FL  #realestate #realtor https://t.co/PT41LBpDGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HJPreller @ChangeThePadres I've returned stuff 2 years later that I wasn't even sure I had bought there and didn't… https://t.co/JXYXrEeqpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Mead For Speed by @SociableCider at @sirbensduluth — https://t.co/rC4xZRGcsn]]></document><document><![CDATA[3/4/2019 - 10:23 Temp: 25.7F   Hum:  52% Wind: 4.0 mph Baro: 30.470in. &amp; Rising Rain: 0.00 in. https://t.co/QhqGWeELtz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I got this for behaving on the @United flight today. @ Orlando International Airport (MCO) https://t.co/wjoDieOqCP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatKaczmarczyk @accessoriness_ @spampinato_erin Here you go! https://t.co/JlO1lCrfs5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Amarillo Bid Qualfier this weekend, both girls going at it  today, one in am pool and other in pm! #winning 🏐💪🏻 https://t.co/Rqr9r3v0TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two years ago today i witnessed the greatest coaching performance of my lifetime  out of @MelissaVillanti]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Interesting... where are the trillions you need for your policies going to come from? 1.7 billion is… https://t.co/LwFhkzicdu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TennIowa @RepMarkMeadows My God how stupid some of you people are! You want to throw away the constitution to serv… https://t.co/1ti47UcbKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Ford Taurus. RIP Chevy Cruze. #autonews #ripsedans (note the sad send-off for the Cruze with a cardboard sign😢)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LHumeSastre @Sheila_Copps I don’t support either of these women. They’re blatant examples of toxic feminists in po… https://t.co/5241B0TcCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noguecito @magdhagomez @lii_cardoso @econoclasta Pero analiza el porque... https://t.co/sczeeRXvn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[welp on the bright side at least it looks like this last hour will be chill.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump campaign spokesperson Katrina Pierson is asked how many blacks work in the West Wing of the White House (BTW,… https://t.co/4L7ILPloeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wreck: delays inbound in #NortheastRaleigh on Louisburg Rd @ Fox Rd near Spg Forest Rd #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[7 months.    How did it go by so fast?   #parenting #Parenthood #7Months #TimeSlowDown https://t.co/HwoqxP4rim]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak @BreitbartNews #JamesClyburn just told #AOC  #RashidaTalib #IIhanOmar to hold his beer.  As he goes aft… https://t.co/Q7HzJD4jqN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TJCarpenterShow He is just a dude, nothing special. If he had been drafted by the Browns he would have already bee… https://t.co/RkPs5avYKD]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a sad state of affairs when the player agents achieve celeb status. Wtf!? Lol.   Either way, this is helpful i… https://t.co/2s6yyPkoQJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hahahaha the dummycrats  are the modern day fascists  you lout Fox News Bans Ad For Documentary About American Nazi… https://t.co/GZVGltIHVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Christianity music video: Yuav Muaj Ib Hnub (Hmong Christian song) https://t.co/cUNgoQr3Ki]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @AmberTurner_x @Neesy_Rizzo  @khloe @SarahRussi @pb_miranda @LindseyPelas @Laci_Kay_Somers @MiSSLHOMMEDiEU… https://t.co/TdUzSKyBTp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows So you mean the trump tower meeting never happened, Manafort never gave 75 pages of campaign pollin… https://t.co/M1HSwtWsXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DOSMutt @PaddyTopp @eswecker @JamesAALongman @sommervilletv @ABCWorldNews Following you because I like the way you… https://t.co/DYccTk7zM3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@funder @Cluelesscomedy3 He was probably trying to put on his Klan mask during these stops &amp; wasn’t focused on his driving]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@marty_lederman Is the claim that precedes this line: "especially one...that represents a doctrine promising redem… https://t.co/wKt8mKRpua]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FCBayernES @jamesdrodriguez Cuándo el conductor, el mago 🧙‍♂️, el diez 10, juega, todos juegan mejor.]]></document><document><![CDATA[you know a 2 inch dick is close to 5 which is close to 10 which means i have a 10 inch dick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics @cnnbrk @HillaryClinton you should be going to jail https://t.co/p0FBs1wckz]]></document><document><![CDATA[#WCW @MileyCyrus @noahcyrus @MollyAMcGrath @MollyQerim @oliviaculpo @AshWilke 😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeBleedBlueNYC Zebras good for a goal a game against us- there was NO call until they saw he was “hurt”. Hit on sh… https://t.co/iquEadDdXU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@margaretcox2299 @Chriskl70208387 @fellspeaks @basedinfidel8 @AlexWY18 @SmackYeti @Americanthatguy @johnw299… https://t.co/RqXOJ99H75]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bravesjt So shameful!  Makes me not want to wear my  " I'm With Stupid 👉 "  T-Shirt ever again!  I may save it in… https://t.co/i0rTxzZfws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_principessa007 @khloekardashian It would have to be during the NBA off season.]]></document><document><![CDATA[New original music.  Please have a listen 🙏🏼  https://t.co/3h8qMmN08T https://t.co/lfuWjhG1HH]]></document><document><![CDATA[He should be ashamed of himself propagating this false informationbut- Mark Warner says there's 'enormous' evidence… https://t.co/1FSYTj5RLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@motionautotv First time getting into the jz motors. If on a budget what’s better 2jzge and turbo it or get a 1jzgte?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He was your fixer for 10 years. Everyone knows Trump is a fraud.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, @MBTA how is the 83 bus supposed to pick up passengers??? #mbtafail @cambikelanes @carsNbikelane https://t.co/lT7r2yIM0c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewrsorkin I followed this for the last 18 months. I read the deal that was negotiated. I thought it protected… https://t.co/CYwHYn1BJ3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@katie_stp We have a friend that is a pro photographer, did a lot for us. Tiffany Bolk is her name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LauraBray_ @AngelaBelcamino If you can make a list like this, who is responsible for those issues now and who is r… https://t.co/J8uyUaMnkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was in HS there was this thing called an asthma mobile. Since so many kids growing up near the refineries ge… https://t.co/OAFbiLPXV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[SGASD will be operating on a 2-hour delay tomorrow, Thursday, February 21, 2019. We will continue to monitor road c… https://t.co/BHkt3q9vp2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deal end March 31 or when the 10 followers reserve. @ The Hibiscus House Bed &amp; Breakfast https://t.co/VlgxXSu3Oh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HorriblePete @lakie_lou I agree usually. But they go great with vodka.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united @DENAirport How long will you service Portland, Maine from Denver? Is this just summer service!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump HUGE - VERY DANGEROUS!! RUSSIAN WEAPONS - MUSLIM Islamic Centers being used to cache Russian weapo… https://t.co/jdYv5fYtdj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever we find ourself wishing we had:  a mentor, friend, encourager, father figure, mom, etc.  What if we starte… https://t.co/gGr8DDUiyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boeing needs to ground those new 737 MAX 8s. How does a brand new plane crash twice within one year? So scary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BMEsTalk @Ayodele_Har78 @ByronDurias @WmStubbs @PhilEchols @CBVentures1 #BMEsTalk   Steve from Atlanta and i was n… https://t.co/CMTVSzfixD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lunar Love  NASA: “We are going to go to the moon, and we are going to go sustainably. That means we are going to s… https://t.co/mXr4F1tVDA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another busy month. Proud, as always, to be a part of the @NC5 team. Thanks for making us the most watched station… https://t.co/WYJxlGt5xF]]></document><document><![CDATA[(My Memories From My Facebook Page). Monday Motivation From The Home Depot Careers FB Page On March 2nd, 2019.  Wha… https://t.co/IpOtKZm6lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KimStrassel You forgot the fact that she is Muslim. That's just about the only religious group that socialist prot… https://t.co/FULbOlateV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beer_parade @KoreyEdwards6 @GoodbyeCali @WarAngel1111 @godbless333 @EnjoyTheQShow1 @SantaPatriot @PA2NY2015… https://t.co/jvwwxRIugC]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we didn’t have to struggle through times in our lives, we would never develop our character.… https://t.co/I7caQ1eNuJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think my favorite that I started doing is making a monthly playlist to keep track of my jams/moods]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes Chris, can you post the tweet you featured with the attorney stating a comparison of sentencing for hi… https://t.co/w5DUGOkup9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cyberwitchlexi I only watch what gets returned in direct search and have assumed for years all recommendation arw… https://t.co/LeXpL61Az0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Night My Friends In Hollywood Los Angeles California. I Love You Guys. Love Our High Functioning Autistic Frie… https://t.co/wW5zGkv3XZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandesIris @TrichomeTony @seanhannity Reg ppl? Like QUINCY MA? City of Presidents? fake news? Most valuable thing… https://t.co/9ezpeER2we]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @Carl834 @FoxNews @TuckerCarlson YEAH YOU HAVE THE MEGAPHONE - BOYCOTT FOX ADVERITSERS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jben0 not sure if you consciously jumped from equilibrium to long run- but agree!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhillyQ_ @uedient @GoboMontaco @LadyStephC @love4thegameAK @TransformativeV @RedPilledNative @TrophyTruck_Q… https://t.co/PIU7CAvTbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Frank &amp; Berry by @BeerdBrewing at @planbspring — https://t.co/H1T8idMVzG]]></document></documents></author>