<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@tina_mac12 I’m living!! Taking each day as it comes!! How have you been!!? How are you?? https://t.co/rB08M0Dbki]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alannah_alfonso @ErickFalero @PanakinCaboose I feel like I've seen enough.  Thanks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying so hard to be happy and not in a mood. Not working. Need something to suppress my feelings, emotions, &amp; anxiety]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scherptediepte this is how California Pigeons #JustDoIt California Spinners TV’s...  #Pigeon Hole w/ Host Damian… https://t.co/XNk1qxzw1r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@therunchat A2: That I can casually wear race shirts as if it was a band shirt and I went to their latest concert. #runchat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ladanieladea @GrahamAllen_1 @realDonaldTrump It's as fake as your hair color.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BruceWolfChi Classic how they strive to mitigate data which don’t support their leftist premise of gender biased compensation.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sad part? All my hard earned money will be gone and it’ll be hard to remake it all again and in turn I cannot go to Virginia on my own.]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those ppl who think POTUS is a criminal must listen gossip or other news media . Nothing my 70years have I ever… https://t.co/CjAi8f0nPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OhioBIkeLawyer @csymrl I dig the genre known as quite-popular-and-familiar-tune-as-done-in-a-different-style-and-o… https://t.co/sjProMqjlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Raptors jerseys seem to equal @DetroitPistons wear tonight....good thing they gave out Blake Griffen jerseys at th… https://t.co/y4Reo6MBjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murphy59 Exhibit 1012047483 why #wallsdontwork https://t.co/Zk2tU3Vgi7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheMarkPantano @1tc @AOC Are you serious, that performasnce was after how many days, 5. God help us, if she is not… https://t.co/awXFguVAko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BallGame723 @mkdikes832 @fibonacci1123 @_mrfo20 @Raphy_Taffy Record broke Fuck Jordan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ghostfeeder I was just saying last week how I was an Alien3 apologist. It has some of the best character building… https://t.co/GMSv6ewYAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbeLopezAuthor @adamcarolla @PaulFitzDosDos @BaldBryan Perfect response]]></document><document><![CDATA[The day has arrived, one lucky couple will have their dreams come true.  Will you be the bride and groom who wins t… https://t.co/UDLu3fffRw]]></document><document><![CDATA[After having had a combo today, who do you think has the better sausage beef combo?]]></document><document><![CDATA[TFW your fluffy cat runs across stove while you are cooking and you smell burning fur so you have to chase the cat… https://t.co/F8oo7xS0tN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Convo I just had:  Her: You do this all the time. You have this way saying the word “Ok” with a tone that says “F**… https://t.co/UvKIG7jq3L]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BFQuinn @Bojangles_3273 And Cazzie Russell for $3? He’s widely regarded as the best player in UM history, along with Glen Rice.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabst666 @Cantguardmike @AB84 Diva? Lol before this season he never said a word. He was only acting that way becau… https://t.co/wK4XtYxlzg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tecnocato @henrikfisker Wow!!! Israel 👊🏼👊🏼👊🏼 Awesome!!! https://t.co/okFnwbitW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@4FutureSake @wacthe3 @John_Hudson @benshapiro And that refutes blocking foreign aid how?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stucam7771 Here’s a novel idea for dog owners, Trump garden gnomes, with the body of a fire hydrant and trump’s he… https://t.co/L98QPgicfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javerias @AdnanSamiLive Yup we did and your chootiya pm is going to avenge that ? Benchod !!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump He would have never been caught if he didn’t work for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheBabylonBee @BDOH HAHAHA! Maybe she should leave the earth just to get away from Israel.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricBandRakim                                   Shaking em Up  ✅                     Waking em Up   ✅… https://t.co/7S1DTreOX0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlazersBySagar If not I'm going to complain about Scott Foster for a week. That LeBron 3 was a 2 as well]]></document><document><![CDATA[TCU 🆚 Texas in a BIG conference showdown 🏀 I'm picking Texas! Who you got? Vote below! @RocketMortgage]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly to god my life is a fucking joke. Happy bachelorette party to me 😪 https://t.co/zHdiovgbx5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The whole idea of “not mixing your friend groups together” is lame af. We can all be friends ain’t no keeping it se… https://t.co/pvGmZTr13w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please come and honor the memorial of former EIU Football coach Bob Spoo. This Saturday from 1-3pm!🙂👍🏈 ⁦⁦… https://t.co/yPjAa22Cj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy will throw a party is someone other than the Phillies get Harper.   My god he’s annoying]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kevinatthelake I’ve had the privilege to work with over 200 wealthy families in my 35 year career and I can tell y… https://t.co/RQIhmeHppI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DesignationSix @Ammaxon1 @samparker926 @tomt_johns @StormMela @CJEM1226 @ward_annie @warrior_4_good @Jayd360… https://t.co/OY0ETd2YMy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE @RondaRousey @BeckyLynchWWE Becky Lynch is gonna destroy Ronnie at Wrestlemania]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TaylorNichelle1 @LWirgau @jsreinecker That’s what I ended up doing as well.  I’m not paying $1000 for a dang phone… https://t.co/o5B1wplSSW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Caught up with both Superman and Action Comics. IMO, Action Comics is the superior book. The art and story are just… https://t.co/Cyo7h0Dl1H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MynameisMok @JoeMomma833 @Riopedre31 @kaysintBB @JonAnthony7 @lynn_maryellen @KingPeachDP @woodywood1999… https://t.co/8MIt557iPD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CamGuthrie @JoeyColeman So this will be the end of closed door meetings. Have true transparency.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[this really one of the best songs ever and it hasn’t even been released  DROP THE ALBUM PLEASE]]></document><document><![CDATA[sooo if i assume two things and then only one assumption is clarified is the other assumption actually being done?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobertStrauss @WWE @WWEUK @WWENXT @WWEPC @WWENetwork Awesome Bro.... Congratulations!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@H5rre61 @KingLadyGaga From an artistic standpoint, sure.  I would just be surprised if WarnerBros/Interscope won’t… https://t.co/FM3gYvHxj8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VolRumorMill It was and Andy Kennedy didn’t have the guts to call out the refs, wants to keep that gig]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎶 Look at my face while you talkin' to me 'Cause we only have one conversation a week Can I get one conversation at least? 🎶]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jontester what do you say for yourself? You disgust me that you would sign on to this. Not #Montana not for #Women… https://t.co/W4va9XVmXx]]></document><document><![CDATA[When Toonami brought back #OnePiece, I started watching it from episode 207. I really enjoyed it a ton so I went ba… https://t.co/wLIGIKmWp1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamLazzara It’s like no one has ever seen a gangster movie. https://t.co/ZnYAnNRWyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chadloder Taxes in which context?   Taxes are an abstract of laws and norms.   What services should taxes provide?… https://t.co/FUaz9txVga]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/FPfAb0gxRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BombosMedallion @rardk64 @forgotthehyphen The Incredibles 1 looks like ass now]]></document><document><![CDATA[He lived 2/22/1732-12/14/1799 (served 4/30/1789-3/4/1797). If you like the main portrait, I did one of all the pres… https://t.co/h9iT5dxGDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shamusroan13 @leeleebb21 @Disney @DisneyWeddings @MomO5Tiff @jbnotbeiber Tuck those damn kids in and save us lady!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AppSame Throw in FREE college tuition &amp; FREE Healthcare - it's a deal🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisMcTague3 I could use one..Michael is going thru some pain as they try to fit him for a steel brace.😢]]></document><document><![CDATA[@3onyourside Parks and Recreation already covered this issue 🥓🥓🥓 https://t.co/WE4k2mpHPK]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Qué les pareció #elmamelucotv de hoy? ¿Se les acalambró el asunto picarones? Hahaha Los esperamos #lunes a… https://t.co/NWC8OxL2uP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@homerclease @bcarrasco09_ @DDuggan21 Thats so dumb. This is a real time business bro that some]]></document><document><![CDATA[The economic damage in Venezuela is among the worst in Latin American history. Staggering Exodus: Millions of Venez… https://t.co/Y2UrRXdPhz]]></document><document><![CDATA[No, no, no. No driver's licenses or municipal franchise for green card or undocumented immigrants. #NYCVotes #PublicAdvocateDebate]]></document><document><![CDATA[Prabu Elangovan registered physiotherapist most recently at Lorne Park Integrated Health Clinic,1150 Lorne Park Rd.… https://t.co/BdDa0zK45i]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Bday @Mal_Whitmore !! have a fucking great day🎉 https://t.co/pBezbZ2CGc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning @JeffNBCBoston , @susantran , and @DeniseNBCBoston 😊 Watching @NBC10Boston right now 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow It's like they are living in a different world.  They almost seem hostile to our country.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lindseywasson @rikkiking Don't forget train people and plane people too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[1 year ago today we reached 61°F here in Lowell, MI and as a result caused a rapid snow melt, which led to the infa… https://t.co/alEgiUxKyB]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is amusing. #hilarity #snicker #grin #amusing https://t.co/vLmH9Zi1ae]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ira wins by Tech Fall 16-0 in 4:37 over VanBlaricum from Alma to move into the consolation finals!… https://t.co/GSjE2uV3pP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@X62048239 @ChiefHubbaBubba @B52Malmet @JustinTrudeau @CDCgov This got barely any play but CDC overestimated prescr… https://t.co/zXFCpMTJpX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Megabite by @HopButcher @ Miskatonic Brewing Company — https://t.co/wSyHmV5bKi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Made in Downtown LA 👟 @ Smorgasburg Los Angeles https://t.co/pAq1SZ1GEb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well yeah, but she dances...and she’s kinda cute...and she’s a fresh new face.  Expecting her to actually know stuf… https://t.co/NoIK4vm1hx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This tweet implies that 90% of men either watch too much porn, too many Seth Rogen movies, or are nerds. This tweet… https://t.co/CmcQRKdXXN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen Blah blah blah it’s getting old Ed aren’t you getting sick of it? I am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@silagechopper We’ve got them on two trucks. It’s really nice when it gets warmed up, but doesn’t help until it get… https://t.co/qfjFOpv1NL]]></document><document><![CDATA[You have to show a look Have a look, or give a look Faces, beautiful No one ugly allowed 👄💋💄 — - - -… https://t.co/J4D9yCQo5c]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #winterwonderland view from the 4th floor of tower B #snowmageddon #idesofmarch @ Center Square Towers Community https://t.co/5qGro9gU14]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tcraigschilling @DSports24 If he didn’t know JJ Evans, highly doubtful Lady Moscona knew Rolo.  RIP.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars,  Mustangs! #readacrossamerica #spiritweek https://t.co/LDVYH9LC0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[1-2-3 for @JoshStaumont to finish off the @Royals first #CactusLeague gsme of the season. #FreeJoshStaumont #AlwaysRoyals]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aila saw these @jumpman23 IV Retro “Valentine’s Day” on the @j23app and “had to have them.” You’re welcome A. Now f… https://t.co/nx6PCZXQ8Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nebrasketball is soft. Always will be until we get a coaching staff that actually knows how to coach.  We need “One… https://t.co/atUTI49wgg]]></document><document><![CDATA[More #Bauhaus at #RockefellerMemorialChapel in #chicago with #PeterMurphy #DavidJ https://t.co/ZA3VrShV9s https://t.co/RVOGG3MHra]]></document><document><![CDATA[Target 11 Exclusive: Pa. congressional members put pressure in feds to transfer registered sex offender who was rel… https://t.co/C1aNwWpUX6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had one of these old school inhalers. Instead I’m using this. #VicksMan. #SickMan #VicksMakesItAllBetter https://t.co/hlt3sioaKn]]></document><document><![CDATA[C.J Smith hits his first homerun of the season in the bottom of the sixth. That homerun was the second of his caree… https://t.co/PypDOt2n6U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel for all these black actors who WASTE their talent on films like cringe inducing shit.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Was there ever a substantive argument presented to the whole "Leaving the EU would allow more funds for the NHS" ta… https://t.co/grr1SdFhA1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Check out my pals new album yo. You won’t be disappointed.  Cheers @ZLenn1 🥂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beccabluesky @ClimateEcho IMO tell her yes since the fact that she asked the question means she already knows the… https://t.co/cVQZ9ukVIG]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐼🎙👊🏼 These type of comedy rooms always filter through the weak ones. I LOVE BAR SHOWS! Thanks @ben9humor for the sp… https://t.co/kN6rj4P3d1]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NorthKorea Hackers attacked American infrastructure cyber-security during #Trump’s #NorthKoreaSummit. “The Art of… https://t.co/CH1hXWadjc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GunnieMadcat @Tactical_review I had a certification for completing a training course in Quebec when I was young (i… https://t.co/VItBJ3kADo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamGMJohnson @jmrivera02 The result of Smollet’s hoax and the uncritical support of his believers is widespread da… https://t.co/ycHySxQZza]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the end, the people must take control of their country and tie down the politicians, judges, government officers… https://t.co/seGgzfh8Rz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dnlnwmn @T_HUD_REPPIN @emilyd333 I bought this for the boy when he entered design school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#tbt to my @ColourPopCo review ❤️ living for all this shine https://t.co/JrIl1jR1fY]]></document></documents></author>