<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@handel_l @EricVonHaden1 @BrendaWinkowsk2 @KayaJones @realDonaldTrump @KayaJones0 @TomiLahren @RealDrGina @JoeBiden… https://t.co/iwQBlGlHfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArshadMTB @xoxo_allyah @IvaPobi @jakeyoncetv @manilaluzon Just saying, not mention challenges were set up for Ben and shangela to excel...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AkihiroArsene oh god they're so embarrassing like I had a subscription to one of those preteen girl magazines just so I could get them]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s been at this a long time. I’ve really grown to respect Cole. He’s not my favorite pbp guy ever, but he’s certa… https://t.co/zvIVIBQLkm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope my friends in Durham will support a “yes” vote to expand housing choices for Durham.  The same thing needs t… https://t.co/VnnNCG37qB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure after last #weekend if I'm behind or I was #productive. I guess it's how I look at it. Now #MondayMotivation I got stuff done.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyO @SpeakerPelosi Transfers from the Army Corps of Engineers must be approved by contracting officers and fund… https://t.co/OTs5ijeIDh]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s a real nice win for #45 Belinda Bencic, beating #2 Simona Halep 4-6, 6-4, 6-2 to reach the Dubai semifinals.… https://t.co/824rykDTcm]]></document><document><![CDATA[OKC hotboxed tf outta the @CriterionOKC for #2009Tour .   Also, @CurrenSy_Spitta a damn fool 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdrianDeLaGarza Y eso en que ayuda para el beneficio de la ciudad o el municipio ? Mejorarian que ?  Nomás es para… https://t.co/sxJMqO9UDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s stop lettin juice wrld day he’s gonna kill his girlfriend if she leaves]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bridge #construction #homosassa #florida @ Homosassa, Florida https://t.co/CRiTaOwdGB]]></document><document><![CDATA[my school really put up signs with a picture of the bathroom and under it they said “this is not a place for you to… https://t.co/6h3otKjWs6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honored to say I’ve received my first Ivy League offer from Princeton University! #MakeHi2t0ry https://t.co/9H8Te0QbSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigmar98 @CivilWarHumor McC has one in DC, one in Philly.  I don't think (😆) he has one anywhere in NYC which is f… https://t.co/ZcFF86hpKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLMcArt I wouldn’t mind bringing him but he sits on the couch next to me in therapy and I don’t want him to get th… https://t.co/k2KxH3AcSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[***EUPORA SOFTBALL*** Oxford Tournament  Pontotoc - 11 Eupora - 2 Mid 6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yoooooo I just remembered I had a dream I was getting chased by a bear that was getting chased by a moose. Wtfff 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanks High School girls wrestling six-straight State titles https://t.co/elqdTI4mrl via @YouTube @HanksHS_Knights… https://t.co/oiP3zGwtaO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisPBaconJr Warning?  Sweeeeeeet...you know I have Daddy issues! 😜❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ranzratte1337 @xmg_gg @OBSProject Über CPU rendern geht auch nicht ? Streamlabs obs ausprobieren, ich hatte Proble… https://t.co/UohbY5tpi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last nights buttered cod with simple side salad #keto #cleaneats #sojerzphood #boom @ South Philadelphia https://t.co/9CsrtXFpmr]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s really pathetic abot @AlexWardVox’s bullshit story is that he was putting HIS OWN WORDS in Moon’s mouth free… https://t.co/DatF2F7kIc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Engagement is high when students have choice on how they want to collect data for their own picture graph.… https://t.co/AVNsepNfRs]]></document><document><![CDATA[You still try to get friends to join @LinkedIn. #SignYouKnowYoureGettingOlder]]></document><document><![CDATA[@levarburton @StephanieCozart @MicaBurton You know I gotta say it: Looking Good! Oh and you too, Levar, hee hee‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers And Alex Smith Add To Previous Investments In High-Tech Helmet Maker VICIS via @forbes https://t.co/0iflef3JiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[The thing about an 8:30 tip is that I’m already three beers deep let’s go Nuggets]]></document><document><![CDATA[have y’all tried NOT being mad at every news headline? it’s nice to not be exhausted]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t fw Young M.A. other than Ooouuu but the Thotiana remix bangs....]]></document><document><![CDATA[SCHOLARSHIPS🎓 Knights of Columbus – 2/23 Stolly Insurance Scholarship – 3/1 R.K. Thompson – 3/7 Lima Memorial Healt… https://t.co/knABnFOtQo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AtravellerERA my “Art of” book is finally supposed to deliver next week too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@primalpoly @agoonforhire @robbysoave So, do you support an executive order that forces public universities to arm… https://t.co/74U9L7EIpg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spanishpronto @travisgeist @olivernoodle @miranndacas @mariokiki bro out here rey turn filipino tho lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@henryimiller I'm 58  I've had 8 operations from 42 years of hard work without all the safety regulation we have in… https://t.co/nVv1eZkyrJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even in a "down year" the #Blackhawks are fun to watch. Maybe one day I'll say the same thing about the #MNWild .]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not going to order something expensive BECAUSE someone else is paying but I’m not changing what I’d regularly g… https://t.co/QC4GJPIeDo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JaylinEison @CoachJamison @CoachTCalhoun @EDGYTIM @lemminginsider @CoachBigPete @CedrickWilson6 Thank you bro!! You’re next just wait]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PhoenixWBB won their first playoff game last night, CONGRATULATIONS! Weather permitting, the team travels to Rosem… https://t.co/laNgJHF38X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lotsa white. Tough to drive on Rt 15. Visibility strained. Periodically plowed lane. @WTOPtraffic @WTOP https://t.co/PPtBm9ey0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows Dems are Diabolical and the enemy of the American people. Never trust them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@guatemayabyesi @jamesrgoodman @DavidHarris707 @clvtrujillo @NaranjoFdez @PrayHard972 @silvamalabet @MarycMallon… https://t.co/7EFR30pZyC]]></document><document><![CDATA[The need has been to study publicity as commodity, with a view to organizing 1/3]]></document><document><![CDATA[To the Dems that are running in 2020,..what I’d also like to see is some tax reform whereby you could take a distri… https://t.co/BbpxzMk2Pu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why is the democrat script for media people and every democrat politician always anti-American, anti-life, and anti-tax cuts?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustDoItJeff @_tupacsqueen @theswac @TSUMensHoops @TXSOTigers @TSUMBB Neither was the play by Johnson when he chok… https://t.co/r9wZZxseWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[#StartupPitchRedFlag: “If we can capture just 1% of the market we’ll make $X per year”]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔥🆕🔥  Get your Ciroc Blend Gummy Jar for only 💲🔟  Handmade mixed flava alcoholic Gummies            🔥🍬🔥❣️🔥 @ Starwoo… https://t.co/DcxEMTdcnu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm heading out soon to go swim at Ballard Pool for maybe 15-20 minutes. I walk there. I didn't do it last week because of work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to @bridgescholars for giving us the opportunity to empower there students. • • https://t.co/asFa06miyP @… https://t.co/fyk4xXa3MG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very compelling article. What are people’s thoughts on the best journals for chem research from this perspective? P… https://t.co/1B9jhLD1c3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP Orrrrrrrr, @GovernorVA has a difficult time speaking in public.   This theme may raise you money, but it won’t… https://t.co/JHbVngv9vC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Your credibility is zero. Therefore I consider this just another White House lie until I see the cost o… https://t.co/jSNFEJBgyL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir On Flight 2093 from PHX to OKC in First, 2 hour flight, still holding my jacket an hour in and nothing… https://t.co/fnGkPC1Hlj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@msdebbieallen @IamDebraLee @ErickaUrsula #legend #dancelife #dancers #Dance]]></document><document><![CDATA[Solid Brown Ale. - Drinking a Crooked Can American Brown Ale by @crookedcan at @crookedcan  — https://t.co/ukVXiVQ2Dv]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cat Savannah does the same thing to me every morning. She's my fur-lined alarm clock.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jeanette01Feb @Southwarkcathed @DoorkinsM Just making sure she gets the respect she deserves 😸]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chris_gilmore @snackmantis Shut up. La La Land was a treasure and should never be mentioned in the same breath as Buster Scruggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dodge Hellcat Redeye is a 797 HP street beast! Please click the link in my bio and SUBSCRIBE to Raiti’s Rides!… https://t.co/gqJmcOZR9g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell Agree 100% but as @stevemagness pointed out the 5k distance is globally recognized and run by all run… https://t.co/Wu6hk37McD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Three-point play for Abigail Jensen brings life to Whalen. Fort Lewis College leads Adams State women 42-38 with 4… https://t.co/yfkmMjMEh5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something tells me it's going to be a long day. Slipped on ice and destroyed my ice coffee. #WinterSucks #PlowTruck… https://t.co/W2zuFlHoRO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanAFournier Did they get good photos and post them to their social media?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos dias a todos !  menos a esas persona que en medio de una conversacion responden con un (Ah)   a esos no !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at F3 Shake Weight - @f3greensboro in Greensboro, NC https://t.co/s4ZviRcnIq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SumitaPahwa @smsaideman @ExumAM Of course.  “Until you’ve been a cop, you can’t say it’s wrong to shoot civilians… https://t.co/L5mTSSY5lK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rob__mccallum @MathoInc Haha! It’s one of those “do once” things.  And that’s it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[A man that has friends must show himself friendly; and there is a friend that's sticketh closer than a brother. Pro… https://t.co/Gaq1rHDvI1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@travisyost Maybe they come to grips that their problem is defense and they trade one of their young forwards to solidify their blueline.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nypost Why is this considered a "scandal" Tristan Thompson is an NBA player in his 20's this is what they do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWE: .@TrueKofi defeats @JEFFHARDYBRAND with an SOS, but Kofi might need an SOS of his own because looks who's wai… https://t.co/wsZQ6bGHEq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmbler @realDonaldTrump The Dems in Congress obviously do. Open borders is the ONLY reason to oppose a wall/fence.… https://t.co/oYbdRqmtYO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday March 7 - The Washington Post Politics:    House Democrats splinter over response to Rep. Omar’s alleged a… https://t.co/DzdmzYGvxK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Todas las mañanas:  Huevitos estrellados, café caliente y esta mamada de noticiero 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 @ElPulsoDeLaRepu https://t.co/S9Kd5m8Kix]]></document><document><![CDATA[@courtgolf @DawnMannix Ditto that. Worthless stuff. My brother in law has bought them all and he still sucks at golf 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DUANEALLEN #MitchMcConnell  for #president2020 https://t.co/Ed7Wz8CE8F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenThePCGuy @thatrobguy I did not need to know that. Young whippersnappers get offa my lawn!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Katie53286169 @Mingcat @Arise_Israel @RepMarkMeadows Wanna bet? https://t.co/L7nHKZTCei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listed 12 Clark Creek Circle Clayton California https://t.co/14t5KExeoZ #eastbay… https://t.co/CRbktwzqIz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LarryFlick We all must look forward and walk towards a positive outcome. Thank you Larry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahluwal The level of cruelty has no boundaries in this Trump era administration. Thanks for fighting for… https://t.co/tBuaQQjpKF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why this game needs to have an actual competitive mode running the length of the season. Not those awfully designed… https://t.co/pi55PZdHz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overthinking something just because you can overthink it isn’t productive.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is definitely not a bad idea but I don’t think the Cardinals would go for it. Don’t know if the Chargers have… https://t.co/SzRVPhuCdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[Avicci Wake Me Up Organ https://t.co/hdseZm149l via @YouTube #bethethunder #GoBolts #nhl #hockey #tblightning… https://t.co/xCKk3aDJZN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want to sleep but my brain life quotes funny quotes cute quote cartoons garfield funny... https://t.co/RFNtx6Fwkk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1067WLLZ Thank You my new reason to dump @SIRIUSXM love it and the on air lineup is pretty damn good]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice 2 mile stroll this morning #Nrc #NikeRunClub @bennettrun 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸💪💪💪 https://t.co/MCzPCylQGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sunset tonight 7p. The last time the sun went down at 7p was Sept 18th. #sunset #extrahour #DST #NJTonight… https://t.co/koXZWwf0Rx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lacktivist Thing is, right up to the wire he was hiring people, formulating policy, and saying he had no intention… https://t.co/3WP8y0dmN6]]></document><document><![CDATA[MLS Extends Contract Of Commissioner Garber Through '23 https://t.co/fRNj4ZgD2p via @sbjsbd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LindsayHanner Wow that’s awesome  have a great time at Daytona 500 this weekend. That’s on my bucket list .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iamjohnpollock UNBELIEVABLE.  Wow.  May never see that again.  Man what a talent.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KristySwansonXO @TankSchottle Check out all these milkshake flavors! These will make ya crave ice cream! https://t.co/XRYqSASzgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craig_botham @Forbes @marcorubio @realDonaldTrump @Vladimirth @briangobosox @marcaross @TweetsMillenia… https://t.co/xHfxe5fWF0]]></document><document><![CDATA[George McGinnis and Zion Williamson are the only two guys that I’ve seen blow out the side of a shoe. #force https://t.co/lzh1NrJpw1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aghigleri95 @kimbrolee123 @facebook Will you send me a friendrequest on Facebook @aghigleri95 I miss you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys I'm watching the credits to Fragmentary Passage  I'm about to start Kingdom Hearts 3  I can't believe this mom… https://t.co/LWJ961AWmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tuesday morning cardio listening...:::: Don't Waste Your TIME :::: https://t.co/VRnfhSc0J8 via @YouTube]]></document></documents></author>