<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Mike Scott seeing Lavine drive on that last play. https://t.co/wp0w7b70hr]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re one of those customers that’s an asshole to customer service ppl and expect them to show empathy...you ca… https://t.co/M5Xv08X9tI]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you make the schedule for work yet schedule yourself when you don’t wanna work #AdultingAndStuff]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lord don’t forgive me for what I’ve done, forgive me for what I’m bout to do]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CricFanUSA @Section_328 Each house league champion gets engraved on it, then they put it on display. They mentione… https://t.co/fDHapStMfb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BatmansBookcase @martinmorazzo What’s this “three issues to go” business? *panics*]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A PIANO IS A PLACE YOU GO, A COUNTRY YOU VISIT UNLIKE ANY PLACE ELSE” FUCK IT UP, FRED !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@crack_is_great Okay.  Choose between giving up sex or watching Mountain West basketball for the rest of your life-right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que egoísta soy, olvídenlo. Muchas gracias por su apoyo emocional. Que gente tan linda]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCalafiore_  says he is not trying to be cool with everyone so after he breaks up with @CaraMariaMTV he has all… https://t.co/bmCDCNyIfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stopped by @Dinosaur_BBQ in Syracuse last night. The place was packed. Great time. Great bbq. #bbq #syracuse… https://t.co/jfLtMcA9xQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lakingsinsider Thanks look forward to reading pregame articles tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's Wrong. The debut single from Kaos Mc with Tito Jackson, Alex Boye and Bull Dogg. A Doc B production due for… https://t.co/Ed0aNsBbFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaw762 The purpose of transit is not to reduce car congestion, not any more that the purpose of cars is to reduce… https://t.co/uHZI04cHEo]]></document><document><![CDATA[My man wait hittin both of em at the same time! https://t.co/t91XVsglnG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1010WINS What a complete beotch. I would’ve thrown the bag out the door.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Opposed to the players slamming in to the cameramen that are courtside on every single drive, wouldn’t it make sens… https://t.co/r1EqbGp3lN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Baalshin @Liv_Boeree @topherhodes @ForbesScience @DrAnnaPowers1 Cant open on flight but an egalitarian country can… https://t.co/aGZQ9p5A9B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Corruption by @dcbrau @ Siena Restaurant Lounge — https://t.co/6sstLhz2Zb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay — let’s add to the formula NCAA basketball championships and re-run to see what happens.  Tar ...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday March 11 - Morning News:     California’s marijuana industry needs an intervention to avoid an ‘extinction e… https://t.co/5VLFQWbHwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HARDLY DON’T DRINK SODA BUT WHEN I DO, I ALSO HAVE A SNICKERS WITH IT, SUGAR HIGH 😋🤗 @ Daly City, California https://t.co/Y1SCuhSROF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JacksonGalaxy I have a question. Got a kitten recently. I love him. But he played bites. He does not do so aggress… https://t.co/7RpJIqZLV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't even type my phone no more I just use a voice command thing now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rethwyll I had to start a 2nd puzzle (this one) because the first puzzle was missing a piece. I have my suspicions…]]></document><document><![CDATA[Studio 54 vibe!  #weekendtime #weekendvibes #rule1havefun #funtimes #saturdayvibes @ Atlanta, Georgia https://t.co/iL6Hffjtrz]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the very least we can definetley say Lavine's contract is def worth it and Lauri is VERY VERY good.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's a crying shame that it doesn't appear that Dennis Haysbert and Barack Obama have ever even been in the same room together.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@islacharlatan @eponawest each action a pattern that resolves tension in a place. So his team identified many patte… https://t.co/kqm0exFPaH]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ACHH253 Here is the link to Mental Health First Aid. https://t.co/uKMMJ55Ulj check it out folks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bendecido y Hermoso dia🙏❤ #SANTISIMO #DIOS #PADRE #JESUS🙏❤NOS BENDICE GRACIAS PADRE🙏❤ TODA LA GLORIA A #DIOS… https://t.co/IfcHytRQLt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmoney1284 @KySportsRadio They're going to win the conference but they're not the best team in the SEC. They're no… https://t.co/GbvdlkEv4R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when women take ironic misogyny geared towards triggering them as evidence that misogyny is “rampant” lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_LyndaLoveland @ApexFerg @girlscouts Now they would have gone good with my coffee earlier this morning!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Relaxing presidential term limits must be near the top of the list of the decades most frequent constitutional… https://t.co/gJSM8jO0Lt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Trump should be kicked in the balls for molesting the flag, no respect.  What a fkn troglodyte.   @POTUS @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachsCornerDC somebody doesn’t know the attendance of the colesium now 😂. Best argument to slam fans is that the… https://t.co/DBTCximj5T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slackermom66 At least you know he’ll take care of you when you’re older.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She was relentlessly teased at school for talking and acting like a boy. Brenda/David's (Brendavid's?) parents went… https://t.co/5O6QRJ5ROS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where you live can affect your health. We are looking forward to discuss #healthequity, programs and services that… https://t.co/9dreXF60JA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlessingJr Oh man, I love this game *so* much, but it’s so hard! I really need to dust off my N64 and see if I can finish it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyen420 @StJeremy55 I want to know who asked the first one about Jeremy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sábado y domingo... Dos días de visitar grupos y comunidades de la #Rcc de #Washington. Esta noche comenzamos el cu… https://t.co/zNcyQyz7T0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelindsayellis Politics doesn’t matter only during election season or only around it. I’m sorry, but the time to… https://t.co/ufY9dnJOtB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OrneVanessa are you ok from last week attack on nxt   From Shayna  and her friends]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rosie Just imagine what the folks at the SDNY are going to do to this criminal enterprise. I wonder why Rudy has b… https://t.co/0PrO5yswNs]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the case of Trayvon Martin, his murderer hunted him and when he tried to defend himself he was murdered. Where w… https://t.co/HpfRUo6DF9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@noticiasvzla360 No hay diferencia entre Chávez y Maduro, solamente que uno es más idiota que el otro,es increíble… https://t.co/26SPKDLobx]]></document><document><![CDATA[“A positive outlook may even be benefit people who already have cardiovascular disease, which is significant, becau… https://t.co/UkFEafu1gh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love Oscar Isaac, but you know who else would make a great Solid Snake?  Wyatt Russell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Palo Alto calls time, 26.6 to halftime and a chance to build on an 11-point lead.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Melania is a disgrace and black stain on The white House https://t.co/jPpkzTHHBG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soashworth The cap point was just that there was never people too far away to see and hear clearly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I was a kid my dad had a book on skiing that had pictures of Corbet's Couloir and I thought to myself, "you've… https://t.co/0srH0y5hAc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NakedMeeple @pegasusspiele Yeah. Like the time I got Hansa Teutonica for $30 and traded because no one wanted to play it. 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[NHL Trade Deadline day.  Be sure to follow @NHLdotcom @cotsonika @drosennhl @AmalieBenjamin @TomGulittiNHL… https://t.co/QrNQon0mkr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Man they did this to me 2 years ago smh. Moms pulled up and everything mid party]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrBluesHat He did great for an 88 year old billionaire. https://t.co/KH8vbBJoz4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dumptrump33 The place is straight out of Caddyshack minus the updates and the 🍊🤡 is Judge Elihu Smails. https://t.co/e1Cp7UCjy2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@randallw1961 Never much cared for the States rights argument myself. Seems to me that people like to champion stat… https://t.co/3qz5GbL3st]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealSaavedra Who cares, I don’t like this lady but cmon this is laughable. Are you going to check her bathroom next to see if she uses TP?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHerd I think if you talked to LeBron privately he'd tell you not to listen to a crackpot that thinks he's a psychiatrist @jonnyray45]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enough said!  #nike  #nikewomen  #anthonyevanscom #onemillioninten #Iownnikestock #nikestockholder @ Northwest Wash… https://t.co/slHcqS1ctn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Really solid free kick from that wide angle by SJ, wow. Almost scored it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MLL_Lacrosse can I enter the MLL draft? Highest shooting percentage in the NCAA in 2014]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Veronica4043 @chinchontepec22 @nayibbukele @waraujo64 @sv_murray @alcaldedsivar Estos personajes no aprenden! El p… https://t.co/8DofMno6Hj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lots of ⚡️CG’s early this morning just west of McComb Ms via MDOT camera https://t.co/B02dVoFa2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[My kiddo just asked me to show her more #starwars ! I am a proud #geek parent. https://t.co/XW4Ptt4ydG]]></document><document><![CDATA[John Allen by John Allen  Photography by Mark Hill @ Camden, New Jersey https://t.co/vezr4NJ23y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodFirstGina @luluHru @jackbgoode1 @marsone2 @FatherofEssen @johnsleitweiler @laurelsobol @PIRATEDANTRAIN… https://t.co/GDz81XRMUC]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay so I just realized last night that @Weezer did an entire album of covers (not just Africa) and my mind is abso… https://t.co/sh3qKDXhTi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephaniexo33 I can’t totally blame them since they weren’t trained properly on how to do it but jeez it’s not roc… https://t.co/3B2AaRRWs9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never thought it would end this way, said 43-year-old Charles Deere, one of countless eyewitnesses who now wish… https://t.co/haCch1ZGvP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DroppedStrike3 He wants to opt out after 3 yrs so why not just give him him 3yrs/ $105mil and call it a day?]]></document><document><![CDATA[#HB1410 bill sponsor Rep. @jimmygazaway discussing several amendments made to the original bill. Most amendments ar… https://t.co/tOhu7dxNxU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We always have fun going out. She is my valentine even though we are just friends. We have been emailing e cards al… https://t.co/Z1HZdSmmLM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioZitella @microStretching Waiting on that first day of offseason testing so we can go head to head! 💪]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump raises a new menace — socialism — and Democrats can't agree how to respond https://t.co/prCacWqBKb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Annie's so sweet I'm glad she's not 14 or I'd feel weird talking to her]]></document><document><![CDATA[The kickoff show at not even 5pm in Colorado 🤨🤔 https://t.co/Oja8wdSHUI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like to believe that @elonmusk really wanted to fill the cabin with a few hundred blue LEGO astronaut mini-figs s… https://t.co/0lEcHpRbEk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abcmusicme123e @RJ_Phillips32 @heyyHaileyRose @SydneyDawson17 @brandalintipton I think you missed the early part o… https://t.co/jTeSejZqm0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@machinegunkelly @Eminem You lost stan stop trying to squeeze out any bit of attention you can get from it just bec… https://t.co/FKwmxSF3KX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mikecoulson48 If there is an issue with overpopulation, why not try birth control, not mass murder?]]></document><document><![CDATA[That does it for Week 5 of Stadium Championship Series 2. These last 2 weeks @scottbuetow has been killing it, notc… https://t.co/5AvlNxqd9a]]></document><document><![CDATA[As it turns out Harris citing medical problem( he'd been hiding?) is not going to run for this seat again.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great action with @by_the_ppl &amp; Congresswoman Tlaib this morning- thank you for your courageous leadership!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Justine351K @P69Jordanp69 Definitely beautiful!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys ❤️ and James Corden Made a Grammys Remix For "Shallow," and Wow, We Stan This Duo https://t.co/NgTUFK88IE via @POPSUGAREnt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenavieyvette Don’t mess with her like that but I hope you have a good time 🙏🏽]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachel_morgan97 Not only that but in a country where the state listens in on literally everyone, it’s hard to fath… https://t.co/3fzHoJDgyd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@adamjones985 live look at Celtics season so far.... https://t.co/ogppvNwTWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nationals Baseball players, have shown visual acuity approaching 20/12 (20/8 best humanly possible vision). Smart… https://t.co/0cR4nEICIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottPresler @realAlexBeard @realDonaldTrump I would add a further move to have every college professor who's indo… https://t.co/Nnyfp8DBZU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lafc_tsg @MumfordBrewing @LAFC3252 @LAFC Interested! Will see you guys around.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mpsever it's totally bonkers.  before Ranieri, Fulham were getting 0.4 points per game. under Ranieri, 0.7.  at th… https://t.co/eH1ITTwNrL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GfromStaeFarm Watching replay now since I was working but dang that was a round. Tim's boxing was unbelievable tho til he got murked lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[I dont support liberal loonies just because they can act or sing. If you are that big an idiot I don't care to hear… https://t.co/iYe1D5wPsO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now I don’t care anymore that @realDonaldTrump is sending us hurdling towards the apocalypse. Bring it on!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Te pertenezco, soy de Ti, para Ti nací, solo para Ti; Te pertenezco esclavo tuyo soy, llévame solo a Ti, te quiero… https://t.co/uarPMZpBm9]]></document></documents></author>