<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I just read a story and saw the police video about how some guy chopped a lady’s head off in Northgate Seattle this… https://t.co/sraiteQByN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras, y’all. 📿👑  #MardiGras #NewOrleans #Louisiana #FireHydrant #MagazineStreet #Beads #Sidewalk… https://t.co/eCAExhXAuu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sarge_MSU Terrell Pryor in person, but mainly in NCAA 2010. Unstoppable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbbyBoruff @KBehr68 @tlhalm I didn’t say the bulk. I said the problem.  Are we saying there is no ay to improve these programs?]]></document><document><![CDATA[At Carver High School where the boys just locked down a trip to the final four beating Cartersville 72-47 and an an… https://t.co/qN8G2hGncA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spphcfggt @GainesvillePD I'll have you know that at least 3 people were upset with my tweets.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IB_Furious @tammigaw @benshapiro That’s exactly the point I was making?? They would be okay with the school making… https://t.co/3y8I3QUP6W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritYah 3) Look, I'm sure whatever method you use to determine if someone is trustworthy is what you are comfort… https://t.co/0pOBuWnK6p]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: HBO doc ‘The Case Against Adnan Syed’ picks up where the heralded ‘Serial’ podcast left off: “Seri… https://t.co/i89WT0UEr8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have an amazing day today my friends love all of you so much💖 https://t.co/YGXekWs8HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[STAR WATTAGE...Loving this Oscars photo of Gaga https://t.co/CmQMppN0pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you vote for the promises of the Dems, the only thing they guarantee is poverty and misery and that way they wil… https://t.co/ROlVXrVRTy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Bukowski When your team gets hit with a T for too many timeouts after taking 4 in the first 10 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BevericStinky Thanks very much for bringing this sad news to my attention. 😢  I'll follow up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@MacLeodLisa #ResignLisaMacleod #lies #bully #criminal? #lockherup #autism #AutismDoesntEndAtFord @OntarioPCParty @fordnation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LadyStephC @MrEarpLA @QBaller_Boyz @TrumpyQGirl @PhillyQ10 @Saintedanon @JodyICEMANJames @freenaynow… https://t.co/BKF9YYlhAi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good time of year to get out on the lake, soak in some sun and enjoy a cool and refreshing Ice V. @ Sylvania, Ohio https://t.co/9rqQpMIFwb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir I’m in your hands for the next 27 hours (or at least as soon as security opens). Looking forward to sm… https://t.co/stLq0GF42o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Baystate Health team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/Zh8v9SPx9y #Greenfield, MA #Nursing]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charliekirk11 @luluhall13 @realDonaldTrump @TPUSA Animals!!! No respect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrunchyKong @Retrogamebrews @thepunisher6353 @AtariVision @AtariVisionWife @wrytersview @mzskharris @wokeupinsane… https://t.co/3YVZsdSrO8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here is The All Mighty Bobby Lashley who's in a bad mood after what happen last night getting beaten down by The Sh… https://t.co/6fE8fCMnDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Walk into the facility with a PURPOSE today! #WeFly20 #OneAtATime https://t.co/uXQo2j5wiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@greggutfeld Hey Greg you guys wana film live on a virginia farm and enjoy a day of bbq and shooting guns, at targets of Dems?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbsunkins @joliehaitian79 They were great together.  Poor Luke.  Would have been nice to see them together again.   The cast has aged well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The girls vetting the ballots did a last minute double-check:   Turns out the winner’s Best Score pick (Beale Stree… https://t.co/xW2mEHjxzQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shout Out To Patrick ! He is manually mixing paint for one of our contractors bc our machine is temporarily down. T… https://t.co/NSYz58zks7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chicagotribune @HeidiStevens13 Here’s an idea: Let Alex use the words he chooses. Stop being the thought and word… https://t.co/EldThKHfaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanBennett26 with the double hat trick! ⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️⚽️ @MilwaukeeWave 8-2 https://t.co/hgGY6FiUVf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimNBCBoston @AspenSnowmass Yesterday the NWS said 6 to 10 inches today for Concord, NH. A look at the maps now in… https://t.co/5nb6ig83dT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiborioGuarulla @UN4Indigenous @RepDebHaaland @sharicedavids @NCAI1944 @ITK_CanadaInuit @frmt_gt @ONIC_Colombia… https://t.co/7v81WsSs83]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RonaldKlain @CDCDirector @USAID @Health_Affairs And I agree, the US can and should do more.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We have a great representation at our state level.  Thanks @reprickhansen for taking the time to help champion supp… https://t.co/1kINV7EpFu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Driscoll designed some of the firm’s best-known lamps, including the dragonfly design seen here. She was the head o… https://t.co/vUJ3hznq7v]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Horny___AF Thanks but that would be an epic fail I could see it now u stay busy lmao 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonnieWahlberg Hello, I'm in New York to discover the places where my favorite series are filmed.  I'm Italian and… https://t.co/inC8dmiGFX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ladygaga #leroe24fotos #enigma #therealfokkingdeal #teamleroe24fotos #blackandwhite #germanotta #lasvegas… https://t.co/NrVmpm0UZD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Your truth is always out of focus... That’s why I have no problem calling you a punk ass bitch!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpencerFujimoto That's understandable those east coast winters make it insanely tough I'd imagine. I just hit the… https://t.co/mdI6GyFTTD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just walked into my mother's house and she's watching this and that was the first thing I heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BeckyBorron In my experience there are times when the willingness to make amends are the end result. Once the atte… https://t.co/dUeoFGfNaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hope you’re brushing up on your Van Buren’s and Harrison’s and maybe Rutherford B Hayes. Here’s from my visit to se… https://t.co/IFY4t8uWIZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/JKlJCvEU0M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pope Defrocks Theodore McCarrick, Ex-Cardinal Accused of Sexual Abuse https://t.co/w3ndTyELlW]]></document><document><![CDATA[All day at Cal Baptist University. . . . Girls D-1: Chaminade vs. MLK; Boys D-1: Chino Hills vs. Santa Margarita; G… https://t.co/Sxjmj2zZbJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Who are these people, maybe they’re just stars in your mind, never heard of them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Griz44John   Great job Managing the Southern B Tourney!  Thank you @GazSportsSchert for coverage]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FoodTravelist A1.) @mammamiamovie made me want to travel to the Greece. #FoodTravelChat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@odienator Wessler PA'd on Empire and Jedi, Farelly co-wrote a Paul Reiser special she appeared in. If you hit up G… https://t.co/YRFYXcrdTc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to close your eyes, count to ten, take a deep breath, remind yourself that you wouldn't loo… https://t.co/HvEKU3W2LX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Disney's Animal Kingdom Lodge - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/t4N2CVDZiq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tennessee this weekend unofficial #GoVols @Jaheim_Bell1   @Trapp_SETA229 https://t.co/HypYV00jqt]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little light fare to get the day started. And a locally roasted El Salvadoran pour over. #HappySunday. #Coffee @… https://t.co/dVrhUyKhsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is quite the beauty. @LiamRSharp #TheBraveAndTheBold #WonderWoman #Batman #TirNaNog @DCComics https://t.co/cwLVDTcAPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Liberals are upset about dissecting frogs in biology, but not about butchering up human babies!! Sick!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Troll Farm totally could have been the name of an animated children's TV show in the mid-to-late '80s.  What a waste.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Coach_Macella @BuckyBrooks @BSimmons25 Agree. My DC played in the NFL it’s a little different going thud or tag of… https://t.co/VyvafkWcAJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My regular reminder that I’m very happy not to work at Google any more. They’re just a creepy company.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NEW SPOT 🍽 Congrats fam at The Fly! https://t.co/zZw8IvKBgQ https://t.co/UlHcM1HWPN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATTCares help, got an email saying I needed to update payment method on an order but the link it the email just ta… https://t.co/urEu8pZMYM]]></document><document><![CDATA[We want to thank @MLVSSF and Tracy Brown for donating computers to @devMission_ ! Most of you probably don’t know t… https://t.co/E1Dk5XwumL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lindsey Sterling at Express LIve! In Columbus. #photooftheday #livemusic #promowestlive #violin #concertphotography https://t.co/SsSpfQSKGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[End4th:🥎🥎Greenwood 2 Fayetteville 1  @GWoodDogPound @_gwoodsoftball_ @smittydp]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ThoughtofFortheDay – “Your worst moment feels like the end of the world. It is not. You can always regroup and fin… https://t.co/kilbLxEe8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[First Ward Alderman Moreno with 37% of the vote, 36% reporting? #ChicagoElection #Huh?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elixir is probably the only language I’ve ever used where running an HTTP server to verify external requests in tes… https://t.co/mixNGz1BKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMarkMeadows @realDonaldTrump @realDonaldTrump You have my vote and support President Trump. #TrumpStrong… https://t.co/73dQaO2FCS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@urgranpappy Cause it's old school af to use a scanner, just get the phone app and take a pic!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity Swamp Queen Pelosi tried to say Omar waz naive about what she should and should not say. It appears Om… https://t.co/1SUZlxlOm3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Smeezy_904 I’m actually legit not fucked up. I didn’t pregame. It was weird. I kinda set out to prove people wrong, ya know]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  BREAKING: Bernie Sanders still won't release his tax returns, claiming they are not ready to turn… https://t.co/dM2Lw3OuD9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sarah Mclachlan with Symphony Orchestra at The Amphitheater is the most magical summer night concert.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino @WalshFreedom is an idiot. I stopped following him. He has no value added material. .absolutely none. In… https://t.co/8FxUFy0mf6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a new comforter today and that’s the most adult thing I’ve done in awhile]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MylesLGarrett The types of literature, other than poetry that you enjoy.  Perhaps you could opine on movies or fil… https://t.co/YVkgZFAydC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robreiner That is the key to victory, that is how to win a Presidential election.that is Priority number one.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're gonna stand up for something, it might as well be this. https://t.co/WAPhb5R7yi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes About to do Trumps Bidding by killing all the his Opposition !Allways tweeting BAD things about our press… https://t.co/NAPrRYus5m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BBoason sir,is this true and if yes why are the economic”analysts”in Nigeria still saying our economy is not growi… https://t.co/YNnqmkeodg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pepper led Peoria Christian with 17 points, which is pretty impressive seeing as how he sat most of the 1st half wi… https://t.co/ekL1fIrCWX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Si te topas con el video de El Cairo y Egipto de choque de trenes, NO LO VEAS!!! No te lo recomiendo!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lil’ Pete wanted to work on some groundballs as a 1B, then as a SS today. Yes, in his PJ’s with eye black. The foot… https://t.co/hlcAhdhXtf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @ABC @NYTIMES @WASHINGTONPOST @MSNBC @CBSNEWS @FOXNEWS America! Russia, China, N Korea, Yemen yes even Iran lo… https://t.co/rmgUvm9m9U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Make sure you point out it had to go through the port because they could not cross where there was a WALL!… https://t.co/5xEe8zkad6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@enigma173 @MarkReardonKMOX @stltoday Unfortunately it’s part of his job. He gets it at work.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyTFalcone "Hmm, Schindler's List, probably a boring historical movie that will put me to sleep."]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidepearson @JessieJaneDuff @Doodisgirl @nytimes I thought she was claiming citizenship. If not, there is no cla… https://t.co/yyYnD3lKD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[ONE LAST MOTHERFUCKING TIME! @WWERollins @WWERomanReigns #DeanAmbrose #TheShield]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ALawRadio waiting to see when Browns pull the trigger on some of these big name players. C. J. Mosley, Kelvin Benj… https://t.co/xRFoatSvZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danqdao Once you cross that 3/4 four month mark of being committed, it becomes natural. Especially if you don’t ha… https://t.co/9Ne2JK5jYU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bruvs That is some low bullshit. Like NY needs to worry about selling enough rec weed.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GuyAllright @stillgray It has to be so odd to be a liberal Jew.  Like your old best friend has a new crowd he like… https://t.co/zvkAoEs8h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Montana_Bound_ @realDonaldTrump Not surprised. Wonder what the people that elected her feel about her now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DA_Osorio I heard he clowned him and I was immediately skeptical but it was funny as hell 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Let’s Get Funky Tonight” by Dream Street just came on and wow hi hello 2001]]></document><document><![CDATA[And be sure to read the report and the response from the hospital. Very well written, very critical of @OIGatHHS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PendegraftMaris @JACCJournals @SJGreene_md @JavedButler1 @gcfmd @HFSA @JAMACardio @ACCinTouch @ishlt Each patient… https://t.co/8MyF3iT9to]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like my big double burger cookout style. These arteries aren't gonna clog themselves]]></document><document><![CDATA[Season 2, Episode 10: Joffrey dumps Sansa for Margaery, which seems best for all involved. Theon gives a speech, is… https://t.co/ITUeACoVFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up $400-$500 entire stream, decides to play a few more hands get felted twice lmao profits $60 on the day]]></document></documents></author>