<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[*me wearing shirt that says “not today Cupid”*  Mom: you know damn well if Cupid brought you a man you’d take him  Me: ....yeah u right]]></document><document><![CDATA[the fact that @DavidDobrik will probably get as old as @jasonnash before he can possibly come to Canada because he’… https://t.co/6Z86leFfe5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mz_ColoradoGrov @itsJeffTiedrich They would probably dig a tunnel to escape only to discover that Frump is too fat to squeeze in.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMARA_SUJU @marcorubio @VP @SenBobCorker @SenatorBurr @SenThomTillis In case you missed this one too]]></document><document><![CDATA[Apps pending at Barton Village Cir #102! #bartonvillage #forlease #forrent #bartonhills #78704 #1bedroom… https://t.co/Mdv9yjMqka]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CuseWBB @em__baller Solid game on both sides of the ball! Let's GO! 🍊🏀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Djewlie Or try a cheap laptop? I used to watch stuff on mine before I had a tv.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting your heart broken by a dude is one thing but has your heart ever been broken by your best friend lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naniraine Best feeling ever!! I still get so hype when my husband has a part during the mid week meeting. I love s… https://t.co/JW2rudgTLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Here I Go Again by Whitesnake. https://t.co/xjemV7TY9W Friday Motivation]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrEricLevi I ask my child to put down her phone when we are eating.  The phone stays down and we chat.  As a paren… https://t.co/IILbv2UG6X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can I be a stay at home mom ...I dont got no kids but just for practice?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissDiagnosis I hope more people will listen and follow you. It is sad that most do not understand how they operat… https://t.co/8yMqUErpfz]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌳🍎🍐🍏🙏🏼 . . #couldntsayitanybetter  #selfcare #selflove #saturday #you  #eastaurora #eastaurorany #westseneca… https://t.co/D4KVGwPQhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[What do you notice?  What do you wonder? #noticewonder #MTBoS https://t.co/p5zw7OkCUt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just watched A Star is Born for the first time and I’m not okay 😭 https://t.co/4qwajoxmBS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qanon February 24 2019 - [LL] Returning to the Headlines https://t.co/f21AnhCOrW via @YouTube = Praying Medic]]></document><document><![CDATA[This sunny, seasonable and DRY Wednesday forecast has got me like... 😀🙌🏻☀️ https://t.co/9IZ6Z5tFsv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@siggyflicker @Loubiegal @afinekimmie @SamusAran2020 @DrJamesMercer @BravoHWFanClub @tiffany_annx3 @lilTNangel… https://t.co/L4khxZTPy6]]></document><document><![CDATA[3rd grade students @Unioncrosselem creating gases in our half-day special! #WeDoScienceWell @TrishSpencer… https://t.co/vzNoctRI6x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummmm, Our 'president' believes Putin, Un, MBS,Xi,- Russsia, N.Korea,Arab Potentates, Communist Dictators- ALL GENO… https://t.co/vAR6gjfpcf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TamiBennett15 @ExorcistBishop Exactly! A true light through rough times!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stevehu01489106 @JessicaSillers @zeliemimi @time_reclaimer @TollRoadJester @jpaceDC Haha, never knew that, but can… https://t.co/QsqbfwplFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[INTEGRIS is hiring in #Edmond, OK! Read about our latest #FacilitiesMgmt job opening via the link in our bio: House… https://t.co/F8DrWfpu52]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SteveKubota @jillianne_gray @StewLeonards @_drazzari @jflorez @boozychef @suziday123 @SideHustleWino @GailBenzler… https://t.co/SFwaINNcKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Breaking News: @NicoFOXIL  thinks “mauve” is pronounced “ mow-v” 😂😂🤦🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent yesterday afternoon getting my #professionaldevelopment on with @PamLCline learning more about the @IMSEOG ap… https://t.co/y7xm3OY8Cd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Isispriest Wow! Thank you for this. I woke up very depressed this morning, feel a little better now. 😗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please give the exact location of this major construction.  Since I am paying for it, I want to visit it. #wall]]></document><document><![CDATA[Up early debating on if I want to start trying to lose weight again. Maybe my mom will give me her treadmill..]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are my KW close circle peeps. Colleagues in Real Estate. Rockstars in their own right. Blessed to have them i… https://t.co/3fAZ2LmGpA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kasey and I are Thundering up on the freezing Sunday evening.  Hoping the Thunder Get warmed up and beat these Griz… https://t.co/fOWAREI4WX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maymt_mena tienes que leer esto. Justo en nuestro corazón rebelde jajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music is an international language.  As I stress health and wellness of the mind, body and soul; there is something… https://t.co/0IAa4YkMJG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Middle school wisdom to bless your V Day from one of the girls in my small group: “Two hoes don’t make a right” 👏🏼🙌🏼😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CountOnVic go get that spicy mac and cheese and chicken ma’am. love you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My nephew 3 today😤 thank you for being an excuse for us to black out... i mean a reason to make this shit pop off s… https://t.co/pnKrFHdGYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Bronx Tale is so good! Go see it!! #openingnight https://t.co/q0yApaaEJg]]></document><document><![CDATA[at the point in the night when everyone is evaluating life drunk off their ass   &amp; I’m just tryna get home and put on sweatpants]]></document><document><![CDATA[@The_Real_Bob Ugh I totally chopped that up.  I meant was the other home run today hit by him.  I was excited over… https://t.co/twb4gu5oGR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally someone is mad at their friends for being my friend!! 😂😂😂 petty much? https://t.co/5L03S18QEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WHOWeather But this is Iowa!!! Are you SURE it will be gone??? I have known some years, that it hasn't let go of u… https://t.co/9Wx7qfT0k3]]></document><document><![CDATA[What the fuck is the matter with you, you heartless bitch. Rot in hell.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Overheard my players calling me a nice DM...guess it's about to get real. https://t.co/gHx3V5jFHC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some antinatalist sentiments on Twilight Zone episode 'On Thursday We Leave for Home']]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom and brothers are on the road to come visit me ! May they have a safe drive all the way here 🙏🏻💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[EPA declares its own fake emergency to spread bee-killing pesticide. #EPA #oxymoronic #FakeEmergency #bees #bee https://t.co/Y93L9TscTa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cristiancrespoj @MonseTalleyrand El grifo está abierto, entiendo qué hay estampida de la FANB.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“If there was some smoke detectors maybe he would’ve had a chance,” says one woman who knew James “Jim” Sauta. She… https://t.co/LuwY7ppbGt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cher I hope you're high and not this stupid Dumb sh$$ like this is why we go so few at midterm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KinderHeather That’s awesome!  Check it out @hibillyby - more fans for your parents’ donut shop! 🍩💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Learning this more and more as I follow a reading plan together with my church. Eat, savor, meditate, and talk abou… https://t.co/5HCP01tkE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[i love PM s’much my old ass made a fan account so if y’all wanna follow me @prettymuchthick or not it’s cool  xoxo- Isabell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can AO have back to back good games for the first time in his Duke career?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simply_donlundy I ordered one and It said delivered and it’s not in my mailbox 😭 I’m hurttttt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chrissyann12345 @davelackie @gerlain Thanks Christine it was a verry nice dinner with family members! Wensday i wi… https://t.co/ME5VHOyNMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Efforts made to hide Trump's school records, Washington Post reports  https://t.co/nrvXHKCaoz]]></document><document><![CDATA[May the Peace of Christ be with you all. See you after Lent. Save the babies.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goodnight Tyler, playing until March 10th at the Hertz Stage! You will laugh and cry and you might get angry too. @… https://t.co/mXQGHG9C7z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KapusongKim @dealwithBARBIE @mikadlacruz Nasa GMA na ba 'tong si Nash Aguas?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hi just bc there is 5 ft of grass between the lanes doesn’t mean your high beams don’t still blind me]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chris_1791 @LegInsurrection Of course they did. Wisconsin is over run with Muslims.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My student teacher gave me the sweetest Valentine present including my favorite flower! ❤️🌻✏️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oxa099 @Danielelorain Ce n'est pas permis pour tout le monde c'est sûr ça! WoW!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@xalliepie I’ve been off for over 2 years, we’re at an age where we can be smart and not have babies with a little… https://t.co/e3QlWKBzXC]]></document><document><![CDATA[leaving class to use the bathroom and never returning&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlphLukau Tell that fool to walk on some water -from the WEST African Coast all the way here to America- then we a… https://t.co/h0zHeIzd0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebbieSummers91 He’s darling. I loved his thoughts and observations. Wish I had been sitting next to him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@polirealm @BernieSanders Too bad a federal judge threw out all your DNC conspiracy hogwash. Sanders is dismissive… https://t.co/E7MWbZ7jM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[GIANT Spiral GUM-BALL Machine Surprise! https://t.co/YfQWb5HkiH via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[Investigators say Coleman bought three tucker suits, candles, names, surgical gloves, odor respirator, and bleach.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen is discredited and going to jail because of his blind loyalty to you. Your business dealings were oft… https://t.co/qaoMxfYghV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the sun is out, does your hair shine? I can bring out the shine for you! #blowout #smooth #shinyhair… https://t.co/gKT3J4aUBZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I want pluckers.. then tacos.. then tamales.. wtf i’m not even pregnant to be craving man]]></document><document><![CDATA[A young #orangutan who had spent nearly her entire #life inside a wooden crate is now finally #free, thanks to resc… https://t.co/NY478UFi4F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomFitton @realDonaldTrump It never ends with the UBER intolerant left!]]></document><document><![CDATA[oh did i mention we all work together? LMAO. won’t admit i’m hurt though cus i fuck too hard for that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JETZIINTHESKY I’m only ever looking at you. Kinda hard not to. Most beautiful woman I’ve ever seen. Luckiest man in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the women of The Morning News on @NewsChannel9 in this #internationalwomensday There is so much that goes into… https://t.co/l0Efx2eEfs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I literally can’t with this...like...I’m in shock that people cannot name 1 👏🏽 fucking 👏🏽 country 👏🏽 on the map. My… https://t.co/X2qJzdkd3t]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m glad @justinamash is receiving accolades for his conduct during the Cohen hearings. But what he did shouldn’t b… https://t.co/I4aE2dYhcr]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BREAKING: Cass County under  #tornado #warning. Follow @kytxcbs19 for your #SevereWx updates!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TBryant1776 hows the struggle going with the hair? Think your going to be able to make it?😂🤣💇‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cats haven’t put away the Panthers yet....it’s 35-24 after 3 qtrs of play. @ORSchools @stefthompson63]]></document><document><![CDATA[that video of that little baby running up the stairs gets me in tears every time I see it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@badov49 these people are so sick!Sending in caravans,protecting them in sanctuary cities &amp; now giving them jobs!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 21st to my bff &amp; forever favorite longhorn🍻 @_RICKY75 https://t.co/rlfKRl6RtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julieplec This is not out of context. That is Alabama.  That is what has been there for decades but now with… https://t.co/kbNqoJt78N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Centennial Sunrise at the Grand canyon National Park. It was about 20 degrees at 6:30 a.m. - we bundled up and walk… https://t.co/cXXRK4EEYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[First look 👀  #overnightsnow #centralmass #mondaysnowtivation ❄️❄️❄️ https://t.co/F8tbk05Ti9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tamarabrock Wtf-wt actual f. If she doesn’t haul his ass right back...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aidanelisabeth How does that even happen.... like, you can just google it and paste an already created map I’m just????]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lmao it’s ados fault that trump is in office. You heard it here first. Y’all here to place blame on everyone but ac… https://t.co/tqiibuJepc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@columbusairport Tonight was second Sunday in a row for the most awful baggage experience. Last week waited a solid… https://t.co/x1Gk86DwaM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I didn’t plan for a second snow day, I don’t think my family will eat the ham again. https://t.co/7aCCOI2hkF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes she goes outside. She’s not the woman who should be hiding her face..... Jordan #homewrecker]]></document><document><![CDATA[One Month ‘til St. Patrick’s Day ☘️ come grab a pint to celebrate! 📸 @guinnessus  We’ll be celebrating St. Patrick’… https://t.co/C7edh3tfKa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShawnFinchum don't make fun of people if you don't want to get blocked]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @lilsquirt11 can’t wait for you all to come over this summer!  I miss you all!  Enjoy your bday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRevAl @JoyAnnReid a good article about Kamala Harris truancy policy. Not what are making it out to be. https://t.co/ApdCZ7EGTb]]></document></documents></author>