<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#magicschoolbus #msfrizzle #dratini #cosplayer #cosplaybabe #cosplayer #cosplayers #comiccon #portland #wizardworld… https://t.co/LdYQNsjPIv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very excited to try this place out!!! (@ Cry Baby Pasta in Philadelphia, PA) https://t.co/MKlwqxIpxS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Howland Township, Trumbull County, Ohio https://t.co/f1HkKE3Tzj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @lana_del_shay I think I might be a #Lesbian now... #LezBeHonest #DatAzz #Booty #QueerBurlesque . . . . .… https://t.co/A9EWBSB6aU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndySwift @MarkDice @AOC Nah, libtard is accurate as it is intended as a derogatory term toward differently abled… https://t.co/dH5WNY3dAp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AudreyRLWyatt @wendellpotter @DylanDusseault @BillGalston Find yourself a DPC doc @ https://t.co/4QwrKEosEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@THEIMCCA #CWNY19 at Cisco NY headquarters “the future is here just not evenly distributed “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlaidHatGames I’m excited, especially for the solo option when I’m gaming on my own. https://t.co/q2K7HXKAWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarkYoungTruth I thought it would be against the law to falsely put information on federal papers?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pastadivingjeet @jetset1990 @kendraswork @jbranham502 @l_ofrance @craigcombs @southpaw89 @spidadmitchell @NCAA You… https://t.co/OrrjeZHJm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LynneBlackburn4 @TOwolfpack @LeighCenturions Hi Lynne, good comment. I was meaning ‘fair’ result balanced on the g… https://t.co/OcuH5lYwcG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Am I able to sell meetup’s for playlist on Sunday?? Mike and I can’t use ours bc we need to head back of jville we… https://t.co/QRDJ6wfMeI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aelamin03 Using scoops or just simply throwing, The 6 Pillars of Power is one of my favorite games.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s #NationalKolacheDay! The pastries were brought to Texas by Czech immigrants in the 1800s. Now they’re a staple… https://t.co/Q1EIJXSBzf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyPeikoff @AOC AOC is providing a glimpse of the authoritarianism that’s inevitable in a socialist manifesto like #GreenNewDeal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annemariayritys Every way I can! BEN FRANKIN saw LIGHTNING as ENERGY! Millions of VOLTS, Untapped? Are we MISSING Something?]]></document><document><![CDATA[A loss on Friday night in 2OT’s and an OT loss on Saturday night.  Back in the gym Sunday morning. 🏀 #getbetter @ S… https://t.co/wAPAfAsGZh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BassNicoh @BassProShops I just so happen to have $70 worth of gift cards I’ve been itching to spend!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am the person who learned how to play Nanase as a side character to pick her song justifiably]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mis relojes :v estos no los vendo. ⌚Me faltan 2 relojes de oro 😏 https://t.co/qVmbD1dxgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Boston__Sucks Manny gives it to you too, plus he's not just a gold glove, he's platinum gold glove at 3b. Makes Brooks Robinsonesque plays.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnneMarieWTHR Still the best looking women on Night time TV.   Happy Valentine's Day]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s go bombs away at @GulfstreamPark race 9. Big longshot would spice some things up. #Due]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NathanLongfield Right. I’m thinking of someone who gets the Trinity wrong or wants to ‘unhitch’ OT from NT. Do you… https://t.co/HLDNuKN40D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@trevorh321 @DanielMyers76 @askye7 @ReverbPlayer @ScarletM1926 @USATODAY I’m failing to see their logic. Denying cl… https://t.co/EnGLqaKfMh]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you just had surgery on your face and your beard is lower than it’s been in a decade and you feel good about y… https://t.co/6hYhdcxdpb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFermtdFruit @OpusOneWinery @JMiquelWine @winewankers @KellyMitchell @DemiCassiani @onceuponawine_ @NapaVintners… https://t.co/lV1MScrCQR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jgoss1971 @TexasChance @johngranato @DJLockdown365 @clintshane nope, sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creativity never ceases to amaze. #wynwoodwalls #miami @ Wynwood Walls https://t.co/AJo4cN70zj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BPFA #APSummit19 ———————————————————— Sunday morning #yoga in the park overlooking the beach. It was a brisk and e… https://t.co/YJAhGPCfVm]]></document><document><![CDATA[DARE report winners with Deputy Graves! #eaglepride 🚫 #drugfree https://t.co/XvjO3WP4AG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@testisfidelis Please meditate on the effect of the elevation of the Virgin Mary on the pius devotion of the faithf… https://t.co/6o91WXCMJi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jerryjamesstone Spent 6 hours on this last edit, but the video was also nearly 20 min long.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DGodfatherMoody @JeffStriegle @SteveGilkey Stop Dragging our Heart Around Striegle. https://t.co/sq9ooEHeIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heytheremissmic I need a direct link please because I want to buy this for, sure for sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It took a long time to make the ideal set up for sound and efficiency. But the time spent was well worth it!   #RCR… https://t.co/aCeQkPCbFq]]></document><document><![CDATA[☄️🌸🔥⚡️⭐️🌟💥I Present The Photo Of The Day!!!💥🌟⭐️⚡️🔥🌸☄️ . . Photo by @mygolfinggirls  . Going low on the composition… https://t.co/nYn7Vp0lTX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeremyeder 8 thousands of a second for my testing using the native executable. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews Trump is a freaking moron and a pathological liar. He lacks any compassion and rationality. He is the w… https://t.co/mCirPAaRlx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DullesDistrict How did you score 2 Zimmermans? Take a kids when he wasnt looking?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN He’s not getting a Christmas present this year. I’m thinking his Amazon Prime account might also have some rel… https://t.co/fw6FyN7RCF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JClarkNBCS How about the biggest https://t.co/m5zuDjY7bT in Philly sports history.  He will never finish out this… https://t.co/7TCuJ4yGUJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Arriadna @B52Malmet I think she needs passion, caring and urgentcy. Trump is surrounded by children and is married. He is still a fuck-up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Imperial Smells Like Bean Spirit by @mikerphonebrew @ Hunahpu’s Day 2019 — https://t.co/Dw9RCUFl40]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylamb8 Ohio State? Yes. Indiana? No. Record isn’t good enough. Beating Michigan St a third time would certainly do it for them. 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wasn’t expecting an hour commute instead of the normal 15 min but here we are.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#motivationmonday #motivationalmonday #inspirationalthoughts #inspirationalpost #inspirationalwords… https://t.co/UwN79oOM4h]]></document><document><![CDATA[The official site is still being worked on right now but my Teespring store is still up https://t.co/Ig5SG5OSYG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Laughs From Santa Monica : Jake &amp; Louie #laughsfromsantamonica #lfsm #spectaclepic #standupcomedy #studio… https://t.co/HeXfEqdTiS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpookyMovies @hallows_hand @horrorfan1979 @SonnyVonDutch @isaacrthorne @ThomasOtterman @SamesCarolyn @BlankPetra… https://t.co/9OzTenrV4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever been black and called the N-word ... no, didn’t think so. You can’t preach if you’ve never been in th… https://t.co/MMBEy70TgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[A little afternoon help from my personal assistant Venti Triple-Shot Cappuccino #Starbucks #CoffeeIsMySiesta… https://t.co/T7yNZArgwT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Chillin by the beach drinking and posting a half assed tweet 🍺 🍻 🍺 https://t.co/rt7Cko1d6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Randy Moss Best Mic'd Up Moments | Sound FX | NFL Films https://t.co/Kl9zCLiA0U via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiesVespers Otherwise thanks for your reply. of Government it was the Engineer Henry Roberts wrote "Robert's Rule… https://t.co/9HRlipMaPm]]></document><document><![CDATA[More #PatchesIhave Maricopa county deputy sheriff, US Air Force, UH-60 Black Hawk, and AH- cobra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What kind of sex act would a septuagenarian be involved in? Could it start with a “f” and end with a “o”?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ggreenwald @TheInterceptBr Religion in politics only leads to evil. https://t.co/QDUV7HrZ6y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to the man that gave me my first political job, the greatest Governor the state of Missouri has ever… https://t.co/TbCy8pTKB1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning Everybody @ Mobile County, Alabama https://t.co/ZwFSp08yxk]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realestate #realtor #realestateagent #home #property #investment #luxury #business #entrepreneur #forsale… https://t.co/mDHlxnySAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tgithursday 💃🏽💃🏽💃🏽💃🏽 (@ Capitol Gateway Apartments in Atlanta, GA) https://t.co/UfsyN3wO4I https://t.co/y9rzb9vhsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MinionCapital @WTCM3 I really like the concept of “cached thoughts” https://t.co/bVnIOjYdNq Pocket’s web/mobile pl… https://t.co/OkuuVOwmnx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@charlieputh What inspired you to write Boy? I absolutely love that song.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBAonTNT we don't need that pointless interview just start the 2nd half]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @JussieSmollett He will blame Fox for driving him to do this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VexingVixxen Find the new glow...been searching for that and find flickering dim lights...being a workaholic leads… https://t.co/qEDbP2tDq8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMPRESSROOTSGAL  Thanks for the follow I look forward to your tweets. 🌊   #Resist]]></document><document><![CDATA[e-News for Small Business Issue 2019-04 https://t.co/is8V8S8XeR via @Granicus]]></document><document><![CDATA[UK Defence chief warns of 'extraordinary increase' in Russian submarine activity https://t.co/V5wnVIL8lj good day f… https://t.co/NLPc1YJfhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BunkerGear_Gal @PokerDame @82ndABNDiv Once again the #82nd Airborne "All American Chorus" presented the Star Spang… https://t.co/skO5go1vWE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNNOpinion @DeanObeidallah SNL makes fun of every president, he aint special. And they most certainly dont si… https://t.co/za5cYfCnm2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PamboleroPuma No se hecho para atrás que fue lo mas importante. Marioni los mando a atacar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid like Zeno's Paradox...as far to the right hand side of the scale as I can travel, each time cuttin… https://t.co/ztc1dBCyfQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alanbaglia @LAShepard221 @NYCParks @JimmyVanBramer @joby_jacob @grievesmith @conradgangone @StreetsblogNYC… https://t.co/IOty5Z7J1P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExtremeInfidel @PBranham @SacPolice 👀 This is what happens when you don’t think critically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump If u got time to talk to me we make whatever happen please let’s talk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOP @RepAndyBiggsAZ #WeThePeople n #WeThePeoplePlus : we are going the old historical way to defend @POTUS against… https://t.co/ANchAeiMpF]]></document><document><![CDATA[My job search is going so badly that I literally just got denied from a job within 2 minutes of hitting submit on my application]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ryangrim @nycsouthpaw It's a nice city with decent airport. Also, beautiful art museum, waterfront, and great pubs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, more snow. :) #snowdog @ Oregon, Wisconsin https://t.co/9qTmxKMCWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Resgatei essa foto antiga de um momento muito especial (com meu filho mais novo e sua filha mais velha) para fazer… https://t.co/rmOzfXKjP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who today can question the wisdom of creating an energized youth cult around the moral challenge, “What are you doing to save the planet?”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deadlifting and Posing.. 5yrs off and only 8wks back with 30wks to go before #tampa weighing 224lbs now and shootin… https://t.co/GO2REtMsfx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch @IlhanMN @israhirsi I had no idea what she even said until you interpreted it DML.  I agree 💯...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well damn, that stream set DOA back a few years lmao.   Fans: It's not just a titty fighter!! Skeptics: Hmm... Team… https://t.co/0On14SBucY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialITM @MariaBrink 35 mph winds and lots of snow. Inside relaxing with some calming music staying warm https://t.co/P35VLldByc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lettiemarie17 @Peelobes @littlejudda @EmmaKennedy @JoshuaYJackson @YoungLabourUK @UKLabour So quit supporting the… https://t.co/PVnagLylWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still cool noone like me keep going never stop stay with Simon https://t.co/osZCl192h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OneGoldenSun I still want a Teddy-Ruxpin-style Baymax, with a chest port where you can plug in cartridges for different games/stories.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are some creative ways you engage parents in the learning process? #BlockBreaker]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cspanwj @washingtonpost @byHeatherLong Hang rock all day, then gas up old blue to deliver pizzas into the wee. Some economy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will you please join us in wishing Michael Leslie Peters, M.B.E. a very Happy Birthday! 🥇🎈@thealarm @LHSF https://t.co/iMM2z4p8i0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi  I won't waste my time listening to you Democrats are you are bunch of lies and corrupt you're so far left you're pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem with many in American churches today is not so much that they would openly embrace heresy - it’s that t… https://t.co/38jaBYahOq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rachel_mkimball My dad wants kolaches from West sooo I think he’s gonna take me 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robbasemusic #hornetshalftime @ Hornets Basketball https://t.co/oHbwTxRFNd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itvnews UK, how is that Free Speech thang working out...oh? You don't have it. Sucks for you. How about the Right… https://t.co/3j7kFSzD1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interested in one of these?  I'm about to order custom knitted bottle coozies from @freakerusa with this graphic de… https://t.co/ayQ3nFwv32]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottMStedman Trump had to leave Vietnam 🇻🇳 probably his mind was on other things]]></document></documents></author>