<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I have already drank 2 Cherry @drpepper in the last hour. Really craving a third one to get me through my Biology w… https://t.co/iQyJFAlSeN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnCoulter Ann sometimes it is better to just say nothing insulting Trump Voters doesn't make you smart it makes y… https://t.co/2DfY9Uswh1]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy birthday to my forever friend @EllenCarly !! love you forever hope this is the best year yet💛💛you deserve it❤️☀️☀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JimWatsonOttawa why has the city not gone after this manufacturer and the companies responsible for yet another LR… https://t.co/sWE5hz4AeP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arriana Benjamin earned All-American honors in the shot put.  She finished fourth with a throw of 14.50m or 47'7. “… https://t.co/AwfbG0kB6S]]></document><document><![CDATA[However long the night, the dawn will break @ New Season https://t.co/IaId6HcE6N]]></document><document><![CDATA[“In order to be kind to each other we have to be kind to ourselves first” - @ArlanWasHere #WednesdayWisdom @theskimm #skimmlife]]></document><document><![CDATA[now that's hilarious. I really won't. You have the money mofo...fix your shit https://t.co/7NMGff61P8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I forget to post these pictures yesterday. We were setting up for the Statler Psychic Fair. This place is beautiful… https://t.co/Y7vY6PW95E]]></document><document><![CDATA[@murazina @_TASOfficial_ Ash looks really good in this outfit! I hope he wears it in the anime.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mother &amp; Son Date Night at Weezy’s and home to play video games! 🌭🎮 @ Weezy's https://t.co/myCCBNPA5H]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is so hard to find true real friends these days. Why are people toxic shit heads lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meant to post this at 11pm. Cuz it was in the teens then. But its still purtty nippley out there! @ Reisterstown, M… https://t.co/idLbYhSpr7]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’m not letting anyone set me back on the progress i’ve made for myself lol that’s ronald reagan dead fr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all when your favorite artist is publicly outted as an abuser/terrible person https://t.co/bLIcHzQcCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moonlight Melody - Irene #REDVELVET #REDMAREinLA_Day1 #RedVelvet_REDMARE https://t.co/FJoVKTl5la]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doqholliday Yes. We can't wait. But we have to until they are removed from society.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happened to follow this Kansas car earlier, hummed "Things Change, Jo" and remembered it's @JoyceDiDonato's big bir… https://t.co/4u8gYGUUo7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Morning☺ TGBTG  *https://t.co/s88lSmxaKS @ Blackshear, Georgia https://t.co/s85W1nMFko]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Quit blaming the cowdog for your stank farts! https://t.co/T6aHhKyxTQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing my 26 weeks baby bump with confidence in this beautiful swimsuit I received from @cocoreefswim. Coco Reef e… https://t.co/d7bfyOvO4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll take one of everything here, please 😍🙌🏼😍🙌🏼 #atl #poncecitymarket https://t.co/fjx3xfqLbq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Penny woke up and asked if she could see a giraffe. So we went and saw a giraffe. @wlc_wildlife @ Wildlife Learning… https://t.co/AiZGTtIXtq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Navy_Lady_45 @lloyd4man @SpeakerPelosi Nancy, You Are A Coward!    You Have Lost Control Of Your Party!   They Are… https://t.co/laxSOtSJyT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonMaloy Roll the videotape! Trump told his rally to "kick the crap out of" a demonstrater.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bestfriends The only thing on my bucket list is to visit Best Friends before I retire to Heaven 😍✨💖🐾😘🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the poet's choice presentation at Savoy bookshop in Westerly, Rhode Island on March 14th at 6:00… https://t.co/ob51ayNTxO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jorleigh1 @JamesFrye @Kobuk440 I can picture them getting to Nome and he is like "Alright, cool rest, let's keep it going!"]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been hanging on by a thread lately. I don’t know how much more I can take]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitamcabello @cavs It makes me happy since Cleveland is where I live !!! @NiallOfficial]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a love/hate relationship with how seeing someone can instantly change your mood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Friday night at #nightingale__la No cover Open from 10:30PM #davidelaffe #Nightingale_LA  #andresrigal… https://t.co/llvgkyB0OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NatalieTysdal Good clip. I miss scenes like this but not the cold temperatures.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had the same motivation to do research for my term paper like I would for some astrology shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @Netfirms is losing my trust minute by minute at this point. No one has been able to help me for 8 days. Unreal.]]></document><document><![CDATA[NICE GUY NOT!!!!!  "SF Giants CEO Larry Baer issues statement after alleged domestic violence incident"  https://t.co/LRi68Twl1j]]></document><document><![CDATA[BEEN THROUGH SOME BAD SHIT I SHOULD BE A SAD BITCH WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT IT’D TURN ME TO A SAVAGE? https://t.co/PuXktWE8bL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bobby is our hobby and we're NOT giving him up!!! @OMaraRules #DocumentaryNow #Company https://t.co/8aNHet8sjm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hulk4Trump @ShawnG927 @Jeopardy Prayers for you both! https://t.co/68VwG4kAcA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can't be the only asshole student that parks in the school's staff/ faculty only parking spots when the weather is bad, right!? 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a great day!  Faculty will be posting mid-term grades by the end of the day on Friday of this week, so a snow… https://t.co/YLX2VvkuzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I fell in love with so many shelter dogs today. I wanna save them all. 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s like society only notices you if you are a certain way, and look a certain type like it a norm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Look at the way they look at each other. Right?!?? Crazy chemistry!!!!! #LadyGaga #BradleyCooper #Shallow #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy fake holiday!!!!!!!! in honor of it here’s some dysfunctional pics :) https://t.co/id3KOlJ8e7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackleenDohlman @johncnnj I am trying to remember that show. I know that I probably watched it. Was it during the Dynasty, Dallas years?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Brilliant first night. Thanks @firelightmedia Media. 🙌🏽 Powerful films. Looking forward to tomorrow.… https://t.co/jm2sczYkPV]]></document><document><![CDATA[The problem isn't Meghan Markle. It's the British monarchy @CNN https://t.co/YMltRWORBI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WTOPtraffic   Stretches of route 123 in Virginia is covered in snow in both directions.]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨 QB ALERT 🚨   Prolific prep passer @Braxton1B intends to transfer to Virginia Tech from Oregon.   DETAILS ⤵️… https://t.co/gLzyR8Ylee]]></document><document><![CDATA[@emilyarmes @ladygaga “Weird” Gaga—still the best concert I think I’ve been to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrankThatFrank Yes !!! I miss those days so much the old emo bands 😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why they got this white ass girl comfortable asf saying “niggas” why all that?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtenney24 @McconneyMichael @FannyAlger1 @tmass34 @LdsSay @NelsonRussellM @LDSchurch https://t.co/z6nPmd3JR0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@APharaoh89 I was thinking that and forgoing my medical advice... but maybe I should just do cardio :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you get fast food and they put meat on it??? Ok I hope y’all realize you make me wanna end my life because of this]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse AND WE ALL WILL LIVE TO REGRET IT!!! NOT JUST THE ONES THAT WANT IT, BUT THEY WILL DESTROY US ALL!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pic from my grandsons photo shoot today 🥰 #LittleGuy #OneMonthTomorrow https://t.co/hUmOdMcwXK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@grahammctavish @CelebFanFest Best place for real food: Blanco Cafe.  Mi Tierra's is best after midnight. Do Not dr… https://t.co/YEa6lUCSVV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats need to be put on the record! Do you stand with @VirginiaGov Ralph Northam in aborting infants once they'… https://t.co/robls31WvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheKliciousShow 😂😂he made his insta private. ALSO on his fb he said you’re using fake pictures of other people for… https://t.co/u00ezfAcRE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @MaryNesham @KamalaHarris @ewarren @amyklobuchar @CoryBooker @BernieSanders @BetoORourke… https://t.co/SYO4u6eEAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QuancyClayborne I hate you! I hate what you've done to my country. I hate most of the children you fathered. I thi… https://t.co/Q595vEY0ZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socr8ive @xaaNrdZvSp8Iyaa @SharkAmagansett @linds4fins @nemesistheshark @JenniHarding123 @mazzylynne… https://t.co/bNEcKrDIMN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@misskylie77 @Terrilltf @ColleenLavelle1 Given that he's also spouting crap about the electoral college, I'm guessi… https://t.co/AFbOn1LBji]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrsblackburn48 @PocomokeMiddle @MrRecord21 Love multiple representations!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robinhartcarrol @CKFinamore thought you would both be interested in this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are these morons implying he's doing all this shit including jail time just so that he can write a fucking book whe… https://t.co/m5WOYyn5jI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_justjuliep literally everyone i know who’s seen them says that! i’m so excited 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[A great Longread about long reads — Where Have All the Music Magazines Gone? https://t.co/mVkYNhnOGx via @longreads]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hbcharlesjr The world at its worst needs the church at her best! https://t.co/MswsgiH3iY]]></document><document><![CDATA[alright one of y’all has to be willing to be my valentine please take one for the team]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nigerians in Nigeria act like America is a holy land and bad things can’t happen here. It’s just by Gods Grace]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is my last day going to work this early and knowing is what got me out of bed today without complaining 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PilarPedrazaTV He’s actually passed away a year ago but my sister in law might!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Leaving Canada to USA  Photographed by Me  https://t.co/wBuctiq7mP #photographer #photographerslife #photooftheday… https://t.co/S65ptqwYNL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Unspoken expectations are real. So let’s be adults and determine if we’re just fucking or if we actually like each… https://t.co/8wpIVpG6El]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cannot wait to see this guy in just a few hours! I don’t know what I did to deserve this beautiful soul  but I’m so… https://t.co/RrGYKEjZLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This was meg when I gave her a full ass edible and she don’t smoke like that]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BAKcollege, @CSUBakersfield partnering to share resources for BC SouthWest #WeAreBC #FinishIn4 #KernPromise… https://t.co/ZG4MFzo3FP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me for sure.. like if Cudi could release an album of him simply humming I would be on that shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shoomlah Jewelry makers on Instagram post awesome photos from the show every year so my desire was at, like, a 6?… https://t.co/HCd57DShyb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KjorObbinsL @Rachel23787645 @lindamckie66 @Annmari15306467 @gillsgdgr @Tillylawson6 @alijb1612 @debsjg1… https://t.co/yEC3Rt74cH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TKMadden @TheSunMagazine Omg I just began reading, but I worked as a gift wrapper at Bloomingdales at the same mal… https://t.co/EMID9gUGCf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll think this is playful. #laughter #tee-hee #smirk #humorous https://t.co/VTxzhGRz1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your dad finally catches up on #TrueDetective but you’re still at work 😧 https://t.co/2oPIhjPBiA]]></document><document><![CDATA[The look of I love my #daddy so much from #Bastet #misadventuresofbastet #ilovemycat #blackcat #mixedbengal @ Newpo… https://t.co/2b3djW8ybi]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am so in love with this month’s #boxofgrace ... plus if you order a box and put me down as a referral, I get a fr… https://t.co/82NHm9jDb2]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know that feeling when you’re the only one cleaning the store after you close? Yeah, than. It sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It is Wednesday, February 27, 2019. One citizen, I humbly call for the resignation of Donald J Trump as President o… https://t.co/74CUF95mvh]]></document><document><![CDATA[#estabrooksgroup #remaxpreferred #sellingthedream #paradise🌴 @ Saint Petersburg, Florida https://t.co/9u7pAjEINU]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOP proves itself shameful and disingenuous at every turn. There is no more a Grand Old Party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kdougggs Comfy pjs, lotion for stretch marks (or bio oil), chocolate, maybe a nice relaxing candle 🕯]]></document><document><![CDATA[LOL - I was looking at this photo going “She looks a bit like me—and her name is Rachel!!!!” 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelEDyson My sincere condolences I am so sorry for the loss of your brother may God-bless you and your family… https://t.co/3oesIwnRx8]]></document><document><![CDATA[a wholesome post to brighten your tuesday morning https://t.co/ovvPqBo8Mq]]></document><document><![CDATA[He's going to keep treating athletes like garbage as long as they'll put up with it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@boi_brice how many country boys you know been arrested for this kind of behavior? NONE! Stop listening to gang rap!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeilDiamond I send my sincerest condolences to Neil, Harvey and the entire Diamond Family for the loss of your beloved Mother Rose]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellaAugust4 @khp333 @HowardMortman @IlhanMN How funny, because in all earnest I accept the Gov of VA apology alth… https://t.co/ruZbayrZK6]]></document></documents></author>