<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Dining room options this round skirted table is so French and perfect for the bungalow #French #Roundtable #skirted… https://t.co/KQdXO15sAx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I told Justin I felt like an ugly Burger King chicken nugget and I wanted to feel like a pretty Wendy’s chicken nug… https://t.co/pd7gCSL99U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillSimmons You're so paranoid. Your anti-Knicks rhetoric has significantly increased this season because you know they're now a threat.]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@TheRealTPizz told me I need to stop turning all my little life instances into tweets. Bet he didnt see this one coming]]></document><document><![CDATA[get me drunk and let me listen to sweater weather on repeat and idc what u do]]></document><document><![CDATA[I work at 2 but i desperately feel i need retail therapy today... think i can make it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Fliggsy @Purrcival1 @ChrisMegerian Some theorize Manafort was the actual target of the “secret expansion” of the M… https://t.co/WsefacrSOc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cs00582scs @SweetKat111 Very cute! Now maybe everyone will understand! Lol 🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@impalachambie @jamescharles @jamescharles @jamescharles @jamescharles no words]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gottogetoutof It would probably trigger me.  I believe you and I would listen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok look it’s like 6:23am here where I’m at and I have NOT had my coffee yet to be and feel this ATTACKED and left f… https://t.co/kzFj1cFZzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol, I’m screaming at the amount of men who keep calling me a player. This a become a weekly phrase by several of y’all. GET OVER IT MOE.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LicenceToMock I do! They are the best part of some Chinese meals and even good in curry!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I took a three day break from life and oooooooo boy a drink or four with my inbox of emails is sounding like fun]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amynessed Teacher wouldn’t let us!! She failed like 10 girls lol a mother complained &amp; she passed us lmaooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[(1973) Empress Gladys &amp; The Pips "Midnight Train To Georgia" https://t.co/qVgG6uxQZw via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @SecretaryAcosta IF the list of people connected to this becomes public there’s a lot of very BIG names… https://t.co/TvZgGONrLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’d watch all of these, maybe not climbing...but add some new sports for sure 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lucasritting @largeben @VarshPrakash The GND isn’t a policy, it’s an idea. If it survives the house what’s your pl… https://t.co/LqmCelg2lR]]></document><document><![CDATA[This. Is. Outrageous. How did the BC Liberal government decide that this was good for the people of British Columbi… https://t.co/AI9dmudr8L]]></document><document><![CDATA[“The ruling class has the schools and press under its thumb . This enables it to sway the emotions of the masses.” ...Albert Einstein]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all there is a GHOST in my apt that changes the turntable speed when I’m listening to records 😭 it’s a manual swi… https://t.co/RX8wmSo4Qx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpikedSally Listen to all of your podcasts through  the NoteCast app! It let’s you highlight them!]]></document><document><![CDATA[4 Ways To Diffuse Everyday Anxiety https://t.co/aMykuIGbdu via @shinetext]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly, American Crime Story season 2 is an incredible work of art and the ending was an inspiring example of tel… https://t.co/ftezW1xPdT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Evangelical Panel: Sexual Misconduct Claims About Megachurch Founder Credible https://t.co/LVFjaq80Pd]]></document><document><![CDATA[A very snowy Skylands Manor Castle  . . . . #photography #photographylover #photographystyle #photographyislife… https://t.co/JuLU2hlyP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrsSOsbourne Your so welcome @MrsSOsbourne We love you and @OzzyOsbourne]]></document><document><![CDATA[My hope for national recovery lies in the fact that these incredibly hard working young congressional representativ… https://t.co/uZXJ86iaSo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaGAGirl @TeriWenzel1 @LisaJohnsonM1 @GatorMom73 @sheri_lynn95252 @CheekyAussieGuy @shergiggles… https://t.co/heyYz2YWeG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conversation Piece for Grammar Nazis. #OtherUsesForWhippedCream https://t.co/lmJM5i4LNS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eat Fresh and Save $. #PerfectPair. Thank you @ITrimceski @mmcmahon09 @quyent @quyentran01]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aligoljahmofrad @LindseyOwn @IamMissRamos @SXSWEDU @WickedDecent I second what Lindsey just said! #SXSWEDU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyep9 Lol I would probably have straight-up published the spreadsheet in defiance. Or sought out court case recor… https://t.co/NjXQxTxjLQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HutchBailieJr @DailyCaller The Dutchess and Prince Harry are showing their true liberal colors. Ugh! Cannot stand this gender neutral bs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I HAVE BEEN A RIDE OR DIE SINCE DAY 1! It would be a complete dream come true to win tickets to this @JonasBrothers… https://t.co/8fiQeXTwu6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our soil sampling toolkit makes a presence at #TXbarnraising #CitizenScience]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate breaking out soo much 🙄 especially since I take really good care of my skin]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton @candicejg1 There is very little about this administration that is NOT inexcusable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miren lo que me encontre! marukis69 @ Los Vallarta Mexican Restaurant https://t.co/1LAb7oi8GN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@malinowskipaige @Jaclynhill Hahaha I posted I got a new lipstick and one of my friends goes, “I’m waiting for your… https://t.co/bHYs8Wec6e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thelaceylondon writing is like sitting in front of the computer, wailing silently while your inner editor shreds y… https://t.co/c17weeqjNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have the best boyfriend 👅 leave work and come love me @JakeMaas7 https://t.co/RtNWTyclhG]]></document><document><![CDATA[#realestate #realtor #realestateblog #sonomacountyrealestate #sonomacountyrealtor #wrealestate… https://t.co/fkNT90k084]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snippet of my #originalsong #devilskiss which will appear on my upcoming #ep I’m accompanied by fellow #chicagoland… https://t.co/LdTGgdlZ74]]></document><document><![CDATA[their homies steady hyping their head up g😭”aye listen to bro shit he going ku”☠️☠️☠️☠️☠️☠️☠️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yah! One of my favorite schools implementing one of my favorite teaching pedagogies. ♥️ My first job… https://t.co/3QErs7gycj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tyler_casper Much depends on the organization, data collected, interpretation and analysis. Some statistics can be… https://t.co/bARWh3g10O]]></document><document><![CDATA[nobody understand how much I appreciate my bf 😖❤️ @justinrg411 https://t.co/Mg79hrN9EF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRickWilson For those of us who purchased the book on audible,  will there be an update with the additional mate… https://t.co/70cCgvVI8P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GavinRossdale Good Morning, Sir Gavin~hope you have an amazing Friday ♥️ https://t.co/TDvxlu7jSQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every Bad Breath You Take @FallonTonight @jimmyfallon #RuinASongWithOneWord]]></document><document><![CDATA[found this in my phone from before work when I was trying to take a selfie lmaooooooo https://t.co/rmVWROQI8T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Andrzej33430984 @Mortici62754246 @West_USA @JestemzWami https://t.co/fZVsWN5hHM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Yusnaby Lo tienen los que Uds que sus hijos, sus madres. no lo saben hablan ,pero vuelven el rostro. Eso no es. tr… https://t.co/GSuyHi2gK2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JackPosobiec @inittowinit007 This breaks my heart.  Not only for the child on the bicycle having to see this, but… https://t.co/n2wYLrLexk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I like these Jughead and FP Serpents future planning sessions. #Riverdale]]></document><document><![CDATA[I foolishly left my Kindle on my @Delta flight 3 days ago, and a Good Samaritan turned it in. Delta got it back to… https://t.co/ffBGcZsq51]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grandpas funny quote of this visit: Idk why foreigners hate Americans so much. I think their just jealous.   I thin… https://t.co/Ccgy1qCov2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Therefore I intend always to remind you of these qualities, though you know them and are established in the truth t… https://t.co/3PZIIM2KBo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Kallas @TOMRJZSR @VikingWilli @KeecoWang5 @RamosEdson1 @adagioforstring @someotherperso3 @astockard639… https://t.co/ebIZoyLz7o]]></document><document><![CDATA[JAY-Z - Money, Cash, Hoes ft. DMX https://t.co/q2qPvvx4oK via @YouTubeb ayhey #Vegas]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ann13Beer @Auzzielvr @reddogsusie Trying to show people how they can change thier lives... It's very full filling… https://t.co/eUAxl4YWx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenatorRomney Congress addressed this when it passed The 2002 Born-Alive Infants Protection Act. This is another i… https://t.co/OoaIO7Btc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleiKing Girl , I know that's right. 😊 I hit my snooze button so many times I have to rush around in the morning to catch up😁]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Elenaandherword Good afternoon Elena. Thank you. Enjoy your day my friend.😘❤️🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curt Cobain came along in the mid 90s.  He got the phrase from quoting https://t.co/wIaZ2fvXWV 🎥 Neil Young- My My,… https://t.co/ohWfPdQMbS]]></document><document><![CDATA[New on my blog, my review of @graciejonesBOX #glutenfree Bake Shop: https://t.co/9sGE7BxmEw #celiac #bahnmi https://t.co/Xs414ee2TV]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you have a scheduled c section in 5 hours and you’re starving already. 😕 Gonna be a long one but so ready to m… https://t.co/svlWuwdZ0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know you’re up above watching over me telling everyone around you how damn proud of me you are. https://t.co/YKQ84HPrxo]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy to help out Kent State’s Bateman Gold team and share the work in diversity I do everyday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wahhhh when I try to use @ATWWDpodcast promo code on @firstleafclub it doesn’t work 😫 #HALP 🆘]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KenzieCourtenay I have watched a few new shows but on different stations. I'm only going back to freeform because… https://t.co/sGeqnxva00]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thoughts to myself “I should go on a diet”. Five minutes later, thinking to myself “you’re right, I should get this… https://t.co/s0a4S2LHlL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anxiouscougar @officerdaddo Yeah. Great. Thanks.   Mom of a 16 year old son https://t.co/tepxkhtW3d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soapcentral Yes I like it but please GH let there be more memory swaps.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daChipster @hopedellon I was really looking forward to finding out who set the great Los Angeles library fire. Oh well.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Curt wins his 2nd event of the day 800m 1:53.29 awesome double @CsubTrack]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m a woman, phenomenally. Phenomenal Woman, that’s me.” 💋💪 Happy International Women’s Day to all the phenomenal… https://t.co/9LxABkfUuG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not all of them had to do with women. Referring yo Trump stiffing Pecker.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which dumbass decided it was a good idea to make cold medicine only last 4 hours 😑]]></document><document><![CDATA[And the men of the place asked him of his wife; and he said, She is my sister: for he feared to say, She is my wife… https://t.co/XQs9xz5QxD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SlutsLoveDuck This is why I need a son in my future. So he can stop the BS with his big sister. 🤣🤣 That's what she gets 🤣🤣🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[No checked bags ☑️ TSA pre ☑️ No small child in tow ☑️ Through @MCO like... https://t.co/rzwMCEFeaP]]></document><document><![CDATA[To my ReaderFriends and Everyone Else In The Whole World....LOOK WHAT I GOT! Much appreciation to @MarkGreaneyBook… https://t.co/Vv5xMsuhp4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t think of a caption tonite. The boys told me to quote Billy Joel or Elton John. Um, no. 🤣 ________  Isn’t It… https://t.co/OcNxFchPnQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cabrosa18 @rolf744 @baladonEve @luisrolando12 @Jorgelibremente @jgamorin @bugabea @oscarsito1956 @alimarve… https://t.co/ehv4aAqqNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I burnt my hand tonight, I can’t stop throwing up, my body is physically exhausted and weak, I feel like I got h… https://t.co/BeKmsipuBB]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌞🤗 GOOD MORNING AMERICA!! 🤗🌞 Who remembers that phrase?!!  This post I had to share....Do you have an answer to thi… https://t.co/BfzBE0Vcj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@simplyemmanuela I admire you so much, Mani!! Can’t wait to be partners with you on the SoACE Board soon! 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Alexander Fleming Day! #antibiotics #science #biology https://t.co/HVh8yEwg9N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who knew that on the day my 8th graders would be doing some deep #JCPSBackpack work, we’d have a brand new interfac… https://t.co/OkL5bIIdus]]></document><document><![CDATA[i started a conversation 10 mins ago and now im finna fall asleep.  why am i like dis.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jenn198523 @ReneeCarrollAZ I’m so tired of this crap! I’m wearing my hat and T-shirt’s !]]></document><document><![CDATA[My red eye out of Vegas was canceled and I’m p sure it’s karma for all the insufferable small talk I made at Shopta… https://t.co/oF0QbZIAPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[hello post-grads in the babysitting game, PLEASE msg me if you’re available Monday afternoon &amp; able to chauffeur some lil ones!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta love @RealGrumpyCat He’s really a sweetheart. #GrumpyCat #GOT #ValentinesDay #Thursday  #SinglesAwarenessDay… https://t.co/lgECDfkFYP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Risen_Savior_JC Mid summer. There will be fire works and dancing in the street.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllenWadford @gofundme Maybe together we can reach more people and in turn we will bless others. Have an awesome day!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lynndarra Nothing helps, I feel like I tried it all. This is how I look every night https://t.co/Ip4eLPcDVa]]></document></documents></author>