<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ErnieAcostaWFAN I’m expecting Bosa to be gone. But obviously if we hit the draft lotto two years in a row, take him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @realDonaldTrump, you going to meet me in Manchester to settle this or not? Coward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[fellas i lived in bad areas my whole life i walk manhattan late i walk north philly dont care im not scared of guys… https://t.co/pk2yaZMltY]]></document><document><![CDATA[¡Abajo cadenas!  Gritaba el señor  Y el pobre en su choza Libertad pidió: A este santo nombre Tembló de pavor El vi… https://t.co/GGg9sugSMW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@medoMerdeezy @_AlexAngeles I’ll give you my card. You do monthly payments or annual?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @marybartkowski1 @freddysuperlano Mark 16:17-18, in Jesus' Name]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Vanilla Porter by @BreckBrew at @staggeringtx — https://t.co/9qbe2FpStW]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@Uber TLDR you need to return my parents suitcases to their home ASAP. Your Uber’s car had them locked in the trun… https://t.co/fYU0vdFFfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheDemCoalition Finish the Wall??  People believe this ONLY because of Trumps lies that it is being built. I don’t… https://t.co/BuQAF2zOdI]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so jealous of people that can just close their eyes and ko with the quickness.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DENbuilder66 @BNYSELECT Good point in a sense they recruit to the school as a whole but the focus seems to be just… https://t.co/kOY6m3zMFk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peter_Fitz I was molested by a family priest and my husband was raped by one. I'm so sick of this Occult Luciferia… https://t.co/u0fpakieLI]]></document><document><![CDATA[replying “oh you were one of those kids” to anyone telling you anything about their childhood]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Los Angeles Dodgers Spring Training https://t.co/7s6n06sCqs]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I slept on this but Green Book was excellent. Acting was phenomenal and the camera and lens choices just bea… https://t.co/iIzfxQHzqH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenFeinstein You are a cancer and an existential threat to national security!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RoobNBCS TO was supposed to be a FA but his agent effed up the paperwork! He should have been a FA!]]></document><document><![CDATA[U15 Boy's Midgets - Championship Bracket (G2) - @MississaugaBall def. @EBAThunder 53-52 #EBAThunder @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Melissa_D_W @WCChargerSB Thanks  for sharing the photo!  I had such a good time today.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@skatefan78 @tingaliing @CoachTomZ I am praying real real hard for that.  I wanna see her on that podium.  I'll bet… https://t.co/bFqalO58WG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zaharias19 @famdocparker1 @DagmarUnger @WineJerk @SuperDario @DavidWohl @drmistercody @KurtSchlichter @UCSanDiego… https://t.co/lPZnajhzIB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ibepacheco Y de paso el jura que todos los que votaron por él apoyan su posición a favor de Maduro.]]></document><document><![CDATA[First franchise win, let’s go! Do I smell a winning streak approaching?! #JoinTheAlliance #AllAboard #SDvsMEM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another weekend on the lake with a great crew! 🍻🎣 @ Cache Bay https://t.co/F3ZIMPogBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it only took me 46 years to realize don’t buy cheap cucumbers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJohnsonLaw Was sitting in a 13-seater when one last passenger jumped on board and asked for the men's room. Since… https://t.co/qLFEBdNkYZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I gotta take a piss but to comfy and cozy underneath my sheets! Bout to have a plastic bottle nxt to my bed LoL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glennovator @gunsnroses @d_goodspeed @chaunceydale 😂 😂 😂 😂 😂 just trying to get everyone’s blood flowing on this Thursday evening.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump A least they're  not going the way of trumpy's casinos #bankruptcy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NormOrnstein She makes Betsy DeVos look like a Macarthur Genius Grant Winner. Trump hires gadflies for important j… https://t.co/aMFBJt8TR6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Church fish fries mean having beer served to you from the same coat closet where you had band class in middle school.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KonartAce @Keith_MooreJr @A1_Romeo Lol no way we would have known that. Easily some insider trading shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoshGen @2iJS3 Wingstop is good for it’s price, but but pluckers smacks]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t want a Breaking Bad sequel, unless I get madd Walt and Fring flashbacks. #periodt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rlal95 You can tell it's not Steph because he jumps for shots beyond the arc. Otherwise they're twins.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you into food storage? Need to keep items dry camping? What about just an easier lid to work with? Look no furt… https://t.co/oO7nCxAGPt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nevada gambling regulators imposes their largest fine in state history for the company’s mishandling of misconduct… https://t.co/7Bnvz2n5Mo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JJS5547 @AnnThacker2 @gatewaypundit @realDonaldTrump This is exactly what happens in a dictatorship or a socialist… https://t.co/wWC7S1Qo9H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanna get away? #NoMoreWinter #SouthwestAirlines https://t.co/ivxqrzX5WR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Michael Davis is inviting you to join Kids Get Money. I just earned $155.00 and you can too! Sign up today for a $2… https://t.co/YuDOXyKg0u]]></document><document><![CDATA[go ahead and say what you want about video games, but @sergejcsgo is 16 years old and just won $30,000]]></document><document><![CDATA[Officially 21. hopefully this year god has something good for me and my family🙏🏼💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[I remember when Hardwick v. Bowers came down and the Maryland libertarian party was delighted that state level sodo… https://t.co/fvwjAFq9iK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ftw_social @ScotchGuyDan @SenMarkey @ShellenbergerMD @AOC Actually support for Nuclear Energy is more bipartisan t… https://t.co/dMV86Enly0]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my brother was married at a courthouse with his wife in Texas, has had a traditional Indian wedding in India, an… https://t.co/kHsQX4eyp7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Transportation is the #1 source of GHG emissions in California - 41 percent! If we want a greener California, we ne… https://t.co/X9rP5FEUEG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fairfightaction @flemingbarrya #TakeOverAttemptGOP #GaGOPElectionCoup #USElectionsAreUnderSiege… https://t.co/ERJ4UCHJDj]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Repost @robisyouragent ・・・ If you are considering buying a home this year take a look at this interesting infograp… https://t.co/zp1tlUMn0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamParkhomenko cuz the buck stops anywhere but here (generically speaking, in dick taster terms)]]></document><document><![CDATA[St. Johns River Life T-SHIRTS bring out the Tarzan and Jane in You!  Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! @ St. Johns Coun… https://t.co/bubD0QNMyw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hiilarious that Cohen's opening statement leads off with the premise that Trump had no intention of winning.  So Hi… https://t.co/uJ2dfe9qXQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EWints @AztecAthletics @HopedaleSports @MetroWestSports @EWints did I go to high school with you ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gotta save and smoke the trimmings off the ribs as well. Duh https://t.co/On7wfCO32C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HaggertyNancy @NewRochelleED @NRXC_TF @sports_broncos @carmelcrazies @SuffernSports @Somers_XCTF @TUSAthletics… https://t.co/NOyj8Mw3Pl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amandapendo Ugh we get it you wrote a wedding book!   I’m writing a romcom right now actually and the thread helpe… https://t.co/Fixc86e0QB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m honestly blown away at how great things have turned out the past two weeks.. All my relationships are all good,… https://t.co/nv8uglLb6r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOPChairwoman Unhinged, delusional, leftist, liberal, brain eating disease !!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will Rioja Wine Increase Its Market Share? via @forbes https://t.co/F95C7WsATQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 minutes into this presser and we have a Trout reference. #itshappening #bebold #phillies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheLastOGtbs @TBSNetwork One of the very best new shows to come out in awhile, so I am fired up that its coming ba… https://t.co/Z7gonrE98R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @Steph56Renee Why would a hate monger be given a Peace Prize?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emancipation for the Infant or war.  Tell them all that. https://t.co/O0HL4w2at0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have found making up a test for my class is easier when you listen to @TheWho at a really high volume! #whoareyou]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wanted to go drinking with my friends but I’m the only one without a wife and kids 😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Black Barn Program No. 1 by @mainebeerco @ Boothbay, ME — https://t.co/eIPfUefSzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's one thing to waste OUR money, it's another to waste it chasing illegals, for DECADES. CA needs to pay for ille… https://t.co/w9k5vMk9Ft]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BustedOpenRadio @bullyray5150 @davidlagreca1 raw woman match over took creative(which two smackdown rosters member… https://t.co/Q8iCCUO9l2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WickerMike @OVCSports @RacersHoops @igotgame_12 He shared with Terry Taylor. Had 42 and 18 on Saturday along with… https://t.co/hTioyfDn6C]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mondaymash #dallasbrakeless rolling #trackbikes at #highspeed just another #monday trying to #getfast #nnr… https://t.co/PyFfYzHwAM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Karen86402519 @Sean_C_Larkin @TomMorrisJr1 Yep security system calls 911 and dispatches fire dept]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Trainer26515167 @Michael_Wrona How about some accountability for Ritvo and his poor decision making from his boss… https://t.co/pGt6ENkIHi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Webroot Spear-phishing only because my management refuses to buy training. 😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brentsobleski I’m not even a big lifting guy &amp; that was tge first thing that occurred to me the other day when I saw it too]]></document><document><![CDATA[My sister had to save this little mouse a couple days ago from our cats. They were pushing it back and forth like a… https://t.co/tNt0d3NQB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ByTheMinGolf @skyetom @tappin_neil In MacGregor DX’s in the 70’s too. I had a women’s set. Saw them in the men’s s… https://t.co/nMPBOIKFYJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final at Farmer’s Hall: No. 5 Gridley 71, No. 12 Central Valley 55. Bulldogs move on to a quarterfinal matchup with… https://t.co/8tUS0gtxho]]></document><document><![CDATA[Streaming would be so much easier if my computer wasn’t fucking stupid and knew how to detect headphones]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yu Yu Hakusho, Kuroko no Basketball, soul Eater, The Devil is a Part Timer, Gurren Lagann, Full Metal Alchemist Bro… https://t.co/9ORyhmJdQe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Peggynoonannyc GOVERNMENT INTERVENTIONS ( FEDS, STATES, CITIES, MUNICIPALITIES ) create major "OBSTACLES" for majo… https://t.co/jluSa8ixAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN  Now there are calls by many saudis.. to Kill and Kill more americans.. the Crown Prince is even  on air telli… https://t.co/R9dwmnIRRJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HadleysMaMa13 🤣 And laser off the hair on my shoulders. Perfect. Problem solved.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last nights concert in Brantford, Ontario at The Sanderson Centre was incredible. So grateful to be part of RUMBLE:… https://t.co/tO8hDf8TTe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooooooo..... It’s 7 degrees right now feeling like -11. And it’ll be 2-3 degrees tomorrow morning. WHEN WILL WE GET THE NO SCHOOL MESSAGE!]]></document><document><![CDATA[My latest for @FanSided on two trade ideas for the #Padres https://t.co/vUrMel9MRQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Getting ready to talk about humor and optimism- thank you NCMLE for the invite.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The U.S. and China have yet to set a date for a summit to resolve their trade dispute, the U.S. ambassador to China… https://t.co/p41OUlxxji]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BWVS #peace #primary hoody #bwoodknows #vinnies #X #madeinnyc @ Lower East Side https://t.co/apJe9UtHOv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice quality roasted malt build to back up the solid weather coast style hops. Resinous, earthy, full bodied. - Dri… https://t.co/AQGXT4jLxy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Guinness Draught by @GuinnessIreland at @oldchicago1976 — https://t.co/dlP9uYGofW]]></document><document><![CDATA[#accmascots are "helping" with the wxii 12 morning show. @ Winston-Salem, North Carolina https://t.co/Zstu7lzbJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[So happy for Bailey to finally get back on the mound, we are so proud of her dedication and perseverance, a tough a… https://t.co/9f0PIJ3Wwx]]></document><document><![CDATA[UFC 235: Ben Askren - "I'm Gonna Crush Tracheas Too" https://t.co/dRtaEQ1K0D via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@news_store_com @AngelCIraq214 @FedEx @RepDonBeyer @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @VA8thCDDems @lowkell @timkaine… https://t.co/nAd0El10xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julianareyesss Duuuuuuuuuude I just about to get out of work and will probably be up until 6 because of this stupid time change.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was once told about music that  Especially with club music its a  4 year cycle unless you reach legend status  An… https://t.co/5DEUgv8tAh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@P_Dubs13 Visiblement, il préfère voir ce que Shome peut faire en 8... il sait déjà ce que Mathieu peut donner.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mentally preparing myself to walk a canvas that won’t fit in any of the 3 Uber XL’s I just called 43 minutes home]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIP Keith Flint.  I remember the first time I saw ‘Firestarter’ on Rage. I was both terrified and electrified. The… https://t.co/MngcDP6C5s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tony_Lippett14 Can only imagine if him and Craig Evans would have been apart of that defense last season 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bee wanted to catch a ride on my windshield.  We took the freeway to get there faster. @ San Francisco Bay Area https://t.co/eBHDqSrsAa]]></document></documents></author>