<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[What do you think of when you think 'Atlanta?' Traffic? 🚗The skyline? 🌇 The Olympics? 🥇 Here are the 25 most popula… https://t.co/wJPTjyxEyl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TweetQTV Cavs game for the bday girl!! Go Cavs https://t.co/V09uFGStAv]]></document><document><![CDATA[AT LEAST CAPITALIZE SOME OF THE WORDS!!! You aren’t texting your friends... https://t.co/IHT1UBrOc3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo I can’t wait for your show tonight. It’s been a CRAZY news day. Wait til tomorrow #Cohen🎆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepBarragan THANK YOU! Please keep this in the news! Still no answers on where are the girls and toddlers! The boy… https://t.co/zANWsHyyVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3 Extended School Day for targeted students, Staff Mentors, SOL Stems added to anchor charts, Book Clubs, Focus on… https://t.co/nVBjPZn4qO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our friends from Oceana are making headlines on the Today show. GO LADIES!!!   https://t.co/M84Wu1LM7X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoycottUtah @shirleyb4433 @AOC @pamelamosquito She is doing nothing but digging in and fight for what she promised she would.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ShepNewsTeam Quit wetting yourself over yet ANOTHER FAKE NEWS REPORT FROM THE NYT! YOU ARE SO WANTING DIRT ON POTU… https://t.co/m5snyNGxdd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jhopeismyhomie I love you too. It that my mom friend and her kids are staying at my house again, they give me anxi… https://t.co/nebJjaYFjO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also just learned that it’s Brussels sprouts instead of brussel sprouts #woke]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump Of course they did. Why won't he show us his tax returns? Unprecedented. He had deals in… https://t.co/YpCiUfInUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[1. Forest Rorschach test. What do you see? 2. Original shot, pre #rollworldapp #hike @ Snoqualmie Falls https://t.co/VHN3WUA96e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jennieduv Mine are failing, too. I tried Google Images + kachina -- nothing. But I can't think what else it might be.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fleissmeister @khloekardashian @KrisJenner She’s not ready .How could she trust anyone right now. Would most likel… https://t.co/Og3lNTkiT5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a video @ Whispering Willows Art Gallery https://t.co/U3mRFNTesl]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you are gonna tell your homeboys about me at least tell them the truth smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, @CardiB turned NRG stadium into a club and I loved it 💃💃💃 #HoustonRodeo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FSCALLmeABC @juviasplace @MorpheBrushes @jamescharles @PeachesMakeup @LashKitty @ABHcosmetics @LuxieBeauty Lol 😂Thank you 💜]]></document><document><![CDATA[@peterlcurry @ChrisCrobert @GOPChairwoman @realDonaldTrump And not one of the trolls were the least bit concerned t… https://t.co/PvuFcjuL4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[@politico Cohen is owning his mistakes and rectifying them.  Jim Jordan is still sitting in office even though he k… https://t.co/f5Nl4uLuWd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo my dad keeps talking about getting a pool this summer and I swear he better not be kidding. 👙🌞💦]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HeartlessMoney6 @_mishamish how was she supposed to know her cousin was posting that? &amp; it wasn’t technically watching if ari was there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@solangeknowles gon have all the hood niggas meditating to ‘My Skin My Logo’]]></document><document><![CDATA[*me talking about my homemade pasta sauce*: she’s good she’s just different  Mrs. Wilson: “She’s Good She’s Just Di… https://t.co/d2NpSgbsa0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MelanieMeehan1 One of our local @Rotary chapters made some of these @LtlFreeLibrary (s)  for under-served… https://t.co/cLZlRHGsbu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if trash is really on the regular pick up schedule this week? @CityOfBoston]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Daddy, forrest_whit26, is in the house. #ForrestWhitley #AgsWin #Astros #TakeItBack #MLB #AstrosST #STBaseball… https://t.co/KzMPHVOD6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Muy Buenos Días 😃☀️🌞 🇵🇷 Feliz Domingo para todos 😀#goodmorning  #goodsunday  #bekindtooneanother #BeKindAlways… https://t.co/BJHlmwQJgN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@curtisatlaw @Haleaziz @DiegoATLaw Well, he could have gotten LASIK. Just saying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@topjibrone @ericty @thangthangthuan @realDonaldTrump Personal attacks- how mature]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally my life trying to resist the urge to start twerking mid cardio 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doorbell camera systems like Ring and Nest may give you peace of mind, but are you reading the fine print? How usin… https://t.co/I9kFFdReNx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think herbalism is great. Holisitic care is great. I think having a more alkaline diet is great. All things that… https://t.co/CPF5PSfpha]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Wonderful evening at @WhiteHouse celebrating #AfricanAmericanHistoryMonth! https://t.co/vvXXyXbgFz THIS IS WHAT REAL NEWS LOOKS LIKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[🐅 Made our first dining reservation today at #disneysanimalkingdom and I can’t wait 😊 3 months and 8 days until we’… https://t.co/xhwoa2Kk2C]]></document><document><![CDATA[A valentine for my sweetie pie yesterday.... @ Lebanon, Tennessee https://t.co/6hR4S0Has2]]></document><document><![CDATA[While Trump is playing Golf my husband and thousands of other innocent Americans have been sentenced to death. Why,… https://t.co/XCpxTGgXkO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is happening all over America in the south.  Irregular #elections because @GOP cheat to win.  They cannot win… https://t.co/S55YG7goYp]]></document><document><![CDATA[So @Delta while boarding flight # DL0510 after waiting in line in the line clearly marked 1st class and listening t… https://t.co/m6I2Oln6Y0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishful thinking in America we have equal justice Democratic Party have broken laws we will be demanding they are c… https://t.co/8vhmK4aBhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fully stocked on coffee, snacks and a decent amount of sleep for this 19 hour day ahead]]></document><document><![CDATA[constituent service work is EPIC!! i am tired, but it's been a real privilege to do this work each day and an incre… https://t.co/2EXDWvnFTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[definitely playful. Click Above to See More FUNNY Stuff :-) https://t.co/SfNt1cJfEU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spend your days off with the ones you love, in the places that inspire you to work towards bettering your community… https://t.co/zc8NEyYncd]]></document><document><![CDATA[More than half my suitcase is horse treats (and shoes) #Priorities #HorseCrazy https://t.co/Oa7Jphb6iq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP This woman does not need to be in Congress! https://t.co/A5KmRH3tq6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@squirrelfromMS @FredFromPlano Oh I agree. It’s just lack of interaction with people who don’t have same means or w… https://t.co/JAcT6HAQHz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m convinced that ppl who really entertain a lot of ppl have too much time on they hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeanCainGallery @RealDeanCain @HatchingChange @DCComics @TheDCUniverse Loved that show!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[... they claim you are —you need honest people in your corner — them being honest about your skill level will get y… https://t.co/GUcdrBQBWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Beachbody @shakeology Happy and full of energy😍 https://t.co/U8ChBqltD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kaled1974 @KarenSoutar1 @Cosmonautdude We's all smart here. 😂 https://t.co/aDOke3FIL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[NOLA-&gt;Destin,FL-&gt;South Padre-&gt; Chilifest-&gt; Ring Dunk-&gt; graduation 😍 so much to look forward to...stay tunedddd🤘🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at McConnellsburg Volunteer Fire Company in Mc Connellsburg, PA https://t.co/fejnj2ye9j]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boo 😒!  Protect your plants, pipes and pets the next few mornings.  Temperatures will be in the 20s!  #alwx… https://t.co/pvwZgREqjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[This boy really asked me if I’d f, marry, or kill him and got offended when I told him I’d go with the kill. Si no… https://t.co/6KxWRYlm9Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepMattGaetz Yes we do and we need to take away all entitlements for illegals. These entitlements are for American… https://t.co/Y7g3ha4Zn4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaughtyNiceRob So much better without a host.  We don't have to endure the lame skits like handing out sandwiches.… https://t.co/h7E99OqTfI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii Keep investing until we find a crime. Interesting take on our justice system do you think?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elguapo64 @alley167 It’s not going to end until parents start pulling their kids out which will cost the district money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[People are invested in shaming you for your circumstances because they desperately want to believe they've never ha… https://t.co/aHTa14yEx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Exploring another important topic this month during Parent Talk at @HBKidsHospital. All parents are welcome. https://t.co/IElXnTosap]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone else just stare at their significant other and think “god, I can’t wait to have your babies!!! You’re so per… https://t.co/VVhu1LmYtM]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hate insecure ass boyfriends. like i’m just commenting on ya bitch picture cause i like the mf fit. this nigga ca… https://t.co/cBj2cqjwts]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 5yo reported: “Today on the playground we found a half a worm. Its back-heart was hanging out. So we dug a grave… https://t.co/NHLrWYKb6s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steeleio_ Cats are genius!!! I don’t know why we’re always so surprised (myself included!) 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love how people just pretend you don’t exist anymore, and it honestly sucks.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesusRCuevas Esperamos que tus planteamientos sean verídicos. Es muy desconcertante para nosotros que les cierren… https://t.co/x6BaZEPL5Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Scrolling through my camera roll and forgot I took this picture of the @EmbassySuites bathroom for @TracyZager!… https://t.co/9TOhBlVpDa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MakeArtYourWar @harrisonjaime I’m writing a piece on it right now. It’s a very personal matter for me, and I feel… https://t.co/F0aiYIa3d2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watched “Fighting with My Family” last night and I adored it. I’m not a WWE fan and I wasn’t sure if I would really… https://t.co/u13Ysau6z2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@george_capen It.means he had TIME to repent if he had actually felt it necessary.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT @sherrynron @julianbarnes @nytmike And add the media in there to.  Right Maggie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So. This happened yesterday. Officially announced that I was accepted as a T3 National Instructor!  So thankful for… https://t.co/opzDAH9u29]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SAP @AvosfromMexico California Haas avocados.  Mexico crossbred and misspelled the name.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anybody else’s baby wake them up at 2:45 this AM and now you’re experiencing the 2pm crash? Nobody?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I could have started my day any better than with this text from my mom https://t.co/cQxVoU7Jwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please help support @MayfieldMaster1 as we go to nationals in Chicago for the first time  https://t.co/gS96DlVmwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had no idea this would be the last time I sang with tuckersterlingjensen but I am so grateful for the opportunity… https://t.co/tHue6al0zM]]></document><document><![CDATA[berenice and amia stay asking if i’m ok and offering me shit😂 like ok y’all like me☺️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BobOldisTowel @luckydoghot @KeithOlbermann Axe was fun when he was on NBC with Bryant Gumbel and Len Berman.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MKSupernova @GanacheSilky Right, but barring Any racially charged narratives, she on a reality tv show about drag, how subdued can she be?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamPelosi I hope it doesn't work because, if he gets away with it, things will just get worse. We have to stop this Orange Menace.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Waste It On Me by Steve Aoki Feat. BTS. https://t.co/OENj4S6DKh @BTS_twt]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really about to see how dry my phone is now that my bestfriend can’t talk to me for 4 days 😂😂😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick business trip to Dallas ! IDLife revolution and Top 100 VIP Gala 🙌 #DoLifeBetter #BlackTie #entrepreneur… https://t.co/ky45BTYghG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcent93 @fuqclout @sportsrapport @NFL_DovKleiman Richard J “AKA Rosie” Palmer is prob a fake name. That may be our guy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This MC'n Shit I Do This! 🙌💯🔥😎 @GBM_YungJae Off The Flap Wit It Lil Bih!🔥🙌 #TrueStoryOfJimmyRayPart2… https://t.co/GZ35WlJiX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Top #TrekMoment was definitely in Monument Valley, nothing compares to this view (Although the Grand Canyon was… https://t.co/xSfk3joYnS]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BTS with @stockx and @TIDAL. 👀 #SocialNTheCity ✨ https://t.co/MB284WTkQ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump All the networks all the media and 131 countries laugh openly at you!!! Fox Entertainment , Russia… https://t.co/XHhSZsLyrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Team_Penske @Blaney @DISupdates @Menards @NASCAR @FordPerformance Hope some are left on Sunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RIPLagerfeld #RIP #KarlLagerfeld #RIPkarlLagerfeld 🥀🖤 #HouseOfChanel #HouseOfFendi @KarlLagerfeld @CHANEL @Fendi… https://t.co/ixIqvJ20Gk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh UR solicitation of defamatory statements is ENTRAPMENT &amp; A CRIME!  THERE!  SUE ME! https://t.co/xzKnElf9ue]]></document><document><![CDATA[i started feeling really sick as i started streaming. i’m sorry for cutting it that short guys. :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone need a new sprinkler? @tsa_overlord you know soapap.illa would probably stab it. @ Danbury, Connecticut https://t.co/ezjRO4l6Ik]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mom: I want you to be happy. When mom said that, I’m thinking that I’m not going to answer her because I don’t want her to worry.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@colleenhoover I still can’t get over #itendswithus you did a great job at addressing the topic of domestic violenc… https://t.co/iwHCf844ED]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just voted for Ja Morant for the @Wendys #WoodenAward. Cast your vote here! https://t.co/olV4eseB2z]]></document></documents></author>