<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@TTruthpost @DIXIEDOODLE12 @777KAB1 @Cordicon @MrsMogul @fglaus @I__LOVE_TRUMP @bigredwavenow @CryptoKoba… https://t.co/crE8MH2CxT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@melissquirtle @GoNintendoTweet Old old dinosaur fighting game pretty fun. I used to play on the original Xbox...i think.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Flying home from #florida. Sitting in Atlanta airport waiting for a connecting flight to #Toronto. Been awake since 1am 😳#sotired 💤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Wheeler @realJacobAirey Liz, can Catholics support the Death Penalty in good faith and principle?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Watch out for low flying Bats 🦇 https://t.co/DYfgYUDJYd]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you don't like the weather in Arkansas wait 15 minutes, it will change. #ThatsArkansas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Training to #capture faint #lunarhalo around #mrmoon 🌚during last night of #firstquatermoon fighting through… https://t.co/lsqfbeXDd7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pigletish Anneli, help me out on this one, too. Your birthday party...formal or come as you are? [hee...hee]]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawn_H11 @SDSU_Recruiting @SDSU_DanJackson @CoachAndySims @EMP1RE7v7 Congrats on ur invite]]></document><document><![CDATA[@blakieshoww @XaeXae23 it was definitely a good basketball play. lights were too bright for hill]]></document><document><![CDATA[Centrists, talking about AOC: “Wow. So bold. So pure. So smart.”  Centrists, talking about Bernie: “Fck him and everything he stands for.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all follow these girls lives like they are worth anything but I’m weird for locking myself in my room watching an… https://t.co/a1uFuL2ALi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jaysview @mitchellvii Trump is exposing the swamp it’s up to we the people to drain it🇺🇸👍🏻 trump 2020#takebacktheh… https://t.co/DFYhc37fI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NHLPlayerSafety Is Boychuck having a hearing for threatening Voracek??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Vamos a Colombia 🇨🇴 (at @JetBlue Airways in Jamaica, NY) https://t.co/ecTTJV77kQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love this from @andrew_wiebe, as I was wondering who he would choose from Seattle. This doesn’t even include Robl… https://t.co/xiknVAwvFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The aftermath staring me right in the face; I'll get around to breaking even one of the days  ~ Patterson Hood Drive By Truckers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ready to battle from 14th tomorrow in Duel 1 of the @nascar 2019 Gander RV Duel at @DISupdates 🏁  @NASCARONFOX… https://t.co/0LSmtOriLk]]></document><document><![CDATA[Double trouble cc sn + cc inferno   What you see is what you get  Contact us for pricing and shipping details. Live… https://t.co/CVxDtIgzJa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lxs alumnxs de @psicologia_udem (entre otras carreras) apoyando la igualdad de género!! #8M #HuelgaFeminista2019 https://t.co/pLbYKSbIpL]]></document><document><![CDATA[فيفا.. 7 تغييرات على قوانين كرة القدم | أخبار سكاي نيوز عربية https://t.co/Ja7cuo32bX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1075thegame anyone know what happened to Heath's show. Heard the intro music, but no Heath. Hope everything is okay!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is this most thorough write-up I’ve read on the #SNCLavalin affair.   https://t.co/FWWAkpF5kW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Chloe's Restaurant &amp; Lounge https://t.co/D2oMV9sITq]]></document><document><![CDATA[im gonna tweet this again in an attempt to crowd your timeline and stray you away from machado think pieces because… https://t.co/MQbQ0WLS46]]></document><document><![CDATA[Greatest encouragements in ministry for me: 1) pastors and ministry friends 2) kids 3) senior adults. 4 realz:… https://t.co/93ddlMhHUc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ya salió el tráiler @MotleyCrue doblada al español como vez @FerNunezV @neciesario "The Dirt" en Netflix https://t.co/HmslAhEuDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrisNeeson @JimmyPiet I'm telling you the racism angle starts tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[Now watching, Carrie (1976). Scream Factory Blu-ray release, 2016. #nowwatching #nowplaying #carrie #sissyspacek… https://t.co/OGP2KTeZcX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @rwsalzman and I from @nkuedu as we talk about Civic Pride and Community Branding at our 3:45 PM panel on Publ… https://t.co/TQT78afoSy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sfeen if you’re flying back from Jupiter this Thursday evening I’m in!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hogan80Hogan @ProudResister @yoyobaba Birds of a feather flock together so PLEASE GO FLOCK OFF!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some pics coming from the @ZvilleBball win this afternoon to advance them to the regional final tonight....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Foxes were domesticated by humans in the Bronze Age https://t.co/ykhDdt9oYx]]></document><document><![CDATA[For 22 years no woman won a women's title at their first Mania until @MickieJames in Chicago]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano The democrats ARE themselves supporting socialism. They support illegals over Americans, they are at… https://t.co/aERGP8qYdl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every now and then I think about what could’ve been if I decided to play college ball 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lo_Gannicus @all_eyezonmi @Diaper777 @r0xie_f0x @CoachforPOTUS @FREETOMMY8 @GhostOfTick @GreekVikingX @Hybrid1979… https://t.co/l9NgSzpvQS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes it choreograph. But not real? That there is a whole new kind of tough! #charlottewwe #2ndNature]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debwrightjones 😂🧞‍♀️😂that’s terrible that democrats feel like they must invent distractions to even have a issue to support 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget to stop by the Student Center tomorrow in Rm 210 to donate! 🤗‼️ bringing a friend always makes it more… https://t.co/ImuJDnjgf0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Morning prayers finished now for some coffee time with St.Faustina. #JesusITrustInYou 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[TOOOOOOOP!!! MUST WATCH 😍 #BattleAngel #JamesCameron https://t.co/ynYyFKYvvF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kittykatya @levarburton Коллекция Мощной и Самой Красивой Музыки | Music and Arts | Cool russian music box (… https://t.co/kKxpv8jMCp]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just heard a commercial on the radio in Spanish. Spanish always sounds fast to me but holy crap the fine print in… https://t.co/IAOxumGyFe]]></document><document><![CDATA[1🏃‍♂️3.02 @CharityMiles @TeamRWB Restarting the streak... https://t.co/lNRRnxUlYI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueSea1964 @sherrynron Gaetz's tweet was not a real treat.  Why aren't all the Dems under attack for making Threats to the President ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm not sure who is all running so please send this to other candidates and people who are still involved supporting the Democratic party.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Don’t you have a sexual predator to protect?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GoldRushRyan @DurtGr @GoldRushTerry @GoldrushRick @Gold_Rush @thedirtGR @DiscoveryUK @Discovery Ah, no.  For you are Hoffmeister II.]]></document><document><![CDATA[On the way to morning shoot around with ⁦@IlliniMBB⁩ broadcast vs PSU 9:30 ⁦@wdws1400⁩ ⁦@whms975⁩ ⁦@Learfield⁩ https://t.co/Gs4JI4uTkl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whenever I'm upset that Trump defeated Clinton in 2016, I read something a Clinton ex-staffer said, and then I don'… https://t.co/ptjMISletP]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 workouts this week:  3 F3 boot camp posts, 1 F3 ruck, 1 run oyo  ... and 1 ruck up and down my block a few times… https://t.co/mczpKszk0Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@puck_20 Ok let’s try it this way if I am #ProLife that means I believe abortion is murder because our country is f… https://t.co/pEOmMXhdK8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OaDebra @TrvlPrst @maziehirono No true Christian will support or endorse abortion which is murder of defenseless b… https://t.co/VKUO6PS0tX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I commented on my mom’s coworker’s Facebook post because she has pups so I told her to bring one to my mom and I wo… https://t.co/35mzw6uD3W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardMigliore Thank you Richard, I would’ve honestly forgotten! Too much excitement today at Aqueduct.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hilarious scene, but the fact that these two bike cops don’t realize he’s dead is ridiculous. Also how do they not… https://t.co/Nr88yyFWeg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump An utter waste of our country ‘s time, energy and money.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Howie says “we’re going to let Nick Foles be a free agent.” No franchise tag. #Eagles]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pat_Weiler He’s good. He did just have shoulder surgery though. Not sure I’d want to use a first on him but depends who else is available.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill This story has been approved by Russian Military Intelligence and the Republican Party. https://t.co/tOsoT7pPCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[“We’re gonna see the inevitable Captian marvel vs WW arguments” Literally does that in the same tweet K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jesus, awaken your church to respond to the root causes of poverty and climate change. https://t.co/irpFNmaTcY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Accurate footage of me every morning for the past week.. It’s been a week since I’ve lost my glasses. https://t.co/0dDTymcUVO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Things on the trail already getting awkward. “Feel The Ber!” #Bernie2020 #PoliticsNation #VT https://t.co/gbTWpof0zS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris It is called a return, for a reason. It means that you paid in to much money to the government. The g… https://t.co/4KnhbkpRZa]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just wrote a review on The Patriot Badass Trial Pack https://t.co/rhk0Z8sMHc via @yotpo]]></document><document><![CDATA[« What are you looking at? » . . . #sanfrancisco #graffiti #california #art #graffitiart #standing #peoplesketching… https://t.co/H286iiFStT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my guy @Carson_Shirley3 ! @pfrost0214 @sheltonshirley6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teams would just put shaq in the pick and roll game just so he would have to guard the 3. He would probably average… https://t.co/pviL9MhTxL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SPD4649 And obviously the FM stuff was just what I bothered taking pictures of. They should have had available tra… https://t.co/jMoQ5nvNkG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Control by @4kingandcountry 3 DAYS! ( @joelsmallbone &amp; @lukesmallbone ) https://t.co/ojw2qyn2xg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feliz cumpleaños compa @ELMICKEyyMIKE le deseamos @LaOriginalBand1 #laoriginalbandaellimondesalvadorlizarraga… https://t.co/vDtgSHk18c]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CrisBaker6 @LasVegasLocally And I had the horror of scraping my windshield this morning.  We'll at least it did not snow.  C'mon 100°!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deskrabbit I wouldn’t say wack. But raising canes is at best, okay. And definitely not worth that wait.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loving these micro brush pens from @pentelofamerica #brettbean #art #artistsoninstagram #characterdesign #designer… https://t.co/gJt5Y1pZao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nbyrne01 @SonyaDevilleWWE @WWE_MandyRose @BellaTwins The Bellas are part timers]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump More Trump lies. Where are some pictures of construction? We need proof of its being built.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump use your deal making skills to bring our man home. 12 years is 12 years too long. Is long overdue… https://t.co/58G1Co2biS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Spring Break, Nashville style!!!! 💋🎊🍾 @ Nashville, Tennessee https://t.co/sLSHQ4wvJw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do not see how Democrats can win an elections. Writing bills to protect sex offenders who attract child, to kill… https://t.co/dgpRk771rO]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZkICu66QOL What are y’all sexual boundaries?.. we also discuss other shit too.. Enjoy! #sex #pegging… https://t.co/10qdZtccbX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@champagnennuts one of my favorite shows... #threestooges https://t.co/sFGcvlXsgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Alex Trebek, Santa Claus, Abe Lincoln, Stephen Colbert connection at 7:25 @Sunny_95 #BeatCancer #CancerSucks]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bucket List Item ✔️Disney’s Animal Kingdom Lodge was the most incredible African experience!! the architecture, foo… https://t.co/SDV5nVmTCk]]></document><document><![CDATA[My girlfriend is in the dispensary but they wouldn't let me in cuz I'm 20 :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls are absolutely crushing 2019 and making my heart race for them everyday!! 🐾😍🔥💃💕]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you’re sorting in Innoventions drinking Starbucks and read the news that the entire Innoventions complex (incl… https://t.co/O0o1S5ctqV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itjustmeg The tours over, this is the final 3 stops to end the tour on a 25th anniversary and go out with a bang.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wlawrence71 @molly7anne It's always a fuckin travesty with you, Walter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every city that wants to be relevant 25 years from now is doing this. By considering our 90 year old network “finis… https://t.co/Rr6WPrjkmk]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Lincoln North Star (@lnsathletics) student section is here and ready to go. Tip against Creighton Prep at the t… https://t.co/xuLYGgKb0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Dear Evan Hansen Chicago Orchestra! I love my job and I love the remarkable people I get to work with every wee… https://t.co/Lbsax6NqA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[CRS Report: 'Evolution of the Meaning of "Waters of the United States” in the Clean Water Act' (Updated 5 March 201… https://t.co/bS1XdMxIt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtsport2 Not a chance, Donny and Gladys were obvious but T-Pain had me stumped 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Favorite @E40 project. Idk if it’s the artwork or the content. Either way shit is flame. https://t.co/2zh6glPTyF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I need y’all’s help! My gf’s mom, Kathy, is graduating with her associates degree soon and would love to get… https://t.co/k7SKy33seD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ain’t nothing like it ... you think your strong till u go to the state meet 😳]]></document><document><![CDATA[To think, Doc thought this was just a gag. #WhatILearnedToday @realBradStaggs]]></document></documents></author>