<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[One of the kids i worked with last summer saw me at ikea and she was literally jumping up and down and screaming lol 😂😭 kids be kidsss]]></document><document><![CDATA[Voter ID Laws Do Not suppress Voting study Finds.  95 percent of Republicans supported voters ID. Tell California d… https://t.co/eCAl88x4sI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CateTolnai @HeckAwesome @sylviaduckworth @mrmatera @Kim_Schepers @missmac100 Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Liz_Mantel @MaskedSingerFOX I was kinda bummed, I liked the Alien. I keep thinking the rabbit is AJ McLean but I f… https://t.co/mtCGV9eBb4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Miss you 🧡👯‍♀️ 🥰 April 2012 catherinetheundistinguished (popped up in my Timehop today for some reason) #bff… https://t.co/zip5rm3P4a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Connections Community Church https://t.co/T9nkqF1C7e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Your message📰 Tap and share😍 @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/wawHp5kIae]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know why my phone is trying to ruin my mood https://t.co/uhLtmp3KvB]]></document><document><![CDATA[My aunt did mine and that bitch fucked them up so now ones higher than the other 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MBryanTimesRec Haha not that the riot is a perk, but the interest value is 100%. I feel you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% sure we got the better looking brother. 😏 #GKG #GoKingsGo #LAKings]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wonder whether people who didn’t watch Russian Doll still noticed the abrupt uptick in Harry Nilsson going on around them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@reepRN @ICURN_ Agree, must clarify and get new order for current facility. CYA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPGEVENTS @AmberRo70828563 @alyssiaaaa_ @Rere_blu @unguardedgrande @khloekardashian Yup]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IamSunitha777 @rpskataria @u_mirella @AnupmaMichael @fghdil @GsjpJyoti @greatairi @SsanjayTaannk @yogeychauhan… https://t.co/C9SgDIC6Qk]]></document><document><![CDATA[I honestly believe we go through everything for a reason. As long as we grow and become better then we were before… https://t.co/9vZngPAPg6]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy traditional thursday even though it’s 7 minutes past, we a ktown doing karaoke and i’m smackedw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Twitter won’t be happy till all conservative voices are silenced... #FreeJacobWohl https://t.co/bu9yKguAUV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hmmm,  Trump we found your terrorist, but there aren’t from the Southern Border!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coastal2002 @ShariDean996 @VincentCrypt46 In my honest opinion, after watching what the senior Bush and his son di… https://t.co/EtTvO0uQ39]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomatoOnTheVine And hopefully we’ll be making fancy butter and clotted cream and panna cotta before too long. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[It might be freezing outside, but it’s blooming flowers in my shop! You’ll have to wait to see color when these bea… https://t.co/MRIjAzJWLZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@2Urban_Wolf seriously I am wicked sorry. I just figured out how to contact you without tweeting and I will gladly… https://t.co/ui4ZdVGeq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jason_Priestley remember this calendarJason from 1993? https://t.co/GgqCbjaA5w]]></document><document><![CDATA[i almost convinced myself i was pregnant when im a virgin LMAOOO silly me 🤣]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks again to everyone who donated to the @OICompanions emergency fund! I had a great birthday in NYC! Now here’s… https://t.co/JkLhfIIJ1J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Let’s give a big Spartan welcome to @robertchanning tonight! Doors open at 6:30! Prepare 2B amazed! @MECSDSpartans https://t.co/zvQNQDo183]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m a transgender girl! No more hiding! I’m out and about ❤️👗 @ Target Store Hicksville https://t.co/rUnwpkUTli]]></document><document><![CDATA[@momtoemryab @Padman4321 @MZHemingway Not really sure what he said was a big deal. In context you understand it was… https://t.co/klyDrK4SrA]]></document><document><![CDATA[La picó 👏👏💙 Se la dedicó a los odiadores seriales😂 les tapó la boquita  👄  a todos los que lo criticaban   ;))  🇺🇾💙… https://t.co/nos52lqXVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[last night i has a dream that i got facial reconstruction surgery to look like @hannah_dusharm because she’s so god… https://t.co/dYzM0fdskz]]></document><document><![CDATA[sometimes holding onto hurt from the past really does ruin the shit you tryna build]]></document><document><![CDATA[On #PBS, the other night, watched the #AARP, films for grown ups, film awards. Really enjoyed it, when I usually don't like award shows.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews I’m sorry, but all you can do is laugh 🤦🏼‍♀️😂.  Gowdy is just a ridiculous, pathetic human being.]]></document><document><![CDATA[why is this tweet becoming such a big hit?? i’m just stating the obvious AND the truth...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Last stop at the bucees to get gas! (@ Buc-ee's in Robertsdale, AL w/ @baseballtrey3 @treylexisdad) https://t.co/Drm4hlm6MJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BraydenJinks @JerryDunleavy @RitaPanahi It's not in the US. I just checked]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichardFausset AGcon Therefore, I was not surprised when a friend of mine - who lives where I conducted research t… https://t.co/Icu2I8YCat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning🌅 Tap and share☕🍵 @ Richmond, Virginia https://t.co/a1HPGdDiXI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mcharlesworth7 Good Morning ☔⚡ OK kids I'm so confused...what the hell time is it really? Some of my clocks (self… https://t.co/sVufnDmMgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angelalarson25 @Tropes1406 @packersfan86 @brianlange77 @mushwear @FalQueen @JohnPaulFAL @jimmyjamny… https://t.co/RRBrnOsBej]]></document><document><![CDATA[commandeered by the acid patch kids @ Constellation Room https://t.co/1yyYLC4lnc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrated my dads 80th yesterday with his friends #mexican #OG https://t.co/xjdR4mGPu1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@El_fur_ez_Back Clearly, he’s getting a new face. https://t.co/BoAW17MCJI]]></document><document><![CDATA[How excited is the President that we are talking about someone else today?]]></document><document><![CDATA[*about to leave for San Diego* me: gram why is your suitcase so heavy? gram: well I got about 7 pounds of meatballs… https://t.co/KRE6g9amyQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me watching @LSUbaseball and @LSUgym at the same time. https://t.co/4iZIuXFiW6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NeensCa @joey_beavers Especially for the Trump family! Supporters to follow meaning zero democracy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to Un-Break My Heart by @tonibraxton on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/HOpax0uyf8 https://t.co/vaaSSVUID8]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is big news coming the next couple weeks... I'm looking forward to sharing soon @maitrainer 💙❄💙❄💙  #CSCS… https://t.co/2dYjOfHlWu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Get. That. Thing. Out. Of. My. FACE! #cats #catsofinstagram #leavemealone @ Reynoldsburg, Ohio https://t.co/DXzO9F8fJc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@harrisburgacad students Elaine ‘21 and Amy ‘21 received the U.S. Metric Association special award!  It happened so… https://t.co/JVoocnVart]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods The fact that she has more than 250K followers is frightening to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[PLEASE AMPLIFY @somedocs @GirlMedMedia @choo_ek @DNC @amandasxi @AMWApremed @AMWA_diversity @DandC @SenateDems… https://t.co/afynTpIQE2]]></document><document><![CDATA[And they advance to the next round!!  Klein Forest is up next! @ Cypress, Texas https://t.co/RoDSvbqgW7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AliLevineDesign @emimcghee7 Awww...she’s a cutie♥️ good looks run in your family for sure!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Please join us to share your strategies around #water #Greenbiz19 @SimplotCompany]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Americans are starting a movement to get corruption out of politics. No more buying our elected offic… https://t.co/6eL6G2TilU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@krassenstein @realDonaldTrump Actually it's Hillary Clinton's turn in Obama's]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kingnickrusso @RODEOHOUSTON Wow I remember that’s when you got me in! God bless you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@catcora My son(now almost 20) eats things I dont like,because I still made him try everything 😉He was 2 and eating… https://t.co/jsk7PqRtGh]]></document><document><![CDATA[If a liar says another liar is lying, does what they say cancel each other out? Or is everything true? Or do we jus… https://t.co/5KQBj5JFmb]]></document><document><![CDATA[A large day topped off with yeshiva little more hockey!!  Super excited to be at the sold out Boston College v. UMa… https://t.co/if1NQkUqe4]]></document><document><![CDATA[PRAISES TO OUR PRECIOUS LORD JESUS CHRIST AND TO OUR PRESIDENT TRUMP FOR STANDING UP FOR GOD'S.CHOSEN NATION ISRAEL.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playing with Leo’s egos are literally the WORST thing you could possibly do to us.... play with our egos &amp; we really might just kill you]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SpringBreak #GalvestonCollege #ContinuingEd #LifesABeach #Fun #Boomerang @ Galveston College https://t.co/tp64Y32txr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Throat is sore from yelling and I’ll be getting less than 4 hours of sleep tonight... but that dub though 😏 #iubb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RDub1701 @RickRosendall @realDonaldTrump Thank you for clearing that up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listen to my podcast, watch my web series, check out my acting reels and more!   https://t.co/adI0hYLbzy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Honestly @ChapD_ gotta be one of my favorite people on the internet lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@austincbishop19 Hahahahaha you just described every Christmas and thanksgiving I’ve ever had😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight was The Incredible Hulk. Which was...just so awful. #mcu #marvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[My most. ❤️ #dumbbitchgang  @maryamg8s @delicatendizzy https://t.co/ZRPE0q3KOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trumps MAGA policies have FAILED!  Trump policies have created an 89+ Billion $ trade deficit, a soaring National d… https://t.co/sBnWZaERyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Aww you never get bored of trying to throw shade at me huh? Get over yourself bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pabstimus @the8o8 😂🤣🤣😂 you guys are making me feel like a kid again 👍🏻😀😀 Nobody wants to address me in a serious d… https://t.co/wKkEqzzOYT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rayray808s You know it’s just history repeating itself... get with a girl, knock her up and move on to the next one...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just need to meet new people actually. I’m outgrowing all my current and old friendships .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Long Beach Performing Arts Center https://t.co/eWsb40wXIi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Literally soooo jealous of @BonnieWoods_ bc she went to NOLA for Mardi Gras and I didn’t.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_Vision_NW @lifeofablindgrl @myblurredworld @Girl_Gone_Blind @kayteebeexx Yes there are! I actually pulled togeth… https://t.co/BsPPJFvJrd]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ValentinesDay2019 wishing everyone a beautiful day filled with 🌹🍭🍷💘 . #LoveYourHeart ❤ fill it with happy memories… https://t.co/5bQxtxC6IM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Actress #SelmaBlair opens up about 'tears' and 'relief' of #MSdiagnosis ... https://t.co/GPCnb8nNxv via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mandahyde_ always has positive things to say I would go to her advice ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Otter_News Steve this is what happens when you eat the whole cheesecake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Arianna Grande: “Yeah, my receipts be lookin' like phone numbers”  Me: I feeeeeel that https://t.co/dDWtPBZGFA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forget the #cheesed challenge ... this Bald Eagle in Cape May is all about the fresh fish... including his friend o… https://t.co/CcTiOFAtgT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrinalsignodia @HippieHealthCo @rashmi1405 @riki_tik @chaudharyneel1 @rikkazimmerman @WeightReed @jenniferrcarey… https://t.co/8CuFU9D2B5]]></document><document><![CDATA[damn, sure thought my future husband gone follow me &amp; slideee in my DM by now. guess not]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rockster62 @MrBrianKenny @GrantBrisbee I’m a purist.  Well, mostly. I do like the DH rule. But why tinker with the… https://t.co/pLOPcqTRKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FreddysMuse I am one of the very few who really enjoys the second movie. My favorite Freddy quote comes from that… https://t.co/Wj8tbfVq1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaireCervenak @MrOatesSoSimple @Evo_Hannan @TornbergLea @JayThompsonEdu @karadowson @inspirecitizen1 Believe me I… https://t.co/Jw3AHgzV1t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WeirdHonie Or maybe every time they do something sweet start signaling thank you. same thing with you’re welcome!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t you just hate it when someone ruins something you’ve worked so hard to achieve?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ima start showing these niggas my bank account and if y’alls ain’t higher then mine dont even look my way 🤣🤝]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen My brothers put their hamsters in the same cage when they were small and one hamster ate the other]]></document><document><![CDATA[The search for a shooter this morning after a man was killed outside a busy South Fulton shopping area that was all… https://t.co/foNDnpX27Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snapshot of the commute home... #DTLA #CityofAngels #nofilter https://t.co/ZL2o8LpruB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RogueSNRadvisor Sorry, I miss read it. I though it was who do I think would win. I too would want a ham sandwich over Trump!]]></document><document><![CDATA[coming from someone who’s competed you can’t just jump into a prep w/out knowing what you’re getting into. it takes… https://t.co/bXGTCnmF5D]]></document></documents></author>