<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[ILL BE SEEING MY BEST FRIEND FROM DISNEY IN ABOUT 6 HOURS! Can’t wait to be in New York and spend the week with her!]]></document><document><![CDATA[i have bronchitis and i just realized that theres no way i can suck dick and that makes me way more sad than it should]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going for a different look this time... welcome to the dark side 🦴🦴🦴 • #allblackeverything #longhairdontcare… https://t.co/9b75G00LzU]]></document><document><![CDATA[We love Read the Day Away! @JamestownAPS @JamestownESPTA #jtownjoy https://t.co/Sn7vPoYTN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpiritAirlines your lack of communication has caused me to miss my son's graduation in the navy. You owe you vouch… https://t.co/9nCkk5s0XU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeamMarci @MarciMiller I was wondering @MarciMiller and @TeamMarci could you please follow me on twitter and my in… https://t.co/tuxPnovOj2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Veo esto y no sé si reirme o llorar ¿Qué dice @nube96_ ? https://t.co/Y5uSfYAl0n]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PLUTOAPLANET @colin_dunlap And they did nothing - of substance - to fix that. Listen. I am not a Ben or tomlin fan… https://t.co/ATXH8WWf4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm so excited I just want to say thank you for all the people that messaged and mention WOMEN'S INTERNATIONAL day.… https://t.co/qkWfoVfEFm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DearAuntCrabby @RynobergAllison @Dax_x98 Would he be more effective in the Senate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deray I've never been a fan of Steve. His attitude towards Mo'nique was disgusting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 5-@ARollman challenged me to post covers of 7 books I love: no explanations or reviews, just the cover! My 7 Da… https://t.co/M4DjdSkbhO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok I didn’t expect Sucker to be so good. I was actually thinking it’d be shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarrsPrincipal @joel_wisdom Mr. Wisdom is so caring and kind. I enjoyed working alongside him at Marrs. In additio… https://t.co/w9pxvZp6bK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cool it’s almost March and it’s windy, snowy, covered in ice and cold. Why #milwaukee just why!?!?? #sundayfunday #winter]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AsiaTater @Carolyncorneli8 @24k_Blonde @JRFelisilda @EPS1991 @jpinkglasses @eurodream @TeresaGresham7 @mcpurvi… https://t.co/kyvHu7usTE]]></document><document><![CDATA[When the man you like plays actual games with you and not your emotions. &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jmonkatthestate @WatchYourRepsSC Most criminals fall into two categories stupid or just plain evil.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DShadowgazer A local Family Dr who does circumcisions &amp; vasectomies -Dr Loveless 🤣 Chiropractor (so not REALLY a Dr) - Dr Quick]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bought myself flowers, chocolate covered strawberries, and donuts because I love me and I had to spoil  myself ✨💛🙌🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will someone please explain to me why Pelosi assigned her to that committee in the first place?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Serious words from a respected man who earned and deserved his security clearance.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anything better then singing 90s country with some of your best friends https://t.co/EUr9MNDr8A]]></document><document><![CDATA[We do not find God in the four walls of a church. We find God in the midst of everyday life because the Lord walks… https://t.co/VZJwfgOLAG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good one. Where countries giving a day off for International Women's Day are NOT located in the Northern Western he… https://t.co/YfF8mDE9Gx]]></document><document><![CDATA[As always, starts out simple. Then goes deep. And as always, ends up #proudlyjoyful. Thanks @ingridfetell… https://t.co/eRk7VrQoTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#this was my fav art, tiny wool fabric creatures in frames... no artist tags, only tiny numbers, 1234... curious, w… https://t.co/JiwFxQs0g5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is so true! When I was little my dad would always watch Jacques Cousteau and his adventures. So thankful dad b… https://t.co/YFv83Cqcgr]]></document><document><![CDATA[do white rich private school kids come out of the womb with a ski mask and ability to ski?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kasual_Kook my life is kinda falling apart but it’s okay bc I’ll be home soon(ish)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThomboyD So boring you’d think he could have released them in 2015. I guess it’s only been four years. Hard to tra… https://t.co/NeR8xoiEKB]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think staying up until 3 AM is finally hitting me. Hopefully I’ll be able to make it through the whole #LivePD episode tonight! 😳😴]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes we want to buy his parents a vehicle that can load this wheelchair! What an inspiring story ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN TAKE MICHAEL JACKSON OUT OF THIS GROUP. HE HAS NOT EVER BEEN CONVICTED OF ANYTHING. SHAME ON YOU. HE IS INNOCE… https://t.co/ml392yIZZq]]></document><document><![CDATA[My new friend #sundayfunday @ Dave &amp; Buster's https://t.co/GApq5KTbVK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Forgive my atrocious pronunciation, I'm still a beginner of the language.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What show are these people brewing up to say, “We are currently casting CONSERVATIVES and REPUBLICANS for a TV Oppo… https://t.co/BCJsYEhty0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here are a few clips of tonight’s training: Shoulders and back in black of course 🖤. #backday #backworkout… https://t.co/6kdU21q0Um]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have a story on the front page of the Milwaukee Journal Sentinel sports page.. #ThisIsNew]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jdavidzimmer @gettymusic @EdCashStudio I love this one, David. Excellent work!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JusstGlo1 I had this same conversation but it was for my first kiss. So yes we were this corny in middle school]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeaBoots @Ray7Cincinnati A funeral home becomes a mosque..great symbolism there]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NoahShachtman Such a bad optic for the GOP... are they thinking being so blatantly on board to cover it up makes them look less guilty?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ejrl Esto era de esperarse ... esperemos q ya con esto se acaben los 90 días de @FedericaMog y sus Ilusos dialogos con Narcos ....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McFaul Am not familiar with who this is, but if he is a leading foreign investor, why would he ruin his business r… https://t.co/klE5WEJaon]]></document><document><![CDATA[A veces uno construye muros, no para evitar que otros entren, pero sí para ver a quiénes de verdad les importa como para destruirlos.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen your husband @johnlegend  is so handsome. Can’t stop staring at him on @NBCTheVoice]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had to catch myself at work🤦🏽‍♀️ I’m driving the forklift and bodak yellow come on my Pandora and I get a little… https://t.co/NRIBNr642m]]></document><document><![CDATA[@euphoriatingz You grew 3 inches in 3 yearss, i only grew 2 and a half😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commentary: Utah has an Orwellian definition of ‘compassion’, via @sltrib https://t.co/6szB1ahvHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monstera Monster  Now on society6 . .   ✳️Link in Bio @NinaZivkovic ✳️ . .  #illustration #art #creative… https://t.co/YnUeUOA6LD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I never realized how much being raised in a traditional religious environment has impacted Lecy. She seemed offende… https://t.co/jlMb67eOTt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frenchieears I did switch to a menstrual cup before getting pregnant, I didn’t fully get to experience using it bu… https://t.co/NRAGEGjXx1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@seanhannity SMH Thank You Hannity And Fox News For Reporting The Truth And For Standing for Whats Right !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephMillerShow @suzannewhang @fromthebunkerjr My sisters from other misters❣]]></document><document><![CDATA[❄️ ice ice baby ❄️ so blessed to dance for this icon at @radiocity ! @vanillaice @ Radio City Music Hall https://t.co/TYpVjXPogf]]></document><document><![CDATA[GLORY TRAIN FIRESIDE CHAT! https://t.co/cvboqjN59I Paula White-Cain God is a Restorer!! Get ready to receive 7 x's… https://t.co/70vIDL3qym]]></document><document><![CDATA[So there's a girl somewhere in her house all alone pregnant with no one she's going to give birth to a baby and she… https://t.co/LBapXmPpI0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Always get butterflies 🦋 when I come here manresarestaurant by chef @davidkinch #DavidKinch &amp; latest CDC… https://t.co/9maZBWyRgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's snowing here this morning. Yuck. Chuckie tried to take my makeup brushes this morning. He loves the big fluffy ones. Silly kitty.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump You will be gone soon and in jail. How does it feel to know NY your home is going to put you away. She… https://t.co/6qYjSAxDFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congressman Bishop invites high school students to participate in congressional art competition… https://t.co/jD63xEeMNm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B52Malmet Sarah Sanders is a grifter and an enabler that people not in the base are paying for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s in more films than just this one!  Rat Race, Mystery Men, Digimon  This song is lame this song is dumb But Shr… https://t.co/QCRFaFJRr0]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you didn’t get to come see Amir ball this year...here he is!  He go Left! He go Right! He go Left! Right! Left!… https://t.co/a4115c4dIJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BP_Hutch @Delta @KLM Are you working tomorrow?! Maybe we will see you?! Our flight leaves late afternoon ✈️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whoever came up with the brilliant idea to bring @DENISE_RICHARDS to #RHOBH Give them a raise! Now! Lol! She is awesome AF!!!! Love her!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS PLEASE help stop Child Protection Services from kidnapping our children and grandchildren for profit and pu… https://t.co/vQgD2ydGz2]]></document><document><![CDATA[ugh the flashbacks... poor agent Keaton 😢 #TheEnemyWithin @Morris_Chestnut]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! @ Stonehaven (Charlotte neighborhood) https://t.co/tDoTutkrmC]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@tamisawyer says renegotiating @mlgw contract with @TVAnews or other options are “on the table.” Calls for environ… https://t.co/dkNe3FHNGf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Minnow1233 I don’t get why people hate him  honestly. Technically his story and setting was most accurate to the c… https://t.co/oZXB9gH6YJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/CLUolCUxj0]]></document><document><![CDATA[5 days until I can go home y’all 😭 I haven’t seen my boyfriend, pets, or family since JANUARY. I am so ready 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waking up at 7:30 on a Saturday to my car covered in snow to get a massage this is DEDICATION also my back has been… https://t.co/xvSkTPNXqX]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s so sad that there’s people that i’ll only get to talk to in my dreams. i look forward to them all the time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[No bueno. I was already going to vote for @CorrinRankin after meeting her at @SFGOP  but this definitely sealed the… https://t.co/ORISuHZgXG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shawridgefarm @raygreidanus Yup.  My sister in law is a carpenter but she got a teaching job and loves it.  I also… https://t.co/6w8dZG0sIo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@standstrongppl Being a believer, I have to differ with you on being dead and not knowing it.  I believe you will k… https://t.co/y6jiCrUnaB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TapeFlip @thedad “I can check both and double check with them, motherfucker”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BuyYourHomeNow @craigsmorgan Goligoski contract expires before the expansion draft (both occur in 2021)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Want some books? MIT Academy's Senior Class of 2019 are selling Mystery Book Bundles For $15 on Facebook Market Pla… https://t.co/4RI70kpc81]]></document><document><![CDATA[New York was fun this past weekend. Would love to go again but maybe when its warmer out 😅  #newyork #topoftherock… https://t.co/DBvgv4lVyt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@briannnanicole1 they just wanna fuck over women and claim it as moral. we’ve already learned. 🤷🏼‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello to all my fans, I’m back and not private so you can all retweet how funny I am now]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MontereyAq Life under the sea, who knew? "Anemone at the gates" best pun I've ever heard.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananavarro It's all about point of view.  I view that cake as simply perfect!  😊💗]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hensctes Wonders how long we have to wait to see Neil again?  I won’t tell you how many times I have watched the Alexis/Neil clips]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ArtKatsudon @catneylang Here... &amp; I was cringing the whole time. I can't believe it broke my heart again. https://t.co/bqp0WkDWki]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mother is too cute to handle, and her smile is everything✨ @ FINKA Table and Tap https://t.co/jY2E8kmGLL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mr_Anderson This is amazing! I didn’t even know it existed...running off to check it out now. ☕️]]></document><document><![CDATA[For you @DonaldJTrumpJr #loserson and to all standing behind you and clapping #shameonYOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Great Neck Board of Trustees has returned after getting advice of counsel. It is 1 a.m. Once overflowing, now V… https://t.co/yHIHIIihrQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Advisors @FSCJ_Official care! Demonstrating the positive power of service today, we made over 70… https://t.co/L6PZwl8FSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey #fairhopealabama graysoncapps and band are playing #liveatfive in about an hour. I will be filling in for Corky… https://t.co/GH92FfgNxG]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's about to get real here in #ATL.  That thunder sounded like a sonic boom!  #aShotOfBrandi #tuesdaythoughts https://t.co/iJNTS20s8X]]></document><document><![CDATA[Part 1 Relatable of Be REAL #REALedu and had to get the highlighter out. Truth! @TaraMartinEDU https://t.co/9iUxUOf5n8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanySikkStixxx @Hayden_E290 @sydneyflach @RacinJason38 What is wrong with you???? I will drive over and give you… https://t.co/upQRH0Qfqz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe it’s been nearly a year since this magical day.  #GraceProject #scarsAreBeautiful 800goddesses @ Ol… https://t.co/DzjbReRHeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am super excited to announce that I have been accepted into Rosalind Franklin University of Medicine and Science… https://t.co/GyFXs4KO2t]]></document></documents></author>