<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I've accepted the #BookCoverChallenge from @pam_bernards  to post 7 covers of books I Love: no explanations, no rev… https://t.co/1DLNmOfnhR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daddyhoseok_twt @lord_zaidi If u can’t tell if I’m joking... https://t.co/baWs6I49lM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Probe me, God, know my heart; try me, know my thoughts. See if there is a wicked path in me; lead me along an ancie… https://t.co/UeBrdDsTaT]]></document><document><![CDATA[SO MUCH FUN and it’s only DAY 1!!! Day 2 is going to be so hard to beat #NCAAindoorchampionships https://t.co/3vPLsWYODi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Sunday Morning! (@ Home in Shelby, NC) https://t.co/bD7JbDrp5r https://t.co/iRgKE6BBlK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VargasChrisv @Rockies You can’t do anything, they won’t follow back 😔🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman Just approach it from an overall cost perspective. We currently spend $9,000 per person per year on he… https://t.co/0H89F4wuG5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fatigue has set in. Moving has become a fantasy. Luckily I have unlimited data and have yet to finish Unbreakable K… https://t.co/PJChqkIfVw]]></document><document><![CDATA[The first annual Chicken Wing Challenge is official done! Congratulations to thehoneypaw for winning the Judges Awa… https://t.co/lgdI79sqvE]]></document><document><![CDATA[#VIP Hyde Lounge at T-Mobile with tine.bean5150.   #TheseSeatsFuckingROCK   #GoLeafsGo #TORvsVGK @ T-Mobile Arena https://t.co/KsGZ6ykzTR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @MarkLutchman for bringing this to our attention. This needs to go viral so everyone is aware. https://t.co/6Tf7lSYSvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Snow day Guac, if one thing good came from me working for chipotle its learning how to make it. #Guacamole #guac… https://t.co/Jv4tAr04TW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loved having Dragon Soccer today at JES.#JESFamily https://t.co/k5K3iCa1Di]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why the Aeron Is Still the Most Coveted Seat in the Office https://t.co/AK6n1wjMrY #design #interiordesign #workplace]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisIsROCK2019 Grant Lee Buffalo - Mighty Joe Moon Son Volt - Wide Swing Tremolo Alejandro Escovedo - Burn Something Beautiful  👍🎵]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NotSoUltraCapo I’d rather lose 100-1 to Seattle every night than be stuck in the minor leagues for all of eternity. Enjoy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you ever had a role like "Pharmacy Technician"? What did you like most about that job? #Healthcare #NewLexington, OH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone send me the video of the lil girl dancing to earth, wind and fire??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hewett follow shot with 1.1 seconds to play wins it for Portsmouth, 40-39 @PHSScores @FostersDailyDem @seacoastonline]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports @PhilipRucker I see that it's now and issue on CNN we've been blackballed and ridicule for the sim… https://t.co/UWJKH4ZrU0]]></document><document><![CDATA[No person can call t Holocaust less than t Devil's ultimate work against mostly Jews 6M+ along w many others. And t… https://t.co/IDjK39JLKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jahmir Young puts DeMatha up 75-72 with 32.9 to go in 2OT. #DMVhoops #ACIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewEraAlex Omg those are real? I thought it was a fever dream I had every day at 4:30 am]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sawsharkman @WhySharksMatter You’re doing vertebrae right? Mostly C and N? Can’t wait to read it after it’s all written up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching a second time this still makes me “well up” - delightful, real and utterly charming from a truly brilliant… https://t.co/BDna9TYlt4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#lightthelion #challenge #protectwhatyouveearned strong,fast and travel Royal Pride @ Queens University of Charlotte https://t.co/TOKnFbAdqi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yanarchy @james_k_nelson @nodefest I think some of us in the US would love to help out with a Japan React conferen… https://t.co/CL3sbvacv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CPopeHC @ComfortablySmug Also if they were seriously considering passing something as major as M4A through reconci… https://t.co/3poyK0IJNG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Palita_40 Muy buenos días tengas tu también pAlita y feliz domingo familiar cuídate mucho saludos internacionales ,!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VABVOX @Steph56Renee Sad to see that even Bernie Sanders has fallen for the GOP propaganda about Hillary Clinton,… https://t.co/6c3NzAMPUm]]></document><document><![CDATA[The dudes @PAKA_FLOCKA and @BigNateChester are BACK. Be sure to check out the latest installment of The Core 4, I p… https://t.co/U09Rakc7Zv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Guihcharito Entendo, não precisamos copiar tudo, EUA masculino tb não usa as três estrelas do feminino, o símbolo… https://t.co/iv2LQDXvcz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClayTravis I think Auburn will beat them next Saturday. It will be a very hostile environment. Glad to see Kentucky go down!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Typical great, long read. This time about the quirky, brilliant Bill Hader.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ForzaCorrado Brilliance at its best!!! Well done brother.  Sadly....its spot on]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatGuy_sk @SconsetCapital @DineshDSouza @RealCandaceO Well then I think you should get off your lazy ass and get… https://t.co/O6885EbJ8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cross #beignets and a #cafeaulait off the bucket list. Now what to do for the next four hours since I seldomly drin… https://t.co/QHkMhLcxm1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gibson_medley @tim1961 @CNN @andersoncooper It is when he’s my president and lying through his immoral ass.  Totally my business]]></document><document><![CDATA[Xev Bellringer vs. Hannah Perez. Who will win this rematch for the Street Fight Championship? Comment your pick. An… https://t.co/eRuwAxz4pb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasmeann The beats x arnt that bad you just cant over charge them or you'll fuck them up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvlt Refs definitely missed this call, but poor perimeter defense and turnovers lost the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is Hard-work, this is Persistence, this is Patience, this is Passion, this is Love, this is Quality, this is C… https://t.co/YDPnrcJRZy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Law98gator @GatorDave_SEC There is definitely a benefit to the school but my argument has always been Home and Hom… https://t.co/smRjkckdv8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is there anyway to set a WKInterfaceTable to scroll full rows like the alarm app does with the crown?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I missed one of my favorite people in the world's birthday the other day. @wndrwheatleys Val we love you and hope i… https://t.co/YApBtITLdA]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s even MORE dope that in the next scene he punches a hole through a guy while his ass (and I’m gonna assume dick… https://t.co/NinHILxN67]]></document><document><![CDATA[i swear you get one time to try and play me 😂 you fuck up once you getting kicked to the curb, your pussy not good… https://t.co/o3XddrbnTx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to Darius at @1stPhorm for the nice note when I opened up my post workout stack bundle. I appreciate it. https://t.co/wxDya5hWCx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just updated my tinder profile. Where the bitches that like GTA Vice City fun facts at]]></document><document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost GEE WAPO, WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL OBAMA A DEMAGOGUE? https://t.co/ktduGkJJz5]]></document><document><![CDATA[One year ago today, I wasn’t the same person because of those thoughts. I was an empty shell that barely even went… https://t.co/5R6XMX8uP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoxingKingdom14 AJ will have a much better chance if he can have the fight in England where he can choose the refe… https://t.co/j6GC85ySde]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandyCoben Sanduuu !!  Hola, oye, me gustaría saber tu experiencia con amor platónico, prohibido, imposible y o friendzone.  Saludos]]></document><document><![CDATA[Five inches of rain on Howell Mnt in less than 24 hours, so far. Napa River starting to get interesting. #napa… https://t.co/ykRXPpQGWB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sang Run MD Thu Mar 7th AM Forecast: TODAY Snow Showers Hi 25 TONIGHT Snow Showers Lo 20]]></document><document><![CDATA[Joe Harris just beat the greatest shooter of all time which means Joe Harris is the new greatest shooter of all time.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@88nae88 @Spotify I know you was over there trying to hit those high notes you ain’t slick]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRightMelissa Can we expect our fair shake at going after the real collusion with Russia and HRC ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tiva1000 it’s both TCs in the same shot.  Why didn’t they call you? https://t.co/6WFSITLqYl]]></document><document><![CDATA[it’s midnight and im at a sketchy Hookah Lounge ready to blast that new @solangeknowles project!! eyes closed, lung… https://t.co/d91hkey8eq]]></document><document><![CDATA[🌞☕🙏🏻 (at @MessengerCoffee Co. in Kansas City, MO) https://t.co/X7pId0aGeE https://t.co/OW0OSLPiPb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealDeanCain @GreyHouseDan We are going with quartz.... overall a better material when considering multiple inputs.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alecmjohnson1 Hope I look this good in 20 years 😭 https://t.co/bsXWJP9CE6]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can also see her struggle with her powers. What I'd like to see is Rogue steal them. Then each progressive movi… https://t.co/yFetzTeGdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Sithlord614 @HERO_15_ @HERO_15_ Don't mind our friend buddy, he means well https://t.co/ygsWohavu5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an All Good Things by @statebrewingco at @StateBrewingCo — https://t.co/2NdjlBwdLx]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board in Philadelphia, PA https://t.co/u23FkUVj2Y]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jcnewbury That shit happens on my wife’s phone all the time.. weird shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you to the student/athletes of @Northmen_Dance for taking a minute out of their preparation for tonight’s sho… https://t.co/pt95XouSgS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TrixieParson @NBCNews @TODAYshow It’s just a period. Fact of life. No biggie.]]></document><document><![CDATA[they DAMN WELL mf recognize y’all 2019 running start students at graduation this year @tacomaschools   running star… https://t.co/aqh5OQ7jHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Duluth East with pregame huddle. Game time 👏#TheTourney19 @FollowThePuck https://t.co/EA02x3oXWR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Picture to the left was my birthday on Sunday and the picture to the right was my birthday 2017. Came across some o… https://t.co/j3FgcOTrnT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EmeraldRobinson @NRO @SpecialReport @stephenfhayes You shill for a criminal POTUS who will be known in generations… https://t.co/uhSWvdZUU4]]></document><document><![CDATA[So YNW Melly kills his 2 best friends and stages it as a drive-by. Then drops a song months later about it that blo… https://t.co/6yaIwv6Oas]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctor: Mr. Trebek, I’m afraid you have Stage 4 pancreatic cancer.  Alex Trebek: ..... Doctor: *sigh* What is, you… https://t.co/ZGZGiMLCMe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cubanos hijueputas , hablando mierda de este país pero cuando llegan acá quieren pedir cuanta ayuda quieran y arrasar con todo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moron Trump stupidly blurts out what his useless wall and ‘national emergency’ is really all about.  Desperate atte… https://t.co/BHAJzei6it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The following is a current Mexican Poem. Enjoy guys: 🇲🇽💚♥️ https://t.co/InayvPUTDP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Son_mamadas @princhipesxa @Una_tal_Dian @DafneHDSM @lopezobrador_ Entonces para ti el cazar huachicoleros ayudar a… https://t.co/SMIIno0u27]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatiePavlich Cool book, a few miles from home. https://t.co/SCjDDT8Pox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Love this tweet. “ before (Paul Revere)...outnumbered...out-gunned...” great reminder of what those who went before… https://t.co/ZutCUwcg3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come join us tonight for our Italian Bistro. @brewsterschools https://t.co/HzhaFHYqU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr And many many people call you, idiot JR, a fucking moron]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect Effort Selfless Attack Do it right or do it again  #RaiderMAKER  #RaiderPRIDE https://t.co/bhLYuPZ19x]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're young and you like sweets then you need to decide now if you like sweets more or your teeth. #ouch #toothache #feelslikedeath  😬😬😬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PabloFMarino Y si ves la jugada bien Pablo hay una falta de Varane antes de la supuesta falta que nunca lo tocan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nfrostie @moonrakerkih @margarethodge @JoRichardsKent @thetimes Well obviously, because cars are in higher demand… https://t.co/Q2OkBt0TZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdamZagoria Which means there will be a presser next week announcing his hire?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I sure wish I understood their game plan. Lots of talent headed for the doors lately.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EspiOnFire Meet @CynLeitichSmith the author of the book #HeartsUnbound that I recommended to our Sophomore you sen… https://t.co/VDPkFG24W1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ncpatte and @profccassara have been the two biggest influences on the trajectory of my career. Both pushed me not… https://t.co/svQLZBZw4d]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/MnPJ1zD7H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you @oculus and @SeaPubSchools for supporting our efforts to integrate #VR more deeply into education and to… https://t.co/QhvhpOZti6]]></document><document><![CDATA[How much I miss my best friends right now. Can’t wait for see Travis and Cheyenne soon. It’s been 4 months since their wedding day. 😔]]></document><document><![CDATA[You’re never going to be content and feel better until you understand what it means to live a life that is not about you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going after women is kinda like playing basketball. I prefer the full court press]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JoeyPokeaim It made me appreciate people that nobody else liked. My favorite was Parasect and all the other kids l… https://t.co/DqAsR1MjUi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@klitsy18 @FDLgolfer Only if you take the under https://t.co/gXcNSmUxf1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsbeargrillz @dimmak @imarriedadj Fuck cant wait to hear this live next weekend]]></document></documents></author>