<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Four font faces on your digital adverts is three too many.  Step away from the Photoshop &amp; hire someone...]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar Arrested in 2013 For Trespassing, Booked At Hennepin County Jail https://t.co/OSX0BvmRH6 via @alphanewsmn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight’s @DU_DIHockey was seriously the best Davenport game I have ever seen! Kept me on my toes the entire time,… https://t.co/x5QCMHsoJQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow trying to decide what to use your off days from work for is so difficult when you want to do so much 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Eating so many cookies that your stomach doesn’t feel good shouldn’t be a problem for a 30 year old. But here we are 🤷🏻‍♀️🍪🍪🍪🍪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Matthew669691 @TheBaileyRayne @KarlaKush420 Yes they are heavenly gorgeous all right https://t.co/EwLRVhkrmz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I REALLY want to try one of these!! Hopefully they'll make their way to KS (don't hog them all VA!! 😃)… https://t.co/G3tgmzAXbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@askjillian So sad been in a funk all day today left us way too early RIP]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Nebraska fan outside told Troy he was confused. Troy says he's a walking contradiction. ❤️ My dorky husband.… https://t.co/fbhlT7YUF8]]></document><document><![CDATA[ARIES COME CELEBRATE YOUR BIRTHDAY WITH US MARCH 23, AT THE DORCHESTER BALLROOM .PLEASE SHARE THIS POST AND BRING S… https://t.co/8e9IlHQt5d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chrray_10 @_skylarhughes If it’s the dog that I’ve seen before, he’s in spruce pine. I think it’s Kassie’s sisters, but I’m not sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClockworkHamma @Iluvinspireu @debratankersle1 @Jesus_Luvs_Us @Peeperpea29 @Jimmysimmonds1 @FRISEEMYRIAM… https://t.co/w2YyKtCI3l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks Rep. @AndyDavis_AR 4 raising this issue. Arkansans have worked 2gether 2 increase # of kids eating school br… https://t.co/SxB1Bd0JsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t forget every $ counts! Thanks to @smuckers your donation will be matched! Listen now @981WKDD to learn more a… https://t.co/TEFGEGRtA9]]></document><document><![CDATA[My uncle is introducing his gf to my dad &amp; uncles and one of my uncles goes “soooo as you can see you chose the ugly brother” 💀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oldandslow1961 @JoeTalkShow @therealroseanne @EMPIRE @FOXTV https://t.co/f7p9INddDK]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is how I just chose to come out to my 16 year old cousin https://t.co/uw3lN9SLt5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need to stop drinking coffee, because now I can’t take naps, &amp; that’s when you know you gotta draw the line]]></document><document><![CDATA[These cute little Teddy Bears are among the happiest and busiest learners in the world.]]></document><document><![CDATA[In the course of one day; I had a son excitedly present a speech for a Model Congress tryout, 2 HS sons dine with 3… https://t.co/QcENMBFpdk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattgaetz @MichaelCohen212 “Let’s leave the Cohen family alone” was not your intention earlier until you got a slap on your wrist.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Totally forgot tomorrow is daylight savings....I’m not happy about losing sleep 🛏]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hwivesfanatic @bravotvobsessed Of course not. But Dorit needed to be shown in the correct light. A heartless assho… https://t.co/Nzhd3AahtQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[QUICK COOKER BARBECUE ROOT BEER RIBS. For recipe go to https://t.co/o1pQAI7Rl2 #OhSoGood #thursdayvibes https://t.co/2xg92wd9T1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quieren estar con gente que no quiere estar con ustedes x estsr con gente que no quiere estar con ellos pff jaja.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pier 39 Seals. #throwback #HolidayPhotos #SanFrancisco @ PIER 39 https://t.co/vSpuFKKJND]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wonderwoman2677 @RedTableTalk In the words of your god baby “She messed with a pregnant black woman....HAPPY Black… https://t.co/OCVgZajN1B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all. @justjanders can name every @DISupdates #Daytona500 winner back to the mid 80s...but can’t remember the name… https://t.co/oPaKGmvrY3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlxEtz I wish I could get some “compact support”. Maybe I just need to act more topologically.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesWilcoxKETV @KETV Appreciate your reports! I’m watching another round of plows be sent up the same hill right now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Color correction! Before and after @ Hair Is My Business:Unisex Salon https://t.co/ApF4U4K5oc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lol my mom just called me a puta for changing to go out with my own boyfriend  Never should’ve moved back]]></document><document><![CDATA[being an only child is overly hyped by people with siblings!!!  one day, when my parents pass away, you know who’s… https://t.co/gpZjwQThhf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Celebrating the brave women who changed the world for future generations! Celebrating these three brave women who a… https://t.co/FgulLVdbrt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why does it take me years to learn basic algebra yet when I decide to learn how to crochet it comes naturally]]></document><document><![CDATA[One officer shot in Roxbury, being treated at Boston Medical Center, Expecting an update from @bostonpolice soon… https://t.co/2fhu4TEAuQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MustRead: “Too often people assume that abuse is black and white, that if a woman stays with an abuser she deserve… https://t.co/kjlih8LvFi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickyrobinbaum @fauldsca 2/2 I am a nurse case manager but I don't do direct care on my shifts. I do however do di… https://t.co/o6HY1loqfY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Does anyone else think canceling Monday would be okay? I would like another day to sleep pls &amp; thx. #letscancelmonday #needforsleep]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have definitely increased my sports knowledge while being on maternity leave. During the crazy hours of the night… https://t.co/9MfX9GAi7B]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Home Games at English Field at Union Park❗️  Due to the weather forecast, the #Hokies🦃⚾️ and UNC Greensboro se… https://t.co/s3H7CmK2Lf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@demiikyless That’s a you need Jesus, you already brown. You trynna be the color purple 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is what I do when we bring home the treasures. Sort them in the dining room!  The Marialva Collection   #rva… https://t.co/FmXLo6FTkh]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎤listen to my latest post on IGTV for all the producers and artists out there !🗣I want you to be great. Tag someone… https://t.co/RdMuAeF9Ui]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going to have a shower now to warm up my bones.  Wise wisdom from #MissLilyssigns https://t.co/yxquxJeTr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport Thank you for clarifying this rarely  discussed or corrected fact. Keep it up. We need you.   Even th… https://t.co/1CLxEfCsLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This red table talk sounds way too innocent @khloekardashian - trust me, I’m a lawyer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HERterus @howloften @WildChild69 @Happywife151 @jasonebeling @tdorris @Ishikawa_Sachi @cheomitII @KymberlyPlaydon… https://t.co/QMMHXL369j]]></document><document><![CDATA[U Now have Tyfus, Congratulations your state is dirtier than Mumbai ! Enjoy stepping around human defecating all.ov… https://t.co/u6jjyMm1sS]]></document><document><![CDATA[😨 i remember when you took me to a gay bar for the first time. And I was let down that day meeting a guy that was g… https://t.co/LtF0priyoH]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you followed my previous instagram account you may want to unfollow it. I was hacked and it is now posting porn.… https://t.co/lsa6Kvcj3E]]></document><document><![CDATA[I saw him do a guest talk the first week of my MA, what a way to start my grad career.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Historic 1 bedroom loft just listed for lease in the sleek Rowan building in #DTLA @ Rowan Lofts https://t.co/NvEXGj2mHR]]></document><document><![CDATA[hey look I'm your ex husband driving in the snow https://t.co/suJ0u9bcZb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another delicious meal last night at Mr. B’s Bistro an iconic award winning restaurant in NOLA. #catersource2019… https://t.co/3WwQ8zbXGq]]></document><document><![CDATA[That was a slick drive into work. I hope you made it safely. #NVWX https://t.co/7gYmuxtIvp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary @jwayy @thomas_zuber @ElizabethWisman and all of our terrific IPEDERs. May your contributions to… https://t.co/tLKylZPHXT]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you ask me to block someone I’ll block them but I expect that same energy from you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DDW7369 Good morning. Maga Monkey said you needed help. Glad to help. I hope you have a blessed day.🤗]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wait, Slums of Beverly Hills is from 1998?!! How was that 21 years ago?]]></document><document><![CDATA[that being said i loooooveee when my horoscope drags me, like even the universe knows im being a dumb bitch]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve disagreed w/Sarah Isgur in past (for starters, she’s no Trump fan) but this is unfair. How many Lefties are in… https://t.co/wUluY8frWh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlueIrishAngel @ChicagosFines19 @BlueWalkPoconos @NatPoliceAssoc @NationalSheriff @EmersenLee @realalexve @lt_gray https://t.co/chmadEZ8Nh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put these together this past weekend.  Bought the same clear boxes from Wal-Mart for $5.00... #mirth #tee-hee #grin… https://t.co/9Us4d8H8Lv]]></document><document><![CDATA[In exactly a week, it will hit our 9 year friendaversary! ☺️💕 Might celebrate by going to the gun range 😬 https://t.co/ElQustea5a]]></document><document><![CDATA[#pareidolia #iseefaces #thefacespotter iseefaces @ Salvation Army Family Stores of Chicago https://t.co/Cue8E0MNRB]]></document><document><![CDATA[With the amount of guys I’ve seen that cheat on their girlfriends/wives. I don’t want nor interested in a relationship 🌚]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwaggyCTV So taking money that was suppose to go to charity is acceptable now?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who else is feeling a little groggy this morning? Some strong coffee and a walk outside in the chilly air will wake… https://t.co/c3vRhzdaXA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheEttiBee Squeezing toothpaste on your fingers and smearing it all over your face when you wanted shaving cream i… https://t.co/oi2N3vMfRf]]></document><document><![CDATA[2. Main fandom?! Do I HAVE to pick just one?   - Batman/Harley Quinn - The Office - Friends - Disney (anything)  -… https://t.co/9QxtTtr9kV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brithume @Feisty_FL Don't think he even read it Brit, but his use of a woman that has every right to her beliefs a… https://t.co/MLJwQ4i7Bm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who is this old ass white man and why are y’all always RT’n him? https://t.co/NqqtUcUE0f]]></document><document><![CDATA[The moment you charm some hardass ppl to liking you! https://t.co/dNyG8ruBan]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m fully known and loved by you, you won’t let go no matter what I do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_W_Pearce @Tatakai_no_Kami @dametokillfor @GailSimone Wait, how did that get threaded?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today in #ShelbyCounty #shelbycountyinnovation several students received a presentation from Shelby County’s Deputy… https://t.co/4KLxrZBDvV]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RQyzBUI8rk.  @AOC @RepAOC  You campaigned against rich developers but I guess you are ok with living i… https://t.co/VzpUpIRL0J]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did King Shark  🦈 just become the character from “The Shape of Water”? Because I’m ok with that. #TeamFlash… https://t.co/ml0m3ntzxA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CBSNews #ArrestedDevelopment is rampant in@GOP, starting with developmentally delayed @realDonaldTrump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scooterdavids2 @vince__cowboy Apo scooter I tried with u and u didn’t wanna hang out with me at SouthPark so]]></document><document><![CDATA[Radly stopped by to check out the diverging diamond #actionartsandscience #washingtonpavillion #engineering… https://t.co/4zo3LwYrt9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Erica N. Fomby Erica @Remedy33  What would your picture look like? Creative Ideas https://t.co/EH45q57jQx https://t.co/mb4Wvoh6al]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KailLowry Girl joe  mad you made something of your self his did normal life he the one didnt want be film on show… https://t.co/xUuUVyC8w4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TuckerCarlson I’m disappointed that you defended Warren Jeffs. He did facilitate child rape in the name of Mormoni… https://t.co/1v26VvRwZf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some girls buy make-up online, and others like myself buy hella gym clothes online🤦🏽‍♀️ #WhyAmITheWayThatIAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[I used Shazam to discover Thy Will by Hillary Scott &amp; The Scott Family. https://t.co/uDBeq7gFRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok so Ellen DeGeneres id like you to see my awesome and amazing professional Performance which only took five minut… https://t.co/9FYwaKFsrS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Junior guard Ivy Smith, Jr. @thatguyIvy of Tacoma, Washington is currently leading the SWAC in assists per game, fr… https://t.co/Gs9jhknmTk]]></document><document><![CDATA[OMG! When does season 2 of  The Umbrella Academy come out?  Just finished season 1. @netflix]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friends is a decent ass show. It’s just the fact that white people over hype that fuck out of it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2019: the year adults take over the theatres for alllll the @Disney releases 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[@espinrichard1 @FlatRockSells @METALS2GO @KariEspin @mkenobbie12 @lisamonthie @chinaspring_ffa @MakersEdgeWaco… https://t.co/9GKnc6HUxW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TNev @aliviaraine @KalieghhLynn @DoorBELL___ @BrittneyMW1 @Tyler_Dav7 Alright I’ll take 10 fuck it then count me out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers won't be the same this time around because the fantasy of me being the girl Nick Jonas marries is go… https://t.co/TWKoNIAddl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsideEdition Spike Lee. Uses his 1 time Oscar winning 2 b a Fucking Racist on tv. U can Stick tht Racist Oscar ri… https://t.co/bJCBWTBAcQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This would be nice... 💜  Aries - Healing spiritual and emotional scars from the past is entirely possible now, whic… https://t.co/wO8A1UFSQE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kimberlydemarse Kimberly! So are you! Thank you for your support! Been too long since we’ve hung out. 😘]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great time at @urbanaxes with the ladies! #axethrowing #wethrowingaxesyall @ Urban Axes https://t.co/iRXqiysmnM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_summerlacey it’s wild too bc when I was pregnant my medium told me he was with him lol]]></document></documents></author>