<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It's just a cruder version of what we do in the U.S. Seriously, structurally, what's the difference? So, please, if… https://t.co/tKa526iNpH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markflagmann @NHLFlyers Guess we should act as if it wasn’t a hit to the head last night. Ok]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jason Rahn started the Cowtown Weekend Half Marathon P/B Sprint! https://t.co/g3s3CzY2jx #RUNCOWTOWN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone remember when in elementary and middle school kids would make fun of eachother and call eachother gay and no… https://t.co/yE8DEIlF6l]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TommyHottovy it was a pleasure to meet you today, and thanks for showing me the Brody Bullpen video at the end of the night. #mechanics]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/4PKo29d9gE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@youfunnyb I thought Travis Scott was putting out a new album at first 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[if this single episode of the bachelor has taught me anything.... snitches get stitches so mind ur own]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @mg1928 Why are you wasting your breathe? @AOC @RepAOC continues to prove, time after time, after t… https://t.co/GHBSMR4Xg9]]></document><document><![CDATA[30 min no uber as 6 da manha eh chato mas n posso reclama pq tem gnt que pega 2hrs em busao as 4 da manha]]></document><document><![CDATA[Goes to CVS to buy 1 item  Gets a receipt back that’s 17,482 feet long   🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews 🤦  How can a supposedly educated adult come out with this stupidly??😠😠😠😠]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjbowles4 @QmagaMike @farmersteve9 @IMISTHEBOWLBROS @currie14_kelly @mikebwonder @jcvasquez52 @formulalol… https://t.co/N8CyS1wyjP]]></document><document><![CDATA[#cryptominer predicts #bitcoin could reach  $740,000. No you didn't misread the prediction. #crypto #cryptocurrency… https://t.co/xKAf98lEkQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@AnaCabrera and I discussed what the FY2020 budget request should include if @POTUS was focused on policy vs. poli… https://t.co/yMKaD5DCHJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When your gf wakes up drunk and wants water but you pour her a mimosa instead #Winning]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paulacblades001 @delete152737 @Katyhul31495453 @Livid2point0 Your not very smart, are you?]]></document><document><![CDATA[So effin smooth and tasty - Drinking a Milk Stout Nitro by @LeftHandBrewing at @craftgrowler  — https://t.co/8UXWnkvCMs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AbundanceAdam @USGA Let’s say 3 players in a group. Player 1 wants pin in always, player 2 wants pin out always, p… https://t.co/WWD191bn3C]]></document><document><![CDATA[@144Fulton I understand not wanting to waste, but this is just nasty. @ChickfilA #SaveOurSauces 🤢 https://t.co/4Ttrz4btLC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@graffitiwriter1 @EdKrassen @realDonaldTrump Paid butt pirates getting it on while on their way to get thier allowance from SOROS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lust never fulfilled in marriage with your spouse will destroy your marriage.   https://t.co/X9l5rONcDt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cmparker999 Gotta hey back over there Charlie they’re FALLING apart without ya 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kirkycheep Probably not very helpful, but I’d like to see whatever you would like to post. Your songs are that good!]]></document><document><![CDATA[If Trump is successful defending his national emergency declaration, I wonder if he could declare Maxine Waters a n… https://t.co/bcoAjGButK]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% agree,The entire GOP could take a few lesson! That’s why we voted him in... doesn’t want to swim in the swamp… https://t.co/P6B8JnMhBE]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's Friday, if that direct deposit alert doesn't get your get your dick at least a little hard idk what will.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Mmmmmmmm, I miss my kids being young for only one reason: Goldfish.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brandondarby That's why every person and vehicle has to be inspected to verify status, as well as our safety!]]></document><document><![CDATA[California High-Speed Rail's Future in Question :  https://t.co/jzegIJFMWK]]></document><document><![CDATA[ICYMI my conversation with @therealmikekb talking #Sixers #joelembiid #nba #HereTheyCome  https://t.co/N2p6D1KtMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@czabe @scottlinn980 @czabe @stevesolomon was that Tess on the broadcast call for the game???]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BShieldsWFTV Very nice bro moment there from @JHolmesWFTV tears of joy. Good morning 🌞. It's 55 now in Cocoa. 56 e… https://t.co/5jdpbFpitU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beltrandelrio Feliz fin de semana ya es viernes Social y batanero pásala y que tu audiencia la pase de lo mejor ! 👍👍👍👍👋👋💯💯💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyleesdk Haha I have at least a year or more before I can really start looking. I just went into the home loan cen… https://t.co/lFKO5aflDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[Colorado National Monument, Grand Junction #coloradonationalmonument #grandjunction #coloradoriver #nature… https://t.co/ibNzRlXgO7]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I am denied (We can stop right there.) admission to the University of Arkansas,  neither @JoeSteinmetz  or the b… https://t.co/FY9ibCKSMq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@julia_janee I got bear. Definitely too young for booboo and blue though. Wasn’t old enough to have that impact]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fabrizio6666 @jcsosazpurua @jguaido Pero es que la propuesta sugiere que ante una operación de la DEA las FANB o u… https://t.co/4jj8ADAKn5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtm8683 Certainly. Wasn’t expecting a response at all, just musing but I think its likely to show just that.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChiSportsHomer @Harlan @KamVTV Dude, I’m still trying to figure that out. And I know several career students.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please POTUS end all entries into our Republic especially the southern borders.There are more inva… https://t.co/ySqqR4hRz7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Photo credit to Belcher Images.....  @LadyPackHoops #StateBound https://t.co/skoP7g1Ob2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lutzie25 That's not an unpopular opinion. I think most of Marina's pairings were gross after Ben died.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nytimes @maggieNYT Just an idiot. Along with AOC. They are assuring Trump’s re-election.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great time today at Furman’s spring game with the brothers. Thank you @FUCoachHendrix and @gwquarles for the… https://t.co/SByObY4902]]></document><document><![CDATA[@arthur_affect It's one of the best "comics, everybody!" examples out there.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@treasonstickers @realDonaldTrump Really?? Cause I got news for you. Your boy Obama. Well hes fighting for his life… https://t.co/tzTFIWFW1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why did Mother Nature wait until the end of winter to finally snow. I’m not here for it]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Smollett story.  How often has the apple/banana media knowingly promoted frauds like this?  It's an important question.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#nahss Valley hanging on to 40-36 lead over South with 4:25 left. Panthers have 11 2nd-half turnovers]]></document><document><![CDATA[He’s just raising awareness for Amazon’s transfer to NY that AOC set up which will bring the liberal state back to… https://t.co/HeRTzV0Slv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JesseRodriguez @Morning_Joe @aaronschock Just make sure someone finally nails him down on where he stands on the D… https://t.co/Fs8h3wVwdG]]></document><document><![CDATA[First two meals of @HelloFresh are spectacular.  Unfortunately, we're short a poblano for the other one, so we have… https://t.co/2MuYxU1MJz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Slate Well @realDonaldTrump SAYS he’s sooooooo smart! And knows more about most any subject “than anyone in the wo… https://t.co/uMQ0MCRsoQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me thinking: Did I beat the meat for tonight already?... Hmm better do it again just to be sure.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It's game day for the Tigers!!! Come out and show @rcc_athletics rccmensbasketball some support at tonight's game… https://t.co/phAfVbVaCq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got snow in the great NW and people think the world is coming to an end! Most snow since 1945. https://t.co/Jq1hlof5U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[No I do not mind the sun shining in my face! Glad to see it and FEEL it!!! Even if it’s only 35 outside ! https://t.co/k6nwG3rV6D]]></document><document><![CDATA[#BoneThugsNharmony #TheForum @theforum bonethugsnharmony_ bonethugsnharmonyfc6 #CapNP #BLG #BigLittleGuy #PaulMims… https://t.co/G3nT8oTBd2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRevvJR @BillLatin @RyanMc23 @FFHitman @jasonffl @andyholloway For me it's B and not that close.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Best team Beilein has ever had and they still wet the bed in East Lansing. I can’t get over... absolute trash.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the retweet! Keep killing it inside and outside of the octagon man!🍻🇮🇪 @TheNotoriousMMA https://t.co/SWQ2u1Pu1Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bad habits are hard to break but so are good habits. "We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then is not an act,… https://t.co/WQ9nCQnHem]]></document><document><![CDATA[@socflyny At least, with this revelation of Dershowitz propensity to predatory behavior, we can understand his attraction to Trump.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Go Girl! Thank you for this encouraging video, keep inspiring others! 🙏🙌❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[YO!!! Degrassi!! @Drake 😠Change your vest, the color doesn't suit. Aubrey Auburn color is your more your type...pay… https://t.co/DC7GveFQub]]></document><document><![CDATA[That Magee guy from Wofford takes some terrible shots. Does he normally make these?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jenny_backstrom Butter and Rolls from @texasroadhouse are the 💣 💥 https://t.co/QqXG23hXH8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PapaBeez @TheCoachesPick St Patrick’s Day without the fear of snow https://t.co/Bl4CPApcZ9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local down syndrome organization members become superheroes  https://t.co/60CLE174nT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be the most open and honest assessment of the city of #Chicago and #DaleyForMayor  https://t.co/uHZF3qH0yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[You ever do push ups and ab workouts and then your arms just go numb like every inch of movement is restricted after]]></document><document><![CDATA[#NLAHoops is partnering with Coaches vs. Cancer for a great cause Tomorrow, March 1st in our game vs. St. Paul Acad… https://t.co/dkcRAA1tGD]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0MbkxQgcwx.   Excited about heading to @AFHS_Baseball for the inaugural NCHSAA tarp slide competition… https://t.co/EpL42Lp1yz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@auntiekar @MsAvaArmstrong @MrEarpLA Voter fraud will be a real problem as long as it’s mostly dems counting. We ne… https://t.co/htf5cEu0U8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations on the new business venture @KVN_03 https://t.co/8emR6Qe1HT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KETV @Calikrystal86 Oops your gonna die... stupid is as stupid does!! Why waste money one reviving these people?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fabric of football // #fabricoffootball #football #soccer #shirts #kits #jerseys #classicfootballshirts… https://t.co/wimnLKuK7G]]></document><document><![CDATA[Temple stil has plenty of work to do as @JoeJulesinq explains.   https://t.co/04uynVYWP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OOHH_GOD @DownToDunk Liking this for the hashtag hahaha. I feel ya Brodie]]></document><document><![CDATA[BeInCrypto: #Square Reports Record-Breaking $52 Million in #Bitcoin (BTC) Sales on Its #CashApp in Q4 2018.… https://t.co/eFzi5GGa5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mtracey Regime change doesn't necessarily mean American military intervention. Right now he's using economic and d… https://t.co/wzP2jZleYW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chinridge Congratulations and well deserved. Your family has also worked tirelessly to promote the seed industry. #greatrespect]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenoBonnalie Why didnt you just hit them upside the head with something in the 1st place]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh and the plane we were changed to has mechanical issues and we are now delayed an hour. Thanks @united 🙄 Who chan… https://t.co/fkm9NyURC5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffdduffy As the saying goes, "You miss 100 percent of the shots you don't take."]]></document><document><![CDATA[As we wish Dr Seuss a happy birthday on this #ReadAcrossAmerica day, let’s not forget all the dads out there. I fee… https://t.co/lihwHibnkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The @christianaudio free audiobook download for March is "Absolute Surrender" by Andrew Murray. “This book, simple… https://t.co/lmN0qkZaBd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenzoBrains @koaleszenz @JeremyDBoreing Bartender raises up an interesting point because there are almost no repre… https://t.co/kdWM2QeERg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gouxforever @howiemationg @joeyrkaufman Watch a big ten crowd then watch this. Tough contrast]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LesBowen Yeah Tate gone but Les can Birds pay Agholor 9 with also paying DJax 9?  Nelly might be gone too ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_erik7 @SportsTalkBarry @SportsCenter The plumber Gallinari king of LA. Leading his clippers to better record than LeBroomed]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing Jon Snow in the throne has implications. Or am I reading too much into a TV ad?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gold Rush..When the sluice box gets clogged and they say all gold has been washed away...Why don't they put the mat… https://t.co/G4rjHemGZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaleLeprechaun @x8Finity I’ve never played any of the older DOOM games. I’ve only played the reboot.]]></document><document><![CDATA[AOC ANSWERS CASTING CALL TO RUN 4 CONGRESS! https://t.co/3aptDscdcR via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxcarolinanews  Lauren forgot to tell me good morning on her Facebook post]]></document><document><![CDATA[@damienisdeadd When she tweet anything basketball related https://t.co/QpS65XmK2R]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes there is Copenhagen stains on my my pillow! And I sleep like a baby...]]></document></documents></author>