<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Don’t waste your $ on the improved recipe @Butterfinger. It’s horrible. Why do companies do this? Change a proven recipe. SMH.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can we please have @RealKurtAngle vs @WWEGable before (or at) #Wrestlemania?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EdKrassen How about giving him a No Bail Prize? https://t.co/3LXG2iUAyc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AndyPallotta Gives welcoming remarks at Committee of 100. @CarlDKorn @nysut https://t.co/NRTfewv3Dg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hay que ser realistas s la economía no se le engaña, sólo a chairos y ciegos. 🤓]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oye master @AristemoFans que te parece si hacemos TT a la frase ESQUITE ARISTEMO ? 🤔😜, en algunos de los días que q… https://t.co/LxvOmH7OU2]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Sixers need a random bouncy big to pair with Simmons when Embiid isn't in the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Real self esteem is getting asked for your Spotify three days into having one and not knowing you can have followers]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Tb to the fall 2015 SJU open house with @DjZeke #tbt #thorothursday #absoseasonyadiggg #wepurttt @ St. John's Univ… https://t.co/jWB2ZJZ1R4]]></document><document><![CDATA[MUY PRONTO VIENE ALGO GRANDE,  ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/33vM9Icv63]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great Win for @HailieDeegan in Vegas.  Fans at @ACSupdates can meet her, along with @KyleLarsonRacin, @ClintBowyer,… https://t.co/KGiquURUIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kramer_74 Yeah. I was going to take the kids today but we would’ve got home to late.]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is all bollox. Britain’s flock to america on holiday and love the food, especially the bbq meats. If this is t… https://t.co/UySxAQfCa6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LegendaryEnergy I haven’t gotten a YouTube notification from your page in about 3 weeks and notifications is on too]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCSCeltics @LiamWBZ @AAANe_MAnews Brad needs to kick ass and take some names!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Toronto hoy cumple 185 años. A pesar del clima gélido la mayor parte del año, esta ciudad me recibe a diario con ca… https://t.co/L0SIG5Ojzv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do I have 6ft fence around my house for security privacy peace of mind!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why are the leaders of the democratic becoming DIM-O-RATs? Omar repeated her support of BDS and you do nothing. The… https://t.co/d2rjCF81uE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UN4Indigenous @UNHumanRights @Europarl_ES @CasaReal @EP_President @FedericaMog @IntlCrimCourt @TAMARA_SUJU… https://t.co/SSpjMqKq31]]></document><document><![CDATA[Teen Wolf   You just dont understand how ridiculously happy this makes me. #laughter #chuckle #smirk #merry https://t.co/XqxCy7uSF1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepAdamSchiff If you want to know TRUMP followers they are on TV tune in to Shameless on Showtime. They represent Trump Followers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jessefullen @PokerNews @ChadAHolloway @JamieKerstetter @TheCSOP 2012 Library baby!!! Cheers!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatStrathman @BohnyardJ I’m going to have a really hard time deciding on what to listen to at about 8:15 on the way back from Emporia.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@garthbrooks - G, so excited you’re in our backyard!! Welcome to town and have a BLAST!  Lifelong role model, unbel… https://t.co/sYn2wxBw79]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can watch setter highlights all day long. My version of satisfying vids lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Stocking shelves (at @Safeway in Chandler, AZ) https://t.co/DxHB6uOdiw https://t.co/9UFBJeVpOh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sparks flying and the welder singing. Winter projects starting to come together. #renegadeiii finally just about co… https://t.co/7qG2UcAqFt]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you can’t love the one you want, love the one the loves you. Happy Valentines Day.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris We have quite a lot of National Holidays already. Our kids are already out of school to much. #ThinkItThrough!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GZCharge Mercy is my favorite hero. But really any support! Support main for life!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Are you who you have been looking for? - https://t.co/PMI3FPbrNX - #KeepWalking]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Talkmaster Just happened again! Hey @NASCAR this is stupid racing! You wonder why nobody watches anymore!]]></document><document><![CDATA[This could be the beginning of the end for Facebook’s social network https://t.co/PqPv3fIeZw? via @Recode This is w… https://t.co/8a0KRdDSqq]]></document><document><![CDATA[We are excited to partner with @PlayhouseHamOnt to do a TICKET GIVEAWAY!!! To be entered into a draw to win two tic… https://t.co/bml0FyRvW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thursday February 21 - Examiner Today:    Putin announces mysterious laser weapon will go ‘on standby alert’;    Tu… https://t.co/HHaflermPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[anyway, here's a selfie I took yesterday cause my bathroom has A+ lighting https://t.co/gOsK8ITYqd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BennyNguyen_0 working hard this morning at 5am. Creating space. https://t.co/Ylpij8Gciu]]></document><document><![CDATA[What changes do you think the field of medicine and research need to make to have an environment where women can ha… https://t.co/LLlajPQ1kc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BlandineP84 @livuniAgeing @LivUni Congrats Blandine !!! Well deserved!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rivs_Fans I gotta head out again 😞 but I’ll have Twitter on. Bring @Riveters home a winner!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place Song Spotlight  Featured Songs for February 19, 2019  Hippie Death Cult - Sactimonious https://t.co/p7C5G9Fdqm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@247Sports No matter what’s done to these COACHES in this latest scandal, I still don’t think it’s no worse than what UNC did.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imma fuck the shit outta sound cloud, marry that bitch Apple Music and kill that mf Spotify]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jjpatt92 @JohnAnzo Wednesday. Effective? You mean when she chose to question the clown Cohen over her other commit… https://t.co/PX1UUxFRpp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bwahahaha! @TheRickWilson owned you! The snowflake has melted....🤪🤭😂✌🏻🇺🇲🖕🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jacobsartorius I do. Loved the millennial test and "hooked on a feeling".]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our 1st Team at CVFC will start their quest for the Adult State Cup repeat this Saturday 2/16.....CVFC Dos will sta… https://t.co/cb0PIjYXsZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vanessadantes1 @GretaThunberg @lillyspickup Bad, but, climate change is gonna get you first]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why I laugh when people compare their STRUGGLE comes close to what it is to black in this country @ Philadelphia, P… https://t.co/27J6NfOBmg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BillRei31970767 @pateng2bourque @GNSensay @EricMCornelius When people stop driving gasoline/diesel powered cars to… https://t.co/8OJPIUqXXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey  man  if if you are an older gentleman or getting on in years or just have an issue with your erections your en… https://t.co/bYVCNRJmkc]]></document><document><![CDATA[ماني على شوفك وله وشفقان وماني على وصلك اطلب زيادة  أن كنت صاحي..عادة ابليس سهران وأن كنت نايم .. نومة الظالم عبادة… https://t.co/hheElxLdix]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it’s hard to get people to tap in with you on this platform at first. But you gotta keep interacting and gai… https://t.co/9BF2uSdb7W]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Epic4050 #first - Drinking a Spotted Cow (2018) by @newglarusbeer at @delta  — https://t.co/9KYK3xDXqx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Carterdsc @MOregonRA @TR0771N @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/24CoXy7MNN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, Ann isn’t wrong. The wall isn’t get built with a “national emergency.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ringer @RileyMcAtee “Will Starks rise from the dead and fight for the Night King?” https://t.co/9heKXF9Yei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doing research for things that will come fall off 2019 #Lunchtime  #MakingMoves]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StDomsAthletics and @LHSBlueDevils  hit the ice for warmups #mesports #VarsityMaine https://t.co/nIpbLfAMZe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Party Bus VIP Party Club Tour for all y'all 3 Clubs 1 Night On Party Bus with Free drinks Going to Hexx Lounge, Tao… https://t.co/XDOJPJrnj9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@all_eyezonmi @Lo_Gannicus @BertJ4411 @joanne48640679 @FREETOMMY8 @CoachforPOTUS @dgvreiman @Hybrid1979… https://t.co/EY4AmSmha3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ColBannister @60Minutes 😂😂you thought I thought the person being interviewed was the president and then called me… https://t.co/pqfWb8WDVu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Boicot a la comida China!   Domingo 6.00 AM ET/ 3.00 AM PT  A levantarse!   SPAL Fiorentina x @ESPNDRadio  Real Mad… https://t.co/6Jm7jfOcHw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stufromoz Just read it’s only Manhattan. All other NY destinations are metered. And I don’t like meters.]]></document><document><![CDATA[STOP LETTING DRS MAKE YOU BELIEVE YOU ARE BROKEN https://t.co/nuWPyz1Hbe]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinbiba I guess before trump people this stupid didn’t get jobs of any power. Every day is a new low in the trump Admin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanSawyersVA @Bigbadchef Looks awesome! This means you 1) have to play baseball this spring, and 2) bring a bottle to a game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FredKatz Ha ha, yeah, totally. It would be weird if anyone thought about that kind of thing during their spare tim… https://t.co/am0iNQBZRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke @RealJamesWoods @RedNationRising @BreitbartNews @johncardillo @JoeTalkShow @chicksonright Most of th… https://t.co/Vy3l4nY17b]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you don't find this farcical there's something wrong with you. 25 creative ways to get asked to prom or homecomi… https://t.co/9lyBCw8gZu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy boy at dog beach  . . . . Edited with lightroom  . . Taken with @canonusaimaging 7D Mark II . . . . . . . . .… https://t.co/36cmuqt7Pp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RiskAndChips @Homologo_oro Fuck off this is the most overkill system and every 6 months it gets 2x more ridiculous]]></document><document><![CDATA[@6TallMidgets @Timcast Wonder how much public services a Amazon HQ worth of people and infrastructure use up?  Prob… https://t.co/SJkN82dQu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[This morning’s been tough... emotionally drained, one of those days where it just seems like I’m just dragging around thinking too much :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Steelers organization is a such a dysfunctional group and so entertaining 😅😂😂😂😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn it must suck being short, looking all dumb not being to reach anything. Like how’s the weather down there?? Ha… https://t.co/to4gufLUbH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AxlSalazar2 @truckin_760 @adriannnn_10 Nigga you know wassup with my hand so don’t try to act like you dont, my as… https://t.co/U6J4VlFcE0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mike_Buda @RVC_Athletics @MeganMarie842 @angelgrinnall @RVCBowling @rvcgoldeneagles RVC athletics are ready for another naty]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @foxandfriends Good we have Presidents Day so we can remember back to previous Presidents who were qualified for the job.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bedevilme666 @TodKAGWarrior @Janethecrusader @VegasPatriot2 @SchaackKaren @theycallmerazor @BobbyKeithKing1… https://t.co/k1wqXzb8oN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats already know they're not getting no information on President Trump taxes, Smoking mirrors are when a grou… https://t.co/KTS9U5GURL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rmnblm @playnosezone Yeah, last I tried it just gave seemingly random numbers. But it’s been a while so maybe they’ve fixed it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m going to scream like a banshee when this lands in my mailbox!!!!!!! 🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾😩😩😩😩😩😩😩👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾👏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WillsWorldMN Although having a game like this and still winning is important.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracybeanz I wasn’t going to see it anyway, but now I’m SUPER not gonna see it 😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mikebattuello the takes that are variations of "proof there’s at least some validity" to @Kaepernick7 lawsuit are… https://t.co/GdYxYrAnmR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chigrl @Samir_Madani @clayton988 $2.02 in DFW area of Texas.  And some stations have really good tacos!]]></document><document><![CDATA[He lied about everything, everything except when he told the truth that there was no collusion. Sooooo. He’s capabl… https://t.co/Kp93DimrB4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Rosters complete for first women's water polo home game of the new season. It's also the conference opener tomorrow… https://t.co/gtQy1TTOtp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThePoniExpress @ChrisMuellerPGH @ChrisMuellerPGH has made you super lame]]></document><document><![CDATA[Kyle Busch becomes winningest Truck Series driver with Atlanta victory https://t.co/PAfPSwfG9T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheFrozenToes24 One thing we got in common I suppose.... https://t.co/HsUxlaaK5o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Artguyj224 Machete is the closest you’ll get to that if you haven’t seen it. It’s a fun ass cheesy movie starring… https://t.co/HFIifACsO6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@howiemill93 Yes, "...a shadow of its future self." Christianity grew in the shadows and dark underground of Rome a… https://t.co/EflgbBZXJv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Grady_Booch @iyad_elbaghdadi @Frances_Coppola @JackMallers You can hack the Bitcoin blockchain? Impressive!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinesh D'Souza reveals why ALL Americans should be thankful for Christia... https://t.co/1k4SVusTl2 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AmyPeikoff @AOC You're correct that New York's response to #Amazon, which had nothing to do with AOC, was not prog… https://t.co/NGRHLdvC04]]></document><document><![CDATA[Griffin scores her first basket since the 1Q, then Alexa Mustafaj goes off the glass. Deficit down to 11 51-40 OHS https://t.co/x51YZA2ciC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wendybyrdm @jozzzlin @LittleMissLizz The cat facts troll is a troll as old as time... https://t.co/xX52lGYR04]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SonOfNumenor313 @PickleFISH96 @Super_Shanko @ShazyReplicant Thank you! I don’t understand how people don’t get this]]></document></documents></author>