<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[It’s always interesting to me the different things you notice about a game when playing through a second or third t… https://t.co/dPQKtCj73p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MattBevin It seems that the @GOP is extremely cancerous, especially since they support iDJiT and his hate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3959 Wilshire Blvd 3959 Wilshire Blvd, Los Angeles, CA 90010 https://t.co/Wpak7kvQvD]]></document><document><![CDATA[if anyone wants to get me a birthday gift @erwinmcmanus book came out today :)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even if what was said is actually true someone has to get up and pull him away from the situation. Athletes will al… https://t.co/t15C43YDRb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Senator @tedcruz has a plan to build @realdonaldtrump's wall and make El Chapo pay for it... Join the fight to… https://t.co/waLcKf9C86]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wvjoe911 Fucking unapologetic racist.Who keeps handing him a microphone?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@huck_jason @R_Kelley85 @BrockNiner Boom! Lose a hole, you do a keg stand!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Tecnologico de Monterrey Campus Chihuahua in Chihuahua https://t.co/EHcvMNRizO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Skrulls can mimic clothes as well as the face and body. Does this mean Skrulls are always naked?#captainmarvel]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HEISCouncil @csgreggUST Let’s not forget @vmvogel for her never ending support of the Cybersecurity Program and our community...]]></document><document><![CDATA[#trowbackmonday i like this one 📸#summervibes #summer2017 en Mexicali, Baja California https://t.co/VabTAXrs4u]]></document><document><![CDATA[In completely unrelated news I’m about to restart walking dead after I finish these last few episodes.. 👀]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LiaOffLeash @Focusonevil @Evict_Twit_ter @SFPDTenderloin Did you know that 64% of homeless people in SF came to th… https://t.co/6JhV37to5h]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jim_Jordan @RepJerryNadler Piss off Jim - aren’t you supposed to be out raping little boys right now? #VoteBlueNoMatterWho]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rayadas @mCadena_5 @DesMonsivais @danielasoliss20 @TecdeMonterrey Mujeres con valor,, en hora buena,, felicidades vamos Rayadas]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not sad because nobody loves me on Valentine’s Day, I’m sad because nobody loves me any other day either. https://t.co/fSkp2OF915]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oscar in his natural habitat. Dude refuses to leave me alone until I fashion a makeshift bed for him out of my lap.… https://t.co/aLqlDD1lD3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChrissyRoseUp @1TechnoBuddy @SandalsAnew @Rangeneration33 @JMaccabbee @rnlynn1958 @LynnShawProd @UnderdogKitties… https://t.co/6SqYPCI0U9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to watch @ArmyWP_MLax this spring! #BEATnavy! https://t.co/fXQlg77THJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EggyEggmann @seanfaircloth Your comment on females makes sense, but I'm pretty sure our remote ancestors didn't ha… https://t.co/Mqhav4Mnb5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bensh__ Was @septa just trying to placate Montco interests with a “hey, look, we tried. Now support us while we bu… https://t.co/a8BjHdlPiZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JFAM1Zi0Zi    Take a listen for great country music🎶 #Texas #Country #Radio #Artist #Music #Airplay… https://t.co/TbEtiLTci9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@teh_jaybee @MartinHowell71 @MattMorganESQ @BPmattmorgan he will suffer the same fate. LOL👑🌟🎳🤩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Waiting to see where our @littlesenator stands on a 70% increase for gas in his constituents #mngop #mn02 #mngov… https://t.co/BCWlh80Sdi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CMichael7135 @anne_tierney @CharlieDeMar @guypbenson @cbschicago To be fair it’s in their best interest to wait until he’s charged.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realnikhove Very powerful and essential watching. Moving, but also depressing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[asked Davis for support for political prisoners in the USSR, was analogously told "they are all Zionist fascists and opponents of socialism]]></document><document><![CDATA[@atc2448 @itsme_algreen @shakalakasarah They need to test on that dollar hot dog Thursday lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a parody account, right?!? 🤨Nobody can really believes this. I mean besides Bernie and AOC? 🙄Read their def… https://t.co/KA7do8gZ8I]]></document><document><![CDATA[🎉😎🕺 TONIGHT enjoy Nelly LIVE as he headlines @draislv Nightclub ! 😎👍🕺 For ALL VEGAS Nightclub GuestLists, VIP Table… https://t.co/wp61RMGsgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[jessetobyfloressoria #boxing #bkb #boxingtraining #training  #boxingworkout #bareknuckleboxing #nyba #besteva @ Cit… https://t.co/fXpSIfQGMb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TyJamPed Goal was to golf with my brother and have fun... goal achieved 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Dulce De Leche Stout by @schlafly @ Shiloh — https://t.co/bbNH04wcgX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wonderworld2016 @CarlBotha2 @PJMedia_com Oh no there is No Division within @TheDemocrats party....LOL....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SportsCheetah Get on that big screen in front of the world and start propping up Bama and whoever else Clemson wil… https://t.co/FM8ZOrCo8e]]></document><document><![CDATA[Smog and pollution, generally true. We largely dealt with these in the 20th century.  Greenhouse gases, not a lot o… https://t.co/hjSbcZn7OX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kylehuckins @Iamdevinnsmart @53kalevasJanice That leap of a conclusion wouldn't happen if those 5 young men were w… https://t.co/jFmWNMm7n7]]></document><document><![CDATA[my bitch don’t even like benihana but gon say let’s go today... all the bitch gon do is get some chicken. we can go… https://t.co/2oeYKdZJrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Maybe, but it won’t hurt to have one of the best tight ends in history coaching him up, will it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WhiteHouse Dear Madam Press Secretary, It's not a national emergency. It  won't be solved with a wall. Use border… https://t.co/7l9arnpZC3]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s a brisk but beautiful morning. Let’s make it a great one! @ Greenwood Christian Church https://t.co/6MF5a91sH3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Democrats Bash Trump for Defunding Planned Parenthood But the Abortion Biz Funds Their Campaigns https://t.co/WIBImYxai9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mi Presidente se llama @jguaido y orgullosanente soy Venezolano pero hoy quiero felicitar en su dia al Presidente d… https://t.co/Fw8dxW4Tzo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MImperatoWESH It's 16 in Cleveland with a wind chill of 8. I think you guys can handle it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[2nd system coming through.. latest radar update for central and eastern Ontario #brighton #quinte #ytr #trenton… https://t.co/owxSv5ff60]]></document><document><![CDATA[@YungChoclateBar im looking back at this and i realized they skipped several years wtf   and 2013 was that fuckin y… https://t.co/TwKJgeCCi2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Send news and information about business journalism for Talking Biz News to croush@email.unc.edu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaihenH Esas 🐀🐀🐀🐀🐀son las primeras q corren xq no van a querer pasar el resto de sus puercas vidas en prision]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Cosmic Void by @Hitchhikerbrew @ Duke's Upper Deck — https://t.co/npSNToQPPz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RomeoErin I don’t know what means but I’ll take it as a compliment. Thanks!]]></document><document><![CDATA[this is weak 😭 its CULTURE for me and its not even close. one of my absolute favorite trap albums ever. perfectly s… https://t.co/uitOa7JMSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StanHorton4 @SECNetwork @RichardCrossSTM I agree. Both guys on broadcast were good last night. Not partial to either team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@almaalvarez9 @XochitlGalvez @CRE_Mexico A VER alma DIME CUAL ES LA RAÍZ CUBICA DE 729, SE CREEN MUY CONOCEDORES NO LO SON, SON BURRAS RT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RexintheABQ Goes to the local little league field to argue with teenaged umpires even though he doesn’t have a kid playing in the game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Garcia's Seafood Grille &amp; Fish in Miami, FL https://t.co/eSNNVaZv52]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TFW you go on #twitter in 2019 and #SpiroAgnew is trending... https://t.co/U66n0FzriD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Ask him if he had his uncle killed , maybe you can take him at his word when he says no . Trump won’t take o… https://t.co/Qxmpq3CHUs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heather realized that train was going to Hogwarts and jumped on board #TheBachelor https://t.co/2rl9ZZDOgJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FudoMouth @Lafayette_CO @ArtsLafayette This was just updated with a bilingual instruction sign. https://t.co/ORP88TcsRZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[There is no better feelings than traveling back home to Long Island and seeing an #Isles⁠ ⁠win!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss Alena! @alena_arshinova The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MO… https://t.co/yTBlIXgkWm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrampaClue @NBAMemes Not really considering Bynum fell off the face of the earth . It doesn’t take a rocket scient… https://t.co/Sr5qjWKH0v]]></document><document><![CDATA[#FF @kathrynvarn @sara_dinatale @law_riza @beyondcre @_IanAnderson  @JoneeLewisTV @d1e1a666fd1b418 @BarclayStockett… https://t.co/RlANBbKYMp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kat55072005 nah that’s you. Everything @aoc says is not golden. Anyone who thinks so is just like the people on th… https://t.co/xmVhRjxSgp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Fuck falling in love and starting a family, that shit is boring. Travel the world and run a business.. https://t.co/3duLyLiFr9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrodieNBCS @Athletics Hey Brodie. Not that I’m necessarily a fan delaying one’s debut to elongate club control (i.… https://t.co/CleJ8lOHNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[#rpsp Para la murmuración,la Oración .para la Sed, la ROCA tiene agua de vida,que no desfallezca su corazón,con Dio… https://t.co/rmdNkpLO0e]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 pointers have become such a game changer in high school basketball. Seems like even more recently.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleEvans123 @doglegpar3 That’s beautiful! No way he’s swinging down thru impact.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Frankwalsh82 Son here too...Walsh of FML FPL said he didn’t like it as he thinks Burnley will grind it out.. but I… https://t.co/A9uxuxvg7K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go! Get on and support @HearthBuzz... they’re doing great things in the @PlayHearthstone community! 3pm CST]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, that happened last night. It wasn’t my fault (I don’t think), so @loveandhydrogen is going to let me do this ag… https://t.co/pWB4LLhqOt]]></document><document><![CDATA[What should @LightfootForChi do to win? Here’s @illuminatemics’ take: “If I were running her campaign, I’d worry le… https://t.co/tfA0m9ATwD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nearly 100,000 Ethiopian Jews have moved to Israel under the Law of Return since the 1980s, but their Jewishness ha… https://t.co/cSAhtpdGaZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[KU is not winning or sharing the Big 12 title this season. Tonight is why.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheSun The girl needs a lawyer ad litem and sue the game manufacturer.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mattfunk985 @TReddy13 @Ken_Rosenthal @JeffPassan @Feinsand You realize you said you don’t care but used it as a re… https://t.co/x6GNRRNoyU]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the light is flashing red at an intersection, FUCKING STOP. Almost saw a bad accident today because people are r… https://t.co/MkyvLLSeAt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnTho2200 @RaceJoy So you were able to have automatic updates posted on here? Cool!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I have breaking news to those whom look to gather and be merry this year at the LaSalle County Fair and WildHog Coo… https://t.co/1eAPUd5YzL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven't posted a pic all week but  about to do something so special for girls who know they made me feel so lucky a… https://t.co/QTgZO4fpP6]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UnitedNorthend @FanaticsEnergy @EASPORTSFIFA @USLChampionship @EnergyFC @FunkDiesel @TheGridOKC @OffPitchPodcast https://t.co/gvwhPPF4RE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Father daughter time with @lakeishafesta at @kanebrown concert. @islandmob662 @SportsXMMA @kenthomson87 https://t.co/P4x22FVGps]]></document><document><![CDATA[FUCKING STUPID HOW DO YOU VIEW BY SONGS??? WHEN YOU'RE VIEWING BY SONG YOU CAN JUST HIT SHUFFLE, BUT NOW THERES NO… https://t.co/XF0hoHiDed]]></document><document><![CDATA[this mf doin triple backflips off the nicaraguan yazz and the perkys. it’s official Breezy is an actual super hero,… https://t.co/IfCo353mWJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Are you delusional? Did you totally forget your defense of literal Nazis?! Good people you called… https://t.co/bpaPbgtDdz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeadlineWH @NicolleDWallace This would’ve been “Mission Impossible” from the start… Trump “conspired” w/Russia and… https://t.co/lvg2O9BG2a]]></document><document><![CDATA[Will be on @BobGrozandTom 2pm today talking @Mariners and other good stuff!  @710ESPNSeattle]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Uber schedule ride in advance no ride as I hit cancel shows you found me a driver 24 minutes away which means I wo… https://t.co/sgt1yJMNxw]]></document><document><![CDATA[black folks give Shannon Sharpe a pass but are overly critical of Stephen a Smith when throwing the term coon yes S… https://t.co/4rWTTQ5FlJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I often get asked who I listen to on a daily .. My car stereo stays on #westcoast @dollasignyoungg @officialslim400… https://t.co/k0vQ88BH1s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MarioBirch1 @KaiKai0699 @StefanMolyneux Yeah, I live in Arkansas and I am poor and it's much easier to get a job h… https://t.co/cAWLJMspZA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Sky Kraken by @fremontbrewing @ Meat Up BBQ — https://t.co/zvYEfYn1VG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going Up Ona T U E S D A Y ✌🏽✌🏽 @jamxlive @P3muzic @2kYates therealzells FREE Before 11pm only $2 After @ Zell's Un… https://t.co/4P1CyzfMOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity LEGALLY SOUND is the operative bit there. Not sure it could be expressed any harder.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IGAnansi I’m going to need your official take on this Wade vs Kobe nonsense]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marceelias @MalcolmNance @DanCrenshawTX is a Republican. So what’s the surprise that he lies shamelessly?]]></document><document><![CDATA[18/19 @PaniniAmerica Select NBA just landed and Make It To Mike's to snag yours and be part of the @PaniniPOD chall… https://t.co/c6GsolWJNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNN Graham you have become a very stupid person since McCain passed, your real stupid side shows loud and clear. T… https://t.co/Ai8LBAnYGF]]></document></documents></author>