<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I am #giving $50 to the 1st 10 who complete the #FREE #signup. 🤷‍♀️🤑🙌 $5 credited to your account right away AND I’… https://t.co/y0BD4zFZ1G]]></document><document><![CDATA[@waronwankers @lephumphrey @Evertt_Knowtiss @EWErickson @benshapiro Bot. #INSTABLOCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProfeJuANTONIO  cuando neva en ti iPhone no tiene precio lol #cydia #Jailbreak #12 https://t.co/EdVLLbsB37]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re leaving Disney today and it’s super sad. But one thing I always take away is that Walt made it possible to al… https://t.co/BGJeZfLr7w]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TorontoStar Best Prime Minister in Canadian History! Shame on Harper!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hibillyby Make sure to leave a good review guys if you go, traffic now is great but longterm traffic is much more… https://t.co/nAQ2JDTjEK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretending to be a friendly person when you aren't anymore is really hard.  #ididit #imasurvivor #funnight  #imdrunk #iknowdoesntmakesense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just once I want the dad to be like, “Hey, she’s old enough to be make her own decision. Why are you worried about… https://t.co/FZDaiv3Je2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshleyCooksey2 @Twitter @jcorippo @TaraMartinEDU @mraspinall @MrNunesteach @mradamwelcome @Greg_Moffitt… https://t.co/EVodROAiur]]></document><document><![CDATA[What fun!! Everyone loves a paper chain that links them to fond memories! Now these kiddos will be linked to memori… https://t.co/1knGY0bRuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[From last night... Dad joined us on our walk... #sunset #lightning #draftcross #percheron #horse #farmlife… https://t.co/qSRUNuzQa4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hkvren_ SAME I mostly do bralettes though sports bras can sometimes be a little tight on me at least I might have… https://t.co/LoBTh9BBdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[💖💖💖💖💖💖💖 💖💖💖💖💖💖💖💖 💖💖                         💖💖 💖💖                           💖💖 💖💖                         💖💖 💖💖… https://t.co/05KB1VxD3x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @Elliott_Abrams there is no end in sight to the energetic issue, meanwhile the humanitarian crisis deep… https://t.co/HxWwKCMxUn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Local emergency status granted to speed up Keel Mountain Road improvements https://t.co/MVAOd7X7vG]]></document><document><![CDATA[May this season make you stronger than ever before ✨🙌🏽 For anyone who needs to know that being strong comes in many… https://t.co/dKEN72bnDO]]></document><document><![CDATA[DC Tango Festival has kicked off already! Don´t miss Tango Movie Night and #Milonga del Festival on March 15 as of… https://t.co/tBadFA6Kuj]]></document><document><![CDATA[me, this morning on my way to the muni station. . two weeks ago exactly, i had a bit of a health scare which i shar… https://t.co/3XuO15MDiJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[okay for those of u that catch this tweet ily im deactivating tho https://t.co/jfQYRfUhkp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAbramson @DaveKelley6 No, this is America. Where the economic meltdown across the world didn't lead to jail an… https://t.co/3uEpmETlA7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ashleehawleyxo It sucks bad and we will honor her along with Aj and DM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel ya dude, it’s been a long one. Cheers. @ Humboldt Bay Social Club https://t.co/I0upxWOyUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[#RecomiendoLeer EL CIRINEO, de Juan Sevillano @RoMemoria Una parábola dobre la impostura. Lee sobre la ambición, el… https://t.co/1FAkKnpl5n]]></document><document><![CDATA[There’s this one guy in the military that I know that constantly trashes the US government and saying that America… https://t.co/ukRD8MTYRd]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Disney's Hollywood Studios - @waltdisneyworld in Lake Buena Vista, FL https://t.co/vjrGCIPH7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SGNSV_ @psstricia @zaptrapped @FixesItself @AgentMcNasty @Silvergirl1072 @CatLSiegel @sunterra1014… https://t.co/6WPTi62FzP]]></document><document><![CDATA[so much bullshit happened in a 3 month time frame i stg y’all 😂😭 with the same ass niggas.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Living at the beach and not being able to get off work and go lay out for the day is the worst, I need summer]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a little torn between A Star is Born and Bohemian Rhapsody but the actor who played Freddie definitely deserved the Golden Globe.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Ales For ALS by @CigarCityBeer at @spg — https://t.co/IKceDPepY8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SFdirewolf @emily_ladau Also what about problems with evacuations @adapts_team. We are working to make sure adapts slings are in planes]]></document><document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Captain James Williams has been transferred from a field position to administrative work after 8OYS invest… https://t.co/JYvfawK30w]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latest in the great-grandmother chronicles: She just made sure to show me the new snazzy cup holder on her walker.… https://t.co/CzoHNjVj5C]]></document><document><![CDATA[So my apt key doesn’t ever want to work when it’s cold outside idk why ?? So now I came to annoy my mans while he’s… https://t.co/nylN5HqfPu]]></document><document><![CDATA[That ska reggae and soul #htown @ The Continental Club, Houston, TX https://t.co/PirtsjErRR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_jayne79 I RT and shared Just for Mandel please people we need to get him out of there,please ADOPT/RESCUE/FOSTER/… https://t.co/5OBsCukase]]></document><document><![CDATA[Loads of NJ youth wrestlers competing to be top 8 in the state today and tomorrow. usawnj #compete #babyAC @ CURE I… https://t.co/R2oyeNJL4q]]></document><document><![CDATA[@quickstickblog @FSULacrosse @MCLA Glad we could keep ur predictions 100% ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MoisesLopez47 @Nykkynut @Lisa130f13 @katefamoconnor @JamieRaee14 @Stephan66424700 @simon_jrees @Jenhuston2020… https://t.co/Ua87JNtBW3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Which Justin is your favorite? 😍😍😍 #ManOfTheWoodsTour @ Staples Center https://t.co/8jTInn1Vrm]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇺🇸This Offer Only For U.S.A👌 Get $1000 Visa Gift Card Now!👉 To get a free $1000 click on the below given link and w… https://t.co/2Sgo1MeTP8]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’ll be out at garnersgreenville enjoying this gorgeous day, 11-5! Stop by and see us! @ Garner's Natural Life - P… https://t.co/WjlQIP2CbF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CatSkoor This is the way the Republican Party has become. Vilify and bully. They claim to be the party of Lincoln,… https://t.co/ehXL2QCkQz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ken60384904 How do you think there would be a flea infestation in the area? People are homeless and living on the… https://t.co/u58XXh0EAI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_TonyGennaro_ @crittykillz @nlaurenm @Lj_era8 But I swear if you take LJ from me again in fantasy we’ll have words 🤬]]></document><document><![CDATA[@davidmweissman The name calling is what makes them so lame. You can’t get a point across legitimately when you name call.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good luck 🍀 in Dubai Fed!! ROGER FEDERER gets underway at the Dubai Tennis Championships today as he looks to secur… https://t.co/LYKzKnfIE9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Only 2 weeks into prep and seeing shifts in weight distribution and definition. This last week was super challengin… https://t.co/qwVTUzCORG]]></document><document><![CDATA[i hope you know that you are and always will be, the downright best thing that’s ever happened to me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TinaC99543925 @asap_rickey One was even on the bed with Michael-come on!  She claimed it was exciting!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[In honor of the new #LionKing movie this year...  I've got a #coffee plan https://t.co/nkmiUUZ8NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending my thoughts and prayers to @LynetteGM, Clarence McElhaney and their family for the tragic loss of their ama… https://t.co/tDhoC8esQf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amirtibon Sad but true. Heck, even blue/white party is being ignored while we watch @dnc protect antisemitics]]></document><document><![CDATA[|Repost 305rod |thexclusivemagazine got nominated for Best Magazine of the Year at the SCM Awards! We don’t do this… https://t.co/GHRkgGm9Xl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FirstTake being a flight attendant we have drug rules so if u live in colorado f.e. where marijuana is allowed and… https://t.co/XMRR0JaRNF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@poetic7000 @Poetic4Life2 @leoparg38 @Sunnydays009 @susanWV309 @sobertj @mrkmrkmoh @DesertPrimrose @SweetDell… https://t.co/m58cgzLYsN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Come sweat it out tomorrow 🔥💪           7 am Inferno Hot Pilates                         9:30 am Bikram method begi… https://t.co/AiNvK7FBVb]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve listened to it over and over several times.... and it hits harder every time. I can literally feel your pain l… https://t.co/zt6ydpCAuz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love sitting at home watching tv while my pups cuddle me , I’m meant to be a dog move forever 💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OSWALDORIOSM @lopezobrador_ Sigue en campaña con selfies y mostrando que es muy sencillo según el.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 5 year old made a hat because the sun was burning his head. #TimHortons #RoadTrip #CanadianToque https://t.co/viNqOMhvd3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Straight up just all bill collectors when is scumbag job everyone's got to make a living but those people must feel… https://t.co/xFIxFCHaDR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Farewell to Luke Perry, part of the cast that inadvertently got me into writing about TV. We're putting on the orig… https://t.co/u52nhd1opW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorgetownISD @CoachDeanEFND What a great choice- great man and great coach!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Enjoy Tatler very much but this is an awful lot of speculation for an unborn child!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_1directioner_ @Harry_Styles #iHeartAwards #BestCoverSong #StillTheOne @Harry_Styles]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Fewer absolute contraindications and more team discussion to develop a strategy.”  I couldn’t ageee more! Having a… https://t.co/DHgeOs3Sxv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I miss coming home, and seeing you waiting for me at the door 💔 https://t.co/uNp8KYWy8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[@83_royce @xjenn123 YOU saying that does NOT make it true.   I do NOT accept that early-stage fetuses are “children… https://t.co/3jw1pwDzjF]]></document><document><![CDATA[“if I go, you go. that’s just how it be 🤷🏻‍♀️” @ Hooks, Texas https://t.co/EzCQn8y7tY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a way to end a great #sunday but a #sundayfunday as I celebrate with my only #brother who turns #50 soon...  I… https://t.co/P90fZltf9G]]></document><document><![CDATA[(and yes, this selfie was an outtake from the author fashion prompt... I’m traveling and don’t have my bookstagram supplies with me 😝)]]></document><document><![CDATA[Behold, this is the joy of his way, and out of the earth shall others grow. https://t.co/FBYH9kCIsU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WWERomanReigns Congratulations! So glad to see you back! We missed you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking forward to a great day of basketball. Cheering on my two best boys and their teammates. @DohertyMemorial at… https://t.co/ZVcWVyEsKY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcome March! ¡Bienvenido Marzo! ☀️ #BienvenidoMarzo #March #WelcomeMarch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erica_suzette Those look good too 😩 I haven’t seen them either but if I find them I’ll let you know sis]]></document><document><![CDATA[A PAC run by AOC’s Chief of Staff, hired her boyfriend as a marketing consultant His staff status is like Schodinger’s cat]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great meeting with Paul from @chrisvanhollen office talking about how #vaccineswork and how impressive it is to sup… https://t.co/jq416mw4CZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t wait for this! We know its for #TS7  It has to be! As with all of your videos, I’m sure it will be 🔥and 🤯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@attorneygeneral @TheJusticeDept @HouseDemocrats @SenateDems @TheDemocrats @HouseGOP @SenateGOP @GOP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning  all. Physical  didn't go as well as expected. But I'll deal with it. Hopevall horse and jocks come ho… https://t.co/FEXuPPEH0H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@united @allisoncook22 @lclemente19 The three of us are on standby for the 5:50....and the 9:30...or we might have… https://t.co/wLM2hY01A2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PirateSmile7 @AutumnHaile @RustonKelly I have since found out that Trista made it for me but you’re not wrong 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whomever made that #ThrowbackThursday playlist @Spotify needs a raise. Best one in a long time 🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would demand an in-depth analysis with SO many angles, @rusty_marks @MandiCardosi must be counting their lucky Ea… https://t.co/pplMPirq1n]]></document><document><![CDATA[A3: Always be willing to step up and help out anyone in need. (Students, teachers, admin, parents, community member… https://t.co/QEIKc2p7na]]></document><document><![CDATA[A girl can dream!!!  #dailyphoto #marchdailyphotos #sunandsand #footprintsinthesand #exploreyourdreams #beach… https://t.co/lVGpnqAngm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vickiep4 @CommonVoices1 @amyacton2 @mhminger @ChiefDanJones Love and prayers of comfort and peace to your family W… https://t.co/whl17nb3az]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dear world, THIS IS NOT BROWN SUGAR.   It is sugar that has a golden hue, but it is not brown sugar. If an establis… https://t.co/bLIZlRUnAY]]></document><document><![CDATA[We had the opportunity to do 2 bathrooms for a RR HD customer!  Great customer service @gemini #RomanoffBath… https://t.co/BYiLryelvu]]></document><document><![CDATA[DDT (Double Dose Tuesday)  Today's Black History Facts. Chisholm carved the path for Waters and many others to get… https://t.co/xhPwj1nvbZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@old_osc @GOP @GOPLeader @senatemajldr @LindseyGrahamSC So tired of all the evil shit going on. Lock them up!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t believe 11 year old me wrote my phone number on a Jonas Brothers tour bus thinking Joe would call me :/]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where did the time go?! Today was the last home @DrakeWBB game. Thanks for carrying us through the season,… https://t.co/q0vsTjr6Gt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChuckCallesto They have now lifted the suspension, but they targeted this girl for no reason. Very disturbing. https://t.co/vE1j6ZbIQk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GenyG9 @ddaeng_team @BTS_twt @Lilygrcia1 @SunnyBangtanRMV @lyzSuga @jess_tutoriales @ArmyRoch @ijikookmin Imagina… https://t.co/SZauDBmez9]]></document><document><![CDATA[“hypothetically what would happen if i fought another staff member?” “oh you’d be fired instantly, yeah.”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Showing the kiddo @theblackpanther for the first time and she is completely entranced. This movie should have won more Oscars.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@yasminv @POTUS obese? Does one need a MD after their name to know that? Does one need 2B a psychiatrist to see thi… https://t.co/UmIFdaRVLl]]></document></documents></author>