<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@ECMcLaughlin But, these well-funded, over-hyped companies create a bottle neck on resources - making it even harde… https://t.co/FqcRxmB0nn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DLoesch To the left it is the equivalent of a cross in an old Dracula movie.  As soon as they see it they go bonkers.]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 NFL Teams Most Likely to Sign Colin Kaepernick https://t.co/hY6muXtnGT. TRAITIOR to America]]></document><document><![CDATA[Playoff Hoops! Howard Boys Lead Catonsville 13 - 10 after 1Q.  #WhiteOut @kylefstackpole https://t.co/vQ9ahFYBzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Teslatunity @Tesla @teslaownersSV Thnx much bro! I’ll be on my laptop shortly. Have a great Saturday!]]></document><document><![CDATA[All set here at New Brunswick! Tune in in about 50 minutes for the #MiddlesexMadness semifinal between… https://t.co/78RjrJ3uOM]]></document><document><![CDATA[3. Incentives for living wage job creation and horticulture training opportunities for previously incarcerated indi… https://t.co/TJFU7PwYM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, Sunday, dawned cold, windy, grey, rainy, stormy. In spite of that smile-sapping vista, it’s  wonderful to ha… https://t.co/RuFMsK0GXj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna sing, in the middle of the storm Louder and louder, you're gonna hear my praises roar Up from the ashes,… https://t.co/6EL6qA8sr2]]></document><document><![CDATA[On Friday, March 1st, the Classic Quiche features the Pittman/Daniels Quartet with vocalist Jr Mack. There are 2 sh… https://t.co/60BwdWBPDI]]></document><document><![CDATA[🔺 enter vortex here 🔺 #biotech innovations @ Lower East Side https://t.co/yyzyouXkOI]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those in my writing world: a post from an author who is actually sharing what she has to do, what it takes, and… https://t.co/gyTDX3T9pm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Scottfromphilly @StonedPhillyFan I really believe that there were many people who saw the daily narrative of demon… https://t.co/vBblKa5QEx]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone: OMG THE JONAS BROTHERS ARE BACK!!!!  Me: https://t.co/ujLEGMG5rS]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well off to another blazing start from 3, let’s start mixing up the line ups and running on fools long range shooti… https://t.co/uxjkXbuixd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chad2623 @NotCodyZeller @SportsCenter They would not be out of the playoff race if bron didn’t get hurt simple ass that]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:37.0°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[The astonished look on my face as billmilluh placed Johnny’s 70’s era @martinguitar D-41 in my hands, and the PERFE… https://t.co/S3DPq3GG1R]]></document><document><![CDATA[SHOW ANNOUNCEMENT! Saturday 3/23 @thehotelcafe (stage 2) get your tickets in advance! (LINK IN BIO)So excited to be… https://t.co/CrIUePjMUa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mojojaxville  Trump was sued for rape by minor girl in a "fixed" Epstein case - Democratic Underground… https://t.co/xx05FrvDCm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracy_forner @GarrisonCarr @lukedunlevy Between Williams Park Nextdoor and Brownsburg Chatter? Very]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MartaMoralesL Adiós Liga, mejor pensar en lo misno de siempre , reconstrucción interminable , ilusionarnos en Octu… https://t.co/ctBjS6U4cj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AristeguiOnline Si no quieren que baje La Luz que no se haga nada solo no anden de llorones por qué CFE fue entreg… https://t.co/YaZhg38bRy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Brownielogic Only a USA hating clown wouldn't support a man so hell bent on fixing America's problems. On amending… https://t.co/IvayGSWjjv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bush_jason @tokenwhitedude @CantankerousCMF @NealjBrown @Schultz975 Frisbee dog? https://t.co/TaxzPD1HvM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Magnus is fired up for the @NWACSports Basketball Tournament to start!  You should be too!  #GoTrojans #EverettWay https://t.co/wX9mss1jWF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I'd rather have a congress full of bartenders, waiters, and other genuine folks that work hard to make it in t… https://t.co/AQyDeGLWI4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luisovich11 @MartinOrozcoAgs NO LE SAQUE PUTO., TENGA LOS PANTALONES PARA AFRONTAR LO QUE SE HAN GANADO A PULSO. E… https://t.co/WzQSkBvt7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[Generally only trusted friends can reveal that spot to you. Be willing to listen! Great point Mark.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EvCoRadio @Babchik high school boys game a couple years ago. Our school board president and his daughter came down… https://t.co/H65Nbxt8mD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coggs_b @mizkris18 @MrYips_fore @PZabroski @punknshine @SB_ShovelSlayer The inability of anybody to consistently m… https://t.co/m0RqP1vohN]]></document><document><![CDATA[How could you cancel the big bad @ThePunisher smh https://t.co/zyvmdLE7RC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ReddHead_13 @MikeZimmersEars @egoltz @lno09281978 @PressRey @stephietweets @chuck_abshagen @Wolfie2424… https://t.co/ajNwo1dpLw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialNBARefs you CANNOT defend the refs in the Blazers vs. WARRIORS GAME.....  SHOCKING]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GabrielGrims @pewenvironment @KmfriResearch Congratulations. https://t.co/ilO5n81MFS]]></document><document><![CDATA[This truly gives meaning to the old adage “a picture is worth a thousand words.” Kudos to artist Jon McNaughton for… https://t.co/eCIpgUSwUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sun Kiss Balayage  -  #sunkissed #makesomeonesmile #salonbenjamin #kingofblonde #besthaircolor #besthair… https://t.co/HIXsyL18sa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JerylBier @AOC They might have said that if there was the ability to realistically model climate systems  in 1969.… https://t.co/f8RQEKrCHA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@50F10ULE une chance que @50F10ULE est la pour flatter mon orgueil démesuré de vomi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This has got to go to the voters to change both the state and US constitutions on voting.  Their law will givenalln… https://t.co/RppZrJLBPW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RSnewsroom I was glad I went! #purplesolutions https://t.co/Wm5l8scYwa]]></document><document><![CDATA[Freedom granted only when it is known beforehand that its effects will be beneficial is not freedom. -… https://t.co/hNnVnxtxga]]></document><document><![CDATA[My fears about improv shows came true tonight when I was brought up on stage to participate. That’s a nervous smile… https://t.co/zArhfxjh1x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Our Rough Rider Cheerleader’s Walk of Champions as we send off our cheerleaders to the OASSA State Cheer Competitio… https://t.co/Xo1AwmjfdH]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: USF right-hander Riley Ornido wins WCC Pitcher of the Week as Diamond Dons head to Texas - San Fra… https://t.co/iuCEsNBbYy]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at U.S. Senate Meeting Rooms in Washington D.C., DC https://t.co/tnnHH6DMNa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@titletownusa73 @Mikehomeseller @WilliamMarquar8 @jeffsnyder72 @ixchelroy @BeverlyWarrren @vivien2112… https://t.co/O4n365g3qP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joelpollak Three incorrect words to describe infanticide--"Reproductive health care." Abortion is none of those three things.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drag Race Reddit makes me laugh so hard, but this tangent about @ArmondRizzoXXX when the initial post has nothing t… https://t.co/oDgbjbjYqa]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was an Honor to have breakfast with U.S. Senator Kamala Harris this morning. #miamidadedems #blackcaucus… https://t.co/c16ExZKlor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricJRacy @RockCrusher2 @timothywjohnson @shannonrwatts Deadliest school shooting was done by handguns. The AR is… https://t.co/CxP0mIhza5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spiritsunrays @Lex_Lutheran Not all believers will be baptized. Under extraordinary circumstances (like death bed… https://t.co/eNDBchG6W3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StockCats Also a good thing the government doesn’t factor in pesky things like food and energy into calculating it]]></document><document><![CDATA[We’re not talking about the Gulf War anymore because it never really ended. I eventually found my way off the stupi… https://t.co/8BxeNYBAQs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheOperaGeek @TheCraftingMuse That don’t have to go to class at 9am due to spring break for MSU😎💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fouroctets @notdan That said, I do believe PIA was recently subpoenaed because of some illegal haxxor, but didn’t… https://t.co/xJunPdWCTg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Pajaropolitico @NicolasMaduro @NewsweekEspanol EL CONGRESO DE USA, YA LE ORDENÓ A LA LOCA DESQUICIADA, QUE PARARA… https://t.co/wVt7AhCiAQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoping everyday for great things and self discovery of what I can be if I push through self doubt and procrastination]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been critical of Rep Omar, but this is hideously bigoted. Islam is a peaceful religion. And it’s a sign of our… https://t.co/SAHhaOe1cc]]></document><document><![CDATA[here's the post facebook says is hate speech.  5% of muslims are bad people.  92% of them voted for hillary clinton… https://t.co/LzcBz6hAVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Now Im days crazy they don’t teach you bout a school they teach you how to do “]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RyanEdw67985004 Why would anybody make fun of Christians? good-hearted people that would give you the shirt off their back]]></document><document><![CDATA[He thinks we care if Michael Cohen goes to prison for longer than 3 years.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“ He needs to learn all Trump supporters are not racist homophobes.” None should be racist or homophobic. What happ… https://t.co/gzUkYNvv8w]]></document><document><![CDATA[At what point will teams just stop doing press conferences after major transactions? It’s been years since I was at… https://t.co/ym0e3zbzgo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@wheredatwifi Nipsey be having you trying to improve your life in so many ways.]]></document><document><![CDATA[👰🏻NEW BRIDAL BLOG POST “Finishing Deborah’s Dress” LINK IN BIO 👉@brooksanncamper . After our final basted fitting, … https://t.co/pQf0C26qJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You can wear short sleeve shirts or tank tops if you want to, bro. There’s no law against bare arms.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@doug987FM I think trading the 1st overall pick for multiple first round picks from the raiders would be a big mist… https://t.co/He4EHbOjBa]]></document><document><![CDATA[NO SE SOFOQUEN QUE LLEGÓ PAPÁ 2020-2024, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en New York, New York https://t.co/yC2mb574dA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Found this little gem. She always looked up to me.… https://t.co/d5T6ZwCftR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Working on a personal family project with the photos I scanned from my grandmother’s house last year documenting my… https://t.co/UcBd9XnAfJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PlayersKlub I got an email and I thought it was my statement so i paid for a qtr and now i lose my old price becau… https://t.co/DkxaTRfEvK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GibsonWrites Gibson seems NOT to have read Martel' book carefully...  detailed and informative and manifestly clear.  Open your thinking...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnMurrayExpos @ezralevant Show me the evidence then... It's not up to Trump to prove he didn't do something, you… https://t.co/aKBLciE4r0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@15Deloreans @okcmeagan @JuliaKirt Gimme DST 24/7 - Consequences be damned.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Anyone in the Boston area wanna go to Lauren daigles concert tonight at 7:30... I have no friends 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since Confederations Cup is done the Gold Cup should be too. Instead, join Copa America and make it every 4 years j… https://t.co/5ERZflCra1]]></document><document><![CDATA[The bats aren't being handled at all, it's just a regularly occurring event being used as a backdrop because come o… https://t.co/0d9zWHGEiV]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’re going to call @IlhanMN an anti-Semite for her Israeli comments that what on earth is @realDonaldTrump?!?!… https://t.co/JFOh5FB8VA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@djphob Ok...literally watching this after reading! 🤣 https://t.co/HyPTodIvgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanielH52093427 @FahAunty @MikeStuchbery_ But he didn't do that, did he? Because he isn't a grown man with self pr… https://t.co/pozs3gK9i9]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might’ve had to act like I wanted to fight him if he had damaged her.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t choose to go to a college and pay $226,000 (LOLLLL) and then complain about your debt afterwards you absolute… https://t.co/KRU6s5Zm8D]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was lucky enough to see this epic snowstorm in Flagstaff. https://t.co/m5JNAXffnX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yes, but don't let the Democrats try anything slick here!😉 Of that 23 billion, 5 billion MUST be used SOLELY for th… https://t.co/f3ZBbBNQX5]]></document><document><![CDATA[The new Power Rangers opening dropped??  I think I’ll wait til Saturday for it. 😄⚡️]]></document><document><![CDATA[#mindfulness @ Chicago O'Hare International Airport https://t.co/tChwRxjrX1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AD_Electrical @yourconnexion @RevereElectric @FranklinEmpire @FrommElectric @VanMeterInc @FrenchGerleman Thank you… https://t.co/7poeD9zT8H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kailah_casillas @CaraMariaMTV @v_cakes @JustJem24 “HoW daRe yOU” y’all are obsessed with Cara and commenting on he… https://t.co/gtfJ59tbQG]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was quoted in The Globe for the #GhostBike I made for Paula Sharaga. Hopefully this will be the last one I have t… https://t.co/xerijNFa1h]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know it didn't show tonight, but I like SE very much, which only added to my disappointment here. I encourage onl… https://t.co/CwNrpMNIGZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuckyLincoln1 ....Are you hiring? Do you need any Terminal Handlers? I can't open the career section on your website.   Thank you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[🕰🚀🕰 Time machine time!!! #HappyValentinesDay In the hallways of romance and #MYSTERY! 🤗 #WBW #WCW 📸 See me &amp;… https://t.co/qJ9W2uqibn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pray for me... our LYFT driver doesn’t know how to get to NRG!!!! This is his only job.... #helpme #rodeohouston @… https://t.co/fTJ0siNkXJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pjrplan @tracyurq I think at some point he’s made it into Spacing now &amp; then. Imagine if he was actually kindly or something.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would also say @StPeteFL during @GPSTPETE is as close to being in European city you can get while in the states i… https://t.co/zOZFy68v9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrewCuse @ExplrUpstate Thanks! I've always liked them since I was a kid too. Going to visit the Tipp Hill light in a couple weeks finally.]]></document><document><![CDATA[So what time and day is everyone going to Rocky point so we can pull up to the oxxo at the same time 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC Overpaid? Seems like you already got yourself in hot water related to funds. Questionable monies to your boyfr… https://t.co/JG8xSF6eJP]]></document></documents></author>