<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you’ve ever been personally victimized by Virginia Tech parking]]></document><document><![CDATA[Then the people began to multiply on the earth, and daughters were born to them. The sons of God saw the beautiful… https://t.co/ly39LyENyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[gooooosh why did my dumbass go and buy myself an iced latte with my lactose intolerant ass self]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PPTeamRafa @XYbazeta @PPTeamItzel10 @polinesiosxlove @PPTeamCamila11 @PPTeamCataSk @PPTeamCarolina_… https://t.co/gV1V0uKRte]]></document><document><![CDATA[@neeks187 Also how are you finding apartments that far out? I feel like any time I look I get told that availabilit… https://t.co/QxV4PRMiCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[If I have any sanity left after this week it will be an absolute miracle]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really think our school boards need to really reconsider taking the recommendation of 1 SW to every 250 students.… https://t.co/mLZWgvgnMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ok. Bring it on. #phdchat #phd #abouttobeadr #phdlife #defensetomorrow https://t.co/NduNNlbVpa]]></document><document><![CDATA[This GIF on the https://t.co/t5uJwaGNVM homepage rn... the moment Mayor Pete Buttigieg was asked if Pence would be… https://t.co/xyDZ74raZw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BrandonBarash Sarah Sanders said that? I wouldn’t knock someone because they’re vegan that’s just plain silly. But… https://t.co/coPcjjk15o]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can’t believe I pinched a nerve in my back again but I’m doing everything to make it go away before my riding lesson tomorrow]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shossy2 @realDonaldTrump we're waiting for your condemnation of this white male terrorist. When is it coming?]]></document><document><![CDATA[My "little" shadow. Chase is only 4 months old and looks nearly full grown! #GermanShepherd @LovingGSDs https://t.co/nCDxhIi66x]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just gotta put on the red lipstick, take a sip of your coffee and handle it! 💋💪🏼 This week I aim to g… https://t.co/DUzb4QAmdV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Reflections on High School State Wrestling - some were winners and NONE were losers. Let GOD keep writing your stor… https://t.co/AN3GBjXN8d]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Shellfloress duhh, we cousins we gotta have each other in mind 25/8 😤💖]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Luke4Tech @bbusa617 @dbongino @seanhannity @TuckerCarlson @MrEarpLA @Jim_Jordan @mattgaetz We should just direct a… https://t.co/EmnrKg26QV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanted to take a photo and tweet that I was about to replay #ffxii again but i apparently had a filter still acti… https://t.co/vNAShLwI4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alvareztany @laurie_azzi @uOttawaEdu @Mrs_T_Cannon @FiorinaBorrello @DanielaARanieri @mme_elghazal @ttgonsalves… https://t.co/MZk7m44hLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kellyg2201 @AbigailHaggerty Thank you so much baby for being my #1 supporter💗I love you so much!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Elvis the Labrador (not to be confused with her namesake, @ElvisandrusSS1 ) would like to announce she is now curre… https://t.co/eKseHzMjeH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just putting out in the universe that we need way more covers of @xtina’s 1999 banger ‘Genie in a Bottle.’ #manifestwhatyouneed]]></document><document><![CDATA[I now have access to a Super Nintendo and I've literally been yelling at my TV (and Donkey Kong Country) since 6am]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dress like a book character day! We’ve got “A Bad Case of the Stripes” in 5th grade! #dresslikeabookcharacter… https://t.co/YFtKRgPBSc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scotontherock5 @AmazingLovelyGM @GeorgeMichael @KathrinLC @etheri A place where love lives.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JinathHyder Me too, so many upcoming zines and other stuff that I want.  😆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JohnsonJags @ADayIn1C @coolcaulfields @Terriyee1 @MeetMissMagee @MrsMcLaughlin13 @schott_mrs @artwithcoacht… https://t.co/NzhH3IbszE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @RepAdamSchiff Money has already been allocated to repair walls along with approved areas for new barrI… https://t.co/SdglR8rjJr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pip_says @lisasavageTC @DestAddict @StromfieldAdvs @travelpantspair @monstervoyage @Sostraveluk @globegrooms… https://t.co/DftlE3TQgm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Millllkyyy Yeah sad. This world is jacked up. Khloe is one to talk. She asked for this, she should have left that… https://t.co/s2qtZ94YMg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Black Cat Myths and Facts (BUSTED) https://t.co/pCvuCAVsYj via @katzenworldblog]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ExeterCouncil Exeter you rock love my new adopted city can’t wait to call it my second home for real]]></document><document><![CDATA[It depends, if it's a criminal case I'm calling Annalise for sure. If it's Financial, I'm calling Harvey.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BabyGo2014 @barbaragetliff @monstervoyage @mywritersnook @ZeeTravelTales @NomadsEmptyNest @NYCREMilton… https://t.co/k6at4AM52x]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RebelScumUSA @fras99 That mad peop look e not think I am so strange for liking Roots/Bluegrass music. I grew up in… https://t.co/GU0EYMY95u]]></document><document><![CDATA[💜this for #motivational #monday  — it’s going to be another #positive #week 🙌🏻🌈 @ Pure Pilates https://t.co/dYb3MYHYAm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spinks_maxine @bccww The ONLY thing that saved me was apple cider vinegar.   My burns were terrible and vinegar wa… https://t.co/RXtWhxeJmM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#myson #autism #specialneeds #iamblessed #familyandfriends #acceptance #thisisourjourney @ Holtsville, New York https://t.co/h1xVQlI0Y8]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a great weekend everyone ! Appreciate what you have.... https://t.co/fZ2qMeBKsA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ReadAcrossAmericaDay with at @ClassDojo! What is your favorite book to read? https://t.co/USHcBz1sbN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PeirsonNews Do you ever sleep?! You’re an AM newser, a PM newser, and everything in between 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this #SupplyChain job in #Madison, GA? Click the link in our bio to see it and more. R… https://t.co/9FTgmJesWC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RileyCookT I retweeted this tweet with a comment that you might not have seen. It is an unsustainable diet for col… https://t.co/wNCMZhSmQA]]></document><document><![CDATA[We must legislate justice. The Lavinia Masters Act seeks to do just that. We are so proud to have bipartisan suppor… https://t.co/Eikx5coPSX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NewTechCoppell @TexasDECA @Sikyra_C_NTHC @SikyraDECA @NTHC_DECA @Coppellisd @CoppellCTE So proud of you!  You did… https://t.co/56hWpDrKiD]]></document><document><![CDATA[This can’t be true. I’ve been told women are being held back by the Patriarchy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jordyn woods full interview #JordynWoods                               https://t.co/CzT1fCZu8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[tomorrow is cancelled on account of i will be supporting @lynelleee during the return of the jonas brothers. if you… https://t.co/bN3V4Wp8Hy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why do people rush in a #crisis 2 make bad decisions?@SoVtCollege is in trouble but delaying a #shutdown 4 a wk isn… https://t.co/tOGTrWjN5R]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually find calling sick in after getting brutally owned pretty relatable]]></document><document><![CDATA[How they breathe is not my problem, is what Aaron Sorkin said when I asked.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Y’all keep saying Kanye was never out of his bag but I’m not letting go “scoop ditty poop” lmao nah , he tryna come back though .]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JazhuStreaming @quill_monger @zaaitir @ReyosB @VioletVampire2 @CarterSteinhoff @eunice_pickett @Kommonsense7 As a… https://t.co/Z5FqgQazWH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fred_guttenberg No wonder my neck hurts so bad throwing these pillows out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to have the summer sun back. God only knows if the bikini body will make a come back 🤰🏼☀️ https://t.co/Z6dkdBDnaL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Missy__562 @moniquelovesvee as painful as it was those were fun ass times]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_adaniss That looks so good can you make that for my sons ? Who are single]]></document><document><![CDATA[But best believe when I break my fast I’ll be having chips. It’s all about balance 🧘🏽‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@inkmaster @DeannaSmith_ink I saw this on #Instagram i thought this is beautiful 🧡🌹🧡]]></document><document><![CDATA[In love with the colors of mmissoni in store now! #mmissoni #missoni @LesleyHern #thewardrobecincinnati… https://t.co/gd52gDACNQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally have the chill station on SiriusXM. My son has it in his car so I got it on my app to play on my Bluetooth… https://t.co/ln68ZvBTJs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OnhellDelgado @DLoesch @greta They have discovered that what is often diagnosed as PTSD is actually brain injury f… https://t.co/gk71AOZDrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[on today’s episode of Overheard at My Office Job:  “i don’t get what’s wrong with killing a cow, cutting it up, coo… https://t.co/ddmIlJzi2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Oh my, but not middle class America? My heart bleeds for you million/billionaires... Luckily I can sti… https://t.co/q6poVGdSXr]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the time! We all contribute.   Everybody needs a Hero and everyone needs an opportunity.  This is one of the be… https://t.co/9LIGzpovLz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not giving a fish credit for swimming !... it’s what you suppose to do !]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @benshapiro White masculine men will not see this movie in theaters. Neither will their wives, girlfri… https://t.co/Q7iAQ2bFTh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CookCountySAO  why contact his legal team to negotiate a REASONABLE surrender? Were his false allegations reasonab… https://t.co/BMhsdcQEN9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sherm and I both have doctors appointments this week so if you need me I’ll be cooking and drinking coffee at home for the next month.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAmLettyB I think it was rinna. She has had it out for lvp since her first season]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh my god I just got back from a YouTube rabbit hole of stand up comedy and SNL sketches. Let me clarify: I was wat… https://t.co/kxKMl5fUPQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Qs now. Mayor: On the police front there’s more work to do... That’s a long overdue debate at the statehouse and I’… https://t.co/OQCdOHKMgc]]></document><document><![CDATA[The commentator really just said how much you can save with Geico after the accident]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am an intelligent @CityofSeattle resident and I still don’t understand “democracy vouchers”.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jackieaina Jackie!! Auntie Jackie listennnnnn 😭😭 https://t.co/Uf9zf0DpSf]]></document><document><![CDATA[The truth is that the Lord’s promise is not primarily that of this world. The values of the Kingdom are not the val… https://t.co/np5mvDQyXn]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wellspringdental #chippedtooth        Thank goodness it was a back molar. I just love Dr Paula Ottaway!… https://t.co/fWCOWocs3X]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustGinaHere1 @Dimitri_B1 @bryonrussell @every1isdying @BernieSanders No.  We knew it would be the train wreck it… https://t.co/XKN2ywuduA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo I’m literally the biggest baby when I’m hungry .. sheesh. Haven’t ate all day that food was smack ☺️😋]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ginn is enjoying the open windows and sunshine today. • • • #dog #dogs #pupper #dogsofig #doggo #dogsofinstagram… https://t.co/FYkNcEHuj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Finally got a chance to meet up with some friends for a car meet ✌🏻  #vdublove #friends @ Sonic Drive-In https://t.co/5bWeSQOT88]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rephangirl4ever Same! I shouldn't since i have to be at work early but oh well]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sky and I have been kinda fighting a lot today and I came home from work and he bought me a whole pizza  💞]]></document><document><![CDATA[The key note speaker is Ed Morales, a lecturer, at the center for the study of Ethnicity and Race from @Columbia Un… https://t.co/yBxIAnoiBr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Mr. &amp; Mrs. Azuara! 3/8/19 https://t.co/VoxZFx2MLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have you started the Journey? Amazon: https://t.co/F5Dgka5KDP  CHILDREN OF STONE 1)Voices in Crystal 2)Going Forth… https://t.co/eweokm6VJn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That feeling when you are the double stuff between two Oreos.  #thirdwheel#foreveralone]]></document><document><![CDATA[M: how do you feel if I wore an Avs hat with my blues gear today?  W: YOURE GONNA WEAR AN AVS HAT WITH YOUR BLUES S… https://t.co/x9ln0hY31P]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oooh my @ItsDarciLynne I am so proud of you. #AGTFinale #agt #AGTChampions]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cuándo veo que se quejan del calor de TGU es en serio,no es ni la mitad de lo que hace acá.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdministrationZ @KaitMarieox @AOC And we should take the word of someone who can't spell the word "and"?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Have a FEEL GOOD day Family!!! Tag somebody that needs to be reminded to embrace the GOOD days!! Love y’all!!… https://t.co/EGDWvD73Gd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SClareBradshaw are these @chaptersindigo comfy socks work appropriate because I don't want to take them off… https://t.co/eo7jjf3UoR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@secjr112 @JoeSilverman7 @Susanperchede @LinklerMatt @BernieSanders I can’t buy deodorant or treat my kid’s cancer,… https://t.co/Z10K7DPNot]]></document><document><![CDATA[This really is scary. I've seriously considered "how bad would it be if I had to run through the tunnel towards jay… https://t.co/l4IP89WDtX]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @5x5Brewing Co. in Mission, TX w/ @badlifechoices https://t.co/cJ4wuCklTl https://t.co/qydEFNJwi0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IAmSophiaNelson Ms. Nelson, I am listening to you on @MichaelSteele 's podcast. I am a liberal. Yours (and, Michae… https://t.co/zkKJEsIRJC]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will always be the one person who gets mosquito bites in the dead of winter. How.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crustless Taco Pie by cr_ketokitchen and salad. Taco night done right! #keto #ketolife #ketoknows #ketodinner @ Sco… https://t.co/cT9Nmmfype]]></document><document><![CDATA[Idk if this is still a thing but the Killer In The Mirror music video says “tell me that I cut throats”]]></document></documents></author>