<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I’m about to take one for the team and get a restraining order on Rednut so he can’t come to the bar anymore]]></document><document><![CDATA[Makin Reali-Tease out of DayDreams! Shout out to everybody out there, still handling all their Dirty Work while bri… https://t.co/wzXfMOJfdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because commie liberalism is their new age religion.  It has supplanted Judea Chritianity as their false idol.  And… https://t.co/AlF8SKm9WQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Agree with pretty much all of this.  The insulated bubble of each side is the gasoline of partisan politics and Twi… https://t.co/aVojqo3kFc]]></document><document><![CDATA[What’s that about history repeating itself? Regulators Move to Ease Post-Crisis Oversight of Wall Street https://t.co/zHZYVtyt8E]]></document><document><![CDATA[Monday night football ⚽️ ⚽️ ⚽️ (@ Ultimate Soccer Arena in Pontiac, MI) https://t.co/EqwSSFQRKf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looks like those Emery balls into the box worked out well in training 👀#Arsenal]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dianaeme @camiloparadag @SantaFe Mi hija pensando en el #oscar2019 y yo en @SantaFe 😜😜 https://t.co/rhqBfi3tev]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t usually do this but it will not be a waste of your time to follow @sarahskkim]]></document><document><![CDATA[Collaborating and learning at the @1819Innovation this morning with our @LovelandTigers team. The @GoBEARCATS early… https://t.co/fyk2T2i5Zd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t opened my Facebook since 2008 but I have to hear this Jordyn shit]]></document><document><![CDATA[The same man who molested her daughter at 12...she still thinks fondly of this guy....how....just...]]></document><document><![CDATA[A rambling 'SNL' cold open can't make sense of Donald Trump's fake national emergency https://t.co/a5dES7yM5C via @mashable]]></document><document><![CDATA[@matthew_arend Is it a day that ends in y? If so...yep!!!! Hahhahaha!! On Wisconsin!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bensh__ Agree on the benefits, but the cost of western extension is much higher than eastern. So they’re not really very comparable.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Two worlds collide. Both wish they could meet the other and live in the moment. https://t.co/kJxyBsVzzF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really excited to announce a full US tour in May with Sarah Longfield! This time my brother Hedras will be join… https://t.co/NuCQ5yQUiM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GregBrozeit @TheeAndyMcGill I think these are the raw results from the article in the Atlantic narrative (survey),… https://t.co/xJ1yDxBvmY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also just to point out, sidewalk safety IS pedestrian safety... if people are walking in the streets to avoid unsho… https://t.co/tjC2oCQj91]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Hawksea24 @SunsNationNBA Just let em have some fun for fucks sake...goddamn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just listed | 651 Brianna Way, Corona CA | LIVE Auction | Live bidding from $449,000 Open house Saturdays 12 - 1pm… https://t.co/1QcEm091z0]]></document><document><![CDATA[When you spend all weekend playing defense and coach leaves you in for the front row and you get the game winning k… https://t.co/QGDpAqrku7]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would say Rabbit Hole, but her monologue in Eyes Wide Shut is a masterpiece in and of itself. Can it be a  two-wa… https://t.co/nSrvoOAZMR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lillypaaad6_ U rite... Its second most expensive concert I've ever paid for.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice victory for the Hall. Next up Big East Tournament in Chicago! @ St. John's University https://t.co/T1E4zPoYFy]]></document><document><![CDATA[#SOSVenezuela El Criminal Régimen de Masburro, ha declarado que necesita ser barrido de la Faz de la Tierra.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días desde Miami les comparto  esta hermosa vista de la bahía en Coconut Grove #miami #inversion… https://t.co/SsOsCRWlxf]]></document><document><![CDATA[#JudicialReview why can't judges on federal appointments be limited to 20 year terms...]]></document><document><![CDATA[I liked basketball so much better when there were one or two charge calls per game; now there are at least ten charging fouls per game.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He says hold on I need to check with our tech so puts me on hold for several minutes. @netflix rep gets back and te… https://t.co/Fr2rg5cAP4]]></document><document><![CDATA[There should be a manufacturer's warranty up till 16 years with full financial reimbursement if defective]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Josh_Sharpe @ssgslack If you can’t figure out how to google an opposing viewpoint from your own, sorry, it’s reall… https://t.co/e5QvZvDkW5]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think I have one of the best jobs ever. Also makes me realize I have taken many things for granted.]]></document><document><![CDATA[5th/6th Grade Boys - Pool A - Cavs Elite 6 def. Memphis Blue Devils by forfeit @exposurebball]]></document><document><![CDATA[Since the trade deadline, Columbus is 1-3-0. Pittsburgh and Montreal each have 77 points and hold the two wild card… https://t.co/OizZnKgcOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[What webcam and mics do you guys use for streaming I was going to go buy a blue yeti and a Logitech webcam today! Lmk what you guys use ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AreaKhodes “This is a political game by the democrats to defame trump” but I’m going to play a political game by n… https://t.co/Y1jKrl0sHT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Destin, Fl.  The sun came out on our final day here.  So we are chilling by the beach.  I tried to simulate my dayd… https://t.co/J7Pype82yl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RobinhoodApp i love free stuff so I decided to text over 200 contacts in my phone to see how many people will make… https://t.co/f0To0VeT2F]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today’s learn - thanks to ppsturge. #greatworkday #ccitteam #dragon @ Delaware https://t.co/72nVQ8AZBc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow that's started this along time ago and found it now I can add more to this.. @ Tolleson, Arizona https://t.co/s6gUxyvJoF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Don’t trust anything anyone promises you. Nobody has your back like yourself and nobody is going to stick through i… https://t.co/1GMxkVtZp5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@goliveros Lo que es molesto en Tampico son los taxis que no dejan de tocar el claxon, por lo demás muy bonita ciudad.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join the Barton Health team! See our latest job opening here: https://t.co/Kb5myRfiR3 #hospitaljobs #Education]]></document><document><![CDATA[I had all this money sitting in my cash app for two months and I just figured out how to transfer it to my bank account. 🤦🏾‍♂️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[me: hey @malfoymores what should I caption this her, an intellectual: uhhh something with “sun” in it https://t.co/Xf4vSADnV5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Excuse me Mr. President Donald Trump if I'm out of line here but I have a question.  Is there actu… https://t.co/meU83WkTyM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You need beer @nmaestas? Say the word, my friend. #LiveTweetThePodcastEpisode72 @ThreeBeersLater]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QAAProphet @MiyaFolick I had tickets, but couldn’t get into the city because of snow. Absolutely killed me. I’m a huge fan of hers. :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sir_scottsman @milivojorlev @DaireFeeney @AnnaSemlyen1 @Alyssa_Milano Rock on . That's actually cool of you to Exp… https://t.co/ORJkQDs2TK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GhotixHook Not if ya got young'uns. Didn't have to clean up for years. Now I'm just waiting on the granyoung'uns to get just a little older]]></document><document><![CDATA[🇷🇺👑👸WOW! BEAUTY QUEEN!👑 Sweetheart!💝 Miss lemurrien The White RACE Russian BLONDES👑🇷🇺Women Are The MOST Beautiful I… https://t.co/rxsWDubeY2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsLioRush has redeemed himself! #Raw #WWE #WWEUniverse #ProWrestling #WWENetwork]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you thought the Steelers were getting a #1 pick for AB you don’t know how the business works. Colbert had no lev… https://t.co/sBEZPKwcCK]]></document><document><![CDATA[We Got It All Contact When Ready To Order Email Us dfinelifestyle05@gmail.com or call/text 914-246-2597 Or What's A… https://t.co/y1kZuPJtO0]]></document><document><![CDATA[DJT was strongly advised NOT to say "when Otto Warmbier's father spoke out about his son, the boy's mother just sto… https://t.co/aPW7YDVLnP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jax_persists @VOLUNTEERS_TN @72infidel @Tactical_review @ZeroLemmings @DrZin14 @Stepheneashia That is a LIE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CallMeDrRage @ssteffieeee @KaceyMusgraves Cut to me raving to “High Horse” in the middle of the desert... https://t.co/1BuUt0NhOx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AJemaineClement @whattheshot What’s Eating Gilbert Grape. That’s Leo on the water tower.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi is playing 3D Chess and understands the risks of an unsuccessful impeachment effort in the Senate due… https://t.co/MWpzsVyo6t]]></document><document><![CDATA[Big s/o to one of our UTS Elite 17u/Bad Boys Alumni (Marcus Gibbs) @MG3______ on having a great season for… https://t.co/pM7gzSuE78]]></document><document><![CDATA[According to my calculations  ━━━━━ ━━ ┃                        ┃ ┃        8008135┃ ┃                        ┃ └━━━… https://t.co/XJtRCmTZFT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trump has a 93% approval rating among Republicans. 71% of ALL Americans do not want anyone to continue investigatin… https://t.co/wyPdy6a4oX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UncleBlueWave @BryanWinsAgain @Bergman14 If he is the nominee and you don’t vote for him in the general you’ll be… https://t.co/FDpU3VkS8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was already against the move. Now that you've put it that way I'm horrified and a little nauseated.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mariaelisasmith 2)La democracia conlleva a una dictadura , cuando 1) Es una democracia relativamente nueva sin muc… https://t.co/0QgSVzN9KE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kwilli1046 It’s called pay it forward! It’s easy and surprisingly rewarding.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elioftheveil Have been there when I get sick in a different climate paired with flights both ways. Drink tons of w… https://t.co/Ju4BBKzG7h]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey, ustedes, par de niños puñetas que se salieron de mi partida de competitivo, váyanse a la verga.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@a_real_life1 Always painful when the mojo runs away.  I always have a tough time deciding - push through without m… https://t.co/fdY42vlInh]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s the “becoming” part I don’t get.  Abusive articling experience has long been a “right of passage” in the legal… https://t.co/yfTUvtJC7O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickjParker99 just dropped a nasty curveball for his second K of the inning]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hello @Twitter @TwitterSupport please have someone contact @RalstonReports so he can be @verified thanks its 3/11/19 already]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jake_burns18 @hiramboyd Charles Barkley said , LeBron is Drama , Nothing has changed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LoneStranger2K @thehalestone Obviously not saying Lonnie = Bowen. Just using the different role part as the analogy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SandraTXAS @CajunGirlMB You said it and I agree! Applause of the world more than love of life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[What are your thoughts on this?Americans Forced To Comply By 2020—No Compliance, No Entry and The Bill ...… https://t.co/iTFhotYgfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @KenTremendous David has a pretty good idea RT @EgosAndDespair: He should use some of that to hire Joe Morgan s… https://t.co/ucJSCZu77B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday • What will you play this weekend? • Me!? I’m gonna work all weekend.. • • • Partners… https://t.co/6HB0YdRRfi]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is going to be awesome. Big things continue to happen down in Auburn. #WDE https://t.co/szikXnBGbg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ImtiazGarcia @sam_vinograd @CNN @OPCW @TulsiGabbard @UN @Reuters And the bodies were staged, with fake foam even.… https://t.co/YClZf1yttX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where does one find friends like this lol , These are the type of friends i need 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EBischoff I’m watching your Documentary on the @WWENetwork, it’s amazing by the way, seeing all backstage pics fro… https://t.co/VsxXb8Bs4D]]></document><document><![CDATA[Landon got $84 million 🤦🏾‍♂️ so that mean Earl go want more.... yeah my Boys not getting Earl.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelcmaronna @RealDeanCain @RubinReport @JoeBiden So you're gonna just lean in on that "idiot" moniker, huh? Feel free.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kawaiisunflower It should be free with the last of us on PS4 when u buy the game]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cle_ItIsGone I never trusted that roller stuff. The theory is make it hurt now on purpose so it might not hurt later.]]></document><document><![CDATA[To hear the chorus of angels, listen with your heart.  Feel their presence? https://t.co/BnExr5Yt19]]></document><document><![CDATA[Notorious drug lord "El Chapo" found guilty on all counts, https://t.co/jy0rcFwvdp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow   I hope Republicans stand with the president it will be a disgrace if they turn coat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @pepper7565 Agreed,  Spike just breaks more racism for the political party that funds him.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thechriswheeler @SeannyDMode12 @iRacing Word on the street is you are now retired as a spotter!]]></document><document><![CDATA[La Vidente Que Me Encanta Ver En 📺 #HoyconMhoni #MhonienHoy #MartesdeMhoni Dia De Ver Hoy @magdaproducer ✨📺🎬🎥… https://t.co/JpQLKdIk0d]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been telling people about this Got Milk ad that I saw as a kid. For reasons about to be explained, it always s… https://t.co/rSxkdtaE6M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had lunch at 11:30am looked back at the clock and it was 4pm. Wish every day could be like that. #Productive]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spring is going to be here soon enough. I'm watching the nighttime temperatures... It's getting near to... PEA PLANTING TIME!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gov. Gavin Newsom calls for tougher enforcement against California’s black market for pot: Before he was elected go… https://t.co/dVmynQhDfR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not talking about the game just the players in general . KD, Lebron , Kyrie etc whine and cry all the time lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Amanda_Balionis @odysseygolf @CallawayGolf @adidasGolf @DiamanteCabo Damn sexy ladies!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would like a rule that would require minimum batters faced like 3. Ending an inning would waive that rule. The ne… https://t.co/8duLFmtBCi]]></document></documents></author>