<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Biggest group of members/students we’ve ever had for #NCANHillDay. So grateful to them for taking the time. Student… https://t.co/Ss8dHV0Rzt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GOLFTEC @CallawayGolf @DnevsCG True story! Just ask my son’s swing coach!   👊🏻💪🏻⛳️💯🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VancityReynolds @ChrisCandy4u @TheRealJenCandy I loved his role in Blues Brothers. #orangewhip]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andy_floress090 O sea me kga que me lo pregunten las personas con más que no hablo mucho 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made a human number line to show the linear/length fraction model #math #fractions @origomath https://t.co/chx7XUQu2O]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Diversity #Equality #Inclusion  @torinellis Time to get real!  Inclusion drives business results.  Let’s go!!… https://t.co/yF5LSNAVCL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mco_xxviii Me too. Right now here it feels like 0F. This is crap for MARCH. Much much colder than normal and I’ve HAD it with winter!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WilliamKliskey @ThisIsVISTA @pollyannanj @grooglesVISTA @ittybittyholly @IAGBooking :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[They really should have faked Gritty getting tased... for old times sake.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marcorubio @realDonaldTrump @SecPompeo please cut the crap! Get this people out! 🙏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[Asking “When’s International Men’s Day” sounds like “When’s National White History Month”... 🤔 just saying]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so off my game. I totally forgot to go to Target after Valentine’s Day for the clearance chocolates and all the… https://t.co/tZqpDPGPR2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Interviewing Courtney Howard today with @SLOCountyPWD to talk about the Central Coast drought conditions and where… https://t.co/LVQJ8PzWyu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just signed up to be a Justice Volunteer! You can join me in doing this important research on the policies and tr… https://t.co/WKq1WdDFQT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sirrockstone TY, Sir Rock! ZORRO's o came 2 get him at #nycacc, and ZORRO is now in an animal hosp🤞🙇‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[What a wonderful montage of saying countries wrong. This is the quality television I came here for. #LastWeekTonight]]></document><document><![CDATA[Third (and final) live game of the (regular) season and we got a WIN! WOOOOOOOOOOOO! Dished out a lot of love to #9… https://t.co/FGQRBaoO6b]]></document><document><![CDATA[@deblethumas @Ronaldfist @Marga2160 Ni idea, Deble. Yo voto y a pesar de que me han gustado algunos republicanos (p… https://t.co/h5dIuvAZx0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cinderella’s castle. 💎 I used to work at Walt Disney World. 💙I was an “attractions hostess”. Which means I repeated… https://t.co/yPsHNAdTGu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ASCD @reshmasaujani @GirlsWhoCode Girl Power ! Coding is awesome. https://t.co/wmJQNG9p4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[huge shoutout to @stanley_alvey for throwing his phone directly at my mouth]]></document><document><![CDATA[a more violent one over time. Thousands of Europeans have gone to fight with the Islamic State (IS) in Iraq and Syr… https://t.co/cT7rMNx0k4]]></document><document><![CDATA[thank you so much Meghan !! I love you so much and am forever thankful for our friendship]]></document><document><![CDATA[We spoke too soon. I think it's a wide open race among UST, FEU, NU, Ateneo and Adamson this season. Parang kahit s… https://t.co/H3WZtYgQMQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iAYoshie what have you been retweeting about this love triangle?! lmfao whose nigga was he first?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just preordered @stassi’s book and I’m too excited but then I realized April 16 is so far away! I’m ready to channe… https://t.co/Gnkdl4LAEE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@andrewhall_14 I’ve also been screaming Rumer Willis since week one and they never guessed her]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The wall is NOT BEING BUILT YET YOU LYING PIECE OF SCUM. STOP YOUR DAMN LIES. THERE ARE IDIOTS WHO BELIEVE THEM.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stassi I love who you've grown into be your freaking hilarious! And honest.. it's a really good look on you sister!😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bigshevmill Girl I swear it’s like homes are grinding together and it always gets locked up randomly 😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karisvalero Jajajaja yo más mana💗 jajaja el jueves me revisan, animooo jajajaja]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soitfuckingoes @mernajajou @IcanBeAPhantom1 @allisongoodlin @karsiaj @NagoyaSwiftie @swlftworld @bflygirl133… https://t.co/vwIRrP2iRr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Harry_Styles. Sorry for the lost of your step dad. I keep you in mine prays Harry. I not going to say it gets easi… https://t.co/hEzsfNAdpw]]></document><document><![CDATA[So grateful with @TolkienTVTalk for mentioning me in their podcast, I’m honored https://t.co/xs2kp5acED]]></document><document><![CDATA[All I want in life. Y’all don’t wanna know how many times I watched it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I ate all the food my heart desired today and let me just say my heart is so happy. &lt;3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@glasgow_bruce @YuliyaInopinaPR @saferprint @BiggiPommerin @HLERadio @KavalonThatsMe @Boondockfinds @PapaPorter1… https://t.co/l1TFIIXzC9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vain4ever @kinshriner @DougDavidsonYR @YandR_CBS Isn’t that John Schneider? #BoDuke]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excited to be representing @SMGTCDSB at the @TCDSB Northern Spirit Games today! https://t.co/TXapM9tHID]]></document><document><![CDATA[@daxtonbrown @Raquel4Detroit @eventbrite @latinorebels @LULAC @BarCrawlLive @Latinos4MediaEq @Latinopress… https://t.co/yDbmUhu5h0]]></document><document><![CDATA[I went to #HLSR and had the best time. That’s all. P.s. pls get the reference https://t.co/7uWDL5pa2k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@paige_tidwell16 Wooooooowwwww they gave me a suuuper long list of all the websites and I got tired of looking each… https://t.co/iFYQapldTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[So I went to Walmart to get some flour cause I can’t get regular flour because of the whole gluten free deal. I go… https://t.co/dp4plal33O]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well this is a bunch of alarmist bullshit written by people who didn’t actually bother to contact food scientists 🙄]]></document><document><![CDATA[And now, here he is, the King of #SundayBunday...the General of the #FlamingoArmy...the one and only @MMasonXXX 💖💖 https://t.co/fnae8uhSOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being fake married is probably the best scam I have ever pulled off 👌🏼 @benschoeller]]></document><document><![CDATA[Never trust a shiny surface. They hide a multitude of flaws. ~Melissa De La Cruz #shiny #favoritecolors #dallas… https://t.co/CqbOaeWRtd]]></document><document><![CDATA[making a list comprised of 75 things to do for your wedding probably wasn’t the best idea when trying to get a good… https://t.co/nRIasb07aO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@shahjayni @amyssorrells @ninaachadjian @StartupGrind What an all star panel!! 🙌🏼🙌🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve never been so excited for a tv show as I am for #RHOBH I literally got chills watching Lisa and Kyle fighting.… https://t.co/cDJpTRcrQ5]]></document><document><![CDATA[This exactly what it feels like when a middle hitter has perfect timing on an a ball]]></document><document><![CDATA[@UCLASemelFriend i also do not have tourettes.  I just also do not have a problem cursing to make a point Im not a… https://t.co/9DM4t0v9wT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Listening to They That Wait Upon The Lord (Live) by Rev. James Moore on @PandoraMusic https://t.co/rLFDgudfUb https://t.co/a9ASpp9iuq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomNovelly @courierjournal @postandcourier Congrats, man! We’ll miss you here.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Destiny29466594 @globalnews @michaeljackson Destiny please reconsider trying to defend a pedophile :(]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kelli_Fields @PFDSullivan @AGirlInPhilly @ConshyBakery @DeniseNakanoTV Tell it like it is!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[That would be Joseph, as in Mary and Joseph – in other words, Jesus’s earthly father figure according to the bible.… https://t.co/W45jV2zXzM]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s that time in the semester where my camera roll is 25 pictures in a row of notes and different things for exams 🥴]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ar00ster @leon1961lee @thehill @IlhanMN You don't trust the govt yet say that she was lawfully elected and expect… https://t.co/MUMANemRbP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Feeling great. I prayed for God to give me an answer for weeks and finally🙏🏾]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Then maybe you should work for the safety of the American people]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope we get the facts don’t want this little one ending up in the wrong hands]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Janet4Justice @Rosie @tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump No collusion found!!!    WINNING!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Friendship Day Parade!  Do you feel all the ❤️?!? @mistral_cec @ElenaBuley @HISDWestArea https://t.co/3uoG9sRlB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MellyG14 Also really express the importance of taking classes from and connecting with professors who share your a… https://t.co/ycMbVDFMDQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[And that is a big Shove your corporate $$ up your ass #nopipeline @DomEnergyVA @RalphNortham @VAGovMansion @vagovernor #saveourtrees]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know those moments when you decide that you don't want anybody around and you're fine by yourself? Yeah I'm hav… https://t.co/oAPa4D3kIf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MsReneeLawless @OWNTV Hello Renee! I’m home tonight for this. #HAHN #WWKCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[My 1st graders are loving all these football players coming to read to them this month for reading month! Huge than… https://t.co/RpOSd9o24S]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fraying Paddleton is worth the time. Brand new on Netflix. I loved it.   https://t.co/WU8qurHrnS  Details: https://t.co/5eEFjTrgrv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenKing Thank you Tabitha King, mother of Molly Thing of Evil, wife of talented Red Sox fan of Maine. My late… https://t.co/bBbhUOEMrM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DennisK9G You guys gotta go! Before last year we saw him like 20 years ago! Just as good this time around if not better!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders How do you answer to those that say you helped Trump win the election along w the Russians ?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happiness is new, much asked for overalls and tiny umbrellas. #matildamaeve #overalls #tinyumbrella #recyclingbin @… https://t.co/EL7y40ethv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tonight's sunset was gorgeous!!   #AvGeek #PilotLife #PilotViews #AirportViews #AirportSunsets https://t.co/R6ezSVnuPd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johnpopham Some of us would prefer waterproof feathers and increased buoyancy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AntonioArellano @MikeOkuda @realDonaldTrump He's such a useless bag of nonsense.]]></document><document><![CDATA[“I’m very much down to earth, just not this earth” Rest Easy you fucking genius! @KarlLagerfeld https://t.co/k1weVSrBNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Tracy143DC @nbcdays He loves J.J and wants to protect him even though he doesn't remember him, but that doesn't me… https://t.co/tKB5xtR9tr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congrats on 20 years! I love you guys so much! You both are such an inspiration to me and I’m so grateful for every… https://t.co/8YA874Lnxr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I believe the best advice a person can give is the one prefaced with, "From my experience".]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ItzYaBoiSamuel @Dat_0ne_DooD @rucoschools Yea that’s pretty obvious, teachers can’t do there jobs right (I was exa… https://t.co/IPiMxdBKzl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Supporting  @TeamHISD Public Education Matters Benefit Dinner with #Table 14 @SSaenzPhillips @alundyja1 @hisdnorth… https://t.co/bU29D9hxa3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My personal hobbies include reading, listening to music, and ruining the good things in my life]]></document><document><![CDATA[And @POTUS. Has been trying to explain this...bit you don't want to listen. The centers are FULL!! Courts are backe… https://t.co/xxY5ZsmHUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Has anyone experienced the Mortal Tour? I went to the show in Phoenix. Advertised everything Michael Jackson. I bou… https://t.co/nnXGrs2LN7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que cada vez soy más consciente que la vida sin darnos cuenta se consume en un suspiro..  #saturday #photography… https://t.co/ltPFWbKcKu]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so mad at my scheduling manager for giving me nothing but clopining (or however you would spell that shit) shif… https://t.co/U5CEh6vlx7]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is #FakeNews. In the very 1st paragraph of this piece it is stated that Sandman, a kid, "confronted" Phillips.… https://t.co/ljvdTv96WF]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm all set up and ready to go! #amwriting #writersofinstagram @ San Diego, California https://t.co/ERZNWJT55a]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Peek at the Hottest Dreadlock Styles for Men That'll Swoon You  https://t.co/JtDhAmvDut  From Discover on Google]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bosma doesn’t like gambling bill. Calls it a major expansion. Would leave one casino in Gary, move one to (likely)… https://t.co/YK5shzOPG6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zip line fun! Swipe left to see return trip in slo mo. #zipline #winterfun #skiresort #vacation #slomo @ Cranmore M… https://t.co/m0uKhRlHBj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aldouga @ColorsTV @VivianDsena01 @RubiDilaik @Vivian_DsenaWeb @TeamRubiDilaik @gagori_uin @AvChahat @viviandesna55… https://t.co/hYnTM38zeR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Started off 2019 right 👌 #grandcanyon #takemeback @ Grand Canyon National Park https://t.co/BvcIikdQ7N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Not bad cocacola #orangevanillacoke @ Hide Away Cabin https://t.co/PNPvx5tbdD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wish my ass was bigger cause i know i can twerk better than most girls lol. Just a little freestyle https://t.co/vGR4YBxtus]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iRachelSumner It comes to show Putnam county gives no support. But I’m not surprised. Welcome to Putnam county.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@luckydayapp I would send it my daughter at college so she has some cash to use]]></document><document><![CDATA[LEGGGGGOOOO @Britt_Don @loganmiller69 😂😂 Southwest Airlines just began selling flights to Hawaii with some tickets… https://t.co/eZMGHEBs3r]]></document></documents></author>