<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Big 'ol snowflake update: They've grown. #Q13FOX #WAWX #snow https://t.co/GB3yeUNcCi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThisAmerLife re groping MD w/epidural. NOT victim shaming...my hospital, ALWAYS have 2nd staff. As woman, always f… https://t.co/M0UYzPxlNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[This #Retail job might be a great fit for you. Click the link in our bio to see it and more. shift supervisor - Sto… https://t.co/tFHwVSRt5v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse won best animated feature. All is right with the world. 🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾🙌🏾 https://t.co/Po2Ly9Yipw]]></document><document><![CDATA[TODAY: Open houses in honor of Tommie, the dog intentionally set on fire, begin. They will go from 2-7 p.m. today —… https://t.co/nh1eaCrLRF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Justo cuando pienso que no puedo cagarla más, me dirijo directo y sin escalas a cagarla más, que buena onda.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@english_sheila No. I had a friend with one. Her younger sibs really thought it was called diving board.😄]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SouthwestAir is a Boeing 737-800 the same as the Boeing 737-Max planes that are faulty and caused two crashes? Try… https://t.co/18XINJmwwP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hanging out in my Birkenstocks #boardwalk #BIRKENSTOCKJYXU  @jys_salesmtg #looksgoodwithatan #jyxu @ Omni Nashville… https://t.co/2va8uScbgn]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 months and 6 days sober from Dr. Pepper. Thank you all for staying with me during these trying times]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mark Turgeon Implores Maryland Crowd To Stop Calling Michigan&amp;#39;s Ignas Brazdeikis Ugly https://t.co/4ZxdlP3f0M via @deadspin]]></document><document><![CDATA[Close game in the cold and rain for @CCSLacrosse @ North Raleigh Christian Academy https://t.co/Rrje0kYQ1N]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #FANBOOST vote goes to @MahindraRacing and #JeromeDAmbrosio. Show your support by doing the same! #passioneering]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sbaileyauthor Just glad someone else admitted it first. It’s almost midnight here, and I have a 5 AM boot camp tom… https://t.co/uqziLt3ap2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do any of you short girls know of good brands that have high waisted jeans that you don’t have to cuff? I find it s… https://t.co/cFgVYQBUtt]]></document><document><![CDATA[These are my favorite cones, when they fall off the tree, they look like roses made of wood.  Beautiful nature.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@karolcummins @ericgarland @jbadomics Governor Phil Bryant of Mississippi with Farage, tRump's inauguration. https://t.co/vRfSu8TRYN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you jesus!! Thank you everyone for voting in numbers too big to mess with!]]></document><document><![CDATA[the best way to watch the sunset: reading flux and drinking coffee https://t.co/fRX4cfqQbj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alexecklin catches Perry Lee in the #Twister at the Downtown Masterskya Location. This is where I train in jiu jit… https://t.co/jpKnt2HjHN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today, I’m exploring eminent domain as it relates to the Durham-Orange light rail. City and County leaders have sai… https://t.co/AN8uqP2KxQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I need a vacation but alone tho, Just to rest, reset, and rethink a lot of shit 💯]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow 😮 so Buddy is a sore loser! Go #TeamDuff #BuddyvsDuff https://t.co/nuDPh2tSzu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Putting my Super Bowl 🏟 volunteer gloves to use this morning! #TeamATL @atlsuperbowl53 https://t.co/k3G4KpGDMk]]></document><document><![CDATA[¿Por cuánto tiempo más tendré que soportar todo esto 😔? Ya me estoy cansando.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StephenotAtHome @TomFitton @realDonaldTrump @JudicialWatch @foxandfriends @FoxNews don't give him any ideas...that… https://t.co/Fx6kCibVUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics They (#theDems)are pulling candidates out of the stands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@esliwhooo Yo también los extraño! Hay que vernos en la graduación de la troll.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TeriWenzel1 @CheekyAussieGuy @sheri_lynn95252 @tazsdog11 @FryPeggy1 @AlexSan85617527 @Djpk10Denise @GatorMom73… https://t.co/RdiM4SJ1Xr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Put together a few of my favorite accessories to gift to some amazing and courageous women tomorrow... @ Coko's Fas… https://t.co/AJtcDJ9lto]]></document><document><![CDATA[Creating helps regulate our brains #ISTAGTC @ISTAmembers @ISEAmembers https://t.co/URTnvc2enf]]></document><document><![CDATA[America you need to wise up. Trump is going to try to get the minority to follow him now because of the election in… https://t.co/OkImJWTW57]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're the Russia puppet.  Keep trying to deflect attention from your family and administration's… https://t.co/mzyvwpWrMz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am in the city drinking with some Korean alcohol with my bestie what’s up  🙋🏿‍♀️🙋🏻‍♀️#drinks #philly #drinking… https://t.co/eRBndEjMKd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CoachMoss30 @loganward99 @NeXupBaseball @FullCountGA Love it!! Keep working hard @loganward99]]></document><document><![CDATA[The rooftop at the @jccsf where I work has a bunch of succulents. There’s a playground up there where we take the a… https://t.co/e4B1wIKsyW]]></document><document><![CDATA[TSA: what’s your last name  me: pantaleo (pan-tel-e-o) TSA: what’s your last name? me: ?? TSA: you just said “i can… https://t.co/MQhXwg7w79]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SebGorka @TuckerCarlson Keep up the good work Tucker.  The fact that the Lunatic Left doesn't like you is proof of… https://t.co/OCObaH20vK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RaptorsOG Lol man Celtics Twitter is in shambles tho. Half of us want major changed and half of us are in denial]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day!  Thanks for being my partner through life.  We are so blessed to have you as a wife and mom.… https://t.co/UejO2zonoM]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@HeadGatorTRK walking into the Lem with another National Championship 🏆 this morning! 🤣 https://t.co/JVrq1AklIe]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm excited to be a part of The Church Without Walls Family,I love my Pastor Dr Ralph D West and amazing Wife, Shereeta West!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nayllors I think he was in a few other series with appearances but nothing major like Cas on SPN. I don’t watch th… https://t.co/5QFocGDeK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NarjustDuma @TGeorgeMD @ASCO @marklewismd It’s like Bono meets Dave Grohl!  #GI MedOnc Rockstars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kyfreak01 @rhoni3369 @seanhannity @trumps_feed I'd love to go to the doctor add well but thanks to Obama with that… https://t.co/QKwTDLXqeO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Still working on studio. #bstarkart @ Art Loft Art Studios and Gallery https://t.co/SMIgHA52eA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so excited to take @Carlson451 ‘s One Story concept back to my students! And that seafood buffet... 👌 Of course… https://t.co/UnVeaiO8Rr]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hope Liberty Hill at least buys these refs dinner for all their help tonight...]]></document><document><![CDATA[My mom calls @M_Ramossss SONshine now☀️ and I think it’s the sweetest thing 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Newsweek He is a mental patient. Why isn’t anybody doing anything about it?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrbluehoodie Y’all always get love from me after being a glorified lineman I realized that shit isn’t easy]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@THEKIDMERO just came for someone in @AOC comments by calling them a “discarded baby wipe.” https://t.co/JNo8l6Y21Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tip: be careful of interaction between estrogen and PREP- makes PREP less effective]]></document><document><![CDATA[omfg the artist coming tomorrow for our critical issues in art lecture is best friends with the one and only Natash… https://t.co/baN08On8vc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@donlemon Happy Birthday 🎂🎁 Don you are one of the Best at what you do. Thank you 🙏 for all of the information and… https://t.co/alwyPxK4os]]></document><document><![CDATA[#buni 😍  mi amor, mi mejor amigo y futuro esposo ❤ gracias por alegrar mi vida todos los dias! te amo*… https://t.co/0IvchoW6LK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Did I just get a job in a lab with my two favorite grad students 😎 epic]]></document><document><![CDATA[National Board Candidates working on Writing the NBCT!! You guys are super stars!! @JCPSAsstSuptTL @kids_inspire… https://t.co/440bIGmZN5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Help me and my girl out. Just got done writing a 5 page paper and we broke in college @kiyadagoat ! @_DomoWilson1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Also, I can't wait to see my boy when he comes back from San Antonio. I better get some mf cuddles, or ima throw hands.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pasco County is AMAZING.   Good booooooi.... Goooooood maaaaan.  Yogi is the dude!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is the first day of the Novena to St. Joseph, Husband of Mary!   Today let us pray for all husbands -- esp Fa… https://t.co/erswRfIalz]]></document><document><![CDATA[I haven’t not had a job since I was like 15. Help. I’m already bored and sad...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AFP Putin &amp; #PatheticPresident should be locked in one of these shelters... #lockthemup]]></document><document><![CDATA[Belle histoire à lire en ce jour de la Saint-Valentin. #❤️  | JDM https://t.co/5VcXFtFeLO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bookgaslighting That’s a wonderful feeling when you realize you are moving forward and becoming stronger than ever before! So happy for you]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BigIndianGyasi It’s unusual, but not inappropriate.  I’ve given flowers to BFs, and they liked it.  I think it rar… https://t.co/5X6WDVxK5i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SimonYTangLab Yay, Simon congratulations. I love hearing this kind of good news]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cillamarie29 I thought #mia was drinking #firestarter or #firebomb or whatever that liquor is called lol #fireball ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @JenniferAdams to post 7 covers of books I love—no explanations—no reviews—just the… https://t.co/vHD5jJc68c]]></document><document><![CDATA[WAKE UP ‼️ if y’all don’t hear me say it enough‼️ y’all go check out 💪🏾 #Flexxin link in bio new ish🔥🔥 be sure to… https://t.co/ytUV5kpgZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women’s day. Feeling refreshed &amp; energized after WW Sales Kickoff Event. Blessed to work… https://t.co/oNEfb00qZ6]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s game day for @PioBaseball! The Pioneers take on Georgetown at noon in the Westin Lake Mary Stetson Invitationa… https://t.co/wW2DPTuhEA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back in September I traveled to London to see my bestie and her 6, yes 6 girls, 5 of them  age 6 and under. (did I… https://t.co/K7VD53sG7l]]></document><document><![CDATA[Khloe girl.....hate to break it to you but your sleazebag, cheating baby daddy is the reason your family is broken… https://t.co/jHISxkoQdc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Conan gray has really latched on to this “never had my first kiss” brand and so has his fan base but that can’t las… https://t.co/IbStvnTHa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@imqueerious One of my faves is Honoré Sharrer! Also Aminah Brenda Lynn Robinson, Maya Lin, and Alison Saar!]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of the Dawson Lady Tigers chosen for this event. I'm especially proud of you @sophiagrace115 for your hard… https://t.co/ffmKXY4G54]]></document><document><![CDATA[O h*** it was just a coincidence and they talked about their grandchildren for 10 hours .LMFAO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Open House 10a to 6p Today! Come see this gorgeous modern farmhouse! I’ll take you on a tour of this beautiful comm… https://t.co/rpLaarBkTW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tomorrow I’m spinning for 2 hours at the @bikeforkids2017 spin-a-thon to raise money for kids with brain tumours. P… https://t.co/rkSTdRzbiu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnasPoison1 I know I didn’t laugh. I am still furious. It makes me die inside that my child’s innocence was taken… https://t.co/eXr7CpgKcb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks for the kind words! ★★★★★ "OMGOSH THIS WREATH IS THE BOMB!!!!! " Beth M. #etsy #homedecor #easter… https://t.co/OGwpmkouql]]></document><document><![CDATA[how cute is this lineup of Indiana state things https://t.co/YoNPsDiHsC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaelsloner My fav bc it's true tbh #iHeartAwards #BestFanARMY #5SOSFam https://t.co/Ry8JX6Gwi3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can someone explain how no one wears a hat north of the Wall? If you took a leisurely stroll without a hat in Chica… https://t.co/OcFUhQmGOU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Haanamiri Guex the Mum has some explanation to do.. there is fire on the mountain😅]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m reading this book right now on iBooks .... good read so far I’ll let you know how I go 👍 #bravenotperfect https://t.co/vdZ7hjHSxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@stephanieryon @nearpod @caitlin_arakawa @nearpodcourtney I could have been your roommate. Glad you are having fun!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crash through the surface, where they can’t hurt us 🌊 @ Lexington, Michigan https://t.co/2bA861OWLX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@artist180 Always work hard at loving each other and make sure it’s not going to be you that causes a separation or divorce.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I think some woman should run on this slogan. It’s perfect!  Preferably a democrat]]></document><document><![CDATA[@soozannawatkins @naomilaynew ohhhh okay. that’s just so strange i had no idea.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@richhomiejenna @audhubillah Thanks!!! It what’s Tess called trash when I recommended it]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SafiMaasai @nickiknowsnada Poor baby. It must really hurt. That’s why nobody gives a big 💩 about what happens to y… https://t.co/CsuYgyLWI2]]></document><document><![CDATA[#LadyGagaQuote "There can be a hundred people in the room, and 99 of them won’t believe in you, but all you need is one." So true! ❤️☝️🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[my neighbor was having a domestic with his partner and locked out of his unit for 2 hours.  its official this is on… https://t.co/N25ReVT7Xo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely card from Cornerstone Hospice.  Spend time with those who lift you up and limit time with those who bring yo… https://t.co/2fsrMGoFUR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GovMattBevin Thank you Governor Bevin! We look forward to working with you to advance economic development and job growth in the Delta.]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made it to New Orleans for MARDI GRAS💜💛💚  #bangenergy @BANGenergy  @BangEnergyCEO]]></document></documents></author>