<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[#Bigdoggpinc Just sayin.... Success in life, in anything, depends upon the number of persons that one can make hims… https://t.co/rFEWifAXZ1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Almost time for the defending third place #Skywalkers to drop the puck on another season...  😁 #LetsDoTheHockey]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abrooks22 During today's #LiveCast by @keepernotes, I was invited on-air to say a few words before I took my "limo… https://t.co/JMa8c9jhIW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good morning Dads of the world Rise and climb subculturecoffee thedad #dadlife @ Subculture Coffee https://t.co/u9xicJzgDT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CalMBBall close again, but the cigar is ever out of reach. https://t.co/feejPzw6aN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lons Hey @HamillHimself , care to weigh in on the epic Dad Vader debate? I mean, he did give the ok 👍 to blow up A… https://t.co/YQRT3kkOrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jake0458 @tomtebbutt Felix’s match was on the app, direct and tsngo yesterday. Couldn’t show it cause it could hav… https://t.co/HRdPl9oa4f]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bronx28Bombers Face it, the Yankees are most likely done signing players.  Have damn faith in who the team has.  I… https://t.co/rNggZmLBFE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KelliBruer @bfwoff Kelli honey this could not be more up your alley. You’ll love it. I’ll see you next week]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EMPosts @business @tictoc Que hueva me parece la peor version de cantinflas, en 45 segundos casi me duermo de tedi… https://t.co/nWdkRLq04R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DROBakaDTM @NateGearyWGR Gimme Paradis and James and the guy I like most at TE is Maxx Williams. Think he's got un… https://t.co/Ivg2NMEuc1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@joel_eisenberg Some Democrats actually support Sharia, or Islamic law.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gtconway3d @MollyMay1923 George what does that say about @KellyannePolls ? At one time she didn’t believe in… https://t.co/IQdTM9lovT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CreativeArtAPE @M_R_E @RepElaineLuria @IlhanMN Arab Israelis- only Arabs in the Middle East with a stitch of civil… https://t.co/7BW82ipxX3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson @SamuelLJackson I am glad you and Sam work great together. Brie you are deceptively strong for your size wow!]]></document><document><![CDATA[BAM!!!! Nailed a 361,75 in the @NBA last night with my #1 lineups of Lowry/Doncic/Russell and hit for 31.8 in the… https://t.co/B23L6rboxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@juanblanco76 nah.... if you add a little cream it's ok.. some coffees are bitter and a little cream smooths the flavor - but never sugar]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @Dax14Dax and @jAxSyRiNg and the other student that made the trip!! #wecanhearu #family]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LuisaMaldonadoM @GuerrerosDRCs @CompromisoRC5 @LuisReinaCh @JCFialloC @FRC_SANBLAS_UIO @Moni_Sandoval5 @AcuerdoSur… https://t.co/qATEVRWVRL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulCastronovo Didn’t @jeremypiven once tell you you gave an “Oscar worthy” performance???]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow, amazing @starbucks location ! (@ Starbucks Reserve in Palm Springs, CA) https://t.co/dPBFQGuCnh https://t.co/sMnaYryhyy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JonesRj1200 @CoachDavidYates @ARHoopScoop I think that falls on THIS coaching staff doesn’t it? By the way, who is… https://t.co/Tju1FjGsSZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimBenzPGH @gdtann Could you also add how the heck he passed a class in college with those sentences? I understand… https://t.co/9wrswIZIwt]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of my family and friends worried  and concerned, thru Facebook and insta, I am alive and kickin it😛🥳 https://t.co/gd7Wp7APrO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ash Wednesday Fellowship Worship  "Lent Season" Bethel AMEC Conway, SC 1530 Racepath Av. Conway, SC 29526 Rev. Mill… https://t.co/FzMIswWMYv]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SquawkCNBC @andrewrsorkin 2/2 has editorialized and summarized the pros and cons of the @Amazon LIC deal superbly.… https://t.co/n8wx1veD6z]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good solid malty choice - cold and yet warming - Drinking a Winter Weizen by LocAle Brewing Company @ Saint Paul Mi… https://t.co/e818NS9qwq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesOKeefeIII @Google @Twitter @facebook Nobody's buying your bullshit in Austin.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JayAndDan have you seen this error in programming? https://t.co/8b8FvdV9MY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sahouraxo @PeterPyke Sure. They lied to us about asbestos, they lied to us about leaded gasoline, they lied to us… https://t.co/yzT2NgF4dY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kristopherkane @mscottsummers You are coming to Minneapolis and didn’t tell me?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. I really just worked an entire overnight shift with my left contact popping out of my eye. Iconic.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some of these sidewalks are like a skating rink.. safe commute gang #Toronto]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mwischoff_64 @de_bovary @JamesPossible @Im_Razed I see you’re a packers fan. I’m a Vikings fan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion NYC probably doesn't need the Amazon jobs. Amazon likely will still thrive without NYC HQ2. Long Island… https://t.co/FWOjUCyOBH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TonyMar59 @CathySalmons Dude.  All of these new Dems did this kind of stuff . I guess they thought they had won th… https://t.co/DwKyF2d6OK]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I am so grateful we have a good jounarlist like you to tell the truth and show the documentation there in]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another great game with @CoachOrr21 and too 15 in the State Apple Valley.   49-49 with 2:50 remaining.]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was a disgrace what happened at Parkview last night. No class at all. How did the coaches and administrators let… https://t.co/vbAh1X5FuD]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jerk BBQ boneless #northernfried chicken bites to the world! 🇯🇲🍗🔥✊🏾😊 . . . . #Toronto #northernfried… https://t.co/u1RBmuSaKN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MOregonRA @Carterdsc @TR0771N @Bab_Blue7 @AmyQt8942 @dividejen @suzystays @ChasingOzPhotog @warrior_4_good… https://t.co/s1i9mcx0qb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Coke head , rehab , wife beating husband , refuse to stand up for women being mistreated . Phony ass Bitch Shut Up.… https://t.co/SPndGFfvmx]]></document><document><![CDATA[This animal is unlike any other on Earth - National Geographic https://t.co/PGeh8axMSu]]></document><document><![CDATA[If anyone forgot, @GroteBrianna is still my fave person. Keep scrolling now.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Antonio brown to the Raiders...Jesus.. better hope they get a QB in there for him]]></document><document><![CDATA[At my office in Seattle. How did I never notice how rock n roll this hallway is? @ Seattle, Washington https://t.co/bBkmWaORqc]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merece_saberlo @shned_org Vaya....veo q hoy es mi día de lectura......ok, dale😉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Taniel @RTMannJr this is why i keep saying, we shouldn't coddle never-Trumpers. The enemy of my enemy is still a terrible person.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Because they believe in when your on top, don’t give anyone a chance to compete that’s socialism! So Democrats keep… https://t.co/BdX1GBOI0N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Milton Friedman on Slavery and Colonization https://t.co/gcRXip4EHF via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeorginaHolguin Gina , te ves preciosa y muy sexy en Expreso te amo 😍😘😍😍😍😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 7:  Running with the Buffaloes by Chris Lear. No picture of book because @ajrich12 has my copy https://t.co/riacTNKTA2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@marklutchman @amcjap Hey, Mark...wake up...pay attention...he's in Hanoi, not NK. https://t.co/rcMFw1SU0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mforbeck My name is Wayne Humfleet the same as a whole lot of people.   I was born in the morning and I will be a… https://t.co/JzsN7VjxvZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ myself stop getting intoxicated the night before i have a lab challenge]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn good thing we don’t have a draft anymore. Could you imagine having to be around these stupid bastards??]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissyGaul @JeffreyGuterman Am sure it is not from eating to many carrots]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS He's allowed to be upset with what he did and still like able to tell us all that you are a… https://t.co/ihPLmL8SOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KateFresePhoto @AGirlInPhilly This is an excellent shot. Well done Kate.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Imagine your favorite starter Pokémon not being Bulbasaur. https://t.co/y4pwmOrygt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Darby_Crush dude - leave the ladies alone.   Have an opinion - but it’s rude to drop your opinion bombs into other… https://t.co/6xiLHeB8XX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Clelandcattle @danoedurass @svbgusmaker @ruralmidiowa @koinzangreg Unless you’re borrowing money to buy the cattle… https://t.co/dDqLDpPeoT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@barrymoltz A con artist was the issue not the  brand ambassadors as evidenced by he still doesn’t think he did anything wrong.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Excelente día para todos! 🤩 #farafaradno #destinadoenaccion  Info 8180548522 en Nuevo Leon, Mexico https://t.co/hVVHsAuRoJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StPatsBurns @gohabsgo999 @K_Savage93 @1HabRising Someone with a keen ability to spot stupidity. You qualify. Thanks for playing.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had a great team dinner the other night @CapitalGrille. Making the playoffs has its perks! https://t.co/duWjO7vqPG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Welcoming Monday with Optimism and Laughter 😍 and lots of Red for #passion #life #love and #laugh 🙏 Thank you to th… https://t.co/dvmHrWSVrj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Que sueño tuve, me abre los ojos a la realidad que nunca te volveré a tener.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vladimirpadrino Ya usted lo confirmo, cuando usted esta muerto y la vida cintinue, la aguila de la libertad comera… https://t.co/Zv5O2NOtei]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lyndsey and I are in college and can’t figure out a 3rd grade math problem for her lesson plan. Help.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@prattprattpratt @vincentdonofrio This looks like a winner! I'll be on the lookout for it! 👍]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Bounce Bros... + Shaylee 🤴🏽💯💕 @ Morgantown High School https://t.co/y9yuoimsJ4]]></document><document><![CDATA[https://t.co/q4geZZTB5t it’s #tuesday and it’s going to be a #greatday #tuesdaymotivation @ West Kendall https://t.co/jTUDcnzfJO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m so happy with life right now and everyone that is in it I wouldn’t want it any other way]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just when I thought I was done watching weather models… here comes March! Oh boy... #WeatherNerd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@radleybalko It’s routine with at least one narc in Long Beach,CA. His favorite tactic is to target probationers, t… https://t.co/RNyQ33U4zT]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is a quote from a physicist, but it’s pretty good theology. “I would rather have questions that can't be answe… https://t.co/0sXJNqRcDf]]></document><document><![CDATA[me walking into stage makeup on wednesday after the teacher asked ~me~ to do the demonstration for brow blocking    https://t.co/oTPYKCCmGQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[#TFCLive says it will be mending two additional players to @OttawaFuryFC this season. Guessing they are waiting unt… https://t.co/FQXtrruTcN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Охх, сегодня проснулся в 2:30 и сна ни в одном глазу. Ну ладно, сон для слабаков ;)]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family and I are in the middle of a weight-loss challenge. I’m home for about 36 hours and my mom just keeps bak… https://t.co/sQxEImjUgQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Adventures of Dartman #1 is available on digital at https://t.co/1QepIUYpiN https://t.co/K5zSF8PpFz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NickyMonsPhoto Hey I learn from example!😉 we grindin’ out here brother!🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[Confession: Completely forgot I scheduled “Mr. Brightside” into “Anything Anything” on @kroq tonight. Luckily, I st… https://t.co/qOADFwQ7J1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sources confirm that 45 y/o Shana Decree and 19y/o Dominique Decree strangled their 5 family members over the past… https://t.co/8FMefqAWhJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO @GianniDAngeloww Countdown to their legislation banning puppies and cute cuddly little kittens]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHoustonWade @Bearded_Cynic @strokjl @SykesCharlie @EWErickson This whole argument is incoherent.  You say Nazii… https://t.co/DDGusMbcmt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Carolina isn’t gonna get nearly the credit it deserves because apparently the only reason they won is because dook… https://t.co/GfLyS3uV3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[@clifftothemound I thought it was understood that it didn’t because it’s Vibranium. And yeah, Killmonger I think me… https://t.co/tf0IrigROY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@granthpaulsen Hmmm I thought that too but looks like Kuznetsov’s blade was inside Ovi’s. Ovi actually pushed Kuzi’… https://t.co/U1pNrZjQ8r]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lets Make a Deallllllll.... BishBeFuReal @ Cincinnati https://t.co/IEkYobvoCe]]></document><document><![CDATA[YA TODOS SABEMOS QUE SÓLO GANAMOS CON ÉL, ESO ESTÁ CLARO!!! en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/KeB24H9ZEf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KVanValkenburg Opposite happened to me once. I was running down Glendale Blvd at night, I run past a car pulled ov… https://t.co/svR4IRyYVr]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who’s had a quieter career as the number 2 overall pick than Marvin Williams? I felt like he was drafted and then forgotten]]></document><document><![CDATA[@michaeljknowles @AnnCoulter Hello @DrJillStein  ....   Hillary's calling!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judah got a BIG surprise today! Uncle Kelley and Aunt Taylor came to be his kindergarten class mystery reader today… https://t.co/TWpNldyaWn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great to chat with Allan Madonik @madzzz1 of Blue Swan Financial about @CAGPTorontoArea and excited that we’ll see… https://t.co/XOPN573W8k]]></document><document><![CDATA[.@BrewDogFTON #Columbus #Ohio #brewery #CraftBeer #brewdog #neon #beer https://t.co/AXdr0apkjA]]></document><document><![CDATA[Keep on asking, and it will be given you; keep on seeking, and you will find; keep on knocking, and it will be opened to you]]></document><document><![CDATA[You and Matt Kuchar should go have lunch and talk about who can be more out of touch and continue to one up each ot… https://t.co/QI6fB7N9tp]]></document></documents></author>