<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@champagnennuts Because it's the NBA All-Star Weekend? Be honest, Andy's the one with the brains and you got the athletic skills, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@merrystacy @JesseSpots @joerogan Mary I am making a compilation of segments where Jesse shames his audience and cl… https://t.co/Zcdg4g0KxZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@essenviews My mother is one of those women. She forgives trump for everything because she’s certain God wanted him… https://t.co/FOGNQSnTMB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Reboticant @CovfefeCapital @tomi I played through Dark Souls I when it came out and have about 10-12 hours on the… https://t.co/ALFkikxlDy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BridgetPhetasy What about that part when they almost made out? That was crazy!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCNews But @jonallendc hasn't learned the limits of Personal Bullsh%t https://t.co/qHIwWHTyuV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @MCChewRocka - hope you’re working. Left you a gift in today’s @9news weather update with @KylieBearseWX #GoAvsGo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@iampatjunior Lol after about 30sum matches I’m getting the hang of it! But yeah bruh it’s dope, was online with… https://t.co/tNaL7WboEt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@scottdaves @heathercampbell @AOC @amazon 25,000 people in New York will not make $150,000 a year. Amazon showed th… https://t.co/o0U4wb2m9e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@R0ttn1 @DavidWohl @realDonaldTrump Ummm...🤔 No, you wait and see... History will treat Trump much better / fairly.… https://t.co/aDtBcC5UBT]]></document><document><![CDATA[Day 2 at my 10th ❤ @CrushArizona_ ❤ was a blast! Can't wait til the next show!  HMU for discounted tickets to… https://t.co/6aZSBdChqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@divadirt Alot of people didn't and Vince is to blame for that. Look at the hole they had to dig out of. But damn did they dig out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Air Force Academy, Colorado https://t.co/uiXYU5FpeT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brittanya187187 Might go back to prison Thursday .... I need some assistance]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ever happened to the 1pm est start time? At this rate its getting to be like the Coke 600. Start during the da… https://t.co/maMt6rPOyz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brenhillspeaks @tedbauer2003 @DreaVilleneuve @katyb_spencer @JimCanto @nplusg @TheComicHunter @ScottOntiveroz… https://t.co/9C5OTL1XAf]]></document><document><![CDATA[I chuze fitness. . . . . . . . . . . @chuzefitness #fitness #gym #fit #workout #motivation #fitnessmotivation… https://t.co/g2AY1ZfNij]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods Thank God the officer wasn't injured. Another reason to support our officers. A demonstration of th… https://t.co/U0Bv5yRRM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[♫High Hopes by @panicatthedisco, from #SoundHound with LiveLyrics® https://t.co/fuu5UcaV25]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MrJonnyConCarne @mattdolloff @Senators Why would he want to leave.. makes no sense.. was probably waiting for his… https://t.co/oG1h8ds8UT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ProudResister @realDonaldTrump Sadly this just is (still) America. Trump’s just given them a voice, incited them a… https://t.co/3GZy0dn3fF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ddale8 Pretty sure his real name is Bucky Barnes. @ChrisEvans can you confirm?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DonaldJTrumpJr @foxandfriends @PeteHegseth @ainsleyearhardt The Trump infestation continues ... https://t.co/bMZcN0D9Ya]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who came out to @BicycleCasino for #KROQGNO. I told you I suck at poker!! Lost all my $$$ but ha… https://t.co/8RACrrWLjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@felixseguin @tvanouvelles Deux chars incendiés = Crise en Haïti !    Ok !]]></document><document><![CDATA[Deandre Hunter could be the best all around player in college, Forsure top 5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where's the fucking IRS in all this don't they have any authority to investigate a crooks taxes?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just my FabLab kids doing random projects ... #jsarocks https://t.co/f61GmAb29e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GodlessApeMan Probably a combination of both. A person can be sincere and still be wrong..]]></document><document><![CDATA[Another amazing #artist and work of #art!  How in the world does he get a #perspective on #what he is #doing??]]></document><document><![CDATA[Praise is heaped by the bucket-load upon anyone who is prepared to stick their head above the parapet and tell thos… https://t.co/9fa88umUpk]]></document><document><![CDATA[@swggrkllr Not yet. But next year will likely be there a few months at a time in between wrestling seasons]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulT_Tennis @ITF_Tennis @_markpetchey I have joined the protesters and sent a strongly worded letter to the ITF.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PushaReese Bruhwhere the hell u find 50€ @LittleDebbie honey buns. Lol they are a $1 here]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tracydavidson @XfinityLive @GrittyNHL @NBCPhiladelphia @NHLFlyers Wish I could make it up tonight but I’ll be surp… https://t.co/ve2JFS7Ghu]]></document><document><![CDATA[My #bff @sierra_tristen rockin it at the rccsuny Home Show yesterday! #tristenrox #realestategoddess… https://t.co/CZHafLROPg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Universities and colleges should fire half of non-teaching personnel and cut tuition.]]></document><document><![CDATA[How can you take the Blazers seriously with guys like Lyman getting time in the 4th quarter?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Gosh, maybe “King” @KingJames will join the cause? He won’t because he’s a coward. Or maybe “Queen” Bey @Beyonce wi… https://t.co/ZTVriWNgv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[It was good seeing all of my #hgrfamily at #nl19 #nolimits2019 great conference! #hgrsleep @ Lucille's Smokehouse B… https://t.co/wWk3isTkrZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[This place is impressive. Nice work @milesherndon @danielherndon gavel.indy @ Fountain Square https://t.co/OTAB7Hlx5p]]></document><document><![CDATA[I will post an extra card when I get home since we passed 200 RTs! Which makes a total of 8 extra cards including t… https://t.co/9nMpQCsvlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@weimaj94 @SWFPodcast I would be on the ground. https://t.co/cSgMzzg17c]]></document><document><![CDATA[Internet trolls are out here acting like the MCU invented Captain Marvel to destroy the patriarchy. Captain Marvel… https://t.co/ccDUXenRaz]]></document><document><![CDATA[How businesses can restore the state’s middle class...ensuring the #California dream works for all and tackling… https://t.co/amEp8fpPlv]]></document><document><![CDATA[God damnnn the edge wins the award for most couples working out together 🏋️‍♂️ 🏆]]></document><document><![CDATA[@the_sarah_rose @andrejoseph88 Damn still mad pressed ... take this energy you have and focus on yourself and stop… https://t.co/VqPwEHD1DN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tom's Music Place's Song Spotlight February 26, 2019  Featured Songs For February 26, 2019 Celine Dion - Falling In… https://t.co/KCFhNqPbnm]]></document><document><![CDATA[😍 Thank goodness, the bike lanes are becoming a bit dangerous from all the debris on them.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 @POTUS @realDonaldTrump Coming from a known liar and a convicted felon you are done, do  Us all a… https://t.co/wHkl84qKEu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Alan Gratzer was a great rock drummer. Nobody talks about that guy but when I signed to Ludwig in 2007, one of the… https://t.co/JoS0b7oc4m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Icatsin Salvador Alvarado lleva cursos a las comunidades a lejanas del Municipio de Salvador Alvarado, como la comu… https://t.co/MG3kWPJH96]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every day is a blessing but today is extra special. 22 years ago today God united my wife and I together . A Grace… https://t.co/F7vbgbiEAV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GlennKesslerWP @DonaldJTrumpJr @BernieSanders The Swedes are still angry that they had a heinous terrorist inciden… https://t.co/zLWw92KTp0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@D_DUBB9 @ReignVillasenor @Psyerking #Breedup Speed kills Technique Destroys]]></document><document><![CDATA[After today,two februarys in a row with catching fish every day  Million fish Paul..Had 25 yesterday, a16 inch Bass,and walleye 19inch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RizzShow @HereLiesMoon @jeffburton1057 decided to stop on the highway I-57 in Kankakee IL. People were hitting the… https://t.co/O07Oe9KIn0]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Hunnies make their in ring debut at @LWMaine at “Welcome To The Dance”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jed Garner, Head Men’s Coach, Dayton High School #soccerchat  A3: I use unopposed training on recovery days or delo… https://t.co/cLsADRv1oZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pcrowe @SkyloftResort @Groupon Never thought I’d see the day. And I’ve parked (ok dad did) in Vail.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heyydanielll The question is, what are you eating on the other 5 days?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricaDa91772503 @HazelThugg @kidsearnmoney Brelynshine3@gmail.cpm.    Antonio shine https://t.co/k2eTYFkY1W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erinbiba Did see that BUT; the fact it's just one model means that 1200ppm cutoff is uncertain in itself, and the… https://t.co/hkvCSPEl8s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brendanchance @andrewt519 Yeah that has flipped. The offense will come out of sheer talent if they stick to the ba… https://t.co/WVykUidtGb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Where was Hillary when this happened? Although I’m sure she doesn’t actually do the deed herself.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am happy to announce that @SouthStyle_MA we are now offering 1 on 1 sessions again.☝🏻 . . Today we had a great ti… https://t.co/7rLX4aFVOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@keyshawn @LZGranderson @TravisRodgers @CMMSpectrum @RojGrobes @stephenasmith @VeniceMase @LAIreland @BergmanGreg… https://t.co/sOYX5SWqgW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@smerconish Just let the kids be able to profit from their likeness. The solution scales to all NCAA competitive cl… https://t.co/qYYuZ3Ciws]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump @KerstiKaljulaid @cafreeland @usbotschaft @usconsmunich I voted for your Dad. And I’m going to vote fo… https://t.co/juJso1cdu0]]></document><document><![CDATA[Settle or get sued: Lawyer gives state Friday deadline in Simpson escape case | VTDigger https://t.co/pwdx649MeR vi… https://t.co/he1pjCNUon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Geospatial_JB @RealJack These videos of Biden (there’s a bunch) should be played in a montage every day on Fox twi… https://t.co/XBC0Fs829k]]></document><document><![CDATA[#UFCWichita Picks 👊🏻  Lewis  Zaleski  Means  Rothwell  Dober  Akhmedov  Rocco  Kunitskaya  Dawson  Hughes  Smolka  Morono  Moret]]></document><document><![CDATA[@edgar224u I’m trying to keep my body in keto. Nothing wrong with apples but I’m not eating any sugar.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Commission Angry Prowl.  #transformers #mtmte #IDW #TFcon #copicmarkers https://t.co/dTEDpfc1Tg]]></document><document><![CDATA[̿̿ ̿̿ ̿̿ ̿̿ ̿'̿'\̵͇̿̿\з=( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)=ε/̵͇̿̿/’̿’̿ ̿ ̿̿ ̿̿ ̿̿                             I overheard y’all talking sh… https://t.co/H9O89JbLfS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WitchOfTheSith @Dodgers Not when I’ve got 🏈🏈🏈 @TheAAF @aafAPOLLOS @SteveSpurrierUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@angienashville Agreed. Envision Cayce CIB items have not been included in the last few Capital Spending Plans. I h… https://t.co/lM1lgWYRDW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dasalla hits the first but misses the second. EW leads 49-43 with 1:35 left]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SeanCovich @GatorsGolf @WVUGolf Thanks, Sean. LOVED having you, @JayWoodward22 , and your boys in Gainesville. Cou… https://t.co/IwRJzuQlZY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don't agree, Cain is great and one of the best. But lack of competing has almost ended this conversation IMO. Als… https://t.co/waAID7nnwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[I picked today of all day to go all the way to the Bronx to get my nails done.   It’s literally like a snow storm r… https://t.co/aqqbcw1vmm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zsports1988 @AllbrightNFL And again, he did nothing from an action or monetary standpoint in the year following to… https://t.co/azew9AVhIr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gehrig38 Curt displayed a talent that sports teams desired. The staffers are replaceable by nearly anyone off the street, HUGE difference.]]></document><document><![CDATA[FREELANCAVERSARY! What I've learned after 2 years of working freelance https://t.co/lz9Qz7QlOM via @foreverursbetty]]></document><document><![CDATA[Cortez on the Amazon deal??? What college did she go to. NYC just lost 25,000 jobs and $20 billion in revenue.  Thi… https://t.co/pLGToKhH5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤼: a Madison County Red Raider is king of the 113's in 4A. Josh Kincaid becomes the fifth individual State Champion… https://t.co/3OBlCYQ6Rm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RodriquezAnton1 @New_Tien0 And they always making these statements w/o asking or googling it 1st 🤷🏾‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@southeastchrist So indispensable has been their aid and comfort to the enemies of the Republic that certain violat… https://t.co/5Se6c54nL4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@McAllisterDen And I support you DC. No pun intended  lmao. You are a classy Lady.  Cleavage is awesome!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GeraldoRivera @realDonaldTrump What is crazy scary is we have a president who believes Putin over his own intelligence agencies]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BellatorMMA @DerekBarbaric Happy birthday Derek come see us at Fraziers]]></document><document><![CDATA[Um excuse me he wasn’t having sex, he was brutally traumatizing a victim with rape https://t.co/x38vtYnt8N]]></document><document><![CDATA[Im worried APEX is gonna get too popular and start attracting Fortnite players and other casuals. Does anyone else… https://t.co/ZdKcx1lQgb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @AriFleischer Robert Mueller won’t produce findings of his investigation ! Will not  be able to ju… https://t.co/QctRuzqujV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@benmaller Adidas are hypocrite's because they should pay the workers of the far East the same as American workers otherwise shut up]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein? You represent deplorables to cover your own criminality!  Money money money money $$$$ Unseal the… https://t.co/cESUKxbFyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[LoL somebody got a 🐓 somewhere in my neighborhood and that lil fuck is determined to wake us up! Gm everyone #HappySunday]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CarisAdel @RoryStolzenberg @bricamz @LyleSollaYates @Jalane_Schmidt @bbwilson3 @jordyyager @AlissaDiamond4 @slaats… https://t.co/RA4AyupJcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hola! Muy buen día!  A disfrutar y aprovechar todo lo que éste gran lunes nos brinda, seamos felices y sonaríamos!  #BuenLunes  #felizdia]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KarenATXMH @GraceCordovano @RasuShrestha @IrmaRaste @JulieReisetter @RBlount @pamressler @glfceo @MandiBPro… https://t.co/w686rLr2t7]]></document></documents></author>