<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[LMK IF ANYONE IS SELLING WEEKEND 2 TICKETS FOR COACHELLA PLEASE! Thank you!! 😫]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jsifuenteess @tumbaburross @FernandoCenic17 No hay ningún empresario que rechace "quitas" impositivas ni extranjer… https://t.co/VicrsDKNfg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sammquinn13 Great, thanks. That town has survived for the most part because of Braun.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Decennial: God Complex 2018 by @rivernorthbrew @ Stouthouse — https://t.co/wbuzYOubxR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm looking for some new colleagues. The Office of the General Assembly is currently seeking qualified applicants f… https://t.co/WOxqgAerOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Morning_Joe @morningmika the problem with @SenSanders running is - #Berniebros ... Who ended up voting for Trump..… https://t.co/rLdibnoohK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking a Penn Weizen by @PennBrewery at @PennBrewery — https://t.co/yGtXBK4gOY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thehill Pelosi is covering her ass,  Glad some republicans  opposed this  sham resolution constructed to shield th… https://t.co/OOrN7JA65H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrote it in PYTHON   On a Switch @NintendoAmerica   RunningOSX+  Got bored   AppleSeed APN @Apple   Fellow -Steve 🔮… https://t.co/jmRf21a17U]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Oasis65 @SnowballManny @WeatherOwen Pretty sure I had Steve muted for a while this winter too lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Fray quick little cover no edit just raw voice. Who wants to see a full cover on YouTube?  #TheFray https://t.co/QCJ3Sg71hp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricSpeakingUp I recently experienced a type of "mandate" as the result of fervent prayer. I was convicted of the… https://t.co/WGl4Nl7PYs]]></document><document><![CDATA[youtube and everyone thanks for the support!!! #roadto2million sethvideos @ The Lakes/Country Club, Las Vegas, Neva… https://t.co/Zf3ZltYyt7]]></document><document><![CDATA[When @AdrianHealey says your last name describing a #Hungarian. #magyar]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at @PlanetFitness in Roswell, GA https://t.co/49YRFuHPD4 https://t.co/L1Gj7i6GRp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jasonlk I'm at the fb party. Are you around later tonight or tomorrow?]]></document><document><![CDATA[We made the overnight haul to spread the word about or show tonight at @CainsBallroom - doors at 7. We’re on around… https://t.co/brORWexeV4]]></document><document><![CDATA[What I love most about Ohio is waking up to freshly fallen snow.. then driving to work in freezing rain.  New goal for 2019: buy awd car.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NightlyPolitics The minimum wage was created so that every American would have, at the minimum, a living wage. It… https://t.co/G904tkVFNO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Paint it black comes on Me: *turns it up Kayley: "turn it down I cant see"]]></document><document><![CDATA[STEPHEN MILLER: Drugs are pouring across the southern border.  CHRIS WALLCE: Up to 90% of them come through ports o… https://t.co/TssuTN23E3]]></document><document><![CDATA[Very nice to have my sis in town!! @ The Crack Shack https://t.co/p9g3jL64ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markstrahl @BalochSami Without truth and goodness everything is garbage.without goal desparate to die. Multicultur… https://t.co/zbIeire5xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AngelDaddy4 @R2D24Life Still hard to imagine Fury having a normie life.   Even if he was just an agent I would ass… https://t.co/9KPHqpJ3Y4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAlligator Then quit showing pretty girls on TV, Movies, &amp; magazines! 🤷🏼‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[I laughed harder then I should have I literally had tears in my eyes 😂😂😂😂 We wish him the best in his future endeav… https://t.co/txuJaISgYF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LithiumPodcast @CoryGroshek @RodneyHooper13 @HowardKlein10 I blocked the “professional plaintiff” aka “Green Bay S… https://t.co/dkUT0UcGao]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jaredrbowers @Ebron85 @calvinjohnsonjr Maybe. Still should do your job that you're paid millions to do. https://t.co/ORMNiLmyAn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi So i hear you are planning an act of Treason Nancy. Hopefully you are overturned quickly.]]></document><document><![CDATA[All the other songs were like 16 bars so I guess this will be over soon #oscars]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrs_hippiequeen Awesome Leigh. I’m very happy for you, it sounds like you’ve landed in a great place in your life.… https://t.co/NEeyj7LmcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CjDig86 @ufc @Ruthless_RL You get rid of people who follow you..? How much of a loser are you exactly??]]></document><document><![CDATA[i’ll never live long enough to see the day where dunkin gets my order right]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perfect vape fucking broke... how much worse can the rest of this week get]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lamphieryeg I guess, as in Nanaimo, the voters will decide that.  It's called #Democracy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jtsparks3119 @DevonESawa Apparently you havent followed Askren very much.the dude didnt lose a wrestling match his… https://t.co/gwFhjX9PwY]]></document><document><![CDATA[I do too. I don't miss a show he lets his guess talk unless they try to filibuster]]></document><document><![CDATA[#beastmode #WWE #dedication #fitnessmodel #model #eosfitness #vegasstrong @GoEOSfit https://t.co/n1ryAS7n1e]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Judgenap Good Afternoon! Nice seeing you on @TheStoryFNC w/ @marthamaccallum Keep up the good work on @FoxNews and… https://t.co/HoSiYOvQV8]]></document><document><![CDATA[For instance, we know that Cohen secretly taped President Trump.  If he does not have President Trump on tape sayin… https://t.co/q09sNVq7AN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you Laura 💅   #757artofnails #nail #nailart #naildesigns #nailartclub #nailswag #nailpro #nailsofinstagram… https://t.co/qBgwPW15ID]]></document><document><![CDATA[What's disgusting are the people who have already murdered over this lie, and will again. Please stop it.… https://t.co/gt0dCC06VK]]></document><document><![CDATA[⁦@jk_rowling⁩ This is how what looked like saucy text to you, I’m sure, actually came to be. And yes, you can cut i… https://t.co/Zx9VyQHiSO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@erickasriggs @_HamptonU @CommunicationNY @MAIP send the link @erickasriggs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to liven things up in baby world with some new shelving and plants. @ Novato, California https://t.co/i5hNPjchDZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at Haunted Mansion - @disneyland in Anaheim, CA https://t.co/KznTfdMArp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@naje_jackson @DreamChasersVA 😂😂😂 let’s not forget him going at his coach and choosing another team over his own co… https://t.co/sQ2cPJrrHo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PaulMattiesJr It’s not “taking a shot” it’s called sensing a slow pace and knowing which horse is in the lead.  Th… https://t.co/O9kvF1rVgv]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ll do it for you @stepickford!  Hey! You’ve all heard about the Haçienda nightclub in Manchester, but if you want… https://t.co/QNOLTa59J7]]></document><document><![CDATA[A Gainesville cheerleader peaks through her arms as Gainesville's Rafael Rubel shoots a free throw with little time… https://t.co/zFQCg4MUPv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Right-lane closed until 4 pm for maintenance in #Apex:WakeCounty on Williams St SB at Hwy 1 #traffic https://t.co/sFRv5PfpVM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mrhughes808 @thehill They thrive on creating stories. The liberal media has been doing that for years. Distort the… https://t.co/4ou6iQF6ry]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_AllieMulich @FAFSA I love FAFSA! My student aid had never any issues or troubles! Everything I did worked out great! 😒😒😒]]></document><document><![CDATA[@freespeech83 @rachael_engel @Brad__73 @krassenstein @realDonaldTrump The hate circling in the world is caused by o… https://t.co/TNv3CFafI5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardJunk braves shiny in the black pack. He spells his name Bryse? Why? https://t.co/uMreJNOUcZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Artists Autumn Knight and Robert Pruitt return to Houston for #CounterCurrent19 to present their latest lecture-per… https://t.co/92MOsHuHhc]]></document><document><![CDATA[Round 2. Antron Brown vs. Austin Prock... Hey look...there’s Matt Sackman https://t.co/uzdOnF3rfa]]></document><document><![CDATA[@javiercitocr @La_Lau17 Eso fue cosa de mi hermano que me las instaló en el Fire Stick. Machilla le puedo pasar los… https://t.co/somql2ea7P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimCarp00 “I need to tell you something later! " Seething swirls of conjecture in your brain until you finally fin… https://t.co/fkC35Ee779]]></document><document><![CDATA[signing probably the most important contract in my life today.. really happy to bring new music/touring later this year]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brianstelter CNN has no credibility, A Jeff Sessions spokesperson is gotta be a loser. CNN criticizes Trump 24-7,… https://t.co/aTUOO9H0xz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lilyfharris I've seen some fairly terrible pneumothoraces, hopefully time is all you need.]]></document><document><![CDATA[100% of what I post is for me God does over an abundantly more then I could ever ask for so...I know sharing is car… https://t.co/TdmJNhji2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[With all the false intel given over the years, it is not a surprise that some Americans are dubious of what they ar… https://t.co/atewwqKScS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@redrock_bball Josh, assuming Embiid is finally returns tomorrow, who should I drop to make the space to bring him… https://t.co/u8Cy2YLYjq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Countdown to St. Patrick's Day. Twice a day, I'll post images until 3/17...one photo of Chicago on St. Patrick's Da… https://t.co/b1qjcxRxT2]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hyde Sunset 📝 Guest List 🍾 Tables 📲 J.R. 818-281-5583 #HydeThursdays 🚨 @DJMarkDaSpot @DJBADMUSIC @ Hyde Sunset https://t.co/UjFmWMUP2Q]]></document><document><![CDATA[Pretty sure I saw @LonTayESPNCU at the @mshsathletics fieldhouse this evening!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NancyLeeGrahn Happy St. Valentine's Day Nancey :) also everyone to hope all have excellent day too with work plus much more tons also!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Ben_T_Johnson Totally!  I really learned a lot though, thanks for writing this. I posted in my beer group, who has… https://t.co/rGuUO3EPPP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Oh why not, another drone shot of the marshes. This was one of my first shots with the mavic about a month ago befo… https://t.co/HKyk9AVUm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CaptainMarvel is an okay film. Some interesting bits here and there. I wanted more time to get to know Carol. Brie… https://t.co/W7QTlXUbLW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anderllama @KornSports Normally really creative. Other times hellbent on plagiarism.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ltarsenal 10 mins into 2nd half saw me log onto BBC Sports to see if he'd been substituted at half time without me… https://t.co/Ra2eJwTCZ0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@antoinetteA Thankfully found and safe.  She should have let people know where she was especially in these troubled times.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@princesslyssa__ @stephbabbbby Depending on what your future hobby is it could help. 🤷‍♂️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@amyfadoolNBCS @TomCarpus Can’t have it both ways Amy. Load management is the big new term. They had been talking a… https://t.co/T314X4sn3n]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ray got a severe head injury when an Avis Bus 🚌 driver violated a major safety ⛑rule, by allowing Ray to get off th… https://t.co/rI2sSgY5DW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EricHolthaus Take a deep breath and imagine yourself here. https://t.co/t6Mi40ys6I]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday @TroyCalder I hope it’s better than this damn haircut! 😂 https://t.co/6HNzUUMNNB]]></document><document><![CDATA[#exercise #cycle #spin #FavoriteThisTweet #pride #fyre #mannequinchallenge #HTGAWM https://t.co/qVNgxupFJD]]></document><document><![CDATA[I would love to show you my #listing at 1616  New York #CapeMay #NJ  #realestate https://t.co/1iW7GjwpTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[Set out for a nice ride and got to link up with the boss! Thanks kyletransition for the motivation to push through… https://t.co/KVrCXsbKCD]]></document><document><![CDATA[@calbert57 A usted todo le parece mal o esta amargado  o nada mas opina porq no tiene nada mejor q decir]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls are straight weird, either tell me what you gotta say or don’t say it at all ... ?? Stupid. How old are we]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #CharlottesvilleVa City Council agenda for today’s meeting. I’ve been told many restauranteurs will be in atten… https://t.co/qUImop9lno]]></document><document><![CDATA[Haven’t seen Jasper but Harrison is not beating Castle or Reitz and Central not beating either of them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HZ_Skimom and I have been skiing a very long time, it’s our first passion. We get so excited to see “the girls” ta… https://t.co/t152V7ABt6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I might be biased, but I really like this teacher’s use of technology in the classroom! ☺️👩🏼‍🏫 @CyFairEdTech… https://t.co/zTkvKOKEv1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dbongino My biggest problem with the #GreenNewDeal: it will cover us in #WastedConstructionMaterials for the… https://t.co/eiHIJ4oF5j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TUHreek20 @Iamyourbrodie @BleacherReport he turned around because he knew that was going to be his last one 💔]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kris_Sacrebleu Tell me his slurred speech is not a symptom of chronic Adderal addiction!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Alejandroooo69 You literally NAILED it, that's government conditioning man. That's why it's important for people t… https://t.co/uN8MAit5PW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KyleBusch @NASCAR @GanderOutdoors @LVMotorSpeedway When is nascar going to pull their heads out their own asses th… https://t.co/Kh4whONJm4]]></document><document><![CDATA[“People aren’t looking for you to have it together.  People are looking at what happens to you when you don’t.” -… https://t.co/b7bvqlCUch]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LilMoochie_ That meat lovers omelette at kissin Cuzins ova anything from cracker barrel‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PonchoGodFather @Thisdayinsuck Are people this dumb? You realize this is weeks old right...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlysonPittman The thing is it’s so cringey looking back now but the music is still amazing?!?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Looking for a few “crazy women w dreams” who want to push the boundaries of what is acceptable. @SantaCruzPolice -… https://t.co/CT2NjLaXSV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sedesol era la caja chica y sus delegados los más corruptos: maestras de estancias infantiles https://t.co/mRPWL2rDfo]]></document></documents></author>