<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[McKenna Haughbook with a steal for Purcell Marian, leads to a step-back 3-pointer from Amil Ali-Shakir to give the… https://t.co/fUhICLSK8j]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BenningtonShow I wake up to “Beautiful Boy” every morning. It’s such a beautiful love song from his dad. ✌🏼💙🎶 https://t.co/NccM7iJJF7]]></document><document><![CDATA[because the Spirit intercedes for the saints according to the will of God. And we know that for those who love God… https://t.co/KMurz4hccT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DKizzy @JennyMcCarthy @TPAIN Him and the poodle were the only two i could never figure out]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m just trying to watch my tv shows but they took my damn website down i watch them on 😡😡]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DevineDestinyy @Arminies Yes just ignore the haters. Log off for a while. Meditate, pray, put on calming music. Breathe. Take care.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AshaRangappa_ Incredibly, it appears that he sees every human besides himself as disposable. Terrifying.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude dude dude don’t even ask me what brought on that migraine nightmare. I hadn’t even been watching horror movies… https://t.co/BuLROtPqbV]]></document><document><![CDATA[OH SHIT ITS THURSDAY THERES A NEW GREYS AND I JUST GOT CAUGHT UP THE OTHER DAY YASSSSSSS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm the exact goth fetish doll I wanted to be when I was in 7th grade. P.s. I'm getting paid for the things I was m… https://t.co/Who9eA5thO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wishing luck to my cousin Carolina, and my buddy Valeria and her partner!! HEY GUYS! WE'RE GOING TO DO GREAT!!… https://t.co/YChSmNg6T6]]></document><document><![CDATA[California, New York and 14 other states sue over Trump’s national emergency https://t.co/4aLyL3Rxhi via @NBCNews g… https://t.co/8JaL1dKi5z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@1168_845 @LindseyGrahamSC @BenSasse That isn’t what this is about. Get informed, Lib. 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🙏🙏🙏🙏]]></document><document><![CDATA[Something the news or anybody else won't show or make a documentary about... I don't condone any of this from anyon… https://t.co/oBYqyiTpDd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TopDogSweeps Prayers thank your family friends for following me cause I’m in the fade-away exit please thank you 😊]]></document><document><![CDATA[So annoyed the cat jumped on me &amp; pawed my right eye like 3 times last night and now I only have like half the lashes left 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jgsalazar93 I went to edc orlando in november solo and met up with someone i met on facebook and had the time of m… https://t.co/WBf9NQJEKy]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I tell Bash to go play with his toys.... He’s coachable 👏🏽🐶 https://t.co/wYYGh0PyFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[This doctor is trying so hard to take me out but I am not interested! He's my dads age no mames 😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bootcampworkout #6am and #7am @NoLimitsSports Come #letsgoworkout #tanksled #trx #bosu #dumbbells #spinning… https://t.co/3f0FFEpiQU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @CoryBooker can go to hell...  WE ARE THE GREATEST DAMN COUNTRY IN THE WORLD!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know I am getting old when the bar announced that karaoke was starting at 10 and the first thing out of my mouth… https://t.co/iquWwOTs1p]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cimarron_Ranch @AbbaDaddyFather Or the chicken Dance! I've started many Sunday mornings watching this activity...t… https://t.co/1pEV8u5JAl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maiamimi @Unconquerable I'm glad he is a MIA. That man is NOT right in the head! #DontMissBatshitCrazyRudy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TenRing2 @TRUMPARMY2020 @hrenee80 @MaureenShilaly @ThisisSabrina @LisaMei62 @Jami_USA @nolefan01 https://t.co/8f2KHIY3U4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wrong!!! Goddam you're wrong. That's inappropriate. Not to mention trumpy pants is high as a kite on Adderall.]]></document><document><![CDATA[If we’re together, it’s not a problem at all. But shit I barely know this man.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeirdreJones54 @jonathanchait McConnell is drawing up a bill &amp; putting it to vote.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KurtBusiek OMG. This explains my life:  "In fact, the formula may overestimate female metabolic rate by as much as… https://t.co/e9hoKuvK4i]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m trying to explain to wes that the Limbo (lambo limo) in Black Monday does not actually drive and every outside… https://t.co/7KK5ssQ4SC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Grande Entrance like a boss 🙌🏾🙌🏾❤️❤️ Amazing show. I still can’t believe i finally saw P!nk live. She getting my fu… https://t.co/Qjg8ryKjG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[i swear i need to just let my guard down and start dating, i’m starving over here but don’t want to get breakfast alone.. the struggle 😭🙄😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously contemplating taking a shower tonight because my legs are so sore from the gym it hurts to squat down.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MikeTay60703904 @Hope2Casagem @JRobertSeguin RWNJs always try to blame DEMs, but are sorely mistaken again. The Su… https://t.co/3k26fVic4V]]></document><document><![CDATA[@beileyarthur @christineh_58 @AOC Socialism is a world where you are a subject, not a citizen. Which is being tempt… https://t.co/VnXUajn5H4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please, you talk from both ends of your mouth. No one believes a word you say. What you say versus… https://t.co/bWIb9uFLpi]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watch me whip.... now watch me neigh neigh 🎶🦄🎶 . . . Catch us horsing around at @beyondwland again this year! See y… https://t.co/UxCDV9Kphp]]></document><document><![CDATA[👀 You are such a leader as this! @suegb1031 @Amy_Jones25 @nomoretwist @T_Outland @NNPSESL @nnpsstem… https://t.co/zJ1Upb1tzb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Had special plans for Valentines Day. Those fell through and now I’m just looking cute with no proof. 😤]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders @SenSanders Hello! Withdrawing your nomination would be nice but at the least, could you get your su… https://t.co/eSwqQQQviN]]></document><document><![CDATA[So glad I got to see you today AND eat at one of our favorite places ever!  @BlackWalnutCafe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Braves baseball up 7-0 top 5 with one out.  Girls softball up 3-2 bottom 5. Let’s go Braves!!  @JBaileySMSports… https://t.co/nDwsJmb82W]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RVAwonk @pookietooth Shit! How many chances is his entitled ass gonna get?!]]></document><document><![CDATA[if you see me out in public &amp; i don’t say hi mind ya business i’m blind]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Nunez_TenaflyPS @SteeleThoughts @johnfabbo Not you either @Nunez_TenaflyPS! Although never my principal, as a dist… https://t.co/m81o2PtOcH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@kaylabcrawford The fact themst he did it this morning while I sat in bed]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bagzyyy @MLBNetworkRadio @Jim_Duquette @StevePhillipsGM @rydonahue4 @Bharper3407 Not happening sorry]]></document><document><![CDATA[This will be interesting, the girls are helping some teams out today! Jess is playing for midget goal and shelby is… https://t.co/c4obl3mXNY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AreYaHavingThat @johnsharpson @SirLisaLevi @GirDraxa Miss you guys 👋🏻👋🏻👋🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[This is me after two consecutive nights of taking a spin class. Carry on—just pay no attention to me today. https://t.co/SXR5aRkmab]]></document><document><![CDATA[Great explanation for Kids and Adults too!!! Elmo should be a regular on The weather channel. 🎈😊🎈]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eric_pratt @WebInbound @jondick @HubSpot @TitosVodka Wait what? What session did I miss?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rn_critcare I understand.have been there. You need time to grieve and put things in a perspective that feels right… https://t.co/qmVGi1bBK1]]></document><document><![CDATA[me texting @ohbecs_  when im at a family event not fucking with any of those fake mfs :) https://t.co/o2ww8Djymr]]></document><document><![CDATA[You know the area you’re in is not popping when it takes 19 minutes for an Uber to come 🤦🏽‍♀️ #UberDiaries]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Coffee ☕️☕️☕️ (@ Nova’s Bed Room in wilmington, CA) https://t.co/0yprTyEbSD https://t.co/tve4zxsJwe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Funny Pictures Of The Day – 83 Pics #hilarity #laugh #grin #playful https://t.co/7WnwGmxN6o]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you're looking for work in #Oxnard, CA, check out this #security job via the link in our bio: Loss Prevention De… https://t.co/0QO1WyQHPH]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm a big rim rider. Give me a Jag I'm gone cut that bitch, give me a lambo im gone cut that bitch. The value went down when it left the lot]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annasproul @CasparSalmon Holy hell, I’m angry, and I haven’t even read it yet.]]></document><document><![CDATA[smdh at 16 year olds bragging about how they’re driving home drunk over 100mph. you ARENT cute]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WipeHomophobia Warning- telling me “Good Morning” may result in dismemberment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[that’s his adopted daughter....... and his wife..... two different people.... he’s still a fucking creep but getnur… https://t.co/2ttWttjsOw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Setting up my studio in the Center for Innovation in Teaching and Learning. More equipment coming.… https://t.co/mzMQ2ywKor]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KayzoMusic I hope I can give this to you one day!! Love you 💕 https://t.co/3k90C1VsXR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Show the Moving Parts Documentary in Milwaukee at Oriental Theatre challenge.]]></document><document><![CDATA[The #Moon is still gliding through the #AirSign of #Aquarius. ♒️ This Moon is a bit more detached. You see, it asks… https://t.co/dufVtpyFN1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akashhhhah20 Exactly and you know what I always tell people if you don't know what to do no one can help you pick… https://t.co/cXFvO4YYkb]]></document><document><![CDATA[😊 Chyna is being inducted into the WWE Hall of Fame alongside DX  https://t.co/PdfVuA0nvv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Somewhere on a beach... sipping something strong https://t.co/GLpNNpf2YN]]></document><document><![CDATA[My heart is broken. At a complete loss for words. @ St Anne's Nursing Center &amp; Residence https://t.co/IMT86KMcNU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EPotterUF @miel Becca (lol Baby Spice, sure) is the WORST. Who didn’t have a Becca in her seventh grade class?!?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bright side- I’m honestly looking forward to reading the inevitable “Iowa winter from hell” chapter in the upcoming… https://t.co/8pVrACIEDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@foxandfriends @RashidaTlaib @AOC Tlaibs apology was CRAP.  She didn't use his name but it was directed at him! Mak… https://t.co/83LSwmhI3g]]></document><document><![CDATA[God has a purpose for your pain. A reason or your struggle. A reward for your faithfulness!! TRUST HIM and NEVER give up!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sooo, I’m finally understanding a lot of things about how a lot of social events are naturally designed around alco… https://t.co/2z57zyeFxP]]></document><document><![CDATA[Taz is really amping up his street cred. He's been outside all weekend since lukes mom was here with her dog and he… https://t.co/nIDLgAyXxV]]></document><document><![CDATA[I decided to take my Kim and Ron dolls off the fridge and actually put them in my room because my sisters like to s… https://t.co/RusP6nqdBb]]></document><document><![CDATA[LINCOLN CO. EMERGENCY SHELTERS:  1. West End Baptist Church 200 Morgan Ave N, Fayetteville  931-433-1949  2. First… https://t.co/kBUhglNDpn]]></document><document><![CDATA[11 Clever IKEA Hacks That Will Make You Wonder Why You Hadn't Thought Of These Before  https://t.co/jBMwb1175j]]></document><document><![CDATA[My @instagram is doing so much off-the-wall shit right now, I’m legit about to call an exorcist.  #instagramdown]]></document><document><![CDATA[I get to see chase and pretend to laugh at his jokes all weekend I CANT WAIT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@oregonvirginia I hadn't seen that article. Thank you for sharing it with me! It's scary accurate 😳 As a kid, I use… https://t.co/NoSKAEd7xb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously, something is wrong with the liberal democrat society. They do exactly everything they claim the other si… https://t.co/gvlynJYkK4]]></document><document><![CDATA[Spent a cool $50 on Girl Scout cookies today... not the kind you smoke either. 🍪]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FeatStinky @Justice4Sgt @philadao Are you kidding?? What fucking morons! Then again, if you have no database, you… https://t.co/h2pTliyz0y]]></document><document><![CDATA[Can you recommend anyone for this job? Outpatient Registered Nurse - RN - https://t.co/ch23fg8DRt #nurselife #Gastonia, NC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Continued #IWD2019 #IWD #InternationalWomensDay2019 #feminism #equality #POC #TimesUp pt 3 https://t.co/TkZOpjq5R8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BxglL @72cricket @BurghPSUFaninPA @ChicagoPenguin2 @sannbs @MrsSpuds @CSonafelt @sharon_schwan @RidenerTina… https://t.co/Clq1tW9I03]]></document><document><![CDATA[facebook memories really likes to remind me I used to have some wack ass friends.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know to like trust the process or whatever but I don’t liiike it right now]]></document><document><![CDATA[Address Records Show Rep. Ilhan Omar Still Lived With Her First Husband Throughout Marriage To Her Apparent Brother… https://t.co/7N0M1SJ5Zp]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s literally been a while and it’s been such an off week not working out]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sometimes i get really sad that i experimented with drugs &amp; alcohol so young, there's nothing exciting to do anymore. Unless i do crack?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelPanico1 Love you, friend-o! More musics together this year please! 💌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Gabrielfmichael I'm not sure slipping someone drugs is all that legal. I hope the video doesn't cause trouble for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking popcorn out of a cup or glass: your hands stay clean, and you can still shovel large amounts of popcorn into your mouth at once ™️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Quick hug and hello ❤ papasanproperties @jaypapasan #Claire #KWSocialAmbassador #KWFR19 @ New Orleans, Louisiana https://t.co/TlCoT9Aheb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craftybettys Shameless. I just watched 8 seasons in about 2 weeks. 😂 and The Ranch was good too.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Four days into March and it still feels like we're in the polar vortex!  How does that house in Naples sound now?… https://t.co/ddlbyTzsmu]]></document></documents></author>