<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@Babchik do you remember the national news about the John list from Alexis Wright in Maine? She just kept releasing names!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@eliaswatama @MichaelGaree @dcpetterson @Douglasreber @kathrynresister @askboomer1949 You know….I just caught that… https://t.co/nOtYAeU3uN]]></document><document><![CDATA[A car jacking ends in Fenton with a suspect at large. Police are still searching. Jason Vogler, an Uber driver in t… https://t.co/CAyIohbqyO]]></document><document><![CDATA[Bill that caps public school students at 21yo and younger would close Gordon Bernell Charter School, which educates… https://t.co/duqJ9kdTfA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mburttram26 @BW_Jones 2011 for me. They did it against tougher competition imo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FergusFSU @DrewBMcMahon1 @Lead1225 Canada is doing more with less per citizen.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@spann glad we left a day early. Avalanche captured on video: Plume of snow covers cars on I-70 https://t.co/1YhqoYoIGD via @KDVR]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey @derekzigs I thought Manhattan was the best college town in the country?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @ecgirlsbb1 D-III District Champions after a 52-32 win over Lutheran East #LoCoGirlsHoops]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yo @Tess_Blanchard @TheTayaValkyrie great match. Absolutely loved it. #ImpactWrestling]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RUMINT79 @SenateGOP No wage increases was the pace for years. I’ve been given three in 2 years. Life’s a hell of a… https://t.co/twOma7QxUw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Ummm @thomasdrayton did you just go #MickeyMouse club on em?? “M I C, see ya real soon!” 😂😂 I love watching… https://t.co/S71ob80LZZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 I’ll consider donating after I hear what you say. If it’s the good, I’ll hook you up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@cody_fish21 I'm aware. Just would like a break from the snow for more than like 2 days.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@InsurgencyNQ Our weather people are almost right to the minute. rain at 11.00am to 12.00 pm .. that's when we get it]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here we go again! Make-A-Wish video shoot! One Dream - One Team #ConcordJH  #ConcordPride  #dreamsdocometrue… https://t.co/ocBPiAgDZj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mjhill1971 @JimmyMaloney1 @bucspens @K_Nett @AmberTussle @Pianomover @EdKrassen @cwhitaker1977 @realDonaldTrump Tr… https://t.co/few9vg7oSq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking  The Smiling Nut by @CigarCityBeer at @CigarCityBeer — https://t.co/JwQYkRKiIN]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm gonna make it... By any means necessary... Manifested in thoughts... #HUSTLE #GRIND #FOCUS @ Stuart, Florida https://t.co/gESSlkA3c4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not proud to say that I’ve missed Justin and am excited to have him back]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is it weird that I’m proud of this and I had nothing to do with the movie, obviously lol.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve accepted a challenge from @KDunn_MAMS to post covers of 7 books that I love. No explanations or reviews, just… https://t.co/NrUVNfJar5]]></document><document><![CDATA[Like I’ve seen people get angry over a lot of shit and just laughed it off, but the people upset over an #AmberAlert can fuck the fuck off.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dillzilla99 @DonaldODaniels1 @Lainyy626 @fritchee @george_capen I wasn’t thinking about Mexico in my scenario, alt… https://t.co/QIvWNZgEyg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NaoMobFanSquad @WrestlingInc He is obsessed with them too don’t matter if he with mella or cheating with her I’m n… https://t.co/Bc6Y6NMnOf]]></document><document><![CDATA[Perry High School principal and mother of student confront each other https://t.co/ODdEXCcqt8 via @azcentral This i… https://t.co/SKOAIMlXa5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ITsavvyLLC @FordMustang Very good run today. The finish is not a true reflection of how good the car actually was.… https://t.co/wlsOuBO5NB]]></document><document><![CDATA[Emphasis on “thus far” 😅 But that’s pretty incredible‼️ The 85th district is lucky to have the representative they… https://t.co/mxLJRTcVLe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hoooooy arranca la #J10CL2019, el famoso #ViernesBotanero, jornada de #ClasicoRegio en la @LIGABancomerMX... AJÚA!… https://t.co/PP1IUbwyGl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Good Lord, we truly are replaying evil's greatest hits of the 20th century.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Lyricoldrap You and your girlfriend to Come my birthday if you want to April 7 Sunday I be 30 ok Venice Florida]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like people in these videos pronounce the towns wrong on purpose, right?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TimDuy @mattyglesias @arindube @ModeledBehavior Talk about first world economic problems, debating if we are or aren't at full employment]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sookie is ready to party! #corgi #FatTuesday #MardiGras19 #dog https://t.co/34T9sPTn12]]></document><document><![CDATA[A night thought: My emotions and mindset were terrible today. They were out of place, like I’ve felt for a while. D… https://t.co/NoLFw4naRI]]></document><document><![CDATA[My beloved grandma would be so pleased that your grandma was impressed. Thank you much.]]></document><document><![CDATA[He needs to be put under the jail. In order to be that far behind on child support means he wasn't paying anything.]]></document><document><![CDATA[My twitter feed is ruined bc of The Jonas Brothers and the Kardashian’s]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chappiesinclair @BetoORourke And so many of us were Sheldon Brown devotees, so I have to paste a link to his writi… https://t.co/qpOFtXXTFO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bballbreakdown Oh yeah. That’s on them. However, there’s a human element here and I think many don’t see that side… https://t.co/yLEiCJV3L0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Stop_Trump20 I believe him and believe he is remorseful. That excuses nothing he did but he is working to make it… https://t.co/yCLJhR6pS4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KLGLASS2 Over, unless you have cats that have access to your bathroom then under so they can't unspool it.]]></document><document><![CDATA[House of Blues. Las Vegas,Nevada.. tonight 8pm with @TheSadies opening for Kurt Vile &amp; The Violators https://t.co/AduYPoxBzN]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Investigate them ,tax returns and https://t.co/rJfsHqlECH what they do to you you need to shitslif… https://t.co/yFI1qUS3Dp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guys will only wash their hair at their girlfriend’s place just so they don’t have to buy shampoo.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IanHathaway Do you evenly equate tax subsidies on future income and direct monetary injections or other types of m… https://t.co/6YPos3YCDL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TerriBraves If you make this your campaign platform, I'll vote for you.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thanks to @ALSCanada for a productive meeting at Queen’s Park on ways we can work together to make life easier for… https://t.co/scBk5RN5jw]]></document><document><![CDATA[Moun fou kouwem Map marye la, men se patqp on ayisyèn vre Pa gon ayisyèn kap pran risk lanmor sa pou maryaj 😂😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ATP_Tour @rogerfederer Let’s get it done tomorrow Roger !!!  You are the greatest !!!!!!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoredStiff415 @bryconmusic The devil see's you coming back around and wants to dance. I got four pounds of, Someth… https://t.co/ZOQoUFHATl]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy International Women's Day  💖 may the men  protect her, love her, marry her, but most importantly respect her.… https://t.co/tkcHseQfAk]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of these guys for 5 mil subs. Also gotta try to win some merch 👌]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ananabanana @TheJackalopeTX @__itsmev I did think of @TheJackalopeTX because there is such a jump from *NSYNC spac… https://t.co/rGHzkPg5Qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump The only way tRUMP is defending us at the . sourthern boarder is with his lies, no wall… https://t.co/yh8yYnA3wd]]></document><document><![CDATA[Some Unicorn Tears by @sadboyeliquid ....have you guessed the flavor yet??? 😂 #sadboyprospect #vapesadness #unicorn… https://t.co/MwHcJWGDox]]></document><document><![CDATA[Final ⚾️: #OleMiss 15 - Arkansas State 3  #RebsBSB totaled 19 hits in this one, their most since May 2016]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealKyleMorris  from a bartender to a congresswoman in New York wow all I can say and I've said it before thank you very much New York]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m really trying to love again, but these women be acting like girls smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[Time to get the stitches out!   #movinghurts #carefulwiththeboxcutters @longstclinic]]></document><document><![CDATA[I stopped by this awesome office a few weeks back, and will be looking to staff a Mobile systems Engineer there. We… https://t.co/ZH04TAmj4M]]></document><document><![CDATA[Join @JeffGriesch &amp; me for @huskerswbb at Maryland 6:45 p.m. (central) today on @HuskerSports Network &amp;… https://t.co/810eW28sUM]]></document><document><![CDATA[#KindredSpirits time @amybruni @AdamJBerry Let’s see what strange things happen tonight?.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy 41st Birthday, @ATeamMarketing @ The Lowe Escape https://t.co/qwAY6uOjUA]]></document><document><![CDATA[#marchmeetthemaker — story behind my name — my last name Nuara is a #sicilian last name — my #greatgrandfather immi… https://t.co/oLL7XZuLGn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AlanDersh Something's happened to you.  Problem is, I don't know what it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Mexico sure believes in border protection.... Mexican customs- 3 hour wait per a friend https://t.co/KQfQ4sk8Sp]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottLeisz @USATODAY The fact that a pardon is possible says a ton about the problems with our constitution.]]></document><document><![CDATA[At the end of Britney Spears’ “Toxic” video when she winks at the camera is it because it was all a dream or is something else going on?]]></document><document><![CDATA[How fucking sacred is @WWE of their superstars leaving for @AEWrestling  when you can drunk drive, fight a cop and… https://t.co/clRGIRvmt1]]></document><document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Desert Vista boys volleyball team. Finished 9th overall in the Best of the West tournament i… https://t.co/NQZECUTtn2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC I STARTED FLYING TO CANADA IN 1968 AND EVERY YEAR UNTIL 1973 , FIRST COUPLE OF YEARS WE HAD TO MAKE 2 STOPS AN… https://t.co/P3u4vIhNFR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PartialCreditEd Jordan is right. Jesse is the new Q https://t.co/QuVHBGxwMX]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks the dad from Friday. Nobody go in the bathroom for about 35-45 minutes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@aerod1011 Of course i support diversity sweetie i just don’t think it should be considered to influence any decisi… https://t.co/mDcBjaNjvo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Chicago. Truly thankful to be a lifelong resident of this city.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SnottieDrippen That’s just stupid. Even at my work gym I lock my shit up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PatGallenCBS3 @PatGallenCBS3 look to the 1980-1981 calendar year, w/Sixers a top team in NBA, Eagles in the Super… https://t.co/oPUdRUseqZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy to be attending #high5conf this week in downtown Raleigh. This Monday speaker lineup is fantastic! #marketing… https://t.co/VToVM4Ps56]]></document><document><![CDATA[Drinking an Even More Jesus by @EvilTwinBrewing at @McGregorsCBW — https://t.co/s41dLNltHt]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CtCathCorner @FergusFSU @PureSpew @Eschatologuy It is highly unlikely that Peter ever preached in Rome. Bible does… https://t.co/kOlS00mwqT]]></document><document><![CDATA[GOOD MORNING INSTAFACEBOOGERS @ Farmington, New Mexico https://t.co/4z9FKjFBa8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hidroituango  Como @petrogustavo  Ver / #Hidroituango  Como Realmente eres. https://t.co/OwRjZXsjyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice job @NASCARONFOX . . can't even interview @RyanSiegRacing . . pathetic]]></document><document><![CDATA[This looks incredible. Can’t wait to revisit this strange lovely game. ❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Heading to work (at @CTA - Wilson in Chicago, IL) https://t.co/AYZwGRKJj3]]></document><document><![CDATA[My friend deleted her social media and now I have one less person I can share memes with.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bellahelix And it’s absolutely okay to doubt, just don’t let it consume you to the point you don’t take anymore ch… https://t.co/9PN3iwJllB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KatrinaPierson Republicans are idiots that don’t believe in science, how can a delusional jerk like Rep Gomhert be… https://t.co/xuucz4aVDD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#patriots #Pats #patsnation #patriotsnation #newenglandpatriots #newengland @ United States https://t.co/68DUSLkHXm]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DCPoliceDept Why did Officers Brown and Thermidor bully and detain a pregnant teen without even reading her rights… https://t.co/xxl7X0GFtA]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IslesRealist Their cap is a nightmare. They knew they couldn’t afford to tag him. They were blowing it up go all t… https://t.co/cBewxElzIK]]></document><document><![CDATA[Canadiens at Rangers preview Sent with @NHL #rangers #nyr  https://t.co/9y9wWTJQaR]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t start working out for the summer until actual spring cause this weather right now still gonna have me eating like a piece of shit 😩😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[. @lightfootforchi holds a press conference to discuss opposition to Rep. @RobertMartwick's bill to make the… https://t.co/t7anpyKWNe]]></document><document><![CDATA[Its been a journey and it's been a battle....but this special woman, @mamadeleon49  has done it!  I told you… https://t.co/abeVotLX3K]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously tho, if Sixers manage that game better at the end/JJ isn’t ice cold, they probably win and sweep the seas… https://t.co/smgawWKmFn]]></document><document><![CDATA[So proud of my students who were inducted last night! Keep up the great work!!!… https://t.co/SLs9WPvFVP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RadioW9LW I absolutely agree! I wish every producer would dedicate extra time for that - but unfortunately some do… https://t.co/vasZk3f2wg]]></document><document><![CDATA[#wooemmawatson I have calmed down a lot since that last chain of brain cysts went.  I think you have your life toge… https://t.co/BAv7V5Xcf7]]></document></documents></author>