<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Crazy girls get married too, @TheCartelMatt. Don’t hate on the Jackholes. #WhatILearnedToday #WeAreCartel @RealRonPhillips]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MindyGiddiens @acakes421 I have to agree with Mindy. You need to weigh all your options.  Especially with a child.… https://t.co/VgCcNacgPF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Jackie Shane, Toronto's pioneering transgender soul singer, dead at 78 | CBC News https://t.co/YOQCxnKWON REST IN POWER.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Successful 1st Family #STEAM Night! Thanks to everyone who volunteered to help make it possible. @EESMaher… https://t.co/nUYsIDISEp]]></document><document><![CDATA[Everyone gets reminded of their past,one way or the other..... It’s how you’re willing to react/go forward.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump LOL you got less with this deal than you would have before you shut down the govt. SO much for bei… https://t.co/Nh2fS728gR]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my favorite gifts a student has made for me.  Not only is it amazingly beautiful but the time and love that… https://t.co/UsXViyhZfM]]></document><document><![CDATA[Even #massage #therapists have to #workout after we've worked on you! #bodytek #fitness #friday #bigbearlake… https://t.co/8BKIdA7na1]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wish I had a nigga mindset when it came to birthdays lol like meh whatever]]></document><document><![CDATA[👏👏👏we got sound boxes coming to our room to help with apps like @Seesaw @Flipgrid and @Microsoft arc, thanks… https://t.co/awaqZCLrzZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RashidaTlaib Just because a family member married and has children with a person of color....has no bearing on you… https://t.co/XwG24y5XCs]]></document><document><![CDATA[@pacelattin @ClarkCountySch @VitalVegas @FOX5Vegas Call every damn child service agency that you can report to. This is child abuse!!👿👿👿]]></document><document><![CDATA[Doctors don’t know what’s wrong anymore but they love to show each other how wild it is.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LaNoviaEnojada Ver por el antes que a mi misma. Y creer todo lo que me decía]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Punch and Judy, Alameda and Rose Parade by Elliott Smith]]></document><document><![CDATA[Who wins today's battle.. Beet 🍅 or Kale 🌿? 👀👉@BProlifestyle #OrganicSkincare #GoVegan #GlowRecipe @glowrecipe • •… https://t.co/eX6EqGFEPT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dimitri11192 @davepperlmutter @stephen_ainley @eddie_author @JEvansthewriter @TudorTweep @VodkaWardrobe… https://t.co/f5WZaaLzNn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Being projectile vomited on immediately after I get out of the shower is something I’ll never get used to.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@h8Wankmaggot45 I understand we have detention facilities for "undesirables" in Arizona...]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DrPol @DrEmilyThomas thoroughly enjoyed tonight’s episode &amp; Dr Brenda &amp; Dr Nicole were awesome as everyone is! @natgeowild]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump 10 years lying for you, covering your ass with Stormy and whoever else you screwed, lying on loan… https://t.co/za660BFlgI]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s here!! make a #SPLASH 🧜🏻‍♀️  Swipe 👈 to see how to #paint with #intention and #lanzalove . . . #salon… https://t.co/wis7oDMlzX]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Keanu is very conservative in his thoughts. For 20 years. Same beliefs. Same style. Same jacket. Same gaze. (We bo… https://t.co/hyG52lvGSj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JosephineCruz5 @marklevinshow They don’t care about other’s offspring only their own who hate just as they do. Rad… https://t.co/D6gOxJiwsT]]></document><document><![CDATA[my Uber tonight: a Range Rover driven by a hedge fund owner, and my co-riders consist of a first year med student a… https://t.co/SXX7eceSBx]]></document><document><![CDATA[@NBCPolitics @MSNBC @frankthorp How juvenile.  Then again, it’s Republicans.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@frogpondRN @MAGAforc @PrimeCreator2 @AboveTheBurgh @HeARTofGod99 @2newearth777 @davidsodell @tee10202 @WILLOWOOD2… https://t.co/rlN8G45zxd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@QTAnon1 LOL You better hope she doesn't get even!! better have a back up plan 🙂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_SJPeace_ @linablue This is nyc at its finest I give money to homeless and when they have pets I give more my hear… https://t.co/Ya9RxMS6qz]]></document><document><![CDATA[On top of being a sexual predator, Robert is actually not that smart. Like, at all. #rkellyinterview]]></document><document><![CDATA[A real friend gone tell you what you need to hear regardless if you want to hear it or not🗣‼️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@EveLambka and @lambka305 getting a bird's eye view @UniversityAir Thank you Larry! https://t.co/MBgrwvOo0b]]></document><document><![CDATA[Watching Tucker tonight was like watching the Superbowl, who can afford the commercials? @FoxNews]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy #internationalwomensday! May we, raise, empower and lift up strong women everywhere. 👭 @oiselle #oiselle… https://t.co/cEa63pvkNZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@whaddupmads OMG too funny! I saw him and how excited he was! This will definitely be us in August!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheAutry very interesting and fun, I will be back. https://t.co/cDBdPBdMh3]]></document><document><![CDATA[I love when I see a pop of color in homes! 💚💖 Although I tend to always play it safe and neutral with my own home’s… https://t.co/6VpMRGZkIQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IJefTomI @peterdaou If you don't grow up people like you will be responsible for another 4 years of trump; Hillary… https://t.co/E8hE2luL5A]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Chantilly #Virginia chocolate 🍫 ! Made in Chantilly! 👍. #BeantoBar #DirectTrade #SocialImpact… https://t.co/jLAYkp9fd5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GobAbiertoBOL @realDonaldTrump ...WHAT PLANET DO YOU COME FROM?????  FORGOT THE 2008 FINANTIAL 'CRISIS'..CREATED B… https://t.co/rPh6DMTBwO]]></document><document><![CDATA[I bought a 2x and I feel like it’s gonna be too big and then I’m gonna be shit outta luck]]></document><document><![CDATA[#bekind #kindnesscampaign #teachersoinstagram #noexcusesuniversity #iteach #bethechange #teacherlife… https://t.co/nXhPBhFMjS]]></document><document><![CDATA[I could be wrong, but I'm PRETTY sure I just saw the tooth fairy visiting a certain six year old that lost his fron… https://t.co/pra6m4hMis]]></document><document><![CDATA[@phil500 Quit my job springs to mind, but maybe get a financial adviser first]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HayleyMAmoss @SerengetiEmp1 @fairgroundsnola @TomAmossRacing @GJoelpoliti @ChurchillDowns So baller!!! 🔥🔥🔥]]></document><document><![CDATA[@chuckyoutwo @bentev28 Are you from Houston? Sorry...my kid may have taught him that. 🤦🏻‍♀️🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you look like a stupid puppet showing your adoration for a brutal dictator.  How embarrassing that… https://t.co/KadGdgu819]]></document><document><![CDATA[@WSWS_Updates @AbbyMartin @D_A_G_Chaos Oh oh, someone over at wsws likes to moonwalk. lmao. The real question is,… https://t.co/BTsZJpMFyR]]></document><document><![CDATA[IN YOU ARE HONEST...the NFL has lost so much money they did pay Kaepernick because he was right, they paid to put t… https://t.co/JqEUounnSd]]></document><document><![CDATA[People that inflict fear or pain on themselves even on small scales are more likely to be masochists.   So the part… https://t.co/8UCRvvLm9u]]></document><document><![CDATA[So thankful DukeTip afforded my daughter a chance to take the ACT in middle school. Looking at her scores this morn… https://t.co/hwrn92Ibih]]></document><document><![CDATA[Hey,  Take Your Favourite Gift Card Offer By A Complete Simple Sign Up      Click Here: https://t.co/y2UazxBM5p… https://t.co/6Az68m5mS7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danivargas_x @c_drew_ Lmao yessss in a heart beat!!! Ain’t no one interfering with my sleep 😂😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[The opinion piece of mine appeared in the March 8th edition of "Greater Kashmir" as well:  https://t.co/EvRv6LdPfZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@heytheredelida It’s okay WV can print out 17 year old ID’s in 30 seconds for $5 😌]]></document><document><![CDATA[RIGHT NOW: Water is rising fast and inching closer to homes in part of north Fulton County. @SteveGWSB has LIVE upd… https://t.co/ZcAKnYy7Ve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@lasanalfabetas 🖤nuestra analfabeta de ésta sale ilustrada y con los deditos echando humo👏🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@abc7george Oh boo...sorry to hear that. My very first favorite boy band!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[To @DAVEYSUICIDE, @nikogemini, @derekobscura &amp; @stitcheddrummer: Good times this wkend in B-More at the… https://t.co/C6QV29rgYn]]></document><document><![CDATA[James and Giant Peach. Indian Creek High School https://t.co/1b2ihTApzW]]></document><document><![CDATA[Is that because they’re black and most physicians don’t believe black people are in pain when they report it or is… https://t.co/XOUGmla6nR]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thickhoney4u Yes, it should be retired in all its fragrant glory. It gets no better.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dude to the right look like he hating. Lol. But yesssssss Queen 👑 better show off that black excellence!]]></document><document><![CDATA[I hate working late, I don’t get to see the babies when I get home b/c they’re in bed 😩😩]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy Mardi Gras 💜💚💛  • Leg warmers jakoboutique  •  Shirt: makeyourselfgreat_llc  • Mardi Gras 2019 • •… https://t.co/fUc7jLLOq7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wey me enamore de la manera en la cual una compañera explicó un tema. 😍]]></document><document><![CDATA[My cousin is going to Washington in 2 weeks and I’m so excited for her. I’m letting her borrow all my clothes and s… https://t.co/TluNbeOUDu]]></document><document><![CDATA[The field is wasted, the land mourneth; for the corn is wasted: the new wine is dried up, the oil languisheth. https://t.co/o1tZjCQGOk]]></document><document><![CDATA[did not a GM plant close just today in Ohio and with it 1,700 jobs @cspanwj]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zerocutster_AK @ZaibatsuNews I did not interpret the encounter that way.  What was there stated purpose?  To prese… https://t.co/ZYEVHb71y3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KathrynAnnette Julia Roberts dress was gorgeous the bright pink was 🔥.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#MSNBC Look, people will want Joe Biden until they don’t! When GOP brings out past campaign baggage like plagiarism… https://t.co/ABeGjsncUy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true! I got to teach my first class @CCofLeawood https://t.co/E28OHFflOH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Shot from yesterday at Snoqualmie. Beautiful day for riding!  🏂 🏂 🏂 #weekdaygetaway #seattle #washington… https://t.co/FBuiFdftDg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@myerschrisj Which is why I can say with all honesty that I have it all ⚡️💛✊]]></document><document><![CDATA[@robweir Haha I have literally read nothing about this going in, my pop culture knowledge is...bad]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_badgirlrere this is why i won’t come over when @realjavivillar cooks🤷🏻‍♀️😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nice time at jazztrotters sold out show Valentine’s Day at Giardino’s @ Giardino Italian Restaurant https://t.co/OWIn2uCCU3]]></document><document><![CDATA[@BoomerGal65 @ProudResister @rkelly @GayleKing Sorry that you can't see excellence when it's presented]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of my biggest fears is someone taking my baby from me in the future.... I’ll go crazy on everyone.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tschromehinge @realP_A_HAS @onlyPAH You condescending prick! Are you saying that black ppl cant get IDs? They are… https://t.co/kyxoCoSbPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@E_ShaManagement @IGotPeace @impettyasfuck @500Ells I swear I will be all the way done if they mess this up.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Invest in yourself! Shop @battlevoguelove EVERYTHING $10 and under at pop-up location. DM for details! ❤️ @ Northea… https://t.co/SVBIVvJpGj]]></document><document><![CDATA[More Sasha photos from Monday #february25th2019 #sashathevolvo #mycar #volvov70 #volvo #volvowagon… https://t.co/QtcrhCU1vv]]></document><document><![CDATA[“This would make sense that queer and trans people are more at risk of transmitting STI’s and even getting pregnant… https://t.co/tme4dLC734]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Debbiefit45 @loseit it! It’s an app that allows me to count calories, carbs etc. no diet really. I should cut all… https://t.co/SSGhqYCaE8]]></document><document><![CDATA[I was honored and privileged to be in Prof. Powers 1st year Torts class. He was one of my favorite profs at… https://t.co/2ud5LViIZl]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_monzon322 @strom_annette @L_ei8ht @brandon7nettles @tpcowgurl @Cha51brolll19 @ruthlesswench @Blabla79021362… https://t.co/qlfYDEY8EQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[My family and I were out at dinner one night this past week. It wasn't real late, in fact it was early evening. We… https://t.co/jJDUiO3BPE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@GrittyNHL will you be my valentine? If you’re unavailable I’ll just move on to Carter Hart @NHLFlyers]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really need a taco or two or ten.   The kind you eat.   Urgh.   A Mexican one not a pink one.  Urgh.  You know what I mean.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm with you. Can't believe we still have that a##%%le around to deal with. Was that all Russian money he raised. W… https://t.co/NqwTmZ9uY9]]></document><document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a new show to watch and you have Amazon Prime I would suggest Sneaky Pete]]></document><document><![CDATA[S1: I can’t wait to do the Disney project in math S2: That’s on our economics playlist in reading S1: Wait, is it?… https://t.co/ZcdY6gysGG]]></document><document><![CDATA[Meagan really just asked what water taste like. Bitch do I look like a water expert to u ???]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just hope everyone who celebrated #InternationalWomansDay2019 remembers to keep that shit intersectional and incl… https://t.co/L44uYqJBU1]]></document><document><![CDATA[@elonmusk : good morning Elon. "Elon Musk says @Tesla won't be getting involved with #cryptocurrency". #investors… https://t.co/g9XqTXZWSY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Trying to be healthy is so hard because all I want to eat is hot fries and takis 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wearing a “crop top” (sort of) to work on #FatTuesday is the type of body confidence I need everyday. https://t.co/AtvTsH5Pw2]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ChatByCC @realDonaldTrump No the MAJORITY of AMERICANS want to know the TRUTH! Obviously the president doesn’t kno… https://t.co/dcKG1cVoPs]]></document></documents></author>