<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[I feel like this is dangerous but I also don’t think anyone cares. https://t.co/RmAF3LN6vu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Nothing about MIKEY really worries him, says SPENCE. Mikey is "traditional" and he's seen the style in the gym.  "I… https://t.co/FsKl0sLsm5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DraftNetworkLLC Deshaun Watson, LaMichael James, Michael Crabtree, Tavon Austin]]></document><document><![CDATA[One of superhuman’s clever tricks is making you feel cool using the keyboard shortcuts that gmail already has]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why am I still with @bulbenergy after a few years? Well, apart from the fact that they are renewable, they also dro… https://t.co/7NKC9nMPjB]]></document><document><![CDATA[when you’re tired, but you can’t stop reading...how i feel about black on both sides]]></document><document><![CDATA[@markpoloncarz @NACoTweets @markpoloncarz where is the large painting located behind you? Looked up some of the art… https://t.co/JNSCwdgz18]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ El Segundo Beach Los Angeles California https://t.co/Q7RN90vPbz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamaicaMadeMe And the thing is they could have kept the email private and asked nicely for a change if it bothered… https://t.co/dqWvaz2Z4X]]></document><document><![CDATA[we all want some mirth. #hilarity #lol #grin #clever https://t.co/fxl5p5eMyn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Well I watched Won’t you be my neighbor and didn’t think I’d tear up. Boy was I wrong. What a special human we were… https://t.co/NCy4ZC2ZGO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TAMPAHDGROUP I would look 👀 really good riding this Harley Davison motorcycle ride on! 🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🇺🇸🦂✌️]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VntgSprintCars Dang, Now that I didn’t remember.... I forget which year (mid 90’s) we were out and Shaffer, Rahmer… https://t.co/jZBsjW8oM4]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IronCobra انا مجاليش اي حاجة عالبيت ، بس المكالمة دي ، و اول ما جت افتكرت حوارات مصر و التايم شير قلت اسألك]]></document><document><![CDATA[Random : You like sublime,? Name five songs. And can’t be Santeria ! Me:  First of all Santeria isn’t in my top 10]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sierra_rebecca @atticsonline @AOC Lol let me guess.  The ny er.  Or rolling stone.  Why dont u take a drive into n… https://t.co/utVgWpOdcM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@steven_brunn @thenfbc I’ve talked myself out of Greinke last couple of seasons and seem to be doing that again. Bu… https://t.co/3WsAWuc4m9]]></document><document><![CDATA[President @realDonaldTrump  please dont let china eat our lunch. https://t.co/VXYl7X0F30]]></document><document><![CDATA[Sending out positive messages to my loves this morning! Remember that a new day is a great way to have a fresh start 🌞]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sharrnat @HIGHMOONMovie @seanflanery @ridgwayj10 @MissEdmundson 🤠👊🏼👊🏼👊🏼]]></document><document><![CDATA[california new york california state contiguous to new york california carolina! state contiguous to new york new y… https://t.co/tPJMHTVeIh]]></document><document><![CDATA[With my thanks to @OutdoorEyes, please support those who support independent music. Have a listen...]]></document><document><![CDATA[🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣 laughing all the way to the Bank. @ Manhattan, New York https://t.co/Z9hnrJE08m]]></document><document><![CDATA[Music playing mood. 🎹 @ The Standard, Downtown LA https://t.co/s3TuzZ3FUv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to see the first bluebonnets of season at the Washington-on-the-Brazos State Park last Saturday! Five varieties… https://t.co/CKtCWUbE66]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TomDegenerate He cost them three games. Two in the regular season (would have given them the bye week) and then th… https://t.co/f495s9lQKE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SpeakerPelosi @carlosvecchio The Maduro Regime is capable of anything at this stage. From hiring armed thugs, to u… https://t.co/y01CgFvgkZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[When I’m sick, I just remind myself the devil just giving mee a taste of what’s to come.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@danclayt0n Aggressive on defense I mean. They havent attacked the paint much on offense]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning!!  Have alot to be thankful for!!!  Have a great day Twitter family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IsraelUSAforevr Clearly, you’re wrong about the President and his base. Aren’t you hold up in Sweden or somewhere. 🤔🤔]]></document><document><![CDATA[I started texting my friends that sports is just a game and that there’s more to life than Ku basketball. I need to… https://t.co/XYFIoJydIn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HunterBadger87 So this guy not only has terrible taste in music but also can’t get the facts straight? Sounds like… https://t.co/23Ry0VZgvs]]></document><document><![CDATA[i'm off to get stuff in grocery store or something like 1.  if you are also on facebook, can you give them the mess… https://t.co/17AKplI5th]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LissetteCBS4 @CBSMiami Weather Wonder Woman 👀’s like you will be a busy beaver with your Forecasts, The ducks 🦆 will be 🎯🤗🇺🇸]]></document><document><![CDATA[Devni on moun yo ka renmen , pase tan kote l e menm gen konvèsasyon san fen 😉 . Rès la , lòt moun nan ki pou reyali… https://t.co/A2ZoLrXG2B]]></document><document><![CDATA[One day someone’s going to research Wareka Deli and see all of my tweets lmao]]></document><document><![CDATA[Wow. Received a campaign funding request from @JohnCornyn touting receiving the endorsement of the president. That… https://t.co/1x81fwOreo]]></document><document><![CDATA[Umberto Eco to the rescue (on the principles of emergence fascism), re: @jordanbpeterson #JordanBPeterson -… https://t.co/LLX9ZxMIvy]]></document><document><![CDATA[Back squat 420 @ 175 Lbs. #fridayworkout #progress #dontskiplegday @ The Summit https://t.co/kqBJ2UMDOj]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm at ADESA Charlotte - @adesaauction in Charlotte, NC https://t.co/8CxZLwrE7k]]></document><document><![CDATA[@anacedragon @Giggler_R @BrianWFoster @samriegel @WillingBlam @Marisha_Ray @matthewmercer @LauraBaileyVO… https://t.co/EwtREY7IG4]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m not really fond of her, but I voted for her... she was right about Trump. 100%]]></document><document><![CDATA[First port of many 🌎 @ Port Newark–Elizabeth Marine Terminal https://t.co/v21zzwIiBC]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AnnBroo32097973 @hoppinmama5 @TaxCreditdotbiz @TheSteveKon @LuckiestMermaid @Lathenerd @gator4kb18 @because93… https://t.co/Cr6EZIGAsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@sebastianbach I’ll be at the Saturday show ! Will you do a meet and greet ? Met you last summer with my GF at the… https://t.co/merr75pUm7]]></document><document><![CDATA[@vinson44718631 @SeanTPendergast Texas and OU run the show. And they're constantly mentioned as having a wandering… https://t.co/65mEbXOQlb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tucker is an asswipe and flushable.  Fire Tucker. #firetucker #foxnewsSucks #foxnewsfordummies]]></document><document><![CDATA[Connecticut hosts Buffalo and Boston hosts Minnesota next Saturday night. Connecticut hosts Minnesota and the Rivet… https://t.co/7NSlmsEhaW]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mdressbcps @LochRavenAcad @Mrs_StaceyJ I voted.  So hard to choose, they are so amazing!]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Proudteacher moment: In analyzing the milieu of Divergent, one of my freshmen drew a connection to the Outsiders:… https://t.co/snfLIuuMhi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RepGosar just like the rest of the @GOP congressmen can only testify themselves instead of asking @MichaelCohen212… https://t.co/dTKtmHqKLo]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just finished running 6.33 miles in 1h:21m:12s with #Endomondo #endorphins https://t.co/zZKebsWqHB]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JamesAFrazier can we get some z nation cast for Chicago please !!!!!! Here are some people u could invite… https://t.co/KQnAGj1NJb]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KellyTownsend11 You are so wrong about vaccines that I suggest you go back to school and take some science courses! Just stop now!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Birthday beers with Vic. - Drinking an Emerald Heart by @rustyrailbrewco @ G Lounge  — https://t.co/4KsVtifBwM]]></document><document><![CDATA[You think there are no actual violations of the law?  What is everybody around you going to jail for then?  Do you… https://t.co/oJP0fCa88B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Went to williamsbridge station first, came back to Chelsea then went to village station, now I’m at radio city stat… https://t.co/JsWY9N50Zx]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Oscar Predictions (Who I think will win not who I want to win.) https://t.co/6wS2Px2qyq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MaeveReston @KamalaHarris @alivitali I think it’s more carnival colors than rainbow. So Mardi Gras is a perfect fit]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MissCindrich Live and learn, you are helping the elephants now and that is what counts!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Without the rule of law or checks and balances, democracy is dead and we are living in an authoritarian state. Full… https://t.co/RZhMasxsGF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AP My fiancé convinced me part of being an adult was throwing out all those old taco sauce packets. Are you tellin… https://t.co/RrHucBXo4H]]></document><document><![CDATA[Damn we really about to lose an hour of sleep this weekend due to daylight savings and idk about y’all but I can’t afford to lose that hour.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Griz @jvn @matisyahu I've hated the violence that gin and whiskey have caused.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DickersonESPN Very sorry for your loss, prayers to you and your family.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Life goal: Make enough money to pay people to pack and move my shit for me.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Mets @jessmendoza So, she is going to still be doing Sunday night baseball?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jonbecker_ @mlbdepthcharts No questions but happy to hear this is happening. Let us know when it hits iTunes.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@FakeBlueCrew He is my 2nd favorite BE coach but he made a big fashion mistake with that look. Wow.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@billdollins at least that would take out a percentage every time the contents of a cell passed over another cell]]></document><document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to my lil funny big head cousin 😂 love you family✊🏾 https://t.co/rvEXi4bwaq]]></document><document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is up against truth,  a sobering reality he's never had to face before in his life.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I know Minnesota is the land of 10,000 lakes, but with the rain Tennessee is getting, we will catch up or be 1 big… https://t.co/k5uYswloGU]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lovely! Old Louisville. Louisville, Kentucky. February 15, 2019. @ Old Louisville https://t.co/ZZNXVwLBoE]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank You 4 the Light (Story), a song by PhillyBlunt2000 on Spotify https://t.co/tjLD4RKeox @ Muzic Empire "You Hea… https://t.co/hEJFwKUYEm]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dont stop. Never stop. As long as im able to stream, i will. People drive me to the next level and free my creative… https://t.co/RgdW8NksTz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@taylorburrowes That is why I chose to shy away from relationships and sex.  I have neither the inclination or the… https://t.co/9PzZ6Bi4Ar]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CardpocalypseNC many thanks sir. Sending ttm out Monday https://t.co/cqpJQrgD9Z]]></document><document><![CDATA[My Houston Texas vacation! #Vacation #Houston #RunningAwayFromWinter @ Houston, Texas https://t.co/bYDy45VqkT]]></document><document><![CDATA[2 seconds round picks. If that’s not enough lob in that second first round pick and get that mofo in GB with AR12💯✅💰]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_syydd @traeyoungtime @TheTraeYoung Shhhh don’t wake up the Luka trolls 🤫😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[A big shot out to our Kearny Strong and 2xx times Wrestling State Champ Jacob Cardenas. Coach Tony Maritza Carratur… https://t.co/CWCn3rRymQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[# Keep America Grate! POTS Trump is evrey God fearing Americans Presedent... Temp:Crab Orchard, Ky.:45.5°F]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ABM_paints @OntarioNDP Furthermore, there is a reason why homeschooling and private schools have been on the rise… https://t.co/Lc7IdLJkQF]]></document><document><![CDATA[Incrementalism...plain and simple.  A little bit this year, some more encroachment next year, yada yada. Cali deser… https://t.co/JTlh0CwPCn]]></document><document><![CDATA[Baseball Bottom of the 5th St Paul 13, La Habra 2 @SGVNSports @ocvarsity]]></document><document><![CDATA[Tough trip to North Dakota for both the Morningside College women's (https://t.co/EcMJdTVX3n)  and men's (… https://t.co/KtTsKjHVyX]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tml21605 My mulberry trees are making mulberries already. They ain’t ripe but I see them]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jon_in_SoCal @TheAthleticSF @timkawakami I think it would be OBJ and whoever 49ers draft at 6 (Sweat?) in TK’s scenario.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@thedcd Plateaus come and go. Incorporating new workouts will help kickstart the weight loss, you got this!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212's potential lie about a pardon would not sink a ship but all of @realDonaldTrump's lies would sink ten ships! #GOFIGURE]]></document><document><![CDATA[What tech trends from #CES2019 should fuel and convenience retailers know about? To learn more, I reached out to… https://t.co/iV3Wt01x86]]></document><document><![CDATA[It’s not a wow brew, but it Bill’s as a “standard ale” ... and, it’s definitely standard. - Drinking a Domestica by… https://t.co/i58o5iej0z]]></document><document><![CDATA[@officialEFCC you’ll be chasing human beings with safes in their house hiding a few millions, this uncle had a priv… https://t.co/B5jiWvQdwd]]></document><document><![CDATA[@creepychief @JasonKirkSBN I have been roasted. Much obliged, good sir. https://t.co/1X6CkKhd0O]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LSValue @ShitFund Literally, no one can grasp how terrible of an idea this is. Sooooooo dumb. So dumb. Soooosooooo dumb.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dougiefischer @GoldenBoyBoxing @SeniesaSuperbad @DAZN_USA Watch it Doug that’s my lady!!!! LOL]]></document><document><![CDATA[Today is going to be rough. Didn't sleep well last night. Can I blame the Spring forward like everyone else will do?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@jeffpearlman It’s awful. I subscribe to the Free Press here in Michigan, but I can only get it Thurs, Fri and Sun.… https://t.co/BwDpFrdSbE]]></document></documents></author>