<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[@JarylanIsCute Neeps are rutabagas and tatties are potatoes. Neeps and tatties are traditionally served with haggis… https://t.co/XEVtIt2BJq]]></document><document><![CDATA[And I’m sure every BH’s FAVORITE line in The Way is “He Don’t F You The Way I Could” ☺️ Damn! 😆 #HanginTough30… https://t.co/mHI43WhTMI]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AOC You are amazing- look forward to seeing what great things you will accomplish !]]></document><document><![CDATA[The stunning @brookelewisla with @mparkerbuzz at 21st Annual @costumeawards ✨📸🖤 #awardseason #costumeawards #CDGA… https://t.co/HKQLeZia43]]></document><document><![CDATA[Work in progress.... #art #artwork #artist #artistic #color #love #fashion #instagood #instafollow #instalike… https://t.co/ZjoOZW0EsQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AceYoungWitt Man look kill somebody? I can't I'm half sleep in this mug]]></document><document><![CDATA[I really wish music photographers would understand that their opinion is not automatically the end-all, be-all in t… https://t.co/XHCurPdgDn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@brielarson My daughter and I loved watching Captain Marvel last night, I know it will do well. Looking forward to watching you in Endgame.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me recordó a Kike saludo de mi casa hace algunos años @TirsoBello @TavoOlea12 @lalincamposv @cuevas_pano]]></document><document><![CDATA[If @RepMattGaetz really ‘doesn’t understand’ he shouldn’t be a Representative of his constituents because he doesn’… https://t.co/Kj29Z9sO7I]]></document><document><![CDATA[I feel like this could be incredible for everyone involved. One we would have the chance to learn more of our REAL… https://t.co/9lancSYBbn]]></document><document><![CDATA[That’s exactly how they fee I got told that all the time by the #CrookedHillary clans!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DaBay4LF @Whaddayaneed @TwitterMoments I am Mexican until I came here I experience racism, my skin is white but yo… https://t.co/ZxCgfEfYHY]]></document><document><![CDATA[YES.. Green Book wins best picture. Minnesotan Jim Burke.. shout out!! @TimLammersFilms]]></document><document><![CDATA[In Europe, drug prices are often set by government health systems and decline over time as countries demand additio… https://t.co/IKpbIQek0p]]></document><document><![CDATA[Why have I woken up at 3am? Can’t fall back to sleep. Guess I’m hitting the  #5amwriterclub early today. Morning fr… https://t.co/PKsqXFl70z]]></document><document><![CDATA[If the Democrats worked half as hard doing what their constitutes elecected them for as they are at trying to ruin… https://t.co/82KSS0qVFQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t know who you are going to be watching this weekend but I’m going to be watching @little_dimdim THE REIGNING… https://t.co/heg8oFBEfo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@LightsCameraPod How BAD did you want them to kiss at the end??!!! I was DYING! 🥰If they were acting, they both des… https://t.co/2PC4iAjvq9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Considering the scandalous heist of 407 ETR customer data by a former PC candidate, their corporate sponsorship of… https://t.co/PsNtrUFAMC]]></document><document><![CDATA[Going out and getting completely wasted is a total turn off to me. There’s a time when you grow up....]]></document><document><![CDATA[@nikjnac16 @MissPassey @kyleipryor @Hollyoaks Aren't you forgetting who she also lost?]]></document><document><![CDATA[Guess what. We do our best in an imperfect world that is dominated by fossil fuels—for now. That’s changing. This f… https://t.co/eM7xCC8j3y]]></document><document><![CDATA[yes. That is merry. Dean Martin, Jerry Lewis, Marilyn Monroe, 1950s #hilarity #chuckle #smile #merry https://t.co/ZTU15JvkvS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@IlhanMN @IlhanMN @isupportisrael_  @aoc @AJCongress @SpeakerPelosi @SenSchumer  Quit treating @Ilhan like a child.… https://t.co/KdJnCMk0TS]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JeffreyWoolfe7 @williamlegate @realDonaldTrump I think you're describing Putin, who has been telling Trump what to do.]]></document><document><![CDATA[i would kill a man to hold a koala  (not rlly but now you know how bad i want to hold a koala)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DanQPublic Buy a food truck. I’ll move to California and run it with you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Cydad @Mason_Gehloff Must have been a stellar performance! I know your Grandparents are super proud of YOU! 🎉]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dawnstaley @dawnstaley Up early ready to see my @GamecockWBB play. Thanks again coach, you made my day! Let’s win this!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Judgement day is coming. @ Preston Lakes, Frisco, Texas https://t.co/wij5AjCkn6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Simone and Bryson scene in the begin 😳 #BoomerangOnBET https://t.co/jRXcoFtx0R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OPDOfcZipay @DentonCountyDA Why is Apartments all together and houses separate?]]></document><document><![CDATA[I actually love this idea in a non-sarcastic. Sometimes I just wanna be around people but I don’t want to be in a b… https://t.co/9KHpMjrdi5]]></document><document><![CDATA[How disgusting!  How many of them have children?  That makes it even worse]]></document><document><![CDATA[So, at this point I’d like to apologize to @philwinkle for threatening him with my sword finger last night. What wa… https://t.co/KFkZKlVzWZ]]></document><document><![CDATA[PERMS ARE LEGIT! I’ve been doing a few lately, and I am really feeling it. This amazing client of mine is also a hi… https://t.co/QqIapWhEb9]]></document><document><![CDATA[Zach just walked in our room an was like “you wanna know the real reason why I got home really late today?” An I wa… https://t.co/1tulekg7m6]]></document><document><![CDATA[I don’t think I could date a boxer it seems like a lot of their relationships end with fist fights 🙁]]></document><document><![CDATA[Night 4/4 before one day off tomorrow, and I know I need to eat the food in my fridge, but I desperately want jerse… https://t.co/QZFyJzFtoy]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DarrylStellmach Me (an archaeologist): this is absolutely exactly what happened and your lack of appreciation is w… https://t.co/Hv6ltvStRY]]></document><document><![CDATA[Thank you for this thread. My first question is why are they going after Sen. Feinstein rather than the GOP who are… https://t.co/H6pLAs2ovn]]></document><document><![CDATA[@korrieleigh1027 One year my whole wallet got stolen on bourbon and then I couldn’t get in anywhere and the whole Mardi Gras was over 😂]]></document><document><![CDATA[@_Naybaybee_ @ILoveBeinBlack Is everyone just going to pretend this video didn’t show it was a man about to beat th… https://t.co/AmoMiHpCbb]]></document><document><![CDATA[Plot twist: Cassie’s dad didn’t give his blessing to Colton just so he can take a free trip to Portugal #Bachelor]]></document><document><![CDATA[Insulin pricing transparency bill #HF289 passed unanimously out of the House Commerce Committee! #MNleg]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ North Hollywood, California https://t.co/BnNOYNfdAL]]></document><document><![CDATA[(Devotion from Unlimited Kingdom)   “We Must Be Born Again”  The most frightening aspect of Christ’s words, “You mu… https://t.co/BcIlih1XB8]]></document><document><![CDATA[🚨,"Spring break travel advisory for Mexico may take on new urgency after deadly attack in Cancun https://t.co/K49WRZvPwr]]></document><document><![CDATA[every year for the last 3 years I’ve ended up at a hoodie allen concert for my bday. it became an unexpected tradit… https://t.co/74vFx75Yx9]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DailyMail MAGA, folks. But,the black female worker, clocked his time, that could only make a parent proud.   Man G… https://t.co/Ab1pVe7gey]]></document><document><![CDATA[We kept talking about the universe today AND BOI DID SHE COME IN CLUTCH.  FOR REAL WHAT YOU PUT OUT IS WHAT YOU RECEIVE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheHardyBoyCats Oh my goodness Frankie, mew made meh meowma's heart smile. She be at work. Mew is so fangshome. 🐾💕🐈🐾]]></document><document><![CDATA[the second fuck always be better than the 1st fuck.. cus now you know what u working with😭]]></document><document><![CDATA[@johncardillo @ThePatriot006 @60Minutes @ScottPelley Why didn’t he ask the big questions]]></document><document><![CDATA[It feels good to be able to love my children without a distance between us- and I’m not talking about miles, I’m ta… https://t.co/TEmb04YaLV]]></document><document><![CDATA[@itsjasonoppa I thought Dtf meant down town Fullerton. That was until something embarrassing and horrifying ( in a lol way) happened lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[@PreetBharara Maybe next year, you’ll consider coming to The Tucson Festival of Books. Beautiful weather 🌵We need you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[What ??? Our (Lord and Savior)Odumbo, commissioned NASA to spray us !!! And we knew that someone was. Look at the p… https://t.co/O5ckqLGtBR]]></document><document><![CDATA[my coworkers all brought me valentine’s yesterday and i work and i could CRY those girliez treat me too good i love them]]></document><document><![CDATA[23 balloons released for the 23 victims of the March 3rd tornado #LeeCountyStrong #BeauregardStrong #NightOfHope https://t.co/WwIs8HPSUF]]></document><document><![CDATA[To all of my cyber sisters out there, thank you for making our world a safer place to Internet.  I love contributin… https://t.co/s4MvU7mHve]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Rrrrnessa Deep down inside, weren't we all expecting this? Controlled by private powers shrouded in secrecy, it's… https://t.co/Mqpg2eC2Bg]]></document><document><![CDATA[@dscc Thank you so much for all of your hard work.  Yes, we have to flip four or more seats.  I know we can do this.]]></document><document><![CDATA[#ReadWithJenna. So excited. I’m a retired librarian and this book was on my list. Yeah. I’m such a dork.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Any recommendations for dinner in Seattle? Something fairly casual — not  too fancy.]]></document><document><![CDATA[She is a creator... @NepherteeteB @ Bronx, New York https://t.co/mQU51jlc2o]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Jreaderwriter Well, let’s lunch and learn! You open Wednesday or Thursday?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@KnucklePuckIL I’d actually playing on the @CinProject for their emo hour what is life]]></document><document><![CDATA[Latin American admits to @UVALaw - we’d love to see you at Admitted Students Open House❗️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Me: goes out to forget how miserable Ive felt   Drunk me: lashes out at everyone close to me for no reason]]></document><document><![CDATA[How's this for #mondaymotivation ? Our newsletter is in your in-boxes! Varadkar's line, Family trauma, UCD visits -… https://t.co/udlMxQazfP]]></document><document><![CDATA[@alejandraregla @ProfDannyOlmos @DominguezHills Thank you! https://t.co/nIXzCk18cN]]></document><document><![CDATA[Roses are red Violets are blue I love this game but I can’t wait to see y’all again soon]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Swazi_Pearl You have very calm energy. This is something that I don't run into often and you are just simply incre… https://t.co/ITElnWfxej]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve reached that point in the semester where I don’t care if I go to class lol]]></document><document><![CDATA[Lowkey starting to hate iPhone my phone been acting up since I got it and they already gave me new and still acting up 🤦🏻‍♀️]]></document><document><![CDATA[idk why but I just remembered one time @morganlester_ made me hold a snake in pet co. I rlly hate her I almost cried.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine @TRPhrophet sounds like Linda sourpuss is running democratic party not Nancy]]></document><document><![CDATA[First time in a salt cave. (@ Caldwell Salt Cave in Caldwell, NJ w/ @wickitrocker) https://t.co/MMRA83gO4s]]></document><document><![CDATA[Here for my cousin’s wedding - excited to spend time with family exploring Denver and celebrating love!! @ Linger https://t.co/9U6Czqnl9D]]></document><document><![CDATA[The Jonas brothers getting back together is a reunion Tour I can get behind ! 🥰]]></document><document><![CDATA[Saw this and it made me laugh. Ask any of us in Michigan where we live and we whip out our hand to show you. https://t.co/UZwnSdvQ6B]]></document><document><![CDATA[Galveston 2-16-2019. Great weekend getaway. Had a great time.🍹💃🕺🥳 @ The Strand, Galveston https://t.co/P2nFmr1BD7]]></document><document><![CDATA[Seriously the relationship my og manager &amp; I have is irreplaceable 😭❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[Whatever, I love the movie Overboard. #fightme ⚓️ 💕 @goldiehawn @RealKurtRussell https://t.co/rZYgsgJ8Tm]]></document><document><![CDATA[3 hours of editing photos... I feel like my eyes are going to dry up and fall out like small little raisins 🙃]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just want to like every  #Oscars2019 tweet so I can see the heart turn into a star. 😍⭐️🌟]]></document><document><![CDATA[The 1st grade performance of “Making The Band” was absolutely fantastic! These kiddos worked HARD! #FalconProud… https://t.co/EJTFBDvAuh]]></document><document><![CDATA[I'm entered to win tickets to @ultra thanks to @iHeartRaving. Enter here: https://t.co/XIRUMwzW7U]]></document><document><![CDATA[All you #TeamJordyn folks are telling me if your friend slept with your bf/baby daddy, ya’all would be fine with it… https://t.co/RNO9x5hbsh]]></document><document><![CDATA[So aggravated that we’re talking about a $333M fucking billl..... @realDonaldTrump is really fighting for a wall an… https://t.co/xDkJShvvWL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AllisonHutchiso @GrimmProspects @JoanNaake @MC_HONRSPROGRMS Aww. We miss you!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @yodesmet @gabe_albertini If ya like Socialism, go try it in Russia or Venezuela and see how ya like it!!!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@timdonovan560 @MsAFromBK @DragonMom98 @kyle3787 @lno09281978 @rtadter @Burke_William1 @Jack_WanderS… https://t.co/BNYwSolc4K]]></document><document><![CDATA[I've just been informed, "Mom, you can file a Lawsuit for Mental Anquish."]]></document><document><![CDATA[I am enjoying all of the research at my first tobacco conference. #SRNT2019]]></document><document><![CDATA[This momo thing is scaring me so bad I don’t want to watch videos no momo #momochallege]]></document><document><![CDATA[happy valentine’s day to the sexiest baby daddddy alive ✨💛🔥😫😍 i love u so much!!! xoxo https://t.co/mr5lW8fDGP]]></document><document><![CDATA[My whole day at work has consisted of me looking up stagecoach outfit ideas and doing absolutely 0 work]]></document></documents></author>