<author lang="en"><documents><document><![CDATA[Preston and Jake’s radio show was cancelled tonight due to university park closing down. That didn’t stop them - th… https://t.co/FvfqBQYsHU]]></document><document><![CDATA[@VP #MAGA #KAG #KAG2020 #TrumpTrain #AmericaFirst #BuildTheWall #DrainTheSwap #2A #FIGHTFOR2020 #TRUMP2020 #SPYGATE https://t.co/2bg2BRlviL]]></document><document><![CDATA[@n1k0 Is it still the case tho, or was this just the case back when it was new (and experiemental).]]></document><document><![CDATA[No puede ser que esto sea un debate politico y no un debate cientifico  #audienciaglifosato]]></document><document><![CDATA[Yall letting females with 12 year old boy bodies break your heart out here? Smh]]></document><document><![CDATA[@akaTimmay @Bharper3407 @Dodgers From a fan perspective...Believe me...you'd rather play baseball in LA type of weather.....]]></document><document><![CDATA[Dinner last night at our favorite Siesta Key restaurant! Les, thank you for always providing us with such hospitali… https://t.co/0Ntlx3E3YA]]></document><document><![CDATA[I let everyone kno I ain't shit before any kind of relationship. Doesn't bother no one lol .]]></document><document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning @dulles_airport this morning #snow #airports @ Washington Dulles International Airport https://t.co/DLRnZbHyns]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DeRushaJ If I was still working down there, I'd use the snow as an excuse to get loaded, down scotch eggs, and wat… https://t.co/jF8SkxMFvH]]></document><document><![CDATA[@JustinMcGeeWX @SCweather_wx Yeah the 1978 and 2010 analogs...for a winter like this. I admit I thought it would be… https://t.co/cPHB66Xtkv]]></document><document><![CDATA[Star Wars Holiday Special Trailer - in the style of The Force Awakens https://t.co/ZUtImFgM70 via @YouTube]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’ve been studying since Tuesday for hours for my test on Friday if I don’t at least pass it I might drop out]]></document><document><![CDATA[@SenBlumenthal Personally, I have always thought that Trump collided with Russia. #ImpeachCriminalTrump]]></document><document><![CDATA[@hgtvcanada @Bryan_Baeumler @SarahBaeumler Island? TAKE ME WITH YOU BRYAN!! ILL SLEEP IN THE TOOL SHED!! 😜]]></document><document><![CDATA[#CosmicMacabre #CFBallou #fiction #nonfiction #writers #poets #teachers #poetry #poems #writing #books #college… https://t.co/EA0OyyUX8v]]></document><document><![CDATA[Do you remember when you joined Twitter? I do! #MyTwitterAnniversary https://t.co/9isXgtSZTT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Downeyangel @la_belle_laide @AllisonRFloyd @harry_wormald25 @KSL5TV 👍🏻]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mfow020 @ajventer @BernieSanders So disgusting to see the 69% of adults with under $1,000 in savings eating BRAND NAME FOOD]]></document><document><![CDATA[#EricMacAdams @DerrickMac55 deserves a big assist for stealing the puck from the Dman in the high slot. #BvR… https://t.co/ajw44VJ8O5]]></document><document><![CDATA[#Feel #Good #To #Be #Back #FaithChurch @ Faith https://t.co/c1AI6KCSs5 https://t.co/YeK3Tn017V]]></document><document><![CDATA[Crikey - Drinking a Boomerang by @ellicottmills @ Ellicott Mills Brewing Company  — https://t.co/Id69VS6y8R]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DebraLindh @MarkCCrowley @sageandsavvy @911well @cannonfyre12 @journeyofdays @KateNasser @HealingMB @LeadToday… https://t.co/9Ec7gAFYUH]]></document><document><![CDATA[Words of The Day: Good, Better, Best... Never Let those rest. ‘Til Your Good is Better and Your Better is Best❣️✍🏾💯… https://t.co/m2q6FzBkwu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Got to meet one of my childhood idols @Dschrempf from the Sonics at the @UW_MBB. Great win Dawgs!  #TougherTogether https://t.co/AcCT0mOFtW]]></document><document><![CDATA[I just don’t understand how the Magic can beat all these top teams then go lose to a top 5 pick lottery team.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@maskarita4 @manuel70m @pelon_73 @ElPincheJuan4 @unttalhanckoc @MmamaceandoO @davidant264 @disanxel… https://t.co/QhcxsxiF7H]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Chestys_Ghost @Gater_Chomp @Beatissima @maria_2020 @AOC @RashidaTlaib He must be doing a good job for them to act… https://t.co/2SFRhRrc2t]]></document><document><![CDATA[wtf is this that im seeing about people legitimately wanting to purge march 21-22 IM NOT TRYNA DIE ON MY BIRTHDAY WTF]]></document><document><![CDATA[@AdavisWilliams @maggieNYT Shameless hussy lies again. How many Chinese trademarks in her name so far?]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Bryesha_Adams Good morning, Bryesha! I hope you have yourself a nice day at work, and a blessed day! Thanks for al… https://t.co/1wRcdZdGdr]]></document><document><![CDATA[@annalisefleetin @yvesraejepsen WUTS IN DA KNEW CHICKEN WRAPS?!?! https://t.co/0tdKECv3Nw]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Couldn't love you more than that scene... And this love goes back to 1977.  Such a powerful scene!❤️❤️]]></document><document><![CDATA[In a wordy world, this is helpful to remember:  🤫 “You will say the wrong thing if you talk too much— so be sensibl… https://t.co/imGpGOwvTj]]></document><document><![CDATA[Again, a symbolic victory but a victory nonetheless.   A year ago, just after some awful events, I was regularly br… https://t.co/bjws3V3FZ7]]></document><document><![CDATA[[deadlift] A few weeks ago I could barely lift the bar with 405lbs on it, but yesterday I hit a new pr with two reps at 405 lbs :,)]]></document><document><![CDATA[@963JACKfm " But You Dig That well Up you'll Find 2 Oranged Handled Machetie's ".......!!!! https://t.co/MhfRoyT2US]]></document><document><![CDATA[We met as little 13 year olds and ever since that day, this love has felt like it was already written. Like it was… https://t.co/Gph6j6fTKt]]></document><document><![CDATA[Así está el pais,nuestra RD necesitamos un Thor que no ayude en Manhattan, New York https://t.co/ZdCorGOpOJ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MashhourII @tastelikehaggis Well, THAT says a lot about 'them', doesn't it!]]></document><document><![CDATA[@gigi273761 @BigMouthJoe @Serremmy @MrFin @RL9631 @jonz970 @tagruber @JKaseOR @Pookahh1 @missled2u @pjbowles4… https://t.co/i8W588mf3T]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RichAzzopardi @Azi @NYDailyNews @klnynews Did his job better than well. Parting column notes the decline of print… https://t.co/PELYxPSsJo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RealCandaceO "Children should be seen, not heard"! After she's taught to read, someone please get her a dictionary… https://t.co/liSiXOwmNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo @ Bluff Heights, Long Beach, California https://t.co/oAh4iJGWsE]]></document><document><![CDATA[@StollerChris Good to hear from you my friend, hope all is well.  Great profile picture!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Might be Pogba's worst performance to date. Absolutely useless. #ARSMUN #mufc]]></document><document><![CDATA[❤️NATURAL BEAUTY-MONDAY🍊🍊🍊🍊🍊#OKINGMEDIA H O U S E of A R T💥 👸🏿MÖDÉŁ priceless_international 🔥PHTO BY @Yoludele1 ⚡️🎭… https://t.co/j08RKNgxYi]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MongoGoesInsane @metman84 For the most part they've had good teams, although it hasn't resulted in Stanley Cups. H… https://t.co/Ym3OoPmWM0]]></document><document><![CDATA[@MichaelAvenatti @Jenseg1073 @CBSNews Huh, where have I heard this before? Oh, I know, the #JudgeKavanaugh hearings… https://t.co/Rs8QCu57iQ]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Kira_Media I wouldn’t be surprised if Media Matters edited the so-called tape.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Every year at the optometrist I am like “bitch I got more blind no need for this”]]></document><document><![CDATA[Girls who thinks the nachos  on the menu at my job are 'really good' the day before #SpringTraining is back at Scot… https://t.co/1XhSF6mhTs]]></document><document><![CDATA[During hug and fellowship yesterday morning. I'm using the 3a drumsticks with barrel tip from @vicfirth. I'm defini… https://t.co/4UAdNw3Lc8]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ClintSmithIII Thin Mint people - you have to feel sorry for them. Imagine: THAT'S their favorite flavor. What a sa… https://t.co/9ha9ck6YyP]]></document><document><![CDATA[I solidify my thought that the Oscars didn’t wanna air best editing because they already knew bohemian would sadly… https://t.co/Pg3Vg95woT]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mymynags @c_siera She needs to crawl back under the rock where she came from]]></document><document><![CDATA[@B_inShortsville If I bump into him: he was always the guy before the guy]]></document><document><![CDATA[For those that follow me check my sons new #instagram account zuzzlespuzzles if you like handheld puzzle type chall… https://t.co/Su1Hvyb4va]]></document><document><![CDATA[@coachtucek You have a great team Coach.  Very disciplined with a ton of hussle!]]></document><document><![CDATA[Early morning workouts before practice begins. It’s just right. #chicagocubs #everybodyin #canonphotography… https://t.co/CFU2nz4ooo]]></document><document><![CDATA[@RandyZiemnik @CuyahogaLib has brought some great authors there.  I’ve seen Sen. Booker and Bernie Kosar and have d… https://t.co/uyFUf7xgHV]]></document><document><![CDATA[Corvettes for days at hotrodshows Detroit Autorama #corvette #corvettes #vette #vettes #chevy #chevrolet #motorcity… https://t.co/vtQITtmnJf]]></document><document><![CDATA[@athomas725 @BidGreenJacket The book shall be divided by events before and after this moment.]]></document><document><![CDATA[I guarantee you, your take on John Wayne is more simpleminded than any movie Wayne ever made, even Brannigan]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays I did what you asked and read the thread. Very interesting.]]></document><document><![CDATA['They're becoming cleverer': U.N. says North Korea is evading sanctions by buying oil, selling coal, hacking banks… https://t.co/bZYPyToJP5]]></document><document><![CDATA[@bipoalfa @camykamy Ya reconozco el problema, igual y si necesitare una evaluación, creo que no esta de mas, aparte… https://t.co/JFSBkVWebM]]></document><document><![CDATA[@craveyjohnny You’re never as good as you think you are because there is only one Christ, in which we should always… https://t.co/qEoRG4z1wq]]></document><document><![CDATA[@CSiriano That tux gown is EVERYTHING coolest thing I've ever seen in a while and he rocks it like no one's business]]></document><document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii @gatewaypundit I certainly hope you are right in this @seanhannity BUT I’ll not be holding my breath w… https://t.co/OHRhrisPb6]]></document><document><![CDATA[Better ways to handle it. That don’t include provoking someone eating lunch is my point.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@fakeleny Please explain to us all, you economics wizard, where the “free” healthcare comes from? Nothings free swe… https://t.co/Wh7EM1hOUz]]></document><document><![CDATA[This makes me #happy. #candy #treats @ Las Vegas, Nevada https://t.co/bhhwRtYpbY]]></document><document><![CDATA[@talktodenene @Jim_Jordan @GOPoversight They could show the pee tape and the gop would complain of the maker had Tr… https://t.co/d9pGQF4K7r]]></document><document><![CDATA[So how does one actually retain information that they learned in class? Asking for a friend who has an exam tomorro… https://t.co/N2Om3ud9ac]]></document><document><![CDATA[@N_Fatale Two years of Kamala awkwardly pretending to be “real” is going to be exhausting.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@zoiedevoe I'm so happy you've found your passion! Congrats :) https://t.co/cDRfwS6jpz]]></document><document><![CDATA[@tsheahan13 @AlanDersh In typical Liberal fashion “You have to pass it before you know what’s in it”]]></document><document><![CDATA[“Now thanks be unto God, which always causeth us to triumph in Christ, and maketh manifest the savour of his knowle… https://t.co/cbHJQy0ZNu]]></document><document><![CDATA[@DavidFiso @PPFA They can't do that silly, @PPFA is the backdoor tax-laundering arm of the DNC to make sure their campaigns are well-funded.]]></document><document><![CDATA[Buenos días ☀️  |  Salmos  37:5  Pon tu vida en sus manos, confía plenamente en él, y él actuará en tu favor;» @ Ho… https://t.co/pZas7zad0i]]></document><document><![CDATA[@Erik_Gundersen Ugh. The irony is that you can now watch docs that actually show behind the scenes biz dealings of… https://t.co/Duh6i6rJqY]]></document><document><![CDATA[YEEESSS! I just rewatched the trailer and got re excited for this. #comedy #snicker #smirk #comic https://t.co/aRhCZsANfc]]></document><document><![CDATA[I’m well aware of that! Also well aware of the George Washington enslaving black people, and was a “founding father… https://t.co/L1HGYmVkST]]></document><document><![CDATA[This guy has been a pleasant surprise.  Salute   https://t.co/og4gIWjAsG]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HBO @chrissyteigen Why don’t you quit worrying about some John guy on rolling skates and worry about bringing HBO back to @dish]]></document><document><![CDATA[@groovygilmour @titletownusa73 @Mikehomeseller @WilliamMarquar8 @jeffsnyder72 @ixchelroy @BeverlyWarrren… https://t.co/gYC1qKao2P]]></document><document><![CDATA[@TheRynheart @AOC @NRA The https://t.co/nMf2jrKeYs to be mind reader https://t.co/njsclmDS4m label people to push a… https://t.co/JvGBcE3tTw]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wake up in a whisky sweat. No room for artists in this city anymore. Time to think about packing up and leaving.]]></document><document><![CDATA[@HoydenMusings @elenawonders @DatingAround KK just my 02..he was rough around the edges for sure but he’s allowed his opinion.]]></document><document><![CDATA[San Francisco :: Luke Perry remembered: ‘a character actor in the body of a heartthrob’: Fans and costars of “Bever… https://t.co/CDglhzsAT0]]></document><document><![CDATA[We're hiring! Click to apply: Sr. RPG Programmer Analyst - https://t.co/8kvJZy4aw5 #IT #Monett, MO]]></document><document><![CDATA[@ratemyplatemate Those weak ass beans look like they came straight out of a cold metal can! 😂🤣 And your 'chips' loo… https://t.co/pn4r88VtAg]]></document><document><![CDATA[The hosts are constantly like “Wow! Isn’t that amazing?!” The couples are just “This is a good situation. Golly.” I… https://t.co/VVWxT51RYr]]></document><document><![CDATA[ABC Talks All My Children And One Life To Live Reboots https://t.co/6Mk5vb9V0g]]></document><document><![CDATA[Okay a little over the top bc there are plenty of diverse podcasts but still this is hilarious]]></document><document><![CDATA[#collage #fluxus #magazines #fashion #hands #worksonpaper #mixedmedia #contemporaryart #baltimore @ Charles Village… https://t.co/MT9M1UdH5U]]></document><document><![CDATA[I wanna get on one of those shows where @GordonRamsay reviews your food  but I’ll just make like a @hotpockets or s… https://t.co/LvYEE32123]]></document><document><![CDATA[@rsmon77 Motorcycle jousting with hand guns would be awesome. #FridayThrillerClub]]></document><document><![CDATA[omgomgomg we get 3! way to go you loooooooons! #mls #VANvMIN @MNUFC (playing #wonderwall at the tomb household)]]></document></documents></author>